♫  Misty dawn and tender dusk, the whole world seems gentle  ♫
♫  A young boy in uniform gallops under the blinking stars  ♫
♫ His eyes are so loving, determined, and happy ♫
♫ Looking back, what transient beauty ♫
♫  Winter, the season when snow falls  ♫
♫  But you have spring in your arms  ♫
♫  The fragrance of sweet flowers fills the world  ♫
♫ During the sunny summer days ♫
♫  Our feelings grow stronger  ♫
♫ I'm so in love with you in autumn ♫
♫  Every falling leaf speaks of my love  ♫
♫ Dancing and swirling in the air ♫
[Fall in Love]
[Episode 11]
Increase wages! Increase wages! Increase wages!
[Resist inequality and ensure equality]
[Improve workers' labor treatment]
Increase wages! Increase wages! Increase wages!
[Fight for equality]
[Shanghai Hongshun Cotton Yarn Mill]
Increase wages! Increase wages! Increase wages!
Give us a pay raise!
[Shangmengjie Cotton Yarn Mill]
Go away! Stop it!
Go!
Smash it!
Stop it! Stop!
Commander.
There are several cotton yarn mill owners who want to see you.
Oh!
Boss Wang, Boss Guo, Boss Chen.
Please, have a seat.
Such rare guests.
Tan Si, pour the tea.
Commander Tan, we have come to see you today because of something very important.
We are not in the mood for tea.
What kind of difficulties have you all encountered?
Commander Tan, your army has two thousand soldiers.
And aside from Mu's cotton mill, the three of us took in most of them.
We settled down at least two hundred soldiers and four or five hundred at most.
Yes. I know all of that,
and I'm very grateful to you three bosses for solving my urgent problems.
Commander Tan, to be honest with you.
Those soldiers we took in have given us unspeakable hardships.
Think about it. If your soldiers go to the cotton mills,
it's not them who will be miserable, but the owners of the mills.
Boss Wang, why do you say that?
Your soldiers, they're great soldiers. But they really can't do any manual labor.
Even the work of five or six of them added up still can't compare to one skilled worker.
Their work efficiency is too low.
But they still take up one of our looms with such a low work efficiency.
It has caused a sharp drop in the production rate at our cotton yarn mill.
I've done some calculations.
Now our output is half of what it was before we took in the soldiers.
Asking a hand equipped for holding guns, to hold a spindle,
will first result in inefficiency.
And efficiency is the life of yarn mills.
These soldiers, they're paid the same as skilled workers
even though they aren't doing a good job.
Even though we're subsidized by the Chamber of Commerce,
the skilled workers will inevitably be dissatisfied with it.
I'm not going to hide it. My mill was shut down for two days.
The workers are all asking for a pay raise.
We can't afford it.
Inequality is a greater issue than scarcity. If working and not working are being paid the same,
(T/N: Wanqing is quoting The Analects)
then who would want to work?
That's true, Commander Tan.
The cotton yarn industry hasn't been prosperous in the past two years.
The Japanese muslin had a great impact on us.
Although the Chamber of Commerce will give us some subsidies,
we can barely make a living.
But the profit is already very low.
Foreign muslin has been dumped these past few years. Local mills are already in a tough situation.
They would not be able to handle a pay raise.
So, Commander Tan,
the three of us come to see you today because we have a favor to ask you.
Please take back your men.
They're all tough men, firm and unyielding.
Spinning and weaving in our yarn mills, their skills are wasted.
Gentlemen, I'm so sorry.
Because when I took office as the Commander of Shanghai,
I made a pact with Provincial Military Governor Xu.
The first clause was to dismiss the Tan Army.
Of course I know, sending these soldiers of mine to your mills
would be like Zhangfei embroidering.
(T/N: Zhangfei was a famous general during the Three Kingdoms)
But whoever started this issue should end it.
We have to wait for Military Governor Xu to give the orders.
- This…
She really didn't miss anything.
- Great.
- This way.
- Farewell.
- Goodbye. See you.
Connect me to the military governor's mansion in Yue City.
What's wrong?
Mu Zhiyuan just called me, saying he wishes me an early happy new year.
But in reality, he was lobbying for those mill owners.
He says that the textile mill industry is currently in recession,
and the soldiers being there is making it even worse.
If he isn't trying to gain pity, he is trying to brush off his responsibilities.
Didn't the Chinese Chamber of Commerce already give them resettlement subsidies?
Did these mill owners just take money but do nothing?
In my opinion, this is Tan Xuanlin's doing.
He's causing these troubles on purpose.
Military Governor,
can't we just ignore these mill owners?
Tan Xuanlin has dismissed his army anyway,
and all his soldiers are scattered in the yarn mills.
There will definitely be some crime happening after a period of neglect.
Then we'll have a reason to deal with him.
Military Governor Xu gave my father a polite rebuff.
He still insists on settling the soldiers in the mill.
But he also disclosed that it won't be too long.
He won't make it too difficult for yarn mill owners.
Xu Bojun must have other plans.
He can't be that kind with my soldiers.
Then you should now believe that I genuinely want to help you.
You've indeed foreseen every step.
If there's nothing else, I have to leave now.
I'm busy with official duties.
What has been wrong with you recently?
You're like a different person. You've stopped joking around.
Don't you like a serious gentleman?
I don't.
Do you like a man like me?
You're overthinking it.
Fine.
Cindy, I'm back.
Cindy? Cindy.
Where are you, Cindy?
Cindy.
Cindy, where are you?
I got you.
Cindy.
[Blood for blood]
[Assassins at Shanghai King's celebration party found to be the work of the Revolutionary Party]
Yes, it was published by the Command. What's wrong with it?
Commander Tan, did it ever occur to you?
If you wrote that, the Revolutionary Army would regard me as their enemy.
Today, my cat was killed.
I'm sure the next one will be me.
I don't care. You published the newspaper,
so you have to keep me safe.
Then, Mr. Joseph, how do you want me to keep you safe?
You must send soldiers to guard my house and company.
Have some professionals follow me at all times.
Mr. Joseph,
I understand what you're going through, and I sympathize with you.
But there is nothing I can do.
The soldiers of the Command are not at my disposal.
Commander Tan, are you joking?
Take it easy, take it easy. Do I look like I'm joking with you?
Although I'm the Commander of Shanghai, it is in name only.
At the beginning of my tenure, I made a pact with the military governor's mansion.
Even if we mobilize a single soldier, it must be approved by the military governor's mansion.
This is ridiculous.
So according to what you are saying,
if I am attacked, I have to wait for instructions from the military governor's mansion
before the troops are sent?
Yes.
What kind of rubbish agreement is that?
How can our personal safety be guaranteed like this?
Commander Tan, you have your own army, right?
If you send your soldiers to protect me,
then you don't need the approval of the military governor's mansion. Right?
Mr. Joseph,
my army has been dismissed.
They handed over their guns. I have no soldiers now.
But, Mr. Joseph,
it's not like there is no solution to this.
- I'm sorry, Sir.
- My God, Joseph.
Look!
What's up, man?
What is it?
Come on.
I'll be back in ten minutes.
My God, what is it?
Cindy.
Cindy was killed.
Right at my house.
It's the Revolutionary Army.
And I'm their next target.
Damn it.
[Provincial Military Governor's Mansion]
Military Governor, Mr. Anton Fay is calling.
[Defense Command of Shanghai]
Commander,
I can't believe
that Xu Bojun will be soft in front of foreigners.
He even agreed to build a militia.
Joseph went to see Anton Fay, with tears in his eyes,
and he insisted on forming a militia to protect the security of the concession.
For the sake of his old friend,
Anton Fay had a showdown with Xu Bojun.
Xu Bojun doesn't dare to reject him in public,
so he has to swallow his grievances in silence.
What do you know?
A cat succeeded in something that even Miss Gu failed to do.
You can't say this in front of Shuang'er.
I know, Miss Gu has self-respect.
And we'll give her the credit for it
as long as she's happy.
Commander, those foreigners are really strange.
There are so many wounded soldiers and refugees in Shanghai
who are being chased by patrolmen all day long.
They never said a thing.
But look how scared they are with a dead cat.
They immediately ask us to build the militia to defend the concession.
Do you know what this is called?
This is as the saying goes, you'll never feel the pain
if you aren't the one getting cut.
To me, Commander is the smarter one.
The military governor's mansion was caught off-guard this round.
It's just a pity for a certain big shot in our Command.
I bet he is being scolded by his father now.
The military governor says that your incompetence
was exploited by Tan Xuanlin again.
It's not your fault.
Who knew that Joseph would interfere at this time?
And that Joseph is the most successful Jewish businessman in the Far East.
He owns half of the Bund.
So how can we compete with him?
I used to think everything would be settled if Tan Xuanlin
handed in the guns and resettled his soldiers.
I didn't expect this. I was careless.
My father's reprimand is right.
We can't blame you for that.
It's Tan Xuanlin. He's so crafty.
You can't believe a word he says.
What did the military governor say?
We can't let him build up the militia, right?
The military governor won't let him get away with this.
He said it was put forth by Anton Fay himself.
He can't reject the Municipal Council, so he wants us to wait and see.
Don't act rashly.
I think Father hasn't come up with a good plan yet.
Military Governor, here is the newspaper.
There are more and more articles about factory disturbances and strikes.
[Spinners protest against inequality demanding labor-based distribution]
I don't need to look at it. I already know
it's that bandit bastard Tan Xuanlin who is causing trouble.
Mill owners want to get rid of their baggage.
The British want to ensure the protection of the concession.
Tan Xuanlin.
He wants to take advantage of this chaos.
This bandit bastard is really sly.
It's not easy to build up
a private army under my jurisdiction.
If he thinks he can use this tactic to make me admit the existence of the militia,
he's naive.
What do you mean?
If Tan Xuanlin's soldiers can't
protect the security of the concession,
and they disturb the public order, can his militia still exist?
Will the British still support him?
Military Governor, you're brilliant.
Mr. Mu wants to stand up for those mill owners
and get rid of the Tan Army.
Can those ruffians in the Tan Army willingly take this loss?
Understood, sir.
I'll send Min Dacheng to arrange it.
[May longevity come with wealth]
[May lucky charms come with life]
[All the treasure right at the door]
[All the felicity right in the house]
Cigarettes. Buy some cigarettes.
Mrs. Mu, how can I help you?
My necklace clasp is broken.
Please fix it for me.
Mrs. Mu, you can have some tea in the back.
- The necklace will be ready in an hour.
- Okay.
[Min Dacheng, Pawnshop Proprietor]
Why did you come here?
You're quite carefree.
Speak. What's the matter?
The tea is nice,
but the liquor isn't.
No way.
I've arranged everything as you asked.
But she's completely fine right now.
Anyway, she's just a girl.
Why do you have to be so ruthless?
I used to think
that little bitch would never be presentable,
but I underestimated her.
She is Guangyao's secretary now,
and she stays next to him.
My Lord is beginning to value her as well.
And her temper is getting bigger.
She even hit Wanting.
What?
She dared to hit Wanting?
Not only did she hit Wanting,
she doesn't return home at night now,
and lives in Guangyao's lounge.
Before long,
Wanting won't be the one marrying him.
It'll be her.
When that time comes,
all of the Mu Family's property will fall into her hands.
Looks like we really can't keep her anymore.
I do... have a way to get rid of her.
We can secretly…
Look at this.
Each grain requires hard work.
Commander,
It's New Year's Eve.
Every family is having a family reunion dinner.
We should definitely have a few drinks.
All right.
Commander,
you miss the old Commander?
Our Tan family
can only have a reunion dinner in the ancestral hall.
My father, my mother,
my oldest brother, and my third brother who died young,
they're over there having a lively family reunion dinner.
They leave me here alone,
cold, and cheerless.
Commander, don't say that.
We still have your fourth sister right?
I'll be thrilled if she doesn't piss me off.
But for real, you really have to discipline her more.
Since she met that Pei Shaojun,
the number of times she defied people is increasing.
Even I can't keep her under control.
That boy.
He's a nice guy.
It's just, these days,
wearing a uniform means leading a precarious life.
I really don't want to see Little Four
live in great suspense and agitation.
I'd rather she marry a scholar.
Even a businessman.
I want her to live peacefully.
Fourth Young Miss is still young.
When she grows up,
she'll understand your good intentions.
She has grown up,
turning eighteen in a blink of an eye. How grown up should she be?
In the past,
I was out fighting with my troops.
I sent her to boarding school when she was eight years old.
Back then, when I sent her away,
she cried and shouted, not wanting me to leave.
I thought I could
spend more time with her when I had the time.
Then, she stopped crying and shouting.
The way she looked at me has also changed.
Now,
she doesn't need me at all.
Fourth Young Miss used to be clingy and good-natured.
She's totally different now.
Yeah.
But I'm really afraid of keeping her by my side.
Tan Si, do you know?
She's my biological sister.
I can't take the risk.
All I want is for her and Shuang'er
to grow up safely and peacefully.
Marry someone reliable.
Then, I'll be relieved.
What's that?
Someone put a lunch box near the door.
Dumplings.
Who else could it be?
It's Little Four.
Other than her, no one can make such an ugly dumpling.
Let's eat.
Little Four!
Slow down, Little Four.
Little Four.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Sister Shuang, I sprained my ankle.
Look at you.
Let's sit there. Walk slower.
Here. Slowly.
Does it hurt? Are you in pain?
Look at you.
Your second brother will have to worry again if he finds out.
In the future, you should listen to your second brother
and keep a distance from that Pei Shaojun.
Okay?
Miss Gu, what a coincidence!
That boy, he's a nice guy.
It's just, these days,
wearing a uniform means leading a precarious life.
I really don't want to see Little Four
live in great suspense and agitation.
Junior Marshal Su, Junior Marshal Pei.
You're here just in time. Little Four sprained her foot.
Can you guys help her home?
It's you again, you little liar.
What?
You want to play the same broken ankle trick again,
so our Old Pei can take you home, right?
I really twisted my foot this time.
You're a junior marshal, standing there talking sarcastically.
You don't have any sympathy.
You even choose to pick up old scores with me.
You're no gentleman.
You…
You're fine. It's nothing serious.
Take a rest for two days and try to walk less.
How do you feel?
It really doesn't seem to hurt anymore, Sister Shuang.
Old Pei, these two girls are on their feet on such a cold night.
Maybe we should give them a ride home?
Guys, look!
So pretty!
It's beautiful!
I wonder if I can have the honor
of enjoying the fireworks with Miss Gu.
Sister Shuang, I want to watch them.
Let's see it together.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Who taught you to meddle?
Let's create an opportunity for him.
Second Brother, it's God who keeps making us meet.
You can't blame me.
Junior Marshal Pei.
You said that I should move around less,
so shouldn't you help me a little?
How should I help?
I want to go there to see the fireworks.
♫ If the rainbow is the reflection of the sky ♫
♫ Your smile is like sunshine after the rain ♫
♫ For you, I'll tramp over hill and dale ♫
♫ Run to the long-lost decision ♫
♫ that belongs to you ♫
♫ If love is the life of land ♫
♫ Your kisses are gentle breezes and light rain♫
Look! It's more beautiful than before.
♫ For you, I'll follow your path♫
♫ Even if I can only grasp ♫
♫ Grasp the dandelion of yours ♫
♫ Your promise makes my heart surge like a gathering storm ♫
♫ I'll give you a cloudless day of sunshine in your eyes ♫
♫ I spent my entire life wanting to be in yours ♫
Although the fireworks are beautiful,
they're only dazzling at this moment,
they dissipate after the smoke.
Although the fireworks are short,
their beauty is enough for me to remember for a lifetime.
Since Sister Shuang likes fireworks,
you should let Junior Marshal Su set some off for you every day.
They are not talking about fireworks but life.
Tonight is New Year's Eve.
It's not easy for us to get together.
Let's talk about something happier.
Okay.
Something happier.
Fireworks are fickle.
May we all be like a river of spring water that never ends.
Yes, never ends!
[Defense Command of Shanghai]
♫ I've tried my best to make a good story ♫
♫ when you suddenly stop for me ♫
- Give me one.
- Brother Guangyao, look!
♫ when you suddenly stop ♫
Look at how good they look together!
So beautiful.
Brother Guangyao.
It's pretty.
Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year.
Miss Wanqing.
Cleaning up?
Had dumplings last night?
Yes.
It was from Fourth Miss and Miss Gu.
Miss Gu came here as well?
Tan Si, you should put yesterday's…
What brings you here? What's the matter?
I wanted to give you some snacks for the holidays.
You don't have to.
Right, your idea was not bad.
As soon as the news of the decision from the Municipal Council comes back,
those mill owners won't wait to send my soldiers back.
Xu Bojun can't stop it if he wanted to.
Then it's great.
Anything else?
I don't think you've been yourself lately. You've been very serious.
Are you in trouble?
You women are so troublesome.
If I'm not serious, you call me indecent.
When I'm serious, you think I'm having problems.
What can I do?
All right, Military Governor Xu will be here soon.
If he sees you at my place this early in the morning, he'll misunderstand the situation.
Commander.
Come in.
Commander, the waiter who drugged Miss Mu has been caught.
What did you find out?
It was ordered by Min Dacheng, the boss of Baoli Pawnshop.
Baoli Pawnshop…
Why would a businessman like him want to hurt Mu Wanqing?
That's right.
A businessman offends the Mu Family.
That's a death wish!
Okay.
Let's go meet him.
[Baoli Pawnshop]
Commander, there's no one here.
Go back for now.
Send someone to keep an eye on it.
Report to me as soon as Min Dacheng returns.
Yes, Sir.
Okay, haven't seen them in a while.
Let them come over.
Xu Cheng, tomorrow is the inauguration of the Chamber of Commerce Militia.
I won't be attending.
If Commander Tan asks about me, just tell him I'm sick.
Okay, Junior Marshal.
[The Defense Command of Shanghai]
Commander, look at your figure.
You were born a handsome man. How can we not win the war?
It is unjustifiable to lose the war!
Stop it. Warfare depends on brains, not all these garish things.
I'm just trying to flatter you.
If you feel happy, you can increase my wages.
Get over that. It's impossible.
Don't go. My shoulder patch is crooked.
Help me adjust it again.
Didn't you say it's garish?
This is not a war, it's a ceremony.
What is the saying?
A man relies on his clothes and a horse with a saddle.
Okay, the saddle is ready.
Right. Go see if Miss Mu and Military Governor Xu are here.
Yes.
- Mr. Zhou.
- My lady.
Mr. Zhou.
After dropping off My Lord, we'll go to the foreign firm on Jisifeier Road
to pick up some furs for Miss.
Yes, My Lady.
- Okay.
Father, are you going to speak at today's ceremony?
I'm not.
Although the militia is the proposal of Executive Director Fay,
the military governor's mansion knows that this is Commander Tan's idea.
Guangyao has made it clear that he's not going to attend.
We can't take a stand when we attend. Just take part in it.
Okay. Then we should go after breakfast.
Okay.
My Lord. My Lord.
Wanting has a stomach ache. She's bedridden.
How can it be this serious? Is she okay?
I can't tell. You must go check on her.
Otherwise, we should call a doctor.
Wanqing, I'm going to check on Wanting.
You go first. I'll be there soon.
- Okay. Then, if they want you to speak, I'll help you turn it down.
- Okay.
The car is here. Let the driver take you first.
Okay.
This alley is usually quite lively.
It's really strange today. There is no one at all.
Back up!
Miss.
Don't move.
My Lord, oh, no!
Miss Wanqing has been kidnapped.
- What are you saying?
- What?
Where?
[Chinese General Chamber of Commerce of Shanghai]
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Today is the day of the establishment of the Militia Bureau
of the Chinese General Chamber of Commerce of Shanghai.
We welcome everyone.
Next, let's welcome Commander Tan to the stage.
Dear Brothers. Today, we're here to establish the Militia Bureau
of the Chinese General Chamber of Commerce of Shanghai.
I'm humbled to be appointed by the Municipal Council…
Commander.
Okay, I got it.
I hope we can all work together to keep Shanghai peaceful.
Commander Tan! Commander Tan!
Old Fu, you stay here and keep an eye out. I'll take some soldiers to have a look.
- Okay.
- Come with me.
Let us all work together.
What are they doing?
All work together to keep the peace!
Bunch of losers!
The order was to kidnap Mu Zhiyuan.
You've kidnapped a woman.
We were clearly following Mu Zhiyuan's car
from Mu Mansion to Deqing Road, and we made a move.
- Who knew it was a woman in the car?
- Who is this woman?
She's the daughter of Mu Zhiyuan.
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫ I immediately saw your charming face ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫
♫ Tears turn into heavy rain ♫
♫  We went back to when we first met  ♫
♫ I immediately saw your charming face ♫
♫  To the endless sky and ocean  ♫
♫ I made a promise ♫
♫  Let’s let the mortals fall down with us  ♫
♫  If I forget your profile  ♫
♫  How would I put back together  ♫
♫  The memories that revived me  ♫
♫  Let’s embrace either during the sunrise of sunset  ♫
♫  I have exhausted myself in this life  ♫
♫  My whole life has become lonely  ♫
♫  Even if my vision is blurred and I can’t clearly see  ♫
♫  I’ll still sing with you on horseback  ♫