♪The dream we dreamed under the stars♪
♪Lights up the sky above♪
♪I charge into your world♪
♪With eyes the same as yours♪
♪When the rainbow in your heart♪
♪Soars high above the peaks♪
♪I will be there by your side♪
♪My heart dances with your feet♪
♪Through twists and turns♪
♪The transformation is for you♪
♪Protecting your uniqueness♪
♪My intuition too,
together through the future♪
♪In the name of love,
I remain steadfast♪
♪Traversing desert sands to find you♪
♪You make me burn with courage♪
♪Together, we rise above it all♪
♪Until you barge into my world♪
♪Side be side, we dream in unison♪
♪I watch your determined gaze♪
♪Sailing toward our tomorrow♪
♪I am waiting for you♪
[Everyone Loves Me]
[Based on the novel "Everyone Loves Me"
by Qiao Yao]
I wonder if there's a player
who can crack your design.
Let's see if there's a surprise.
Finally got it under control.
I am so good.
Impressive.
This player's anticipation
of racing lines,
exit points,
and braking points
as well as their precision in control
far exceed the average player.
He's a real pro.
Whether a pro or not,
we'll find out soon.
Such steady mountain roads
must have traps.
A dead end?
Well,
I'll create a road then.
Impressive.
He actually knew
he could break through barriers
to forge a new path.
Not bad.
Interesting.
Once I drive through this S-turn,
victory is mine.
[Walter Games
Game Level Design Competition]
So there's actually a surprise.
Okay, everyone,
now our four teams...
The last game was fascinating.
That was so fun.
Next up...
Must be Gu Xun's work.
We now invite players here
to vote
for these four teams.
[Ciao Mate Team, Hero's Path Team,
Joy Team, Cells Team]
We won...
Our support rate is over 50% now!
We're getting there...
We're getting there!
The final mystery
will soon be revealed.
[No. 38 @StickyDoughTwist, etc.
52%, Hero's Path Team]
Dough Twist?
She's here too.
The winner
of this competition
is...
Congratulations
to Hero's Path Group
from Dongning University!
[The Final's Race Results,
No. 1: Hero's Path Team, Captain: Gu Xun]
Look...
Gu Xun won first place!
- I told you!
- Qianling.
I knew the last group was Gu Xun's!
- Got it.
- Gu Xun, you're the best!
Excuse me, lady.
Please hurry and leave the venue.
Okay...
I'm on my way.
I'm just moving a bit slowly.
Please hurry.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
- I haven't found Gu Xun yet.
- Let's go.
- Sorry.
- Wait.
Is anyone not leaving yet?
Please, guys, hurry up.
Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Do you know
where player Sticky Dough Twist is?
Sorry,
with so many players here today,
we really can't keep track of everyone.
[Dough Twist]
[Episode 1]
Gu Xun, have you lost your mind?
Turning down such a great offer
from Walter?
You owe me an office
on the 88th floor by the river.
Can't believe you'd turn down an offer
with a million-yuan annual salary,
world-class resources,
and a producer role to start with.
In our field,
it takes years
to get promoted to gaming architect.
If you accept Walter's offer,
I'll turn down the offer I secured,
and work for you with all my heart.
But the projects I want to work on
would never be greenlit by Walter.
If you want to make AAA games,
just tell them.
My works
must take root
in Chinese soil.
A company that allows creative freedom
and is 100% Chinese?
Where on earth
are you going to find such a company?
- Exactly.
- Right.
There will be one.
I just don't get these players.
When it comes to voting
for their favorite character designs,
they don't even consider
the artistry or skill involved.
Right... They've got no taste.
As long as it's bright and colorful,
they think it's top-notch.
Morning.
- Hopeless.
- Morning, Qianling.
Morning.
Turns out the one with the most votes
is Yue Qianling.
Quite impressive.
Yue Qianling,
from now on, could you
maybe move a bit closer to me
when I'm talking to you?
[Resignation Letter.docx]
What? Qian Ling,
you're resigning?
But you're about to graduate.
I thought you'd stick around.
You're leaving?
What about the characters
for the New Year's special?
Mr. Jiang specifically asked you
to design them.
Well,
we have Mr. Yin, right?
I'm sure he'll do a fantastic job.
Exactly.
The New Year's special,
isn't that something
anyone with hands could draw?
Qianling,
we've worked together for so long
and formed such a deep bond.
How about this?
Let's have a dinner party tonight
as a send-off for Qianling.
What do you think?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Sounds good.
Here, Qian Ling...
Cheers.
Honestly, Qianling,
you're something else!
You're the first person to get
Mr. Jiang's approval
- on the first try.
- Impressive.
- Cheers to you.
Truth be told, the boss
wasn't keen on our proposal.
So why do we get to be here today,
[Monday]
peacefully enjoying ourselves?
[Let's work hard! Comrades!!]
Why?
It was me.
I took all the blame for you guys.
After all, as the group leader,
I have both the privilege and duty
to lead us through adversity.
Awesome.
Yin Jun, thank you for your sacrifice.
It's fine.
- Here.
- This one's for you.
Here's another glass to you.
Cheers. Cheers to you.
Qian Ling, I've been at this company
for ten years.
Do you have any idea
how it's been for me all these years?
Do you know how much pain
I have to endure every day,
and how much I want to progress?
[Tuesday]
I want to make progress,
[Let's work hard]
but they won't let me,
you know?
It's not easy being the group leader.
Cheers to you...
Eat, come on.
Mr. Yin, you're awesome!
Get up,
[Wednesday]
or Yin Jun might tell you off.
[Can anyone rescue me?]
No, thanks. Not going.
How about
the grilled fish place downstairs?
Let's give Yue Qianling
a proper send-off.
I said, not going.
My cup!
I don't really want to waste time.
You,
you,
you...
You guys going?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
[Employee Resignation Form,
Name: Yue Qianling]
Are you sure about this?
Back then, you outshone
a bunch of job seekers with your work.
The bosses loved it.
Until now, I still haven't seen
any entry work that's better than yours.
Qianling,
if you're having second thoughts,
I can still
cancel the procedures for you.
No need, Yin.
The main reason I'm quitting
is that I haven't figured out
if I'm sure
I want to draw otome characters
for a living.
So I decided to go back to school
and finish my graduation project first.
You want me to step aside?
Have you lost your minds?
Replacing me
with some wet-behind-the-ears brat
who hasn't even graduated from college?
Can you be more insulting?
I quit!
Which department is he from?
Even the way he quits is cool.
The 9th Business Unit.
You know how it is.
That one
that's gathered
a bunch of industry elites,
hired at high salaries,
supported by the entire company's profits,
allowed to burn through cash
to create the real
next-gen games?
Is it that 9th Business Unit?
Rumor has it, they've made
no progress for seven months.
The board is quite unhappy
and wants to shut them down.
But the big boss is firmly backing them.
Not only is she keeping the unit,
but she also went to great lengths
to bring in a new producer.
He's here already?
What's his background?
Apparently, it's a college student
who hasn't even graduated yet.
He's supposed to start today.
What's his name again?
Let me check.
It's...
[Chief Producer: Gu Xun]
Gu Xun.
Hello,
I'm here to report for work.
The 9th Business Unit,
Gu Xun.
♪Pretending it's all chill,
the vibe's just right♪
♪Only you and I
know the subtlety of this night♪
♪My heartbeat's a mess,
hidden out of sight♪
♪I keep smiling and being polite♪
♪I dwell in a castle made of memories♪
♪Every second, longing wraps around me♪
♪Your smile so unique♪
♪I see it again, it's destiny♪
♪In this moment I search for you♪
♪My heart races, again I see you♪
♪Moments of mischievous grins,
I want to spend with you♪
♪Worries or hugs,
I want to share with you♪
It's...
your first day?
Done.
[Non-Compete Agreement]
Thanks.
♪You and I, the vibe's right♪
♪Lose the distance,
you know we're tight♪
♪Gut feeling leads,
you and I are destined to meet♪
♪At the perfect time♪
You two know each other?
Oh, right,
you're from the same university.
Wait...
Qianling,
goodbye.
Oh, no.
It's done.
I'm free now.
Congratulations to Qianling
for leaving a terrible boss
and being one step closer
to human wisdom.
But I regret it.
When I was going
through resignation procedures,
Gu Xun was going
through onboarding procedures!
Gu Xun?
Didn't he just vanish
after winning that championship?
Exactly.
I've been searching for news
about him for the past two months,
but he just had
to start his job at HC today.
I wish he could have been here
an hour earlier.
Then this might just be your fate.
Fate's mysterious.
Fate?
[Two years ago]
Follow me!
Hey, you two,
could you at least
act like you're here to play?
My limbs have already degenerated.
This is no news to you.
Qianling,
this is just for social and fun.
Take it easy.
Don't scare off all the cute guys
from the computer science department.
They definitely regret doing this today.
[Live Scoreboard,
1. Gu Xun, 2. Yue Qianling]
I'm just two kills away
from being first.
I can't.
I'm exhausted.
Just shoot me.
Shoot me too.
This
is not cool, is it?
I don't mind at all.
- Eliminated.
- Thank you.
Eliminated.
[Outdoor Real-life CS]
♪Pretending it's all chill,
the vibe's just right♪
♪Only you and I
know the subtlety of this night♪
♪My heartbeat's a mess,
hidden out of sight♪
♪I keep smiling and being polite♪
♪I dwell in a castle made of memories♪
You're a snake,
even taking down teammates for kills.
What's a snake?
It's gamer slang
for someone who likes to play dirty.
In plain terms, it means
lacking martial virtue.
♪Moments of mischievous grins,
I want to spend with you♪
♪Worries or hugs,
I want to share with you♪
♪I want to be your reason
for a silly smile♪
♪You don't know what secrets
I'm hiding inside♪
Gu Xun,
time to go.
♪You and I, the vibe's right♪
♪Lose the distance,
you know we're tight♪
That girl played fiercely.
And she's very cute.
Which class is she from?
What's her name?
No clue.
I just know she's a snake.
His face
is so symmetrical.
How could someone
have such a symmetrical
and perfect face?
I should
have been more merciful earlier.
With his skills,
does he really need you to hold back?
Symmetrical, huh?
You art majors like someone
for very weird reasons.
This is fate.
Maybe he's just into someone
like Qianling.
Really?
Look how excited you are.
Qianling,
I heard there's a new head
in the 9th Business Unit
who's also from Dongning University.
His name is Gu Xun. You know him?
I do.
Really?
But when I met him just now,
I asked if he knew you,
and he didn't say a word.
Seems like you two are not that close.
You know Jay Chou,
but does Jay Chou know you?
That's not the point.
You know him?
Of course I do.
But does he know you?
Well, I fell asleep to his songs
last night.
Let me introduce.
Gu Xun,
Jiang Junnan.
Starting today,
Gu Xun will head the 9th Business Unit,
focusing on AAA game development.
Gu Xun was handpicked by me,
and I have full confidence
in his abilities.
Last time, I suggested
dissolving the 9th Business Unit,
and the board agreed.
AAA game development
is crucial
for HC's future.
The board and I
have reached a consensus
on this matter.
As we all know,
in AAA game development,
engine development alone
takes
a minimum of three to five years.
Gu Xun,
have you considered
the timeline?
AAA titles require
high-definition graphics
and immense processing power.
Standard engines can't balance
graphics and optimization
at the same time.
However, engines upgraded by me
can significantly reduce
computational demand
and ensure smooth graphics.
In short,
we'll be able
to save on development time
right from the start.
Include "completion of a game
within three years"
in the contract then.
I hope you can elaborate
on your project
at the project meeting next month.
Is that okay?
No problem.
Let me be clear up front.
At the project meeting,
if the approval rate
of your project doesn't exceed 50%,
you should resign.
Oh,
and Project Department 1's new title,
"The Love Broker,"
will also be up for approval next month.
We all know only one project
can pass at each project meeting.
As everyone knows, Mr. Jiang
is the best at getting approval.
If he's competing,
I'm afraid the rest of us
might not have much of a chance.
Looks like
I have no choice but to compete
with Mr. Jiang next month.
My apologies,
but the office space
of the 9th Business Unit
is being renovated now.
So,
we'll have to ask you
to make do with the warehouse
as the temporary office space.
That's okay.
But Mr. Wang,
given the limited space
in the warehouse,
I'd like to conduct
internal and external
recruitment simultaneously
to ensure that my department
is filled with the best.
No problem.
Yes, no problem.
Thank you all for your support then.
Thank you, directors.
Will I ever
have a chance with him?
Yishi,
I didn't expect to see you at HC too.
Looks like we have someone
to back us up now.
Don't try to cozy up to me.
I knew long ago that you guys
couldn't possibly produce a triple-A game.
What you said back there
was just a waste of time.
The meeting hasn't even started, Yishi.
Don't rush to a conclusion.
Giving you one month
is just delaying the inevitable.
Speaking of which, Gu Xun,
for someone aiming
to create a triple-A title,
how could you poach
from other departments?
Doesn't internal recruitment
ultimately depend
on the employee's own will?
The people I've hired
have been under my guidance for years.
You'd better keep your hands off them.
No way,
how is this any different
from a college office?
You can still back out if you want.
No way.
I've boarded your pirate ship.
How can I jump ship
before we've even set sail?
[The 9th Business Department]
New office space, new staff.
How about
a new name?
Everything should be changed,
but not the name.
From one to nine,
it's a cycle.
Nine
is both the beginning and the end.
We should stick
to our original aspiration.
I think the name is quite fitting.
Why are you suddenly
so poetic?
It's gross.
Then let me be more practical.
In the following month,
we'll do our best
to get our project approved.
The most crucial part of a game proposal
is to define the core gameplay.
So we need to keep our team
as lean as possible.
Lead programmer,
lead designer, lead artist,
those are essential.
As for the other roles,
we'll see if we can find
suitable candidates.
If not,
we'll take on their job for now.
Hiring...
- Two, four, five...
- Right,
how much
do you plan to pay them?
The highest salary in the industry.
The highest?
How much
do you plan to pay me then?
How much do you want?
We're practically family,
so...
For now, we two don't have a salary.
But once the project gets approved
and we are officially onboard,
we will.
What?
Why do they get paid and I don't?
If you want,
I can pay you out of my own pocket.
That's so kind of you.
The selfless Mr. Gu,
spending all the earnings
on development,
and even signing
an exorbitant non-compete agreement.
Forget it.
I must have owed you in the past life.
But I believe
that our project
will definitely be approved.
[Domination Arcade,
Inferno Arcade Machines]
- The legend has arrived!
- The legend is here!
[Leaderboard, No. 1: WakeNaturally,
No. 2: SleepTillWake]
"Wake Naturally"?
Who's that?
Your three-year undefeated streak
has been broken
by a newcomer.
[Leaderboard, No. 1: WakeNaturally,
No. 2: SleepTillWake]
Beat him...
That's so...
"Wake Naturally,"
are you trying
to copy my name "Sleep Till Wake,"
or are you deliberately looking
for trouble?
So awesome, oh my goodness!
You are in great form.
I'll put you back at the top in no time.
Sir,
who on earth
is this "Wake Naturally"?
Feels like they're mimicking my name.
I don't know him.
It's his first time here.
But
he's as good as you,
and he's quite handsome.
Want me to introduce you?
To me, an ordinarily handsome guy
is like a skeleton.
I'll move you back
to the top spot right away.
Gu Xun?
What's he doing here?
Sir,
could you do me a favor?
Gu Xun,
what a coincidence.
You come here to play games too?
Today's their anniversary.
Members get free game tokens.
What's your membership number?
Want me to check for you?
Look,
they gave me 300 tokens.
I can't use them all by myself.
Why don't we play together?
What should I talk to him about?
Thanks...
Got enough game tokens?
I'll return them.
What a great opportunity wasted.
[Campus Hunk]
Coming?
Four of us waiting for you.
Hello?
Do you need me
to invite you at your doorstep?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
What, can't handle a gun without me?
[Campus Hunk]
Right.
[I'm busy]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Hello, boss.
This is @StickyDoughTwist,
your playmate.
I live to protect you
and heal you when you're hurt.
I am flawless except for my pricey rate.
It's 500 yuan per hour.
If you can't afford it,
the chat ends here.
Bye.
[Camel]
Shall we start?
- I'm here.
- Hurry up.
[The Dream of 900 Million Girls]
Coming.
[Campus Hunk]
Wait a bit longer.
[Camel]
You can't be serious.
Bro,
do you have to wait for Dough Twist?
If she doesn't come, you won't play?
You're practically turning
into a "wife-waiting" statue.
I see now.
You never played shooter games before.
But ever since we teamed up
with Dough Twist,
you play every day.
I almost thought
you got addicted to games.
Shame on you
for favoring love over friends.
I didn't play because you guys were bad.
Don't say we didn't warn you.
You're falling for Dough Twist
without even knowing
what she looks like.
What if she turns out
to be some feet-scratching guy,
right?
Yin Xue,
where's Yue Qianling?
You two really don't give me
peace of mind.
I'm...
Qianling, you're back!
Stay right there.
Come here...
I was just looking for you.
You've come at the perfect time.
I have something to ask you.
Tell me, why you and Yin Xue
missed the exam of your PE elective?
When was this?
Two months ago.
What do you mean by "oh"?
We went to watch a design competition.
Now the only PE elective exam left
is lion dancing.
Do you know how hard
I've pleaded for you two?
I'm exhausted.
Can you please behave yourselves?
We will.
No problem.
Gu Xun,
Jiang Junnan,
there's a PE makeup exam next week.
You missed the last one
because you were busy with a competition.
I don't blame you,
but
you must pass this makeup exam,
or it might affect your graduation.
Did you hear me?
- Yes.
- Understood.
Why are you looking at me?
I passed the exam in my first year.
What are you laughing at?
What's so funny?
So you've passed.
What's the big deal?
Yin Xue, how could you set me up?
You know
who I saw today?
What,
why are you
looking at me like that?
Do you still regret it?
I'm telling you, I'm full of regret.
But what good does regret do?
Even if I kept working there,
he still wouldn't know my name.
You can't say he's a jerk
because he doesn't fool around,
but you can't say he's nice either
because he pushes people away.
Seems like he can only
be your muse now.
[From @CampusHunk: 5000.00 yuan]
Go back to your game.
[Campus Hunk]
I'm booking you for ten hours.
Get online.
Where are you?
You didn't run off
with the money, did you?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Transferring money to an internet friend?
There must be many more
foolish netizens like you out there.
I'll friend a few more later.
Dough Twist,
did you miss your big bro?
Camel,
leave some opportunities
for us young men,
or I'll tattle on you to your wife.
Nine, do you have to be mean?
Mr. Hunk
urged me to get online,
but he isn't online himself?
Something's not right.
Why aren't you
at work today, Dough Twist?
I quit.
You quit?
Why did you suddenly quit?
Look, Mr. Hunk is online.
I don't want to talk about it.
It was insane.
Come on...
All of you,
pick up your guns.
[@StickyDoughTwist]
[@CampusHunk]
Oh, no.
[@Camel, @TheDreamof900MillionGirls,
@Wheat]
Dough Twist,
feeling down today?
Is it because you got fired?
No,
I resigned on my own.
It's mostly because today I...
What happened today?
Someone broke my heart.
Broke your heart?
She... She's taken a fancy to someone?
♪With me, in the promised land of love♪
♪How I wish you'd give me
your fully committed heart♪
♪In both worlds, you reside in my heart♪
♪Carrying memories, I search for you♪
Someone broke my heart.
♪In this boundless realm, I'm waiting♪
Someone broke her heart.
Dough Twist, you've got a boyfriend?
No.
I met my crush today.
We've met so many times before,
but he said he didn't know me,
so he really broke my heart.
She's still single.
You still have a shot.
You have a crush? How old are you?
That poor guy.
What are you laughing at?
[Dongning University]
Wheat, your noodles will turn into a lump
if you don't eat them now.
I'm waiting for my girlfriend
to respond to my text message.
A text message?
You're texting? So old-fashioned.
Don't get me started.
Just the other day,
I met a girl in the library.
She was also studying
for the postgraduate exam,
so we ended
up studying together now and then.
My girlfriend saw our chat history,
and then she blocked me,
claiming she was a white lotus.
Read the chat.
I'll give you some analysis.
Alright, here are the messages.
"I am so sorry
that your girlfriend's overthinking.
We should probably stop chatting."
She seems considerate.
"Look how inconsiderate
your girlfriend is."
That's what she meant.
Is that so?
Hold on.
"How about
I talk to her for you?"
What a kind-hearted girl.
"Why haven't you broken up yet?"
That's what she meant.
What? You...
What about
"It's okay,
don't worry about me"?
Even I feel sorry for her.
"Don't you feel sorry
for how strong I am?"
That's what she meant.
Aren't you insightful?
How come I don't see you
in a relationship?
I'm not interested in her type.
Then let me ask you,
if Dough Twist is also like this girl,
what are you going to do?
I'm hungry anyway.
[Another Win (5)]
[Campus Hunk]
One more round?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Not in the mood.
[Camel]
Because your crush
didn't notice you?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Don't get me started.
He didn't even look at me!
[Camel]
You've got hope again.
[Campus Hunk]
I'll teach you a way
to make
an unforgettable impression on him.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Talk.
[Campus Hunk]
The persona that no straight guy
can resist is the naive girl.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
You like that too?
[Campus Hunk]
Of course.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
What should I do?
[Campus Hunk]
Act like a lady.
Basically,
be soft and gentle.
The naive girl?
I thought you weren't interested
in this type?
You're cunning.
I get it now.
You're awful.
I must learn from him.
Learn what?
Is this a good trick to learn?
[Easter Egg]
[20 minutes away from Gu Xun
starting a one-sided online romance]
[@SleepTillWake, Upload]
[Upload work, Preview, Post]
Oops, forgot to change the settings.
I got matched with strangers
because I didn't have teammates?
I said I wouldn't team up
with strangers.
What if they're terrible?
This Campus Hunk, what a narcissist.
Who is he to look down on me?
What,
afraid you're too bad
to carry me?
Don't worry. I won't blame you.
[Campus Hunk]
Give me your game ID.
Let's play one-on-one, you up?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
One-on-one?
Bring it on.
58851325.
Can't believe I got shot in the head.
Another round.
Victory.
Not bad.
You're not bad either.
We won.
This Campus Hunk
is really something.
Are you dating him?
What are you talking about?
We're just teammates.
Be cautious with online romance.
What online romance?
I'm done talking.
I'm running late.
I'm going to miss the school bus.
Bye bye.
[School Bus Waiting Area]
[School Bus for Area A]
[Yin Xue]
It's almost like fate.
I ran into Gu Xun on the school bus.
How should I greet him?
[Yin Xue]
We Chinese express affection
by subtly asking,
"What are you doing?"
♪I dwell in a castle made of memories♪
Gu Xun,
what a coincidence!
What are you doing?
I'm...
driving?
♪In this moment I search for you♪
♪My heart races, again I see you♪
♪Moments of mischievous grins,
I want to spend with you♪
♪Worries or hugs,
I want to share with you♪
Oh, no.
Chose the wrong question to ask.
♪You don't know what secrets
I'm hiding inside♪
♪Thinking of you,
what a beautiful sight♪
♪My heart spins round and round♪
♪You and I, the vibe's right♪
♪Lose the distance,
you know we're tight♪
♪Gut feeling leads,
you and I are destined to meet♪
♪At the perfect time♪
♪In this moment I search for you♪
♪My heart races, again I see you♪
[Community DM from Campus Hunk]
[Campus Hunk]
What are you doing?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Trying to dig a hole to hide inside.
♪You don't know what secrets
I'm hiding inside♪
♪Thinking of you,
what a beautiful sight♪
♪My heart spins round and round♪
♪You and I, the vibe's right♪
♪Lose the distance,
you know we're tight♪
♪Gut feeling leads,
you and I are destined to meet♪
♪At the perfect time♪
[246 days until Gu Xun unilaterally ends
an online romance]
[Camel]
Hunk,
you're a senior now.
Once you graduate,
you will never be a campus hunk again.
Shall we celebrate?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Takeshi Kaneshiro once said
that those who label themselves
as handsome or beautiful
are usually not presentable.
Why not share a photo to prove it?
[Campus Hunk]
You first.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
I'm too ugly.
I'm afraid you'd use my photo
to ward off evil spirits.
[Campus Hunk]
I'm too good-looking.
I'm afraid you'll use my photo
to catfish others.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Send me and we'll see.
You can send a fake photo to deceive me,
but don't send a real one
to scare me, okay?
Send me the photo.
It looks pretty good.
Take a look.
Let me see.
Right?
My eyes closed.
Did they?
You don't think I'm good enough?
I won't take your photos next time.
[Campus Hunk]
Dough Twist,
do you want to see a photo of me
playing basketball?
Send it.
Silly.
[204 days until Gu Xun unilaterally ends
an online romance]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Log in.
[Campus Hunk]
Busy.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Busy playing solo?
What's wrong?
What's up with Campus Hunk?
I asked him to log in
but he said he was busy.
Then I found him playing solo.
[Camel]
Miss,
don't you know what's going on?
Go pacify him already.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Huh?
[Camel]
Didn't you agree to play with him?
But then you ditched him two days
in a row
without an explanation.
He's obviously upset.
Why is he so petty?
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Let me tell you a story.
[Campus Hunk]
I'm busy.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
There was a little duck washing clothes,
and there was a spot
that just wouldn't come clean.
The duck's mom
got really angry and said,
"Can't you scrub properly?"
What should the little duck say?
"I did scrub..."
[*screw up]
Was I
not clear enough?
Let me try another one.
One day, I fell down
and couldn't get up.
Then you laughed at me and said,
"Do you plan to never stand up again?"
I said angrily,
"Sorry, never!"
Can't you see?
I'm trying to apologize.
[Campus Hunk]
Hmph.
Don't be mad, okay?
I went for an interview yesterday.
That's why I wasn't online.
No reply?
How about
I tell you a joke too?
Why are you telling me this?
I don't mind.
[The day when Gu Xun unilaterally ends
an online romance]
♪Confession imagined, a thousand times♪
♪How my heart beats for you♪
♪How I adore you, I dream of the day♪
♪To earnestly tell you how I feel♪
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪The moment we met, a familiar spree♪
♪Do you recall, on that day, you and me♪
♪Brushing past, then longing ensued♪
♪A daydreamer,
by thoughts of you imbued♪
♪Such complex tests we've pursued♪
♪Just small talks beside you♪
♪Make my heart warm♪
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪My heart races,
I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪In dreams' origin, you're all I see♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪
♪Jealousy and sleepless nights,
I try to forget a bit of you♪
♪But my longing only doubles,
through and through♪
♪Your understanding,
my adventurous guide♪
♪Embracing in a crowd,
our heartbeats amplified♪
♪Continuously falling,
our hearts can't hide♪
♪Our hearts connect, no matter how far♪
♪You are my world♪
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪My heart races,
I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪In dreams' origin, you're all I see♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪