♪The dream we dreamed under the stars♪
♪Lights up the sky above♪
♪I charge into your world♪
♪With eyes the same as yours♪
♪When the rainbow in your heart♪
♪Soars high above the peaks♪
♪I will be there by your side♪
♪My heart dances with your feet♪
♪Through twists and turns♪
♪The transformation is for you♪
♪Protecting your uniqueness♪
♪My intuition too.
Together through the future♪
♪In the name of love,
I remain steadfast♪
♪Traversing desert sands to find you♪
♪You make me burn with courage♪
♪Together, we rise above it all♪
♪Until you barge into my world♪
♪Side by side, we dream in unison♪
♪I watch your determined gaze♪
♪Sailing toward our tomorrow♪
♪I am waiting for you♪
[Everyone Loves Me]
[Based on the novel "Everyone Loves Me"
by Qiao Yao]
[Episode 3]
It's not much.
Why don't you just...
sign it?
Is Program Department 1 too idle?
Tell the HR to come.
OK.
It's okay, Mr. Gu.
I'm not angry.
It's very expensive.
My dress
isn't too expensive.
I'm talking about my pendant.
Quite good looking,
but so bad-tempered.
It's a pity.
Qianling.
Mr. Wei.
Have you completed the formalities?
Do you know why I asked you
to come back?
To be frank,
you're a good artist
in this group,
but there are a lot of good artists,
so you have to prove
that no one else can replace you.
I called you back to save the day.
If you can,
you will be a heroine.
If not...
The New Year's Eve event starts
on the 27th.
You have less than three days.
Make adjustments to the version
you made earlier.
I want to see the first draft tomorrow.
If you can't,
tell me before it's too late.
I still have time to replace you.
Don't worry, Mr. Wei.
I'm sure I can do it.
Qianling.
If you can't,
please also tell me.
I'll contact an outsourcing company
for you.
It's OK even if your drawing is bad.
The most important thing is
that it doesn't affect the schedule.
That's the first thing.
Don't be so stressed.
After all, you're still a student.
You haven't gotten
your diploma yet, right?
It's okay, sir.
If I really screw up,
you can still help me out.
Besides,
It'll count
towards our team's performance,
won't it?
Let's all die together.
You're right.
I'm just a student,
so what loss will I suffer?
I can just go to grad school,
but what about you?
You have a family.
What if you lose your job?
Nice.
[HCGAME]
Are you in love?
No.
Mr. Wei.
Can you tell
from the cards I drew?
I can tell you didn't put any thought
into it.
What do card game players want
in the New Year?
It's the comfort,
surprise, and even warmth
that a character brings to everyone
during this special holiday.
What's the point of just looking good?
I'll think about it.
If that's the level you're at,
it's a mistake
to ask you to come back.
He must be out of his mind.
Maybe I'll have
to save the day in the end.
What do card game players want
in the New Year?
It's the comfort,
surprise, and even warmth
that a character brings to everyone
during this special holiday.
[Private message from Sticky Dough Twist
in the community]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Are you there?
[Campus Hunk]
Yeah.
How do boys usually like
to welcome the New Year?
Is there a difference
between boys and girls in this regard?
Watch your attitude.
Stay at home.
And?
For example,
Going out with a girl.
You mean you want me
to ask you out on New Year's?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm doing research.
There's no point in going out
with a girl.
I'd rather feed stray cats and dogs.
Thank you.
It's here.
Are those dark circles made up?
Man.
Do you know how many chores
I have to do,
how many departments
I have to communicate with,
and how much business I have to do?
And I also need
to look for Scissorhands.
But luckily, I'm competent.
This guy
is a hidden treasure in our company.
[Wei Han's resume]
Wei Han?
Jiang Yishi's right-hand man?
Yeah.
Mobile Game Division's
top CGGD.
He was responsible for the company's
highest-grossing Otome Game
back in the day.
If you poach him,
Jiang will fight you to the death.
Why should I be afraid of Jiang?
I don't like what you're saying.
Jiang is scary.
Do you know the game
"Nine-state Journey"?
[Nine-state Journey]
Of course.
It's like most
of the other Chinese Triple-A games.
It seems that the project
has been dormant since its inception.
Wei Han started it.
[CGGD, Wei Han]
So he was a big fan
of Triple-A games too?
Then why did the project die?
It was just
a matter of circumstance.
No one cared.
No money.
No technology.
It's normal.
Wei Han had experienced everything
back then.
He may be even more pessimistic
about the future
of Triple-A games in China.
The mobile game department's revenue
is huge.
The future of "Hero" is still unknown.
So convincing him with program earnings
is hard.
Why don't we
give him a temptation?
He's been working for years,
so he's not stupid.
So, according to you,
no hope?
Are you stupid?
Me?
Of course not.
I'm very smart and attractive.
Mr. Gu, Mr. Jiang.
What's up?
Mr. Gu bought a new car.
Let's try it out.
The Dream of 900 Million Boys
is you, right?
You're really good at games.
Yes, really good.
It's awesome!
Mr. Gu.
What do you want to say?
Gu Xun.
Just call me Gu Xun.
That's right.
You're too much of a stranger.
Don't call him Mr. Gu.
We're friends.
["Hero" project proposal]
Mr. Gu,
I have to say,
"Hero" is really the best idea
I've ever seen in my career.
I've seen many things
with an oriental worldview,
but "Hero" is already exceptional
in its worldview
and the presentation
of its spiritual core.
I hope to see
"Hero" come out someday,
but your partner
must not be me.
Wei Han.
A single piece of concept art
of "Nine-state Journey"
gaining public attention
and making a name for itself
in the industry
shows that you've put in the work.
It's not easy for a Triple-A game
to get that kind of success.
Won't you regret
if you give up on Triple-A?
I would regret it.
You've done a lot of preparation
to find out what I'm up to.
I know what you're gonna say.
To be honest,
I was really happy
when I saw "Hero",
but the truth is
that it's extremely difficult
to make Triple-A games in this country.
I've encountered all the dilemmas
you're about to encounter.
Being creative at this stage
means nothing.
I've studied your personal work.
They're ahead of the industry,
which means you haven't given up
on Triple-A games.
Am I right?
Wei Han.
If there's anything you want,
you can ask for it.
We can fulfill them all.
How about this?
Let's bet on the success
of next month's project.
If it succeeds, you come.
Why is the project
for "The Love Broker" so slow?
Mr. Jiang,
your request
was suddenly moved up by a month,
so we really didn't have a chance
to consider a lot of details into it.
That's right.
The art team is full of work.
Everyone is preparing
for the New Year's card launch.
So...
I don't want to hear any excuses.
Now you guys have to speed things up.
It has to be submitted next month.
Man...
I insist
that we must show oriental aesthetics
and promote Chinese culture.
This is the purpose of creation.
We can't change it.
Mr. Gu.
You're absolutely right.
It's all about oriental aesthetics.
In Oriental aesthetics,
the oriental element
is Wuxia.
This is the most common way
of expression.
In that case,
I'd like to add some elements
of surreal power
to combine the surreal
with the realistic part.
It can greatly enhance the gameplay
and the setting innovation.
That's a good point.
We can make Wuxia new,
which can reflect a high-level
oriental element
and avoid
the traditional martial arts fighting.
There are temples and ganghoods.
I agree.
You're so right, Yi Hong.
This is more reflective
of the kind
of impactful fighting we want.
Yes.
We
can work on the new martial arts
and add the oriental aesthetics,
as well as the surrealism we pursue...
[Another Win (5) community
group chat...]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Time for a lunch break.
Let's talk.
Look at this.
It's supposed to look like this.
Yeah.
[Wheat]
I can.
[Camel]
Me too.
[The Dream of 900 Million Girls]
Campus Hunk and I have a dinner party.
Campus Hunk,
why are you online so early?
Aren't you having a dinner party later?
Yes.
I haven't finished my lunch yet.
[Campus Hunk]
I was stood up.
Where's Mr. Gu?
Mr. Gu?
Suddenly in a hurry.
Stood me again.
So who's treat?
Mine.
How do you make it look like
you've stood someone else up
when you're stood up?
He's been like that since he was a kid.
You've known each other
since you were kids?
We lived upstairs and downstairs.
I used to hear his mom yell at him
in our kitchen at night.
Did he have a crush
on a girl before?
What?
You care about my love life?
Of course not.
I just wanted to see
if you've ever had a crush
on anyone when I saw you so arrogant.
I really don't know.
After all, I'm much older than him.
He doesn't tell me what's on his mind.
Wheat...
Do you know?
I don't.
But I've never seen him
get close to any girl
or heard him mention any girl.
He is very much of a homebody.
He's probably in love
with anime characters.
Why don't I leave now
to leave the chat room for you?
But..
He's been talking
about a girl a lot lately.
Tell me. Who is it?
Yes, who is it?
You.
Me?
Right.
He said he'd never seen a girl
who could stand up
to a bunch of guys in a game,
but you're the first.
Thank you.
Why is my screen black?
[HCGAME]
I'm leaving.
See you.
Did you add this kitty?
I want the male lead
to have a pet.
What do you think?
It's cute.
Male or female?
Male.
Why do I think
this cat's temperament
resembles a person?
Resembles who?
How do I know?
I think
he looks like
a good-looking guy with a little bit
of arrogance.
I'm off. Bye.
Okay, bye.
A good-looking guy
with a little bit of arrogance.
Isn't that Gu Xun?
[Yin Xue]
Sweetheart, aren't you coming back yet?
Look at the time.
[Yue Qianling]
Don't mention it.
Less than three days left.
I have to redesign two cards.
CGGD said in the morning.
If I can't make it,
I'll be out.
For Gu Xun's sake
and my own,
I have to compete.
Women...
Gu Xun's department is hiring.
As soon as I'm done
with this New Year's special,
I'll rush towards him.
[HCGAME]
What a cute puppy!
What's its name?
Penpen.
How old?
Four years old.
Good boy.
Hello. Can you do me a favor?
Here you go.
Thank you.
Come on, Penpen.
Help!
I'm afraid of dogs.
Somebody help me!
♪In this moment I search for you♪
♪My heart races, again I see you♪
♪Moments of mischievous grins,
I want to spend with you♪
♪Worries or hugs,
I want to share with you♪
♪I want to be your reason
for a silly smile♪
Are you okay?
I'm glad you're okay.
I was so scared.
Good boy.
Go to your mommy.
♪Gut feeling leads,
you and I are destined to meet♪
Thank you so much for that.
I was worried about the dog.
You were suddenly
not afraid of dogs.
Indeed.
That's strange.
Why was I suddenly
not afraid of dogs?
Gu Xun.
I heard
that the 9th Business Unit is hiring.
Actually, I also like Triple-A games
and especially
envy and admire the 9th Business Unit.
I've done some online drawings
that many people like.
Are you that disloyal
to your job?
No.
Then...
Are you free to rehearse
with us tonight?
No.
Have you been
having trouble with Dough Twist lately?
How is that possible?
Since you found out she had a crush,
you've obviously been upset.
Aren't you
in love with her?
Would I be in love
with a girl I've never even met?
A freak like you, maybe.
[Another Win (5) community
group chat...]
[Campus Hunk]
The New Year's Eve is coming.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Yeah.
What do girls do
on New Year's Eve?
I don't know.
I'm not like usual girls.
I'm a pretty girl.
Do you want to ask her out
right after meeting her?
Why are you saying this?
Who said I was going to ask her out?
What do pretty girls like you do
for New Year's?
Just ask her if she wants
to spend New Year's together.
Why are you making it so complicated?
Who said I'm asking her
to celebrate New Year's Eve?
Can't I just research?
At the rate you're going,
you'll be an old man and an old woman
by the time you meet Dough Twist.
Both of you will be old.
The love of the old.
Just like this.
Eat your food.
Some people don't say
what they mean,
but they must know
what they're suffering from.
Hello.
Can I take out food now?
What a coincidence.
Why not ask her to join us?
Yue Qianling.
Here.
Xiaoye was late
for our get-together the other day.
He didn't eat anything.
Really?
Hi, guys.
Join us.
OK?
- OK.
- No.
Then eat quickly.
We have to go back to work afterward.
Enjoy your meal.
I have to take a call.
Are you working
so late?
Are you busy?
Thank you for this.
Let me treat you some other time.
No need.
It's embarrassing.
And,
can we exchange our WeChat?
I've found some videos of lion dance.
I can send them to you.
No need.
Just rehearse on time.
What a killing.
OK.
I'd better find an excuse to leave.
I...
Oh, no.
It's too late.
My dorm's closing.
So...
I'm sorry, I have to go.
I'll get yelled at
by the dormitory manager.
I'll treat you next time.
Does this girl
have a split personality?
Where is she?
I scared her off.
What?
It's like you.
I was trying to recruit someone
for our department.
Her?
No.
Do you think this is too pretty?
It's beautiful.
This is not so good.
- Two stars with the moon.
Everyone's taking pictures,
but I can't.
[Another Win (5) community
group chat...]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Two stars with the moon!
Wait.
Where are you going?
Enjoy your meal.
Two stars with the moon.
Oh, my God.
Yes.
Shoot it.
It's beautiful.
That's a good angle.
It's in the same spot
as Dough Twist's photo.
We're in the same city.
[Campus Hunk]
You're in Jiangcheng?
Gu Xun.
He's Campus Hunk?
How did you know?
Is it really him?
"Two stars with the moon" in Jiangcheng
is on the top search.
You scared me.
How did I?
I thought you were in the same city
as me.
That shouldn't be a scare
but a surprise.
I'll give you a chance
to withdraw your message.
What have you been up to?
Work.
I see.
I thought you were busy dating.
How could that be?
I told you it was just a crush.
You're not so young,
but why do I get the feeling
you're gloating?
♪How should my heart beat?♪
Are you going to suffer
in the rainforest?
I'll be with you.
♪The first moment of confession
is tipsy♪
So,
don't make it long.
♪How I adore you, I dream of the day♪
♪To earnestly tell you how I feel♪
[HCGAME]
As a domineering CEO, the male lead
is already very fleshed out.
Too much attire would only
blur the player's impression of him,
so I added a cute
and aloof cat
that creates
a special contrast.
Just one more cat than I drew.
Get ready for the release.
If you don't think it works,
go beg Mr. Jiang now.
Maybe we can get an alternate
from someone else.
It won't work?
I remember
someone isn't even alternates.
It's none of your business.
Mr. Jiang said it's okay,
so it's okay.
That's the only thing I can do.
If unlucky, I'll disappear.
Your group leader is really funny.
He doesn't even care
if the players are satisfied
but if you will make a fool of yourself.
He'd rather
be blamed now
than be proven wrong.
But why did you draw a cat?
It's not like you.
Don't you think that Maine Coon
looks like Gu Xian?
Feels like
he's a little aloof,
and,
a little arrogant,
that feeling.
What feeling?
Cute.
So?
How's it going?
I'm panicking.
I don't know.
I'm worried.
I'll take care of you
if you lose your job.
Come on.
You don't even have a job.
Make some money first.
Okay, I'll go make some money.
See you.
[Yin Jun]
I'm going to lose my job.
Qianling,
I can only do my best to put
in a good word for you with the boss.
I've told you
not to be too confident.
If you can't, don't show off.
[Private message from Campus Hunk
in the community]
[Sticky Dough Twist]
Are you there?
I'm doomed.
[Huang Jie]
Things don't seem to be going the way
the group leader said.
[The Love Broker]
[The Real Broker 1]
Why didn't you hire this artist
to do it earlier?
What was wrong with you
a few days ago
that you came up with that?
Don't cooperate
with the previous artist.
If I see that kind
of undignified style again,
I'll never recharge.
[Mi Mo Meow]
This artist knows me too well.
This is my favorite.
Gu Xun is really helping me.
[Yue Qianling]
[Campus Hunk: Doomed?
What happened?]
Mr. Gu,
we're done discussing.
Please take a look.
Regarding the worldview,
we have refined its original design.
It mainly highlights
multiple time and space,
eastern fantasy civilizations,
and ancient creatures.
Good.
See?
The project meeting in three days
will be the 9th Business Unit's
first appearance at HC Game.
At the meeting,
I'll be emphasizing our core gameplay,
which is long-distance interaction.
- Come on.
- Yes.
- Long-distance interaction.
This concept
will allow us
to accomplish multiple achievements
to highlight our high quality
in all aspects of technology,
content, interaction settings,
and screen optimization.
Let's take a look.
This is good.
This has
never been done before.
Of course. It's my creation.
Let me see more.
You need to learn from it.
[Private message from Campus Hunk]
Doomed?
[Campus Hunk]
What happened?
Nothing.
[Sticky Dough Twist]
I've been reborn and upgraded.
How about 7:00 tonight?
Will that mess up your weekend?
But we are friends,
so you must come.
I'm not available.
It's not up to you.
She doesn't go out on weekends.
Obviously, she doesn't have a boyfriend.
Don't talk nonsense
during office hours.
You're so prude.
You're chuckling to yourself.
Do you know Dough Twist?
["The Love Broker"]
We designed
[Four male characters]
four different styles of male leads
and made their age
ranges a little broader.
Except for urban women,
some of the characters' ages
and personas
are more suited to campus students.
As planners,
we wanted to present players
with a different
relationship experience.
We want to create an urban
and have the heroine
meet a different him
through a different time and space.
It's a romance concept
with diverse stories.
It's still not enough.
[Diversified love]
Yue Qianling.
What do you think?
I think
female players
will favor interaction more.
After all,
there are so many romance games
on the market.
They still want to have more interaction
with their dream lovers.
So,
that's still the planners' task.
Su Zheng.
You have to give me
a conspicuous design.
Everyone,
optimize this plan again.
Go back to your work.
- Okay.
Boss,
wouldn't it be a bit too hasty
to submit it this month?
Actually, it would be easier
to submit it next month.
It's none of your business
what I decide.
Boss has a good reason for his decision.
Don't forget
the lion dance training at 9 pm tonight.
Maybe
I'll get Gu Xun
in one go.
Got it.
I'll stop talking. Bye.
Bye.
What's wrong with it?
I've only used it a few times.
Gu Xun.
What are you doing here?
I'm cleaning the elevator.
Wait.
Oh, no.
Gu Xun is allergic to this smell.
I'll change it when I get back.
Time flies.
We'll be
training together again soon.
By the way,
will training with me on Friday
disrupt your schedule?
Yes.
[Huacai Interactive Entertainment Co.]
I'll see you tonight.
He's so cold.
This new map feels good.
Let me play a round
before I go to the lion dance.
What are you doing?
Does your crush know
you're so reckless in the game?
It's better to be reckless.
I became more feminine as you said,
but he didn't react at all.
First of all,
why did you say "became"?
Do you think you're not a woman too?
Shut up!
I'm going to see him soon,
but I feel like
he doesn't want to see me at all.
What are you doing?
What can we do at campus?
That's not important.
What's important is
that you should tell me
what I'm going to do when we meet.
When you meet, be gentle.
Extremely gentle.
For example?
For example,
have you seen idol dramas?
What kind of girl
does the male lead usually like?
The girl like me.
Then follow your opposite.
Use your softness to provoke
the protective desire
of your dream lover.
I see.
I'll trust you one more time.
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪The moment we met, a familiar spree♪
♪Do you recall, on that day, you and me♪
♪Brushing past, then longing ensued♪
♪A daydreamer,
by thoughts of you imbued♪
♪Such complex tests we've pursued♪
♪Just small talks beside you♪
♪Make my heart warm♪
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪In dreams' origin, you're all I see♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪
♪Jealousy and sleepless nights,
I try to forget a bit of you♪
♪But my longing only doubles,
through and through♪
♪Your understanding,
my adventurous guide♪
♪Embracing in a crowd,
our heartbeats amplified♪
♪Continuously falling,
our hearts can't hide♪
♪Our hearts connect, no matter how far♪
♪You are my world♪
♪You approach, close to me♪
♪Scattering light,
sparking memories to be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪In dreams' origin, you're all I see♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪