♪The dream we dreamed under the stars♪
♪Lights up the sky above♪
♪I charge into your world♪
♪With the same gaze as yours♪
♪When the rainbow in your heart♪
♪Soars high above the peaks♪
♪I will be there by your side♪
♪For you, my heart beats♪
♪Through twists and turns♪
♪The transformation is for you♪
♪Protecting your uniqueness♪
♪My intuition too,
together to the future♪
♪In the name of love,
I remain steadfast♪
♪Traversing desert sands to find you♪
♪You make me burn with courage♪
♪Together, we rise above it all♪
♪Until you barge into my world♪
♪Side by side, we dream in unison♪
♪I watch your determined gaze♪
♪Sailing toward our tomorrow♪
♪I am waiting for you♪
[Everyone Loves Me]
[Based on the novel "Everyone Loves Me"]
[By Qiao Yao]
[Episode 24]
I've always believed
that making a Triple-A game
was the most correct decision
I've ever made.
- Please sign.
- Okay.
[Stella's Team: Stella 34% + Mr. Li 15%
= Total 49% Shares]
[Walter Entertainment's Team: Mr. Wang 30%
+ Mr. Zhao 21% = Total 51% Shares]
This way, Mr. Lu.
I'd like to introduce you to this man.
Lu Xin.
He is a renowned domestic investor.
I'm sure you've heard of his name.
I'm here today
to compete with Walter Entertainment.
I hope Mr. Wang doesn't rush
to sign with Walter Entertainment yet.
These agreements that I brought
have better acquisition terms
than Walter Entertainment's terms.
I hope you'll make a wise choice.
Your terms are pretty good.
We had a deal.
You can't go back on it.
Steve,
I'm a businessman.
And we're talking business now.
There was a time
when the three guys in this picture
wanted to make Triple-A games too.
But it will never happen.
Gu.
I hope you can fulfill
our unfulfilled dreams.
Good luck.
Thanks, Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu,
your offers are very nice.
How about this?
I'll give you
all my shares.
I'll sign it now.
Wang Shiguo!
Don't sign!
What's going on?
In the past few years,
Mr. Wang has used his position
to engage in illegal matters.
I am
Mr. Wang's driver.
Mr. Wang's job misappropriations,
such as improper use
of distribution channels
for profit,
were recorded
by the dashcam.
Xu! You!
If the evidence
of violation is true,
then I'll consult a lawyer
to take over Mr. Wang's 30% shares
in a legitimate way.
Mr. Lu,
thank you very much for your support
of HC Interactive.
See you in court.
Stella.
Mr. Zhao.
Stella,
I've decided
to continue supporting you.
Mr. Zhao,
you're too late.
It's all settled.
Not at all.
The most important thing is
to show my attitude.
Let's go.
I'll guard the fruits of our efforts.
HC Interactive
will definitely become better!
Boss, can we
have a half day off?
Day off!
- Fine.
- Day off!
Then,
the workday will go on.
But I'll organize a celebration.
Xinyi.
Luckily,
I let Mr. Zhao
hold 10% of the shares
behind your back.
Mr. Zhao?
Out of the 20% of shares held
by Mr. Zhao,
the 10% is mine.
I'm afraid you'd use it all up,
so I didn't tell you.
Zhao Yu.
Sir.
You bend with the wind,
easily misled by others
with ill intentions.
- Sir.
- Take a look.
Do you see how well
my daughter manages the company?
Sir.
Please stop it.
I know
it was my fault.
I shouldn't have listened to Mr. Wang.
There are more things you shouldn't do.
Go now.
- Get in the car.
- Yeah.
I'll be off then.
Dad,
when did you become so familiar
with Mr. Zhao?
We used to be brothers
from the same alley.
I was the one
who helped him get his first bucket
of gold.
But Dad,
did you think
about what would happen
if you can't persuade him?
If he sells
the 10% shares he's holding,
he can get a large fortune.
How much do you need
to redeem the company now?
HC Interactive is valued at 1.2 billion.
Its 10% would be
around a hundred million.
Dad,
what are you doing?
Are you selling the house?
One more thing I didn't tell you about.
Back then,
it was 5 units that were demolished.
I told you two less.
Later on,
I made a lot of money
in stocks
and made other investments.
Now that the house prices have gone up.
And these other projects are making
money too.
This money is
more than enough
to buy Mr. Zhao's shares.
How is it?
I always tell you
to have a backup plan.
That came in handy now, isn't it?
Thanks, Dad.
You're welcome.
But,
I've done you such a great favor.
Shouldn't you be thanking me,
with something like a promotion?
Like a promotion to security captain?
No problem.
No problem at all.
Xinyi.
It's all over now. Come back, okay?
I'm fine in Project Department 1 now.
The work is challenging
and the leaders trust me.
I was wrong.
What did you do wrong?
Why are you apologizing to me?
I'll tell you everything first
from now on.
I'll have absolute trust in you.
And,
I can't do this
without you.
So you're asking me to go back
because you need a secretary.
I'm sorry.
I refuse.
No.
That's not what I meant.
No, I'm not looking for a secretary.
I just hope...
Alright, I get it.
I'll consider it.
Then...
But, the time hasn't been set yet.
Don't rush me.
Alright!
Everything's on your terms.
What's up?
What's in your hand?
It kicked me.
It's for you,
to give Coconut a buddy.
Coconut
is having a good time by itself.
But,
Latte
looks so sad
and alone.
Coconut Latte.
Look how much fun they're having.
Oh yeah.
I even made him a tortoise cottage.
Get in.
See,
my tortoise is a male,
and yours is a female.
Maybe
they'll become a couple in the future.
No, they won't.
Coconut is also a male.
They can't be boyfriend and girlfriend.
Coconut is a male?
I...
I didn't know that.
Bought the wrong one.
Alright, Mr. Jiang.
I'm going to work.
Xinyi.
Since you're considering coming back,
can you consider another thing?
What is it?
I hope you'll give me a chance
to be your boyfriend.
No.
Are you still angry at me?
Not that too.
How about this?
Three months.
A probationary period,
like when you first started.
If I
pass the test,
I'll be your boyfriend.
Let's see how you do.
Then where do you want this?
Snacks in case you get bored
on the road.
I plan to eat it with you on the train.
The gifts are your New Year gift,
as well as your parents'.
It's a little heavy.
I thought I'd carry it for you.
Don't be mad.
It's not like I'll never
bring you home.
I just think
that meeting the parents this
New Year's Eve
is a little too hasty.
And I didn't tell them officially.
How about I tell them this year,
and I'll bring you back next year?
Fine, please don't be mad anymore.
I can't bear to part with you either.
How about
I come back earlier?
I don't believe you.
Then we'll
have a snack first?
Take this
as an early train ride with you.
No.
It's that...
Lollipops are the best.
♪Pretending it's all chill,
the vibe's just right♪
Fine.
Then give me your home address.
I'll mail it to you.
That's great!
You're the best.
♪I keep smiling and being polite♪
How am I supposed to greet your parents?
First impressions are very important.
It's fine.
We're not that particular in our home.
All you have to do
is send a New Year's greeting message
to my parents.
♪You don't know what secrets
I'm hiding inside♪
♪Thinking of you,
what a beautiful sight♪
♪My heart spins round and round♪
♪You and I, the vibe's right♪
♪Lose the distance,
you know we're tight♪
♪Gut feeling leads,
you and I are destined to meet♪
Hello?
Are you really with Gu now?
Why didn't you tell me
about this great news?
How come
Gu is such a good kid,
and he's got his eye on you?
I'm so happy!
Mom,
I'm your own daughter, okay?
That's why I'm happy for you.
Gu is so nice.
What does he love you?
No...
Who told you that?
Anyway,
come back soon.
You said you'd be back this year.
There's some good news this year.
Alright.
I'm hanging up.
Yue!
More food for you!
There's good news.
You'd be happy about it!
What's going on?
Young lady,
your parents
are pretty rare.
Sir,
do you still need a daughter?
Hello?
Qianling,
your cousin just used your account
to play a game.
I thought it was you.
So, I told her
"Honey, let's play."
I see.
No wonder!
It's fine. It's nothing.
I'm not finished yet.
Your cousin added me on WeChat
and dragged me into your family group.
You what?
You mustn't say anything in the group.
If they ask you anything,
just reply with stickers.
Don't say anything, okay?
Fine.
[Chat Gu Xun]
[Loving Family Group Chat(20)]
[Flower in the Mist @Gu Xun]
You're Qianling's boyfriend, right?
I'm her aunt.
What do you do for a living?
[Gu Xun: May you have
a prosperous future!]
[You claimed Gu Xun's red packet]
[Natural and Unforced]
How long have you known Qianling?
[Rainy Night]
Qianling is a very good girl.
A lot of guys go after her.
[Gu Xun: May you have
a prosperous future!]
[Gu Xun, Why do you keep giving out
red packets?]
[Yue Qianling]
Why do you keep giving out red packets?
[Gu Xun]
I thought you didn't want me to talk?
[Gu Xun: May you have
a prosperous future!]
[Disappeared Moon]
Uncles and aunt,
I think Qianling's boyfriend
is pretty good.
[Rainy Night]
I think
he's a nice
and well-mannered guy.
What's going on?
A successful announcement
in the family group.
[Gu Xun: May you have
a prosperous future!]
Wake up.
Mom!
It's cold!
So you did know that?
Do you know what time it is?
Get up and eat now.
It's the New Year.
Why don't you help me clean up?
You neglect so many chores.
Can't you care about me?
I'm getting old already.
What are you doing?
Playing with your phone every day.
You have a better relationship
with your phone than we do.
Mom,
people get sick of it
when they come back for a month
and it took me two days.
Because you're worse
than everybody else.
- Mom!
- Get up now.
Listen to me.
Mom, is there a delivery for me?
No.
Get up and eat already.
Quickly.
Alright.
Hello?
Good morning.
What happened?
Why greet me like that?
I can't call you if there's nothing?
I thought you said
my present was coming soon?
Why hasn't it arrived yet?
Almost there.
About that...
I...
I miss you already.
Me too.
Really?
Then come on out.
Sign up for your New Year's gift.
I...
Watch your back.
Go slowly.
Girly!
Hold it right there.
Where are you going?
You're in a hurry even in your pajamas.
Dad,
my...
my boyfriend is here.
What?
Boyfriend?
- What...
- Your boyfriend is here?
Boyfriend?
Gu is here?
What are you waiting for?
Bring him in.
Wait a minute!
It's not that easy
to get in our house.
What do you mean by that?
Girly,
do you really like him?
Yes, I do.
I've seen that young man.
He's really nice.
He brought her breakfast,
did the housework,
did the laundry, mopped the floor,
and even gave massages.
The key is, he's kind to our daughter.
But not as good as you of course.
That's obvious.
Call him in!
Wait a minute.
How about this?
Let him prove
how well he treats you.
Right?
How?
Dad's got a trick for you.
Why are you here?
I had a New Year's Eve dinner
with my mom yesterday.
And I came here at night.
Well, why didn't you tell me?
I wanted to give you a surprise.
Come in!
Would it be inconvenient?
It's fine.
Mom would be so happy.
Oh yeah?
As for Dad,
I don't know if he'll be happy.
Is Mr. Yue mean?
We'll see in a minute.
Dad!
Mom!
Gu!
Happy New Year, Mrs. Yue.
Hello!
Got something for you.
Oh, you!
Why did you buy it for a visit here?
So, you're Qianling's boyfriend?
Happy New Year, Mr. Yue.
You just showed up without any notice.
Just in time for New Year's Day today.
I thought I'd pay my visit and respects
to you both.
- Yeah.
- And meet with Qianling.
You haven't eaten, have you?
Come, Gu.
Let's eat.
It was a long journey. Let's eat.
Is this what you're wearing?
Go get changed!
Didn't even wash your hair?
Here.
Be careful! Here.
Mom. Here.
- It's hot!
- Careful!
It's hot!
The food is ready.
Gu,
we're especially happy
that you're here today.
That's why I've made you a table
full of food.
Didn't know what you like to eat.
So, just eat.
Make yourself at home here.
Eat whatever you want.
Okay?
Yeah, when I come home,
mom doesn't even cook that much.
Eat up!
Let's eat.
Here, Gu.
Let's try a piece of pork trotter.
Mrs. Yue got up in the middle
of the night to cook it.
It's really soft. See.
- It's like no bone at all, right?
- It's melted.
Here.
Careful.
Grab with the bowl.
Alright.
- Here's a prawn.
- Thanks, Mr. Yue.
- Give him a prawn.
- A very fresh prawn!
Have a taste.
Have a taste of the prawn.
Pork trotter and prawn?
Prawn?
Have a taste.
You don't have to spit out the shell.
Just swallow it.
It's real wine this time, isn't it?
As Zhuge Liang said,
real nature can be observed
when drunk on wine.
Mr. Yue, you're so artsy.
Now, I'll ask and you'll answer.
Whenever I'm not satisfied,
you'll have to drink.
Qianling, pour the wine.
Wait, Dad.
If he drinks alone,
then when do you drink?
I can drink whenever I want.
Quickly.
Introduce yourself first.
Alright.
My name is Gu Xun.
I'm 23 years old.
My height is 187cm.
Weight 65kg.
I'm
Qianling's boyfriend.
Drink.
Are you
unsatisfied
with my height and weight?
Everything!
Especially the word boyfriend.
Actually, I'm also Qianling's leader.
I hate office romances.
Like in the TV show.
Male leaders rely on their status.
At work time,
they send messages
to female subordinates
to play games
and chat.
Even called himself her best friend
and deliberately moved in
across the door.
Always greeting
and said he was the best neighbor.
Also...
Mr. Yue,
let's stop here.
I'll drink.
How far along are you
with my daughter?
Dad!
Relax, Mr. Yue.
Although we were together
for just a short while,
if you think
we're going a little slow,
I can propose to her earlier.
- What are you saying?
- Rest assured,
I'll be good to Qianling.
Is my daughter yours to propose to?
What's on your mind, kid?
You're out of your mind!
Drink!
I'll drink.
Dad,
that's about it.
Too much will make him sick.
Fine.
Last question.
Then how do you prove
that you will treat her well?
Mr. Yue,
here's my paycheck card.
And?
This is my car keys.
Just these?
This is my insurance.
The beneficiary is Qianling.
And then?
Also...
Also, I'm...
I'm left with this.
Sleep on these.
How can you sleep
on such a small couch?
Can't even stretch your legs.
It's all right.
I got you a new pillow
and a new comforter.
Thanks.
I'll go back to my room then.
What's up?
Have you forgotten something?
What is it?
Good night.
Go.
Good luck for tomorrow.
Good morning, Mr. Yue.
What time is it already?
It's only five o'clock.
Do you think it's early?
Five o'clock...
Follow me
and practice sword with me.
Mr. Yue, you're really healthy.
That's it. It's got a nice shape.
Sunny side up.
Why sunny side up?
Because my daughter loves it.
Medium well.
Be careful with that heat.
Then I'll turn down the heat.
It's in nice shape.
Is it okay?
Yes.
Fried eggs are here.
Sunny side up, medium well.
It's your favorite.
Thanks.
Let's eat.
Um...
I think the bulb is broken.
Why doesn't it light up?
Do we have to change it?
Let me do it.
Being taller is useful.
Why is this chair rocking
back and forth?
I'll take care of it, Mrs. Yue.
Here.
Thanks.
It should be...
The eggs are delicious.
Delicious.
There's something wrong
with the toilet.
I think it's stuck.
Let me do it.
- Can you?
- Can you do it too?
I can, Mr. Yue.
He's fine with that too!
Mom,
do I need to change the sheet?
Oh, I forgot.
Mrs. Yue, take a seat.
I'll do it.
- It works.
- Really?
Great idea.
You've worked hard.
It's fine.
Then...
Keep going.
Yue!
Come and do the laundry.
Let me do it.
Gu,
Qianling is lactose intolerant,
so she can't drink milk.
Grinding her teeth at night
is a sign of calcium deficiency.
Also,
she doesn't like to eat breakfast.
It's not gonna work.
Young people skipping breakfast
is bad for the stomach.
You'll have to keep an eye out for me.
You know that?
Okay, Mr. Yue.
I'll watch her for you.
Boss.
Give me one of those.
Okay.
Qianling loved fried chestnuts
since she was a little girl.
She had it every day before.
That's why her teeth have gone bad.
You should buy her less
in the future.
Thanks.
Fifteen yuan, right?
Yes.
It's through.
Mr. Yue,
Is there anything else
I should keep in mind?
Let's get some soy sauce.
We're back!
You're back.
Where's the soy sauce?
It's here, Mrs. Yue.
I'll cook for you.
Let me do it, Mrs. Yue.
Not his time.
Girly!
Dad!
You're back!
Girly,
Gu is rarely here.
Keep him company.
I'll call you for food later.
Is it done?
How did you take care of him?
I didn't just take care of him.
I know what you're planning to do.
What?
Like empty plates,
pork trotter.
Did he tell you that?
I also know you chipped your tooth
eating chestnuts when you were a kid.
Did he tell you that, too?
He also told me
that you used to wash your face
with toilet water.
Dad!
[One year later]
Oh, yeah.
Should we invite the members
of Empress Dowager?
We've been playing together for a year.
Let's invite them
for such an important moment.
Alright.
Then I won't invite Jiang Junnan.
Okay.
Let me ask you.
Would you be nervous
on that day?
Why should I be nervous
when you're with me?
[Invitation for Guo Luo]
♪My first intuition tells me
there's sweetness in the air♪
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Please come inside.
Congratulations!
- Congrats Mr. Gu and Qianling.
- Thanks.
Please come inside.
It's about time.
Let's wait a little longer.
Maybe there's someone else coming.
How was it?
Nervous?
A bit.
You?
♪Missing the right moment
but in the blink of an eye♪
I look forward to it.
♪The first moment of confession
is tipsy♪
Camel!
Wheat!
Long time no see!
Congratulation!
Oh, you two.
Dressed to the nines.
It's a big day for you two.
- We'll have to dress up.
- We prepared for it.
Alright. Here.
We'll go in first.
I'll see you later.
Congratulations!
Get a child soon.
You're here.
We're all here.
Come on in.
See you later.
What are you two doing?
Hurry up.
♪To earnestly tell you how I feel♪
They're here! Quickly!
Thanks.
Qianling.
Gu Xun.
Congrats!
Thanks.
Give us a few words.
Give us a few words!
[Hero's Path Sales Breakthrough
10 Million Copies]
First of all,
I'd like to thank everyone here.
Making Hero's Path has been
a hard journey.
A lot of people
didn't think much of it at first.
No one believed us,
and no one cared.
We just have to keep trying
again and again,
to get such a small chance.
Honestly,
I couldn't have done it
without you all.
♪Through twists and turns
The transformation is for you♪
Luckily,
I met HC,
I met Stella.
So that this dream
I've had since I was a kid
can officially take off.
Jiang Junnan,
you'll always be my strongest support.
Yi Hong,
thank you for giving up
a good salary abroad.
To come back to the country
and do something
that seems so impossible.
Wei Han,
thank you for bringing a visual feast
to everyone
in a most professional manner.
Su Zheng,
thanks for your ideas and innovations
that brought a new breath
to Hero's Path.
Fan Xing,
thanks for your high standards,
making every detail
of Hero's Path
impeccable.
And Qianling,
thank you for your support
and companionship along the way.
Your growth
exceeded my expectations.
♪Protecting your uniqueness
My intuition too♪
So I'd like to thank everyone
in the 9th Business Unit.
With our efforts,
Hero's Path sold over 10 million copies!
♪You make me burn with courage♪
♪Together, we rise above it all♪
I've been waiting for this moment
since I came back to do Triple-A games.
Mr. Gu, I was right to trust you.
What the 9th Business Unit
bragged before
has become true.
You were the one bragging.
We did it with our own hands.
With our own hands.
Oh no. I...
Mr. Jiang!
Fine.
Then we'll ask Stella
and Mr. Gu
to cut the cake.
♪In the name of love,
I remain steadfast♪
♪Traversing desert sands to find you♪
♪You make me burn with courage♪
♪Together, we rise above it all♪
♪Until you barge into my world♪
♪Side by side, we dream in unison♪
♪I watch your determined gaze♪
♪Sailing toward our tomorrow♪
♪I am waiting for you♪
Here, eat this.
There're so many people here.
What are you afraid of?
Mr. Jiang, eating cake here?
Is it good?
Fine.
- Fine.
- Mr. Jiang, Xinyi.
You're so blatant in your
display of affection.
Is it great?
Of course, it's great.
Why?
Then we'll join you then.
- Yeah.
- Let us join you.
Eat it.
Xinyi,
if he ever bullies you,
just tell me.
We've got your back.
Yeah!
How could I bully her?
- In the future,
- What are you doing?
I'll listen to your everything.
- I can't stay here anymore.
- Forget about it.
I'm not staying.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Why?
I'm not happy you're doing this.
What's wrong with my girlfriend?
Have another one.
I'm getting fat.
♪You approach, close to me.
Scattering light♪
♪Sparking memories-to-be♪
Everything today
seems like a dream.
It's so unreal.
Yeah.
We finally did it.
♪Sparking memories to be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪You've been there
since the beginning of my dreams♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪
♪Jealousy and sleepless nights,
I try to forget a bit of you♪
♪But my longing only doubles♪
♪The adventure my mind is on,
how I wish to show you♪
♪We embrace in the crowd,
our heartbeats amplified♪
♪Continuously falling,
our hearts can't hide♪
♪Our hearts connect, no matter how far♪
♪You are my world♪
♪You approach, close to me
Scattering light♪
♪Sparking memories-to-be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪You've been there
since the beginning of my dreams♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪
♪You approach, close to me.
Scattering light♪
♪Sparking memories-to-be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You approach, close to me.
Scattering light♪
♪Sparking memories-to-be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪You've been there
since the beginning of my dreams♪
♪Each day, for you, I pursue my dream♪
♪You approach, close to me.
Scattering light♪
♪Sparking memories-to-be♪
♪My heart races♪
♪I think of you uncontrollably♪
♪You are right beside me♪
♪You've been there
since the beginning of my dreams♪
♪Each day, for you♪
♪I pursue my dream♪