(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
I'll carry your bag.
Thank you.
Didn't that feel great?
Yes, but it's so illogical.
We should've watched "Crying Fist."
It still helped me de-stress.
But you never get stressed.
What did you say?
- Hey, Sang Eui.
- Am I wrong?
Did something happen?
Okay, I'll be right there.
What is it?
Hey, I'll get going.
Hey! Where are you going?
Hey!
Jun Seo.
Isn't...
Isn't this Kyung Tae's house?
Where is he?
- Where's Kyung Tae?
- Wait.
Let me go.
Where's Kyung Tae?
Where is he?
You can't go in.
It's already...
It's already too late.
Move. Kyung Tae!
It was an accident, Jun Seo.
Just an accident.
We must find safety!
Let go! Chae Kyung Tae! Hey, Kyung Tae!
Let go of me!
Chae Kyung Tae!
No... Let go.
I said, let go. Hey!
(Connection)
It's me.
Jeong Yoon Ho
was near my apartment just now.
I don't know which road he took,
and I think he's using
public transport other than a taxi.
He just used a payphone.
Track the number.
Hang on.
The number is 031-0325-7898.
Yes, thanks.
What are these photos?
I'll explain.
I'll explain. Give me my phone.
Talk to me.
I told someone to follow Choi Ji Yeon.
That's how I found out
she was seeing Tae Jin.
That's how I got these photos.
Are you insane?
What if Tae Jin were to find out?
I told you.
He could be behind all of this.
And Yoon Ho is now a suspected murderer.
Don't you get that?
I got it.
One verse is enough.
Choi Ji Yeon.
Is your tail still on her?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
We're leaving?
(Episode 10)
(Kim Woo Sung)
Where are you?
Put it on speaker.
I'm at Cossack. CW went in on her own.
Follow her inside.
I'm about to.
I'm Jang Jae Gyeong
from the Anhyeon Police Station.
- What?
- Can you get a recording?
It's okay. We're on our way there.
Yes, I can.
If Park Tae Jin shows up,
tape their conversation.
Don't do anything else. Just wait.
Okay.
Where is Cossack?
It's on Hwansung's cafe street.
- I'll find it for you.
- Okay.
- Let's hurry.
What does CW stand for?
What? Oh, that?
It's Choi Ji Yeon's nickname.
Why is she CW?
You don't need to know.
Follow this route to the cafe.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
I'll have an iced Americano.
Okay.
Woo Sung.
- Yoon Jin.
- Hi.
Hello. I'm Kim Woo Sung
with Anhyun Economic Daily.
Put it on.
Okay.
Do you have anything?
What did Jae Gyeong say?
I want to ask you something first.
Oh Yoon Jin.
What did she have with Jun Seo?
Did they date?
Did they?
You don't know?
I think they briefly did in high school.
Why do you want to know that?
Did something happen earlier?
How did they get together?
Oh Yoon Jin was a transfer.
I think she joined
Jun Seo's music-listening club.
What is this about?
They dated back then?
How long were they together?
I don't know. I barely remember.
They dated for a bit...
before breaking up over something.
What something?
Something happened.
Jae Gyeong got transferred
and the music club disbanded.
I think that's how they broke up.
That's it.
What did they say that you're like this?
What about recently?
Did Jun Seo...
mention Oh Yoon Jin before he died?
- Ji Yeon.
- Did he?
Keep your voice down.
What are you doing?
You called me over
at this hour to ask me that?
Is this that important?
Yes.
It's important.
As far as I know, nothing happened...
between those two.
If you keep asking about that,
I have nothing more to tell you.
All three of them seemed to be wary of me,
so I didn't find out anything else.
We'll go to Boryeong together soon.
I'll get something then.
Did they seem clueless...
about Boryeong?
Yes.
Stay close to them if possible.
You're leaving?
My family's waiting at home.
And...
I'd like you to make up your mind
before this weekend.
Once this weekend is over, that money...
means nothing to me.
Why is that?
Tell me when you've decided.
As soon as she left,
she called Tae Jin over...
just to ask him if you dated Jun Seo?
I guess so.
I can't figure her out at all.
What?
You have all the conversations
between Tae Jin and Choi Ji Yeon, right?
Do I? I don't know.
Do we have them?
I kept some...
and deleted others.
What did they talk about mostly?
As if they did much talking.
They went straight to motels.
You don't know
because you didn't date much.
Oh Yoon Jin.
What?
You knew this wasn't the first time
they'd met at this cafe.
What did they talk about?
They really didn't talk about much.
They had the typical
cheating couple conversations.
"Get a divorce." "I can't do that."
"Let's leave together." "I don't want to."
- Is that true?
- Yes.
What's the money about, then?
Tae Jin said the money...
meant nothing to him
once this weekend was over.
Is that topic new to you?
Yes.
Maybe those two invested in a company.
Even if we don't get the password,
Tae Jin might say...
what the account is and how much is in it.
(Anhyeon Police Station)
I checked the CCTV of the area
you mentioned yesterday...
and got nothing.
He hasn't left Anhyun yet.
He might not leave at all.
What about Kang Si Jung's interrogation?
I asked if she knew of
any places for him to hide,
but she wouldn't answer.
Send her home...
and have people watch the area.
Okay.
Did you run the payphone number?
We'll get the results soon.
Hey.
Hello, Unit Chief.
Straw.
(Written Statement)
What does all this say?
It says Lee Geun Ho...
drove the car you asked about.
- Lee Geun Ho?
- Yes.
He's a kid from the suburbs
who used to drive girls to bars.
He recently came into a lot of money...
and took up swinging a golf club...
as well as spending way more.
Is that all?
Would that be all?
If you look at the bottom,
you can see Lee Geun Ho's address,
"Join-dong 18-49?"
Was anyone hurt in the process?
I'm not sure what you mean by "hurt."
Did anyone end up in the ER?
Oh, in the ER?
No one went to the ER.
Most of them were quite cooperative.
Good job.
Does that mean...
I have nothing to do with the case now?
What?
I'm off scot-free?
You have that look again.
(Written Statement)
Join-dong, 18-49.
You thought we wouldn't know
if you didn't tell us, didn't you?
We're going to go to this address now.
I was wondering if you had anything
you wanted to say to us.
- I don't.
- You don't?
- That's right.
- Okay.
Oh, right.
Do you know who is sitting next to you?
He's the actual owner
of the car you used to drive.
This is a connection too.
Why don't you two say hello?
Hello.
You only have a famous nickname
and not a famous face, don't you?
Introduce yourself.
Darn it... Straw?
Eleven years ago,
this guy alone went to see...
An Hyung Sik, the boss of the largest gang
in Western Seoul.
Of course,
his body was thoroughly searched,
so he went into the room...
with An Hyung Sik and five of his men
pretty much in the nude.
In that room, just like now,
were six cups of iced Americanos.
When I got the call
and arrived at the scene,
the six men who were in that room...
had all died
of ruptured carotid arteries.
This guy was covered in blood
and sitting there...
with no intention of running away.
And in his hand,
there was a single straw.
After that, everyone called him Straw.
Come here.
Listen carefully.
You have just made the legendary Straw...
into the suspect of a mere drug case
on the outskirts of town.
Look at his face.
You've just gotten yourself into
a very awkward spot.
Also,
we're going to go to this address now.
Everyone will think you gave us
this information.
So, you'll become a traitor too.
If you still insist
that it was a solo act,
we intend to accept that too.
What will you do?
But...
What?
Send him over to the prosecution
for grand theft auto...
and violation
of the Narcotics Control Act.
Wait!
But it wasn't me.
It really wasn't me.
How would a guy like me
do something like this alone?
The name of the guy I was with was...
- Lee...
- Lee Geun Ho?
No! It was Gong Jin Wook!
Gong Jin Wook.
Our big boss' name is Gong Jin Wook.
He told us to do everything.
Is this Gong Jin Wook?
Yes, that's right.
Is Gong Jin Wook the Doctor?
No, the Doctor just makes the drugs.
We only distribute it.
Have you seen the Doctor?
No, I'm sure even the big boss
hasn't seen the Doctor either.
The Doctor tends to stay hidden.
Where does Gong Jin Wook live?
I'm not sure...
No, I really don't know!
Only Geun Ho knows
where the big boss lives.
What about CEO Yoon?
You know CEO Yoon, the distributor, right?
Yes.
Most of our products get distributed
on the market through CEO Yoon.
Where is CEO Yoon?
I'm not sure about that either.
What is it you do know?
You didn't even know anything,
yet you didn't cooperate until now...
and kept joking around with us?
But I really don't know anything.
Darn it.
Sorry.
Run a background check on Gong Jin Wook,
- and try to find his location.
- Yes, sir.
But Lee Geun Ho is
probably not home, right?
Look into Gong Jin Wook first,
and if that doesn't work,
let's go to Lee Geun Ho's place.
Yes, sir.
- Where are you going?
- I have somewhere to go.
Let me know right away
if you locate Gong Jin Wook.
Got it, sir.
Check your balance
and choose a transaction.
Thank you for doing business with us.
- Yes.
- Jin Wook.
Today is collection day.
I told you not to worry about that.
Just lie low.
I've always done this.
Why are you so worried?
I mean,
if the police really were after us,
we would need some money
to hide ourselves.
I'll go and get the money today.
No. Listen to me.
If CEO Yoon finds out Dae Sung was caught,
we'll be in trouble too.
How would CEO Yoon know that?
And Dae Sung doesn't know anything
besides my address.
Lee Geun Ho. Listen to what I say.
I'll come up with a way.
Don't do anything and just lie low.
Jin Wook.
Darn it.
What did the directors say?
So, you should do your job...
and make sure they don't say
anything weird, you punk.
Seriously.
You're busy.
Okay, hang up.
Who let someone into my room
when I wasn't even here?
What brings you here?
You didn't even call ahead.
Hey, be more amicable.
The mood is so scary
that I don't know what to say first.
Do you want some tea?
You heard what I said to Chi Hyun, right?
Well...
I heard you knew that we were all there
on the night Jun Seo died.
So what?
Do you need me to confirm the facts too?
I looked through Lee Myung Guk's logs,
and there was a lot of interesting stuff.
Youngryun Cold Storage.
Lee Myung Guk made pills there
and sold them, right?
And you had
Jun Seo deliver the pills to you.
How many pills do you take?
What?
Well, I'm just curious.
How many do you take?
But what caused the falling out
between you and Lee Myung Guk?
Did Lee Myung Guk ask for
too much money for the pills?
Did you make Yoon Ho do it?
To kill Lee Myung Guk?
What utter nonsense are you spewing?
No.
It would've been hard for Yoon Ho
to move a body by himself.
Hey.
You did it with him, didn't you?
Hey, Jang Jae Gyeong.
Both the guy who made the pills
and the guy who delivered them died.
Now, there's only you left,
the guy who took the pills.
Doesn't that mean we have the answer?
Did you have them both killed?
- Hey!
- Isn't it true?
I didn't!
I didn't.
Guys who have nothing in their hands
are always full of talk.
Hey.
If you had something,
you wouldn't be sitting here
running your mouth.
Why?
"I killed Lee Myung Guk,"
"and I also killed Park Jun Seo."
Do you want me to say that?
I have no interest in getting confessions.
I just came because I was curious
and wanted to see...
how flustered you'd get at what I say...
and how anxious you'd be after I leave.
But when I come back,
I'll be sure to put handcuffs
on your wrists.
I'm off.
Bye.
Where have you been?
Nearby.
What about the taxi?
Did you take care of it?
I hid it well.
Give me what you have to give me.
You can't call anyone else with this.
You can only talk to me on this phone.
Got it.
Hey, but what proof did
Jang Jae Gyeong have...
to come after me?
- We don't know yet.
- You don't know?
Hey, Tae Jin.
I'm not the only one in a rush, am I?
You should step up to help.
What's your plan from now on?
Nothing.
You should come up with one for me.
That's what we always did.
Chi Hyun and I make the moves,
and you use your brain.
Gosh.
Shouldn't you be especially thankful
to me?
Don't be so cold-hearted, Tae Jin.
You were the one who said...
whether I did it knowingly or not,
burning the security camera server...
allowed what happened that day
to remain under wraps.
If anyone murdered Jun Seo...
and staged it as a suicide,
you're the only one I can think of.
What?
Jong Soo is softhearted,
though he might be immature.
Chi Hyun might beat people,
but he's not cruel enough
to give someone a disability.
But you're different.
When it's really necessary, you'll do it.
It looked like...
it would've been necessary this time.
If Jun Seo had found out
about your affair with his wife, that is.
Right?
I burned that security footage,
and you were probably on it too.
Luckily, we weren't caught.
Am I wrong?
Yoon Ho.
Yes?
You really shouldn't use your head
like you just said.
More than that, don't jump to conclusions.
Otherwise, you'll kick the bucket sooner.
All right.
I plan to do just that.
I'll keep my mouth shut...
and do as you say.
Please look after me.
Yes?
Gong Jin Wook is 34 years old.
He has two criminal records,
one for assault
and one for assisting prostitution.
He was arrested while running
an adult establishment.
He must've met Lee Geun Ho there.
I assume so.
But how did he ever get in touch
with a drug manufacturer like the Doctor?
It's all about networks in their world,
and they're in different lines of work.
You're right.
Kim Dae Sung also said...
that they were new to the job
and didn't have a distribution network.
They relied on 70 to 80 percent
of the sales on CEO Yoon.
Where are you right now?
I'm on my way to Lee Geun Ho's.
Do you want to meet me there?
Okay. What's the address?
Wait.
The guy came.
Please head over right away.
I checked yesterday...
and found this on the tracks.
Usually,
people return to adjust the volume.
Chang Soo, now is not a good time.
Please check on your own
and report to me if you find anything.
Okay.
Can you say something?
Can you hear me well?
Yes.
Hey.
Are you a butcher?
No.
- Why do you ask?
- Well,
I smell something I usually do
when I go to a butcher's.
Are we finished?
We have to work on the other side.
Give it to me.
- Gosh. I'm here.
- Hey.
Welcome. You're early.
Yes. I missed you.
Is Mr. Gong Jin Wook doing well?
Of course.
I'd like to count today's collection.
As you should. Hold on a minute.
What now?
Guess where I am.
Where?
CEO Yoon's office.
Didn't I tell you not to go there?
Why won't you listen?
We need to do what we must.
She's completely clueless.
She asked how you were doing.
- Geun Ho.
- Please don't worry.
I'll get the money and head over.
Get out of there right now.
Get out now.
Come on, brother. It's fine.
She went to get the money.
Geun Ho.
Lee Geun Ho!
Here.
Should I go over,
or would you like to come here?
CEO Yoon.
Don't you dare lay a finger on Geun Ho
or I'll kill you.
Like I said,
should I go over,
or would you like to come here?
I'm coming.
Okay.
I want the burner phone
with the Doctor's contact...
in exchange for Geun Ho.
Put Geun Ho on the phone.
Well...
He won't last long.
You better get here within 30 minutes.
Darn it.
Here, try it out.
Gosh. I can hear well.
Then it's finished.
Please come back
if there is another issue.
Thank you.
(German Digital Hearing Aid)
What are you looking for?
I searched just in case,
but it's not here.
By the way,
did this person ever visit here?
No.
All right. Thank you.
Sure.
I told him to take this off
before throwing it out.
He never listens.
Gosh.
(Gong X Wook)
Hello?
Detective Kim.
I called because I have a gift for you.
I'll catch Gong Jin Wook
and Lee Geun Ho and hand them over.
I'll have them delivered safely...
in 30 minutes to the boiler room
in our building's basement.
Quietly...
Come and arrest them quietly.
(Anhyun Shopping Mall)
Excuse me.
Did you see a man pass by just now?
He's about 180cm tall and has a hat on.
I'm not sure.
I see.
(Anhyun Shopping Mall)
(Antiques)
You came right on time.
Sir.
Did you ask the kid
with the hearing aid what his job was?
You haven't caught him yet?
Do you know what he does?
I didn't ask him that.
Kim Chang Soo.
Kim Chang Soo!
What are you doing here?
It's that way.
What happened?
Goodness.
Was that a gunshot?
- Excuse us.
- Gosh.
Make way.
- It's dangerous. Step back.
- Okay.
Step aside.
(Anhyun Shopping Mall)
(Antiques)
Hey.
Anhyun Shopping Mall, first floor.
We have a gunshot victim.
Who are you?
Did you get me addicted?
Why?
Tell me.
- Did you call paramedics?
- Yes.
Hey. Do you know Park Jun Seo?
What about Park Tae Jin?
Do you know Park Tae Jin?
Did he put you up to it?
Hey.
No, stay with me.
Do you know Park Tae Jin?
Did he make you do it?
Talk to me.
Hey. Did you get me addicted?
Tell me. Who was it?
Come on.
Yes. I'll tell you
after I schedule a meeting.
We need to figure out
the password Park Tae Jin wants.
You don't know what Park Tae Jin's like.
He's going to make Choi Ji Yeon
tell him the password no matter what.
Even if we don't get the password,
Tae Jin might say what the account is...
and how much is in it.
- You're back.
- Yes.
What's that?
Gifts to send our clients.
I see.
Okay.
I need to take care of something
away from the office.
Okay, go ahead.
(Twostar Holdings)
Hello.
You were in.
Yoon Jin.
Is she your only employee?
Yes. Take a seat.
You're pretty successful.
Aren't you?
When you said you sold insurance,
I wasn't sure you were even capable.
Will you clean up after yourself?
What is this?
Hey. They're gifts for my clients.
- They're gifts?
- You can have one.
I'll mix one for you.
Is it a health supplement?
We give out quality gifts.
Yes, you actually do.
Why are you here?
What?
I came to ask you something.
Thanks.
What do you want to ask?
I don't know...
how to explain this.
- What if...
- Yoon Jin.
Saying "what if..."
and asking what I'd do in that situation.
Can you stop talking like that?
Is that what I always say?
The passcode.
It's your birthday, isn't it?
Zero, three, zero, five.
Yesterday, Ji Yeon...
Her dead husband used...
his ex-girlfriend's birthday
as a passcode...
and that's why...
she rushed to throw up.
And as soon as she met Tae Jin,
she asked him
about you and Jun Seo. Right?
How did you figure all that out?
The money must belong to
Tae Jin and Jun Seo,
but Jun Seo is dead.
Tae Jin needs to withdraw the money,
but he thinks
only Ji Yeon knows the passcode.
But the passcode is your birthday,
and the only two people in the world
who know that are you and Choi Ji Yeon.
No, there are three including me now.
How much do you know?
If what I said so far is right,
Yoon Jin.
Why did you come to see me?
The money.
Can't I have it?
You can't.
- Why not?
- You didn't earn it.
Okay.
I didn't earn it.
Do you think Tae Jin did, then?
Hey.
What do you think that means?
It means it's Jun Seo's money.
To let people like Tae Jin
and Ji Yeon have it...
when they stabbed him in the back.
Is that right?
It's like...
I found a treasure chest.
What's inside?
It's hard to prove whose it is,
and we don't know
how that money was earned.
It just belongs to whoever opens that box.
But it just turns out...
that the password to open
that box of treasures...
is my birthday.
Can I still not keep it?
If you think that way,
why did you come to me?
What did you want to hear?
(An insurance plan designed just for you!)
Yoon Jin.
You also think that this isn't right.
That was why you came to see me,
and you were hoping that I'd say
that it wasn't true.
No.
That I could keep it.
I was hoping to hear
that you'd tell me to keep that money.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Wait. One moment.
All right.
I found the CCTV files.
I'll watch them.
Oh, right.
So she was already dead when you got here?
And there weren't
any firearms at the scene?
- Is it CEO Yoon?
- Yes.
I'll check the identity.
They'll find out soon enough that
the wound is from a .38 caliber bullet.
Please let us know as soon as possible
when you get the analysis results.
Unit Chief.
Will you take a look at the CCTV footage?
Oh, let's go.
You also think that this isn't right.
That was why you came to see me,
and you were hoping that I'd say
that it wasn't true.
Ye Eun.
He... Hello?
Ye Eun?
- Ye...
- Mom, it's me!
Yes, it's Mom.
Were you still awake?
It's morning here.
Oh,
that's right.
Gosh, I always forget.
By the way,
how did you call me?
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Mommy
- Happy birthday to you
Thank you.
I'm so happy that my daughter
is wishing me a happy birthday.
Your birthday was yesterday,
but I forgot to call you. I'm sorry.
Goodness.
That's okay.
I miss you so much today.
Me too.
Mom, I have to go to school now.
Oh, okay. Bye.
Ye Eun.
Ye Eun, I love you.
I love you too.
That guy didn't even have a murder charge.
The fact that he suddenly got bold enough
to point a gun at her chest and shoot...
It means he had a glimpse into his future.
In Korea, a nation surrounded by
the sea on three sides,
if you shoot and kill someone with a gun,
it means he intends to
stop dealing drugs here.
Then, what about the fact
that he shot CEO Yoon?
He must've known CEO Yoon would chase
him down until the end if he didn't.
Also,
if the Doctor leaves Gong Jin Wook out...
and deals directly with CEO Yoon,
it would leave Gong Jin Wook
with no cards to play.
He was probably thinking he wouldn't leave
the Doctor any other choices.
I've already put him on
the wanted and no-fly lists.
He won't have any other choice
but to stow away.
Check to see if Gong Jin Wook has
any ties in China or Southeast Asia.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Look into stowaway routes too.
Chang Soo.
You still haven't answered my question.
Sir?
How did you get here?
You went to Lee Geun Ho's place.
Oh, that?
Well, I was searching Lee Geun Ho's house,
and I found Gong Jin Wook's address.
So, I went to that location,
and Gong Jin Wook was just leaving
right then.
So I tailed him.
You went to Gong Jin Wook's address
by yourself?
Not even requesting backup...
or making any reports?
Yes, sir.
I was going to stake out
at the scene and contact you.
I was the one who was surprised...
to see you here.
Got it.
So, Captain...
Have you perhaps been taking Etaphen?
Yes.
Are you all right?
So far.
That's a relief.
We should catch them soon.
I'll gather the evidence,
and return to the station first
with CEO Yoon's man outside.
Get back safely.
I'll see you there.
Yes, sir.
(Anhyun Shopping Mall)
Get in.
The scene is busy. Go and help.
I'll take him in by myself.
Yes, sir.
Key.
Why did CEO Yoon call Gong Jin Wook?
I'm sorry, but could you speak
a little louder?
I have bad hearing.
Why did CEO Yoon call Gong Jin Wook?
Because she wanted to make direct deals
with the Doctor for Lemon Mulberry...
She wanted his burner phone.
Was it a trade for Lee Geun Ho?
Yes.
Where are we going now?
Listen carefully.
What?
If you keep the fact
that you saw me last time...
a secret until you die,
I'll let you get out after a short stint.
Got it?
By "a short stint,"
how much are you talking?
I don't know that, you punk.
If anyone asks, just keep your mouth shut.
Got it?
Detective.
I...
did what I did because CEO Yoon made me,
but I've killed quite a few people.
Are you sure you can reduce my sentence?
That's probably unlikely.
Why don't you just let me off...
on the shoulder over there?
Are you out of your mind?
Numerous people saw me take you away.
I can't free you.
Darn it! What do you want me to do?
I know you and CEO Yoon are close.
I saw you accepting money from her.
It's not like keeping this a secret
would allow me to get out faster.
Right.
That other detective at the scene...
I remembered him.
He's the one I drugged
with Lemon Mulberry.
He's a druggie, isn't he?
What?
What's wrong with detectives these days?
One's a druggie,
- and...
- Shut your mouth!
I can assure you
I'll live quietly in hiding.
Just let me off at the intersection.
If you don't, I have nothing to lose.
Hey! Stop the car!
Stop the car!
(Gold Internet Cafe)
How could they book
the whole Internet cafe?
- How annoying.
- I was going to play all night today.
(Gold Internet Cafe)
Hey.
Take a seat.
(Gold Internet Cafe)
(I know the password.)
What is this text about?
It's just as it says.
Do you even know
what password you're talking about?
No, I don't.
You're trying to feel me out.
I guess
you could keep asking Ji Yeon instead.
Let me ask you one thing.
The money.
Where did it come from?
Why do you want to know?
Of course, I want to know...
since I'll be taking half of it.
I don't want to get in trouble later.
Answer me.
Where did it come from?
Is it dirty money?
If that's the case...
If that's the case,
are you going to keep the password...
a secret from me
as an act of social justice?
I know you don't care
where the money is from.
I've seen many likes of you
while working as a prosecutor.
"I didn't know it was something bad
in the beginning."
"I never meant to do that."
At the same time,
you still do whatever you want.
Just look around.
You chose this place.
You booked the whole place
to transfer money online,
but you demanded me to tell you
where the money came from.
Yoon Jin. I'll say this as a friend.
You should be more honest with yourself.
Don't you agree?
So, enough of the nonsense,
and tell me the password.
Goodness.
You're really photogenic.
(Disclosing the affair
of Prosecutor Park Tae Jin)
Anti-Corruption
and Civil Rights Commission,
the Supreme Prosecutors' Office,
broadcasting stations,
Anhyun District
Public Prosecutor's Office,
Anhyun City Hall,
Oh Chi Hyun, and Won Jong Soo.
Is that enough?
You prepared a lot.
I'll put in the password myself.
Once you transfer half of the money
to the account I want,
I'll return all these pictures...
and recordings back to you.
Oh Yoon Jin!
How dare you?
Die!
Yoon Jin.
Yoon Jin?
Hurry.
- Chang Soo!
- Wait. Chang Soo!
Chang Soo, are you all right?
Don't move. What happened?
It was my mistake.
I thought it would be okay
to transport him alone.
So what happened?
I had him sitting in the back
in handcuffs,
then Ko Gi Sung started to kick me.
Maybe he felt uneasy,
but he went out of control.
I tried to calm him down
by blocking him with my arm,
but it was useless.
I was trying to keep
the steering wheel steady,
but this was where I ended up.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
- How do you feel?
- I'm fine.
I'm glad you're not any worse.
It was a close call.
We have to transfer him now.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Chang Soo, take care.
I'll visit you at the hospital later.
- Soo Hyun, take care of him.
- Okay.
Gosh.
That was unexpected.
Someone died from a gunshot,
and while transferring a related suspect,
he also died.
I'm scared of what tomorrow will bring.
The police commissioner will be
on the chief of police's case.
And the chief of police will want
to kill me.
What is it?
- Nothing.
- Just say it.
You think something is suspicious.
What is it?
Ko Gi Sung attacked him
from behind the passenger's seat.
From this street,
the car swerved right...
and went off-road in a straight line.
What?
Didn't Chang Soo say this?
He said Ko Gi Sung kicked him,
so he blocked with his arm.
Doing that would make his body turn left.
Which means,
the steering wheel would also turn left.
But, the steering wheel turned right.
Well...
If the steering wheel had turned left,
he would've crossed the centerline
to run into that.
Maybe he subconsciously turned...
the steering wheel to the right.
While doing that,
he turned it too much
without realizing it.
I think it could happen.
I guess so.
Let's go.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
How did the driver Kim Chang Soo escape?
When we got here,
he was already on the shore.
Did anyone touch the window
by the driver's seat?
No, we just got it out of the water.
But it's automatic.
It wouldn't have opened underwater...
since the engine would shut down.
I see.
Wait...
Does that mean he went in the water
with the window open?
In this weather?
Did Chang Soo...
(Connection)
Now that Jun Seo is dead,
who's running the Lemon Mulberry business?
- Good job.
- Thanks.
Sang Eui.
I told you not to discuss such matters
on the phone. Didn't I?
Are you the Doctor?
- Sang Eui, did you meet with Jae Gyeong?
- Yes.
I knew it.
This won't do.
Do you really want to kill him?
Do you have a better idea?
Park Tae Jin is behind it all, you fools!
I won't die without a bang.
I'll drag you all down with me.
Did you kill Jun Seo with Tae Jin?
What do you mean?
You must be confused.
You believe
one of us definitely killed Jun Seo,
but you don't have the evidence.
Right?
You put a lot of work into it.
Too bad.
My hunch tells me I'm almost there.
I just have to reach out...
and you'll be done.