My dad would sometimes say…
that I was too softhearted
because I took after him…
I'm going to keep it.
I said no. Put it back where you found it.
No, I'm going to keep it.
Mom and Dad are busy.
Who will take care of it?
I will do everything!
And how will you do that?
Nobody will be helping you.
Come on, Mom. Please!
No.
Please, Mom!
- Take it back!
- …and that I became attached too easily.
Hey.
Are you…
going home like that again?
This won't do. Hop on the back.
From now on,
tell everyone you're my little brother.
Where are the kids
who've been bullying you?
Hold on tight.
Especially to pitiful little things.
You know,
those things go away easily,
so you may end up feeling hurt.
But I take after Mom.
Right.
You are brave, just like Mom,
so I'm sure you'll bounce back.
Goodness, you've grown so much.
I should buy you a bigger bicycle.
How about a pretty red one?
Enjoy your ice cream.
Perhaps Dad already knew what was to come.
KONG
PROPERTY FOR SALE
Hey there,
lady who pretends to be mean
but is actually kind as hell.
- I was practicing my line.
- That's not your line.
You've memorized my lines again.
Your interest in me is overwhelming.
But this one isn't little…
Giddyap, horsey
Giddyap…
…nor is it pitiful at all.
- Have a safe trip home, sir!
- Take care!
- Good work, sir!
- Bye, Director Ma!
- Good night!
- See you again!
Hit the road!
Next round!
- Let's go!
- Next round!
- You've done well. Bye!
- Good job, guys.
Round three!
He's just the weirdest person
you'll ever meet.
Hey, one second.
As you can see,
I've had too much to drink today.
Yes, so go home already.
- No, wait.
- What are you…
Be my designated driver just this once?
Just leave it here
and come back for it tomorrow.
That'd be pretty careless
in a country of bicycle thieves.
It doesn't even look expensive.
My brother bought it for me.
Hey, aren't designated drivers
supposed to give their friends a ride?
Zip it, or I'll drop everything and leave.
Red is definitely a tacky color.
The thing is,
my brother said
red is, hands down, the best…
Are you and your brother close?
Wanna hear about him?
My brother is tall and handsome.
He was super popular in high school.
- Girls bombarded him with chocolates…
- I'd never get attached to him.
There's just no way I would.
Wait. Let me see that scene again.
Maybe my dad's prophecy,
or curse, or whatever…
- Hey, Seong-tae.
- Yes?
Is Gyeom still out of reach?
Yes, that's right.
He wanted to see the editing process…
…was the reason
I got left alone yet again.
KO GYEOM
At first, I was worried.
It's your day off. Why don't you rest?
Then came the anger.
And in the end…
Shitty, huh?
Sorry?
I meant your days recently.
No, ma'am.
You don't seem like the type
to be naturally quiet.
Your long face tells me
you're going through something.
I'm sorry.
I had something else on my mind.
You know,
when you're making a movie
like we are now,
you can do more than just forget.
You have the opportunity to gather
all those distracting thoughts
and burn them to ashes.
Work it off.
Work yourself to death,
and make your own movie later.
As for what you've got going on in there,
use it as kindling and burn it away.
Ma'am, we are ready.
Would you like to come and check?
Sure. Let's go.
It became clear what I needed to do.
That day, I decided to work
and just forget about him…
Kim Mubee!
Yes?
…and believe that he'd died
just like everything else.
Fortunately, his blood pressure
and vital signs have stabilized.
But he suffered severe brain damage
from cardiac arrest,
so it may take a great deal of time
for him to gain consciousness.
Everyone said
it was a miracle he survived.
There was a bit of confusion
as there was no CCTV in the area.
But the dashcam footage showed
no other cars nearby.
We'll have to rule it as an accident
caused by the early morning fog and rain.
They said it was lucky
the accident wasn't a lot worse.
And what was it that they said?
If we see no improvements
in the next two weeks,
I recommend you prepare for the worst.
"Prepare for the worst."
So you really do say that.
Why are you here again?
To give Jun a break.
He's super annoyed
with you never leaving his side.
As it turned out,
all those words were nonsense.
If that's true,
try kicking me out yourself.
Because my brother
would never let me go through
this "prepare for the worst" stuff.
Okay, now.
Recovering enough to lead a normal life?
I don't know about that.
Like this.
It'd take at least six months,
maybe even years.
Now lower your bottom lip.
His communication impairments
make it unlikely he'll fully recover.
Want to go pig out on pork cutlet later?
Hello.
Have…
you eaten?
Want to go…
pig out on
pork cutlet later?
Sounds good!
Above all, the patient's willpower
counts the most with rehabilitation.
I simply can't guarantee
how long the recovery will take.
Want to take a break?
There's underwear too.
So change it regularly.
Sir.
About this month's rent--
You've gotta be kidding me.
It's fine. Don't worry about that.
I'll pay you back later.
And you? How are you holding up?
Is it getting too much for you?
Nothing is too much.
I think I was born to be a caregiver.
I've been away for too long.
- I'll get going now.
- Sure.
- See you again.
- Yeah.
Call me if you need anything.
I will.
Hello?
Hello, this is Kang Ji-yun with Film 25.
I reached out to you via e-mail.
Are you free to talk
on the phone right now?
How much are you offering?
Sorry?
Do you mean the writing fee?
We cannot offer you too much, but--
How much per word?
MR. GODAM'S CLEAR-CUT MOVIE REVIEWS
2009, AIMLESS BULLET
WHY HAVEN'T YOU BEEN POSTING?
I'M WAITING FOR YOUR REVIEW
HOPE YOU'RE OKAY
I STILL VISIT YOUR BLOG
TODAY'S MOVIE
Nothing is too much, is it?
Mr. Chairman,
congratulations on your discharge.
You're at it again.
I took care of the Hongsi Gang.
They won't mess with us again.
Let me escort you to the pork cutlet place
with your reservation, sir.
All right.
- Let's go, Executive Director Ko.
- Yes, sir.
There are moments like these in movies.
Hey, have you ever seen this go so fast?
Don't make me laugh.
Can't you see me working out?
Jun, are you okay?
- Want some water?
- Yes.
Okay.
Get up first. Oh no.
Here.
It's that kid again.
Hey, what are you doing over there?
- Get to work, will you?
- Yes, sir.
Jun!
- Jun, come here.
- Okay.
Oh man.
Sorry.
One, two…
Slowly.
Times like these usually fly by
as short shots in a montage sequence.
And this phase of my life
seemed to fly by just like that…
though quite some time has passed.
FIVE YEARS LATER
Even so, this isn't right.
We'll move on to the next question.
The person in one of the back rows,
second from the left.
Could you please stand up?
I enjoyed your movie, Ms. Kim.
To barge back into my life like this…
But I have one question.
That's just absurd, isn't it?
Here already?
Why are you in my studio?
Just be grateful I'm here for you.
I have to go back out. What's up?
Is something going on? Where's Jun?
At the rehab center.
By himself? That's progress.
Hey, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Were you at the movies?
I gotta go.
Turn the lights off when you leave.
All I wanted was to check it out.
"What kind of movie could she have made?"
- A lot happened last year.
- I was curious.
And the principal's health
dwindled after that.
DIRECTED BY KIM MUBEE
Did you enjoy the movie?
Allow me to invite the main cast
and the director to the stage.
Please welcome them
with a round of applause.
But…
I really didn't mean to do that.
But I have one question.
Is this really a melo, a romance movie?
I know that hybrid genre movies
have become more mainstream lately.
But the narrative leading toward
a fatalistic view of the world
felt rather gloomy to me.
If this is a movie about love,
why did you choose to go
with this type of narrative?
Yes.
I was asking about your reasoning.
"Yes" doesn't sound like--
Yes, I have my reasons.
I'm afraid our time is up for today,
so we'll move on to the next program.
Finally, let's hear from the main cast
and the director themselves.
Hello, I'm U-Ju,
and I play one of the main cast.
- Hi, I'm a huge fan!
- Hello!
- I'm a fan.
- You were great.
Drink after work?
Han-sol.
Yes?
Where can I watch
the recording of today's session?
I'll send you the link.
Okay.
Do you know about the origin
of Jack Daniel's?
Let me explain it to you.
It's a full house tonight. Where were you?
You told me to take out the trash.
Take orders from table two, will you?
The story of Jack Daniel's goes back
to the time when slaves from West Africa…
Come on in!
He should be cleaning the tables
as soon as the customers leave,
but he just sits around instead.
Listen.
I'm going to quit
if you don't hire another part-timer.
All right, punk. I've been looking.
But the hiring market is tough these days.
I can't seem to find anyone.
Find one within the month, or I'll walk.
Fine, do as you wish.
You've been singing "I'm gonna quit"
for five years, you punk.
Good grief.
Who would've known
my business would take off in five years?
I know.
Why did it have to become so crowded?
Back then, my dear Ju-a said,
"Sang-sik, retro is the way to go.
You should redo the whole store…"
What I'm saying is that I had no idea
that these outdated VHS tapes
would help my business so much.
- You're not in touch with her, are you?
- Of course not, kid.
Me? In touch? With Ju-a?
No way!
Don't you dare.
Boy, you're being so immature.
Listen, man.
I am a man of loyalty and sincerity.
I have no idea how Ju-a is doing!
My back hurts.
Did I work too hard today?
Damn it.
Gyeom!
This late?
Come on!
Gyeom!
Hey.
- Have you lost your mind?
- Come with me.
What? Hey!
Hurry up, man!
People will think we're delinquents
sitting here like this.
Damn you, jerk!
Hey, have you lost it?
You knew about this.
You left it there on purpose, right?
Oh, you saw that?
That was quicker than I expected.
I thought it'd take you a week.
Are you a lunatic?
When was this even published?
This week.
I bought it as soon as it came out.
Since when did Ju-a start
writing scripts for…
Forget it.
- Did you see it?
- See what?
The movie she wrote.
I watched it as soon as it came out.
You crazy bastard!
Why would you go watch that?
Why not?
Hey, there's no reason for me not to.
Plus, Ju-a wrote it.
All the more reason to watch.
Are you serious?
- Want to hear about it?
- Get lost, you punk.
What are you so mad about?
Just be like,
"Oh well, she must have worked hard."
How can you be okay?
- What do you mean?
- For me…
Let's say she called it quits
because she hated my guts.
She was friends with you for ten years.
But she didn't visit once
after Jun's accident.
That's unacceptable. So how could you
watch her movie like it's no big deal?
God! You're such a pushover.
You know
that I get curious as hell
when it comes to movies.
I couldn't help myself.
But
I ended up watching another movie
out of my stupid curiosity.
- What you did…
- I know.
That was a dick move.
Was I that bad?
Why did you do it?
No idea.
My mouth moved faster than I could think.
What can you do?
It was messed up from the start.
You'll never see her again anyway.
Is this really a melo, a romance movie?
I know that hybrid genre movies
have become more mainstream…
Congratulations, Ms. Kim!
Hey, you're overdoing it again.
No, I mean it. Our box office numbers
are much higher than expected.
Yeah?
There you go again,
pretending you don't know.
Thanks.
Have you read the reviews?
Do I have to read them?
A lot of directors can't wait
to read their reviews.
You should look them up.
They're really good!
Cheers!
That burns!
We'll be doing a few more Q&A sessions.
Is that okay with you?
Well…
Do you remember the last question
we had in our last discussion?
The last…
Oh, the guy who talked about the narrative
and how it's gloomy?
How odd. There's always one.
Ignore what he said.
I mean, the question wasn't so bad.
Everyone had to sign up
to be there, right?
Yes, some of them signed up
and won a spot.
Some were invited. Why do you ask?
No reason.
Why, thank you! Cheers!
Cheers.
Good morning, Ms. Kim!
Get something for that hangover.
Oh, don't worry
about what you said last night.
Leave it to me.
What is she talking about?
Whatever.
That's all. Thank you!
You can go now.
RETURNING HOME IN GLORY
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR PARK SEONG-TAE
Darn it.
Seong-tae. I'm busy right now.
I have to check something. Hang up.
You're reading the reviews again,
aren't you?
I'm telling you.
This time, it was received very well.
Hey, man!
Why do you keep stopping me?
That's even more suspicious.
Just tell me.
It's bad, isn't it?
No, it's… it's good, really.
Hang up.
It's true.
RETURNING HOME IN GLORY?
THE RISE AND FALL OF DIRECTOR MA SEONG-U
THE TRUTH ABOUT THIS MOVIE?
IT MADE ME UNCOMFORTABLE
Damn these critics. How ridiculous.
Hello.
Director Ma!
You shoe thief!
You okay there?
There, my bad!
You come and go as you please, don't you?
After all that movie-watching,
you must think you're the main character.
That's some way to tell me
that you missed me.
You were such a pest, but you took off
as soon as filming wrapped.
Keep that up in this industry,
and your career will end for good.
Did something happen?
Just some things.
Spare me the complicated details.
Do you make a living for yourself?
To be honest, I gave you roles
because I'm a generous guy, you punk.
You should be grateful.
But I still had quite a screen presence.
I'd say I was a scene stealer.
Stop stealing scenes.
My movie flopped
because you stole everything.
Wait a minute. It was your fault.
Come on. Don't say it flopped.
I liked your new movie.
You saw it?
How was it? Was it okay?
I liked it.
I knew it!
The audience thought it was good.
What's wrong with those clueless critics?
They don't know what they're saying!
Get up.
- What, me?
- Yeah.
We can't say goodbye like this.
Come along.
Isn't it nice to be called "Director"?
Hardly.
Why didn't you warn me
that it was the busiest job on set?
I'm running around more now
than when I was a rookie.
That means you're doing it right.
Anyway, your retrospective is coming up.
Doesn't that sound like
something you'd do for a dead person?
It doesn't feel right. I don't want to go.
It's your own retrospective.
You, of all people, should be there.
Is that so?
What about you?
Have you found peace
now that you've made a movie?
I don't know.
I'm not sure yet.
You're back.
Ko Gyeom? How long has it been?
- What?
- Look who showed up!
Gyeom!
You all haven't ditched Mr. Ma yet?
What have you been up to?
Hey, get back to work now. Back to work!
- You. Come this way.
- Okay.
Hey, sit over here.
Sure.
Sir, you're a little too fond of Gyeom.
It's the other way around.
Let's talk about movies for once.
Seong-tae is way too boring.
Yet I still haven't ditched you, sir.
Wow, I'm thankful to death.
What's this?
- Director Chu's retrospective?
- Yeah.
She's not the type
to do something like this.
I wonder what's gotten into her.
It's at someplace really far too.
Her movies are all so great.
Please say all my movies are great too!
Your movies?
A few of them are great.
- I hate this punk.
- I agree.
Oh, right. You know her, don't you?
She used to work with us. Kim Mubee.
She joined Director Chu's team
and made her debut recently.
Weren't you two close back then?
Am I mistaken?
Director?
Gyeom hasn't been here in a while.
- Can we have dinner tonight?
- Shall we?
I'm sorry.
I have to be home early today.
Gyeom.
Yeah. What? Do you want water?
What have you been doing lately,
other than working and looking after me?
Well, I've been doing pretty well.
Watching movies and meeting people.
Have you?
Are you worried about me?
I'm faring well, old man.
It's just
we used to talk so much
when we watched movies.
Yeah, it was more like a chat session
than a movie night.
It was really fun hearing you talk about
just about anything, you know.
Remember? You even told me
you had a crush on someone once.
Why are you suddenly bringing that up?
I was young back then.
I did all the talking
while you just listened.
But now, for some reason, it seems like…
you're doing all you can…
not to enjoy your life.
You're wrong.
It's just that I've now matured
into a calm, decent grown-up, okay?
The thing that has bothered me the most
about Ko Gyeom's return…
is that all my efforts
to believe that he was dead
had gone to waste.
Once again, I was looking for an answer…
to the question
I'd asked myself over and over.
MELODY
Why did he disappear like that?
Mom.
Yes?
Don't you miss Dad?
I mean,
what if Dad hadn't died?
What if he'd gone on a trip instead?
What's all this nonsense in the morning?
Come and sit. Let's eat.
How would you feel if he came back?
It's just a thought that came to me
while reading a script last night.
I'd like that to happen.
It seems the house
across the street was sold.
That place?
Who would move in there?
It's been empty for ages.
It must be run down.
I know.
Eat your spinach.
It's like we're going on a trip, right?
I told you to go alone.
Why are you taking me?
This is someone
who made a mark on Korean filmmaking.
You can't miss it because it's too far.
Keep that up in this industry,
and your career will end for good.
Look at you.
I haven't been
in a beat-up car like this in a while.
Classy, isn't it?
Who cares
as long as it gets you to places?
Speed bump!
Hey, you're trying to kill me here.
Sir, let me show you something cool.
I have my reasons for buying this car.
Show me what?
Go!
DIRECTOR CHU HUI-YEONG'S RETROSPECTIVE
NEVERTHELESS, CONTINUE,
AND JUST MOVE FORWARD
Congratulations!
Are you working on your next movie?
Well, I never stop preparing
to make movies.
But we will have to see.
Were there any actors
you wanted to work with?
I wouldn't say that.
That is something I'll need to think about
once the script is complete.
There are so many good actors
in Korea right now…
I know I sound crazy.
But that day,
Ko Gyeom looked like someone
who was returning home from his trip.
I thought I saw a sense of relief
and inexplicable exhaustion in him.
Ms. Kim, here you are. I was calling you.
Even better.
I thought I'd tell you in person.
- It's about what you told me last time.
- Sorry? What do you mean?
When we had drinks the other day,
you asked me to find someone.
By that, you mean…
That person at the Q&A
who asked you a rude question.
Oh, no. It's okay now.
You said he was a total fraud.
I've been watching that clip nonstop
to find out his seat number.
It turns out
that he was one of our invitees.
You didn't have to. It's okay.
It's not okay.
Do you know what's even crazier?
That person was--
Hey, Gyeom!
What are you doing? Come this way.
Well, he was a movie critic… What?
- This jerk! It's him!
- No, it's not.
- No, you have the wrong guy.
- It's him!
- He doesn't look like him.
- Wait. That's the guy.
No, you're wrong.
- I'm telling you.
- No.
- That's not him.
- But…
- No.
- Oh, I get it now.
Did he give you a bad review?
No, it's not that.
Unbelievable.
That's what critics are like.
They only say bad things about movies.
Yes, I guess so.
Ms. Kim.
Directors and critics are enemies, okay?
Oh my. It's almost time.
We have to go!
Goodness, look at the time!
Director Kim.
Congratulations on making your debut.
Where are you?
Everyone is saying hello here.
Party's up next!
Something came up,
so I have to go back early.
I'm really sorry. Bye now.
This is just the worst.
Oh God!
How did you disappear like that?
How are you so fast?
Did you follow me?
You dropped your car key and ran off.
I thought you wanted me to follow you.
Give me that.
What are you…
Be my designated driver just this once?
Since when were you a movie critic?
Since I started getting paid
for writing reviews?
Did you review my movie too?
- Not yet.
- Are you going to?
- That's up to me.
- Why did you even come to see it?
- I was curious.
- Curious about what?
I wanted to see
what kind of movie you had made.
You were curious about me.
That's why you looked me up.
Who, me? No, I didn't.
I heard her calling me a fraud.
Apparently,
directors and critics
are supposed to be enemies.
You've changed a lot.
Though, even back then,
I didn't think you were the quiet type.
Were you ill?
No.
Then, did someone die?
Did you commit a crime and get locked up?
- That's not it either.
- Then what?
You must've thought I was that easy.
Don't show up in front of me ever again.
Hey, Mom.
Hey.
Looks like some major renovations.
How long has it been?
I heard they're flattening the floor
for someone in a wheelchair.
Is that so?
Excuse me.
I live right across the street.
Excuse me!
What are you doing here?
I'm fixing my house.
Wait, what are you doing here?
You're my neighbor?
Are you crazy?
What? Wait a minute.
You're making it sound like
I followed you all the way here.
Then what? Are you saying
this is all a coincidence?
Gyeom, how about jjajangmyeon for lunch?
Jun, hold on.
My brother picked this house, you know.
I don't like what you're implying.
But how can this…
Well, I guess it can't be helped.
Keep your enemies closer, right?
What?
You said we were enemies.
Let's try to get along
like the enemies that we are.
MELO MOVIE
THREE YEARS AGO
Please check the insurance settlement
and sign here.
I'm afraid you aren't insured
to have a caregiver.
No, it's okay. We won't need one.
I'll care for him myself.
Will you?
One moment, please.
Have some corn.
I don't want any.
What's gotten into her? She loves corn.
I need to get off!
HAWON SEOGANG HOSPITAL
Hello?
- Are you a member of Mr. Ko Jun's family?
- Yes.
This is the hospital.
We need you to come immediately.
KO GYEOM
BLOCK CALLER
BLOCK CONTACT
MUBEE
The number you have dialed
is not available.
Please try again later.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon