Jun!
Jun…
I forgot I had a therapy session today.
See you later.
Oh, what…
Damn.
Here's what I've been thinking
ever since I was a kid.
Life seems to have
a fixed amount of happiness.
That's not so bad.
What?
Come on.
Yeah, whatever.
Who cares
as long as it gets you to places?
In other words,
there is also a set amount of misfortune.
What? What's going on?
This can't be happening!
No. Come on now.
WAXY CORN
STEAMED CORN FOR SALE
It's simple.
If someone suffers a string of hardships,
they should believe
that good things will soon come.
Good for me. I was hungry anyway.
I get to eat corn and rest.
Hey, where on earth
did you find this ancient car?
It's going to keep stalling.
You should get rid of this car
and get a new one.
It's still going strong.
Can you take a look at the wipers too?
They keep popping up randomly.
I'd appreciate it if you could fix it.
What's that now?
WARNING: FALLING ROCKS
ROAD CLOSED
DETOUR THROUGH ROUTE 101
All right. I haven't been
working out enough lately anyway.
It's like a kind of auto-suggestion,
and it's actually pretty effective.
CHEONHYE MEMORIAL PARK
If I hadn't thought that way,
I probably wouldn't have been able
to tough it out.
I came alone again.
Did you have a fight with Jun?
I guess he doesn't want to see you anymore
because you put him through so much.
When my life hit rock bottom…
I would've easily given up
if it hadn't been for that.
I should go.
I might stop coming too.
Honestly, I don't remember much anymore.
I've got nothing to say.
Jun and I will be fine.
Don't worry about us.
That's why I simply chose
to believe what I did.
It's about time
something good came my way.
What the…
So this is how it's gonna be today.
Good grief.
What? Why isn't this working again?
Oh God.
Are these…
What is wrong with this?
How…
What are you doing here?
Does something need fixing?
To suffer a string of hardships…
Hold this.
- You--
- Why did it…
…is a sign that only happiness is to come.
You fixed it.
Yeah, I guess.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT
What is your goal, Mr. Ko?
You know, such as fame
or making a lot of money.
Recently, your features have been
the most well-received in our magazine.
Your writing has
a rather cynical approach.
It reads easily,
yet it's sharp and impactful.
How would you like
to become a famous critic?
Famous critic?
Is that an actual job title?
I can make it happen for you.
You can be our magazine's main critic.
It's about time we had a fresh face.
I thought a critic's job
was to just write reviews.
We can take it up a notch
by putting you out in the media.
That means presenting yourself on TV,
YouTube, and radio shows
as the hottest movie critic
on the scene right now.
Not as Godam the blogger,
but as Ko Gyeom the movie critic.
But I like the way it is now.
More people will read your writing
and trust your opinion more.
Your influence will grow just as much.
And it goes without saying
that your fee will increase significantly.
By how much?
A lot.
A lot…
This is a great opportunity for you.
For now, keep up the good work.
But I'm open to something more provoking.
What are you reviewing next?
I'm planning to watch
Director Koo Yeong-sik's new movie.
A BUDDING DIRECTOR
IN PURSUIT OF UNIVERSALITY
His writing is not too shabby.
No, it was me.
I gave him great answers to work with.
I knew it.
He's reviewing every movie but mine.
You think you're all that, huh?
It really wasn't about me.
TWO SEASONS
Am I here too early?
Maybe he's still sleeping.
That startled me!
Why was he even out this early?
Who are you?
Am I at the wrong place?
I must be at the wrong place.
Bye.
Who was that?
No idea. Must've got the wrong address.
- When did you get here?
- Just now.
Where have you been all morning?
I fell asleep waiting for you.
I just thought I'd catch a movie.
I've never seen you do that.
Having trouble writing songs?
I love your latest song.
Can I sing it?
Hey.
Don't try so hard to help me out.
I never thought
I'd see your confidence get so low.
I liked you better when you were cocky.
Get up. Let me try recording it.
Aren't you a successful nerd?
A nerd who's plummeting.
Enough browsing. Let's play some games.
- Can I borrow a few of these books?
- Sure.
Or you can just read them here
and spend the night.
Hell no.
Sir, do you have a daughter?
Why, do I look like
I have no family of my own?
Well, you never talked about your family,
so I thought
you were a successful nerd
who lived alone.
That's also true.
Do you live apart?
Who'd want to live with me
when I'm always out making movies?
Pitiful, isn't it?
Hard to seem pitiful when you're sitting
in a very expensive massage chair.
These are all worthless things.
You better navigate your life wisely.
By the way, why aren't you
posting anything on your blog?
I enjoyed your older posts more.
Pros only write when they get paid.
You call this a pro review?
Your recent reviews are right on the edge.
Aren't you being too harsh?
I'm only harsh on the bad movies,
not the good ones.
Having to coexist already makes critics
and directors mortal enemies.
Don't make those enemies hate you more.
It'll only get tiring.
We're just doing our jobs.
There's no reason to take it personally.
Hey, it isn't always that simple
when you're dealing with people.
Huh? What do you have there?
My brother loves all of these.
How am I ever gonna get them home?
Things would be much easier
if I could replace one person here.
You're trying to kick me out
of my own home now, aren't you?
Sir, can I bring my brother next time?
Whatever. Suit yourself.
You sound like a darn kid
when you talk about him.
Okay. I'll hang out with you
for just two hours.
Oh yeah!
- Get up.
- Oh yeah!
All right.
Hey, close the blinds.
MR. GODAM'S CLEAR-CUT MOVIE REVIEWS
His writing becomes more smug by the day.
Okay.
Ms. Son Ju-a is on her way.
Oh, show her to the meeting room
when she arrives.
Okay.
And you were invited to a preview today.
I don't think I can make it today.
Whose movie is it?
Director Koo Yeong-sik's.
Is it?
I'll do the movie.
Are you sure you can do it?
I wouldn't say that,
but it's worth a shot.
That's all?
It reminds me of La La Land
and even Begin Again.
A Star Is Born also comes to mind.
So it's a mix of everything?
But it's also an original story,
and that's what's important.
A universal yet unfamiliar story.
Stories about love
and chasing dreams always sell.
Do you need a more grandiose reason
to make a movie?
I find your overly simplified sentiment
a bit concerning.
As you already know,
this is a story dear to my heart.
I hope you can turn it into a good movie.
Even a dear story can be a flop,
and a neglected story
can be a huge hit in this industry.
I can't promise anything.
Our sentiments really don't mesh well.
You know the music is everything, right?
I do.
May I make recommendations?
You can, but I will be the one to decide.
Fine.
How is it so difficult for this family
to eat a meal together on a weekend?
Everyone is busy, that's all.
Are things at the hospital busy?
It's always the same for me.
How about you?
He's been busy lately
with the clinical tests.
- Which stage is it this time?
- The third.
It's nearly done, then.
Take this.
Put it away. I don't need it.
Si-jun.
Mom and Dad have been waiting long enough.
Come home now.
- I'll take care of myself.
- You obviously can't.
You said that music was just a hobby.
Why did you quit everything
just to live like this?
You must think
you're making the most of your twenties.
Giving everything up for music
seems like an ego trip.
But you didn't give up anything.
- What?
- Tell me one thing you gave up.
Mom pays the rent for your studio.
You get pocket money
for reluctantly eating with us.
You're just doing whatever you want
'cause you have a safe haven to return to.
You should have
something to show for all you've done.
If you haven't made it by now…
Si-jun, how much longer
do you expect us to wait in blind faith?
Hey.
What faith are you talking about?
What?
Has anyone ever
even believed in me just once?
It really is you!
What are you doing?
I don't think this is my seat.
Sit down. They're about to start.
Thank you all for coming to this preview.
I'm Yu Yong-hyeon, and I'll be…
It's our second time
watching a movie together.
…Director Koo Yeong-sik and the cast
will come out to meet the audience.
Hello. I am Koo Yeong-sik,
the director of this movie.
This movie is…
Well, it's neither difficult nor profound.
My movies are known to be rather…
Thank you.
Do you want to have dinner?
I've cut you some slack lately,
but you can't continue acting like this.
What's wrong with family
grabbing a bite together?
What family?
Neighbors are like family!
Stop talking nonsense
and keep your distance.
Do you understand?
Oh, come on!
Well, he accepted that awfully quickly.
What's wrong?
Is something up?
You don't have to tell me.
Sang-sik,
how many years have I been working here?
Let's see.
Wow, six years already…
Are you reminding me that it's time
for another salary negotiation?
Hey, I gave you a massive raise last time!
Are you serious?
It was meant to be a temporary job.
Has it been that long?
So… are you going through
a rough patch right now?
I just think…
I'm a bit pathetic.
Come on, don't call yourself pathetic.
Did you think
it'd be easy to be an artist?
I'll take the trash out for you today.
The way I see it,
you're doing perfectly fine.
- Attaboy.
- Hey, what the hell?
- Stop it.
- Look at you.
That long face doesn't suit you.
Hey, let's have a drink on the rocks.
Okay?
- Sure.
- Get the drinks ready.
Listen, Hongsi.
Blind date.
I forgot that I had a blind date!
What?
You can wrap it up and go home.
I'm leaving first.
I thought we were having a drink.
You can drink whatever you want.
Just lock the door before you do.
Bye now.
Seriously, what's your problem?
Blind date, my foot.
Why are you in such a rush?
What do you want now…
Want to have a drink with me?
You don't want to have a drink with me?
No, I don't want to ruin a good drink.
I told you to stop acting
like you know me. Why are you here?
Last time, it was all so sudden,
so we didn't have
a proper chance to talk--
Just cut to the chase.
Do you want to get back together?
Or do you want to just be friends?
Hong Si-jun.
I don't want either option.
Is that clear?
Now go.
You're unaffected as ever.
It's annoying as hell.
Five years ago, I screamed, cried,
and begged you to take me back
or at least remain friends.
You were really something then.
You still are.
- You weren't the only one who suffered.
- Right, I'm sure.
But what's the point of all this now?
I feel nothing when I see you.
What if that's not why I'm here?
I'm not here to get back with you
or to be your friend.
What?
I wrote about us.
You wrote what?
As you said, I got desperate
and used anything I could as inspiration,
so I wrote about us.
I want to make it into a movie,
but I need you.
You know better than anyone that
I believed in you for those seven years.
I loved your music more than anyone,
and I need it now.
I really need your music.
Did you get to the hospital okay today?
Yeah, I sure did.
I may have overexerted myself.
My shoulders are feeling a bit stiff.
Are they now? I thought the appointment
was yesterday, not today.
Yes, that's right. I was there yesterday.
I guess I'm still in pain from yesterday.
It was today.
Jun… I got a call from the hospital today.
They said you haven't been coming lately,
which is odd
since you said you were there
the day I went to see Mom and Dad.
Well, the thing is,
I was feeling a bit restless,
so I went for a walk around the block--
Do you think you're all better now?
You've been struggling to walk recently.
Why do you keep skipping your sessions?
I'm much better now. You know that.
When you've gotten this much better,
it's enough to just
move around the house a little and--
Are you a doctor now?
Who said you could call the shots?
Look, the medical bills are so expensive.
I don't care. Just keep going.
Why would you care about that?
I've been asked to appear on many shows,
so my pay has gone up tremendously.
Expensive, my foot.
I can pay double, even triple that,
so just don't skip it.
Okay. All right.
Did you just raise your voice at me
because you're the breadwinner now?
That makes me sad.
When I got the call, I thought,
"So this is what
parent-teacher conferences must be like."
Don't you dare skip it again.
I heard you.
I have high hopes
for the Korean movie industry.
In particular, Kim Yeo-jin's new movie…
What's this?
- I really enjoyed it.
- What's he doing?
That was a positive outlook…
How ridiculous.
What, is he a celebrity now?
Why on earth is he on TV?
That guy looks familiar.
Doesn't he live across the street?
Is he famous?
Not even close.
Anyone can be invited to those shows.
Do you want me to be on it too?
He's eloquent.
You can't talk like he does.
Excuse me?
What are you talking about?
I can do much better than him!
But I think
that's part of my job as a critic.
What's he saying?
Instead of cutting
these new directors some slack,
we must share the hard truth
and keep them on their toes
so they can produce better movies…
- Hello.
What's this?
Oh, hey.
I'm looking through the list to see
if this critic recommended your movie.
So? Is it on the list?
No, it's not.
I wouldn't waste my time on a list
that's not even credible.
But he's quite popular
with the younger audience.
Is that so?
LIVE: AN INTERVIEW
WITH RISING MOVIE CRITIC, KO GYEOM
Why is he suddenly everywhere?
We Must Love Each Other.
It's the new movie by Director Lee Ru-ri.
If I were to describe this movie
in one word,
it'd be "easy."
That's my boy! He's good with words.
He's literally popping up everywhere.
What is happening?
He was always an attention seeker.
But you know what?
He earns his keep, unlike some…
People ask me if I've been single
since birth because I write harsh reviews.
I have not.
It hurts me more
that you're walking on eggshells.
Walking on eggshells? Me?
Yeah, right. That's absurd.
I can see right through you,
just like last time when you pushed
Ju-a into the bar and left.
What? I pushed Ju-a in here and left?
No way.
Anyway, what did you two
talk about that night?
She wanted to work with me.
Work? What kind of work?
She asked me to write the music
for her screenplay.
That girl really is something.
Goodness, that's cold. Cold as ice.
Am I really that pathetic?
Is that why she's offering me a handout?
You're taking it to the extreme again.
You have a tendency
to look at things way too negatively.
It's possible… that she's sincerely
interested in working with you.
Who knows? She may have thought
long and hard about this.
Never mind.
I haven't the slightest intention
of getting in between you two.
What am I gonna do with you, pretty boy?
You and that attitude of yours.
You two are…
Nope, I'll say no more.
Just clean those glasses.
Let's get ready to open.
Oh my gosh!
Can I come in?
Sure.
So what did your ex-boyfriend say?
Did he say yes?
He looked at me
like I was insane and then left.
Figures. I would've done the same.
I should've said something nicer.
How am I going to persuade him?
Does it have to be his music?
I wrote it while thinking of him.
But it's no use if I don't like his music.
You will definitely like it.
You seem very confident.
It's just not his time yet.
I'm sure he'll become a greater songwriter
than anyone can imagine.
Does he know
you have that much faith in him?
That's the problem.
People never communicate these days.
Are you sure
you don't still have feelings for him?
That would complicate things at work.
I have zero feelings.
I think I can say the same for him.
He seemed to have a girlfriend.
That's good to hear.
Did you get rid of that guy
who was getting on your nerves?
Get rid of him? No.
He's becoming more clingy, so I've been…
I told you about that?
What now?
We shared quite a lot of stuff, you know.
Civil Servant Kim.
I must've said all kinds of things
to get free Pilates lessons.
So? Tell me.
Not tonight.
Tell me! I'll give you Pilates lessons.
How? You aren't even a Pilates instructor.
I can teach you.
You don't want me to teach you?
Well, I mean…
Do you want them or not?
He's the talk of the town right now.
Please welcome movie critic Ko Gyeom.
Hello, I'm Ko Gyeom.
Your writing is getting
a lot of attention.
You criticized Koo Yeong-sik's movie
in a daring and brutal way.
Can you bear the consequences?
I stand behind everything that I write.
What disappointed you most
about the movie?
Sir, can you raise the volume a bit?
Sure.
It doesn't really matter to me
whether a movie has a happy or sad ending.
But it's rather irresponsible
to render the ending unimpressive
and simply turn it into a tool
to teach the audience a lesson.
That was truly a cutting remark.
I can see why they call you
"the people's critic…"
MOVIE CRITIC KO GYEOM
…and why the public
is so interested in you.
I just think it's a critic's duty
to share accurate reviews with the public.
I do share critical views of movies,
but it's also my job to introduce
well-made movies that don't get noticed
just because
they aren't considered entertaining.
It's a double-edged sword,
but critics need to exist
for those who make movies because…
This is dangerous.
I told you, didn't I?
It took no time for you to become famous.
Well, I don't really care about that.
Will I get more commissioned work now?
You should attend more public events
while people are interested.
You're quite eloquent too.
You have more star quality than I thought.
Let's keep up the good work.
Sure.
Now, I'll take my star quality
and make my exit.
How did you get so busy?
I'm seeing you everywhere.
It's such an eyesore.
I hate it, but I force myself out there
because they are begging me.
As if. You're reveling in the attention.
Hey, they pay me a lot.
I can deal with the unwanted attention.
Sure, go ahead.
Make a lot of money, my friend.
You're looking awfully down lately.
Are you having trouble writing music?
It's just…
I always knew I was pathetic,
but I feel more pathetic than ever.
Hey, you knew that?
Ju-a suddenly started writing scripts,
and now she's made one into a movie.
You used to lurk around sets all the time,
and now you're earning your keep.
But what about me?
What am I even doing?
Should I just quit?
When I started making music, I thought
that I'd know if I had what it takes
and when to give up without being told.
But… I think that ship has sailed.
Now I'm just a fool who runs his mouth
without realizing he'll never make it.
How fucking embarrassing.
Hey, are you crying?
Thank God.
It almost got really awkward just now.
Cut the shit and just drink.
You said it.
You should cut the shit
and keep doing your thing.
You know, everyone gets their big break.
And you've always been the best among us.
I won't deny that.
Cheers.
FILM 25
How could this happen?
Oh my. Is he all right?
I don't know.
What if we take the heat for this?
Tell me about it!
What a way to start the day.
DIRECTOR KOO YEONG-SIK RESCUED BY FAMILY
AFTER SLEEPING PILL OVERDOSE
KOO YEONG-SIK RUSHED TO ER
AFTER SUICIDE ATTEMPT AT HOME
Excuse me.
Is Director Koo Yeong-sik all right?
I guess. He had his stomach pumped.
He's been hospitalized.
Where can I go to visit him?
Are you an acquaintance?
Wait a minute.
It's that critic!
Ko Gyeom?
It's him!
- It is!
- Why are you here?
- Don't you feel any remorse?
- Tell us how you feel right now.
- Are you here to apologize?
- Do you intend to?
- Please say something.
- A word, please!
- Do you feel any regret?
- Please share how you feel.
Do you think your review caused this?
- Do you feel bad for him?
- Please say something.
Please don't do this here.
My father needs rest right now,
so please leave.
Please go.
You'll only cause a bigger scene.
Okay.
What?
- Is he really leaving?
- What? Mr. Ko, one moment!
- Wait!
- Mr. Ko!
FINE LINE BETWEEN CRITIQUING AND ARROGANCE
ARE CRITICS ALWAYS RIGHT?
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN
DISSING IS NOT THE SAME AS CRITIQUING
THIS IS WHY YOU NEED TO BE HUMBLE
I ALWAYS HATED HIM
ARTISTIC FREEDOM? RIDICULOUS
ARE CRITICS ALLOWED TO TRASH-TALK?
Here.
I'm fine.
Why did you go there
and add fuel to the fire?
You should've laid low.
I don't know.
I didn't really think about it much.
Exactly. I told you to play it safe
because critics are easy targets.
But hey, Director Koo will be fine.
Don't worry too much.
I'm sure you've realized now.
People don't care
when you write good things about movies.
But the moment you call a movie a flop,
they come flocking in.
Then they hide behind critics like you
so they can talk crap about movies.
When something like this happens,
they turn a blind eye
and beat the hell out of the scapegoat.
So don't be too concerned about it.
- I said I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
Don't bother reading comments online.
I don't have to. My inbox is already full.
All right, just ignore them. You got it?
- Come on in!
- Director Kim. Over here!
You called someone?
I made plans with her first.
I only invited you out to cheer you up.
And you know each other anyway.
The more the merrier, right?
Director Kim, have a seat. Want a beer?
A bottle of beer, please!
Which beer?
Just anything that doesn't sell well.
Here.
Based on what they write about me,
you'd think I betrayed my country.
- What's wrong with people?
- Director Ma!
Park Jun-tae! You're still alive.
- It's been a while.
- Yes.
Where have you been lately?
Well, I screwed up my movie,
so I had to lie low.
Hey, don't say it like that.
Why don't you have a drink with us?
No, I have company. Maybe next time.
Really? Okay.
Did you quit smoking?
Let's go for a smoke.
- Shall we? Let's go.
- Yeah.
Let's go.
- Have you had a lot to drink?
- Boy, I sure have.
Are you all right?
What do you mean?
I mean, you've been grilling that
all by yourself.
Should I do it?
It's okay. I'm an expert at this.
- Well--
- It's you, right? The critic.
It is you. I'm Kim Yong-u.
Do you remember me?
You left a review for my movie.
You directed Balcony.
You do remember!
- Of course I do.
- You do?
Would you like a drink?
Would I like a drink?
Thanks to you, I'm not in the mood.
You're a funny guy.
Unbelievable.
You made me out to be a freaking idiot,
and now you offer me a drink?
Did you find my review uncomfortable?
I got bashed for no reason.
What do you think?
Hey, you're really something.
I guess you'd have to be this brazen
to be able to put out that kind of drivel.
And…
are you seriously having a drink
after what you've done to Mr. Koo?
If he doesn't survive this,
then his death will be on you.
What are you doing? Get up.
Who are you?
None of your business. Get up. Now.
You didn't have to listen to him.
You must be feeling uneasy about all this.
That was freaking rude of him.
Why would I feel uneasy?
What?
Am I supposed to feel uneasy?
I didn't do anything wrong.
I mean, it's not my fault
the movie flopped.
Not all movies do well.
We're all bound to face some misfortune.
This isn't about the movie.
Someone got hurt.
I know, and I'm saying
that it's not my responsibility.
It's not my fault.
Mr. Ko.
I never said it was your fault.
People who say that
are just looking for someone to blame.
Don't you think the same way?
Have you always been so twisted?
Anything else you'd like to lecture me on?
Ms. Kim.
I want to comfort you, not lecture you.
I'm empathizing, not criticizing.
Didn't you notice
how Mr. Ma and I were trying to be there
for you while watching you closely?
You can pretend
like you're indifferent to your pain,
but don't disregard those around you.
Do you know what made me angry
when I saw you again?
You only cared about your own pain,
just like you do now.
You aren't concerned
about the other person.
Okay.
Let's work together.
Starting now,
I'm betting everything I have on this.
What would that be?
My pride.
The pride that made me refuse to be
bailed out by someone I once loved.
Si-jun.
So I'm going to make it big.
Even bigger than you.
Mom, I'm leaving now.
You should take this.
Okay.
KOO YEONG-SIK
You're Mubee, aren't you?
It's okay. Don't get up.
You still look the same.
And you've grown quite old.
Is that right?
Your mom used to tell me about you.
I was so proud to hear
you became a movie director.
And I loved your movie too.
Hun-dong would've been thrilled
to see this.
So what brings you here?
What happened to you?
Did you really…
It wasn't like that.
The reporters twisted it.
Really?
I haven't been able to sleep
without sleeping pills for a while.
I also have anxiety issues.
That night, I took the pills
after drinking too much and…
I didn't know
things would blow up like this.
This line of work sure takes its toll
physically and mentally.
Are you doing all right?
You have to look after your health.
I've been staying healthy to prove
that I can do this
without burning myself out.
Your dad always bragged about you.
He said you were very smart, unlike him.
If the worst had happened to you,
I would've been left with
only my hatred for movies.
What is it with movies
that make people this way?
Goodness me. I'm ashamed.
You should dust yourself off
and start your next project.
I've loved your movies
ever since I was a kid.
All right. Thank you.
You need to recover,
so I'll leave you to rest.
I would love to rest,
but that kid keeps pestering me.
I tell him that I'm fine,
but he still comes by every day.
What are you doing here?
I'm… just waiting.
For what?
I'm waiting for something good
to happen again.
And it's you again.
Though I hate to admit it…
my weakness is
that I still open up my heart too easily
to pitiful little things.
I'm tired.
Yeah.
Me too.
And I'm afraid that Ko Gyeom
might just be one of those things.
MELO MOVIE
I don't think I'm too happy to know
that Kim Mubee is yet again the luck
that follows my misfortune.
Because then the next time
and the time after that…
Where'd he go?
What was that? He could've woken me up.
I can't believe he just left me there.
You startled me.
What's going on? I thought you left.
And you shouldn't scare people like that.
You looked cold, so I got a blanket.
Were you going to let me sleep out here
and not send me home?
Oh, you're right.
Why didn't I think of that?
I'm leaving now.
You should stop being so miserable here
and go home already.
You're really frustrating.
Mubee.
Who said you could use my first name?
…I hope that will be the case every time.
I…
want to like you again.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon