What kind of movie are you going to make?
An awesome
melo movie.
Melo?
I know that I don't exactly
seem like the romantic type.
Even when I look back on my childhood…
I'm going to school!
I'm home.
How was your day?
What on earth
are you getting into out there?
Hey, come in.
Hello.
Hey there.
We'll play in my room.
Sure.
Come on.
Hey, is Mubee bullying you by any chance?
…romance seemed to have
no place at all in my life.
Let's go.
Hey, watch me.
I can even do a backward roll.
One, two, three.
Kim Mubee!
I was the type of person who'd get bored
sitting at home watching romance movies.
Hey, it was you guys again, huh?
-Run!
-Run away!
Get back here!
CHRISTMAS IN AUGUST
Found you!
Dad, what kind of movie is this?
A melo movie.
What's melo?
Stories about people who love each other.
Love?
That sounds boring.
Why would anyone watch that?
Because watching it makes you feel good.
You need that sometimes.
Like when?
You'll find out when you're older.
Want to watch it together?
Sure.
I didn't know what he meant at the time.
But, well, I think
it was a pretty nice feeling.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Mubee
Maybe that was why…
I picked up the habit of seeking out
all the cliché love stories.
Stanley Kubrick is the best.
The Shining was great,
but I think Dr. Strangelove
was the most groundbreaking.
I say Hitchcock is still the best.
His top seven movies?
I could name them right now.
What about you?
Chungking Express.
No other movies have been able to depict
intense emotions like loneliness
and futility better.
Mubee, what's your favorite?
Love Actually.
No, your all-time favorite,
not the stuff you watch to kill time.
Love Actually.
Hey, Mubee.
We're film majors.
Don't you think we should discuss
something more profound and artistic?
I guess not.
-Let's drink.
-Drink up.
Cheers.
Even so, a slender woman like her
carrying a corpse like it's nothing?
-Isn't that a bit far-fetched?
-Right.
-If we use a cart--
-Here.
If she chopped up the body like this,
she could carry the corpse in pieces.
Using a bone knife or a saw
would help make nice, clean cuts.
She'd be able to do that by herself.
How do you always know this stuff?
What kind of movies do you watch?
You should definitely do
a thriller next time.
But I'm going to make a melo.
Why?
I don't know why.
I heard the news.
You're marrying Eun-gyeong.
ON-SET FILMING VEHICLE
I still don't know what love is.
But I do know there are moments
when you really need it.
Like when someone loses a loved one.
I'm not sure how much time has passed.
The weird thing about death is
that you expect it to change everything…
but… it changes nothing, really.
MOVIE CRITIC KO GYEOM
A SUMMER THAT WENT PAST
WITHOUT HEAT OR STYLE
TO KO GYEOM
No one's life…
including my own,
has changed one bit.
Hey, Gyeom. Wanna grab a drink tonight?
Gyeom, have you eaten yet?
Should I drop some food off later?
Except that people started bothering me
with frequent messages.
What're you up to?
It looked as if Gyeom was naturally
settling back into his life.
Of all the movies I've seen recently,
that was the hardest watch.
The soundtrack was constantly distracting,
and the character placement was very odd.
I better go watch it again.
What do you think?
Me?
I had no idea what…
We walked together every single day.
-Gyeom.
-Yes?
This is really good. Try it just once.
I really can't eat pineapple pizza.
It's really good. Just one bite.
Trust me.
We ate together
whenever we could make time.
We also spent all night
chatting over trivial things.
Oh no!
I told you we had to leave earlier.
We would've made it if we ran.
-I forgot you had such short legs.
-What did you say?
Shall we just walk and sober up?
It's only a 30-minute walk.
No, I don't feel like it.
Let's grab a taxi.
Come on, let's walk.
Come on now.
Let's go. That's it.
-Gyeom, let's just get a taxi.
-Let's just walk.
We were just like
any other ordinary couple.
Except for the sudden…
anxiety that crept in at times.
Hey, Ko Gyeom.
Yes?
Look at me.
What are you doing?
Transmitting.
What?
Didn't you receive it?
Bye now.
TO KO GYEOM
HAVE YOU EATEN?
Making movie soundtracks? You?
Yes.
Can you even make a living
doing that these days?
Well, I am responsible
for the movie's entire soundtrack.
Really? Have you started?
What do you have so far?
Want to hear it?
No, next time.
Why are you here?
Why didn't you tell me about Jun?
I heard it from the hospital thirdhand.
CONDOLENCES
Give this to Gyeom.
That's all?
It's more than enough.
Our parents have a reputation to uphold.
That's not what I meant.
Don't you have any words for him?
That man had been ill for a long time.
He got unlucky
with the sudden complications.
But Gyeom must've been preparing
for the worst. Am I wrong?
What?
Send him to me if he's struggling.
I'll set up a counseling session for him.
What's wrong?
This will be more helpful
than some useless words. See you.
Hey.
This is your first time here, you know.
Fine. Sorry for coming empty-handed.
Get whatever you need with this.
You can't part with your loved one
and just be done with it so easily.
Who said she's done with him?
She's moved on with her life
and back to working hard again
as if she could set her feelings
over the breakup aside.
It shows how you can pretend
to go on with your life
when you're actually dying inside.
But what I'm saying is
that even if that were possible,
those broken parts inside
are bound to crop up now and then again.
Don't you think we need more scenes
where the female lead faces her pain
without her realizing it?
Okay. I get what you mean.
Once we edit that part,
I think we'll be almost done.
I thought you'd rewrite the entire script.
This isn't so bad.
Let's end this meeting on that note.
How's Gyeom doing?
I'm not sure.
He seems to be coping in his own way.
I'm sure you're already doing a great job,
but please look after him.
It seems like you're the only person
he can depend on right now.
Has he ever depended on anyone before?
I don't think so.
He was always so cheerful on his own.
I don't think he ever has.
-When did you get here?
-Do you know what the weirdest thing is?
You?
Have you read my recent review?
It was well-written,
so why is everyone bashing me for it?
It's not a critic's job to write
only good things about movies, is it?
I would if the movie was good.
Just take some time off.
I don't get why you're so diligently
dissing all those directors.
I'm not taking any time off.
I'm going to do all the work I can get.
I can rest
when I stop getting work like you.
Just curse at me.
Know what the second weird thing is?
Yeah. Again, you.
You come to your office every day,
even though you have no work.
I guess my reason is the same as yours.
It's because I don't like being alone,
you punk.
Any news on your next movie?
Sheesh! Goddamn it!
How can I possibly make a movie
when nobody's willing to fund it?
Who would want to invest in a movie
by a washed-up director?
Dear me.
Moping around after one dead project
is not charming at all.
Gyeom.
Yes?
Are you here to comfort me
despite what you're going through?
Such a frustrating kid.
You know,
that's the thing about the pain of a loss.
At first, there's so much going on
that it doesn't hit you.
But when you need that person
so desperately
and you realize
they can't be there with you…
that's when the pain really sets in.
You don't even read.
Why did you buy so many books?
Likewise with death.
No.
It's painful beyond words.
When that pain hits,
you can't do anything about it.
You have to face it.
When that happens…
just don't be alone, okay?
This wasn't what I had in mind.
I came prepared to tease you today.
I'm not appreciating this vibe.
What did you prepare?
-A grand retirement party?
-Hey!
It was only one dead project.
You can't make me retire!
You just wait and see!
I'm not leaving this industry
unless I'm booed off my director's seat.
People in this industry are ridiculous.
They're not getting rid of me.
Wanna play video games?
If you don't start coming here often,
I might stop being nice to you.
Enjoy your food.
What is it? Are you feeling sick?
Indigestion, maybe? My chest feels tight.
Goodness.
Something must be stressing you out again.
My work isn't going so well.
Why are the songs all so depressing?
Are they?
God, that's how I'm feeling lately.
I have no idea how Gyeom is doing.
Hey, Si-jun.
Why don't we close early today
and visit Gyeom at his place?
Hey.
What do you say?
I'm behind on my work,
so I don't think I can.
Is that so?
I guess we can take a rain check.
You must be busy these days.
It's a good thing that you are,
but check in on Gyeom once in a while.
Seriously.
Hello.
Hello there. It's great to have you.
We have two romantic seats back here.
They are for you.
Okay. I'll take the order.
What's wrong with me?
Gyeom seems strange, huh?
I mean, he's constantly pretending
to be okay.
I think he might be suffering all alone
on the inside.
But isn't it always better
to share your struggles with people
than to suffer alone?
I don't know.
He might need more time to himself.
Were you like him?
When your dad passed away.
Knowing your personality,
I bet that you suffered all by yourself.
I just didn't have anyone
to share it with.
Maybe that's how he is right now.
-Mubee.
-Yes?
I'm sorry.
You always kept me safe when I was a kid,
but I wasn't there for you
when things got tough.
I'm so useless.
It's okay.
I'm more worried about you.
Are you sure you're okay now?
You're not sick, are you?
I don't lie about being sick.
It gets really lonely
when you suffer alone.
Aren't you going?
I was going to barge in
when Gyeom came home.
Why is that dude still not home
at this hour?
-He must be working.
-Are you kidding?
Where would a freelancer work
if not at home?
And it's dangerous out there.
He should be home by now.
He's got me worried.
Hey, you seem to care more
about Gyeom than you do me,
and it's getting on my nerves.
Aren't you worried about him?
Have you tried calling him?
Gyeom is a grown-up.
You need to go. Now.
-Go.
-Okay, I'll go.
-I'm leaving.
-Yeah, bye.
Bye.
-See ya.
-Yeah.
We're closed.
You're done for the night, right?
Yes.
Can I take a seat?
I'm not here to pick a fight or anything.
I just…
I was too depressed to be alone.
Have you been busy?
I said we should meet Gyeom,
but you ignored my text.
Have you talked to Gyeom?
I'm sure he opens up to you more.
So? How is he? Is he having a tough time?
There's not much to say anyway.
You haven't talked to him yet?
Don't tell me
you haven't seen him since then.
Si-jun!
I don't even know what to say to him.
What?
Right, the same old Hong Si-jun.
You have no idea
how to express your feelings.
I can't believe I forgot that.
Picking a fight again?
If you don't know what to say,
don't say anything. Just be there for him.
Gyeom has known you long enough.
He knows what you're like.
Stop avoiding him.
At least try to make an effort yourself.
Call or visit him,
and tell him what's on your mind.
What are you doing?
I knew it. Indigestion.
You always get indigestion
when you can't say what you want.
I noticed you massaging
that pressure point for a while.
You seem so chill all the time,
but your body says otherwise.
Not true.
What's wrong with you?
What's so hard about sharing
a simple word of comfort?
It's because…
You know I tend to be rude when I talk.
It's better to keep my mouth shut.
Words don't sound sincere at all…
coming from the likes of me.
Have you seen your family lately?
You aren't like that.
Yes, you can be super rude sometimes,
but I can feel your sincerity.
Whatever.
Isn't this reserved
for one of your customers?
You can drink it.
How come? What if they come back?
They're obviously a couple.
See the bottles
with pairs of names on them?
Not a single person came back for them.
How can you be sure?
They might've been too busy.
For years?
It's been that long?
They were pathetic enough
to write both their names.
Now they can't even come back
after their breakup.
Did they think they'd last forever?
Nobody expects to break up.
And who says all those couples are over?
What if they come back?
Not gonna happen.
Wanna bet?
You never grow up, do you?
How's 100,000 won?
Deal. I'm going to ask Sang-sik and check.
You never know how things will end.
Hey, stop drinking
from Huni and Soni's bottle.
My God.
Do you want to talk about Jun?
I want to talk about him,
but I can't do it with Gyeom.
Sure.
I remember when I first met him.
I couldn't believe such a handsome guy
was standing at the school gates.
It was even more unbelievable
that he was Gyeom's brother.
You're right. They look nothing alike.
That's why I asked Jun so many times
if they were really brothers.
-You asked him that?
-Yeah.
I'm home. What are you up to, Kim Mubee?
Are you in bed already, Kim Mubee?
Movie directors usually stay up late,
you know?
I guess he's sleeping.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was looking for something.
Gyeom.
Yes?
Did you spend the night in your car?
I came home a little late last night.
I saw you getting out of your car
the other morning as well.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen the lights on
in your house lately.
Have you been sleeping
in your car every day?
Why?
Gyeom.
There's…
no one at home.
No one's home, Mubee.
No matter how hard you pretend
to go on with your life…
So I can't go in there.
…the broken parts inside
always seem to crop up again.
Why didn't you say any--
But I'm fine now.
I was going to go inside today.
It's a beat-up car,
so it's uncomfortable to be in.
And the house is a mess,
so I'm going to start cleaning.
Are you?
Yes, so you don't have to worry.
And the anxiety repeatedly creeps in.
All right.
I have to get ready for work.
I'll go in now.
Okay.
Ms. Kim, here are the meeting materials.
She has long, straight hair now,
but after one year,
we would have to change
her hair into something
that doesn't overlap with…
About the wardrobe…
I did go inside, but…
Yes.
Mubee.
Yes?
I think something's wrong with me.
It's okay.
Transmitting.
Did you receive it?
Gyeom.
Yes?
When tomorrow comes…
let's go home together.
Yes.
Sorry.
Hey, wait! What are you doing?
Open the door.
So that's the passcode.
Okay.
But…
What's with that pillow
and all that stuff?
What's going on?
It's like you're moving in.
-That's right.
-What?
I am, for a while.
Are you out of your mind?
Your house is right there.
What will you tell your mother?
She's not that uptight.
She liked it, actually.
You already told her?
Yes, that I'd stay at the office
since I was too busy.
I mean, "office" can mean
quite a lot of things.
So you lied?
Did I?
But habitual lies are a must
in a mother-daughter relationship.
Goodbye now.
Get more comfortable with your home.
By the way, this feels pretty good.
Leaving you here at home
and going to work.
How so?
Can I expect to come home
to your homemade jjigae?
Why?
Think of it as a preview
of your married life with someone. Bye.
What?
What are you talking about?
Married life with who?
I'll be home right after work.
Make sure you're home then.
Ms. Kim,
you're going to have to visit the set.
Today?
Excuse me?
You left a bottle here five years ago?
Yes.
I think we wrote,
"Sang-gyu loves Jeong-yun."
"Sang-gyu loves Jeong…"
It's Jeong-yun.
Right. Ms. Jeong-yun.
-I'll check.
-If you don't have it, it's fine.
I know you. I remember!
My goodness. But it's been too long.
-It's been a while.
-Ta-da!
Sang-gyu and Jeong-yun, right?
Oh my God!
You kept this here all this time?
I'm so touched, really.
-Let's take a picture.
-Yes.
It's been here for so long.
I don't think it's safe to drink it.
-You should throw it out.
-What do you mean?
They've come all the way here to drink it.
So why did it take you five years
to come back for it?
Actually, we were broken up.
Then we got back together.
And we're getting married.
Wow, really?
Congratulations. In that case,
I should treat you two to a drink.
This is one hell of a drink.
Wait a minute.
Is there a thief around here?
I swear there used to be this much.
Is this your bottle?
Yes.
Who are Huni and Soni?
They are my beloved dogs.
Now, let's each take a drink,
although I'm missing some liquor.
Have a drink each.
-So when is your wedding?
-Next spring.
Did you get home safely last…
About that whiskey…
You asleep?
I wrote a new song.
SON JU-A
Gyeom! Ko Gyeom!
Gyeom.
Ko Gyeom!
Gyeom?
Oh my God!
Come on. You startled me.
You startled me more.
Did you just get home?
I mean, what are you doing
with all the lights off?
The electricity and gas got cut off.
I guess I was overdue on the bills.
What?
Should I have lit more candles?
Are you crying?
Were you that surprised?
And to shoo away the sudden anxiety
that creeps in again…
Gyeom.
You're not alone.
…just one moment or a few simple words
will do.
I am in love with you.
So,
we will never be…
alone from now on.
Hongsi, what took you so long?
Should I have just gone to the bar?
Why are you so surprised?
-Why are you here?
-You said you wrote a song.
I want to be the first to hear it.
I'll play it now.
What do you think?
What?
How is it? Is it bad?
I was sure this one was good.
Who else did you share this with?
You're the only one.
Let me be the first to hear your songs.
Why?
I listen to a lot of music,
so I can tell right away
if it's good or not.
So how is it? Tell me.
It's good!
Let me hear it again.
Why are you in such a rush?
Sit down.
Okay, here goes.
-Listen.
-Okay.
Si-jun, you really are the best!
-Was it okay?
-Yes.
That was the best thing
I've heard in my life.
I almost cried listening to it.
-Do you mean it?
-Yes.
Is this why you were in a rush?
Yes, I had to have you hear it first.
What?
Because seeing you smile like that
reassures me.
Come here.
I'm so relieved.
I'm proud of you, Hongsi.
STAR - UPLOAD
J: WOW! IT'S BEEN A WHILE
I'M ALWAYS ROOTING AND WAITING FOR YOU!
J: AGAIN, ANOTHER GREAT SONG!
I HOPE EVERYONE WHO LISTENS TO THIS SONG
HAS A WONDERFUL DAY
J: IT'S SNOWING OUTSIDE!
THIS SONG MAKES THE WINTER WARMER
J: THE KIND OF MUSIC I WOULD HEAR
IN MY CHILDHOOD DREAMS
J: COMFORTING MUSIC, JUST WHAT I NEEDED
J: THE SOUND REMINDS ME OF THE COLD SEA
Let's go inside. I'm curious.
Ju-a.
Yes?
Are we over? Or are we…
on our way back to each other?
MELO MOVIE
That punk. Clean up a little, man.
Damn it!
What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing over there?
You punk. Why do you keep sleeping
in your car and not your freaking house?
Is that why you brought survival supplies?
What is all this?
What? A humidifier?
Isn't this way too extra?
Hey, this one tasted good.
And that blanket gets too staticky.
You knew?
You left me all this stuff.
Of course I knew.
You slept here again?
No, Mubee caught me sleeping in here,
so I went back inside.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Hey, I--
Screw it. Let's just go to the sauna.
Okay, sure.
I don't wanna hear
your annoying little chitchat.
Does my car stink?
Yeah, man, it reeks.
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon