(Red Balloon)
(Seo Ji Hye)
(Lee Sung Jae)
(Hong Soo Hyun)
(Lee Sang Woo)
(Jung Yu Min)
(Yoon Mi Ra, Yoon Joo Sang, Lee Bo Hee, Jung Bo Seog)
(Kim Hye Seon, Choi Dae Chul, Lee Sang Suk, Seol Jung Hwan)
(Red Balloon)
(All characters, organizations, and events...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Final Episode)
Have you been well?
How is your health?
How did you know to come here?
Mr. Lee.
I would call him from time to time if I wanted to know how you were.
I heard you got kicked out.
No.
I left on my own.
I wouldn't get kicked out.
I'm not that easy.
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
It's comfortable and nice.
More than before.
It's true.
You look so pretty.
Totally.
I'm at a loss for words.
Whatever.
I'm a mess. Aren't I?
This is what happens when you live in the countryside.
I have to live like this.
You still look handsome.
You're the best.
I wanted to look...
as pretty as I could for you.
Remember this.
You're leaving.
Finally.
Mr. Ji.
Don't let me go.
If you tell me not to go, I won't.
Eun San.
No matter...
where you go...
Don't say your last goodbye.
Never give up.
(Tan Bus Terminal)
Eun San.
(Brother-in-law)
What is it?
What?
(Attorney Hall)
I looked into it after you called.
There...
are gangsters involved.
Can you find out who it is?
We'll be in trouble if we get involved with the wrong people.
I heard you ran a junkyard.
It's not a junkyard.
You should come out to our alumni gatherings.
We redid the flooring when we renovated the interior!
Right...
I cleaned them off, so I wouldn't get dirt on the floor.
You should've studied for the bar. Why...
Who would've thought you'd come asking me for help?
I'll look into it.
Attorney Bae.
Please do me this favour.
- Then... - I won't see you out.
Hello?
Yes.
Let's go for a workout together soon.
Yes. I'm right outside the office.
Okay.
(Myeongil Law Firm)
Are you done?
Yes.
What's the point of making porridge after what you did to your father?
This is all because of you.
Your father collapsed, and the family is a mess.
We even got conned.
We're practically ruined.
I don't feel good about this either.
Don't be like this too.
You lived your life as a princess, so you can't relate.
Do you think I don't have anything to say?
I didn't know.
Your father took care of all the household manners.
Are you proud of that?
Father practically sold me off.
He thought he could save the family by bringing in a smart son-in-law,
so he didn't even think about what my life would be like.
I lived like a fool for 50 years.
What's the point of dating someone you ended things with already?
You're a housewife with two kids.
I can't end things with him.
It was fate that we met like this again.
You want to live with him when your family's falling apart?
He's uneducated,
and he's younger than you.
If you don't know anything, just stay quiet.
What don't I know?
You've just lost your mind.
I'm not dating him because I lost my mind.
Then why are you seeing him?
What's the reason?
Later.
Tell me.
What's the reason?
What's the reason why you're seeing him?
Did you lend him money?
It's not because of money.
You want to have an affair because Nam Chul had one too.
What other reason is there?
- Is that it? - Don't say that, Mom.
To be honest...
Chairman Ko.
Hey.
What happened? Did you catch them?
Not yet.
The CEO is running around trying his best to find them.
What CEO?
Who else could it be?
I'm talking about Mr. Ji Nam Chul.
He reached out to his connections from Seoul University Law School.
He comes up early in the morning and leaves late at night.
He's going through a lot.
We leave right after the meeting at the airport. I'm aware.
Yes. I'll check my email right now.
(Defence on the Lawsuit for Adultery)
(Defence Summary)
- What is that? - What?
(Defence, lawsuit, adulterer)
(Template for lawsuit defence)
What is this?
You looked up lawsuits for adultery.
Are you being sued?
Eun Kang.
I need to write a defence in a month.
I can't write a single word.
What on earth did I do?
I must be getting punished.
I'm so scared.
I feel like I've been stripped naked and thrown to the wolves.
I'm terrified to death.
Eun San. What should I do?
What could I possibly do?
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can join the team today.
Something urgent came up.
I'll join the next team.
Yes, thank you.
Are you serious?
I just found out too.
Imagine how my sister felt when she received the lawsuit.
Most people are scared when they get a call from the police.
Did you know that aside from this lawsuit,
she was also charged by the police?
"Charged?" For what?
She's being charged as an accomplice for stealing a design.
You don't know much about my sister.
Are you even worried about her?
Eun Kang. I'm at the law firm I used to work at.
They said mediation was better than going to court.
- "Mediation?" - Yes.
You'll be at a disadvantage if this goes to court.
The plaintiffs usually prefer to mediate too.
Cho Eun Kang?
Tell me everything you know about that person.
Including her family.
- Did something happen? - No.
I thought you'd know since you dated for four years.
It seems like you came to me...
because you feel uncomfortable asking her.
It's impossible to describe Cho Eun Kang in one word.
She's nice, diligent, and sacrificial.
She's also spiteful, lies a lot,
and doesn't get flustered when she gets caught.
She's hard to read,
so I don't know her despite dating her for four years.
There's a video...
of you guys getting yelled at by Ba Da after getting caught together.
Is it okay for me to ask what you're planning to do?
I guess it's not.
If I were to give you advice as someone who dated her first,
run away...
before the entire family comes and tries to get a piece of you.
What do you mean?
Her father is a taxi driver,
her mom works at a restaurant,
and her sister is a brat who works part-time jobs.
Have you been to her house?
I visited it once, and it was something out of a nightmare.
The front gate fell off as soon as we entered,
the floors squeaked,
and they gave their future son-in-law restaurant leftovers.
They asked me how much money I'd give them each month,
if I would live with them,
and to marry her before the house fell apart.
They were really ignorant.
Her uncle is a male escort.
Do you get the picture?
I heard she passed the exam to be a teacher.
Just wait.
The entire family will try to live off of Cho Eun Kang.
Her entire family is a lost cause.
Will you be able to handle it?
There's only one person who can save my sister.
I'm scared she might end up doing something stupid!
I'm praying to a deity that has never been on my side.
No, it doesn't matter if you're the devil.
Please be on my side just this once.
If you allow me to become a teacher,
I'll do anything.
I'll even...
give up on that man.
I was waiting for you to come.
If you follow the plaintiff around, it's considered stalking.
Should I call the police?
Hold on, Ba Da.
About the plagiarized design,
I gave the police all the records of my texts and phone calls...
with Na Bun Nyeon I had recorded.
Once the truth comes out, you'll believe me.
And...
as for the indemnity lawsuit...
That sounds complicated.
Just keep it simple and say lawsuit for adultery.
Why?
Why? Does it feel awkward to call yourself an adulterer?
Can we...
mediate the lawsuit for adultery instead of going to court?
I'll try to get more money than listed in the lawsuit.
If you want, I'll sign a contract.
A trial will take a long time...
I don't want to waste my breath.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
I told you I didn't file the lawsuit to get your dirty money.
Let me tell you again.
What I want is the judge's sentencing.
Who else will you take advantage of after wiping out your past...
and changing your identity?
Don't worry about the time.
The lawyers will take care of it.
You'll end up paying for my legal fees as well.
You know that. Right?
What are you doing?
Just kill me.
Kill me.
I'd rather die in your hands.
You're blackmailing me.
Ba Da. I was being foolish.
If I had thought about the future,
I wouldn't have done something to ruin my life.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I'll give everything up.
I'm sorry I coveted what was yours.
I'm sorry I hurt your pride.
I'll spend the rest of my life...
paying for the sin of betraying you.
Ba Da, please forgive me.
There's only one thing that's important to me.
I need to make a living.
I want to sell my soul to the devil.
Please save me.
My family can't survive without me.
If I fall apart now,
my mom, my dad, and my sister...
Ba Da.
I'll live quietly and never show my face around you again.
Please save me. Please?
Please, just this once.
(Sale on suits)
(Daean Local Bar Association)
Attorney Bae.
I have plans.
Your secretary told me you weren't around.
I'm sorry I waited for you like this.
I heard you did a demolition bidding fraud case last year.
I heard that it was the same group.
Help me.
I don't know.
Attorney Bae.
Please.
I looked into it,
and you're the only one who can help me.
I won't forget this.
I bought a suit and dress shoes...
to come and see you.
You were popular when we were students,
and you're still the best now. Who cares?
Come upstairs for a bit.
- Come in. - Where's Mi Poong?
At my parent's house.
It'll be just us two today.
When did you prepare all of this?
It's been a while since I cooked.
Have a seat.
(Defence on the Lawsuit for Adultery)
Your Honour.
(Your Honour)
You're an animal caught in a trap.
You want me to drop the lawsuit?
You humiliated us at the café, and the video spread online too.
So filing a lawsuit...
Stay out of this.
This is between Eun Kang and me.
What am I supposed to make of this?
You invited me for a meal.
To be honest, I was excited to be here.
But this was about her?
She had been good to you for 20 years.
She ran all kinds of errands for you.
She took great care of your mother and our daughter.
No one could have done what she did for us.
You always said that.
You said you could live without me, but not without her.
You were so grateful to her.
I'm asking you to be nice and forgive her just this once.
Are you asking me to be nice to her right now?
I was going to let your affair slide at least.
But do you know who's responsible for my bankruptcy?
I can't put up with this anymore.
Ba Da.
She only did that once three years ago.
She had to do it because she needed money...
for her mom's surgery.
Can you see how desperate she must have been?
She was raised in a poor family. She probably had no choice.
Someone's life depends on your decision.
Put yourself in her shoes just this once.
How could she live with a criminal record...
and a ruling that brands her as an adulterer?
Please drop the lawsuit just this once for my sake.
For your sake?
I knew that you were slow, but you just crossed the line.
She did everything for you.
It's true that Eun Kang helped you all these years.
What do you know about her?
You just wait.
I'll show you who she really is.
Don't do anything you'll regret.
I know you'll regret it.
That's my burden to carry.
Ba Da!
I apologize for barging in early in the morning.
I need you to come with me.
It's important.
Dae Geun!
Call Ms. Cho first.
Right.
It's so true that old habits die hard.
Did you make up with Dae Geun?
When did we fight?
Don't underestimate our brotherhood.
Ms. Cho, your meal is ready.
This isn't Korean beef, right?
I made that for Ms. Cho, not you.
What are you barking about? I'm Ms. Cho's father.
What are you chirping about?
I'm the one who brought her into the world.
Hey, we're such a good match.
I can't believe our daughter became a schoolteacher.
Exactly.
My goodness.
I can't believe our luck!
- My goodness. - My goodness.
Where are we?
You'll know when you go inside.
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
Goodness.
- Gosh. - Go inside.
Who's knocking on our door this early?
What?
What are you doing here?
Is this your house?
Why are you...
Are you two married?
I'm sorry.
Why did you bring us here?
Did you bring us here to see these two?
The boiler is broken again. I took a shower with cold water.
What? What are you doing here?
You were a family.
You said you were a Joo, not a Cho.
I'm sorry, sir!
So you are...
Eun Kang's mother?
I guess I am.
It's been a long time since I gave birth to her.
You said your parents died, and you were an orphan.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
You should have woken me up.
Geum Ah.
I bought tofu.
- Goodness. - What?
Gosh.
What on earth is going on here?
How could the entire family work together to deceive us?
You.
This is worse than not being good enough for him.
You're a defect!
Unbelievable.
I've been conned before.
But no one has done anything like this before.
Everyone in that family is a con artist.
What do you think? Did you know about this?
He probably didn't.
This is no joke.
I bet she approached us to ruin us.
She got her mother a job here and her sister at my company.
She got them to work for us, so they would spy on us for her.
Their daughters seduced my son and my son-in-law.
And the guy who rolled out of his room...
seduced my daughter.
What do you see in him? Why do you want to get a divorce?
Did Eun Kang introduce him to you too?
No, she didn't.
He and I have known each other for 24 years.
Chun's friend introduced Eun Kang to us ten years ago.
This was all a coincidence. It couldn't have been planned.
I'm sure she didn't intend any of this.
She must have been desperate to secretly help her mom...
get a job here.
And the same goes for her sister.
She must have been anxious every time she was here.
- What? - Whose side are you on right now?
I'll take her side for now.
I'm the only one...
who can protect her now.
Even after everything?
- Break up with her. - I can't.
As a doctor, I'm supposed to save people.
How can I call myself a doctor if I turn my back on my people?
Gosh.
I raised you to be a doctor!
How could you use that against me?
- I'm so lonely. - You're so awful!
How could you be so cruel?
What do you gain from this?
Did you say I was cruel?
Think about what she did to me.
I'm just getting started.
Would her death make you happy?
You know nothing about her.
She'll never die.
She's way too attached to her life.
I'm utterly disappointed in you.
I really didn't know you would go this far.
(Tents, imported awnings, banners)
Why were you born into this kind of family?
There's nothing for you to pick at here.
If you're born again,
be born as the youngest daughter of a rich family.
The front gate falls off as soon as you get there,
and the floor creaks.
Is anyone home?
Nice to meet you. My name is Ko Cha Won.
I'm the person who has promised to have a future with Eun Kang.
It's me. You've seen me before.
You haven't met my husband before, though.
I'm Eun Kang's father.
Hello.
Let's go out and talk.
I'll stick with her no matter what happens.
I came here to tell you that.
- I said, we need to go out. - Just talk here.
Don't get mad.
She takes after me, so she gets mad when she likes something.
I'll see you next time.
Just go home.
I know you're having a hard time, Eun Kang.
How would you know when you haven't experienced it?
It's so embarrassing I want to die.
I can't even look you in the eye.
We're on the same side.
- Look at me. - No.
Let's stop.
I'm tired of everything now.
I don't want to see anyone, regardless of love.
I'm sorry, Cha Won.
If I hadn't tempted you,
you would've been living happily right now.
I'm really sorry.
Don't say that.
We agreed to do this together.
I shouldn't even have started it.
I feel like an animal caught in its own trap,
writhing and unable to escape.
I have no strength left to struggle or a way to get out.
Just leave me and go.
I'll never leave you.
We're together, so why are you struggling alone?
Just rely on me. Leave your trust in me.
Don't pity me.
That's really mean of you.
You know it's not pity.
Let's go somewhere far away and live together.
As long as I have my medical license,
I'll always be able to make a living.
- Come with me. - No.
I've already become a laughingstock.
There's nowhere left to go where I can live as a human being.
I'm a flawed and deficient product.
- Eun Kang. - Please, just go.
Don't even look at me.
Leave before I start cursing at you.
I'm so embarrassed it's driving me insane.
I told you I was tired of everything now.
You asked me not to give up.
Because I didn't know.
I didn't know it would turn out like this.
Eun Kang!
Is this the place? Are you sure?
It's right there.
What are you trying to do?
You want to get hit?
Who are you? You punk.
Darn it. You punk.
Hey, let's just go.
Darn it.
I don't have the time for this.
Mr. Ji, bite him!
Why, you little punk.
You punk.
Let go, punk.
You're in trouble now.
Do you want to die?
I'm really going to kill you.
Let's go!
What are you doing? You punk!
Let go!
You rotten punk.
Sir, no. Please don't do this.
These two were about to flee to China...
but were caught by those two over there.
Nam Chul!
Mr. Ji found everything out...
and made a plan to catch them.
If it hadn't been for him, we would've been helpless.
Did someone hit him?
It was while we were fighting with them.
Let's go to the hospital, Nam Chul.
I'm fine.
I'll go now.
Wait.
- Nam Chul. - Excuse me, Ko Mul Sang?
We need you to confirm some things. Please come over here.
But...
(Geum Ah)
Where are you? I've been waiting.
Geum Ah.
Don't wait for me.
I can't see you.
- Dae Geun. - I'm sorry.
I can't overcome the hurdles of reality.
Just forget about me.
I know.
I was so shocked that day.
I know it's all so tangled up that we can't do anything.
But I just wanted to see your face one last time.
I have something to tell you.
You need to know.
I think it'll be harder if I see you.
Geum Ah.
You have to be happy. I'm hanging up.
Wait, Dae Geun.
Hello? Dae Geun?
(Ko Mul Sang)
Where have you been? I've been trying to contact you.
Nam Chul just packed his bags and left.
I tried to stop him, but he left without a word.
He found the money that those scammers tried to take.
His face was beaten badly too.
What's wrong with her?
(Divorce Papers)
My plane leaves on the first of March.
Make me stay.
(Teacher Cho Eun Kang committed adultery...)
(with the husband of her friend of 20 years.)
(Taeju Middle School)
(She is currently being sued as an adulteress!)
(Teacher Cho Eun Kang)
Where have you been?
I had business to take care of.
She'll never be a teacher.
How dare she mess with us?
What are you talking about?
I hung up a huge banner in front of her school.
"Teacher Cho Eun Kang committed adultery..."
"with the husband of her friend of 20 years."
"She is currently being sued as an adulteress."
- Sounds good, right? - That's illegal, Mom.
That's okay.
I'll just pay the fine.
She destroyed someone else's family...
and betrayed her friend. How can she be a teacher?
She needs to be humiliated and fired to realize what she has done.
I bought tofu.
Gosh.
What on earth is going on here?
How could the entire family work together to deceive us?
This is worse than not being good enough for him.
You're a defect!
How could you be so cruel?
Do you feel better now?
Do you want her to die?
Even next year...
Goodness, Cho Dae Bong. That's some special care.
You'll wake Eun Kang.
It's my daughter's first day going to work.
I'm going to take her in a nice, clean car.
Is that bulgogi?
Yes, I'm making gimbap for Eun Kang.
She can't teach on an empty stomach.
- That looks tasty. - No, you can't.
- What's wrong with you? - Quiet!
- Gosh, you fool. - Quiet.
Here, you can have a bite.
It's hot!
(Taeju Middle School)
(Teacher Cho Eun Kang committed adultery...)
(with the husband of her friend of 20 years.)
(She is currently being sued as an adulteress!)
Here.
It doesn't hurt at all when you massage me.
I got strawberries, your favourite.
Don't cry.
It must be hard for you.
You have to be confident in these times.
- Hello. - Did you get my email earlier?
- Ms. Han wanted to confirm... - Do you have rubies?
I can live without my husband,
but not without you, honestly.
Trust wasn't the issue. You thought I was insignificant.
Is that why...
you introduced me to a divorced man with two daughters?
You stepped on me, and I squirmed in response.
That night, you two...
What I could hear from your room...
I'm not blind or deaf.
I was your errand girl for 20 years.
But I still didn't hate you.
I just envied you.
- Why won't you pick up your phone? - I didn't know.
Before I found out,
Eun Kang said she asked you to break it off.
Is that true?
It's true.
Yes, she asked to end things during the returns incident.
She said this wasn't something we should be doing.
(Teacher Cho Eun Kang committed adultery...)
(with the husband of her friend of 20 years.)
Don't take it down.
We need to get revenge.
We need to make sure she'll never live as a human being.
This is wrong, Mom.
Even if I get revenge, I won't take it like this.
She has to be humiliated.
She wants to ruin you and become a teacher?
She looked after Mi Poong and took care of you, Mom.
She did every errand I asked of her.
For 20 years, she ran every errand for me.
You paid her to do that.
You think people would do that for money?
She was my hands and feet for 20 years.
I can't destroy her like this.
Stop it.
Stop it!
Mom!
This was Eun Kang's dream ever since she was little.
She worked so hard for this.
I really hate her too.
I hate her,
- but this is wrong. - You fool.
That woman smeared you with dirt and didn't even glance back at you.
Why are you being a fool, all by yourself?
This is why you got your husband stolen from you.
Now it looks like you'll lose your daughter too.
Mom, if Eun Kang had been born into a rich family like me...
and grew up with a good mom like you,
would she have done this?
I tried all sorts of things.
I tried everything,
but I don't feel good at all.
I thought I'd feel good once I got revenge,
I feel like I'm going insane instead.
This is wrong, Mom.
Please.
(Cho Eun Kang)
Hello.
I am...
your Korean teacher, Cho Eun Kang.
I'm happy to meet you.
Everyone,
I've been...
wanting to meet you all so much.
(Korean Bar Association)
I wanted to say the things I could never say...
even if I had to be drunk.
We're friends,
but you can say anything sober when I need alcohol.
I think I wanted him not because he was Cha Won,
but because he was your husband.
These words are categorized into three types.
The first shows changes in tense.
Its function in a sentence...
I learned how to give up soon after I was born.
I learned how to hold back my desires.
I was jealous of you throughout the 20 years.
I struggled to become like you.
I got to experience bits of your world thanks to you.
It was really sweet.
They call this relative deprivation.
Who's done?
(OX Quiz and Fill-in-the-Blanks with Teacher)
You were...
my red balloon.
I wanted to be you and live your life.
I'm sorry, but please take down the video.
I am the wife.
I'm worried my child might see this...
after she grows up.
Things have been settled on a good note,
so I'd appreciate it if you delete it.
Ba Da. You were...
the best friend I had.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
Thank you for everything.
I'll never forget you.
(Principal Lee Ji Hoon)
(Letter of Resignation)
(Taeju Middle School)
I wanted to show this sight of me...
to you first of all people.
It was my first day at work today.
How do I look?
Even now,
I think of you first when I wake up in the morning.
If you texted or called me,
I keep looking at my phone.
It must've been much more of a case for you.
You rely on me for everything.
I had a tough childhood in a poor family,
so I can bear the problems.
But you grew up like a flower in a garden.
This situation must be difficult for you.
When I think about it,
my heart breaks.
You mean brat.
My twisted desire caused it all.
My foolishness caused me to lose a good friend...
and ruin my life.
I won't write a defence paper.
I'll get punished as you want.
Above all,
a love affair is the most humiliating thing to do.
I guess it made me feel a little satisfied,
thinking I beat you at least once.
I was deluded and proud.
Like you said, my wrong moves came back to me as a trap.
I played smart just to make my life easier,
and it led to this disaster.
I shouldn't have done something I would regret.
Now that I'm dying,
I can't care less about love or anything else.
I'm having a mental breakdown.
I was foolish to rely on people,
and I realized...
I needed to rely on myself by guaranteeing my future.
I thought I had nothing to lose,
but I got scared when I got a teaching license.
Early this morning,
I did everything carefully...
like a soldier going out to war.
I got dressed, carried a purse,
and put on heels.
For the first and last time,
I went out to work.
What do you mean by that?
When I arrived at school,
I saw you and my mom arguing.
I hid in the alley...
and heard you trying to stop my mom.
What you said in tears...
The last time?
What do you mean by that?
I resigned today.
Are you out of your mind?
Why did you resign, you fool?
It was so hard for you to become a teacher!
Stand up. Who received your resignation letter?
Let's go take it back.
I don't think I can do it.
I don't think I can stand in front of students.
A trace remains no matter how hard you try to erase it.
What I did can't be undone.
I dropped all the charges.
I even asked them to take down the video.
I ran around all day to cancel everything.
How is it...
that you act just like your name means, the sea?
I heard...
you wanted to break up with Mi Poong's dad first.
And you didn't tell him...
about what happened in Italy.
I didn't sue you for adultery from the start...
probably because I wanted to be easy on you.
I had our friendship necklace on...
right until I found out that you were working with...
Na Bun Nyeon.
For the first time in my life,
I went to your house and got stunned.
I went there out of spite,
but when I actually arrived, your house...
and your family...
I thought I could understand...
how your life had been...
and how much you struggled, wanting to escape.
I felt so bad for you like crazy.
But then, I hated and resented you.
I thought I'd regret it my whole life...
if I was harsh on you.
Thank you...
Let's go.
We'll take back your resignation before it's accepted.
I thought...
I'd never get to hold this hand again.
I wish all this were a dream.
Shut it, and let's hurry on.
Did you submit it to the principal?
No.
Your forgiveness is enough.
I already made up my mind.
What is wrong with you?
You have to survive somehow.
I didn't give up.
I'm doing this to live.
I have forgiven you.
I can't forgive myself.
I need to punish myself for how foolish I was.
Only then, I will be able to live.
I've taught the students once, and that's good enough.
I'm done struggling to catch the balloon that's flying away.
Ba Da.
From the age of 17 to 37,
I had my most beautiful days...
with you.
I was so lucky...
like splendid spring.
Spring is back,
but I won't have another spring in my life.
(Storage Lockers)
(Express Bus)
Wait!
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I'll be alive somewhere.
I'm sorry.
(Cho Eun Kang)
The truth is,
your father isn't on a business trip.
He and I had an argument.
He needs to come back home,
but I can't go get him alone because I wronged him a lot.
Will you go with me?
Nam Chul.
- Father. - Dad!
Father...
Father.
Have at least a bit.
I don't think I can.
Why is it so quiet in the house?
I guess everyone went outside.
I can't sleep, worrying you might leave me.
I've talked big under your wings.
Without you,
I'm nothing.
You snored and even farted in your sleep.
Send the old man off to rest in peace...
and live with a young guy.
Who would want to live with a hag unless he's out of his mind?
Or he'd be after my money.
So you know.
You see,
some things should remain as a lie...
or stay buried.
I thought...
I was smart.
But I failed to keep the balance.
And you nagged that I failed to hold my fart.
Now there's no one...
left by my side.
You have me.
There's nothing you can do.
Not to mention the company,
and our grandchildren are young.
What am I supposed to do?
We'll live on by exchanging our steel with Taffy.
It's going to take forever to exchange all that steel.
Goodness.
Father.
Nam Chul's home.
Welcome back!
- Mr. Ji! - Welcome back.
Welcome back.
It's good to see you.
Gosh, kid.
Are you okay?
Aren't you hurt? Let me see.
I'm okay. You didn't hit me.
Are you sure you're okay?
Shouldn't you go see a doctor?
I'm not hurt.
Wait.
Hey, kid.
Didn't we meet near the amusement park before?
Oh, gosh.
I'm sorry I keep bumping into you.
Wait, don't just go.
Are you really not hurt?
You didn't tell your parents back then, did you?
Call them.
I'm okay, though. I need to go.
Hey, wait.
If you just go, the country will punish me. Come on.
- But I shouldn't. - Do it.
It's my mom's number. Tell her that I'm not hurt.
Goodness.
- Be careful on your way. - Okay.
I have something to tell you.
We met about 12 years ago.
Mi Poong betrayed me.
I admit that you are a better parent...
- than me. - Meet her anytime you want.
- I hear you're leaving for Italy. - Yes.
To study and grow my business.
I'm going with my mom.
I used to think...
it was weird for a divorced couple to be friends.
But I'm going to do just that.
We're friends as of today.
Tell me if you need help.
And take care of yourself.
Don't worry about Mi Poong.
Ba Da.
I'm sorry I broke your heart.
(Courthouse)
(One year later)
- Look. - You got the hang of it now.
There are so many.
We're so grateful for your help.
Ma'am, I'll come back tomorrow.
Okay. Thank you so much for your help. Seriously, thank you.
- No problem. Bye! - All right, bye.
- See you tomorrow! - Okay!
- Get back safely. - I will!
Ms. Cho.
Yes.
Let's see.
Yes, it's right. Well done.
- Eun San! - Hey!
My gosh!
What are you doing here? You didn't even call me.
I followed a team of medical volunteers I know.
- When did you return from Africa? - Last week.
Has everything been well with you? How's your health?
I'm doing great.
This looks nicer than how you described it.
You seem relaxed and comfortable.
Here, I can focus on myself.
I don't have to compare myself with others or be compared.
I can just be myself.
I didn't know a freshwater fish could die dreaming of the ocean.
If only I had known what I know now...
I shuck clams as a side job.
Life becomes no fun when you're too mature.
That's true.
Do you have a boyfriend now?
I told you that I wanted to stay single.
I got these for you. They're books and school supplies.
"LFW." You rock.
I told you not to use such abbreviations.
Gosh, you sound like a boomer.
Hey, these are heavy.
"IGIW," seriously.
When do you plan to leave?
I'll give the kids haircuts and bake some bread for them too.
And I'll help the medical team when they treat the ladies.
- I can stay for a few days, right? - Yes.
Oh, they told me to video-call them upon arriving.
Mom! Here's Eun Kang.
Move aside!
That's nonsense! I'll go first.
That's rubbish! She said "Mom" first.
You're doing well, right? How's your health?
Gosh, my dear daughter.
It's me, your dad.
When will you visit us?
I'll make braised short ribs for you.
With premium Korean beef.
I'll visit you next month.
Mom, I could only send 100 dollars this month.
My goodness!
Money is the best remedy for her.
Bye, Dad. I'll be home in a few days.
I'll call you, Mom. Don't fight with Dad.
We never fight.
Life's boring because we never fight.
My dear daughters, take care of yourselves.
- Okay. - Bye!
I'm so excited that you're staying with me for a few days.
Let's go inside.
Eun Kang, I have another gift for you.
Go to the dock.
(Volunteer Team Donations, Food)
(Chairman Ji Nam Chul)
Here, enjoy.
- Thank you. - Enjoy. How adorable!
You're so excited.
Which one do you want? This one.
A short-lived love.
A long-lasting longing.
This is our final goodbye.
My first and last lover.
Goodbye.
(Chatting)
(Delete)
Never give up.
"Never give up."
Yes, the jacket for your world tour.
It'll be around a million Euros in total.
As a world-famous star, you certainly deserve it.
We'll have a meeting as soon as we have the design ready.
Thank you.
(Ko Cha Won)
Hi, it's me.
I've been busy ever since I got back.
I have a press conference,
and I've been really busy...
preparing the show for winning the International Awards' Grand Prize.
I'll be participating in Paris Fashion Week too.
I'll stay with Mi Poong for a few days.
My mom misses her.
Okay.
(My red balloon, Han Ba Da. Congratulations on your success.)
(Rooting for your radiant days ahead)
Eun Kang!
Cho Eun Kang!
I'm home.
Everyone! Come out.
I'm so lonely!
My gosh.
Bow to Mr. Chairman.
- Welcome home, Mr. Chairman. - Welcome home, Mr. Chairman.
You must've had another long day, Nam Chul.
You don't have to do this every day, Father.
What are you talking about?
You worked so hard all day.
Of course, we must greet you like this.
I'm making dumplings, your favourite.
Everyone, wash your hands and help me make dumplings.
Gosh.
- "I'm so lonely!" - "I'm so lonely!"
(Red Balloon)
(Thank you for supporting and watching Red Balloon.)