(Red Balloon)
(Seo Ji Hye)
(Lee Sung Jae)
(Hong Soo Hyun)
(Lee Sang Woo)
(Jung Yu Min)
(Yoon Mi Ra, Yoon Joo Sang, Lee Bo Hee, Jung Bo Seog)
(Kim Hye Seon, Choi Dae Chul, Lee Sang Suk, Seol Jung Hwan)
(Red Balloon)
(All characters, organizations, and events...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
I'm fine.
You can have it. It's good.
The suspect put sleeping pills in a drink and drugged the victim...
Aren't you going to drink it?
Why? Do you think I drugged it?
What?
We shouldn't have listened to the news.
Don't you trust me?
Drink it if you trust me. If you don't, don't drink it.
It's so good.
You should wash your hands too.
Right.
Mom, have you eaten?
I just got a bite in.
I know you're on a business trip,
but I'm worried.
I had a nightmare last night.
Stay safe, okay?
Don't worry, Mom. I'll look after myself.
- What was that? - What do you mean?
It seemed as though you were putting something in.
Did you see that?
It's good for your health.
It looked like some sort of powder.
What on earth do you think I put in there?
It was collagen.
Collagen?
You should take care of your skin too.
It looks delicious. Let's eat.
The noodles are nice and chewy.
What's wrong?
I don't think my stomach is up for it.
But you're the one who wanted cold raw fish soup.
Do you think I spiked the soup?
Of course not.
I'll be the prime suspect if anything happens to you.
I may have let my friend steal my husband away,
but I'm not an idiot.
See? It's collagen.
I didn't add any in mine since I had some this morning.
(May our friendship last forever. Cho Eun Kang, Han Ba Da)
I feel refreshed.
You should shower too so that we can drink.
Sure.
What's wrong?
The floor...
Are you all right?
The floor was slippery.
I spilled some oil earlier,
and I forgot to tell you.
I hope you weren't injured.
I'm fine.
Who may you be...
and why are you lurking around my house?
Apart from the hair loss, you look pretty much the same.
Living the good life must have done wonders for you.
Do you know me?
You must not remember me.
Before your daughter got married,
she was involved with a Chinese restaurant delivery man.
I was the one who told you that.
So what brings you by?
I showed this to your son-in-law, but he won't take action.
Please stop your daughter.
Why can't the two stay away from each other?
Goodness.
My gosh.
Mr. Ko, I ran over as soon as I got your call.
Actually, I drove my cab here.
- You needed 10,000 dollars. - Right.
What I want in return is your service.
My service?
There's someone who got on my nerves...
about 20 years ago.
He's back at it again.
Who dares to get on your nerves?
Is he someone you met while running your business?
That's not something you need to know.
For now,
just rough him up.
Don't lay him out flat, though. Just teach him a lesson.
Sorry?
Get this done for me, and I'll pay 10,000 dollars.
It won't be a loan. I'll pay you.
Goodness.
Mr. Ko, I'm not as gutsy as you think,
and I haven't indulged in any illegal acts.
You won't get caught.
He couldn't report you to the cops.
Trust me and get it done.
It's 10,000 dollars.
Mr. Ko,
can't you just lend me the money? I don't think I can...
You'll be getting the money for free.
Actually, I'm not getting that money for free.
I'll be committing a crime.
Sir, I desperately need the money. But I can't hurt someone.
I'm sorry. I'll get going first.
Hey, come on.
Hey, Joo Dae Bong.
Joo?
I think it was Cho Dae Bong.
Was I that popular?
I was so sick of it.
I ran the errands for all the boys too.
They awkwardly approached me.
"Can you give this to Ba Da?"
Seriously.
I was so jealous.
- Were you? - Of course.
You grew up in a nice family, so you didn't have a dark side.
But I was dark and twisted. Like the twisted donut.
You gave them my number and got free twisted donuts.
A few times.
I had the most fun in high school in my entire life.
We used to secretly exchange notes during class.
We found everything so funny back then.
We got caught, and our teacher punished us side by side.
When we were getting punished, we cracked up and got punished more.
Seriously. We used to laugh whenever we had the chance.
I skipped going to my cram school and went to your house to hang out.
But after high school,
I can't remember any fun moments.
I don't know why I miss the past.
Right.
Why did you do it?
I'm 37 years old.
And I was with you for more than half my lifetime.
You had been with me every single moment of my life.
Even now,
losing you was the most painful thing I went through.
More painful than losing my husband.
Even now, when I wake up,
you're the first person I think of.
I do too.
Whenever I wake up, you're the first person I think of.
"Will she text? Or call?"
"Does she need me to run an errand? Is there anything I can do to help?"
I was drunk the last time we talked.
Forget all the bad things I said to you.
I really wanted to be more like you.
And I envied you.
Then at one point, this idea was planted in me.
Once it was planted, I couldn't go back.
At that moment, I felt as if...
I had been under some kind of spell.
That day,
if the lipstick didn't roll under your feet...
and if we didn't become friends...
I'm sorry, Ba Da.
I ruined everything.
To be honest, this whole trip made me feel anxious and nervous.
"What will she say?"
"Will she scold me?"
"If she hits me, I'll let her."
All kinds of thoughts crossed my mind.
You weren't scared that I might kill you?
If that was what you wanted, I couldn't have stopped you.
There's no knife.
What?
It's gone?
Did you drop it in the car?
Why do you want a knife?
You said you couldn't stop me if I wanted to kill you.
Why would you say something you didn't mean then?
I was going to eat an apple.
Then let's go with plan B.
Plan B?
Let's go out.
Let's get some fresh air by the beach.
We should see the sunrise too.
It'll be cold.
How cold could it be?
We can't go back without seeing the sunrise.
Get dressed.
Okay.
The suspect even gave the victim alcohol.
The suspect then led the intoxicated victim to the beach...
What are you doing?
What?
Are you scared that I might push you into the water and drown you?
If you were to fall into the water and drown,
what would they say on the news?
"A 37-year-old woman, Cho,"
"coveted the husband of her friend of 20 years."
"She was found drowned to death."
Would that be it?
Don't be scared.
You're good at swimming anyway.
Don't worry. I won't kill you.
Let's go out.
Okay.
You brought the necklace, right?
Yes.
You should throw it too.
I'll throw mine.
This is the end of our friendship.
Let's put an end to our 20 years together.
Thank you for coming on this trip.
Take care.
You too.
I know you'll save your business.
I know you'll be successful again.
I must.
Let's go back separately.
I'll go back to the hotel first, pack my stuff, and leave.
Can I...
hug you one last time?
Ba Da.
You were...
the best friend I had.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
Thank you for everything.
I'll never forget you.
(Police of Dreams and Hope, Safe and Happy Citizens)
Can you reduce the settlement money?
I have never made that much money in my life.
Well,
can you lower it to 3,000 dollars?
Please.
I don't have any money.
Why don't you just sell me off then?
No one wants to buy you. Why do you keep saying that?
You know how hard he worked to be a private taxi driver.
Whatever.
Will you take your money to the coffin?
I'd be happy if I had money to take to my coffin.
Ban Sook, if you keep this up...
What?
I bet you wouldn't give me money even if I get a terminal illness.
How can I trust you to have my back?
I'm so sick of you!
What took you so long?
I had been sick of you ages ago.
Dae Geun is all he cares about.
I'll give you 5,000 dollars for now.
I'll give you the rest once the deed is done.
Understood?
Can you write a contract for me?
You can't leave a paper trail.
Sometimes, you can be so dense.
Don't you trust me?
I don't trust the world.
But...
I'll trust you.
By the way,
who is this man? I have to know who he is...
You can't know who he is.
Seriously. I'm so lonely.
Then how many times should I punch him?
Hello?
It's been a while.
I need to talk to you about Geum Ah.
Meet me without telling anyone.
Not even Geum Ah.
Okay.
I'll be there.
Take a picture for proof.
Dae Geun?
Dae Geun!
Dae Geun, what happened?
Dae Geun, wake up.
Dae Geun, it's me.
Hey...
Don't die.
Or I'll scold you.
Dae Geun...
Stay still. I'll call an ambulance.
Don't.
You could get arrested.
Don't die.
Dae Geun, please stay with me.
Dae Geun.
Dae Geun?
Dae Geun!
(Divorce Papers)
There. Be careful.
Careful.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I was so startled when I took the call last night.
You must be unlucky this year.
Things keep happening to you.
Thank goodness you didn't die.
You should've been careful, especially with your head.
- Did you get a CT scan? - Yes.
You know, I have a hard skull. They said I was okay.
Are you sure you got into a car accident?
You look like you got beaten up.
- No, that's not true. - No, that's not true.
Did you have to say that together at the same time?
Well, let's go inside. You should lie down.
Uncle, take care of yourself.
Does he seem like he got beaten up to you?
Yes.
Did he get into a fight or something?
I guess spring is coming.
It already has.
Some forsythias have blossomed already.
I washed the blankets thanks to you.
You should do laundry this big at a laundromat.
You know my father.
"Why bother? We have a washing machine at home."
"Gosh, I'm so lonely."
It's jujube tea.
Thanks for today.
You even helped me with the spring cleaning.
Cha Won's house needs a big cleaning too.
I'm going to do it before I go to work.
Eun Kang, please understand why I was so cold to you.
I had my circumstances.
I know.
I've known you for ten years.
You're always amiable and shrewd.
No wonder my mom wants you to be her daughter-in-law.
And it's about to come true.
I think you and my brother make a great couple.
Like my father says, get married next year.
Thank you.
Are you in touch with Mi Poong's mom?
- I am. - Really?
She suggested a trip, so we went on it yesterday.
We had a long conversation...
and buried the hatchet.
Really? I didn't think she'd be that cool.
I mean, it wouldn't have been easy.
You better be good to her.
I'm planning to give her a gift when I get my first paycheck.
Do that.
No wonder why you seemed bright.
I don't want to lose a good man like you.
(Cho Eun Kang)
Ta-Da. I finally found Ddolbang.
Where are you? Are you at the hospital?
Yes, I'm a little busy.
Mom!
Mi Poong!
Mom, I can't breathe.
Wait.
Just a little longer.
Have you been well? Did you miss me?
Yes, isn't Grandma coming?
She's being treated at a hospital.
I wish she wouldn't come.
I hate it when she hits Auntie.
Don't say that.
She's been like that ever since she saw your mother hit Eun Kang.
Mom, are you back for good?
I'm back from Italy,
but I have to stay at school.
I'll come and see you once every few days...
until I finish my studies.
Is that okay?
You can focus on studying.
I have Auntie, so it's okay.
This is a gift for you.
How exciting!
I want to stop by home for a bit.
Okay.
Where's the plunger?
What did you do?
I played on a trampoline and played house with Ji Eun.
Do that with me next time.
I'd love to!
You're so excited.
Are you happy to see me?
Yes, I'm really happy.
Oh, my.
Is it pretty? Do you like it?
You're the best, Mom!
You can wear it by yourself, right? Go get changed.
She's still the same.
Were you cleaning?
Yes.
I seem like I'm back from Italy, right?
Don't let Mi Poong notice.
And stop frowning.
It's so clean.
It's almost spotless.
I guess you clean the house every day.
Did you change the sheets?
Yes, this morning.
I see.
Even a linen spray?
Don't tell me...
you did it for me.
Don't get too serious. I was joking.
Others might think we are strangers.
Oh, my.
Is this Ddolbang?
I bought it just in case.
Don't give her all at once.
It should be one by one.
I'll do it.
It's been a long time...
feeling this way.
What did this happen to us?
Everyone was jealous of how dear we were to each other.
Should I sleep over here today?
I signed the divorce papers, but you're still my man.
A new bed sheet. A linen mist.
This vibe somewhat makes me flutter.
Just like when we first met.
Tell me. Should I sleep over?
I have...
dinner plans today.
I can wait.
I might be late. I'll be drinking.
I don't care. I can wait.
Mom!
Okay.
Mi Poong's just like you.
She's a bigmouth and dense.
Mi Poong, you're so pretty!
Mi Poong, you're the best.
Mi Poong, your mom's busy.
Let's say goodbye for today.
I can stay longer.
I need to get going.
I was going to leave her with my parents.
I'll come and visit sometime.
Let's go eat something good next time.
Okay. Let's go.
Come on.
Say goodbye. "Bye-bye."
Come again. Goodbye.
Okay.
I'll get going. Leave my luggage in your trunk.
Mi Poong, you should go and get changed.
You can wear this to kindergarten.
Come out.
I told you to call me before you came over.
I came to return Ddolbang and decided to clean up a bit.
Do you know how nervous I was?
May I ask what happened?
She said she wanted to come and see Mi Poong.
I didn't tell you because I didn't want you to take it the wrong way.
You already made that happen.
I'd like you to be honest and tell me things in advance.
I'm sorry.
You should leave before Mi Poong sees you.
You never know what she'll tell her mom.
Okay.
Ms. Cho Eun Kang?
- Is Ms. Cho Eun Kang here? - Who is it?
I have registered mail.
Gosh, I have a cramp.
The door's open.
Cho Eun Kang isn't here, but I'm her mom.
I'm Yang Ban Sook.
- Can you sign here? - Sure.
Your front gate falls off the hinge.
It always does that. Just leave it and go.
Goodbye!
(From Han Ba Da, To Cho Eun Kang)
My gosh. This is driving me crazy.
- Come out! - Be careful.
Is there a ringing in your head?
No, there isn't.
Be careful.
Do you want me to bring it to your room?
It's not that bad.
People would think you had a kid or something.
When it comes to your brother...
He almost died because of me.
It's my fault for not having a younger brother.
You almost killed your brother while trying to save him.
Have some rice.
- Oh, it's not rice. It's porridge. - I'm not hungry.
You don't eat because you're hungry.
You eat to survive.
You should have a bite, so you can take your medicine.
I bought beef to make your porridge.
I didn't just buy beef porridge from the store.
If you say that, it sounds like you bought it.
What nonsense is that?
Do the dishes after you eat.
I'm going to the supermarket.
Go ahead.
I'm so sorry.
I'm glad you didn't die.
Why would I die?
I still have so much to live for.
What kind of twist of fate is this?
I never imagined you'd be connected to that old man's daughter.
Why would you go and meet him because he asked you to?
This happened 18 years ago too.
I went out knowing I'd get beaten up.
I thought that would be the only way to resolve this.
You should've shouted for help.
You didn't make a sound.
What's the point?
It'll only make the person hitting me feel worse.
Your hits were quite strong.
I know how to take hits,
but I could barely handle yours.
I regretted playing baseball for the first time.
This wretched life.
Uncle. You have a guest.
Honey. What's wrong?
- Gosh! - My gosh!
What happened to him? Did he get into an accident?
I told you not to drive a taxi.
I told you I'd make enough for both of us.
Was it you?
Did you rat me out?
- What? - You ratted me out 18 years ago!
You told them where I lived!
Dae Bong, tell her to leave.
Imagine how I felt to have done that.
Listen here.
He ended up like this because of you,
so how dare you show your face around here?
Get out. I'll take care of my brother,
so get out!
What nonsense is that?
Why would you take care of him when he has his wife?
His ex-wife.
She follows him around like this because she likes him so much.
- Dae Geun... - That will never happen.
I told you we'd never get together again.
Don't make me mad and just leave.
I've decided to spend the rest of my life with her.
What?
Do you want to die?
Once you get involved with that family, you're dead meat.
Do you think that old man will be okay with it?
I'm not scared.
You never know when you're going to die,
so I want to live with that woman.
I don't care if he kills me or not!
What's wrong with you, Honey?
I won't allow it.
Even if the world ends tomorrow,
I refuse to let you die.
You can't die before me.
Don't you know why I got beat up?
I wanted to call it even by getting beaten up!
You don't know how I feel!
Cho Dae Geun. Come to your senses!
If you lived a pitiful life since you were young,
you should at least live properly now!
I'm doing this because I want to live properly!
Don't count your chickens before they hatch!
Did she say she'd get a divorce and come to you?
I met her husband,
and he will never get divorced.
It's my life. Stay out of it.
Both of you stay out of it!
Your life?
You want me to stay out of it?
Why did you hit him?
How dare you hit my husband?
You little brat.
How dare you push my husband?
You shouldn't say that to your brother.
You know he cares more about you than his own kids.
My gosh. There's nothing you can do when someone goes crazy over a girl.
Honey!
Gosh.
I think I should go home early today.
Go ahead.
You were fine for a while, but I guess it's flaring up again.
I'll finish up here and report it to you.
Hold on.
Who are you?
Do you know Cho Dae Geun?
I'm his older brother.
Come here for a second.
Don't see...
Dae Geun anymore.
I'm sorry,
but we're getting together after I get divorced.
As long as I'm alive, I won't allow it.
I can't see my poor brother die.
Die? What do you mean?
When did you see Dae Geun last?
We were supposed to meet today, but he said he had a cold...
and that we should meet another time.
What's wrong with him? What happened?
How hurt is he?
Your father...
hired people to beat him up.
My father?
My father doesn't know we're seeing each other.
Of course, he knows.
This isn't the first time either.
What do you mean?
On the day of your marriage,
didn't you and Dae Geun...
plan to run away after the wedding?
That night, your father hired some thugs...
to beat Dae Geun to a pulp.
He was half dead and passed out in front of my house.
If I didn't see him at dawn on my way out,
Dae Geun...
wouldn't be alive today.
Because he hurt his back that day,
he hasn't been able to do any work that requires labour.
I can't allow it anymore.
I got hurt working in construction.
If you care about my brother, let him go.
His only sin is being poor...
and being uneducated.
If he cherishes his own child,
he should know to cherish other children too.
How much better are you than him...
to ruin his life like this?
Father!
Come here!
What's wrong with her?
- What's wrong? - What did you do Cho Dae Geun?
You hired thugs to beat him up 18 years ago,
and he hurt his back.
This time, he split his head open.
Wait... What are you talking about?
- I don't understand. - Stay out of this, Mom.
- I'm home... - Why did you do it?
Why did you do something so scary?
What is it that you wanted to protect? Money?
Did you do something like that...
to protect the money you saved up?
You didn't marry me off to Nam Chul for my sake.
When you stopped me from divorcing him after his affair,
it wasn't for my sake.
It was to protect your assets.
I won't live according to your will anymore.
I lived according to your wishes up until now,
but I won't be your doll anymore.
Wait... What are you talking about?
Can you help me understand?
I was forced to break up with him because of you,
and I married the wrong person.
I had two kids with him,
but I lived as an empty shell with him.
I want to divorce him.
I want to live the rest of my life with that man.
I don't need your inheritance!
I don't want to be your daughter anymore.
Give up on me,
and let this man live with that young wench.
I'm going to pack my things and move out!
Based on what I just heard,
this is all your fault.
My daughter changed because you cheated on her.
It seems like she started seeing someone else because you cheated,
so you should take responsibility for it.
Does it feel good to divide a daughter from her dad?
Get on your knees and beg for her forgiveness upstairs.
Why are you just standing there?
Go up and comfort her!
I'll leave.
What?
Don't pour gasoline on a fire and just stay quiet!
I'll leave.
You don't have anywhere to go.
Do you have money?
I don't have anywhere to go nor do I have any money.
I already knew...
she was seeing someone.
I even made the effort to make her come back to me.
I pleaded with her,
and I even asked her boyfriend to let her go.
But I'm at my limit.
Since this is how we are,
we will go our separate ways.
- What has gotten into you? - I can't take it anymore!
The humiliation and shame I felt as a man?
I only tolerated it...
for our children.
I put up with it year after year,
and I made it this far by letting you walk all over my pride.
But I can't do it anymore.
We will handle the legal matter gradually.
When I first came here,
I didn't even have a single new pair of underpants,
and that is how I'll leave this house.
You're not kicking me out.
I'm leaving on my own accord.
Goodbye.
But... Hey!
Nam Chul, wait!
My gosh. Mul Sang!
Mul Sang.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
Hurrah!
I'm going to have to ask you to delete the video.
Please know that I can press charges.
- Hello. - Welcome.
As if you have anywhere to go. You're broke, aren't you?
You might die inside at this rate.
You've lived your life putting on a faade,
but this is what came of your hard-working life.
Did you devote your life to a Taffy vendor...
just to end up in this state?
Your daughter stabbed you in the back,
and your son-in-law exploded in your face.
Life was for nothing, and you must be lonely.
Gosh, I'm lonely.
Where's Geum Ah?
She packed her bag but then the other one left,
so she went back upstairs to unpack.
I don't get her, though.
Why is she back with her ex-boyfriend?
And I was the only one who was in the dark.
I also can't believe Nam Chul.
As if leaving this house will do him any good.
He's brazen for someone who's broke.
Just you wait and see.
He'll come back begging for forgiveness.
Hey.
Why did you sleep out here instead of coming in?
Right. I got here too late and couldn't wake you up.
Why did you come here late at night?
Well, I took time off from work.
I couldn't even call in advance though.
Good for you. You should get a break too.
Clear your head and rest all you want.
Thanks, Nam Soon.
Dad will be delighted. Let's go inside.
I bought a few snacks for Dad.
Why did you buy so much when you're broke?
I have money.
Dad, it's Nam Chul.
You didn't eat, though. Will you be all right?
Food isn't the issue right now.
The company needs a boss present.
How else will I know who's tanking my business?
What is it, Mr. Lee?
What?
(Authorized personnel only. Enter at your own risk.)
(This building is planned for demolition.)
(Three Brothers Resources Corp.)
We got here only to see this.
What happened?
Why is it not us that's in charge of the demolition?
I think we've been duped.
Mr. Ji was against the bid, but you insisted...
How much did you wire in advance?
- Four... - What?
We wired four million dollars.
You've got to be kidding me.
Mr. Ko!
Hurry.
What do we do?
What if he doesn't recover from this?
Even if we report it,
it'll take a while to make an arrest.
They immediately leave the country, making it hard to catch them.
I'm afraid we'll need Mr. Ji.
He was against us bidding on this project,
but Mr. Ko insisted.
Ms. Cho.
That's new.
Why aren't you calling Dae Geun first?
Don't give him anything to eat. He won't even listen to his brother.
He has been dealt a rough life, hasn't he?
What does he see in an older woman?
Things would be great...
if he got back together with Eun Byeol.
That's nonsense. She's out of the question.
Others work hard wanting to live,
but you're actively trying to ruin your life.
Do as you wish if you want to sever ties with me.
- Where's Uncle Dae Geun? - Leave him alone.
Something happened.
Ms. Cho, here's a gift for you.
What's this?
It's pretty.
I was thinking about getting a purse like this.
I read your mind, didn't I?
Do you like it?
- It's pretty. - It's genuine cowhide leather.
How much was it?
It was 200 dollars, but I got it for 180.
That was ballsy of you.
It was the least I could do for my daughter's first day at work.
See how it looks on you.
You really look like a teacher.
But she is a real teacher.
You'd look amazing going to work like that.
Thanks, Dad.
I may not be good at choosing women,
but I'm an expert at picking out purses.
What nonsense is that?
As if you could've married someone better. Goodness.
Eun Kang, here's my gift. A pencil case and stamps.
What's that?
She can stamp them on her students' assignments.
"Good job," "You're the best," and "Thumbs up."
The last one is a red balloon.
It's for the student who did the best job.
You love red balloons, right?
Nicely done.
Don't you have anything for her?
Isn't cooking for her enough?
Cook her breakfast early in the morning.
We will now have breakfast when it's appropriate for Ms. Cho.
Raise your hand if you agree.
Mom doesn't have to cook early in the morning.
I'll grab my own breakfast.
Nonsense.
School teachers are hungry all day.
Teaching others drains your energy.
And having breakfast as a family...
is our family tradition.
You know Poong Sang, right?
- The one at the auto shop? - Yes.
I stomped all over his confidence...
while on the phone with him yesterday.
Good for you.
His in-law's second cousin twice removed...
is a high school teacher,
and he rubbed it in our faces.
Didn't you say that his younger sister was a doctor?
He lied. Not everyone can be a doctor.
Tell me about it.
That reminds me. I have to treat my friends...
to a meal when we meet.
It'll cost me at least 100 dollars.
Go ahead. Treat them to a meal.
We should now be able to hold our heads high.
Why should we feel intimidated when our daughter is a success?
- You're right. My goodness. - My goodness.
(Overseas Volunteer Program Schedule)
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Is Mr. Ji doing well?
He doesn't answer my calls, so I'm asking you instead.
Look, Eun San.
The truth is,
Mr. Ji...
(Yongwang Police Station)
Hello?
This is Cho Eun Kang.
How can I help you?
We need you to come in for questioning.
Questioning?
You know Ms. Han Ba Da's design plagiarism case, right?
She is suing you for being an accomplice.
You're the accused. Come in for our investigation.
The accused?
Ba Da.
Ms. Cho Eun Kang?
- Yes. - Ms. Cho.
You stole Ms. Han's design and gave it to Na Bun Nyeon, right?
We confirmed you received money from her.
I didn't steal it.
It was a sketch she threw out.
Tell the truth.
How much did you receive?
I didn't receive any money.
I didn't have a choice. I was threatened...
You received money from her three years ago.
How much did you receive?
I'm just cross-checking the fact.
It was 500 dollars.
It was only that one time three years ago.
I had no idea this was what she'd do.
She asked me to get her a discarded design at least.
A few months ago, you even gave her a design...
for her department store exhibition.
- That's... - Tell her to be honest.
I gave her a discarded sketch.
Who says I discarded it?
You crumpled it, so I thought you threw it out.
Ms. Na threatened me,
and I just gave her what you didn't need.
She kept threatening me with the 500 dollars I got.
She said she'd tell you.
I gave it to her out of fear.
I had no idea she'd make knock-offs with it.
Ba Da, I'm sorry.
She says...
you knew it all and still cooperated.
This means you are an accomplice.
No, I didn't.
I want a confrontation.
Ba Da, it's true. Please believe me.
Are you friends?
- Yes. - No.
She's just a part-timer.
Ms. Na is probably right.
Cho Eun Kang has seen how I've worked for a long time.
She must've known that I reuse discarded sketches.
She had free access to my office.
She could unlock my computer, my safe, and everything.
I once caught her sneaking around on my computer.
- Ba Da... - Did you...
get anything stolen?
I'll recheck my safe.
What she did...
caused my business to go down.
I'm about to get kicked out of the industry.
Please make sure...
she gets punished for her crime.
Ba Da.
The 500 dollars was...
to pay for my mom's appendectomy.
My family was too poor...
to afford anything.
I was so rushed...
that I handed her a design you didn't use.
That dragonfly wing design.
You decided not to manage it because it was a waste of money.
I took the money for my mom,
but I was anxious you might find out.
And Na Bun Nyeon dragged me around over it.
I was a fool.
The sketch you threw out before the exhibition.
I thought you threw it out. I swear.
I meant to cut her off after that last time.
I had no idea she'd make...
bad blood between you and the department store...
and even make counterfeits to cause that refund incident.
It's true.
I never meant anything against you.
Don't beg me.
Beg the judge.
Ba Da.
Just this once.
Please forgive me this once.
We're friends.
Friends?
Ba Da.
Ba Da!
Eun Kang, are you home?
Yes.
I forgot to give this to you.
What is it?
It's from the court.
But why?
It's nothing, Mom.
(Plaintiff: Han Ba Da, Defendant: Cho Eun Kang)
(The defendant will pay 30,009.90 dollars to the plaintiff.)
(The defendant spent a night with the plaintiff's husband.)
What?
(From Han Ba Da, To Cho Eun Kang)
Is it your first time getting sued for adultery?
What?
How does it feel?
I've never been through this before.
I heard everyone got terrified when they received this.
You're a bold girl, so I didn't think you would.
But you seem terrified.
I thought we meant what we talked about on the trip.
Of course, I meant it.
I don't dupe a 20-year-long friend like you.
You wanted to bury everything that happened in the past.
Yes, our 20-year-long friendship.
Don't you get it?
You've become stupid.
I dumped our friendship by the shore.
From now on,
you're not my friend,
but an adulteress I sued.
You stole my design and sold it.
You stole my husband and wrecked my family.
I'm a victim, and you're an assailant.
I'm a plaintiff, and you're a defendant.
First off, you must be punished for making me go down.
You ruined my well-built career.
You caused me to go out of business and end up with this shabby office.
You made me debt-saddled.
You stole my design and sold it.
You'll be punished...
for everything you did.
You saw that the lawsuit said...
I was demanding 30,009.90 dollars, right?
No matter how much you pay, it won't be enough to soothe me.
If it's less than 30,000 dollars, there won't be a written judgement.
I'm demanding 30,000 dollars so it leaves a written judgement.
I'll only get 15,000 to 20,000 dollars anyway.
I'll leave your crime...
on a written judgement...
to make it your life-long scarlet letter.
I doubt you have any sort of fame to your name,
but I'll defame you all I can.
Oh, right.
The 9 dollars and 90 cents is...
for a home-shopping cheap product.
In short,
the 9 dollars and 90 cents is your worth.
Very cheap.
Even if it hurts your pride, put up with it.
You better write a defence paper as soon as possible.
It bears interest from the day you receive the lawsuit.
It's quite high. Was it 12 percent?
Write it within a month.
Be honest and truthful so that the clueless judge...
can see the situation through.
That's what you should do.
One more thing. Cha Won and I are putting off our divorce.
I'll think about it after punishing you first.
Didn't he...
tell you anything about this?
Why would you trust someone else's man and get cheeky?
He is still my man.
I'll take any kind of punishment.
But please...
I can finally put the pieces together.
Your plan moved with every chess piece you played.
Your whole family was the pieces.
My in-laws' housekeeper.
She was your mom.
The taxi driver we called for errands.
It was your dad.
What's more surprising is...
your sister.
What and how much did you gain by introducing them one by one?
This is like the movie, "Parasite."
It was for money.
You can't imagine what it's like to be poor, can you?
We don't get even a single penny for free.
We make ends meet without anything left.
You won't know...
just how tough that is.
I simply wanted them to make more money.
I regret it too.
I never thought things would end up like this.
Look at yourself floundering about after getting caught...
in the trap you set for yourself.
You didn't know this would happen?
I never should've become friends with someone...
who hid the lipstick when everyone gave theirs to the teacher.
Cho Eun Kang. You ruined my life in one go,
but I won't end yours all at once.
I'll kill you...
little by little...
and drain every ounce of blood left in your body.
If you let a cockroach go,
you'll be too nervous to sleep.
You need to kill them completely in a gruesome manner.
Oh, right.
That house is still mine.
Aren't you embarrassed hiding there?
I was going to prove that he was my man,
but I held myself back.
I'm sorry. Ba Da.
Please...
Please forgive me just once.
What do you want me to do?
I'm going to start working soon.
You know how badly I wanted to become a teacher.
- Please help me. - Save your tears.
This is just the beginning.
You adulterer. I'll see you in court.
I was forced to break up with him because of you,
and I married the wrong person.
I had two kids with him,
but I lived as an empty shell with him.
I want to divorce him.
Mr. Ji.
Don't forget me.
Promise me.
Eun San.
Dad, how long is your business trip?
The house feels so empty without you around.
Hurry up and come home.
(Plaintiff: Han Ba Da, Defendant: Cho Eun Kang)
(Defence on the Lawsuit for Adultery)
- What is that? - What?
Are you writing a love letter?
What are you talking about?
I was wrong no matter what.
(I was wrong no matter what.)
(Lawsuit)
(Plaintiff's Demand)
On November 30, 2022,
the defendant purposely sent the plaintiff on a trip to Sokcho...
with the intent of committing adultery with her husband.
She then spent the night...
with the plaintiff's husband in their home.
She put on the plaintiff's robe and used her perfume.
While there's no physical evidence of adultery,
the plaintiff's child confirmed these facts.
On December 10, 2022,
the defendant and the plaintiff's husband...
stayed at Souvenir Hotel and committed adultery.
I have a handwritten letter from the defendant as proof.
I admit to everything.
Your Honour. Please forgive...
(I admit to everything. Your Honour. Please forgive...)
Nam Chul. I brought snacks. Have some makgeolli.
Okay!
(Red Balloon)
Tell me everything you know about that person.
Hurry up and run away.
Why? Does it feel awkward to call yourself an adulterer?
- Eun Kang! - Don't make me curse at you!
You're really mean.
Hold on to me.
If you tell me not to leave, I won't.
Eun San.
You're an animal caught in a trap.
Don't do anything you'll regret. You're bound to regret it.
Ba Da, just kill me.