(Red Balloon)
(Seo Ji Hye)
(Lee Sung Jae)
(Hong Soo Hyun)
(Lee Sang Woo)
(Jung Yu Min)
(Yoon Mi Ra, Yoon Joo Sang, Lee Bo Hee, Jung Bo Seog)
(Kim Hye Seon, Choi Dae Chul, Lee Sang Suk, Seol Jung Hwan)
(Red Balloon)
(All characters, organizations, and events...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(Episode 18)
I get slapped over here.
I get slapped over there.
I've become a punching bag.
This isn't what I wanted.
Nam Chul.
Is there no ending...
where everyone is happy?
People who like talking about others can say,
"That man cheated" or "That woman cheated."
They can gossip and insult others, and nothing comes of it.
But the people involved get affected somehow.
You try to smooth things over on both sides by being the good guy,
but you end up getting pegged as the bad guy.
Eun Kang seemed like...
she had her trust in you.
How do you know that?
I met her on the streets coincidentally.
I know it's not my place to say this,
but you won't be able to...
turn things back to how they were with Ba Da.
If that's the case...
I don't know what to do.
I just wish...
I...
could disappear...
into thin air.
Mi Poong.
You left Mi Poong with your parents.
Goodness.
Another round.
We've already had three rounds.
Ma'am. Ramyeon, please!
You ate ramyeon already.
I wish I could disappear...
into thin air too.
I struggled to become like you.
Can't I be you and live like you?
Eun Kang.
(Cha Won)
I'm sorry.
I don't have any cards up my sleeve.
I don't have anything solid...
to make a decision.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for being a coward.
(Cha Won)
What a pathetic loser.
- Hello. - Mr. Ko?
I'm Cho Eun San, Cho Eun Kang's sister.
I'm heading to your house.
Please come out.
I'm Cho Eun San.
Eun Kang didn't give me your number.
I can check her phone without her knowing,
so don't take it the wrong way.
I saw your pictures too.
I was going to curse at you but didn't want to feel dirty,
so I decided to stop at one slap.
I'll get to the point.
They say people speak the truth when they're drunk.
You're sorry?
Why did you do something you'd be sorry for?
I saw my sister on her phone without saying anything...
listening to that crap in the middle of the night.
I came here because I got mad.
You had fun with your wife's friend for one night,
and when you get caught, you're not going to be responsible?
My sister is enduring everything your family is doing to her.
Do you know how damaging your indecisiveness is?
Are you scared of getting cursed at?
It won't kill you.
Let's end this.
Let go of my sister.
Don't torture her with false hope.
I didn't even know I called.
I was drunk and made a mistake.
Do you even know...
what's happening to my sister?
I've never seen her like this before.
I'm scared she might do something.
What's really annoying is...
that the only person who might be able to save her...
is you.
You should take her side...
so that she can get through the world pointing fingers at her.
But you're running away like a coward.
You shouldn't say sorry...
if you love her.
And you call this love?
You really leave me speechless.
What brings you here at this time?
Where have you been?
I suppose Mi Poong is at your parents' house.
Yes.
I came because I thought you wouldn't be eating proper meals.
I made bean sprout soup with kimchi.
Sit down.
I microwaved instant rice.
I should've come earlier and cooked some rice for you.
You're not even well. It's not good to walk in the cold wind.
Who cares whatever happens to me?
Cha Won,
I was too harsh on you last time.
I'm sorry.
You're at no fault.
It's all because of that girl.
About the divorce...
Please reconsider.
Ba Da only wanted a divorce because her pride was hurt...
and didn't want to deal with it anymore.
But I don't think she really meant it.
She couldn't sleep at all last night.
I bet you don't want to get a divorce too.
I'll talk to Ba Da.
Please just endure...
through whatever she says,
just this time.
Please, Cha Won.
Ten...
Ten thousand dollars?
That's gross!
They said they would settle at 10,000 dollars.
It's a small dent in the bumper.
They want 10,000 dollars?
Why did you bring up becoming a private taxi driver?
He knew your record had to be clean...
and wanted to extort money out of you.
I thought he would be more understanding.
You know what? I believe that all people are born evil,
not good.
I was naive when I was young, so I thought everyone was born good.
But life has taught me that people are the nastiest.
You must be to survive in the world.
Being dense won't get you anywhere.
I can't have an accident on my record.
- Honey. - I don't have it.
- You don't have what? - Whatever it is, I don't have it.
I know that you do. You always say you don't have any money.
I'll pay you interest.
Helping him out must be our priority.
Why don't you just sell me instead?
I knew it wasn't going to last. I thought you wanted to change.
You still haven't changed. You're clinging on to your money.
I can change my last name or my husband.
But when it comes to money, I won't change a thing.
Hey, Eun San.
I'm sorry. But can you help him out?
How dare you ask her for that money? No way.
Keep it safe with you, and set up a store or something.
I'm sorry.
I already spent it.
On what?
I donated it to a volunteer organization.
- What? - What?
The entire 100,000 dollars?
Yes.
It was never my money. Nor did I earn it myself.
Don't you know what that money means?
It was the price of ruining your youth!
How could you give it to people you don't even know?
They never helped you or looked out for you!
You donated all of it?
You didn't even think about it? You just did it?
Could you leave after making that donation?
Get up now. We must go and get it back.
I can't take it back. It's already done.
I don't want to start a business and make a living that way.
Hey! Rich people are supposed to think like that!
Poor people like us don't have that luxury!
- Get up. Let's go and check. - Okay.
Let her be.
Like she said, the money was hers.
It was only fair that she decided what to do with the money.
She might seem fine, but I'm sure this must've been tough on her.
Let that comfort her a bit.
But still. That's a lot of money.
You can donate 1,000 dollars.
Can't you get the rest back?
Dae Bong, stop it.
I didn't want to cause trouble.
What?
That's a huge decision. Why didn't you discuss it first?
I had already decided to go. So I'll just go next week.
I was waiting after I applied for it.
A spot opened up at the last minute, so I said yes.
I got the baking and hairstyling certificates before.
I'm a certified nurse's aide and have a driver's license.
So I'm sure I'll be helpful to someone.
I want to be helpful.
But still. That was sudden.
I told you.
Travelling the world on the RV and volunteering...
had always been my dream.
But I'll put off travelling the world on the RV for now.
I'm okay with everything,
but I'm worried about you.
I want to see you happy before I go.
Don't tell our parents yet.
I'll tell them when it's time.
Eun Kang.
I have a favour to ask.
Give up on him.
Even if he decides to choose you,
this won't work out.
He'll find out everything. What are you going to do?
Mom worked for his parents as a housekeeper.
Dad was the taxi driver who sold used goods to his father.
I should do my best to make it work.
Don't say anything until we decide on anything.
Let's say our parents don't become an issue.
But what about me?
Tell him you don't have any sisters.
Pretend that I'm dead.
How much?
Is he hurt badly?
It was a minor fender bender.
He probably didn't come to work to clear things up.
I see.
I apologize for my behaviour that day.
I bought some Korean beef.
I'm sorry, Ms. Na.
They already filed the divorce papers.
What's the point of coming here?
They will withdraw the divorce papers soon.
It's my daughter's fault for keeping a bad friend.
It's not Cha Won's fault.
She was determined to seduce him.
How could he not fall for it?
Seriously? You're changing your words.
You lied about being sick, didn't you?
You said you were sick. Why are you wearing makeup?
Wearing makeup has been an old habit.
I made sure to wear makeup ever since I got sick...
because I didn't want people to treat me like a patient.
I'm not sure if it is indeed Korean beef.
I bought the most expensive set at a department store.
If my husband were alive,
this wouldn't have happened.
My daughter has no one to rely on other than me.
Please find it in your heart to be understanding.
She had your son's child. She's your daughter-in-law.
In name only.
She didn't do much.
Why do you keep slapping me? That hurts.
- That's so lame. - I'm so sorry.
Mr. Ko. Ms. Na.
If you can overlook what happened,
she'll come back.
What do you mean?
My mother went to see them?
Yes. My father wanted to know if you felt the same way.
No. That will never happen.
Never.
She said it would never happen.
She sounded firm too.
No?
I told you this marriage was over.
I can't believe her mother either.
She got ahead of herself. Look what she did.
My father used to be like that.
That reminds me of Taffy. And I'm craving some now.
I should go and buy some Taffy.
How could you be so immature?
It's not because I'm immature.
I'm just telling you to stop worrying.
Given Cha Won's conditions,
women from good families would line up to marry him.
Gosh.
It's me.
Change the passcode of the house.
Don't let my mom visit you again.
Don't open the door for her either.
Ba Da.
When you get caught, you're not going to be responsible?
I'm scared she might do something.
Eun Kang seemed like she had her trust in you.
Let's not give up.
I want to see where the end of this path is.
I've made my decision.
Are you sleeping?
No.
Come out.
I rushed here because you're the person I missed the most.
You've never...
made me feel uncomfortable.
You must have been so miserable to say all those things to me.
My answer is...
I won't give up on us.
We should see...
where this leads.
Let's see my parents this weekend.
Let me handle the rest.
- Where's Nam Chul? - Hello, sir.
He had a meeting with a business partner.
Call him.
Goodness.
I didn't bid for it.
I've been hearing some weird things, so I'm looking into it.
What's there to look into?
I taught you how to fish. Then bring me fish.
This is a ten-million-dollar deal.
Let me look into this more and...
There's no need. I already put in the bid.
What?
Father. You can't do that.
I'm on my way to the office now.
Please wait.
Father!
Sir!
Father.
Father, the demolition project...
Forget it.
This is why I can't retire.
Must I be looking into this too?
Can't you do your job?
Gosh. I'm so lonely.
But...
He won the bid with 8 million dollars, not 10.
They wanted the down payment, so I just wired the money.
How much?
It was supposed to be ten percent.
But since they lowered the price, they wanted 50 percent.
What?
Then...
You wired them four million dollars?
The chairman said he knew them.
How could you wire the money? You should have stopped him.
You know that he doesn't listen to me.
What do we do?
I also heard that con artists were involved in the bidding process.
(Under surveillance)
Geum Ah.
Why couldn't I get hold of you?
You didn't answer your phone.
I heard you were trying to resolve an accident.
How did it go? Did it not go well?
Well,
it went well.
I had to get a lot of documents...
and go to the auto shop. So I was busy.
I have to head back to the auto shop again.
I'll call you later.
Dae Geun, I know you.
You can't look me in the eye now.
Be honest.
What happened?
Tell me.
Your husband came to me.
My husband did?
What did he say? Did he curse at you or hit you?
No.
He never said anything bad to me.
He only talked like a gentleman.
He begged me not to see you.
I don't care.
I care.
Geum Ah.
Let's be more patient.
That breaks my heart.
That's what you said to me before.
Then you left me after a few days and disappeared.
Are you having second thoughts after seeing my husband?
My ex-wife cheated on me with another guy too.
So I can understand how he must feel now.
Dealing with this must've been difficult as a man.
But he didn't even curse at me.
I beat up the guy my ex-wife cheated on me with.
I want to give him...
what he wants even if it's for a while.
I at least want to pretend I'm trying.
There's no need to do that.
I'm thinking about divorcing him.
I'll get what I want now.
My father forced me to marry him. I had never wanted him.
Even when I had children,
I felt empty inside as if I had been shot in the heart.
I want to spend...
the rest of my life with you.
I'm not scared of my dad anymore.
Your wife still hasn't come to her senses.
She even went to my husband's work.
Do you know how dangerous an affair can be to a woman?
She'll throw away her children and leave home.
Are you sure...
you're okay with your children finding out about her affair?
Your son seemed like a smart boy.
If you approach my children,
I won't be so nice.
You'd better handle this by today. Or I don't know what I'll do.
No wonder why she's cheating on you. Look at you.
- What? - You're not scary.
You ought to teach her a lesson even if you have to hit her.
You'd better handle this by today.
I'm home.
Why did you go to him?
You've already talked to me. Why did you go to him?
Stop seeing him.
How could you show up at his work?
Did you have me followed now?
I can't believe you went that far.
You're so awful.
Yes, I am.
That's why I'm in this marriage.
No more of this. You've done enough.
Think about our children.
Don't get back at me like this.
This has nothing to do with you.
Did you think I was seeing him to get back at you?
Why would I do that when I have zero feelings for you?
We're not like you and that tramp.
You must have fallen for her because you liked her young body.
Our relationship isn't like your worthless affair.
What we share is real. It's real love.
I don't care if it's real or not.
That doesn't matter. Listen to me.
If you see him again tomorrow, it's over.
Don't you know we live here too?
Why are you yelling?
I'm sorry.
Is it because Geum Ah went out?
She had to meet her friends to get comforted.
You cheated on her.
That's so lame!
Do you want to have a meal?
I'm not hungry.
You're the first person I wanted to put on my family registry.
What?
Why don't you ask me to share the trash bags?
Or the mileage points.
Don't waste your energy.
I'm going abroad next week for a volunteer abroad program.
Next week? To where?
Will you follow me?
I'm ready to leave at any moment.
Look. I always carry my passport with me.
This is the new version too. Did you know?
(Republic of Korea, Passport)
I'll buy you a roll of gimbap. You can eat that.
Thank you for processing the severance pay.
I met with Ms. Cho Eun San during lunch.
She said she was leaving next week abroad for a volunteer program.
Don't tell me about her.
Okay.
I ordered the expensive black herb tea on purpose.
I asked them to add the egg yolk. Like the traditional recipe.
I'm buying, sir.
What's this about? You've been quiet for a while.
Today,
I've been thinking about my relationship with you...
What is it?
Nam Chul did?
Why would he raise his voice?
Let's talk at home. Bye.
Gosh, I'm so lonely.
I had all sorts of mixed feelings, and it made me feel surreal.
I remember the first time we met.
Your RV ran out of gas in the countryside.
So you were on the road, not knowing what to do.
I was passing by at that moment and spotted you.
I went to the gas station and brought you gas.
It was a very cold day in winter. Imagine if I wasn't there to help.
You remember that, right?
Of course.
I also remember paying you handsomely.
"Handsomely" would be going too far.
Afterwards, I hooked you up with cheap camping items.
The bond between you and I...
must be quite strong.
You're bragging a lot today. Is this about money?
I knew it.
You're so cool.
I wouldn't lend money even to the deity of the black herbal tea.
Lending or borrowing money.
I had never done that in my life.
I'm buying you this...
even if you don't lend me money.
Please drink it.
This is such an urgent matter.
Chairman Ko, please help me.
I'll make sure to pay for the interest too.
How about 10,000 dollars?
That's it.
Gosh, I'm so lonely.
Everyone is making me feel lonely.
Chairman Ko!
I'm on my way.
I was meeting up with a taxi driver I knew.
He suddenly brought up money.
How could he ask for 10,000 dollars? We're not even close.
When you befriend poor people,
they always end up asking for money.
This is why I don't meet people.
Gosh, I'm so lonely.
Sir, can you stop over there?
It's 18 dollars.
Get out.
Darn it.
Hey, you punks! Stop right there!
Let's run.
You jerks!
Don't look down on people.
I'm not letting you go because I can't catch you.
You should pay for your ride!
How could you dash without paying for it, you punks?
You shouldn't do that.
(2023 Teacher Certification Exam, Cho Eun Kang, congratulations.)
My gosh. No way!
Ba Da...
My gosh.
Is this for real?
What is it? Did she win the lottery?
Our daughter is now a teacher.
What? Let me see.
Goodness.
Eun Kang, no way! Congratulations.
Eun Kang, you're the best!
I knew it. I knew you'd become a teacher.
Ban Sook, you're lying through your teeth.
Didn't you tell her to learn how to drive a taxi?
That was my way of getting her to study harder.
You're just clueless.
For the first time, I chuckled at what wasn't money.
Have you been secretly studying?
None of us knew.
I was going to tell you after I passed.
She can be so sneaky.
She's considerate, not sneaky.
- She's tight-lipped as well. - Well,
I know what it's like to be tight.
I'm tight here and there, aren't I?
This is the best day of my life!
Who dares to belittle me?
I may not seem like it, but I'm a teacher's father.
Don't think less of me!
And I'm...
her uncle.
And I'm her mother.
And I'm her younger sister.
Things are finally looking up for our family.
Let's now buy a house of our own and go on trips abroad.
Darn you, ladies!
My daughter is now a certified teacher.
Are you that happy?
- Must you ask? - Must you ask?
All our troubles have been washed away.
Now that you're a teacher,
decent men will want your hand in marriage.
Choose the best of the best,
date him, and then marry him.
This is where your happiness begins.
Aren't I right, Ms. Cho?
Even at home, we'll address her as a teacher.
- Of course. - Of course.
Ms. Cho, I'll prepare the party.
Ms. Cho, do you want galbijim?
Dae Bong, this calls for a performance.
Of course.
There's nothing I won't do for Ms. Cho.
We are back from our tour in South-East Asia.
I am Cho Dae Bong.
And I am Cho Dae Geun.
The brothers will put on...
a congratulatory performance for you.
Cue, music.
Eun Kang.
Ms. Na Bun Nyeon.
We're the police.
You have the wrong person.
Get her!
Move.
- Get her. - Got it.
- Go! - Right.
Ma'am.
All right, fine. I'll come with you.
I couldn't sleep at all.
- How do I look? - You look pretty.
Look at it fly away.
You're pretty and so is the balloon.
I have something to tell you.
I...
passed.
I'll be appointed to a school before the new semester begins.
Really?
You worked hard.
One of your dreams has finally come true.
You're admirable.
Come on in.
- Mom. - What?
- What brings you by during the day? - Hey.
I had something to tell you.
- Dad's home, right? - He probably is.
Why are you there and not coming in?
Come on in.
- Mul Sang, get out here! - Dad!
What's all this fuss? Why are you all calling for me?
Dad, Mom. I apologize for my behaviour.
From now on,
she is who I'll be with.
It has been a bumpy ride,
but I believe that we were meant to end up together.
I will cleanly end my relationship with Ba Da.
What do we do? Should we kick them out?
Have a seat for now.
Before you say anything, we have good news to share.
She is...
See? I knew it.
Hey! Are you pregnant?
Mom, I mean she passed the exam.
She's now a certified teacher.
Really?
This is why one shouldn't be mean to youngsters.
Go and get us some tea.
Got it, Mom.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Geum Ah.
Get over there. My dad must have something to say.
Cha Won, I read the letter you wrote.
No wonder. I knew it was weird...
that your father didn't yell.
If that's what you want,
and if you're sincere about her, I won't object.
But your divorce is yet to be finalized.
We'll revisit this in a year's time.
I'm not saying I want to marry her right away.
I'm just telling you where I stand.
Mi Poong is who I'm worried about.
Make sure that she isn't hurt in the process.
I'll keep that in mind.
This is great. You can get married next year.
One should live with the one they love.
Ba Da threw away her own fortune.
What if she doesn't agree to the divorce...
because she's annoyed by their relationship?
You said no one was allowed to divorce...
and kept Nam Chul in the family.
Are you really going to allow this?
Who knows what'll happen in a year?
Being on bad terms with my son will only make me lonely.
I'm putting a lid on it and letting it pass for now.
- No wonder. - Besides,
Nam Chul and Cha Won aren't the same.
Cha Won can live his life the way he wants,
but our family can't function without Nam Chul.
My dad was correct.
He told me to be aware of those who were different on the inside.
Being that way is how our marriage lasted.
You just don't know what's important.
You stole my saying. "Gosh, I'm lonely."
You're so lame.
My heart was pounding in there.
You didn't seem nervous at all.
I thought they'd yell at me and kick me out.
I didn't know you had sent your father a letter.
I told you to trust me.
When should I meet your parents?
Maybe sometime later.
We'll soon be moving to a new house anyway.
He said we should marry next year, so you can meet them then.
I'm curious, and I can't wait to meet them.
Get in. We have somewhere to go.
My gosh.
I don't think this suits me.
I haven't worn a suit this expensive before.
It looks perfect on you.
It's my gift to Cho Eun Kang, the teacher.
That's not how a teacher should be.
One shouldn't be like this in front of her students.
Stand up straight, Ko Cha Won.
How dare you look at a teacher with lust in your eyes?
Follow me to the teacher's lounge.
Thanks, Cha Won.
I'll wear it on my first day. I'm super excited.
And I love to see you excited.
Let's go buy some shoes.
You should get ones in a matching colour.
Oh, dear.
In return, I'll take you out for a meal.
Not meat in boiling water but grilled Korean beef.
I already made reservations for a full-course meal,
Ms. Cho.
Mom, let's replenish our energy today.
I came here before, and the food was nice.
I can see why.
You should be the one eating more, though.
You've lost weight.
It's our first time dining out together.
You're right.
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Boo!
It's not a dream, right?
That was so mean of you.
I'll go buy some wet wipes at the convenience store.
I have a call to make.
Head inside first and order for us.
The beef looks incredible.
Before, we used to eat at restaurants...
where the servers grilled our meat for us.
I'll do the grilling for you instead.
I'm off to the restroom.
- We booked a room, right? - Yes.
My gosh. Ba Da!
Goodness.
Why couldn't I get a hold of you?
Hey, Il Sook. It's been a while.
What on earth is going on?
We'll talk some other time.
It's best not to keep your friends waiting.
I can't believe what's happening.
My husband told me...
they were getting married.
His family already approved,
and that tramp even passed the Teacher Certification Exam.
We'll talk some other time.
How can fate be so cruel?
Someone who stole a friend's husband shouldn't be living the good life.
I can't believe you either.
How could you let someone like her steal your husband?
I told you before to watch out for her.
You said you'd never let someone like her steal your husband,
but look at what happened.
Il Sook, please.
I'm furious, that's all.
Your in-laws have gone insane.
How could they accept that tramp?
They approved...
of that tramp?
That's right.
Mother, how could I not be furious right now?
Our friends kept saying bad things about you too,
so I gave them a piece of my mind.
They were making fun of you...
for being a loser who lost her husband to that tramp.
Just stop.
- Mom, let's go. - Once she finishes.
There's nothing to hear.
But the meat...
Ba Da, call me, all right?
There you go. Thank you.
I sure am glad to see you.
Did you think you'd live happily ever after?
- Mom. - You!
You'll get what you deserve, you tramp!
You won't live happily ever after.
Got it, Director Shin. I'll take care of it.
- I said I got it. - That tramp.
She'll get what's coming.
How dare she?
Let's hang up. I'll be right there.
That's her, right?
It's her.
Remember the video on the online caf for moms?
The wife slapped her husband and his mistress who was her friend.
You're right.
The one who left is the wife, and she's the friend.
My gosh. I can't believe it.
You there.
Did you come for a barbecue after betraying your friend?
How can you even eat?
How dare you seduce your friend's husband?
Tell me about it.
You look like the type to be good at it too.
She should be publicly humiliated...
so that she can't dare to go anywhere.
- Let's go. - That's him.
Look at them both taking off.
Hey! You won't be able to live your life in Korea.
The video of you is all over the Internet.
This is bad.
Clients have been cancelling their appointments.
Are we supposed to post an apology on our website?
What on earth is going on?
Someone as smart as you should've seen this coming.
Why did you stay at the caf?
You should've left or told them not to film.
Both weren't an option.
I had to sit there and take it.
Videos like this can't be taken down after they spread.
We reported it to the police, so let's be patient.
That reminds me.
Your school.
The parents won't let this slide.
(Cho Eun Kang)
Hello,
I'm Cho Eun Kang who will teach Korean.
I hope we get along.
Hey.
You call yourself a teacher?
I won't let a home wrecker teach my child.
Get out here.
Get out here!
- I'm sorry. - How dare you teach our children?
How dare you?
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
Your father must be heartbroken...
to see the way we're living.
He won't be.
I'm sure Dad will come to us with a smile.
Please don't cry during the ancestral rite.
(We're celebrating our first anniversary!)
- Hurry. - What?
Why are you calling me here when I'm busy?
It's one gift per person.
We shouldn't pass up on freebies.
Right. Thank you.
Hello.
Gosh, we meet for the first time.
Mom.
- You should take one too. - Gosh.
- Unbelievable. - Let's go.
- I can't believe you. - Thank you.
- She's the company bookkeeper. - I see.
Mom, can you go home without me?
What is this about?
I'm sorry to ask you this,
but I will, despite being rude.
The bookkeeper at the company.
Is she Cho Eun Kang's little sister?
What?
No.
She's not.
Be honest with me.
It's important to me.
The relationship is over anyway,
so there's no reason for you to hide it.
She has nothing...
to do with Ms. Cho.
I only came by to confirm what I know.
The helper at the house.
She's Eun Kang's mother.
Mom, the home shopping channel called me in urgently.
I'll head home once I'm done.
Don't cook the food without me, okay?
- I won't be long. - Really?
Han Ba Da?
That's right. She stole someone else's design.
That's why the exhibition...
at the department store got cancelled.
The original designer released knockoffs...
to teach her a lesson.
So she was running a business by stealing others' designs?
That fraud.
Winning the Grand Award at the International Jewellery Awards...
- must also be a lie, then. - Probably.
Ma'am.
I was going to go by your residence next week.
What brings you by?
No wonder you stopped me from coming to your office.
- I can't believe it. - Gosh.
Please have a seat.
There's no need for that.
I heard your business tanked.
Are the rumours true?
Those are groundless rumours.
Business is as usual.
I just moved to a new office, that's all.
I'll soon be moving to a bigger one.
The wedding gift for your younger daughter-in-law...
Forget about it.
I don't trust you enough.
Return the deposit...
and terminate our contract.
Ma'am. I'm Han Ba Da.
Don't you trust me? You know me.
People don't lie. Money does.
How would I know if your jewellery is real or fake?
Don't think my words are too harsh.
Think about it from my perspective.
What could you do in a place like this?
I'll send my secretary, so take care of this.
Wait a second.
I already sent it to the factory,
so it'll be ready next week.
- If you cancel your order now... - That's not my concern.
If your company went under,
you should've told me honestly!
Ma'am...
Ma'am!
(Ba Da's Father's Death Anniversary)
Who is it?
Why are you here?
Did you enjoy the meat that day?
Did the meat taste good...
after you drove your friend into a corner?
I'm sorry.
I know it's Father's memorial today.
I brought some Jeon.
I always got it for you for his memorial.
You're so brazen.
How dare you show your face here?
Ba Da's father would roll over in his grave.
Looking at you makes me sick, so get out!
This brat brought Jeon.
She's so thick-skinned.
That's why she could seduce her friend's husband!
My father wouldn't want to see you, either.
Leave and take this with you.
Let me go!
- Let's go inside. - I should teach her a lesson.
Let go of me!
We should tear her apart! How could you just let her go?
Ever since she was young, she was conniving...
and then she'd stab you in the back!
That's enough, Mom.
I can't just let her go. Let go of me!
Let go of me!
Leave!
Did you know that today was your wedding anniversary with Ba Da?
How could you make someone so pitiful?
Why didn't you get what we were trying to tell you?
I heard you guys were getting married.
Is that true?
Today's my father's memorial. I want to spend it quietly.
I will sign the divorce papers...
when the time comes, so leave.
Why would you sign it?
Who will it benefit?
Don't you dare sign them!
You should torture them!
Do you think you'll be happy?
Do you think you'll be happy...
after ruining my daughter's life?
Ba Da's father's watching you!
You evil jerks!
I can't let them go like this. Let go of me!
Let go. This is so unfair, Ba Da.
This is so unfair, Ba Da!
Let go of me.
Let's start, Mom.
Yes?
Yes.
You caught Na Bun Nyeon?
Okay. I'll be right there!
Mom. I'll be right back.
Where are you going?
Na Bun Nyeon ran off to China...
and got caught at the airport two days ago.
How could you do this to me?
What kind of grudge do you have against me?
I can't forgive you.
Hey.
You did this to yourself.
You ended up like this because you're a know-it-all who meddles.
Is this because you got pushed out of the association...
and the home shopping network?
This is theft and fraud.
She was already wanted for fraud...
for cases other than yours.
Make sure she gets punished.
Is Cho Eun Kang doing well?
Think of it as punishment for making bad friends.
What are you saying?
I stole what was yours?
Do you think I went to your office?
Or that I went through your safe or your computer?
I'm not afraid of anything, so I'll tell you everything.
This is all Cho Eun Kang's doing.
There's no way.
You want evidence?
This is the original.
What was submitted to the department store was a copy.
This is yours. Isn't it?
These are the texts I exchanged with her.
(Should I tell your friend that I paid you to help me?)
(I understand. I'll send it to you.)
(I told you not to contact me, so why do you keep calling?)
These are the phone records.
(Cho Eun Kang)
Why else would I call her?
If I wanted to punish you,
all I had to was release something that looked exactly like yours.
That's why I paid her.
I can't believe you called her a friend.
The video was leaked. What should I do about your school?
Eun Kang. Hey.
Honey.
Please watch over Ba Da.
I have no other wish.
Please resolve Ba Da's sorrow.
Our poor Ba Da...
She's living in complete misery right now.
Mom.
When I was young, whenever I saw a cockroach,
I used to scream and run away. Remember?
You were particularly afraid of cockroaches.
One day, I was home alone,
and a cockroach came out.
It was so gross and scary,
but I thought it'd be scarier if I didn't kill it.
So...
I got the roach spray...
and started spraying it at the cockroach.
It kept struggling as it ran away,
and it'd start struggling and then run away.
It wouldn't die easily.
I...
kept following it around and spraying it.
I kept spraying until it was covered in the spray and knocked out.
Once the cockroach died and its wings and feet stopped moving,
it was smaller than I thought it was.
I grabbed a bunch of tissues...
and picked up the cockroach.
I squeezed it into pieces with my hands...
and threw it in the toilet and flushed.
I finally felt relief and was proud of myself.
I guess I forgot how to catch cockroaches.
I remember now.
You shouldn't...
let go of cockroaches.
You have to make sure...
you kill them in the most gruesome way.
Was Mi Poong all right last night?
There was so much thunder and lightning.
I slept with her.
Good job.
The reason why I asked you to meet me so early in the morning...
was because I wanted to apologize.
When everything happened,
I felt like I'd go crazy over the anger I felt toward you guys.
But after some time passed,
I began to wonder if it was my fault.
I thought, "What if I had done this? or what if I had done that?"
I thought about every moment,
and it was so painful.
I thought I ended up like this because I was immature and foolish.
I didn't want to admit that it was my mistake,
so I kept trying to blame other people.
I said all sorts of terrible things out of anger that day.
I take back calling you a cockroach.
I'm sorry for saying you were the worst.
You're not.
Honey.
Thank you for putting up with me for the past seven years.
I made you suffer every time I had trouble with your mother.
And paying off my father's debt...
and pushing off having a second child...
weren't things I should've decided on my own.
I'm sorry.
I understand why you were mistaken about Shin Ki Han.
Ki Han's feelings crossed the line a little,
but he's really just a friend.
It's my fault you were mistaken.
The biggest mistake I made...
was keeping Eun Kang by my side.
I would've been shaken too.
I understand it.
It's my fault.
I ignored you,
and I looked down on Eun Kang.
More than anything, our dear Mi Poong...
I was so invested in my feelings that I didn't prioritize her.
I really don't deserve to call myself her mom.
After living apart from you,
I reflected on myself.
After my father's business failed,
and your family was against our marriage,
you grabbed my hand and said you'd die without me.
I thought that I should put you on a pedestal for the rest of my life.
My feelings are so fickle.
Once something I never imagined happened to me,
I packed my things and left.
It wasn't like me.
I should've stopped myself.
I'm sorry.
I had so much to say, but I'm all over the place.
I'll just be honest.
I don't want to lose...
a good man like you.
But it's not like I can pretend it never happened.
I want to be neutral and think about it.
We need to heal from the wounds we gave each other.
Let's do that.
Let's not tell the adults,
and let's keep it between us until we make a decision.
Do you have any objections?
Let's meet over the weekend with Mi Poong.
I'm coming back home from Italy.
Tell Mi Poong that.
I'll call you.
(Text messages, Han Ba Da)
Do you want to go on a trip?
I want to resolve our issues.
What do you think about going to the beach in Sokcho,
the place we took our first trip together during winter break...
our freshman year of high school?
Sounds good. When?
Right now.
Okay. Let's go.
I rented it.
Let's have fun during our overnight trip.
Seatbelt.
Right.
It's too quiet. Let's talk.
What should we talk about?
Anything.
Can you liven the mood?
How should I liven the mood?
Ba Da.
I passed.
I heard. Congratulations.
After I found out, I ran to the old office.
I went there inadvertently when I heard the good news.
Everything is starting to feel like spring.
The sunshine and wind are different too.
I think the flowers will start blooming soon.
Time flies by so fast. Right?
Is it fast for you?
What?
What do you want to eat?
Should we get sashimi since we're going to the beach?
What about cold raw fish soup? I know it's your favourite.
I'll look up a good restaurant.
When we went on trips together,
we used to laugh and talk as soon as we left.
I know.
Do you want me to look up some fun Memes for you?
Or do you want to listen to music?
It's fine.
According to the police investigation,
the suspect threw the victim into the ocean...
and strangled them to death.
It was revealed that the suspect and victim...
were friends for 30 years.
The suspect, who was in debt,
lured the victim out by suggesting they go on a trip.
The suspect put sleeping pills in a drink and drugged the victim...
and even gave them alcohol.
The suspect then led the intoxicated victim to the beach...
That's terrible.
I'm glad we didn't get involved financially.
Right?
Yes.
Do you want coffee?
Sure.
The closest rest stop...
No, check the bag in the back.
I bought us some coffee.
I asked them to put it in a tumbler, so we can drink it until tomorrow.
I also bought some snacks.
Why did you bring a knife?
They don't give you knives at hotels.
I wanted to eat some apples.
But you don't eat peeled apples.
We have to cut them.
What are you going to do if you chip a tooth biting into an apple?
I'm fine. You can have it.
It's good.
They have good coffee.
The suspect put sleeping pills in a drink and drugged the victim...
Aren't you going to drink it?
Oh, right.
I had some coffee before I came out.
I'll drink some later.
Why? Do you think I drugged it?
We shouldn't have listened to the news.
- It's nothing like that. - Don't you trust me?
I do.
Then drink it.
- What? - That coffee...
If you don't trust me, don't drink it.
If you do, drink it.
(Red Balloon)
I never meant to make you go under.
Please forgive me just this once.
We're friends.
- Friends? - Ba Da!
Go beg the presiding judge.
I want to divorce him!
Since it ended up like this,
let's go our separate ways.
Don't tell anyone and come out.
We may have submitted our divorce papers,
but he's still my man.
I feel excited for some reason.
Just like when we first met.