Why'd you call us up to the rooftop?
Here. I wanted to give it back.
Cheon Namhee, is this yours?
His name isn't Cheon Namhee.
It's Cheon Namwook.
Yeah! That's ours!
Ours?
You can have it back if you go on a date with me.
He'll go on a date with you if you give it back.
I will?
You must not need it.
No!
Calm down.
- Careful.
- Don't do it.
Buy a first date gift?
Yeah.
With what money? You're broke.
With what I made at my part-time job.
You have to chip in for rent, not buy a gift!
This is pretty, isn't it?
It is pretty.
I'll get this then.
Hey! Focus on getting on your landlord's good side!
I've made things too easy for you, huh?
Why am I so sleepy today?
Today?
You always nod off.
Did you pull an all-nighter?
Of course, he wouldn't.
Why is everyone studying so hard?
Minjung, even you?
I have a conscience, you know.
The exams are in an hour.
What? That was today?
Namwook was very sleepy,
so he spent most of the exam napping.
And then,
the three days of exams came to an end.
Cheon. Nam. Joon.
Hey, is it hot in here?
No, not really.
I guess it's just you that's hot.
At least someone appreciates me for what I am.
What do you want to do on our date? Where should we go?
He can't get it back like that.
Get what back?
Oh. My pen.
I lent it to him.
- Where's Namwook?
- He has a date.
He does?
With who?
Tell me!
Let's get out of here and have some fun.
That's random.
What? Love that idea.
Where do you want to go?
Karaoke? Ice cream?
Asked him out on a date?
I did?
I asked Namho out? Why?
Namwook is on a date with her?
Why are you all here?
Are you waiting for me?
♫  Almost Paradise. Brighter than the morning  ♫
A must-have for hot guys is military boots to match his outfit.
Tuck your pants into the boots.
Want to know what's trendy?
Chains are good.
Wear a black vest with a white t-shirt.
Making sure you look stylish.
Add a fedora for a modern, trendy look.
It'll add a little flair to any mundane look.
What the heck is he wearing?
I just gave him a nice haircut!
Ina will surely decide not to see him again.
Is he insane?
Your incredible sense of style makes me fall for you harder!
You look like you're from 2010.
They say retro is the most stylish of all.
A style icon indeed.
Alert the fashion industry that
the revolution has begun.
Mind if I sit with you?
I'd like to sit at the same table as the man who revolutionized fashion.
In that case, absolutely.
That darn Namwook effect.
Why would I sit with you?
I take that back.
Are you Noh Yejoon of Yeonli High?
Yes. That's me.
I'm a huge fan!
Can we get a picture with you?
Of course.
Can you by any chance...
Oh. Me too, huh?
I'm feeling a bit shy.
Please take it however you want.
Oh. Right.
What a real celeb you are!
Get any more famous and we won't be able to ride the metro together anymore.
Whatever.
Don't worry about it.
Namki, you're the only real celebrity I see.
Ah.
No thanks.
I only want to be a celebrity to one person.
Yeah?
I guess that comic book isn't all that important.
I guess I can just keep...
You make a cute couple.
Thanks. You two make a cute couple, too.
- You two?
- You.
- Whatever!
Just look at you two.
Just a minute.
My intuition is telling me something.
- About what?
- Who is it?
Her? Or Sunnyeo?
- What's that?
- This is a selfie you took with Matilda. She posted it.
I'm allowed to do readings with my co-star.
Then, is it Sunnyeo?
Right.
Pool halls are best for hanging out in a group.
Pool halls are so out these days.
What? I think it'll be fun.
You're so awesome!
Namjoon, how do you play pool?
Stretch your left arm out to create a straight line
between the bridge and your grip.
How?
Will you help me with my stance?
Sunnyeo, have you ever played pool?
Of course not.
- Put your arm out like this.
- Like this?
Keep your torso still.
Keep this part steady.
- Keep what steady?
- Over here.
Play and bet something!
I think I got it.
There's one thing I'm not good at.
Losing at a game I want to win.
Like right now. I want to beat her so bad.
Do what I did.
- What are you doing?
- This darn chalk!
Sunnyeo, it's all over my hand now!
You go like this.
Namjoon!
Not there. A bit higher.
You can't do it for her!
Hit it very lightly.
- There you go!
- Nice!
- It went in!
- You win!
Woohoo!
Nice!
What are you doing?
Sorry.
Thank you.
This is all we get? Weak.
That's true.
How about losers buy dinner? What'd you say?
Sorry.
We have somewhere to be.
We do?
As in you and me?
Bye.
Where are you taking me?
Can't you tell me?
Come with me and you'll find out.
I'll give you your comic back, too.
I have to get going, too.
I have lines to memorize.
I figured you were hanging out more than usual.
Bye, superstar.
Sunnyeo.
Yeah?
I'm leaving.
Oh. Okay. Bye.
- Who do you like more?
- What are you talking about?
The man of destiny your mom made for you or Yejoon, your friend?
I thought it was Namwook this whole time,
but I realized today the better, more modern-day story would be to choose
Yejoon over Namook, don't you think?
What are you talking about?
Hey! I'm not your comic book character!
I don't have to live my life the way you want me to.
I'm not saying you have to.
Why? Who do you like more?
I'll help you get who you want!
What? She didn't give it to you?
She said she left the comic book at home.
And you believed her?
She's just trying to get more dates out of you!
- You think?
- So? Are you two going out again?
- When?
- Tomorrow.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Why do you ask? Jealous?
You're even cuter when you're jealous, Kitten.
Jealous? No way.
I'm just worried you won't get the comic book back.
I'll get it from her tomorrow, no matter what.
Don't. I'll get it from her.
I can't believe this. Can it be more awkward?
If you dress like yesterday, I'm never hanging out with you again.
I'm okay with looking awkward since you picked it out for me.
Are you going to keep following me?
Why? Can't I come with you?
When Ina sees you, the Namwook effect may get worse.
Ina, Namwook...
You came in his stead?
What a relief.
Right. Well, did you bring the comic book?
Yup.
I'm sorry it took me so long to return it.
I feel so out of control lately.
Sunnyeo, I think you're really amazing.
The Sunnyeo from the comic book
can't compare to you.
I see.
Thanks.
I don't know why I tormented you like that.
Why do I even like Cheon Nami?
It's probably not your fault.
It's yours.
Is that what you thought I'd say, just like that?
Hey!
Hey. I'll take this.
I'll put it in your bag.
- Daebak
- What?
I'll send you something interesting.
-   Matilda and Yejoon, new actors who just became a couple.
- OMG.
Yejoon and Matilda became a real couple thanks to the drama?
Is this for real?
I'm hurt. Why didn't he tell me?
What?
Yejoon. An article just popped up saying he's dating Matilda.
Oh. Really?
What are you doing?
About to head home.
Why?
Sunnyeo, I have something to give you.
Something to give me? What?
Tada!
You're giving it to me because you couldn't give it to Ina, huh?
It was for you from the start.
Thanks.
You two were together?
What are you doing here?
What you saw isn't true.
What?
The article isn't true.
I'm not with her.
I don't even like her.
You ran all the way here to tell me that?
- We're here.
- Where are we?
Where I'll confess my feelings for you.
I like you, Namyoung.
I'm sorry.
My name isn't Cheon Namyoung.
And I have feelings for someone else.
Who?
Han Sunnyeo?
I'm sorry.
I only have enough room in my heart for one girl.
You know Sunnyeo and Namwook have a sad ending, don't you?
Your happiness won't last!
She and I have nothing to do with that story.