♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of the first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
♪Every foreshadowing
is for a happily ever after♪
♪There will be storms and hurricanes
but they are not the main themes♪
♪I want to make a montage of you♪
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
♪I'll bottle your tenderness
and thoughtfulness♪
♪I'll indulge all your tantrums♪
♪I'll watch every scene that features you
and replay them in my heart♪
=She And Her Perfect Husband=
=Episode 12=
I figure no one
knows Ms. Lan better than you
so at the moment,
Cheng & Hui
is our best option.
First thing first,
who exactly are we
representing this time?
Ms. Lan
or her husband, Mr. Pang?
Both.
In that case,
we can...
Believe me. Believe Pang.
He isn't like what the rumor says he is.
Luowei Yulan isn't lacking in money.
Why should we
con others for their money?
Someone is slandering
Luowei Yulan, I tell you.
Calm down, Ms. Lan.
Calm down.
Let's set that aside first.
Second question.
Did you partake
in the daily operation of Luowei Yulan?
I...
Wait.
Answer me
once you have thought it through.
By partaking,
I mean using your identity
as an operator of the firm
to sign contracts
to close a deal.
Or perhaps use that identity
to access financial information
before taking out a loan.
Did you
do it?
Please answer honestly.
No.
Okay.
I believe you.
Jin.
Thank you.
You're the first one
who looked into my eyes
and said he believed me.
No one trusts me anymore.
They say I'm a liar.
Those who used to look
and smile at me
now became demons
who want a piece of me.
You have no idea what my life
has become.
I don't even dare to go home.
Fortunately, Danping is here.
Otherwise,
I might truly
kill myself.
Ms. Lan.
This is just the beginning.
It will become worse.
Would you like to hear
our opinion on this?
Go ahead.
Ms. Lan.
Although you are the defendant,
you are not the operator
of Luowei Yulan.
The plaintiff's attorney
does not have any evidence
that proves you were aware of it.
Therefore, it's highly unlikely
that you would be charged
with fraud or illegal fund-raising.
But your husband
is another story.
He is abroad.
This makes him look bad.
He is more likely
to be found guilty.
Fang, Tan.
What do you think?
Fraudulent fund-raising
is a criminal offense.
If the sum
exceeds 2.5 million yuan,
it will be considered as a huge sum.
Not only will all your assets
be confiscated,
you will also get either a life sentence
or death sentence.
It can't be.
Pang isn't a fraudster.
He isn't.
Calm down.
Evidence means everything in court.
The judge will not hand out
death sentence easily either.
Aunt.
Let's let Mr. Jin finish.
Okay.
At the moment,
the operator of Luowei Yulan,
Pang Dingfang,
your husband,
is abroad.
The best way to prove his innocence
is for him to return home.
Next,
I'll ask you the third question.
Go ahead.
Ms. Lan.
Can you make sure
Mr. Pang comes back?
Yes.
If this hasn't happened,
we had agreed
that I would visit my son abroad
for two weeks
and we would come back together.
He even called me yesterday
to reassure me.
He would book a flight ticket
and when he's back, everything
would be all right.
You talked to him?
Yes, he calls me every day
to ask about me.
You told him everything?
Yes.
Shouldn't I?
Miss Qin.
I don't know what your hunch is
but this
sounds familiar.
Mr. Jin.
Just be frank with me.
And now,
I will tell you
the worst-case scenario.
If your husband,
Pang Dingfang, was found guilty,
and he fled abroad with the fund,
then you'll
be in this situation.
Criminally,
if they don't have direct evidence,
Ms. Lan,
you won't be found guilty.
But in civil laws,
you have to shoulder
the debts.
As of speaking, Luowei Yulan
owes two billion yuan.
Your company will turn insolvent
and you will file for bankruptcy.
And then,
the court will liquidate your assets.
Since Mr. Pang will be guilty
of a criminal offense,
according to the relevant laws,
his personal property
will be confiscated
and that includes
community assets.
You have been married to him
for three decades.
If you two did not sign
any prenup,
any property or real estate
under the married couple's name
such as savings, jewelry,
bond, stocks,
or even stock option
will be liquidated
to pay the debt.
And then,
the stocks of Yulan Group
that you own
will be taken away.
Then...
She'll have nothing.
In that case,
even if my uncle did commit a crime,
my aunt shouldn't have
to bear the consequences.
Danping.
Aunt.
If you don't care about yourself,
what about Qiuqiu?
He just started university.
His tuition fee is around 500,000 yuan.
And what shall
he do in the future?
Luowei Yulan
is a sinking ship.
If you don't want to drown with him,
there's only one way.
What way?
Miss Li?
Divorce.
No.
Impossible.
Calm down, Aunt.
We have to prepare
for the worst outcome.
No. This is non-negotiable.
This is just a hypothesis.
The worst-case scenario.
I will hear none of it.
Let's go.
Pang will be back soon.
I won't listen!
Aunt.
Sorry, Mr. Jin.
I'll talk to my aunt
when we go back.
Miss Zhao.
Please think carefully
about my first question.
Who exactly is Cheng & Hui
representing?
If you have the answer,
feel free to contact us.
Thanks, Mr. Jin.
Thank you for what you did today.
I thank you on my aunt's behalf.
I will
talk to her too.
Let's go, Aunt.
Let's go.
Thank you, Mr. Jin.
Mr. Jin sure is something.
He turned down
the case of Luowei Yulan
because it is a divorce case.
It's hard for us
to understand how his mind works.
You only get it now?
When I saw Miss Qin and Miss Li
enter the conference room,
I knew something was going to happen.
Think about it.
Why would two attorneys
from the family department
attend the meeting
for a financial lawsuit?
Miss Qin, Miss Li.
I count on you
to pull through.
If you can win this case,
you two will be famous.
We still don't know who
will handle this case.
We don't even know if they
will come to us or not.
Also,
if Cheng & Hui takes up this case,
it belongs to us.
You're too humble, Miss Qin.
Whether it will happen or not,
it's just a matter of your decision.
Isn't asking people to divorce
the specialty
of the family department?
Mr. Tan.
You are accusing us here.
I get it if others have misconceptions
regarding our department.
But since when
did you stoop to that level?
People from the family department
might also think
those who work
in the criminal case department
are actively persuading people to kill
just so that you can have a case.
I know, right?
If you ever need our service,
we will tell you
to work it out
instead of getting a divorce.
(HOUSEHOLD SECTOR)
Miss Qin.
I don't know what you think of it
but I don't
think I'll take up this case.
It's tricky
for hardly any gain.
What do you think?
You make it sound like
we already have the case in the bag.
Even Hui or Mr. Jin
isn't definitive about it.
I will pay it no mind.
Besides, I have enough cases
until the end of the year.
In my opinion,
I handle someone else's case
but I live my life.
What do you think?
Hello?
Okay. Noted.
I need a favor from you
but don't tell anyone.
Stop whatever
you're doing now.
You will leave early today
and go to your friend
in Xi Mei PR.
Ask him to check
Lan Xiaoting's financial status.
I know
Ms. Lan has been working
with Xi Mei PR
so they should have the info.
Sure, Miss Qin.
Are we
representing Ms. Lan?
No, I didn't say that.
But that doesn't mean
we can't investigate.
I see.
Create an illusion to mislead
your opponent.
Wonderful.
Jot down this address.
It's Pang Dingfang's overseas address.
(Miss Zhao, if possible,)
(can you give me)
(Mr. Pang's oversea address?)
(Better safe than sorry.)
(San Francisco, USA)
Have someone check
Pang Dingfang's situation abroad.
Okay.
Keep a low profile.
Don't...
I'll go now then.
Don't meddle in this case.
What you need to do now
is get into the corporation department.
Just keep it up
and don't make any mistakes.
This case
is a hot potato.
If you screw up,
it will backfire on you.
So?
Your mom surrendered already?
She promised not to
mention marriage
within the next three months.
Really?
Thank goodness!
Praise the lord!
Do you know?
Your mom
calls me
every day.
Honestly,
she is very persistent.
If she's 20 years younger,
she can be an interrogation expert.
I almost gave her the code
to my credit card.
Thank you for doing this.
I'll give you
an extra chicken drumstick later.
Make it two, at least.
Oh, did the agent
find you any good apartments?
Why though?
Don't you have a place to stay already?
I want to move out.
Move out?
Why?
Miss Qin kicked you out?
Aren't you two working together?
Is she kicking away the ladder?
No.
But I can't impose myself like that.
I will affect her life.
What do you mean by you can't?
You were living with her.
That you two were on a symbiotic
partnership.
Also,
you did a huge favor
to her company.
Why can't she let you crash
for a few days?
If you
feel bad about it,
pay her rent then.
It saves you the hassle of finding
an apartment.
Yang.
Who's to say
that nothing will happen
when time goes on?
What I mean
is that looking for an apartment
that fits your criteria
is too difficult.
You manage to cohabitate
with Miss Qin peacefully.
That's like a miracle.
Never have I imagined
that you could
live with another female
other than your mom.
What a miracle.
Qin Shi is the third female.
God of Wealth is second.
It's a female.
If you put it that way,
I have to mention
your ex-girlfriend, Yao...
Yang.
Where are you going?
You're not eating?
Wait for me.
I'm stuck.
Oh my god.
Yang.
Mr. Jin asked me to speak
in the meeting.
Why did he do that?
What do you think?
I think
maybe
I won't be
a trophy attorney this time?
You...
I can't believe this.
You're smart when you're handling cases
but when it comes to another thing,
you become stupid.
Excuse me?
What's your opinion then?
Qin Shi
saved Hui from paying
25 million yuan in damages.
What do you think she is now
in Hui's eyes?
Like a daughter.
The apple of her eye.
If a parent forbids
his or her kid
from taking part in an activity,
what do you think is the reason?
Because the activity brings no profit.
Not only that,
it might harm the kid too.
So,
imagine,
if you're about
to be promoted
to the corporation department
and now, you have to turn back
to handle this complicated case
from the family department,
will you do it?
In that case,
there is no hope for me then.
I spoke too much.
Eat.
I'm not hungry.
See?
You're always like this.
Don't ask me to treat you next time.
You'll treat me.
This is expensive.
Have some. Come on.
(Real Estate Information Spreadsheet)
(Mr. Tao Junhui)
Come in.
Hi, your food is here.
I didn't order any.
Mr. Tao.
Are you sure you didn't order anything?
How long has it been since I last saw
my baby?
Now, you know.
You are
always busy.
I almost forgot what you look like.
Good thing I'm a sensible person.
Otherwise, I would have come way sooner.
You're the most sensible person
in the world.
Of course.
When do you finish work?
Right now.
Getting smarter by the day.
Of course.
You came.
I have to catch the hint somehow.
Right?
What should we eat?
You decide.
Let's have a hotpot back home.
Okay. Let's go.
We'll shop for some ingredients.
All right.
Bye.
What are you doing?
We have a lot of meat in the fridge.
You won't have enough place.
Slice this and cook it inside the hotpot.
It's delicious.
This is red meat.
There is a huge issue
with your diet.
Too much red meat.
It contains a lot
of saturated fatty acid
and is one of the factors
of cardiovascular diseases.
Also, the consumption of meat
is not good for your health.
It's also a symbol of indulgence.
It's not a bad thing.
Being motivated
is a sign of ambitiousness, all right?
Also,
vegetarianism
doesn't mean desireless.
Adam and Eve screwed up
by eating an apple.
I beg to differ.
Adam and Eve were corrupted
not because of the apple,
but because they broke their oath.
The one who seduced them
into breaking the oath
was a snake, an animal.
I've been using this brand.
This one is on sale.
It's famous too.
We need two shopping carts.
Spare me, please.
Tell me.
If you were me,
would you try to take up
Lan Xiaoting's case?
No.
Why?
Because Madam Tang has told you
the pros and cons of it very clearly.
This is a tricky case.
That's why I'm an attorney.
You know,
I actually
want to take this case.
It's not because
I want them to get a divorce.
But based on my experience,
Pang Dingfang
planned his escape
and he has done all the preparations.
You're too negative.
His wife is still here.
It's not about pessimism.
If he
wanted to protect his wife,
he would have fled with her.
Leaving Ms. Lan here
is like leaving a ticking time bomb to her.
You don't get it?
Let me explain.
How goes the lawsuit
against Luowei Yulan?
When is the trial?
The court has made a case
but due to the amount
of information involved,
it will take some time
before we have a date.
How likely are you to win?
Why are you so interested
in my case out of a sudden?
Didn't Cheng & Hui
decide against representing
Luowei Yulan?
I just want to know more
about your work.
Please.
What do you want?
Come clean now.
I have a bet with someone else.
You're the representing attorney
so I bet that you would win the case.
But Pang Dingfang
is abroad.
He won't be able
to come back now.
So even if you win the case,
you cannot distrain.
Everything will be in vain.
What do you mean by I cannot distrain?
It will be difficult. That's all.
We have asked the court to proceed with
property inspection
and property preservation.
Do you like mutton strips?
I like this one too.
This one, it is.
Okay.
Property inspection
and property preservation
have to be carried out, of course.
However,
Lan Xiaoting has retired
from managing the firm for many years.
I believe
she doesn't know much
about the assets she possesses.
In the worst-case scenario,
she possesses negative equity.
In other words, her real property
was leveraged.
Other than Yulan Group,
the properties
under Lan Xiaoting's name,
her numerous high-end beauty centers,
and education centers,
we applied for their seizures.
What?
What what?
You seized them.
Of course.
Asset seizure is the worst.
In terms of property appraisal,
education centers and beauty centers
belong to asset-light businesses.
In the event of bankruptcy,
they won't sell for a lot of money.
If you run it,
it produces a lot of liquidity.
But should panic arise
from the seizure...
It's done for.
Yes.
But
he deserves it.
He only has his greed to blame.
Oh, the benevolent sage,
if everyone has
plain dishes like you every day,
will this society
be full of love?
Profit-seeking
is the nature of capitalism.
The society becomes the way it is
because of capital, isn't that right?
Bringing up anti-consumerism
in a cosmopolitan like Pujiang
is an act
of hypocrisy.
You masked
your negativity
with desireless.
You don't have the right
to say I'm a hypocrite.
Although you may have a valid reason,
you walk the path
of deception.
You live like this
because you seek success.
If you seek
something less ambitious,
maybe you wouldn't have
as many troubles as you do now.
I know what you're trying to say
but is justice achieved through lying
true justice?
You poke at where it hurts the most
so I'll return the same favor.
Have you found an apartment?
I'm on it.
You asked me so many questions.
It's my turn now.
Did Lan Xiaoting
visit Cheng & Hui?
No.
Not at all. No.
Do you know you have this habit?
Whenever you lie,
you repeat the same words.
It's good. It's good.
No. No.
No.
You don't need to lie to me.
Lan Xiaoting has consulted
all law firms in Pujiang
but none
wants to represent her.
Cheng & Hui insisted
that they wouldn't be
the plaintiff's attorney
so it makes sense
for her to turn to you.
And now,
everyone is speculating
if this was a mere coincidence
or of this was planned by Mr. Jin.
He hasn't said he would take
Ms. Lan's case.
Also, he's smart
but he can't
possibly think that many steps ahead.
That's impossible.
Baby, have you done the homework?
You are naive
but your boss
isn't as naive as you.
He plans ahead.
He plans ahead?
Miss Qin.
What a coincidence.
You're having hotpot too?
Sorry, Miss Qin.
I forgot to tell you
that Junhui is my fiance.
The company didn't say you have
to declare all your relationships.
Since Mr. Tao
is your fiance,
then the owner of Xi Mei PR...
It's my dad.
Miss Wu.
You sure kept a low profile.
Miss Qin, don't tell
anyone from the firm about us.
You have such an excellent fiance.
Shouldn't you let everyone know?
It's not about that.
It's about my dad.
Please keep it a secret.
Even to Madam Tang too?
If I were you,
I would proclaim it.
It'll make you look good
because a lot of people
do mind your family background.
Isn't that right, Mr. Tao?
All right. We can eat now.
Hold on.
I'm concocting for you
an exclusive sauce.
I'll wait then.
♪And throws us off our rhythm♪
A little bit of garlic.
♪Because of excuses♪
And lastly,
the final touch.
♪I tentatively begging♪
♪For reasons♪
Miss Qin's Special Sauce.
Fresh out of the oven.
Thank you.
Can I dig in now?
I'll wait for you.
I love to have hotpot in a group.
If you like hotpot,
I'll eat it with you.
Try it. Do you like it?
Come.
♪Hiding the everlasting love
that cannot be given up♪
What's on your mind?
Did you hear her?
I want to have hotpot.
He wants to have hotpot.
I'm serious.
When are you getting married?
The end of this year.
Congratulations.
Thanks, Miss Qin.
Since you're Junhui's schoolmate
and my superior,
I expect you to be there
for our wedding.
Miss Qin is very busy.
How do you know?
It's true.
Nonsense.
If my senior schoolmate sends me
wedding invitation,
I have to attend it.
Don't force yourself.
Not everyone
likes to attend a wedding ceremony.
Considering our relationship,
you don't have to be present.
It's okay.
Junhui, what are you on about?
We're close.
Mr. Tao.
I like your candor.
If everyone
can be like you,
socialization
will become less grueling.
Let's go home.
Miss Qin.
Now that you know
my relationship with Feifei,
please stop asking
her to fish info
of Luowei Yulan from me.
No.
Miss Qin didn't ask me to do that.
She didn't?
No.
Wu Fei is your fiancee
but she's only my subordinate.
I allocate tasks
to my subordinates.
However,
I agree with you.
Wu Fei
will not follow up on this project
so as to avoid
unnecessary conflicts between you two.
Miss Qin, you're mistaken.
There's no conflict whatsoever.
Thank you.
Miss Qin.
I like your arrangement.
You're welcome.
I'm hungry. Let's have hotpot back home.
Miss Qin, we're having hotpot too.
Why don't you join us?
No need.
Enjoy, you two.
Come.
What's wrong with you?
Because of you, my job is gone.
So be it.
I'll take care of you.
Didn't you say
the firm gave you too much work
and you have a cold boss?
When did I say that?
Don't make things up.
Wonderful.
To think that I
have to go to the office
with a smile tomorrow...
I finally achieved
something in my work
but you ruined it in one sentence.
But isn't this great?
You no longer need to coddle her.
You have many
senior lawyers in the firm.
Why can't you work for another one?
It's easy for you to think that.
But I believe Miss Qin
is the best attorney.
If I want to learn something,
I learn from the best.
She isn't worth your time at all.
If you want to practice laws,
I can teach you.
Something's wrong with you today.
Are you hiding something from me?
No. No.
You're imitating me.
You're hiding something from me.
No. No.
Did you two cross each other?
Aren't you hungry?
I want to have hotpot.
Answer me now.
Let's have hotpot back home.
Hurry up. It's hotpot time.
Something's wrong with you.
You drive very fast.
Let me drive.
I think
we should all learn to move on.
Your ex is about to get married
and his fiance
is young and accomplished.
That will
certainly affect you
in one way or another
but
don't get all defeated.
You're accomplished too.
Aren't you pursuing
the life you want?
Am I right?
Car! There is a car.
No.
What no?
Luowei Yulan's case
will not go swimmingly.
Tao Junhui has a bad stomach.
Whenever
he is under pressure,
he'll drink a lot of sodas.
And I noticed
he bought a lot of them.
Besides, he must have known very early
that Wu Fei worked for me.
So what Wu Fei told me
might not be accurate.
You...
So you were
thinking about this?
Yes.
You're hopeless.
Your ambitiousness
has deprived you of the need
for emotional connection.
That doesn't sound too bad.
Aunt.
I bought your favorite
seafood congee.
Aunt.
I'm coming in.
You're still sleeping?
Aunt.
Aunt?
Danping.
Calm down now. Speak slowly.
When did Ms. Lan leave?
(I left to buy something)
(around 7 a.m.)
(My aunt was still there.)
(I was out)
(for 40 minutes.)
I'm so worried now.
Will she do something reckless?
Danping, we need
to remain calm now.
Check if she took her passport with her.
Passport. Passport.
It's still here.
(My aunt won't run away.)
Never.
In this situation,
we need to eliminate all possibilities
one by one
to narrow down the scope.
Danping.
(Give me Ms. Lan's photo)
(and tell me what she wore)
(before she left.)
(Then, list down)
(where she could possibly go.)
Wait at the hotel.
We'll be there now.
I'll drive.
Danping.
The Ms. Lan I know
is not weak-willed.
Trust me.
She did not rely
on sheer luck to get
what she has today.
(Therefore, she won't give up
that easily.)
(Wait for us.)
Okay. I'll wait for you in the hotel.
Inform Shen
from the criminal case department,
Pan, and Fang.
The more the merrier
for a search party.
Shen.
It's Tang Yihui.
Miss Sun.
You can't tell me that.
You can't do this
or that.
So this qualification letter
is just a sheet of paper?
My demand is very simple.
I paid 50,000 yuan for my membership
and I am not satisfied
with your service.
Therefore, I demand a refund.
It makes sense, doesn't it?
You violated the contract first.
If you won't perform the refund,
I will take legal action.
(Don't. You have a high income.)
How much I earn
has nothing to do with you.
My money
did not grow on trees.
Don't you agree?
(Miss Li.)
(This is not our fault.)
Sorry, Miss Sun.
I have to answer
an important call.
Think about what I told you.
We'll touch base in a few days.
Hello, Madam Tang.
(Please come now.)
All right.
(If you have any helpers around,)
(bring them too.)
(Just the trustworthy ones.)
(Those who won't tell anyone.)
I got it.
See you.
(Recent Calls)
(Qin Shi 2)
If you're about
to be promoted
to the corporation department...
Right?
And now, you have to turn back
to handle this complicated case
from the family department,
will you do it?
I don't think
you can stay out of it.
Pick up the call for me.
I'm driving.
What's up?
Ms. Lan went missing.
Coming.
You must be getting impatient.
Careful. Don't burn your hands.
Let me serve you.
Junhui.
Are you stressed lately?
What stress?
Let me help you.
I can do it.
You're beside yourself
since just now.
We agreed to have hotpot
but now, we switched to fried rice.
Miss Qin upsets you?
Impossible.
Actually,
I get it.
You do?
You're afraid.
Being with her
is stressful, isn't it?
Don't use your smile to shield
your unease.
I saw it through.
I wasn't
very fond of Miss Qin either.
I thought
she would achieve her goal
by all means possible.
She was tyrannical
and domineering.
She is like the monarch
in the family department.
A woman like that stresses
men out.
You think
she is too aggressive, don't you?
Upon hearing your analysis,
it seems like you have changed
your view of her.
I don't judge a book
by its cover.
Do you remember
the case involving
25 million yuan?
We've been trying to identify
the leaker.
I helped Miss Qin investigate
and we found out that the leaker
was Miss Qin's rival.
Miss Qin didn't report her
nor ask her for a favor.
Why?
I asked her that too.
A gentleman
knows what to do and what not to do.
It's the same for a lawyer.
We have seen the worst of humanity
but that doesn't mean we should
surrender to it.
Pulling tricks.
Cheating.
What sweet victory can you get
from them?
She may have a lot of shortcomings
but that alone
shows true character.
Who's the better person? Me or she?
Why are you competing with her?
Are you that competitive?
By the way,
if Cheng & Hui
decides to handle Lan Xiaoting's case,
will Qin Shi be the
main representing attorney?
No.
Even if they decide to handle it,
she won't be
the main representing attorney.
She's from the family department.
This is a criminal case.
Right.
Wait, no.
There's no way Miss Qin
shows this much interest
over a case she can't handle.
Unless...
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
♪Don't worry♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them♪
♪To keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes♪
♪We give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes♪
♪We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Let it heal♪
♪Grow♪
♪To be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season♪
♪We all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants♪
♪To keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible♪
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪