♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of the first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
♪Every foreshadowing
is for a happily ever after♪
♪There will be storms and hurricanes
but they are not the main themes♪
♪I want to make a montage of you♪
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
♪I'll bottle your tenderness
and thoughtfulness♪
♪I'll indulge all your tantrums♪
♪I'll watch every scene that features you
and replay them in my heart♪
=She And Her Perfect Husband=
=Episode 29=
Take a guess. When did Yang Hua
leave Hengli?
Around that incident happened, I guess.
Correct.
Therefore, we can conclude that
It turned out that
Yang Hua was the fund manager
who led to the chaos.
Am I right?
Maybe.
What do you mean by it's possible?
As the fact we can see.
It's not as simple as you think.
Everything relies on evidence.
A woman's intuition is the evidence.
I've come up with a bold speculation.
Would you like to hear me out?
I reckon
Yang Hua didn't work
at the investment bank
after leaving Hengli.
He was lying.
That's all?
Enough, just be contented.
You only gave me a name.
Nothing else besides that.
I've done a good enough job
of discovering these.
Do you think Qin Shi knows
that Yang Hua is telling lies?
Poor thing.
Where are we going?
You didn't have dinner.
I'm taking you to a great meal.
I do feel a bit hungry.
What are you going to eat?
A healing cuisine meal.
Junhui, you're the best.
Are you done eating?
Are you feeling better?
I knew
that everything in the world
can be settled with a bowl of hot Malatang.
Let's go with two
if one is not sufficient.
Two incoming customers.
There's a table inside.
- Let's go.
- Take a seat.
Miss Qin,
what a coincidence.
Mr. Yang, you're here too.
Aren't you feeling unwell?
Did the Malatang cure you?
The Malatang here is a panacea,
it can even cure a simpleton.
Miss Qin,
after you left,
Mr. Wang told me a lot about your husband.
Your husband
won't necessarily tell you these.
But if you buy me dinner,
I might tell you about it.
Can this be redeemed for a free dinner?
Well, Senior, from now on, your girlfriend
will have to pay for my dinner.
Let's go.
Watch out!
Sorry, I'm sorry.
Junhui!
It's an accident.
Sorry, I'm very sorry.
Did you get burned?
Are you alright?
- Are you alright?
- Sorry, I'm really sorry.
It's alright.
Are you okay?
Sorry, I'm really sorry.
Quick, wipe it off.
It's alright.
Does it still hurt?
Take my car to the hospital.
It's not necessary.
I'm familiar with this area.
We'll get there soon.
Just stay away from him.
I'll drive.
Be careful.
Give him a call later
and ask about him.
It feels like he's burned badly.
It's not necessary.
Anyway, I'll see him
at the law firm tomorrow.
Actually, I've been reluctant
to admit this.
But I had to say
that Tao Junhui is a nice guy.
I suppose you'd be quite happy
if you two got married.
It has nothing to do with me.
Besides,
I'm already married.
We're fake-married.
No matter what, legally speaking,
we're husband and wife.
If you want to go back to him,
we can get divorced.
You're going there, aren't you?
It's an entrapment.
I won't divorce you, I'm determined.
We'll get divorce sooner or later.
Even if we don't do it now,
it'll happen in three years either.
After today, I'm
worried
that they'll be suspicious
about my resume.
I'm afraid it'll implicate you.
So should we just...
Okay, I got it.
What happened today
is my fault, I'll apologise.
You've done nothing wrong.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have been so selfish
and made you go
to the business dinner
because of my ambition.
Then, exposing you to the guy
you don't want to see.
It's my fault, I'll apologise.
I won't do this again.
I won't make you face this kind
of complicated relationship again.
So can you forgive me this once?
There's no need to ask for forgiveness.
Since the first day I met you,
I've known that you're
an ambitious person.
You won't avoid it
even when facing difficulties.
You'll go straight ahead.
So I won't be mad at you.
I won't be mad at Tao Junhui either.
Then, why did you...
Because I had to face a fact today.
Because I'm a coward.
It's true that I'm a coward.
Slow down.
Watch it.
Be careful.
It's getting late.
Why don't you go back first?
I'll do it.
How can I go back when you're like this?
You can't even brush teeth, wash face
and get a shower now.
I'll stay to keep you company.
It's not that serious.
My right hand is injured.
But I still have my left hand.
What do you mean you're alright?
The doctor said
if it doesn't recover well,
there'll be a scar when we get married.
We should just postpone our wedding.
Anyway, our marital home is not ready yet.
Marital home?
Didn't my dad already
buy us a house?
I'd like to give you
a house with my own efforts.
I knew you'd be mad.
I'm not.
I'm not that petty-minded.
Why would I be mad?
I'm not mad.
You are.
Since you signed
the stupid prenuptial agreement,
you've been mad.
Don't worry, Junhui.
In fact, it was me
who made my dad buy us
that house.
When we get married,
I'll put your name
on the property title, okay?
You don't have to,
just put your name on it.
What do you mean? I'll do it.
I insist.
Let me tell you this, Junhui.
All I have is yours.
I can give you everything.
I don't want nothing.
I'm fine with having nothing.
Junhui,
let's get married quickly.
Feifei.
Get married quickly.
Didn't you always
want a perfect wedding?
But my hand is injured now.
It's all my fault.
It's my fault, it's me.
I'm to blame.
I've thought of it.
I can't let Qin Shi stay
at Cheng & Hui anymore.
Feifei.
Don't try to stop me.
The more you try, the more I hate her.
It's not necessary for you
to be mad because of her.
Qin Shi is already married.
What if she wasn't?
It's pointless to talk about this.
Why is it pointless?
Junhui,
I know you can't forget about her.
I know you've always cared about her.
I know.
I know no matter how hard I work,
I can never make you forget about her.
But I don't understand.
She treats you that way.
Why would you...
Why would you still care about her
and look out for her?
That you'd worry if she feels
cold or hot?
You even looked at her
with that kind of expression.
What do you mean?
It's pointless to say this.
♪Because of excuses♪
Why is it pointless?
Don't you know what I'm talking about?
Junhui,
can you please think of me
and take my feelings into account?
Just don't
make it so obvious.
I really can't take it anymore.
♪Like a bottle of aged liquor♪
♪It's transiently invalid
but soberly patched together♪
♪Hiding the everlasting love
that cannot be given up♪
♪Having it once is not what we want♪
♪Hugging is the feeling at the moment♪
♪Being apologetic about the past,
praying for the future♪
♪They are all excuses♪
♪Learning to endure is not what we want♪
♪We should've enjoyed holding hands♪
♪Exploring the sea of stars
and sticking together in difficulties♪
♪Why does it become a luxury?♪
♪Because of excuses♪
♪The process diverges our path ♪
♪And throws us off our rhythm♪
♪Both hearts are stuck at the junction♪
I was bad-tempered.
And I succeeded young
so I was kind of arrogant.
And all the colleagues were very nice to me.
Then, I realised
that it was a pretense.
Wang Jiesen,
the fund manager
who Qiu Jianxiang was most proud of.
And he always wanted
to take Mr. Qiu's place.
But my presence
seemed to have ruined all his plan.
He was good at acting.
He had silently endured me
for two years.
I was so naive that I treated him
as my best friend.
Was he related to the incident
back then?
Haibo Biology was not a stock
that Qiu Jianxiang and I would choose.
But its basic feature was too good
that it was practically perfect.
Even when Qiu Jianxiang
told me to buy the stock
in enormous volume,
I couldn't find a ground for refusal.
In the first month after buying it,
it rose by 35 percent.
But a month later,
the competitor launched a new product.
This product was enough to beat
all the products of Haibo Biology.
So we failed miserably.
Would this be a coincidence?
How could it be?
After that, I found something unusual
about the purchase
and sold of the stock.
But everything was too late.
Wang Jiesen,
he knew the ins and outs of this incident.
But he didn't allow me to say it.
He asked me to trust him.
He said he'd tell the board of directors
about it.
Yet,
he did this.
Why would Qiu Jianxiang
set you up back then?
I have no idea.
I've been taught to be
a brave man since childhood.
To face difficulties head-on.
As long as we're brave enough,
we could defeat failure.
I always did that back then.
Until later,
when I was struck hard,
I only realised
that bravery has nothing to do with failures.
Hua, you're back.
Come, give me the luggage.
Yang, Yang, our son is back.
Hurry.
(After returning from Canada,)
(I took a break at home for two months.)
(With a step-by-step approach,)
(I sent out my resume
to seek for a job.)
(But none of the companies
was willing to accept me.)
Qiu Jianxiang practised
what he preached.
(If I left him,)
(there's no way I could set a foot
in this industry.)
(Only then I knew)
(there'd be a series of problems)
(when one experienced major defeat.)
(I started to suffer hair loss, lose weight.)
(I didn't even leave home for a month.)
(So I came up with a new mantra.)
(Which was to lie down at where you fell.)
(Learn to store our energy
when we're at a low point.)
(Don't make a feeble attempt.)
Get up.
I've got something to tell you.
Right now.
How much longer do you want
to sit at home lazing around?
You made your room look like a pigsty.
What are you trying to do?
How much longer do you want
to waste yourself?
Talk nicely, don't get violent.
(My mom had endured me for six months.)
(At last, she couldn't stand it.)
(She gave me a choice that time.)
Go out and work.
I don't care what your job is.
It doesn't matter if it's a cab driver
or a vegetable seller.
You must feed yourself.
No trash is allowed in my house.
My son can't be a neet.
You're not allowed to be a neet.
I won't.
I'll pay all my living costs in time.
I won't work
but I will make money.
I don't need you to take care of me.
But I hope
that you could stop worrying about me.
And take care of your bodies.
Get a haircut.
Right away.
And shave your beard.
I will.
If there's nothing else,
I'll head back to my room.
Sometimes, it's really comfortable
to escape from reality.
As long as you admit that you're a loser,
then, you can feel comfortable
to be a terrible person.
Because you've degraded yourself.
You won't care if the others degrade you.
But,
then, I found that I was wrong.
Because your failure
won't disappear over time.
It'll give you a strike
when you stand up again.
Don't you think
they're very patient?
Actually,
it's no big deal to fail.
Everyone has failed before.
Well,
is it a bad thing
to be liked by someone like me?
What are you talking about?
There's nothing
good about me.
But I'll protect my loved one.
If you keep speaking ill of my husband,
I'll be mad.
Actually,
it doesn't matter if you stand up
and face it bravely or avoid it like a coward.
But you have to know this.
We are together now.
You can rely on me.
From now on,
we'll go through hardships
and overcome difficulties together.
This is what a relationship is for.
Don't you think?
♪In the cold season, we all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants to keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible, don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪
Are you awake?
I've made breakfast.
Do you want to eat it with me?
Hello.
I'd like to sleep a little longer.
Well, then.
The breakfast is on the table.
Remember to eat it
when you wake up.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
I'm thinking
that Yang Hua is
in a bad mood today,
remember to take care
of him for me.
Please, come on.
Everyone is a precious individual.
I've got many works to do everyday.
Who... Who takes care of me?
Cai Liang,
I'm a woman
who always knows
how much you have with Yang Hua.
(Are you sure you want to go there?)
Rest assured, Miss Qin.
(When your husband comes
to work today,)
I'll be sure to take care of him
like I do to my wife, okay?
He didn't got to work today?
You're living together,
even you don't know
if he has come to work.
How would I know that?
Excuse me, make ways.
Excuse me.
Be careful.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, thank you.
Is he still crying?
(Don't think too much.)
(I'll bring good food for you tonight.)
Wait.
Is this yours?
Yes.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Let's go.
(File cover)
Dad,
why are you here?
This is...
Look.
a lawyer came to me yesterday.
It was from her.
(Qiu Jianxiang)
Mr. Yang,
Mr. Qiu is Yang Hua's mentor.
They've had their clashes before,
but Mr. Qiu has tried
his best to protect
Yang Hua that time.
Even until now,
Mr. Qiu still thinks
that Yang Hua is
the most outstanding disciple
that he admires most.
About this matter,
Yang Hua is the only person
who can help him.
Yang Hua is simple and kind-hearted.
I'm sure he won't want
his mentor to spend
the end of his life in jail.
Why not?
Why can't he do that?
Qiu Jianxiang still
has the nerve to ask Yang Hua for help.
I can't believe he could say that.
A perfectly fine kid
followed him to Canada.
But look what
he's turned my son into.
It's been four years.
He was jobless
and a good-for-nothing
for four years.
It was all because of this mentor.
Yang Hua was jobless for four years?
How is that possible, Aunt?
Everyone in our law firm knew
that Yang Hua used to be
an executive of an investment bank.
Get out.
From now on, no one is allowed to say
this bad guy's name in my house.
Mentor? My foot!
If I knew he turned my son into this,
no matter what,
I wouldn't have allowed my son
to learn things from him.
Now that he's in jail.
He deserves it.
He ruined someone's beloved son,
it's tantamount to killing people.
Calm down, Aunt.
Yang Hua has a happy family
and a successful career now.
It's being exaggerated
to claim that it's a killing.
That's because my son is lucky.
Otherwise,
why did he sit at home lazing around?
I would've gotten grandchildren now.
I would've lived better than now.
Your mom has had a good cry.
Actually, I know
that she's not blaming the others.
Rather than blaming Mr. Qiu,
I'm afraid she's putting
the blame on herself.
Just that she didn't
spit it out all these years.
It happened to give her a chance
to vent it all out at once yesterday.
Dad,
you want me to help him?
I think you should help yourself.
Hua,
(Qiu Jianxiang)
I have no idea what happened
to you back then.
But judging from the state
you were in after your return,
I've got some leads.
It's necessary to experience
hardships in one's life.
It can't always go smoothly,
don't you think?
It requires two secrets to get a happy life.
I've told you
about the first secret.
Do you still remember it?
Learn to enjoy failures.
The second is
to learn to forgive others.
(Qiu Jianxiang)
Letting them off is
tantamount to freeing yourself.
I don't know if I can do it.
Give it a try.
You never know if you don't try.
(Qiu Jianxiang)
Hello.
Hello, Mr. Tao.
Hello, Miss Yao.
Hello.
Nice to meet you, I'm Yao Yao.
I was the manager on duty
on the day
when Ms. He Dongna checked in.
Hello, Miss Yao.
Before we start the conversation,
I have an obligation to inform you
that all our conversations
will be recorded.
It might become an evidence
that's unfavorable to you in future.
Are you sure you want to start the conversation?
I'm sure.
Are you here on behalf of the hotel or yourself?
Today, I'm here
as the party concerned
to make a clarification.
It's purely my personal behaviour.
It has nothing to do with the company.
So you're saying
you don't agree with what
Ms. He Dongna said?
The fact is unlike what she described.
Those are groundless accusations.
Ms. He checked in
to the Presidential Suite
of our hotel at about nine that night.
(Before she checked in,)
(she requested for butler service.)
(As one of the content in butler service,)
(the butler will have to
stay with the guest at night.)
Ms. He,
Ms. He, are you in there?
I'm coming in.
Ms. He?
Why are there so many towels in the bathroom?
These were the requests from Ms. He.
She suspected that there were cameras
in the hotel's bathroom.
So she used many towels
to cover the places
where she thought
there might be cameras.
Ms. He said
she was showering
when the glass broke.
But from what I saw that time was
that she was fully clothed,
that she wasn't showering.
It's not the point.
The fact is that she was injured.
And it's a fact that Ms. He was evicted
from your hotel.
It's true that Ms. He was injured
at our hotel.
But we've told her many times
that we're willing to bear
the corresponding responsibility.
Just that Ms. He didn't accept it.
(Besides, we didn't try to evict her that time.)
(It was her who requested to leave.)
Let go.
Quickly contact my assistant.
Tell her to come pick me up now.
Right now!
Calm down.
I'll take you to the hospital
in a while.
Let me help you with the wound...
Don't touch me.
Be careful.
Go away!
Ms. He felt very agitated at that moment.
We kept trying to calm her down.
Actually, our hotel
could've provided some
simple medical attention.
But Ms. He didn't accept any kind
of our assistance.
She clawed and bit our staff
and she made a lot
of unreasonable demands on us.
Like what?
Like
she wanted us
to send a chopper over.
She wouldn't accept any local
or domestics medical attention.
She wanted us
to send a chopper over
to send her abroad
to meet her personal physician.
We're going to take you
to the hospital.
To the hospital?
What hospital?
I want to go to the foreign hospitals.
Are you trying to kill me?
Ms. He,
we can't send you abroad for now.
But we can take you
to the best hospital here.
Let's have your wound dressed first.
Is that okay with you?
I'm not going.
Mister, pull over!
Calm down!
Calm down, Ms. He.
It's not safe like this.
- Pull over, Mister!
- Don't do this!
(Partner Counsel)
(Actually, we've got)
(a lot of evidences.)
(These are only part of it.)
(But in the hotel industry,)
(we're not allowed to leak)
(the privacy of the customer)
(due to our professional ethics.)
(If Ms. He insists on making)
(a big deal out of it,)
(I'll publicize the evidence in court.)
(I'm sure Ms. He won't want to see it.)
Actually, the hotel and I are
willing to bear
the corresponding responsibility
with regard to the unhappy experience
Ms. He had in our hotel.
We hope that Ms. He
could accept mediation.
Who is this Yao Yao?
Madam Tang, I've got the information.
(Yao Yao, 29 years old,)
(a divorcee, single,)
(has a five-year-old son.)
(She was a flight attendant
in an airline company.)
(After leaving the airline company,)
(she joined a hotel)
(as a junior clerk.)
(Now, she's the marketing manager of the hotel.)
(And she's the only person in the hotel)
(who's graduated from Holand Butler Academy.)
(She has Grade Four Certificate
of International Wine Taster.)
Impressive.
She even got a grade four.
She spent over a million yuan just on the wine.
Yao Yao is mainly in charge
of managing
the important customers of the hotel.
And all these customers
have high status.
In the past six months,
there's been four to five complaints
against Yao Yao.
It all happened
when both parties had conflicts,
Yao Yao spoke up of the hotel staff,
causing dissatisfaction
of the customers.
After getting complaints
from the clients,
she's still able to work in the field.
It shows that
the superiors have high regard for her.
Not quite.
Yao Yao has signed
a long-term contract
with the hotel.
Besides, the hotel has spent a lot on her.
Normally, the hotel won't fire her
unless she tramples
serious dereliction of duty.
In short,
Yao Yao has no problem at work.
Well, it means it's impossible
to ask the hotel to fire this manager.
I think it's not impossible.
It mainly depends on
how I make use
of the public opinion.
I've looked into Yao Yao.
Her family has been poor
since she was little.
She didn't have a happy childhood.
It's a single parent family.
Her mother is in poor health.
Her private life is
kind of like a Cinderella Story.
Leaving the airline company
was for getting married.
She was married to a man
who was born with a silver spoon.
This marriage made her a trophy wife.
But she wasn't happy in her marriage.
She got divorced two years later.
But Tianhang Hotel is
still our main target of the public opinion.
In these few days,
the public opinion will
constantly emerge.
It's mostly negative news.
My current plan is
to hand the information we have
to the media step by step.
To put constant pressure on them.
And solve the problem
in short period of time.
What do you think?
I think we should be more cautious.
Because there'll be dire consequences
once the media is out of control.
Public opinion is a double-edged weapon.
We don't have the evidence of the fact.
It might backfire on us.
It's a bad plan to make
personal attack towards them.
Now that both parties have
serious disagreement
on what happened that day.
The action the hotel took
was indeed unreasonable.
Our client is a public figure.
She'll receive more attention
and support of the public opinion.
But we should turn all the attention
back to this incident.
Now that the controversial point
of this case is
whether if our client
was injured at the hotel,
if the hotel has immediately
taken remedial measures.
The answers are still uncertain now.
We got two versions of stories.
Which should we believe?
Of course we should trust our client.
We're her attorneys.
In fact, in the case,
whether the client is telling the truth or lies,
it has nothing to do with us.
A lawyer has
no obligation to determine
the true and false.
But we have the obligation to tell the client
that whether she's telling the truth or lies,
there'll be corresponding consequences.
All we do is to provide advice.
Of course.
The final decision is made by the client herself.
All we need to do is
to provide corresponding
legal service according
to her decision.
That's all.
That's right.
But Madam Tang,
this client of ours is not
only a person concerned
to the law firm.
How likely do you think
it is that Miss Yao has
a solid evidence?
I think it's impossible.
If she got the evidence,
she would've handed it to the media.
Why would she hide it away?
Now that both parties
don't have a third party's testimony.
We can only say it's a 50-50 deal.
Miss Qin.
Mr. Zhang went to Wuhan early.
So this office is now yours.
I wasn't lying, was I?
How is it?
Feel it.
Are you satisfied?
So-so.
Okay.
As long as you're satisfied.
Well, you continue.
Come to me if there's anything.
What is this about?
What's wrong, Miss?
Are you mad?
Tell me in private
if you have an opinion, okay?
Is it necessary to say that
in front of the people?
I was just being matter-of-fact.
And I think your tactics are
not smart at all.
It's suspected of violating the law.
You're a lawyer.
Aren't you aware of that?
Calm down.
I don't want to drink it.
Do you think it's a rash move
as I choose
to hold the conference now?
I've looked into the Tianhang Group.
They're poorly managed.
The superiors have always wanted
to look for someone to acquire it.
Now that there are
several buyers bidding for it.
Negative news and lawsuit are
what they fear most now.
The most likely outcome of this matter is
that Tianhang fires Yao Yao
to advertise itself as a company
that rectifies its mistakes.
Do you think I begin
a public campaign
only for our sake?
I'm just showing
Tianhang the way out.
Besides, Dongna will donate
all the compensation money
to the charitable organization.
So the fact you reckon
doesn't matter at all.
Then, why didn't you tell me this?
I wanted to tell you about it.
I wanted to tell you this yesterday.
Well, stop being mad.
I have no idea
why I do this.
This kind of working environment
is more suitable for Miss Qin.
I knew you care about me.
What happened to Yang Hua yesterday?
Why did he feel discomfort
all of a sudden?
What was the problem?
It was an acute gastroenteritis.
He felt better after taking medication.
Thanks for your concern.
Don't mention it.
Qin Shi,
I've got a very important mission.
After much thought,
you're the most suitable candidate.
Will you help me?
Is it something serious?
That you even
solemnly discuss it with me.
For your record,
I'm not going to do dirty things.
But if you want me to look into
your Jin's hidden reserves,
just leave it to me,
there won't be a problem.
You're puffing yourself up.
♪Don't worry♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them♪
♪To keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes♪
♪We give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes♪
♪We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Let it heal♪
♪Grow♪
♪To be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season♪
♪We all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants♪
♪To keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible♪
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪