♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of the first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
♪Every foreshadowing
is for a happily ever after♪
♪There will be storms and hurricanes
but they are not the main themes♪
♪I want to make a montage of you♪
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
♪I'll bottle your tenderness
and thoughtfulness♪
♪I'll indulge all your tantrums♪
♪I'll watch every scene that features you
and replay them in my heart♪
=She And Her Perfect Husband=
=Episode 26=
The renovation period
of these commercial apartments
ranged from three months to a year.
The commercial apartment
which has the longest renovation period,
the cabinets still contain high level
of formaldehyde.
Mr. Cao,
this is not some kind
of individual phenomenon.
No, you...
You're indeed
impressive, Mr. Tao.
But, I've made some preparation
before I came in here
for business.
I pay my taxes
and conduct legal business deals.
I'm the pioneer and innovator
in this industry.
All of these
won't shake me.
If I deal with it properly,
it can never be a threat to me.
However, do your partners
and investors know about this?
Besides,
does Mr. Sang of Xiaoyun Finance
know about this too?
Mr. Cao,
your leverage
has reached a critical point.
Once the vacancy rate of the apartments
is raised by one or two points,
you will face liquidation.
Now that you're going
to marry Ding Fangfang
and the problem might be solved
as you can have Mr. Ding's
fund and status in the finance industry
in the palm of your hand.
Am I right?
Our country welcomes investors
from all around the globe.
However, under one condition,
that's the businessmen should act honestly.
Mr. Tao.
I used to think
that we were cut from the same cloth.
That's you.
Please come to the firm
to sign the prenup.
Take your time, Mr. Cao.
You may continue with the meeting.
I'll wait for you.
Did Cao Yiren throw in the towel
with just one testing report
you brought?
One report isn't enough.
I brought over twenty reports to him.
Where did you get those?
I have a friend
in the inspection bureau,
he helped me with this.
Besides, the testing report
is only for the cabinet.
Did you lie?
I did.
I didn't expect that from you,
Tao Junhui.
You've grown up. You can lie now.
It depends on who's it.
I'll use tricks when I have to.
Good.
So, would he come this afternoon?
Maybe.
Maybe?
It means...
I need to tell you something.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
I'll step out.
Bye.
Cheer up, bye-bye.
What has happened?
(File Folder)
Are you angry?
No.
Why don't you talk to me?
I don't feel like talking.
Let's sit down.
Let me check
if you're feeling unwell.
Drink some water and calm yourself.
This is insidious.
What has gotten into you, Miss Wu?
Why are you lashing out?
Why could you accept my father's request
without letting me know?
We have an agreement.
Miss Wu.
You're being harsh.
I won't take this.
Indeed.
We had an agreement.
You wanted to transfer Tao Junhui
to the corporate department
which I had made it happen.
Besides, you requested
to be the attorney
of the family department
and I granted your wish as well.
You even wanted me
to make Qin Shi embarrassed,
I did so.
Except for these,
I think there's nothing else
I've promised you.
Your dad cares a lot about you.
He wants to know more
about Tao Junhui's character
and behavior.
I find this request reasonable as well.
The camera on the 11th floor
is visible to everyone.
It depends on them
to do what they want,
I can't control them.
Don't you think
it's unreasonable
to blame me for this?
Besides,
the past between Tao Junhui and Qin Shi
isn't a secret.
Don't tell me
he has been keeping it from you.
No, he doesn't.
He confessed everything to me.
That's good, then.
The way he treats Qin Shi
is just normal
and understandable.
Dear girl.
First love is always unforgettable,
let alone they were once
going to marry each other.
Even my husband, Jin
still remembers clearly
the school romance that happened
between him and his puppy love.
But,
Qin Shi has hurt him hard before.
Stop grinding on the past.
Don't forget
you're his current fiancee.
He never sees me
with full affection in his eyes.
You should stop comparing.
Let me tell you this.
To women, jealousy is fatal.
Once jealousy takes over you,
you lose.
A proud and confident person
never gets jealous.
Instead of being jealous,
you should set your eyes
on your advantages.
I never reckon
that Tao Junhui chose you
because of your father's money.
Don't you even
have that confidence?
I do have.
Are you curious
what's the secret to lead
a happy marriage?
The secret is
never to expect
that there'll be someone
who loves you more than your parents do.
Only you can make yourself happy.
What's this?
Read it yourself.
(File Folder)
(Prenuptial Agreement)
Are you upset because of this?
If you insist to know
whether Tao Junhui loves you or not,
there's a way to justify it.
See if he's willing
to sign this agreement.
What are you doing?
I'm signing.
Nothing to be worried about then
after signing this.
Why didn't you even read it?
No necessary. No problem with it.
No problem?
I see many problems in this.
Which one of these
do you find problematic?
The whole thing.
This prenup is an insult to you
and to our relationship.
Why don't feel angry about this?
You should retaliate
when someone bullies you
or hurts you.
You should
rip this agreement
and throw it into the dustbin.
Why are you so silly?
Why do you sign it?
Just why?
You mustn't be soft-hearted.
You can't just be kind to everyone.
Don't cry.
You'll look ugly if you cry.
Feifei.
We can't throw a fist
whenever we are upset.
Otherwise, we'll be trapped in wrath
and achieved nothing. Alright?
Life isn't as simple as you thought.
There are moments
that go against us.
We just can't do anything
if someone misunderstands us.
Your rage
won't help change their mind.
Besides,
I couldn't care less about
other's opinions,
I only care about how you see me.
There, there. Don't cry.
Junhui.
Let's get married as soon as possible.
Sure.
What's the hurry? Where are you going?
Oh right.
What time is it for the prenup session
this afternoon?
Three or four.
Good. I still have time.
I want to take a leave.
I'll be back after the session starts. Bye.
Be careful.
Do you know we've lost
a black cardholder
because of what you said?
How dare you spewed nonsense
and nitpicked the product of Fangyu Finance?
Do you know
how valuable Mr. Qiu
of Fangyu Group is?
I can't see why
an account manager
who just came
could be so bold.
It has nothing to do with courage.
It's true that something's wrong
with Fangyu's product
and I've submitted
an analysis report to you.
You would know
that I'm right
if you read the report.
Don't trick me with that.
Listen.
Mr. Qiu is an important partner
of our bank
who has projects that are worth
tens of billions.
What if the trouble you caused
affects our partnership?
Can you afford the loss?
As an account manager,
my duty is to protect the benefit of clients.
I can never introduce
a defective trust product
to my clients.
This doesn't fit well with my work ethic.
You!
Good. Very good.
This place is too small
for a capable person like you.
I hope that you hand in your notice
right now.
Why are you at home?
I'm hungry.
So, I came back to cook some noodles.
And...
And you made a mess in the kitchen.
I'll clean this up.
Did you get hurt? Are you fine?
Don't strain yourself
if you can't cook.
Tell me what you want to eat.
I'll make it and send it to you.
You have your own work too.
Hold on.
Why do you come back?
I came to fetch something.
I will head back later.
You should put your feet up.
I'll clean it and cook the food.
I'll clean up the mess.
Let me do it.
- Hello.
- Be careful.
This is your order.
Why did you order two servings of rice
for yourself?
I'm a heavy eater.
Fine, I'll own up.
I was thinking
to prepare some food at home
and send it to you
as a surprise.
And now you've seen this.
Hence,
I came out with Plan B
to pretend that I cooked this.
I didn't know you'd come back.
Why do you suddenly think of
cooking for me?
The idea doesn't come on a whim.
I've been thinking
to do something for you.
And this is what I could think of
after racking my brain.
All this time,
you've been taking care of me.
I can't imagine how messy
my life would've been without you.
Honestly, I just want to tell you
that we're one.
I can look after you
and do anything for you too.
You don't need
to force yourself into something
you're not good at.
I only came to realise this today.
Yang Hua.
I understand that you have your own work and life.
And you will choose family
over your career.
However, I don't wish
the family is a nuisance to you.
I hope both of us lead a better life,
not because of one's sacrifice.
What if
I lose my job some other day?
I'll take care of you.
Anyway, you'll do a bang-up job
no matter where you are.
You did well when you were at home.
But on one condition,
that's you must enjoy
what you've done.
Regardless of what choice you make,
I'll root for you.
I'll back you up
like what you did for me.
Thank you.
I should thank you instead.
Thank you for being here for me.
Thank you for being here for me too.
♪A wrong timing♪
♪Can't stop a destined meeting♪
♪Fortunately, that someone is you♪
♪That must be the reason for love♪
(Cheng & Hui Law Office)
Sure, I'll fetch it for you.
♪Even though it can be painful♪
♪It's still worthy to go for it♪
Well,
we'll wrap this up then.
See you around.
Dear, let me see you off.
Don't be dejected.
It's not your first me
losing to me.
I lost?
Darling.
You're as naive as you used to be.
Well, don't grind on this.
I'll buy you a meal next time, okay?
Do you know who did Mr. Cao meet
before signing this agreement?
Mr. Ding.
We meet at last.
What do you think
about Cao Yiren's intention
to meet with Mr. Ding?
It could be any reason
except that he persuaded Mr. Ding
how deep his love is for Ding Fangfang.
Hui.
I feel like I'm being outwitted.
Think about this.
We've sifted through
everything about him
to find the evidence.
Even someone has no sense of business like me
deemed that he's natural for business.
Though his company
encounters all sorts of problems,
however, by just getting funds,
he still can make a profit.
Do you think he made a deal
with Mr. Ding?
That's possible.
You see.
Although I don't know Cao Yiren well,
I'm familiar with Mr. Ding.
Mr. Ding is a businessman too.
If he accepts Cao Yiren's proposal
and offers him the fund,
probably he'll be benefitted
of the business too.
The thing is,
the benefit is more alluring
than the property
he wanted Cao Yiren
to give up.
Hui, it's a big loss for us.
Why?
Think about this.
We merely received the money
for the prenup
yet we've done a due diligence service
on financial and lawyering.
Not true.
I think
it's not as easy as I thought.
I can sense
that there's something else
apart from Cao Yiren's trap.
It really bothers me.
Hui.
Don't tell me you trapped me too.
You just came to this department,
though.
Why are you so suspicious?
Tell me
what lesson have you learnt
besides this dumb fooled feeling?
Well, I won't say it's a lesson.
After these days of setbacks,
something has dawned on me.
Go on.
Given my shallow experience,
there's a long way to go
before I establish myself
in the corporate department.
You're a realist.
As compared to Tao Junhui,
he's a better choice than me
and he possesses resources
and connections.
Therefore,
he's more capable and influential.
You have a mind of the management.
Besides,
the reason why you put me
in an awkward place
on the 11th floor
not because
you wanted me to keep an eye
on Tao Junhui,
instead,
you disapproved of me
and wanted me to reflect on myself.
You're learning.
I know I used to be
self-centred before.
Qin Shi.
Who do you know
what's the greatest virtue about you?
I'm young and beautiful.
The greatest virtue of yours
is that you're quick-witted
and resourceful.
Your hands aren't tied by the restriction.
Likewise, the greatest flaw of yours
is that you think quickly,
uncontrollably,
and overly ambitious.
You fail to realise
how deep the world is
and you need to restrain yourself.
I'm at fault.
I'm wrong.
I'm to be blamed.
Please give me a chance.
Let's set some ground rules.
Never take matters into your own hands.
No problem.
Never hide any information
concerning the company's interest.
I'll be frank.
Never cut corners
when I task you with something.
I'll accomplish anything
you want me to do.
You're my guardian.
Very good.
Now,
I have a very important task for you.
Could you please take a look at it
for me?
Sure, I'll.
Madam, don't worry.
Though
you're not registered on
the property ownership certificate,
you possess
half right of this house
as it was bought
after you married your husband.
After your husband passed away,
his possession
turns into an inheritance.
Both you and your son
are entitled to the inheritance.
Besides, you have the right
of habitation over this house.
Your son can't drive you
out of the house.
Don't worry.
Alright, I understood.
Sure.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Madam, wait.
Please take a photo with me.
Qian, do you mind helping me?
(Charity Law Consultation)
Three, two, one.
Good.
Thank you.
Thank you, see you.
Do come by if you need help.
Sure.
Miss Qin.
Why don't you
come back to the family department?
I'm doing good
in the corporate department, though.
Why would I?
Because
we miss you very much
and we wish you can come back.
Am I right, Qian?
Yes.
There's no room for improvement
for me
in the family department.
Besides, I went
to the corporate department
as I wanted to step out
of my comfort zone
and challenge myself.
Being a lawyer needs lifelong learning.
Well, I shall end here.
I'm going strolling around.
Work well.
Phone me if anything happens.
- Sure.
I'm around the area of your bank.
What time do you get off work?
I can pick you up.
(I have an extra shift today.)
(I might be coming home late.)
Extra shift?
The system of the bank
is off on time though.
Why would you work overtime?
(Training.)
(We have training sessions.)
(We're asked to stay for the training.)
Training?
Where are you now?
What's the loud noise over your side?
Say that again.
What did they do to you?
Nothing. It's just
that the job doesn't suit me well.
Just now, you said
you detected a problem
from the product
and helped the client to sidestep
the risk of losing the property
and avoided a potential crisis for the bank.
However,
you lost your job because of this.
Is that so?
Well, you can say it that way.
Bad guys.
Jia.
Cai.
Mr. Qiu called me just now
saying that he was dissatisfied
with the cancellation
of credit products
he offered.
He promised
to introduce me to the person in charge
of the New Energy Smart City this week.
It's all gone up in smoke now.
Are you going
to bear this consequence?
Calm down.
Please sit, Jia.
Sit down and drink some water.
Take a sip.
Jia, do you believe me
if I tell you I can?
Besides,
you can't always threaten others
with this project.
I heard
that you've been following this project
for a long time.
Yet you haven't gotten
to meet the person in charge.
I wonder what's wrong with you.
Anyway,
we've helped Fangyu to sell products
and make sales that are worth
billions of yuan.
Cai, what are you trying to imply?
What am I trying to imply?
I was saying
that although
we helped Fangyu distribute the product,
however, we promoted
their product to our important clients.
Do you know what will happen
if the clients find something wrong
about the product?
Something wrong?
Fangyu is an established
finance company,
okay?
By the way,
I heard
that it was you
who cut Yang Hua some slack.
I'm curious
what's the relationship between you two.
He didn't have rich working experience,
yet he got to waltz in here
to be an account manager
who nitpicked the product.
I recruited Yang Hua
as I'm well aware of his capability
to deal with this job.
I tell you what,
being an account manager
is just too small for him.
When he was
an analyst of the best finance company
in Canada,
he was just twenty-two years old.
I can promise you
that the product is defective
when he said so.
You can promise?
Can you take the blame
if he's wrong?
Can you?
What do you want now
when you've fired him?
What are you up to?
Mr. Cai.
You need to come out now.
Why?
Yang Hua...is back.
Why does he come back?
Perfect timing.
I want to see him now.
Why do you come here?
Who are you?
Take a seat.
I'm Yang Hua's wife.
Impressive, youngsters.
You caused a big problem at work
and now you ask your wife to stand up for you.
As a man,
I feel shameful for you.
How may I address you?
My last name is Jia.
You're the bank manager?
Did you sack my husband?
Yes.
Can you please tell me your reason?
My reason?
You're the fine one to ask.
Why don't you ask your husband?
Listen up.
You better apologise to Mr. Qiu now
and take back your inappropriate words.
Put everything right.
Otherwise, you have to bear
all the consequences and financial loss.
Do you hear me?
When I was young, my mother taught me
to act sensibly and reasonably,
show respect to others,
don't make noise while eating
and never point my finger at others while talking.
And I realised
that there are people
who are uneducated.
Who are you referring to?
Mr. Jia.
It seems
you don't quite know about laws.
In Labour Law,
employees can only be dismissed
under the following situations.
First, employees
who don't fit the requirement
during probation.
Second, violation
of the rules and regulations
of the employer.
Third, dereliction of duty,
favouritism and fraud,
and causing great loss
to the employer.
Fourth,
sign labour contract
with other employers.
Fifth, the labour contract is invalid
according to the rules.
Sixth, prosecuted
for criminal responsibility
according to law.
May I ask
if Yang Hua has violated which of them?
The second...
Think twice before you talk.
Yang Hua
raised reasonable doubts
about the risks of products
released by
an external financial institutions
entrusted to the bank.
Please tell me
which of the laws did he violate?
He...
That's not
within the scope of his job.
The job scope of an account manager
includes
serving the clients.
He's being responsible for the bank
and the client.
Please explain to me
what's his job scope
instead of this?
You...
You're messing up with me.
You're the one who messes up with me.
Per Labour Law,
the employer isn't entitled
to dismiss the employee
even if they discover the incompetency
of the employee.
The company must offer
training for the employee,
which is the duty of the employer.
Even if you intend
to dismiss the employee,
you must inform them
via written documents
thirty days before
the termination date
and pay the employee
the wage for their contribution
within the period.
The behavior of your company
has violated Labour Law.
Arbitration Court or the media,
you can choose either one.
I'll see it through to the end.
You!
Who the heck are you?
I'm the attorney
of Cheng & Hui Law Firm of Pujiang.
My name is Qin Shi.
Before you try him,
you need to ask me first.
Let's go.
Miss Qin.
The exit is over here.
- You should tell me earlier.
- That's right.
Spend a good night with your wife
tonight.
She's amazing.
Miss Qin.
I knew it was you.
We meet again.
It's a shame to waste your talent
being an account manager here.
Do you want to join my company?
Mr. Qiu.
Glad to see you here.
Well,
regarding that incident,
I've settled it seriously.
Back in the day,
Qiu Jianxiang
was a god in the security industry to us.
All of his classic cases
were recorded in the textbook.
Our lecturer
of the security course
was his loyal fan.
Normally,
we common people
could never cross path
with a person like him.
Qin Shi, guess what.
During the last year in college,
the two of us participated
in the University Investment
Simulation Competition
that led to a massive change
to the life of two young men.
Take a guest.
Who won first place?
It seems you were foreshowing.
It must be that man.
Wrong.
You know what?
The competition lasted for one month.
The participant wasn't restricted
to individuals and groups.
The result of the competition
is determined
by earnings yield.
So, Yang Hua and I
shared one account.
I remembered
that the market index
started at 4289.72
and it ended at 3686.92
which was reduced by
12.02 per cent.
Two of us only took two-weeks time
to raise the earning yields
to 17...
17.32 per cent.
Do you know what that means?
First place.
Guess how much is the yield
of second place.
I feel ashamed of them.
They were just dumb.
Only 10.02 per cent.
What was the problem with them then?
Hua.
Stop solving that stupid game.
Alright?
That Little Prairie Prince
managed to raise his yields
to 14.3 per cent.
Just now,
he sold off
the stock
of Dongfang Electronics
at 12.26 yuan.
I remember that he bought it
with 11.76 yuan.
What do we do now?
His gain is around 3 to 4 per cent.
Only ten days left.
If this keeps on going,
we'll surpass us.
Let's open a position.
No.
I've picked four stocks.
Four of them
fulfil our requirement for the trade.
It'll work. Shall we?
No.
Previously, we talked about
Yizheng Chemical Fibre.
We did some research on it, right?
If the price is ranging from 6.90 yuan
to 7.20 yuan,
we can buy it, right?
Now that it has increased to
7.10 yuan.
We can give it a shot.
No.
Well, the stock of Hongcheng
has raised to
20.58 yuan now.
You said this yourself
that we can buy it
if it's below 21 yuan.
Shall we?
Let's buy it.
Yang.
What's wrong with you?
Therefore,
second place surpassed you
as you didn't open a position
and sit idly?
On the 23th August,
we bought 2000 shares of Hongcheng
with 20.62 yuan
and sold them at 19.50 yuan
at the 27th August.
Lastly, Little Prairie Prince
topped the rank
with 17.6 per cent
which was 0.2 per cent slightly higher
than the second place.
Who's the person
that caused this failure?
That was why I came to realise
that I wasn't suitable for trading.
After graduation,
I chose bank over stock exchange
without hesitation.
Since then,
I started to count the money for others.
Afterwards,
I never stand straight
before him
as if I've owned him five million.
He bullies me a lot.
You've been talking for one hour.
Can you tell me about the hero?
Miss Qin, please don't be as impersonal as him.
You should listen to the story
of the supporting character
besides the hero.
Do you know how much
my time is worth an hour?
Don't talk to me like that.
I work the entire eight hours
dealing with money too.
Despite this, I'm a man with feelings.
After the contest,
I received a call.
Hello.
(Hello.)
(You're Mr. Yang Hua, right?)
(I'm Qiu Jianxiang.)
(I suppose you know who I am.)
(Wonder if you would)
(meet me and have a little chat.)
I see.
Among all the students,
I paid most attention to you.
Someone bet me
you would open a position
when you were going to crack.
But, I didn't think so.
Though I lost the game,
anyway, I got to learn the truth today.
As a trader,
one must have a strong determination
and a firm belief
and stick to it till the end.
Did you learn something
from this failure?
The lesson I've learnt is
that a partner who slows you down
is scarier than a robust opponent.
Would you like to be my partner?
After graduation,
I went to Canada
to learn from him for two years
and then I became the fund manager.
Excuse me,
please get me two flasks of sake.
- One flask.
Let's just take one flask.
Nurse your drink.
♪Don't worry♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them♪
♪To keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes♪
♪We give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes♪
♪We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Let it heal♪
♪Grow♪
♪To be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season♪
♪We all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants♪
♪To keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible♪
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪