♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of the first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
♪Every foreshadowing
is for a happily ever after♪
♪There will be storms and hurricanes
but they are not the main themes♪
♪I want to make a montage of you♪
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
♪I'll bottle your tenderness
and thoughtfulness♪
♪I'll indulge all your tantrums♪
♪I'll watch every scene that features you
and replay them in my heart♪
=She And Her Perfect Husband=
=Episode 40=
Okay, I got it.
What's the situation now?
I just received
a piece of inside news from Tianhang.
They've received a notification
that Yin Zhiqiang
has been transferred away.
Transferred away?
Where is he transferred to?
He's transferred
to the Supervision Office
to be the team leader.
Supervision Office?
What kind of a department is that?
It's something
like a department
for the old and retiring employees.
It's like the Cold Palace
of our corporation.
So, Yin Zhiqiang
is already finished
before we can sue him.
This is not good.
The thing is,
because of this merger and acquisition,
he signed
a lifelong supplementary contract
with the HR Department.
He
can't retire early
or resign.
Or else, he'll have to pay
a large amount of penalty.
Moreover, he can't work
in the hotel
and catering industry anymore.
He deserves it.
Yin Zhiqiang has lost
his power.
It means
that Tianhang
will not protect him anymore.
And I don't think that Cheng & Hui
will take his case anymore.
His case
has been given to their legal assistant.
Are we still going to continue
with the case then?
Of course.
Our enemy
has already lost his shield.
If we don't defeat him now,
when are we going to do it?
I'm going
to file a complaint today.
Wait for my return.
Then, we can celebrate.
- Okay.
- Great.
All the best!
- Cheers.
This is great.
Qin Shi.
To be honest,
this is my first time
harbouring an admiration toward you.
Do you know why?
Why?
They say that women are narrow-minded
and petty.
After 18 years old,
women will lose all their friendships.
But not you.
You gave up your job
for a love rival.
And you can even drink together
with your love rival.
What kind
of enlightenment do you have?
I don't understand.
And I don't dare to ask.
Who told you that she's my love rival?
Have you forgotten
what my occupation is?
That question
is an insult
to my IQ and my occupation.
Li Dai, you don't have any IQ.
I'm not trying to hide a secret.
In my life,
there's no such thing as a love rival.
If there's a man
who I want,
no one will be able to compete with me.
I need to use the toilet.
It's just because you've never met
a tough opponent before.
What kind of a tough opponent?
Someone like you?
Yes. Someone like me.
What do you think? Do you admit defeat?
You look so cute
when you are being so confident.
Let me drink to you.
Come.
I need to use the toilet too.
Junhui.
Don't worry.
Everything
is going according to plan.
Okay, I got it.
Okay, I got it. You can rest assured.
It's not...
It's not something...
Don't take my phone.
(Brother)
Hello.
You are Yang Hua, right?
He's my client. Not Yang Hua.
Let me ask you.
Between me and Yao Yao,
who will you choose?
Look. He's really just a client.
I...
Junhui.
Okay. I'll call you later
if I need to talk to you.
Okay. I'll hang up now.
Tomorrow, I'm going back to Australia
with Sunny.
When are you coming back?
I don't think I'm coming back.
You are not coming back?
I'll leave the case
to both of you.
Don't worry. Everything will be fine.
There's something else
that I think Miss Qin doesn't know.
What is it?
Yang Hua will be coming with me.
My dear.
Why are you so funny?
Yang Hua is not your luggage.
Go with you?
How?
Pack him up and ship him over?
They are already divorced.
What?
Qin Shi, are you and Yang Hua divorced?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm supposed to be the next one.
How can you cut the line?
Qin Shi
did so much for this case.
But what are you doing now?
You want to kidnap her husband
to Australia.
How can you do that?
I'm really mad now.
He won't go with you.
My flight
is at 11:30 tomorrow.
If you are that capable,
make him stay.
I'll get going now.
Don't turn back. Come with me.
They have left.
Chase after them.
They are really gone now.
Miss Qin needs to be straightened out
with more force.
I don't know
why the two of you
are fighting like this
although you love each other.
But I can tell
that you like her.
And you like her a lot, right?
I really like her.
I've never liked
anyone else as much as I like her.
Can't you at least reel it in
when you are with me?
I'm sorry.
That's why you have to listen to me.
In this relationship with her,
even if you can
walk all the way to her,
she'll have to be the one
to take the last step toward you.
Do you understand?
♪Because of excuses♪
♪The process diverges our path ♪
♪And throws us off our rhythm♪
♪Both hearts are stuck at the junction♪
♪Because of excuses♪
♪I passively accept it
instead of enjoying it♪
♪I tentatively begging♪
♪For reasons♪
♪A clearly unconvincing excuse♪
♪Like the blame placed on another♪
♪So eagerly cast away,
but so painful to part with it♪
♪Pretending to tolerate
in painful frustration♪
♪A clearly reckless idea♪
♪Like a bottle of aged liquor♪
♪It's transiently invalid
but soberly patched together♪
♪Hiding the everlasting love
that cannot be given up♪
♪Having it once is not what we want♪
♪Hugging is the feeling at the moment♪
♪Being apologetic about the past,
praying for the future♪
♪They are all excuses♪
♪Learning to endure is not what we want♪
♪We should've enjoyed holding hands♪
♪Exploring the sea of stars
and sticking together in difficulties♪
♪Why does it become a luxury?♪
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
We couldn't find out anywhere.
We were so anxious.
What's wrong?
What happened?
♪So eagerly cast away,
but so painful to part with it♪
You are fine now.
♪A clearly reckless idea♪
♪Like a bottle of aged liquor♪
Finally, I found you.
What happened?
What's wrong? Did someone bully you?
Who is bold enough to bully you?
Wenyu.
What's wrong?
Qin Shi, are you too tired?
Just cry all you want.
We are all here.
You are fine now.
♪Learning to endure is not what we want♪
♪We should've enjoyed holding hands♪
♪Exploring the sea of stars
and sticking together in difficulties♪
♪Why does it become a luxury?♪
♪Because of excuses♪
♪The process diverges our path ♪
♪And throws us off our rhythm♪
♪Both hearts are stuck at the junction♪
Are you awake now?
Wash your face and brush your teeth.
The porridge will be ready soon.
Here.
Why are the two of you here?
Looks like you've forgotten.
You were drunk yesterday.
And we sent you back.
It was too late.
So, we stayed here.
Where was your husband?
Why didn't he pick you up?
He's on a business trip.
You are no longer young.
How could you
drink so much
and wander around under the rain
in the middle of the night?
What if something happens to you?
Even if you can take it,
our father and your mother
can't take it.
Now,
even you can lecture me.
This is called growth.
Do you understand?
After you eat,
take the flu medicine.
You are usually a force of nature.
But you don't know
how to take care of yourself.
Even I can take care of myself.
You need to grow up too.
Do you understand?
Okay.
You manage to keep this alive.
Put that down.
What's wrong? Can't I look at it?
So petty.
No.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I...
Let me help you with it.
You don't have to. Move aside.
Stand back.
Let me help her.
Come. Let me clean it up for you.
Here.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I really didn't do it on purpose.
Be careful not to cut your hands.
Let me do it.
I'll get to work then.
Okay.
I really didn't do it on purpose.
Get up. I'll clean this up.
Even Wenyu is going to work now.
Wenyu
has changed a lot this time.
I thought
that he would be depressed for a while.
I never thought
that he would be working diligently
in the company.
He said
that Meimei could come back at any time.
He doesn't want Meimei
to see him as a dispirited
and depressed man.
By the way,
Qin Shi.
Later, tell Meimei
to take good care of herself.
Ask her not to come back too quickly.
This time,
we need to make sure that Wenyu
can turn into a better man.
I've only managed
to contact her recently.
Are you having a fight
with Yang Hua?
No.
Really?
Will this
mint plant
die?
You dummy.
Don't be frightened by the despair
that you see in other's life.
Because that is not your life.
You need to believe in yourself
that you'll find
your own happiness.
I don't think
that I have any rights
to own any kind of happiness now.
I don't know
what I should do now.
I don't know what happened
between you and Yang Hua.
But I know
that a person's happiness
depends on the person's sense of safety.
Your home is where
your peace of mind is.
Okay now. I have to go to work now.
Remember to take your medicine.
Be good.
You are home.
You are here.
I'm on leave today.
So, I want
to come here
to check on you.
Look at you.
If I didn't come,
your house would be a mess.
You came here two days ago, right?
You bought me a bunch of food.
I haven't even finished
the food in the fridge.
This...
I didn't buy the food.
I wasn't here.
You weren't here?
Qin Shi,
your father and I already know
about you and Yang Hua.
What are you talking about?
Everything.
You?
Is this
a joke?
How can you
treat your marriage so lightly?
Mr. Qin, Mrs. Qin.
Qin Shi and I
chose to start
and end like this
not because
we treat our marriage lightly.
On the contrary,
Qin Shi cares about marriage
more than anyone.
She's doing her best to protect
every marriage
in this family.
Because of that,
she has no confidence
in her own marriage.
And that's why
I choose to divorce her.
You are talking in circles.
What are you trying to say?
Qin,
let him finish.
Yang,
go ahead and continue.
I don't want to let Qin Shi
run away from her true feelings anymore.
And I don't want her
to use this fake marriage
as a way to avoid
the happiness she deserves.
So, I've given her something
that I can provide.
Freedom.
Today, I'm here to beg you
not to pressure Qin Shi
anymore.
Don't blame her for this too.
Marriage is not important
to me at all.
The most important thing is
to be with her.
As long as she's willing,
I don't mind even if
we don't get married forever.
I want
to get your permission
to let me take good care of Qin Shi
forever.
Did we go overboard yesterday?
What if our plan backfires on us?
It's okay. Leave the rest
to me.
Not bad.
You are a real man now.
Are you really not going
to go to Australia with me?
There are many women
like Miss Qin over there.
Mother.
Look. Even your son
doesn't believe you.
What is it?
I have a girlfriend. I can't do that.
This is your marriage fund.
Keep it well.
I didn't use
any of the money.
We'll get going now.
Let's go.
Bye.
(International, HK, Macao,
Taiwan Departures)
♪Don't worry. How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry, don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them
to keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes, we give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes,
we want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry, do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry, let it heal♪
♪Grow to be
the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season, we all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants
to keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
(Seven Months Later)
Are you ready to start now?
Are you ready?
Miss Qin, Miss Li.
Hello.
We are from the "Legal Ethics" column
of Pujiang Television Station.
First, I want to congratulate
both of you.
After more than seven months
of waiting,
Our city's
first sexual class action
has already come to an end.
Can you please tell us
the verdict?
The verdict...
The court has upheld
all of our litigation claims.
The court has given us
the highest financial compensation
within the scope of legal aid.
Although the compensation
is far from enough for the victims
who were mentally abused
for a long time,
it can set an example
for other similar cases.
Besides civil compensation,
what other punishments
does Yin Zhiqiang
have to face?
From what we know,
during the lawsuit, Yin Zhiqiang
has already been suspended from work.
This case
involves forced indecency,
attempted rape,
and abetted perjury
of He Dongna.
So, the procuratorate has filed
a public prosecution
against him.
And those who are involved
in the He Dongna
abetted perjury case
will be put into detention too.
Look
at the office
that I've decorated for you.
What do you think?
Look at this. This is
a massage chair imported from Japan.
It's very comfortable.
Qin Shi.
You've done well
with this lawsuit.
You've earned both profit and fame.
Besides, a lot of corporations
want to carry out
sexual harassment prevention now.
It's a huge market.
You are here this time
as a senior partner.
Just tell us the salary
and benefits that you want.
If I can do it,
I'll fulfil your requests.
Come and take a seat over here.
Let's not beat around the bush anymore.
Do you have a case this time
that I have to take?
You fox.
Do you still remember Ms. Lan?
Life has come back to a full circle.
Last week, Ms. Lan
received a call from abroad.
Pang Dingfang was speeding
on the highway abroad
and got into an accident.
He and his lover passed away
from the accident.
Ms. Lan has to go abroad
to inherit
all of Pang Dingfang's assets.
And she has appointed you as her lawyer.
Qin Shi.
I know that you care the most
about our firm's principle
regarding lawyers who are single.
Actually, after you left,
Yihui and I
have reflected on it.
We realise that it's inappropriate.
So after that,
we've already corrected
that mistake.
Now,
Cheng & Hui's principle is,
regardless of one's single status
or having to take maternity leave,
we'll treat everyone the same.
Yes. Not only that,
as long as the lawyer has a child,
regardless of the lawyer's gender,
they'll be given
an allowance accordingly.
We are working on the nursing rooms
and childcare facilities too.
That's great.
I think
that Yang Hua is right.
If Cheng & Hui
wants to continue improving
in the long term,
we can't lose our faith.
As lawyers with professional ethics,
justice and righteousness
go hand in hand.
This is the conscience of our firm.
Am I right?
Are you still in contact with Yang Hua?
Of course.
He is the CEO of the Capital Markets
under Mr. Hu now.
When we opened up a new branch
in Australia,
he was there too.
He was still the same.
Didn't he tell you
that we are divorced?
I...
Hui.
Will you still allow me
to join Cheng & Hui?
Qin Shi.
Will you listen to me?
Cheng & Hui
is not a perfect firm.
When we are progressing and developing
in a fast pace,
there are things that can get neglected.
But one thing for sure is,
all the lawyers in our firm are great.
We are inviting you to join us today
not because of Ms. Lan's case.
And it's not because
of your relationship with Yang Hua.
But because
you are a good lawyer.
What's so precious about you is,
you are a lawyer
with a firm principle and conscience.
Not only Yihui,
even I have to learn from you.
Actually,
we founded Cheng & Hui
because we couldn't take it anymore
when our previous boss
compromised for money.
We hope that just like you,
we can hold true to our principles
no matter what pressure we are in.
But the most regretful thing is,
we couldn't do it.
We've become matured
and more accommodating.
But we know
what we lost.
We are asking you to join us today
not just because of your victory.
We also hope
that we can regain
our past principles and persistence.
Even if
it's something
that we have once abandoned.
Yihui, Mr. Jin.
I'm really thankful
that you are telling me this
today.
I think that today
is the most unforgettable day
in my life.
Thank you for telling me this.
It makes me know
that my persistence before this
is worth it.
But I think
I still have to reject your offer.
I know that by saying this now,
it'll seem like I'm being ungrateful.
But
during this period of working alone
in the outside world, I'm quite happy.
I am
really thankful to you
for giving me this chance
to do something crazy.
A chance for me
to do something outrageous
regardless of my own safety.
So, I've decided
to work alone.
As you said,
I'm a stubborn person
who can't work under anyone.
If I work under you,
I'll only frustrate you more.
So, for everyone's sake,
Let's work together starting
from this case with Ms. Lan.
Let me think.
We can split the agency fee in half.
What do you think?
Deal.
Thank you.
You are so nice to me.
You are back, Miss Qin.
Yes!
Mr. Tao.
Bye.
Mr. Tao, are you leaving now?
Yes.
Do you need any help?
It's okay. Thank you.
Miss Qin.
You've resigned?
Why?
It has nothing to do with you.
I already have my first big case
at my firm.
If you are interested,
you can come to my firm.
I won't go.
Don't be petty.
Why should I give up
millions of annual salary
to work at your lousy firm?
Let me inform you officially now.
I am now the person in charge
of the Northwest Division
of Cheng & Hui.
Really?
If you have any big cases after this,
remember to find me.
Depends on the situation.
I wish you happiness.
You better
think about yourself.
Don't come back to me when you've become
a lonely old woman.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Qin Shi.
You'll find your happiness.
Same to you.
Bye.
Hello.
Qin Shi, I'm going into labour now.
Isn't it one week away?
I got it. I'm coming.
Mr. Tao.
Hello, Mr. Tao Junhui.
I'm the new legal assistant.
Wu Fei.
Hope that we can
get along well after this.
Nice working with you.
Learn well.
My wife is going into labour.
My wife is going into labour!
Hang on.
I'll be there soon.
Let me sing you a song.
I can't take it anymore.
What song do you want to listen to?
What do you want to listen to?
Well.
♪If you're happy and you know it♪
♪Clap your hands♪
Stop it.
Keep it up!
We'll be there soon!
♪High on the mountain♪
Okay. You are fine.
Keep it up.
Okay. Keep it up.
Look at your grandmother.
I'm so happy.
Qin Shi, I'm so happy.
Aunt, let's take a family photo.
Here's your aunt.
My big and small baby.
(This is the ending)
(for the story of most people.)
(I've thought about it a lot)
(in this period of time.)
(You have your freedom
when you are alone.)
(But it feels comfortable too
to have another person with you.)
(Yang Hua is right.)
(I need time and space)
(to figure out what I want.)
(I realise)
(that now.)
(What about him?)
Hi, little kid.
Where are you from?
Why are you here?
You look familiar.
Let's move the bed now.
Hey, handsome.
Are you looking for it?
♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
Didn't you leave with Yao Yao?
Why are you back?
Who told you that I left with her?
Didn't you see?
I was renovating the house
besides yours for three months.
How would I know it was you?
I miss you.
Me too.
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
Don't leave again.
Don't leave ever again.
No problem.
It's a deal then.
You still haven't answered my question.
What question?
Are you...
Are you here for Yao Yao
or me.
There's only
one person in my heart.
And that's you.
In the past,
in the now,
and in the future.
By the way,
what is the meaning of those numbers?
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
Enter the password.
♪I want to keep looking at you,
and may our love last forever♪
That simple?
It's that simple.
How can you be so stupid?
How did you win the lawsuit?
Why is it losing so much money?
The code of this stock
is the date of our wedding.
And it's the only time
I bought a stock
without analysing it.
Whether it's going down or up,
I'll still buy it every month.
Although it was losing a lot of money
at one point,
I still didn't sell it.
Even if it's not making any profit now.
When are you going to sell it?
I plan to keep it forever.
For how long?
Forever and ever.
What if you lose too much money from it.
I believe that it can
outperform everything.
And this will be
the assets
for our future generation.
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them♪
♪To keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes♪
♪We give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes♪
♪We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Let it heal♪
♪Grow♪
♪To be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season♪
♪We all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants♪
♪To keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible♪
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪