♪I want to be with you every day♪
♪With the press of a button♪
♪Watching this love drama
that updates every day♪
♪From the first episode of the first season
to the never-ending finale♪
♪I want to see the sweet you
in every episode♪
♪I want to watch a romantic scene
♪Like a music video♪
♪Every foreshadowing
is for a happily ever after♪
♪There will be storms and hurricanes
but they are not the main themes♪
♪I want to make a montage of you♪
♪I'll focus on your cheekiness
and cuteness♪
♪I'll capture your little emotions
with precise shots♪
♪Following your steps in the dream♪
♪I'll bottle your tenderness
and thoughtfulness♪
♪I'll indulge all your tantrums♪
♪I'll watch every scene that features you
and replay them in my heart♪
=She And Her Perfect Husband=
=Episode 38=
When a lawyer talks seriously
about professional ethics,
he's just trying to cover up the fact
that he has become
a gunman of money or power
or a legal technician.
Okay, I admit it.
I have no principles
other than winning the case.
You have no principles?
You refused me
because of your principles.
Sorry.
I was drunk that day.
But I remember every word
I told you.
I respect your choice.
But let's look at the relationship
and career separately.
Please don't refuse
my help with your work.
Let's go to the spicy hot pot restaurant
at the school gate.
It's on me.
I still have work to do.
I'll wait for you
at the school gate at ten o'clock.
How's your mother recently?
My mom passed away three years ago.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I think
it's a relief for her.
How are you doing?
The situation was
a little special last time.
I haven't had time to ask you.
I'm all right.
I can tell it.
I thought
you and Mr. Qiu's daughter have...
I won't do so.
I've said it earlier.
I recall that
I once cursed you angrily that
your career and marriage
would be ruined
and you'd regret
everything you've done.
But then
I saw the news
of Qiu Jianxiang's accident.
I was scared and happy at the same time.
I thought I cursed him too hard.
Look.
I'm not doing well now.
Recalling what happened in the past,
I even thought
it was right that
we weren't together.
I mean it.
I was too stubborn before.
Actually, I feel inferior.
I always feel that
I'm not as good as others.
I was competitive in every aspect.
Even if I got it,
I still felt uneasy.
I think what others give me
is not mine.
I feel insecure.
And I don't know how to cherish it.
What are you going to do after this?
Wait for the verdict.
And then find a way to raise money.
Have you found a way?
I'll give it a try.
Our house relocated before.
I got a small house.
It should be worth
about one million yuan now.
Take a look.
Is there anything you like to eat?
Chocolate flavour.
Give me a piece. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Be careful.
Say goodbye to Uncle and Aunt.
Goodbye, Uncle. Goodbye, Aunt.
- Goodbye.
Thank you.
There's no need.
I didn't help you much.
I appreciate your kindness.
We're leaving.
Let's get in the car.
Goodbye.
Be careful.
I seem to know something amazing.
But I don't have any evidence.
It's hard to say.
And I don't dare to ask.
Do you think
I should tell Qin Shi?
Is he a gentleman,
or he's good to every girl?
(It's true.)
(If you see Yao Yao's son,)
(you'll also doubt it.)
(He looks just like Yang Hua.)
(Yang Hua is serious about this case.)
(No wonder.)
(Yao Yao is his ex-girlfriend, after all.)
Now she's a single mother.
And a weak woman
suffering from social bullying.
It makes me want to protect her as well.
You called me just to tell me this.
Are you getting so bored now?
Isn't it worth gossiping about?
Let me remind you.
You have to be more vigilant
and keep an eye on Yang Hua.
(You know what you think of him.)
(I just kindly remind you.)
It's hard to find
a suitable boyfriend
in this society.
If you let go of him,
they will be a whole family.
These photos don't look good.
That's my skill.
What else do you want it to look like?
Can you take
that kind of photo
that is casual but beautiful?
Give it a try.
Casual?
Not this kind of angle.
Be natural.
If you keep doing this,
I'll be more unnatural.
Be natural.
Okay. Like this.
Good.
Like this?
No.
Delete it.
Miss Qin, the thin face filter
is too over.
I'm out of shape.
Your hair is messy.
Come on. Let's take another photo.
♪When sadness comes♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes
We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪If possible
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪
Hello.
Where are you?
I'd better not go.
It's not right.
(Meimei)
Thank you so much.
Let's not say anything else.
Don't think too much.
I'm waiting for you at the company gate.
(Call hold)
Hello.
(Your second brother is missing.)
Hello, Cai Liang.
About the loan application.
Stop it.
Don't rush me, okay?
I made it urgent for you.
You both have divorced, anyway.
What's the hurry?
Please withdraw the loan application for me.
You're not going to buy it?
No, Yang Hua. Think it over.
You've paid the deposit.
(You'll suffer losses)
(if you're not going to buy it.)
Please explain this to the landlord for me.
I'm hanging up.
Hello?
Hello.
Yang Hua? Why are you here?
Meimei asked me to come.
You're finally here, Shi.
I can't get through to your brother.
I'm so worried.
What should I do?
Don't worry.
It's about 10 p.m.
What can happen to a man?
Don't you know that
he went to collect the money today?
Your brother carries a cheque of millions.
There are many people at the collection place.
Will something happen to him?
I'm afraid.
Did he go alone?
No, with Bai
from the finance department.
But Bai came back long ago.
He brought back the gifts from
the customers of
the seafood market to me.
He said Wenyu
went to the last shop himself.
Which shop?
I think it'd be safer
to call the police first.
The police don't have
to do anything else
if they go to the bar
to catch a husband fooling around.
Can you drive faster?
Okay.
After I get in,
if someone stops me,
pull him away from me.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
What are you doing?
- Leave me alone.
- Are you kidding me?
The security guard
may not let you in if you're like this.
Can you use your loaf?
Then what should I do?
You're looking for your brother, right?
I'll go. Wait for me here.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you.
Come on. Let's drink.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Why are you standing there?
Go and have a look.
You too.
We'll deal with it immediately.
We'll deal with it right away, okay?
Don't go.
We'll deal with it.
Immediately.
Don't worry, everyone.
Don't go.
Boss, is it all right?
It's not all right.
Didn't we pay the electricity bill?
I don't know either.
You don't know?
Go and solve it.
Hurry up. Don't just stand here.
Honestly.
It's been a while.
(Where is he?)
(In the hotel near the bar street.)
(I'll bring him back.)
(Qin Shi.)
(If you still regard me as your friend,)
(don't move. Don't go inside.)
(Don't do anything.)
(Wait for me.)
(I'll see it myself.)
♪I've gone through heartbreak,
I've seen hope♪
♪I have to keep going to keep growing♪
♪Getting lost in love,
the power of love♪
♪The feelings of love♪
♪Choosing to forget, choosing to stare♪
♪My gaze is what I desire the most♪
♪The wandering breeze,
the voyage of the rain♪
♪The reward of love♪
♪Passionate love glows, passion shines♪
♪My initial aspiration is
to not let go of your hands♪
♪The dream of a dream,
the swaying of a dream♪
♪Tonight,
the window of my heart will be open♪
I'll talk to Meimei later.
Meimei.
Is it this room?
Room card.
Meimei.
We just saw the surveillance video.
Wenyu is really drunk.
He's drunk. He...
Room card!
She has to face this.
(It's said that women are weak
until they become mothers.)
(But how many people know that)
(the moment a woman becomes a mother)
(is also her most vulnerable moment?)
(If there was no one to rely on,)
(no room for retreat and in danger,)
(who would burst out of a small universe)
(in a peaceful life?)
(But as a mother,)
(she has to become)
(the strongest fortress in the world.)
(And she has the softest heart in the world.)
Sunny.
Do you know that I love you?
Go to sleep. Goodnight.
Goodnight, Mom.
I'll turn off the light.
Mom.
I hope you can still be a soldier.
The enemy I meet now is too strong.
What if I lose?
Mom, you told me
victory or defeat is temporary.
If you lose this time,
you'll know what your shortcomings are.
You'll become stronger next time.
So it's not terrible to lose.
♪Passionate love glows, passion shines♪
♪My initial aspiration is
to not let go of your hands♪
Go to sleep.
Tuck yourself in.
Time to turn off the light.
♪Tonight,
the window of my heart will be open♪
Is Meimei asleep?
She's asleep.
Then I...
Are you hungry?
Let me order something for you to eat.
You're eating takeout again.
You know my cooking skill.
Have you moved back home?
Not yet.
I rented a house temporarily.
Do you get used to it?
Not really.
But I may adapt to it.
By the way, I finally understand
why you're afraid of getting married.
The last time when they had a conflict
and caused chaos,
I could feel that
Meimei actually enjoyed it.
But she was unusually calm this time.
But I think her calmness
is more terrifying than her outburst.
A marriage with problems
will really wear a person out.
It seems that I've made
the right choice.
At least I don't have to face
such a situation.
Fortunately, you divorced.
Otherwise,
we may get into
a bigger conflict than them.
Will we?
♪Don't worry.
How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
Spend more time with her. I'll go first.
Let me see you off.
It's okay.
Go to bed early. Don't think too much.
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them
to keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes,
we give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes,
we want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry.
Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry.
Let it heal♪
♪Grow to be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season we all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants
to keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible.
Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪
Hello.
♪Don't worry.
Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
(When I was a child,)
(I couldn't understand why the heroine)
(would work so hard to clean up)
(when she encountered a problem)
(and couldn't release it.)
(At that time,)
(I thought she was very pretentious.)
(But it turned out)
(I would do the same thing)
(when it happened to me.)
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants
to keep the best memories♪
(Yang Hua.)
(Do I miss you?)
(Or am I just being silly?)
♪If possible.
Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪
Didn't you sleep well?
Where's your son?
He's not at home?
He went to a tutorial class.
The lessons in Australia
are too easy for him.
His father doesn't want him
to skip a grade.
After returning to China,
he takes math classes here.
The basic education of Science
in China is quite good.
Why are you looking for me?
If you want to
get out of this case,
you must cooperate with me.
Are you going to help me?
I have a win-win solution.
Would you like to hear it?
Is it unconditional?
No, of course.
Stay away from Yang Hua.
Miss Qin.
What's the matter?
Why did you mislead Yang Hua?
What did I do?
You know clearly what you did.
Are you here today
to talk about business
or personal matters?
I know
you're in a bad condition.
But why did you
make Yang Hua misunderstand
that he's the father of your child?
It's shameless of you to do so.
Have you ever had a fight?
Although you're older than me,
you look like a good student
who only loves reading since childhood.
Reading more is a good thing.
But people who read a lot
have a big problem.
They're very reasonable.
It's no use being only reasonable
in this society.
Shameless. Shame on you.
I didn't use such childish lines
in quarrelling
when I was 14.
And how do you know
I mislead him?
What are you trying to say?
Turn off your recording.
What recording?
One more.
I don't know how much
you know about Yang Hua.
He seems very open-minded
about everything,
but he cares about
the people he loves.
Do you agree with that?
In fact, there's a turning point
in this case.
As long as you cooperate with me,
I can win over it.
Cooperate with you?
As far as I know,
you've always been
on the side of Yin Zhiqiang.
But I'm not Yin Zhiqiang's lawyer.
I'm Tianhang's lawyer.
What I have to do
is to protect the interests of Tianhang
to the greatest extent.
Miss Qin.
What are you trying to say?
I want you to withdraw the lawsuit.
I look forward to working with you.
Me too.
And I don't care about
your past relationship with Yang Hua.
Whether Sunny is his son or not,
he's mine now.
If you dare to lay hands on him,
I won't let you go
whether I can beat you.
She left. Why haven't you come out yet?
You heard what Miss Qin said just now.
What's wrong with you two?
Why didn't you tell your wife
before you did anything?
She looked like
she would eat me alive.
She's always so reckless.
I didn't know
how she became a lawyer.
For goodness' sake.
I'm annoyed enough.
Yet, you come to me
and show off your affection.
But Yang Hua,
you were not so considerate before.
I used to be annoying, right?
A little.
You changed so much
because of her, right?
If Miss Qin really did
what she just said,
would her law firm make things
difficult for her?
That's what I should worry about.
Then can I trust her?
Absolutely.
She's a good lawyer.
I'll try then.
Oh, right.
Take the money back.
There's no need.
You don't owe me anything.
Take the money.
You'll use it later.
I can earn it more.
But don't tell Qin Shi
what I just said.
It seems you really like her.
I'm leaving.
Meimei.
You're not up yet.
She's not here.
That's great.
I was scared.
Really.
(Portfolio Qin Wenyu)
(Missed call Qin Shi Missed call Meimei)
(I'll send the photo to Mrs. Qin)
(if you don't give me a rent reduction.)
Pick up the phone.
(Hello, the number you've dialed)
(has opened the inquiry reminder service.)
Meimei.
I'm home. Where are you?
Well.
Come back and tell me
what you want to say.
I know I was wrong.
You can beat me or scold me
when you come back.
Let me explain it.
I really know I was wrong.
Come back first.
(Qin Wenyu
The message has been sent but rejected.)
I...
Hello.
Where did you hide Meimei?
(Let me tell you.)
(Meimei is now pregnant.)
If something happens to her,
I won't spare you.
I was framed.
I really went to collect
the rent yesterday.
Hu set me up.
I don't know anything.
I don't even know
how I got into the hotel.
What can I do?
I didn't do anything.
Qin Shi, please.
Trust me.
Every word I said is true.
If I lied,
I'd be hit to death by a car
or killed by thunder.
I trust you.
Thank you.
You're my sister, indeed.
Where's Meimei?
I don't know where Meimei is.
Qin Shi!
It's what Meimei told me.
Listen to it.
(Qin Shi, I'm going out for a walk.)
(Don't worry.)
(I won't do anything stupid.)
(I understand all the situations)
(you analyzed with me.)
(I know)
(you may be right.)
(Wenyu might be drunk)
(and was set up.)
Go upstairs first.
I'll go home and pack some clothes
before I come to accompany you.
It's okay. I can go up myself.
Well, I'm not going back.
I'll go upstairs with you.
Well, I'm really all right.
I want to be alone for a while.
Please.
(I couldn't fall asleep.)
(I lied in bed thinking a lot.)
(I forgave him again and again.)
(I was betrayed again and again.)
(I was heartbroken again and again.)
(We reconciled again and again.)
(What do I love,)
(look forward to,)
(and what can't I let go of)
(in this marriage?)
(The answer is simple.)
(I love Wenyu.)
(This kind of love has become a habit)
(and a dependence.)
(I was really scared)
(when I knew that I'm pregnant.)
(I don't know)
(if Wenyu can be a good father.)
(I have no confidence at all.)
(When I stood in the hotel room,)
(this fear)
(turned into a great fear.)
(I didn't know how to face)
(what I was going to see.)
(If he cheated on me,)
(how could I face all this?)
(How can I take care)
(of my child alone?)
(But it's not the most horrible thing.)
(The most horrible thing is that)
(even if Wenyu doesn't cheat this time,)
(how about the next time?)
(And the next time?)
(When I thought of this,)
(I found that)
(I had completely lost)
(my trust in Wenyu.)
(Many people say that)
(it's either cheating several times
or not even once.)
(I believe it.)
(I don't want)
(to be a resentful wife.)
(I hate to be suspicious)
(and check his phone)
(all day long.)
(I don't want to play)
(the chase game anymore.)
(Shi.)
(I'll leave the rest )
(to you.)
(Wenyu may not stand it)
(and come to me.)
(Persuade him.)
Meimei won't go.
How about the company if she leaves?
She won't leave the company behind.
She won't leave Mom alone.
And me, right?
She just went out for a walk in anger.
Qin Shi.
Take me to find Meimei back.
Qin Wenyu.
I really can't help you this time.
A completely disheartened woman
can leave in many ways.
No.
If you hadn't instigated Meimei,
she wouldn't have left.
You're responsible for it.
You asked me to be responsible for it?
It's your marriage.
Did I make Meimei angry again and again?
Did I ask you to hang out
with those bad friends every day?
Did I make you surrounded
by so many women every day?
How dare you tell me that.
You don't deserve anyone to help you
just because you said that.
I was not worried every time
you quarreled with each other,
no matter how fierce it was.
I don't think
you two will be apart at all.
I know how much
you love each other.
Because every time
you look at each other,
there's light in your eyes.
But it's different this time.
It's useless for me to say anything.
I think I can't help you this time.
I know you feel bad.
The one who left may feel upset too.
Whenever you feel
you should reconcile,
it consumes your trust and affection.
Take responsibility for your life.
I've said enough
about this.
I don't want to say anymore.
No matter what decision Meimei made,
you'd better
live your own life first.
♪Don't worry♪
♪How can I forget?♪
♪We have become♪
♪The most important person
to each other♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Don't doubt it♪
♪Keep some memories in your heart♪
♪In case you need them♪
♪To keep you company♪
♪When sadness comes♪
♪We give up easily♪
♪Sadness without a wound♪
♪Doesn't have to heal properly♪
♪When happiness comes♪
♪We want it to last forever♪
♪Happiness without tears♪
♪Is hardly memorable♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Do not hesitate♪
♪Waiting will not pull you closer♪
♪To the opportunity you want♪
♪Don't worry♪
♪Let it heal♪
♪Grow♪
♪To be the best version of yourself♪
♪In the cold season♪
♪We all hide♪
♪A relationship without a bond♪
♪Is as fragile as eggshells♪
♪Everyone wants♪
♪To keep the best memories♪
♪For the nights they have dreams♪
♪So stubborn that they know no fear♪
♪If possible♪
♪Don't give up♪
♪I used to want to find you♪