From this night on
There’s only us under the lights
As if time itself has stopped
So I can remember
Your face before it's gone
PREVIOUSLY
I want to live my best life
in the Best Before End period.
If you didn't have me,
you wouldn't be so tired. Right?
I will become a musician.
I will become a doctor.
I'm not ready to leave yet!
PUSH
Please come in.
This way.
Where are you, Alice?
When will you come back?
You have to come back.
I’m not ready to leave yet!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, can you see me?
Hello.
Are you going with us?
Alice, get on!
Where did you get the motorcycle from?
I borrowed it.
What? I don't believe you.
I really borrowed it.
It's from the smoothie shop at Siam.
I borrow it all the time.
I already texted them.
They'll come pick it up later.
Wait, hold on.
Hm?
How can you even see me?
I'm glad I found you, Alice.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Three years ago,
I went to visit relatives upcountry.
One day I went out
for a bike ride near the house.
And then…
Hey!
How are you feeling? You're awake?
Let me check your condition.
Take a deep breath.
Exhale.
Okay, good.
Yes.
Please rest for now.
I'll come check again around noon.
MALE PATIENT WARD
Are you okay, sir?
I'll call the nurse for you.
Come with me.
- Let go! Let go! Help!
- Come with me.
- No! I won't go!
You're coming with me.
- Help! Help!
- Sir, calm down.
Please calm down.
It's okay, sir. Take it easy.
It's nothing, calm down.
Please calm down.
It's nothing.
Calm down. There's nothing wrong.
Please calm down.
Since that car accident,
I've been able to see spirits.
They come to me all the time, to talk,
to tell me something,
to ask for help.
No wonder
I always saw you talking to yourself.
Well, what do you need me to do?
Where should I find it?
Can you remember your house?
If you can, try going back there.
Or maybe go to a temple.
Okay, I'll dedicate merit for you.
Pizza? Okay, I'll send you pizza, okay?
Stop following me already. Go.
And who told you to come find me?
To give you pizza?
Oh, that guy, right?
Whoa, come on.
I'll take you home, okay?
But promise me
you won't tell anyone about this.
It'll get complicated.
Understand? Come on, let's go.
Thanks, Auntie.
Here.
A green soda. You wanted it, right?
Drink as much as you want.
Then stop following me everywhere,
You follow me everywhere. It's awkward.
Let's go our separate ways.
If you're going to reincarnate, do it.
At first, I thought
you were bonkers
Well…
that's why I pretend
to be on the phone.
I wear this earbud, but actually,
I'm talking to ghosts.
Hey, I'm not a ghost. I'm just…
I know, Alice. You're not dead yet.
I visit you every day at the hospital.
Come on.
Don't worry too much.
There has to be a way for you to
get back to your body somehow.
I don't think there's a way anymore.
Because I just ran away from him.
Who?
There's no way.
Your time has already ended.
Hey, what are you doing?
Who are you? Why are you saying that?
I don't need to tell you who I am.
When your time comes, we'll meet again.
Don't you remember me?
Huh?
Hey, let go!
You let go.
If you don't, we'll all go together.
We've met before.
Don't you remember?
No? Fine.
Welcome, both of you,
to this special train. Once it departs,
it can never return.
Actually,
you really shouldn't
have followed her here.
Do you know
when you refuse to let Alice go,
what happens to your body
in the living world?
Has Punn arrived yet?
How was he when it happened?
- Not yet? Okay, I'll check.
- I don't know either.
He was just standing there
talking on the phone,
then suddenly collapsed.
Maybe heatstroke, I'm not sure.
Punn. Punn!
Hey.
What's wrong with my friend?
Hold on. Please calm down.
- Your friend…
- Punn.
The girl who reported it said
he just suddenly fainted.
Let us take your friend
to the doctor first.
- Punn.
- One, two, three.
- Can I go with you, please?
- Yes, come with us.
Punn!
Hey, what's wrong? Wake up.
Punn. Punn.
Is Punn going to die?
Maybe.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Calm down,
young man.
I warning you.
If you stay in the afterlife too long,
you might not be able to return.
Then let's go back now. Come on, Alice.
I'm not ready to leave yet.
That trick won't work again.
It only works once.
You finally came.
I've been waiting for hours.
If you hadn't shown up in 15 minutes,
I was gonna go home.
Where's Punn anyway?
Punn…
I…
Hey, wait.
He…
Hey.
Calm down, man. If you keep stuttering,
I can't understand you.
Punn…
Hey, calm down, bro.
Take it easy, okay?
Stop crying, please. Stop crying.
Just tell me what happened.
Take a deep breath.
The doctor said Punn's in a coma.
I don't know…
They said his body
isn't responding anymore.
You mean
Punn's dead?
I don't know. He…
Hey, calm down. Calm down!
I don't believe you.
Take me there right now.
Calm down.
If you once gave me another chance,
can't you give Alice one too?
What to do?
My duty is quite complicated.
When a mortal's time has run out,
I cannot simply spare a life
or allow someone
to remain in the living world.
Please.
There's still so much I want to do.
I don't want to die yet.
The song I wrote isn't even finished.
I haven't released it.
I want to sing, play music,
and live a life with the person I love.
I'm begging you too.
Please, give us one more chance.
We'll trade it for anything.
I once saved someone's life.
So why
can't I have the chance to live mine?
Because you saved someone else.
Now you're here in their place.
Then what about me?
Why didn't you take me back then?
Because at that time,
someone else
sacrificed their life for you to stay.
Hey, I told you I'm driving,
I can't talk right now.
I'll call you back, I'm going to pick up
my kid and my husband.
Please don't hang up.
I'm calling to inform you that your
husband and your child have passed away.
You can claim the bodies at… Hello?
Hey!
See?
You're shocked, aren't you?
But that's not even the end of the story.
That woman
didn't know her husband and her kid
weren't actually on that bus.
The kid had a stomachache,
so the father took him to the restroom.
But when they came out,
the bus had already left.
What a tragic story.
Back then,
she willingly traded her life because
she couldn't go on living
without her beloved family.
Now you see?
Do you understand yet?
Then that means…
for Alice to keep living,
a life must be exchanged.
That's right.
So whose life will it be?
- Yours?
- No.
I won't allow it.
- How can I live if you--
- I'll do it.
No, I won't let you.
- Take me instead.
- Enough.
Alright then.
I'll give you both a mission.
And if you complete it,
you'll get your life back.
Do we have a deal?
Do we?
Hey, wait.
What kind of mission? Tell us first.
Let's see
how it'll turn out.
- Punn, are you okay?
- Yes.
Wait, did that car just pass through us?
Are we both spirits now?
Yeah, looks like it.
Jinny. Jinny.
Jinny. Jinny!
Hold on. Why are we here?
Shouldn't you have gone back to your body?
Exactly.
Are you okay?
I have to be.
There's still too much I want to do.
From now on,
I won't let anyone take away
my hope, my dreams,
or the life I want to live ever again.
Let's go check on you.
I don't want to waste any more time.
Let's go.
MALE PATIENT WARD
Found me.
Hey! What are you doing?
Get out!
I said get out!
What should we do now?
Let's try this.
Do you feel anything?
Nothing. Why?
So what now?
If you keep fooling around,
you'll run out of time.
I'm not fooling around.
I just don't know
how to get back into my body.
And what did you mean
by run out of time? What was that?
If you don't get back into your body soon,
something else will.
What about my body?
You mean someone else could possess it?
Right?
Yes.
But don't worry.
I'll keep a special eye on you two.
Because you both
still have to complete my mission first.
So how do I get back into my body?
All you have to do is just stand still.
Alice.
I'm awake, right?
Yeah, Punn. You did it.
Don't celebrate yet.
Don't forget
you still have a task to complete.
So what do we do now?
What you have to do now is
go home.
Your time is up.
Uh, excuse me, these flowers…
Oh, those are mine.
I dropped them off this morning.
I see
They're beautiful.
I brought these for you.
Do you like them?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Let me carry them for you.
Let's go, Alice.
Yeah.
Where?
- The counter?
- Yeah, go ask.
Uh.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
I'm here to visit a patient named
Punn Suparerk,
the one the rescue team brought earlier.
- Punn Suparerk?
- Yes.
- Okay, let me check for you.
- Sure, thanks.
Punn…
Su, S and U.
- Yes.
- S?
- And P.
- Yes.
Then A…
- A…
- Who are you here to see?
- Hey!
- Hey, Punn!
Hey, Punn!
Excuse me,
loud noises are not allowed here.
Sorry.
- Come here.
- What?
Let's talk.
Weren't you in a coma?
I was. But if I told you,
you'd think I was crazy.
Damn, I'm just glad you're okay.
Yeah, you know what?
Bombay was crying his eyes out
like you were dead or something.
- I was really freaking out.
- Whoa.
It's good you're fine now.
Guess even the Grim Reaper
couldn't take him down.
Come here. Give me a hug.
- My best friend.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Oh?
- Enough teasing.
Alice.
Alice woke up?
Come on, tell us.
She really woke up, didn't she?
Hey.
You actually believed him? He's joking.
How was I supposed to know?
I really thought she woke up for real.
So, who's that bouquet for?
I came to visit Alice this morning,
but the nurse wouldn't let me bring it in,
so I had to carry it back out.
So how's Alice doing?
She's okay.
I mean, she's just lying there.
Looks like she's just sleeping.
But she only drowned,
how did it turn into a coma?
Dude, haven't you ever watched the news?
Sometimes, just a few minutes
without oxygen
and the brain dies.
The blood can't reach it in time.
When the brain dies,
that basically means death, doesn't it?
No, no, no.
Sometimes the spirit
just goes wandering for a while.
It's not back in the body yet, that's all.
Once the spirit comes back,
she'll wake up again.
And if it's done wandering,
can it really come back?
Hey, I was just asking.
Honestly, I believe in science
more than all that.
But still…
I just worry that
if the brain's dead,
and the body's unresponsive like that…
Well…
How long will she have
to be in a vegetative state?
It sucks.
We only just met her.
It's such a shame.
I mean, I really wanted
a female member in the band too.
Hey, it's fine.
Alice will wake up soon.
Trust me, just wait a little.
But still,
right now,
we still need new members.
We've gotta keep auditioning new members.
Honestly,
I don't want to audition anymore.
I'll wait for Alice.
I just want to know
If the way we miss each other
Feels the same
Tell me, has your heart changed?
I'm not imagining it, right?
The longing I sent to you
Never reached you at all
I think that's enough for today.
Look at you.
You don't look good, man.
You shouldn't have come to practice.
Didn't you
just get out of the hospital?
If you're not feeling okay, just say so.
I'm fine, really.
Totally fine.
It's not that.
It's like you've got no soul in you today.
Normally, you're not like this.
I get it, you just got discharged.
I think you should go home and rest.
Let's pack up.
Alright.
Maybe I just have a lot on my mind lately.
I get it.
Alright, I'm heading out first.
- Okay, see you.
- See you.
- Take care of this for me.
- Okay.
Let's go.
But I don't know where to go.
I don't wanna go home and see my mom.
Then just come with me.
Come on.
Who's Punn talking to?
Forget it. He's been talking
to himself forever, hasn't he?
Yeah, but he's never done it
in the studio before.
So how am I supposed to
practice alone like this?
Ugh, whatever.
If you can't see it, it's not there.
Does it get boring being a ghost?
Hey.
Who's a ghost? Stop saying that.
I'm a spirit. But I just realized
I'm really just a wandering spirit.
A lost spirit.
No place to go,
no idea what to do.
Who said that?
We've got a mission to complete.
You're right.
A mission.
- You live alone?
- Yes.
But not really.
My parents work out of town.
Aren't they worried about you?
Worried? Come on.
I'm 17 already. I'm a grown man.
I can take care of myself.
I have self-defense skills and all.
Wanna see?
Left hook! Bam! Bam! Bam!
Anyone messes with me? Bam, bam, bam!
See? You're smiling.
Well,
my parents usually visit every weekend.
Or when they don't,
there are cameras all around the house.
They can check on me anytime.
But lately, I told them
they don't have to come
since I've got band practice with friends.
So what, if you bring a girl home
or throw a party, they'll see everything?
Well…
Not really. If the girl's a ghost,
they can't see her anyway.
You're calling me a ghost again.
Don't you get lonely living by yourself?
Not really.
I guess I'm used to it.
When I'm free,
I play guitar or practice singing.
No time to be lonely.
By the time my head hits the pillow,
I'm out. Day's over.
That's what loneliness is, you know.
Maybe I was lonely before.
But now I'm not
because someone's here with me.
Are you hungry?
No.
But honestly,
it's kind of strange.
This floating feeling.
No hunger, no sleepiness.
Part of me thinks
being a wandering spirit isn't so bad.
I get to do crazy things
I could never do as a human.
And
I feel like
it makes me stronger
and gives me more freedom.
Being a ghost is kinda good.
No need to go home.
Do you miss your mom?
I think about her
but I don't miss her.
Honestly, I'm still mad at her
for ruining my audition.
But I think I'll go check on her tomorrow.
But tonight,
just stay here.
Mm.
Anyway,
what exactly is our mission?
He never told us. And we don't
even know how much time we have.
This is stressful. What do we do?
Punn.
If it's stressing you out that much,
maybe we don't need to
follow what that guy said.
No, Alice.
I won't let you die.
Even though we don't know
what we have to do yet,
I'll use this chance
to bring you back to life.
Thank you, Punn.
I want to live again too.
Being alive
really is precious.
Don't worry, Alice.
I promise I'll never leave you.
I'll do everything, anything,
to bring you back to life again.
Mm.
But we still don't know what to do next.
Next time we see him, we'll have to ask.
If we ever see him again.
Hey, Alice.
Remember that person
we saw get hit by a car?
Of course. There was blood everywhere.
Why did we end up
on that street when we came back?
Could that be…
our mission?
But then what?
We still don't know what to do.
Jinny.
This girl's interesting.
She's got attitude.
Yeah, attitude, sure.
But is she any good?
You brats. Get lost!
I just wanted to ask about you and Wut.
Hey! You don't understand! Just go!
Hey, that's too much.
- Hey.
- Ah.
If I wake up,
I'll do everything you say, Mom.
Jinny.
Subtitle translation by: Panuwat Baikeawon