The hospital has planned to elevate our department to become the premier orthopedic facility.
Both of you have been selected as finalists by the board.
I like you.
You are too vanilla for me.
Are you joking with me, Doc?
Want to watch some series together?
Tell me. Regardless of what gender I am,
why don’t you like me?
You are too vanilla for me.
Am I tasty?
Well, I didn’t expect you to be this tasty either.
I’m indeed tasty, right?
Um.
Right?
How can someone like me be vanilla?
Hey!
Boxer guy.
Yoryak. My name is Yoryak.
Whatever, tell me honestly.
I’m not vanilla, right?
Come on, Doc. What’s wrong with you?
Do you have OCD?
Just answer. I really want to know.
I can’t remember.
Maybe I need another round to jog my memory.
Do you have short-term memory?
How come you already forgot?
Yoryak.
What?
Stop.
Don't you want to know if you really are tasty?
Hey, Yoryak.
Boxer guy.
Yoryak, stop.
Anyway, thanks for taking me home.
My pleasure.
Couldn't bear seeing you alone by trash like a little pup.
You act all high and mighty during the day,
but when you're drunk, all that haughtiness disappears.
It happened only last night, Boxer guy.
If you know you’re a lightweight,
have a friend accompany you when drinking.
Understand?
No fear here.
Last night at the bar, no one wanted to do anything with me.
Are you being dramatic?
No.
Don’t feel bad about it, though.
No need for any awkwardness.
Next time you come for a check-up at the hospital,
feel free to see Dr. Nop, as you did before.
We can just act normal around each other.
You may pretend not to know me. Whatever suits you.
One-night stand?
Um. Once is enough.
No next time.
So the one “night” quota is used up.
But I still have one “day” quota remaining.
If you’re interested, add me to your contact.
No more one day or one night with you.
Over!
Doc.
Doc!
Isn’t it impolite to shut the door in people’s faces?
Yes.
Go, go, go go!
Good.
Please accept my sincere apologies, ma’am.
Yoryak doesn’t have time for personal coaching.
Initially, he did have some availability.
But after winning the recent bout,
he needs to train at the camp for the next bout,
so he's not available now.
Would you like to train with other coaches instead?
I can give you a special discount.
Also, I’ll send Oyei, Yoryak’s brother to take care of you exclusively.
What do you think?
(The former world champion Oyei will take care of me?)
Your inner thoughts are quite loud, ma’am.
That’s settled then.
Thank you for choosing Phadetseuk Boxing Gym.
Goodbye.
You now promote your boyfriend to customers?
Yes.
You’ve trained so hard to get this body.
I shouldn’t be the only one to see it.
Yei.
Don’t you feel possessive over me a bit?
Yei, get off me.
- You’re soaking wet with your sweat. - Why?
Why?
You stink.
My stink repulses you?
Um.
Let’s go.
Go where?
You said I stink.
I’ll let you clean me.
As for the part you want to smell good…
take care of it yourself.
You dirty mind!
Stop.
I have something else to do.
I have to go buy you and our son soy milk.
Cher.
No. Do you want soy milk or not?
Cher, babe. Come on.
You don’t need to buy it now. Do it later.
I must buy it for our son.
You can buy it later.
How could he survive without it?
Yei.
- Come on. - Yei.
- Please. - Yei!
Yei!
This again?
Yes, just gulp it down.
Ouch.
What’s up with you two again?
Hey, your customers are upset that you don’t do personal training.
Sorry, Cher.
Fine. It’s just a shame that we missed out on those course fees.
Our gym had to close down for 2 years during Covid.
Forget about it, Cher.
Don’t force him.
He earns more money as a boxer than as a personal trainer.
The money we could make from those is not small, Yei.
You do know the expenses for running this boxing gym are quite a lot.
You’re like a nagging champion.
Stop it. People don’t nag during breakfast, you know.
You little pup.
I’m really sorry.
The training schedule Oyei made for me is already jam-packed.
Oh, you realize that too.
With such a packed schedule, you can still enjoy a night out every night.
I go out for tutoring too,
not to hit the clubs every night.
Where were you last night? You came home in the morning.
Yeah, I wonder.
Who’s the lucky person who got hold of Yoryak Phadetseuk all night?
Usually, you leave right after you finish.
Nosy.
Were you under my bed when I was doing it?
What’s up?
I’m fine. What about you?
You called to check?
Yes.
If anything bad happened to you,
I could help arrange your funeral.
I’m not dead yet, you moron.
That’s a relief.
So…
which security guard carried you to your room last night?
I didn’t really remember.
What are you going to do now about Dr. Ter?
Ter who? Who is Ter?
I don’t know anyone by that name.
Wow. That’s an attitude.
I wish I could see when you confront him.
It’s gonna happen soon.
Dr. Apichart asked me and…
that man to talk about the scholarship.
Really?
Do your best on that.
I’ll send over my support from here.
Thanks. Go do your stuff.
Put some money toward your father’s merit-making ceremony on my behalf.
Thanks, man. See you.
4 punches.
1 2 hook!
Jab.
Wait. How’s your shoulder?
It got better.
You’re free today, right?
Go have physiotherapy at the hospital.
Okay?
Okay. I have nothing else planned for today.
That’s strange. You didn’t object.
Why would I?
It’s for the benefit of my boxing, right?
- What’s with that soft tone? - Come on.
Alright, keep going.
4 punches.
1 2 hook.
Good.
1 2
Straight.
By the way, Yak.
I already called the hospital and booked your old doctor.
That doctor you told me–
What’s his name? Wandee, right?
Why? What’s up?
Yei, you.
What?
You should have asked me first?
I’m telling you right now.
Why?
Gosh.
Where are you going?
- To the hospital. My shoulder hurts. - Come back.
- I said my shoulder hurts. - Yak!
Yak!
Damn this little.
How’re you doing?
Dee.
After seeing Dr. Apichart, let’s have a coffee together.
Talk to me.
I’m done talking to you.
Have you already made a decision about the scholarship?
Yes, I would like to apply for it.
Good. Well then finish up the application form.
Understood.
What about you, Dee?
I talked to him last night. He’ll…
I’m in too.
Dr. Ter taught me not to waste any opportunities.
Not everyone gets an opportunity to knock on their doors.
I’ll try my best.
If the board considers me for this scholarship,
I’ll give my all to deserve this opportunity.
Good. We’ll find out in the next four months
the first person receiving this scholarship in our department.
Okay, sir.
Good afternoon, Mr. Yoryak.
Today you have a checkup and physiotherapy with Dr. Nop.
What about the doctor who examined me the other day?
What is his name?
Oh, that’s Dr. Wandee.
Why?
Well…
We changed back to Dr. Nop for you.
We apologize that we changed your doctor at the last minute last time.
Uh…
I don’t think you need to change my doctor.
That doctor seems okay.
But Dr. Wandee is not available at the moment. He’s in a meeting.
If you don’t want to wait, Dr. Nop is ready to examine you right now.
But I’m not ready.
I will come back later then.
Come have a word with me.
Let go of me.
Dr. Ter, let go of me.
What else do you want?
I think I have made it clear.
If you’re angry because I rejected you,
I’m sorry.
I know that you are upset.
I’m too upset.
I’m not upset at all. I’m all fine.
Last night, the moment I walked away from you,
I counted 5
Everything was erased.
We’ve known each other for so long.
I know that you are not the person you claim to be now.
You don’t really know me.
Same as I just realized
I don’t know you at all.
We don’t need to have a fight like this.
Dee, my focus right now is on the scholarship.
When I complete the scholarship,
let’s talk about this again.
About what?
About your feelings for me.
If you really have feelings for me,
give up that scholarship and let me have it.
Please do me this favor.
But the feelings I had for you never had any conditions.
I think we should end things between us right here.
It’s too damn tiring.
As for the scholarship,
who will receive it?
Let the board decide.
I’ll be your compatible opponent.
I won’t pull a punch, Senior Ter.
Is this how you want it?
Challenge accepted.
Does it still hurt?
I thought you requested to change doctors.
I don’t want to be too demanding with my sponsor.
I see.
Overall, your condition has greatly improved.
Probably last night…
I found the best cure.
Please don’t speak dirty in this room.
Just kidding.
I want you to relax.
My focus right now is on the scholarship.
When I complete the scholarship,
let’s talk about this again.
But the feelings I had for you never had any conditions.
This pen looks nice.
What’s up with you?
Nothing. I just like this pen.
I’ve got your next appointment booked, sir.
Okay.
Moo~
This is how you exercise with the right methods.
Let’s utilize sports science to make our lives healthier.
Cut.
How was it?
Not bad at all.
You said all the words in the scripts precisely.
It doesn’t look too silly, does it?
Not at all.
With this video together with the paper I finished for you,
this subject is good to go.
Sure?
Sure.
That’s a relief.
I want to graduate already.
I don’t want to be a grandpa senior here.
Come here.
Come with me. I’ll help clean your face.
Is it sticky?
A bit.
Taem.
Hm?
You are a great help to me.
If there’s anything I can do to help you,
let me know.
Free of charge?
Yes.
Great. Be prepared then.
I’m gonna have several favors to ask from you.
This girl.
You don’t hesitate a bit to take this opportunity, huh?
Absolutely not.
You are a strong woman.
I never saw you cry or be dramatic even once.
Why would I cry?
Crying is tiring.
Seriously, I’m just like everyone else.
Nobody can be strong all the time.
Everyone has vulnerabilities that can trigger them.
Fighto!
I like you.
But I like you as a brother.
You are a very nice guy.
But you are too vanilla for me.
I’m not vanilla, darn it!
(Plakao : Don’t be too wild. You have to get up to work tomorrow.)
(I know. Are you my friend or my old man?)
May we cling glasses with you?
Sure.
What’s your name? I’m Mac.
And that’s Aun.
My name is Wandee.
Really? You are cute.
But your name is cuter.
Really?
How about we go bottoms up?
Excuse me. What do you do?
I’m a doctor.
Where do you work?
At a hospital.
Don’t doctors have hospitals as their workplace?
You’re right.
Here you go.
Let’s do bottoms up for this round too.
Get off me.
Come on.
He’s such a lightweight.
Just a few rounds and he’s already out.
Totally.
Have you told the chat group to be ready to watch some good stuff tonight?
All done. Many people have already transferred money to see it.
Let’s go.
I’m not going.
I’m not going!
He said he wasn’t going, didn’t he?
Who the hell are you?
This is none of your business.
Let go of my guy.
Don’t be funny.
He’s here alone.
Let’s get out of here.
Doc.
I’m not going.
Go home.
Doc.
I’m not going.
My goodness.
It’s hot.
Hey, Doc.
Take it easy, Doc.
Hot?
Didn’t you feel hot? Come on.
Alright.
Time to sleep.
Don’t go.
Don’t leave me.
Stay with me, please.
(Nobody can be strong all the time.)
(Everyone has vulnerabilities that can trigger them.)
Alright. I’m here.
Stay with me.
You’re okay now.
(Eat this for a boost of energy.)
You know who prepared this, right?
1 2
Good, 1 2
Straight.
1 2
Yak!
I don’t think this is right.
Sorry.
Let me get changed. I’ll be right with you.
Do you think it’s that easy to attain a world championship title?
I told you to see a doctor, but you went MIA.
You didn’t show up at the evening’s training.
I couldn’t get hold of you.
And you are late for this morning's training.
What is wrong with you?
Calm down, Yei.
I said sorry, didn’t I?
I won’t do it again.
Okay now?
Yak, hurry and get changed.
Relax.
Calm down.
I think Dr. Ter will seal this scholarship.
(In 4 months, you have the power to decide.)
(Who'll be the first orthopedic physician to win a scholarship abroad?)
Do you agree, guys?
Do you agree, Dr. Kwan?
Yes.
Dr. Ter.
The judging panel has come to a decision.
In addition to the writing test scores,
you two will have four months to develop a campaign for our department.
At the end, the employees in this hospital,
as well as the patients, will cast their votes.
This aspect will account for 70% of the total score.
It’s not too late to give up now, Dee.
At this rate, I would be a coward to back down.
Team Dr. Wandee. Yeah!
Here you are.
Yummy cakes for you.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Here.
Look yum, eh?
Yes, but we didn’t order them.
You didn’t need to.
It’s on the house, a special service for our loyal customers.
Congrats on being a candidate to get the scholarship.
What? The news reached here incredibly fast.
I think a reporter might be a more suitable job for you than being a nurse.
I can’t help sharing this news with Golf.
And she told me to bring you to celebrate here right away.
Yes. Please do your best.
- Thanks. - Don’t worry at all.
You have my full support here.
Give your all.
Please enjoy your cakes.
Thank you.
How lovely of her.
Let’s dig in.
Are you going home right away?
No, I have to go meet someone.
Go on.
Let’s celebrate.
Hello, Mrs. Monthakarn.
Hey, Wandee.
What are all those things you're bringing?
I’ve got you a variety of things.
You don’t need to.
When I crave something, I can order it via food apps myself.
What a beautiful way of saying thank you.
It’s my pleasure.
I miss you so much, Grandma.
Give me a hug.
Look, your shirt got dirty from hugging me.
It’s totally okay.
If it’s dirty, may I ask for a three times damage fee?
My little puppy.
How has it been for you lately?
Same old, same old.
Are you sure?
Well, I’m facing some new challenges I’ve never faced before.
That sounds quite challenging.
I’m in love with this smile of yours the most in the world, you know.
I’m also in love with this stubborn nose of yours.
Can I lay on your lap, Grandma?
Why not?
Go ahead.
Mrs. Monthakarn.
Hm?
Do you think Dad and Mom up there will think of us at all?
Of course. I’m sure they do.
Why do you ask?
Do you feel lonely being by yourself?
I’m not lonely. The work at the hospital is so busy.
Tell me honestly. Are you still single?
Come on, Grandma.
I’d like you to learn to live life. Find someone.
I don’t have time for that.
I’ve got my patients
and also I have to be prepared for the scholarship test.
That’s true.
His punch seems really strong.
You watch boxing now?
Sometimes.
I think we need to audit the Student Union
and see if there are any discrepancies in their finances.
This is also our Student Committee’s responsibility.
Let's assign tasks and form teams to conduct this audit.
Taem, can I ask you to closely monitor this?
Sure, Ohm.
Tan, I asked you to get some info. How’s that going?
Any updates?
They’ll provide a summary report later.
(I’ve arrived.)
I leave that to you then.
Please excuse me a sec.
Here.
It’s done.
The Student Committee meeting is not finished?
Um.
But we have a movie plan today.
It’s the movie that you chose.
I don’t think I can go with you now.
Can we watch it later?
I assure you I won’t bail again.
Okay?
Please, please.
You sure?
Sure.
I’m getting back in.
Are you messing with me, Doc?
Are you changing from a boxer to a homeless person?
Boxer guy, where are you headed? I can give you a ride.
Where do you want to go? I can take you there.
I don’t know.
I don’t know where I want to go.
I feel pity for the female lead.
The male lead is such a red flag.
He may have his reasons.
It probably isn’t his intention to hurt her feelings.
You came to drink in my room.
Don’t you want to share with me what upset you?
Hold on, I won’t ask now.
Let’s watch something else.
Doc.
Do you want to do it?
Ah, I forgot.
You don’t have sex with the same guy.
I’m just a one-night stand.
Forget it.
I should leave now.
Wait.
You can’t leave.
Doc.
Are you so busy that you don’t have time to change that light bulb?
Um.
Hey.
How about we become friends with benefits?
You want that?
Um.
Well,
what are the rules between us?
Simple.
We won’t intrude on each other’s private matters.
We meet up and have sex.
We can tell each other what we like and what we don’t like.
If one of us wants to try something new, the other party must give consent.
Okay.
But you don’t allow me to kiss you, right?
Sorry.
It’s a silly romantic idea I built up.
I want to keep my first kiss for the person I truly love.
Are you okay with that?
That…I’m not okay?
Why?
I mean you keep calling me something else instead of my name.
I don’t like it.
What do you want me to call you?
I do have a name.
My name is Yoryak.
Try calling it, Doctor.
Stop playing around, Mr. My Name is Yoryak
aka Giant Fang.
So, what do you say?
Deal or not?
Okay.
Deal.
But…
can I have one more round?
I really loved how you moaned earlier.
Let me have another round.
And please…
moan even louder this time.
Sure.
But this time, Mr. Yak must play with…
a little longer.
Sure.
I’ll do it for you.
Hey, Doc.
Huh?
If I turn up here often, people won’t suspect, right?
Well,
I’m afraid that some reporters may create a scandal about me.
It can ruin my image as a boxer.
How about you do this?
Hey. A security guard must keep his uniform neat.
Every time you come see me,
you just have to…
disguise yourself.
(24/7 AC Service)
I’m here to clean the fridge, sir.
Please give it a thorough clean.
(The Beginning of FWB)
(You don’t allow me to kiss you, right?)
(It’s a silly romantic idea I built up.)
Do you allow this?
How about we pretend to be in a relationship these four months?
I’m a hopeful world championship boxer.
How can I announce to the public that I’m dating with…
It’s been days that you haven’t come to watch a series at my place.
Stop seducing me.
I’ll agree to be your fake boyfriend,
only if within the next five minutes, you can land a punch on me.
Can I ask?
About this fake relationship. Why does it have to be me?