You once told me I can’t do it.
Do you remember?
I’m still thinking like that now.
This time, I’m gonna take your belt away.
You need to find a way to finish the match as quickly as possible.
Is your shoulder hurting badly, Yoryak-san?
I think I should be able to be there before your match starts.
Are you sure?
Dr. Apichart, his blood pressure is dropping.
Can you come here as soon as possible?
Thank you, Doc.
Um…
Are you ready?
I have to be.
I should get going.
Yak.
Something’s wrong?
No.
Yak.
Actually…
Remember what I told you
about the day of my championship fight,
that I could not be with my mother before she was gone.
It became a trauma that re-emerged every time you stepped into the ring?
But Kao helped erase that trauma in you, didn’t he?
Well…
he actually still appears.
Okay.
But can you manage to control it for now?
Manage?
I used to think I could manage.
Let’s go.
Go get the world champion title.
Okay. Let’s do it!
Stick to our game plan.
Watch for signs when his energy starts to drop
and knock him out.
Alright, go!
Go get’em.
Hey, Taem.
Thank you very much for the ride.
You’re welcome.
Yak is doing okay, right?
Okay.
I hope he stays okay throughout the fight.
Yak!
Woo!
Is this seat taken?
Dr. Ter.
No, go ahead.
I was trying to find a parking lot.
So many people today.
Yes, it’s packed here.
Here. I bought a drink for you.
Dee.
Go, go, Yak!
You’ve got this, Yak!
Taem.
Thank you.
What the?
He’s only aiming at Yak’s shoulder.
Look.
Mason Jordan isn’t holding back at all.
Oh well.
Woah, look at that.
Yak…
Hold on.
It looks like Yoryak Phadetseuk isn't doing too well right now.
Could it be that Mason Jordan is able to defend his title from just the first round?
Yoryak-san.
Yak!
- Yak!
- We can’t blink for this match.
Yoryak Phadetseuk!
Yak!
Go!
Come on.
Good.
Yak,
you sure you can handle this.
Oyei, let me.
Hang in there, Yak.
Doc,
I saw him again.
Yak.
It’s time for you to let him go.
It’s so damn hard, Doc.
Yak.
I talked to Dr. Aphichart today.
He told me he took care of your mother before she passed.
She talked about you all the time, you know.
She said she loved her sons very much.
The old Yak might feel guilty for missing his last chance to be with his mother.
But it’s time
that you let him go.
You can do this. Come on.
For some traumas, we cannot turn back time to fix them,
nor can we erase them from our memories.
However, you can at least free yourself from their hold.
Your life right now is yours.
Here we go.
He’s got this.
Nice.
Yoryak is stepping up his game now.
- That’s my boy.
- He’s back in form.
Our world champion is losing his balance.
Jab!
Good.
This round is neck and neck,
but Yoryak-san must stay in top form.
Let’s see who can last longer.
Good. That’s more like it.
Oh.
Yak!
- He’s down, Yoryak Phadetseuk.
- Get up, Yak.
Yak, get up.
(I love you, son.)
I’m getting closer to being a champion.
Am I great?
You are, dear.
My son is the best.
(She talked about you all the time, you know.)
(She said she loved her sons very much.)
Get up!
Hang in there, son!
Yak.
Yak!
There you go!
You can do this.
Hang in there. You can do it, Yak.
Yak!
(Watch for signs when his energy starts to drop and knock him out.)
Attack!
Yeah!
Does it hurt, honey?
A bit.
He’s indeed the dashing boxer.
Lift him!
One, two, three.
And here is the latest GBF Middleweight World Champion,
Yoryak Phadetseuk!!!
Alright.
It’s worth all the tiredness, right, Yei?
When it comes to Yak, I’ve never felt tired.
Alright, as the newest world champion,
do you have anything to say to your fans watching from all around the world?
Go ahead.
I might not be very good at speaking formally...
but right now, what I want to say the most is...
Mom,
I did it!!!
Thank you, my brother Oyei.
Thank you, Cher.
Thank you, my dad Yingyot,
Aunt Nipa,
and every single folk at the Phadetseuk Boxing Club.
Thank you, Taem,
my college friend for helping me with my studies.
And more importantly,
I would like to thank this one person
who has been a key driving force
in making this big dog, Yoryak,
believe in and love himself once again.
Honestly,
this man believes in me
more than I believe in myself.
Dr. Wandee,
could you do me the honor of being in this ring with me?
Thank you
for not letting go of my hand.
I was able to seize this belt
mostly because of you.
This belt
is yours.
Don’t be cheesy.
Yak.
Stop it.
Yoryak Phadetseuk!
Wow, Dee and Yak are amazing.
This video clip is going viral right now.
Love between a world champion boxer
and a hot doctor.
So romantic.
Before they reached this beautiful and romantic moment,
it wasn’t easy for them at all. You know?
Really.
Blue.
Yes?
I truly appreciate that you understand me.
You even took your day off to run my errand with me in Chonburi.
No need to thank me.
I’m really fortunate to have met you.
You get where I’m coming from on this kind of thing.
I always believed there’s someone out there
who’s ready to understand the way you are.
You just have to find them.
Have you found them, though?
I’m not gonna tell you.
You’re not gonna tell me?
Really?
Are you asking for a pinch?
What should I say?
Blue, how about we go out together?
Like… go as far as we can go.
When it doesn’t work for us anymore,
we’ll stop.
Um…
Okay.
Seriously?
You’re serious, right?
Don’t kid me.
It’s not easy to find someone I can match with.
This is not something to kid about.
For someone like you,
if I miss out on the chance to be with you,
I would regret it.
You have such a sweet mouth.
Do you want me to fall head over heels for you?
Thank you.
Woah.
You look quite cool too.
I do, right?
Yak, can you grab my phone from the bedroom for me?
Let’s take some selfies.
In the bedroom?
Okay.
Where did you put it?
I couldn’t find it.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, happy birthday
You were at the training camp on your birthday,
so I couldn’t give you a real cake,
only a sticker on chat.
Take this as a happy belated birthday.
Thank you, Doc,
for not forgetting my birthday.
I told you, right?
I never forget.
Those who are important in my life,
I remember all their birthdays.
Make a wish.
I hope the wish comes true.
Yeah.
Yak, what did you wish for?
You seem so serious about it.
Well, it’s quite important.
Surely, I need to be serious about it.
What else would you want?
You’re already a world champion
and you’re almost graduating.
It’s a wish that
I can’t do it alone.
What is it?
You’re not gonna tell me?
Fine.
Then, get this.
Doc.
You asked for it.
Doc, don’t play with this.
Come on, it’s messy.
I told you, don’t play.
Who said I was playing?
What?
Why do you look like that was our first time having sex.
No.
I just felt like…
this time made me feel better than any other time.
After you let me kiss you on the lips,
your lips seem even sweeter than before.
Don’t you like it?
I do.
I’m just not used to it.
Usually, we both have it rough.
Doc,
honestly,
It feels like paradise
to make love to the person I love.
Really?
Was it more thrilling than winning the world championship title?
That’s a hard question.
I’m not sure.
Perhaps another round can help me decide.
Enough.
Yak,
stop it. Stop.
Where do you get all that energy?
You high-energy boxer.
Yei.
Here.
Let’s celebrate.
Cheers.
Feeling proud, huh?
Yes.
Finally, we could own Phadetseuk Boxing Club again.
Yak is really amazing, right?
Um.
But you’re amazing too.
I know you’ve been through a lot as well.
Thank you, Cher.
You have always believed in me.
Without your support,
I don't know if I could have pulled through.
You flatter me too much.
I’m so proud that I get to take care of you.
I love you.
I love you too.
Yei, smile like this more often.
I love it the most when you smile.
Doc.
Yak!
Looking for this?
You’re about to take an important scholarship test.
How could you forget this sacred charm by Master Yoryak,
Dr. Wandee?
I was too rushed.
Anyway, thanks a lot.
I’ve got to run now.
Wait, Doc.
Let this Master blow a lucky spell on you too.
Done.
Yak, what did you do?
People might see.
I guarantee you'll ace this test, no doubt!
For this testing round, you’ve got three hours to complete it.
Got it, sir.
The room is ready.
Regardless of the outcomes,
I want you to know that
neither of you has ever disappointed me.
Well,
after I told my exes I wasn’t into sex,
they all ditched me.
But Blue is cool with it.
So I think we should give this a shot.
Yeah, I’m also questioning myself
if I’m asexual like Dr. Plakao.
I’m not really into sex either.
That’s cool.
Most people think
asexuality means being celibate
and free from desires
like aiming for the afterlife or something.
Just because we don't want sex
doesn't mean we don't want love.
We still want someone nice to be with.
Awesome.
Let me jot those phrases down.
So sharp.
I’m going to get more sweets.
Do you want anything else?
No, thanks.
I know as soon as I leave the table,
you all will talk about me.
So,
go ahead.
There’s a menu over there at the counter.
Knock yourself out. It’s on the house.
Kao, I like your new guy.
Congrats, man.
Thanks, man.
I’m not sure how far this relationship can go,
but I’m giving it a try.
Just go for it, Doc.
You never know unless you try.
I get it now.
I haven’t had anyone yet.
Maybe I’m asexual too.
But from my medical experience,
I don't think…it's related.
What?
Why?
Not having anyone pursue you
and being asexual…
are unrelated.
Kao!
Really?
Well then, allow me to ban you from my cafe for one week.
Golf, that’s mean.
For being too honest with me.
Hey. You’re so mean.
I’m not.
Let’s clink.
No.
There’s no such thing as a perfect day, Gooddy.
But that doesn't mean we can’t have good days.
Do you agree?
Have a good day, Gooddy.
Our good days might be those mornings when we wake up
and share a warm, aromatic cup of coffee…
Morning kiss.
…with someone.
Coffee?
Or those days when we do something for others
with all our might.
Namphu is really strong, ma’am.
He’s completed the chemotherapy cycle,
and it seems there's been a very good response to it.
How do you feel, Namphu?
Can you eat well now?
I'm eating much better now.
Sometimes,
our good days come from knowing that
- even though the road ahead may not be easy...
- Let me help.
…we are never alone on that path.
Move to this side a little.
Is it good now?
Or those days when we dare to refuse to spoil those we love,
all for their own good.
What?
It’s pretty salty and oily.
This doctor recommends you skip it.
Yoryak, help me.
Sure. Uh…
You wuss!
Or for some people,
- their good days are when they try something new…
- Wait. Wait.
Is this your type?
I’m not into the muscle type.
What do I do if I find someone I like?
If you like someone you see, swipe right.
…or start a new relationship.
I noticed you like gardening.
Can you help take care of this plant for me?
Sure.
But if it dies, don’t blame me.
For some,
good days can happen quickly.
For others,
it takes a lot of patience and determination
for those good days to come.
So good days are different for each person.
It all depends on our choices, Gooddy.
My Good Day, My Choice.
I hope you’re happy, Wandee, Yoryak.
Be happy to your heart's content, okay?
Got it, my idol.
I love Mrs. Monthakarn the most in the world.
I know that. No need to say it often.
You say it again and again.
Thank you, Yak, for coming.
Mrs. Monthakarn is really happy.
I had to come.
Mrs. Monthakarn is my idol.
I was invited, so I had to be here.
Isn’t it strange?
Last year, we were like strangers to each other,
but now you’re an important person in my family.
Thank you, Doc,
for…
letting me be an important person in your family.
You’re important in mine too.
You sure?
Certainly.
New Year’s Eve, right?
The party at your hospital.
And the scholarship winner announcement.
Um.
It’s kinda exciting, right?
But I don’t think I’ll get it.
Dr. Ter is really talented.
How about this?
The night before the party, I’ll smack Dr. Ter in the head.
Hey, Yak.
I thought being a world champion
would stop you from talking nonsense.
What?
That’s out of my good intentions.
Want to sit by the pool?
Why not?
Whoa.
It’s cool.
Doc.
Hm?
When we grow old,
do you think we’ll be together as long as those grandpas?
Probably.
Imagine this.
If you were bedridden,
I’d be the one to flip you over.
What? Why does it have to be you?
I’m a boxer. I’m stronger, no doubt.
But I'm an orthopedic doctor.
I’d be the one to flip you over.
Whatever.
We’ll see when the time comes.
Doc, when we’re really old,
can we still have sex?
Yoryak!
Sex has nothing to do with age.
If you don’t want to, you can abstain alone.
Hey, Doc.
What does that mean?
There are still boxers available in your boxing gym, right?
Seriously, Doc!
You cheeky thing.
Woohoo!
Oh baby, L
I can’t find it anywhere
O, still can’t find it here
V, tell me where to see
E
Where can I find what they call LOVE
I really want to experience one
I’ll be back soon.
Ouch.
Sorry, Dr. Ter.
No worries.
Are you alright, Dr. Dee?
I’m fine.
Are you here with Yak?
Well, Taem is my plus-one tonight.
Though I’m here with Dr. Ter.
I made it clear to him that I’m rooting for you.
Ahem.
I heard that.
See you around.
See you.
Later, Dr. Dee.
I thought you were the one who could move on fast.
Dr. Ter and Taem outdid you on that.
I know, right?
I’ll go get this refilled now.
I’ll wait right here.
Alright, we've reached the most important moment of the evening.
It's time to find out who will be the first doctor
from the orthopedics department to study abroad.
Are you ready?
Without further ado,
please welcome Dr. Apichart to announce the result.
Dr. Apichart, the stage is yours.
Thank you.
May I correct something?
Actually, we have several doctors in our department who studied from abroad.
However, this person will be the first to receive a scholarship to study abroad.
But first, let's give a round of applause to our two scholarship contenders,
Dr. Ter and Dr. Wandee.
I've personally mentored them,
and I am confident that
both of them will definitely become highly skilled medical professionals.
And now, the moment we've all been waiting for.
The first doctor from our department
to receive the scholarship to study abroad is...
Dr. Ter.
Dr. Dee.
Dr. Wandee!
- Dr. Dee.
- Dr. Dee!
Dr. Wandee!
Dr. Wandee.
Dr. Wandee, please come to the stage.
And to add some extra sparkle to our event tonight,
we have a crown and a sash for our winner,
the first scholarship recipient from the orthopedics department.
Thank you, Dr. Apichart, once again.
Dr. Ter may actually feel relieved to not be crowned.
Probably.
And now Dr. Wandee, could you please say a few words?
I’m actually quite excited right now.
Uh…
Thank you to the committee of Tanwarin Hospital
and everyone who voted for me.
I'm grateful for your votes, giving me the opportunity to study abroad
so that I can come back and help develop
our premier Orthopedic Center.
I know that effective treatment means racing against time.
So, I’ll do my very best with this opportunity.
Thank you to my professor, Dr. Apichart,
for always guiding and teaching me.
Thank you to my seniors, juniors,
colleagues, staff,
patients, and their families.
Also I would like to thank my idol
who inspired me to become an orthopedic doctor--
Dr. Ter.
Dr. Ter, to me, you are the best.
My best friend, Dr. Plakao,
who has never disagreed with me
but always finds a way to handle my stubbornness,
Thank you, Vivi,
for being my number one supporter.
And I want to thank this person
who is very important in my life.
I don’t think I need to say who that is.
Yak, he definitely means you.
What should I do when all eyes are on me?
Just keep cool.
Trust me.
I would like to thank…
My grandmother, Mrs. Monthakarn.
Last but not least,
there's another person who has been very important in my life,
especially during the past four months.
The thing is…
this person likes to go big
and never does anything ordinary.
So, I’ve prepared something extraordinary for him.
I used to believe that love wasn’t meant for me
Those who came by just didn’t feel right
I don’t know why
Then I met you
You made me realize
What true love is actually like
The one I’ve been looking for who feels right
It’s you
Just having a good day with you
It’s good to have you
Just us having each other, that’s all I could ask for
It’s good that I have you, it's good when I'm with you
All I need is you, that’s already too good to be true
Just having a good day with you
It’s good to have you
Just us having each other, that’s all I could ask for
It’s good that I have you, it's good when I'm with you
All I need is you, that’s already too good to be true
You went quite big too.
Mr. Yoryak Phadetseuk,
would you be my ‘real’ boyfriend?
You went big earlier.
You went even bigger now.
I’ll give you only five seconds.
Five,
Four,
Three,
Two,
One...
A big yes.
I've long wanted to have you as my boyfriend.
How could I ever change my feelings for you?
And now,
Mr. Yoryak and Dr. Wandee
have brought the wedding rings for our wedding couple today.
Mr. Oyei, Mr. Cher,
please exchange your rings.
Thank you so much, my dear brother.
Yeah, yeah.
Congrats, bro.
My face isn't too messy, right, Dr. Dee?
It's still good.
A little smudge makes you look kinda sexy.
Thank you so much, Cher,
for choosing me.
It's not a one-sided choice.
You chose me too.
Thank you.
I love you, my dear.
I love you too.
Alright, everyone.
Thank you so much for coming to our wedding
as our honored guests today.
Finally,
we have the opportunity to be legally married with marriage equality.
Cheers!
Well I also want to thank you
for giving me the chance to be part of your family
and also for treating me with respect.
In fact, we've been living together for a long time,
but getting married is a different kind of excitement.
It feels like the transition from the end of being boyfriends
to the beginning of a new journey as life partners.
It hasn’t been easy for us at all.
It has required a lot of mutual understanding
to be in each other’s lives.
Whether it was coincidence or destiny,
I’m grateful for the chances that brought us together.
We might have started off with just sex,
a no-strings-attached relationship.
But before we knew it,
love had filled every part of our relationship.
I don't know what the future holds,
but I’m confident that as long as we remain committed
and believe in each other,
love will guide us through everything.
Cheers!
Now kiss!
Kiss!
Yak, stop it!
Here's what we'll do.
Whatever you want us to do,
show us how it's done first,
and then we'll follow.
A challenge, huh?
Doc!
Huh?
Guess we need to lead the way and set the standard.
Your turn.
How’s the studying abroad thing going, Doc?
My enrollment has been accepted.
They’re working on the transfer process.
I should be able to travel in two months.
Study hard, alright?
I’ll come visit you.
Thank you.
In America?
Yeah, of course.
America isn’t far when my heart is there.
You haven’t even left yet,
and I think I’m already starting to miss you.
Yak,
maybe we should…
put our relationship on hold for now.
What do you mean?
No way.
You can’t make me love you and then break up with me.
No, I wasn’t going to break up with you.
I just don’t want to be selfish.
I have to be there for several years.
While I’m away,
you may find someone better than me.
I don’t want you to feel guilty
from closing the doors to opportunities.
Up until now,
whenever you asked me if I love you,
I never gave you a straight answer
as I didn’t want my ‘love’
to block any good opportunity that might come to you.
I think
I’ve kept myself open to those opportunities long enough.
Now I’m certain
who is the one for me.
And that’s you.
But I will be away for years.
Can you really wait for me?
Sure, I can.
Finding someone as cute, handsome, and with fine skin like you
is really hard, you know.
I love you, Doc.
I love you too, Yak.
I love you more every day.
Do you remember the first time we met,
when you asked if I thought you were tasty?
Of course, I remember.
I lied.
Why?
Honestly,
I think you're a bit vanilla.
Yak.
Me? Vanilla?
No way.
Then prove me wrong.
Are you challenging me, young man?
An ordinary day
Becomes special when I’m with you
With days and seasons passing through
I want you to know how much you mean to me
Then I met you
You made me realize
What true love is actually like
The one I’ve been looking for who feels right
It’s you
Just having a good day with you
It’s good to have you
Just us having each other, that’s all I could ask for
It’s good that I have you, it's good when I'm with you
All I need is you, that’s already too good to be true