This is coming around again? The hospital’s anniversary.
I would like to ask you to go with me.
For this ball, I must bring my special someone.
So, are you going to that hospital’s anniversary ball?
I have something to talk to you about in private.
Can you go to the ball by yourself first?
I have to take care of something.
I don’t think your fake boyfriend can make it here tonight.
Be my dance partner tonight.
Would you do me the honor of dancing with me, my prince?
With pleasure.
Our dance practice paid off.
Did I do alright?
You did okay.
I give it a 9.
Doc!
Where did the missing point go?
I need to deduct it
for making me anxiously wait for you.
Ah,
Taem got into a little incident.
Not really a little, actually.
It was quite serious.
Thank you so much, Dean.
Take him and follow me.
(Yak, how’s it going? Is everything OK?)
We’ve arrived.
You can send me off here.
Are you sure you’re okay now?
I can stay and keep you company.
You have to attend the ball with Dr. Dee, don’t you?
Well…
yes.
As we walked back here,
do you know how many times you looked at your phone?
If it shows read receipts and you don’t reply,
Dr. Dee could get really worried.
Yak,
you like Dr. Dee, right?
Is it…
Is it that obvious?
It couldn't be more obvious than this.
Come on, Yak.
Don’t be the person who realizes their feelings when it’s too late.
Even the leads in series these days are smart
and accept their own feelings, you know.
Just go.
Taem.
Follow what your heart wants.
Don’t worry about me.
Thanks, Taem.
Hurry and go already.
Make sure you get there in time, Yak!
Grandma said dancing is all about rhythm and trust,
taking turns in leading and following,
and harmonious coordination between two people
to make it perfect and beautiful.
If only I could freeze time for a good moment like this one,
it would be wonderful.
And the voting results for the hottest dancing pair tonight
are…
Dr. Wandee and Mr. Yoryak.
Congratulations!
May I invite Dr. Apichart to present the award?
Please give them a round of applause.
They really deserve it.
Another round of applause, please.
And then,
here I am with you.
Thank you
for finally making it here.
I’ve done a good thing.
Give me a reward tonight.
Always a reward!
Excuse me.
The board would like to have a photo with you, Mr. .
Do you mind?
Uhh…
Okay.
Are you coming too?
No, you go ahead.
The board probably wants the photos of you for the hospital’s fan page
as your main sponsor.
I’ll wait here.
Fine.
Alright then.
This way, please.
The air out here is much better than the air inside, don’t you think?
Please look at the camera when you’re ready.
One, two, three.
One more photo, please.
One more.
One, two, three.
Okay, thank you very much.
I’m rooting for you. Do your best.
Thank you.
Mrs. Vivi.
I’m done here, right?
Just a moment, please.
Please, sir.
Let’s do a boxer pose.
I like you, Dee.
Can we start over, Dee?
I think there’s nothing left between us.
Please stop.
Dr. Ter!
No.
Stop!
I’m sorry.
I just wanted you to see
how I truly feel about you.
Dr. Ter, no.
- Dr. Ter!
- 	Hey!
Yak.
Get the hell off my boyfriend!
Are you sure you are his boyfriend?
Dr. Dee
is
my boyfriend!
Loud and clear?
Both of you quit putting up an act already.
I gave in to you, didn’t I?
Just admit that, over the past eight years,
how happy we were together.
Doc, let’s go home.
Let’s start anew together, Dee.
Doc.
Yak and I are fake boyfriends.
Yes,
we started like that.
But you know something?
Yak is a huge green flag for me.
When I’m with Yak,
I never question myself if I’m good enough.
It’s Yak who makes me realize how worthy I am.
Right now Yak is my peace of mind.
I still don’t understand
why I wasted those eight years with you.
Because right now,
I really love myself when I’m with Yak.
Thank you, Yak,
for coming into my life.
It’s all my pleasure.
Alright then. Let’s go home.
Just having a good day with you
It’s good to have you
Just us having each other, that’s all I could ask for
It’s good that I have you, it's good when I'm with you
All I need is you, that’s already too good to be true
Cheers.
Yeah.
What a day, huh?
I know.
A lot of things happened today.
Well...
you aren’t mad that I hit that Dr. Jackass Ter again, right?
I’m not. Why would I be?
Did you hurt your hand, though, punching him?
Let me see.
How could that little punch hurt my hand?
I’m a boxer, come on.
But wait,
did you get kissed by Dr. Ter?
No.
It’s a shame, though.
Doc!
I was just joking.
I don’t believe you.
Let me check.
Yak.
Yak!
I said I didn’t get kissed.
I didn’t.
Let me prove it.
Don’t be so smooth. Go away.
Come on. It’s a reward.
I rushed to the ball to be with you.
Let me kiss you for 10 seconds.
Please. Please. Please.
Fine.
But only for two seconds.
No.
I need 10 seconds.
I went to great lengths for you, Doc.
I also saved you from that prick.
Please. Please. Please.
Happy now, Big Bunny?
No.
What is in this package?
This is probably from Kao.
(I heard about your win. This is a gift from me.)
(It’s my new collection designed with a theme of fairy tale characters.
Just like your prince outfits.
Have fun.
Don’t forget to take a picture
and leave your review on my Sleepless Sleepwear fan page too.)
Shall we open it now?
Okay.
Dr. Kao’s new design?
Holy shit.
Doc,
let's release the mermaids back to the sea tonight.
Bye-bye, mermaids.
I can't believe Kao.
His designs get weirder every day.
Doc.
Hm?
I really meant what I said.
About what?
About what I told you
that I love you.
Do you want us to become real boyfriends?
Come on, Yak. Don't skip steps.
All this time we've been together,
you've never really flirted with me.
Right after we met,
we ended up in bed together.
You dirty mind.
I know.
We might've started with sex,
but I think we are more than that now.
I'm serious about us, Doc.
Here's the deal.
From now on, I'm going all out to win you over.
I'm fine with not having sex with you
until we're officially a couple.
Are you really that serious?
Can you be that patient, boxer guy?
To prove myself to you,
I can definitely do it.
Then, brace yourself for it.
At the end of the year, when our 4-month deal is up,
I'll ask you for your answer again.
Okay?
Yak, what are you making? It smells so good.
It’ll be ready in three minutes.
How about you go wash your face and brush your teeth now?
Um.
(Don’t brush your teeth too hard or you’ll get bleeding again.)
Woah.
Hold on, Doc.
Hmm?
Why?
Here you go, sir.
Please sit down, Doctor.
Are you being too polite?
Let me be a bit.
Alright, let’s eat.
Um. I’m digging in.
Doc.
Hmm?
What do I have to do to be your boyfriend?
Any to-do list?
Are you serious about it?
Yes.
Actually, it’s not hard at all.
Just that…
you must give me a flower every day.
Doc!
You must make time for us to go on a fun trip together.
Let’s go on a trip.
I’ve booked everything.
Doc, it’s burning.
It’s burning!
Are there any fish here?
I can't seem to catch one.
Just be a bit more patient.
And…
you must go to see Kao…
Kao.
Never miss an appointment.
Your patient is here.
Hello.
This room, sir.
What do you think?
Looks good, right?
This place has a good star rating, you know?
How is it?
Is it good?
Yes, it's quite good.
That's a relief.
Yak.
I think...
Well…
Doc.
For you.
Yak.
Enough!
Listen to me, Yak.
Can you stop trying to be like someone else?
I know what you're doing here.
You want to be like Dr. Ter was before, right?
This is totally unnecessary.
If I love you,
I'll love you for who you are—
the man who can make me happy every day.
That's all it takes
to make you the sweetest man in the world, you know?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Can we have the bill, please?
Are you mad at me for being so direct?
No.
I just want to go do things that are me now.
Gosh.
Smells nice.
It looks really good, Doc.
Good source of protein.
Look, Doc.
You need to remove their legs first
otherwise they might poke your throat.
Tada.
Wanna try?
No, thanks.
Holy moly, it tastes heavenly.
This is the Yoryak that I like...
What did you say?
Huh?
"Yoryak that...
I like?"
Say that again.
No,
I wasn’t going to say I like you.
What I wanted to say was...
Yoryak that...
I…
like to help him study.
You sure?
Are you sure sure sure?
Stop talking and just eat.
Ooh. Tom Saeb.
Water. Drink water.
(Why does a bright and lively man like Yak
have nightmares and see hallucinations?)
Kao, so what’s exactly wrong with Yak?
Come on, Dee. You know I can’t say.
We’re doctors.
We must not disclose patient’s information to anyone.
But I’m not just anyone.
I’m your friend.
Even friends are not allowed.
Hey.
(Confidential)
Hi, Kwan.
Dr. Ter.
On the ball night, where were you?
I was looking for you but couldn’t find you.
I just felt
what I was doing was a waste of time,
so I left.
Kwan.
I’m sorry.
No need to be sorry.
What you did was actually good.
It helped me decide more easily.
Kwan, have I kept you waiting too long?
Not at all.
Please excuse me.
Let’s go.
What the hell was this?
Are you calling this ‘training?’
Why are you all not taking this seriously?
You came late for training.
What are you guys up to, Phadetseuk folks?
You just arrived?
Konnichiwa,
Yoryak-san.
I’m glad to meet you again.
This place has a nice atmosphere.
This is Mai,
my girlfriend.
Nice to meet you all.
What brings you here, Zazaki?
In the recent match between you and me,
I defeated you.
I remember that.
No need to remind me,
or you might just set off my temper.
Yoryak-san,
Let’s have a rematch.
I want another fight with you.
Because I know the man who fought me in the last match
is not the Yoryak-san I know.
What?
He has the audacity to challenge you on your turf?
I know, right?
If you were me, you'd be mad too, right?
Absolutely.
We're both quick-tempered too.
Because we're boyfriends.
We share the same mind.
Not yet!
We're not boyfriends yet.
Seriously, Doc?
I'm not winning you over yet?
Come on, Doc.
I've been flirting with you non-stop.
Still no luck?
No wonder
people these days just go for FWB and one-night stands.
What?
Don't tell me you want to give up already?
Who gives up?
Not me.
But if you don't want to see me give up,
let me into your heart already.
Please, my dear doc.
Let's not waste time for our happiness.
Are you not happy now?
I am,
but...
would you let me be your lover?
Please, Doc.
Please. Please. Please.
Please. Please.
Just say yes already.
This can tire me out too, Doc.
No.
Say yes, please.
Stop talking.
No means no.
Do you think your former world champion title
gives you the privilege to avoid paying your debt to my boss?
No, bro.
Please take it easy.
I'm short on cash right now.
Please give me more time.
I don't think you have much time left.
You clumsy old man.
How could you walk into a brawl between young gangsters?
Come here.
I'll clean your wounds.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I just think
our gym is starting to wear out.
It is.
It was built when your father became world champion.
Back when your mother was still alive.
Yeah.
I should find some money for renovation.
Go for it.
Alright, it’s done.
Do you think…
If my mother were still alive,
she…
she would be proud of me?
Of course she would.
I'm also proud of you.
You little one,
you know how to sweet talk.
I’m not little.
Does it hurt badly?
Not anymore.
Keep going.
His training is quite intense, Cher.
The match is near.
You know what?
Even though this is a small match,
many people have sent inquiries to our fan page
asking to be in the audience.
That’s great.
Can we sell tickets then?
It's a way to earn money for the club.
I wish I could do that,
but Yei won’t let me.
He said it wasn’t in the agreement with Zazaki.
I even told him I would talk to Zazaki myself,
but Yei strongly refused and gave all sorts of reasons.
I just don’t get him.
That’s a pity.
You could make a lot of money from it.
I think you could even do a livestream.
I’m sure many people want to watch this rematch.
That’s true.
I need to stand my ground and bring him around.
I’ll talk to Yei again.
Way to go, Manager Cher.
Jab.
One, two
One, two, hook.
Good.
Jab.
Four punches.
One, two, hook.
Oyei.
Yoryak.
Dad.
I haven’t been here for quite a while.
I just noticed you painted the place yellow.
We made it look younger.
It looks strangely good in a way.
Yes, honey.
It looks bright with yellow.
It’s Mom’s birthday color.
Cool drinks for you…
sir.
Here, Aunt Nipa.
Thank you.
Thanks.
When did you two come to Bangkok?
We came straight here for you.
I heard about the rematch,
so I wanted to come to give you support.
Thanks, Dad.
You also had to gain weight to go up a weight class, right?
Just a bit.
I watched the recording of your last match.
Why did you just stand there and let him beat you like that, son?
He was sick.
That’s all you're here for, right?
We can go back to training.
Yei.
Come on, Yak.
Let’s continue your training.
I’ll see you off here then.
Goodbye.
Hey, Yei.
Yak, move it.
I have to go back to training now, Dad.
Honey,
let’s get back.
We shouldn’t reach Kanchanaburi after dark.
Alright. Let’s go.
Why didn't you wait for me, Mom?
I was wrong.
I was too late.
I’m sorry, Mom.
Can you stay with me?
My son is very talented.
You flatter me too much.
My back is itchy. Can you scratch it?
Okay. Here?
No, a bit to the left.
One, two, three!
Kao,
there's nothing to worry about with Yak's condition, right?
Not yet at the moment.
It actually tends to be improving.
If there’s no harsh trigger, there should be no need to worry.
Anyway, please help observe him for me too.
Okay?
Doc.
Do you know where my elephant pants are?
No, I don’t.
Hey, Doc!
Give them back.
No.
Come on.
Give them to me.
No.
If you want them back, you must ask nicely.
Seriously, Doc.
Say “Can you please return the boxing elephant pants to Little Bro Yoryak?”
Come on, Doc.
Say it. Come on.
Come on.
My dear Dr. Wandee,
can you please return the boxing elephant pants to Little Bro Yoryak?
What a lovely boy you are.
Here.
You're really fond of those elephant pants.
You wear them all the time.
Can I buy you a new pair?
Nah.
These pants are not like other pants.
Look.
Tada.
Look. Do I look like the elephants?
Well…
When I've found what I like,
why bother looking for something else?
Yak.
Can I break the rules?
No begging, you big dog.
Doc, you know something?
Some world-class athletes should have sex before competition,
so their bodies would be less tense
and their minds would be clearer.
And you know what?
Some of them lose
because they're not in top physical form.
You're too uptight.
I just want some support.
Please. Please. Please.
Please. Please. Please. Please.
Okay.
Yoryak.
This doctor only allows you just this.
Fine.
I’m actually excited.
Tomorrow I have to fight Zazaki.
You can do it.
Of course I can
if you're there cheering for me.
Should I go or not?
Please go.
I’ll fight for you tomorrow.
Since when did you become such a sweet talker?
I really meant it.
You're my peace of mind.
With you around,
there’s nothing I fear.
But...
about the world-class athletes...
Yoryak, how about you sleeping on the floor tonight instead?
O…kay.
Just this is good enough.
In just a moment, a rematch between Yoryak and Zazaki,
a fighter from Japan is about to begin.
How does everyone feel? Are you excited?
Hi.
This match is sure to be intense.
Can you type in the comment box who you’re cheering for.
Type ‘99’ for Yoryak.
And type ‘567824’ for Zazaki.
Dr. Wandee.
You’re just in time.
Yoryak asked me to reserve a seat for you.
Cher might be too busy.
Ah.
Thank you, Taem.
You’re welcome.
Have a seat.
Alright.
And the rematch is about to begin
between Yoryak Phadetseuk
and Zazaki, aka King Jr.
Go. Go!
Yoryak!
Yak, stay focused.
You’ve got this.
Okay, bro.
Go.
Show him what you’ve got.
It’s still vivid in my memory.
Yoryak got knocked out in the first round last time.
I’m curious to see how he’ll perform today.
Yoryak Phadetseuk.
Taem,
how much longer until the match begins?
A while.
Oh.
Don’t disappoint me.
We’ll see.
Alright. Here we go.
Oh, gosh.
From the way I see, Zazaki is looking great here.
Yak, Go Go!
I hope history doesn’t repeat.
How is it going to be?
Yak, come on. Get him.
Yoryak. Yoryak. Woah.
There he goes.
Yoryak is taking down his opponent, just like his last name's meaning.
Yeah!
What’s wrong with Yak, Dr. Dee?
Hey, Yak!
Yak!
This way.
Hey, Yak!
Yak.
Move.
Yak. Come back!
Yak!
Woah, he’s down again.
Will history repeat itself? I hope not.
I really hope not.
Yak.
Yak, I’m right here.
Yak!
Don’t let him beat you!
Yak, hang in there!
You’ve got this, Yak.
Oh wow,
he's able to stand on his feet this time around.
Probably because of great support.
He’s back.
Yak, Go Go!
Zazaki also got hit.
Come together.
Box!
Oh wow.
He's hitting with all his force.
Zazaki is down and out.
The referee is counting.
Don’t tell me that…
And the winner is Yoryak Phadetseuk by TKO.
Amazing, Yak!
Woah. His performance today is totally different!
Yoryak Phadetseuk!
Yeah!
Hey, Zazaki!
I invited Mai and Zazaki to join us.
Can we join you?
Yoryak-san.
Today,
you were amazing!
Arigato gozaimasu.
You gave your all in the fight.
I was honored to fight with Yoryak-san.
Despite my defeat, I didn’t regret it at all.
Best experience!
You were really cool too!
In the ring, I almost couldn’t make it.
Oyei-san.
Yoryak-san.
I have a favor to ask from you.
What is it?
Can I become a boxer under Phadetseuk boxing club?
What?
I’m serious.
I’ve been checking out many boxing clubs.
None of them make me feel like a family like yours.
Sure. Welcome to Phadetseuk family, Zazaki.
Really?
Arigato gozaimasu!
You’re welcome!
Yeah!!!!!
Take a seat.
Oh-oh!
Are you Doctor Wandee?
You dropped this.
I found it, so I brought it to you.
I saw that you took it from the hanger.
Hey. Don’t ruin the mood.
Come on.
Play along.
Oh, that’s mine.
Where did you find it?
Give it back.
You dropped it right in my heart.
Thank goodness you didn’t use this flirting approach in the beginning.
Look at this face carefully.
One month from now,
this will be the face of your boyfriend.
How cute is this badge, and also its owner?
Can you be any cheesier?
Give me the most cringy line.
How about…
Oh, do you feel like fainting?
You’re having difficulty breathing too?
I need to give you a kiss.
No, I mean
I need to give you CPR.
Yak.
Yak!
You’re breaking the rules again.
Just a bit.
I won my bout today.
Can’t I get a reward?
No.
Rules are rules.
What about this?
This doesn’t break the rules, right, my dear doctor?
Yak.
Who just said “Rules are rules?”
This winner…
doesn’t want a reward anymore?
Our house is being seized.
How could you do this?
Our family rules–we settle conflicts with punches.
Seriously, do you still see me as your brother?
Doc, can you hug me?
If their love is strong enough, they can definitely get through this problem.
Your hug is really warm. You know that?