Morning will surely come.
Make a pot of miso soup
with seasonal vegetables.
I'm digging in.
Having breakfast while
watching the weather forecast.
Prepare the lunchbox.
Check on the condition of the marimo.
A morning just like any other.
It's just that, except for that one thing.
Are you home already?
Yeah, what about Mashiro?
I'm here too, taking a shower right now. The
mackerel sandwich is absolutely delicious.
Three plates really was too much after all.
Oh no, a sudden wave
of drowsiness just hit me.
Don't fall asleep in the bathroom, okay?
I'm done with my shower.
As I thought, this isn't a dream.
What he said yesterday.
You just said you used to like me, right?
Fall for me all over again.
Because I like you too.
But I still can't fully believe it.
No matter how I think about it.
It all just feels like a fantasy made
up in the mind of a lonely single guy...
Can I really trust you?
If you really don't like me, Kanade...
I'll think about it.
I don't dislike you.
"Stay By My Side After the Rain"
(Episode 2)
A confession from your first crush?
Yeah, we ran into each other by chance a while
ago, and out of the blue, he told me he liked me.
I can't believe something this
dramatic actually happened.
In the end, I got fooled.
Huh?
He already has a girlfriend.
I was just played by him.
Come on, you can't
just believe it right away.
Something that feels like a dream
like that could never actually happen.
Sorry, just a moment.
Kanade-kun.
Are you free tonight?
Tonight?
If it's convenient for you…
Sumire-chan wants to spend
more time with Kanade...
Oh, sorry, please wait a moment.
If you're free tonight,
let's grab dinner together.
I've already made a reservation
at the restaurant for 8 PM tonight.
If it doesn't work for you, just
let me know and I'll reschedule.
Here's the location!
I haven't even said I'm going yet.
- Hm?
- Huh?
Oh, it's nothing, sorry about that.
I've got something going on tonight.
I see. Let's plan for another time, then.
Mashiro always manages to cut off
my escape route before I even realize it.
But actually, it makes
me feel a bit relieved.
As long as there's a way out,
I'll always want to run away.
Got it.
Kanade, over here!
Thank you for waiting.
Wow, here it comes!
Is it okay if I just order whatever?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is there anything you don't like to eat?
No worries, anything's fine.
Then... the assorted skewers, eight of them,
and the extra-large fried meat patty, and...
He's totally my type.
No, rather than saying
Mashiro is my ideal type.
It's more like my ideal type has
turned into someone just like Mashiro.
Then let's add an order of potato salad.
Alright.
And some edamame, too.
- Sure.
- That'll be all for now.
Understood.
Thank you for your help.
Let's make a toast!
- Great job.
- Thanks for your hard work.
Feels like I've come back to life.
Kanade, are you doing okay?
Huh?
We just saw each other yesterday.
I've been thinking about you.
Saying that might surprise you, right?
Are you good with alcohol?
Ah, I'd say I'm pretty average.
How about you?
Do you think I look weak?
Mashiro, you're always so bold,
whether it's eating or drinking.
People often say that about me.
They say I eat way too fast.
I had ramen for lunch today.
There's a place I go to a lot.
I always order the large bowl.
I went with the large bowl
again today, just like always...
Thanks to Mashiro.
I'm slowly starting to feel less nervous.
But the sense of unease just kept growing.
Thanks for waiting.
Another cocktail, please.
Alright.
- And then, I started wondering...
- Why doesn't Mashiro ever get nervous?
Is he just used to this kind of thing?
Having dinner one-on-one
with someone you like.
Normally, your heart
would be racing, right?
I guess he really
doesn't like me after all.
Sorry, I'm going to the
restroom for a moment.
Okay.
What am I feeling disappointed about?
Hasn't it always ended in disappointment
whenever I let myself hope for something?
Sorry...
Falling for you.
Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do anything wrong.
But...
Let's just stay friends from now on.
Sorry about that.
Good morning.
Oh...
Hey, can I borrow a pen for
a sec? I forgot my pencil case.
If you could just bluntly turn me down with
some harsh words, it would be so much easier.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
What's going on?
You haven't seemed very energetic lately.
I never realized I was such
a narrow-minded person...
- What?
- Ah, it's nothing, really.
I just want falling for
someone to be normal.
Just to have a normal relationship.
Just to date like any ordinary couple.
I just wanted something simple like that.
Kanade, you're really interesting.
Want to go on a date next time?
(Sure, I'd like to see you too.)
- Sorry for being late on our first date.
- Oh, it's okay.
Is it okay if we go here?
What?
Let's go.
Um...
Huh?
Sorry!
Why is it that I just can't do it?
I don't want to hurt myself
or anyone else anymore,
just for the sake of building a
deep connection with someone.
Wait for Mashiro to come back.
Let's just go home.
Incoming call from Mashiro Kosuke.
Mashiro?
Kanade...
Help!
Mashiro! Are you okay?
I can't move...
Wait a second.
I'll call an ambulance…
I feel like I'm going to throw up…
Huh?
I'm really terrible at holding my liquor…
Ah! No, I can't!
Wait! Over there! Hold on, are you okay?
Ah! Just a little longer.
Over here, over here,
over here! Yes, that's it!
Ah! Wait!
No way!!!
You saw me in a really embarrassing state.
Are you an idiot?
You know you can't handle your
liquor, but you still drink like that.
I can't help it.
Because I was really nervous.
Huh?
Drinking alone with someone you like. Just two of us!
Can anyone really stay
calm in this situation?
But Mashiro, you been
totally normal the whole time.
If they find out I'm nervous…
wouldn't that be kind of lame?
Today, I really...
It took so much courage
for me to ask you out.
Was what happened
yesterday really not a dream?
I kept checking my phone over and over.
I was worried about whether it
was okay to ask you out right away.
"First date," "relaxed," "delicious."
I was stressing over what kind of place
to pick that would make you happy.
I really agonized over it for a long time.
I misunderstood.
I thought you were really used
to this kind of thing, Mashiro...
Overthinking things on my own.
Overthinking?
Actually, what you said
yesterday, Mashiro...
I still can't believe it.
I understand.
If you think about it carefully.
A lot of things just happened so suddenly.
Meeting again.
Suddenly saying I like you and all that...
Hmm...
I'm really happy to see you again.
I'm afraid you'll slip away again.
I'm starting to get a little anxious.
When it comes down to it.
Even I'm not really sure how I feel.
Huh?
Doesn't that just mean
you don't like me...?
Like you, don't like you.
Believing, not believing.
Feelings are just like that.
It's something shapeless
and hard to define.
Being asked to show proof.
This isn't something you
can just show or prove.
That's true, I guess.
But...
I've always remembered.
You.
Huh?
Ever since graduating
from high school until now.
The anniversary of Dad's passing.
When I first came to Tokyo.
After I started working at the company.
The days when everything went smoothly.
On days when things aren't
going so well, and times like that…
Whenever something
happens, I think of Kanade.
I find myself wondering what
you might be doing right now.
I really want to see him.
I really want to talk to him.
Before that
I've never given a name to my own feelings.
But when you told me
you liked me, Kanade...
I think I must feel the same way.
Back in high school.
I've always… liked you.
I wonder if I managed
to get my feelings across?
You got your feelings
across, loud and clear.
Mashiro, you...
You never forgot about me.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
So... so close...
He keeps looking at me.
Um, Kanade...
W-What?
I want to kiss you.
What?! What are you even saying?!
You...
Saying something like that out
of the blue… in a place like this…
- Is that not okay?
- Stay away!
Because...
It's… it's my first time.
I've never had that kind
of experience either…
At our age already.
I know I'll get laughed at for saying this…
I just feel like doing something
like this while drunk isn't really right.
Does that mean it's okay
as long as I'm not drunk?
Huh?
Are you saying it would
be okay if I wasn't drunk?
No, no, no, that's not what I meant.
Ah!!
Why do you need to drink?
I'm such an idiot!
Mashiro!
- Damn it.
- Don't be like that.
- Hey, you two guys!
You've got a lot of energy!
There are lots of cute girls here.
Want to come and join us?
It's a great deal right now.
No, thank you.
Don't say that. Isn't it kind of boring
for just two guys to drink together?
Shut up, idiot!
Huh? What did you just say?
I told you, shut up.
I told you to mind your own business.
Even if it's just two guys hanging out, we can still
have a great time. Don't go saying it's boring so easily!
That's right, that's right.
You've got some nerve, huh.
You guys.
Hey! Let's talk somewhere else.
Huh...?
Run!
Hey!
Stop! Hey!
Stop right there!
Don't look back!
Keep your eyes on the road ahead!
It's always like this
when I'm with Mashiro.
Ready.
Go, go...
- Take this!
- Hey! Cut it out already.
Hey!
This really makes me feel alive.
That must be because
Mashiro is by my side.
I...
I want to have a normal
romance with Mashiro.
I had a great time today, thank you.
You'd better take some antacids.
How about going somewhere
together during this break?
Let's go, let's go!
Let me think about where I want to go!
This time, I definitely won't drink again.
Um... could it be that...
Does that mean you want to kiss?
Are you home yet?
I want to hear your voice.
Can I give you a call?
Hello.
Sorry I couldn't get in touch with you.
Nothing's really changed.
I really want to see you too.
(Next Episode)
Kanade, I've kept you waiting, haven't I?
(First Date)
Today is my first date with Mashiro.
How do you think we look to other people?
Why did you fall for me?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
(A woman's shadow?!)
Who is Mitsuko?
(Is their relationship
moving at lightning speed?)
Mashiro, I...