This is bliss.
I'm starving.
Mashiro is still fast asleep.
Kanade.
I went to the convenience store.
I wanted to make breakfast, but we were out of everything.
Oh, so that's what it was!
By the way, could you put some clothes on?
Huh?
Can I have the pollock roe one too?
Sure, but you've got a big appetite for this early in the morning.
Because I didn't eat much last night.
Plus, I worked up quite a sweat afterwards.
Delicious.
You've got a grain of rice on your face.
Something about this feels really nice.
Hm?
I wish we could have breakfast together like this every day.
Yeah.
Hey, Kanade.
Yeah?
Let's...
live together.
Huh?
What?
"Stay By My Side After the Rain"
(Episode 9)
Nice work.
Kanade.
Yeah?
Can this go in the closet?
Sure.
I'll help you.
Thanks.
Starting today,
I'll be living here with Mashiro.
By the way, we haven't had lunch yet.
Should we grab something from the convenience store?
We could do that.
But it's our first day, isn't it?
Let's get something exciting...
Like pizza.
Nothing hits the spot like junk food when you're exhausted!
I know what you mean.
Sorry the room's a little cramped now.
Not at all.
Living together will help us save money.
Once we've saved enough,
we can move to a bigger place.
Yeah.
That said,
it's really hard to save money.
I want to keep sending money to my grandma.
And it'll be a long time before I pay off my student loans.
There's no rush.
Just living with you is enough for me, Mashiro.
Before I forget.
Here.
This is your key, Mashiro.
Um...
I know I have my flaws,
but from now on,
please be patient with me.
I should be the one saying that.
Please be patient with me too.
Kanade is always by my side.
What was that about?
I bought some pudding.
Let's eat.
Pudding again?
I'd like to have a Mont Blanc or something for a change.
But I like pudding...
Ah, wait.
Please don't stack the greasy plates.
Okay.
Pudding, pudding~
Man, work at the construction site was exhausting today.
What do you usually do for lunch?
I usually just go to a ramen shop nearby.
Eating out every day isn't good for you.
How about I start making a bento
for you too, Mashiro?
For real?
Thanks.
I'll make yours extra large, Mashiro.
Um...
Yeah?
About what we call each other...
From now on,
can I call you "Shinichiro"?
Sure.
Then...
Kosuke.
Shinichiro~
Wait...
Stop it, Kosuke~
Stop it.
Kosuke~ I'm ticklish there.
Good morning.
I made breakfast.
Make sure you eat.
Thank you.
Alright, I'm off.
- Be safe.
- I will!
Curry first thing in the morning...
Aizawa-san.
Mind if I sit here?
Go ahead.
Thanks.
Kanade-san, did you get a new bento box?
Yeah.
I figured, why not? So I bought us a matching set.
Huh?
Actually, we're...
living together.
You started living together?
It's been almost a week.
Oh, I'm so happy for you, Kanade-san!
That's wonderful.
Thanks.
On that note...
Do you mind if I share some good news, too?
Actually...
Niijima-san and I have started dating.
With Niijima-san?
Yes.
He confessed to me the other day.
By the way, Niijima-san...
Just curious...
Yeah?
Are you two seeing each other?
You and Aizawa-san...
So he liked Aizawa-san.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Kanade-san.
Let's both find our happiness.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
You were late, so I already ate.
Hey, you need to dry the dishes after you wash them.
Oh, sorry.
And the laundry isn't folded.
I forgot.
Should we make a rule from now on?
Whoever brings in the laundry has to fold it.
Do we really need a rule for that?
Can't whoever has time just do it?
"Whoever has time," huh...
I'm going to take a shower.
Your phone's ringing.
Thanks.
Are you coming home for the Obon festival?
And, Dad's worried about you.
Yui is your sister, right?
Huh?
It was just lying there. I saw it by accident.
Oh...
Shinichiro, what's your dad like?
He's just an ordinary guy.
I met your mom back in high school.
But I've never met your dad, not even once.
You don't look just like him, do you?
Not at all.
We look nothing alike.
I see.
You should go home for the Obon festival.
Your parents want to see you, don't they?
This has nothing to do with you, Kosuke.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm not asking you to tell your family about me.
But you could at least tell me about yours.
There's nothing to tell.
Instead of that, why don't you tidy up the room for a change?
I'll get to it.
You always say that,
but I'm always the one who ends up doing it.
That's because by the time I get around to it,
you've already done it, Shinichiro.
That's only because you never do it, Kosuke.
I do things on my own schedule, okay?
I make breakfast every day. Isn't that enough?
You just microwave those food pouches.
And who eats curry first thing in the morning?
I happen to like curry!
If you're going to make it, clean up after yourself.
You always get curry all over the kitchen.
Kosuke, you're such a slob.
What are you so mad about?
I'm not mad...
I'm sleeping on the couch tonight.
Huh.
I just don't feel like sleeping in the same bed.
I see...
Fighting and still having to come home
to the same place is exhausting.
Sigh...
Aizawa-san?
Long day?
You too...
What's wrong?
Why the long faces, you two?
You and Niijima-kun...
Did something happen?
It's just that Niijima-san...
Whether it's deciding where to go for a date...
or what to eat...
he always just says it's up to me.
Isn't that just...
Niijima-san's way of being considerate?
Well, that may be true...
But it almost feels like Niijima-san
doesn't even care about going out with me...
I don't know...
I'm starting to feel really insecure.
If we can't understand each other now...
can we really make this work?
It's okay.
It's like that for everyone at the beginning.
Huh?
Since you both like each other...
as long as you don't give up, you'll eventually
find a rhythm that works for both of you.
So don't worry about it.
A rhythm that works for us?
What about you, Kanade-kun?
Why did you look so down earlier?
It's nothing...
I'm fine.
A rhythm that works for us...
How are we supposed to find that?
Kosuke is still mad at me.
It's impossible.
Fried rice ball.
Huh?
But I didn't order this.
I messed up the rice by adding too much water.
This one's on the house.
Thank you.
Go on, eat up.
Huh?
Okay, I'll dig in.
This is so good.
Even if you fail...
don't give up.
You're right.
Once you give up, it's really over.
When he gets back, I'm going to have a proper talk with him.
And I'll really listen to what Kosuke has to say.
Is he avoiding coming home
and just wandering around outside?
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone...
and begin your message.
(9:02 PM: Service on the Toei Line
has been suspended due to a personal injury incident.)
That's the train Kosuke takes...
It can't be...
Kosuke!
Are you okay?
Thank goodness.
Thank goodness...
Huh?
I was so worried about you!
You weren't home, and I couldn't reach you on your phone.
Sorry...
My phone died on the way.
Were you late because of the incident on the subway?
That was part of it.
This...
I was late because I was waiting in line for this.
The most popular Mont Blanc
from the department store food court.
Pudding again?
Sometimes I want to eat something like Mont Blanc.
No...
I thought I could solve the problem with food...
even though I knew it wasn't the right way.
That was delicious.
My first time having mackerel curry. It was so good.
The cafe owner taught me how to make it.
Since you like curry, Kosuke.
Thank you.
Should we have the Mont Blanc now?
Before that...
About yesterday...
- I'm so sorry!
Let's split the chores properly from now on.
Otherwise...
I'll become too dependent on you, Shinichiro.
I'm truly sorry.
No, I'm the one who should be sorry...
When it came to my family,
I said things that pushed you away.
I was too harsh, too.
You have your own...
family situation, Shinichiro.
I...
I don't get along well with my dad.
Huh?
My dad...
He's the type who thinks
a man isn't a real adult until he's married.
And I...
can't get married.
That's part of the reason...
I don't go home very often.
Although, I have been thinking it's about time I did.
I didn't know any of that.
I's sorry.
Don't be.
So...
let's make up.
Huh?
We've made up, right?
We've made up.
I never want to fight again.
Don't you think so, Shinichiro?
Well, I think...
it's necessary once in a while.
Huh?
That's ridiculous.
It's fine!
What good comes from fighting?
From now on,
even if we clash,
as long as we can slowly figure out
our own way of being together.
As long as we don't give up,
we'll be totally fine.
(Tanaka Kaito, Shirahama North High, Class 3-A
Let's all get together for Obon!)
(Let's have a class reunion!)
(For everyone who's moved away, let's meet up!)
(Next Episode)
A mini reunion?
Shinichiro.
Want to go back together?
(Their first time returning home together)
I've been putting it off.
(Clashing with his strict father)
Stop acting like a student, just messing around all the time.
I'm not messing around.
A grown man like you...
It's pathetic.
In this town...
(Reliving memories from their school days)
is the part of me that I used to hate.
It's really been a while.
Have some of mine.
There it is! The Mashiro block.
I'll cover Kanade!
I'm so glad I came back.
It's all thanks to you, Kosuke.
Thank you.
Dad...
What are you doing?