I got all the ingredients here.
Making a simple stir fried vegetable dish shouldn’t take more than 10 minutes.
I really can’t do this!
Don’t you see how much I’m trembling?
How’d you know you killed her?
Maybe Chef Hong didn’t kill herself.
I can’t help but wonder what my life would be like
if I didn’t get hit by that car three years ago.
Did you ever find out who the driver was?
No.
It was a hit-and-run.
Here they are, guys.
Alright. Grab yours.
Cheers!
Why did you kill me?
What’s wrong, Home?
I had a nightmare.
Go back to sleep.
I’m here. Don’t be afraid.
- Come on. - Okay.
Peach.
How the hell did you get in my bed?
Yeah, good question.
Wait.
I remember now.
I came to see you, Home.
You killed me.
You killed me!
You killed me. You killed me.
You killed me.
…Crap.
Guys.
It’s all thanks to you that
half of the Vimarnsukman properties
that were once infested with ghosts
are now sold.
There are only a few places left.
Mainly Avenue Khlong Sai Daeng that Ms. Somphorn is taking care of,
and the grand mansion Mr. Home hasn’t decided whether to sell or not.
See?
It’s because everyone on the internet believes you can really exorcise ghosts, Peach.
It’s giving fabulous.
It’s giving dream team.
Home, congrats.
Soon enough we won’t owe each other anything anymore.
What’s wrong?
Hey.
You okay?
Home, are you alright?
You look like you just saw a ghost.
Are you feeling unwell?
Maybe Mr. Home is getting haunted by all these ghost stories
that the stress starts giving him some kind of hallucination.
How about we call it a day for now?
I suggest we hold off on ghost-hunting this week.
I’ll call Mr. Suradech to come pick up Mr. Home.
You sure you’re okay?
It’s too sweet.
Did you ask for extra sugar?
Sugar helps reduce stress.
I don’t need to ask if you’re okay, do I, Mr. Home?
Hey, I’m super.
It’s just like you said, Kan.
Too many ghost stories just kinda mess up my mind.
If you need some advice,
or just need to talk,
you’re free to let me know.
Kan.
Have you ever made a mistake?
The kind of mistake that’s…
Deadly?
Severe.
It happened long ago.
But now that the truth has come to light,
it’s back to haunt me again.
Did you just find out this truth?
If it is weighing on your mind,
why not confess to whomever this concerns?
In court, most convicts who confess end up with a reduced sentence.
By half, in the worst cases.
But I don’t want any sentences at all!
Is there no way I’ll be 100% forgiven?
But you must take the consequences of your actions.
Did you think the other party went through any less pain than you did, Mr. Home?
If it were me, I’d confess as soon as possible.
It is better than concealing the truth until it reveals itself.
What if…
I’m not ready to confess?
Come on, Mr. Home!
Just confess before things get worse.
The sooner the better.
That is my fair warning.
THE FOUR-EYED EXORCIST
Hey.
Peach.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah?
Let’s say someone did you wrong,
and then apologized one day…
Would you forgive them?
Well, it depends on what they did.
Like, do I hate them or can’t even stand looking at them?
Well…
Kind of, I guess.
Then…
No, I won’t forgive them.
I’ll even make their life miserable.
What?
Why you gotta be so mean, man?
I’m not saying I’ll hurt them or anything.
I’ll just ignore the hell out of them
and just focus on achieving my own dreams.
That’s the best revenge there is.
Hold on. Hold on.
What do you mean?
I don’t get it.
Well, it’s basically rubbing in their face that I’m living my dream
so I don’t care about you, kind of thing.
Something like that.
You get it?
I see.
What is your dream, though?
It’s cooking.
I want to make a full-course meal that
tells my life story.
What?
That’s it?
That’s not it.
We gotta cook at a palace and invite all the high-brows to dine with us.
This will be broadcast live on national television, no less.
It’s gotta be exceptional.
Sure.
You agree?
Sure, whatever.
That’s your dream now. It’s not mine.
Stop it.
Since when are you sarcastic?
Hey.
Kan said I’m taking the week off, but I changed my mind.
I’ll have Suradech pick you guys up first thing tomorrow morning.
What? Why?
I was thinking we’d get to relax a little bit.
Yeah.
It’s not nice to go back on your words, you know?
You don’t have to come, Pangpang.
What? No way!
That’s worse!
I’m coming.
Take me with you.
I’m coming with you.
What the hell’s going on?
Where are you taking me?
Hang in there.
You’ll find out soon enough.
Ready?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Ta-da!
Don’t tell me…
We’re exorcising a ghost in a palace now?
Oh, my gosh.
Are we… exorcising a royal ghost?
I’m actually making your dream come true.
What?
Don’t be ridiculous.
Are you being serious?
This ain’t no joke, man.
You’re cooking at a palace, Peach!
Oh, Home, you sugar daddy, you.
I’m not done granting wishes.
Look at this.
Are we going to be on TV?
Who’s the host?
Are they famous?
Can I get a photo with them?
Of course.
So it’s gonna be a selfie, then.
You love it.
I can tell.
Clearly I do, mama.
FAKE CHEF
Wait.
I did not sign up for this.
Can I love you? How many scores do I get?
What should I do to be with you?
If you refuse to do this,
I guess it’s time the world gets to know…
Vimarnsukman’s best Lawyer-Singer.
Mama, you’ve got good taste in music.
Welcome to Master Coming-Back Chef Thailand!
PANGPANG, HOST We get a chance to watch this challenger chef take back his pride.
Peach.
Hello.
I’m Peach.
Chef Peach. PEACH, CHALLENGER
Oh, come on!
Can you make it more dramatic?
Give me that energy.
Fit the mood, will you?
Take this seriously!
Are you slacking off?
KAN, FAKE CHEF
Can you please cooperate so we can get this over with?
You only have one day
to achieve your dream.
Take this seriously.
This feels so much like the real deal.
I wish I had Chef Hong with me now.
The Fake Chef Hong is here! HOME, FAKE CHEF HONG
Fine.
Since you guys seem to be really invested in this,
I’ll do my best, too.
And now…
Please give a round of applause to the owner of this palace
who will also be our judge for today:
Mr. Chai-Un!
CHAI-UN, JUDGE
Chai-Un, thank you for meeting up with me and my team, sir.
Our families have been friends since Mr. Samai was alive.
Of course I’m okay with helping you with this little thing.
No problem.
Well, if that’s all you need me for…
Bye.
Wait, sir.
My team and I are grateful that you have granted our request to film here.
What request?
As thanks for that,
we’d like you to take the honor of being the judge for this event.
My brother is a new man now, sir.
I assure you he’s not unaliving you with his food this time around.
What did she say?
What language is that, dearie?
Peach, introduce yourself.
I—
We’re back with the mission to achieve the challenger chef’s dream.
Let’s see what his first dish is.
Hello.
Allow me to officially introduce myself through this soup.
PEACH SOUP, CHEF PEACH
I really must eat this?
Can’t we just fake it with the camera angles?
You really must eat it, sir.
There’s no way around it.
The camera’s right in front of you.
Oh, my God.
My name is present in the soup.
Now that you have tried it, what did you taste, sir?
Fish sauce?
Is that your name?
There’s no fish sauce in it.
I knew that.
Who would name their child “fish sauce”?
Weird.
I feel citrus.
What’s the smell?
Fruity.
Peach?
Is your name Peach?
Yes.
That’s my name.
Peach!
Well, the first dish had us all on the edge of our seats.
Let’s move on to the next.
They really gotta test me if I’m still scared, do they?
Home.
Can you toast this for me? Should be easy enough for you.
Sure.
Keep tossing and don’t stop.
Yep.
Mr. Peach.
Yes?
What inspires this dish?
This dish is inspired by when I was hit by a car.
Were you in a severe condition after the hit?
Well, let’s say this is how smashed I felt.
Are you sure your brother really is okay?
I’ll be honest with you. I don’t trust him.
My brother is all good, honest!
That scream just now sounds a lot like Home’s, though.
What’s wrong, Mr. Home?
No–nothing.
I’m alright.
You seem strangely agitated.
Did you graze your finger on the stove?
Can you do it?
Well, it’s time to hurry up and finish it.
You’re running out of time.
Hurry.
Yes.
This dish is called Smashed Shrimp Pad Thai on Death’s Door.
SMASHED SHRIMP PAD THAI ON DEATH’S DOOR, CHEF PEACH
It’s a reimagined version of the famous Pad Thai into an appetizer.
Interesting.
My dream was to become a chef,
but a terrible accident had prevented it.
I didn't look much better than the shrimp in your dish right now.
Oh, you poor thing.
That’s a terrible story.
I never knew that.
By the way, Chef Peach, what’s with all this?
A lot.
I thought I’d make enough for your family, sir.
So funny.
It’s so good.
But there’s no need to make so much next time.
It’s just me here.
So good.
What three words would you use to describe this dish?
Fun.
Delicious.
And…
Soft Power.
I can’t wait to taste the next dish.
I’m so excited.
Oh, excited?
What is this dish called, Chef Peach?
This is the main dish.
I have to be very careful because it has peas in it.
Peas is one of the ingredients.
But didn’t Chai-Un get hospitalized because of his legume allergy last time?
It’s not actually peas.
This is a plant-based protein that looks and tastes just like peas.
PLANT-BASED PROTEIN, MAIN INGREDIENT
Home, will you grab a bowl for me?
Sure.
This is the moment-of-truth dish
that surely puts our challenger under a lot of pressure.
Where’s the peas I asked you to toast?
It’s here.
Wait.
Why are there two bowls of them?
One of them is mine.
I’m about to take a shot of it to compare the real one to the plant-based one.
CHICKPEAS, IN COMPARISON TO THE MAIN INGREDIENT
But they look exactly the same once they’re toasted.
Which bowl is plant-based?
It seems our challenger has come face to face with a colossal obstacle.
Which bowl carries real peas?
And which carries plant-based peas?
Find out after a short commercial break!
This programme is brought to you by
the Vimarnsukman Ghost-Hunting Company Un Limited.
We guarantee a ghost-free satisfaction.
Which bowl carries real peas?
And which carries plant-based peas?
Suradech.
You’re not supposed to mess around when someone’s in the kitchen.
Oh, my God.
What are you going to do now, Peach?
He takes a while to cook this dish, doesn’t he, Kan?
My stomach is digesting itself.
The priority is my stomach.
I will give him a nudge, sir.
(Are we almost done?)
(Buy us some time, mama.)
(Use whatever is available in my bag.)
Are you hungry?
Mr. Chai-Un, do you like to sing?
No, I don’t.
I don’t mind listening to music, though.
If you’re going to sing, I’ll be your audience.
Let me try it.
They taste exactly the same.
Think again.
Which one were you toasting?
How would I know that?
You toasted it so you gotta know.
Hurry up.
I’m missing you, my love.
- Never knew I’d be missing you—
- P–Please.
For the sake of everyone watching at home,
and for my sake.
Stop.
The manual states that
the mic sounds disconsolate
because this is the only frequency in which ghosts understand.
Really?
Can it get across to ghosts?
Yes.
Can I try?
Ghosts, you sure?
Yes.
Check, check.
Niw, you lowlife little sister.
I know you stole my makeup and trash-talked me and Mother to the press
You wretch!
You’re the reason why my life is miserable, you snake.
You idiot!
For someone dead, you guys sure are lively!
Home, pick.
Hurry up.
Peach, I think…
And you, Grandfather.
You were old and slow as hell.
Old man, you fool.
Like a snail.
I hate waiting.
What’s the point of waiting?
What?
Home, hurry up.
Don’t you hear he doesn’t like to wait?
Peach, I think you shouldn’t serve this dish.
How could I not? It’s my main dish.
Mother, I have something to confess.
I told you I had a wife.
I really was telling the truth.
My wife just happened to be a man.
I’m sorry.
Peach, I…
I have something to confess.
Yeah?
Actually, I—
Peach.
We have to serve the main dish now.
I’m being serious.
Keep that for later.
You just need to tell me which bowl is the peas you toasted.
I think it’s this one.
I can see the peas I burned.
This is today’s main dish.
It’s called Scaredy Lamb Steak.
SCAREDY LAMB STEAK
It is paired with pea salad.
Oh, my God.
I am allergic to peas.
I am well aware, sir.
That’s exactly why this dish scares me.
This once ended my career and my dream.
But this time,
I added a lot of trust into this dish.
A trust in myself.
And a trust in my friend.
If you refuse to try it, I’ll understand.
It also took me a long time to get myself back.
I actually love peas.
I know I’m allergic, but I just love peas.
It’s been years since I’ve had some.
I believe the same mistake won’t happen again.
I want you to get over your fear with me, sir.
Is this real pea—
Peach.
Mr. Suradech, get the car. We’re going to the hospital.
I’m sorry.
No.
Wait.
It tastes exactly like real peas!
I can’t tell at all.
I have no idea!
What is your verdict on this dish, Judge?
It’s delicious.
It makes me feel so elated
to have overcome my own fear.
It’s never as scary as it seems, is it?
It’s not that bad.
This is the last dish on this course.
Nothing to present here, Chef?
I’ve said everything in my food, sir.
FORGIVE ME NOT
FORGIVE ME NOT, CHEF PEACH
I want you to decide how you want this full-course meal to end.
FORGIVEN
Our Chef Peach has finally and officially taken back his pride and dream!
Congratulations!
You go, Peach!
How was it, Mr. Chai-Un?
I’M A FAN OF THIS CHAI-UN GUY.
NOT OVER THAT PEACH-HOME HUG SOON.
BRO, MY MOUTH WATERING.
How was your second time dining with Chef Peach?
GETTING HUNGRY.
I WANT TO TRY THE FOOD, TOO.
I nearly died.
I meant, it was so good I thought I’d been to heaven.
HE’S SO OVER THE TOP.
HAHAHA, HE’S FUNNY.
It’s a shame…
That the dead will never get to experience it.
SHADE HAHAHAHA.
CAREFUL WITH YOUR WORDS.
You’re amazing, huh?
What?
That’s so unprompted.
What do you want?
I don’t want anything.
I meant it sincerely.
How’d you come up with the idea to cook for him
to ask for his forgiveness?
Because I’m amazing.
That’s it. Period.
Oh, dear.
Not humble anymore, are you?
Thank you, though,
for making my dream come true.
Speaking of which, what is your dream?
It’s having a huge house in the States and, like, 10 wives.
Come on.
Be serious.
I just want a normal family like any normal person.
Oh, pulling a sad homeboy stunt today, I see?
Home.
Pang and I are your family.
If your definition of family doesn’t involve 10 wives, that is.
Oh, right.
You said you had something to confess. What is it?
FORGIVEN
Peach.
Will you wait for me?
I just have to talk to my family about this first.
What is this about?
It sounds like something super serious.
I’ll tell you as soon as I talk to them.
Okay.
I’ll wait, then.
Hey, hey there.
What’s my dear nephew doing?
I’m learning how to make pancakes.
You wanna try some, Uncle Kid?
I’ll have to pass on that.
I’m watching my carbs intake.
I’m more worried about you.
You don’t look like you’re doing well.
Let me help.
No, it’s okay, Uncle Kid.
I want to do this myself.
Alright, then.
REAL ESTATE HEIR HIT-AND-RUN KILLED CHEF
Pok, I’ve sent you the file.
(Peach, you saw the news?)
(I think it’s your case.)
Going viral last night
was this video of a drunk driving case from three years ago.
Posted by an anonymous account,
the truth has come to light overnight.
Let’s take a look.
REAL ESTATE HEIR
DRUNK DRIVING
NEARLY KILLED YOUNG CHEF!
3 YEARS AGO
Here they are, guys.
Alright, grab yours.
Cheers!
Again?
We’re at a club and you’re not drinking again?
Well, I don’t need alcohol to have fun when I have you, baby.
Hey!
Hands off my girlfriend.
What?
You said you broke up with him.
Home, wait. Home.
Home, will you listen to me?
Home.
I can explain.
Home, talk to me.
CHEF HONG: YOU’RE RESPONSIBLE FOR ONE DISH FOR CHI-UN TOMORROW.
DO YOUR BEST, OR ELSE.
OF COURSE. I WILL DO MY VERY BEST. SEE YOU.
Damn it.
What a bummer.
Hello there, my dear nephew.
Uncle. Uncle.
What should I do?
Uncle, what should I do?
Home, what’s wrong? What’s happened?
I–I just hit someone with my car.
I hit someone with my car.
Home, calm down. It’s going to be okay.
It’s not going to be okay!
He must be dead!
Listen to me.
Is there anyone around?
N–No.
Let me check on him.
Don’t you move.
Send me your location and get out of there.
Aren’t–Aren’t we going to help him?
I’ll do it.
You leave that place immediately.
I’ll call the ambulance and the cops.
Just get out of there, Home.
What’s wrong?
You look super serious right now.
FORGIVE ME NOT
He knew all along and never thought to tell me?
Peach, calm down.
Let’s hear what Home has to say first.
“Calm down,” Pang?
Was any of what he did for us even real?
Uncle Kid.
What’s up?
Home, have you seen the news?
What news?
REAL ESTATE HEIR HIT-AND-RUN KILLED CHEF
I don’t know how the video got out.
But it went viral online last night.
I think everyone knows about this now.
Suradech, hit the gas.
Where are you going?
I have to talk to Peach.
No. I got that covered.
Listen to me, Home.
This isn’t just about you and your friends anymore.
This is about Vimarnsukman now.
I already sent Attorney Yai to take care of this whole thing.
Uncle Kid, how could you do that?
You should have talked to me about it first.
This is the only way out, Home.
Suradech, we’re leaving.
Don’t you dare move, Suradech.
Home.
Home, wait.
Home, don’t go!
Home!
Home, wait!
What’s going on, Mr. Yai?
Where have they gone?
I have negotiated with the plaintiff,
and they have been evicted.
There’s nothing to worry, Mr. Home.
Mr. Yai.
What did you say to them?
I’ve come here on behalf of Mr. Home.
This contract contains one important condition.
You two must not report, pursue litigation, speak about,
or even post about Mr. Home or the Vimarmsukman family.
This is your offer.
Can I add one more condition?
This money,
together with all the money I’ve received for my service,
I’m returning it all of to you
in exchange for…
Never being in contact with anyone from the Vimarnsukman family again.
For good.
In all my career,
I’ve never met a plaintiff who backed down without a fight before.
This is the best solution for you, sir.
How would you know what is best for me?
How?
How would you?
Let go of me!
Let go!
How could you do that to my friends?
Let me go!
How could you?
NOT FORGIVE
Let go of me!
GO TO HELL.
Have you heard the kind of things people say about us?
You troublemaker!
If you want me to lay low,
I’ll just sell the rest of my properties quietly.
Are you the buyer, Dr. Phoom?
If this is the house we’re hired to exorcise, then I refuse.
I just can’t stand the owner.
I can exorcise ghosts just fine on my own.
It’s not like what you usually do will work this time around.
Don’t get so cocky.