♪Time drifts like mist and rain,
the grass still green♪
♪Mountains fade, waters stretch afar♪
♪One pot of liquor, a path of life and death,
endlessly entangled♪
♪With the long wind and distant roads,
we roam the martial world carefree♪
♪Aspiring to reach the heavens♪
♪A pale face glows in the cold sky,
when will it end?♪
♪Side by side, we ride the wind and waves
through all the chaos♪
♪Through the twists and turns of life♪
♪A lone shadow stumbles in snowy mists,
the cold moon like a blade♪
♪Eventually, we must walk through fire,
laughing wildly through sorrow♪
♪Hot blood stains the grief,
snow blankets bow and blade♪
♪Strong liquor burns the heart,
loneliness torments the soul♪
♪This game of chess, life as the wager,
shrouded in the abyss♪
♪The will won't rest,
no escape to be found♪
♪Hot blood stains the grief,
snow blankets bow and blade♪
♪A loyal heart turns into waves,
breaking through endless tides♪
♪A life of wandering,
yet today is unforgettable♪
=Returned Master=
=Episode 11=
You.
Get out of here.
- Yes.
Let's go.
Come.
Who are you?
Where am I?
This is Blossom Manor.
(Wan Qianhong, Blossom Manor)
And I'm its mistress, Wan Qianhong.
Wan Qianhong?
I don't know you.
Why did you capture and take me here?
I didn't do that.
I saw you wandering all alone
in the mountain,
so I decided to save you.
I'm both beautiful and kind-hearted.
And I've done you a favor.
Not only are you not saying thank you,
but you're also suspecting me.
Well, thank you, Madam Wan.
You haven't told me your name.
I'm Little Walnut.
Little
Wal...
nut?
May I go now?
Little Walnut.
It's not peaceful out there these days.
There's a group of bandits
who violate women and rob.
They're nothing but evil.
It's too dangerous
for you to head home alone.
Why don't you stay here?
What do you think?
But...
No but.
Do you think I'll hurt you?
I want to go home, madam.
I said,
this is your home.
(This flower came
from the Blossom Manor.)
(It must have something
to do with its mistress, Wan Qianhong.)
(To save Little Walnut,)
(you two must seduce her
with your beauty.)
I don't think we should take it.
Fine.
This man's got a nice physique.
I'd love to touch it.
I wonder what it feels like.
They're looking at us.
They're so handsome.
What a coward you are.
No one is going to do anything to you.
Chest up, stomach in.
Maintain strong eye contact.
Imagine you're a dashing wolf.
Do we really have to do this, Jianwei?
You weren't this bashful
back in the Ghost Valley.
Now we're dealing
with an important business,
but you're shy like a lady.
But this is the public space,
not the Ghost Valley.
Besides, I'm nervous.
Also, why am I wearing
this more eye-catching outfit?
Little Walnut is your sister.
Naturally, you'll have to do more.
But you ran away from home
because of you.
I didn't mean it that way.
It's just that...
It's alright. It was my fault after all.
Come, let's go meet her.
(Yunque Pavilion)
Here.
Please enjoy it.
The view by the window is gorgeous, Xi.
I'm not in the mood for this now.
Xi.
You're a man.
How could you be so lovelorn?
In my opinion,
that woman is a flirtatious
liar.
You bought her freedom,
but she ran away
with the other man right after that.
It tells how cruel and unfaithful she is.
I have myself to blame
for loving her so deeply.
I was blinded by love
that I didn't figure out her character!
Longing brings no good at all.
Yet melancholy
may well be a kind of mad grace.
It's rare to come across
such a lovesick man like you.
Don't mind him, madam.
My friend is still tormented by love
and can't move on.
On the other hand,
you're a breathtaking beauty.
Of course you've stirred his heart.
You may look refine,
but you're slick-tongued.
He's more honest than you.
Let me toast to you, mister.
I'd love to get rid
of your sorrow with this drink.
Thank you, madam.
Come home with me, mister.
Deal?
I adore you.
Why aren't you bringing me home?
If you say so. You're coming with us.
- Xi.
- Madam.
I've got this performance
especially for you.
Do you like it?
Come and meet your new queen!
My queen, are you...
Are you going to get rid of me already?
I beg of you.
Please don't do that, my queen.
You good-for-nothing.
Since you can't make me happy,
what's the use of having you around?
However...
I can use you as a fertilizer.
Madam!
Xi.
Madam.
Afraid not, my Xi.
We're born to live life to the fullest
and enjoy every moment.
Let's cast all our worries aside
and do the happiest thing
in the world together.
Deal?
Join us.
Hold on!
Madam.
Since we're doing the happiest thing
in the world,
of course we have to be left alone.
Besides, I'm the new queen.
What do they think they are
to share your love with me?
To my surprise, you're pretty greedy.
Fine, you all should scram.
Wait.
You'll stay.
Go find Little Walnut now.
Xi. I know both of you are friends,
so I have him here to keep you company.
However, why are you paying attention
to him instead of me?
Madam.
I'm a loyal man.
Since you want to get together with me,
naturally, he should excuse himself.
How unthoughtful of me.
He's nothing compared to
a lovesick man like you.
You.
Get out of here.
Didn't you hear that? Get out.
Play along. Don't mess up our plan.
It's only both of us now, Xi.
Since I've granted your wish,
shouldn't I have some fun now?
Let's have a drink first, madam.
Well, after this,
we'll play a game.
Could this be a maze?
Where exactly is Little Walnut?
Little Walnut.
I wonder why
our madam cares so much
about that lass.
I know, right?
She's well fed.
Little Walnut is indeed here.
Once you've seen the vast sea,
no other waters compare.
Once you've known Mount Wu,
no other clouds will do.
Among the flowers,
I glance back with no desire.
Half for the Dao, half for you.
Winter Solstice, Year Seven of Yongning.
Li Pu?
Father?
♪The soul within the dream is started,
and flames consume that soul♪
♪Beyond the dream, a friend leads the horse,
smiling, urging the journey to begin♪
♪Through the turmoil of the martial world,
who is without regret?♪
♪Heaven's will toys with innocence
time and again♪
♪When the fog settles,
who owes the deeper debt?♪
♪Clashing spear tips and flashes of blades
reflect on youthful faces♪
♪Passion masks the sorrow beneath♪
♪Side by side in peril,
life hanging by a thread♪
♪Life and death are easy,
feelings are hard to express♪
♪Snow falls on green hills,
stirring the eyes♪
♪Its sharp edge grazes the temple♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent,
letting love and hate swirl free♪
♪But this karmic entanglement
can't be severed♪