♪Time drifts like mist and rain,
the grass still green♪
♪Mountains fade, waters stretch afar♪
♪One pot of liquor, a path of life and death,
endlessly entangled♪
♪With the long wind and distant roads,
we roam the martial world carefree♪
♪Aspiring to reach the heavens♪
♪A pale face glows in the cold sky,
when will it end?♪
♪Side by side, we ride the wind and waves
through all the chaos♪
♪Through the twists and turns of life♪
♪A lone shadow stumbles in snowy mists,
the cold moon like a blade♪
♪Eventually, we must walk through fire,
laughing wildly through sorrow♪
♪Hot blood stains the grief,
snow blankets bow and blade♪
♪Strong liquor burns the heart,
loneliness torments the soul♪
♪This game of chess, life as the wager,
shrouded in the abyss♪
♪The will won't rest,
no escape to be found♪
♪Hot blood stains the grief,
snow blankets bow and blade♪
♪A loyal heart turns into waves,
breaking through endless tides♪
♪A life of wandering,
yet today is unforgettable♪
=Returned Master=
=Episode 13=
They're just my toys!
How dare they deceive me!
How dare they poison me!
My head... My head hurts so bad!
My head...
It hurts!
Are you alright, madam?
Calm down. They mean no harm.
What did you say?
They mean no harm?
Are you calling me evil now?
Mother...
What did you call me?
Mother.
Little Walnut. Little Walnut.
Are you alright?
I... I didn't mean to hurt you.
I didn't mean to do that.
It's all my fault.
No! It's all their fault.
It's all their fault!
I will get rid of them.
I must kill them!
Calm down, Mother.
You're drunk. Are you alright?
You're very drunk now.
You should get some rest.
Jianwei. It's me.
You gave me a fright.
Instead of dying
at that crazy woman's hands,
you almost killed me.
Who told you to get so close to me, then?
I was just trying to...
Forget it. I won't argue with you.
Don't be dramatic.
I've never been to such a place.
I told you this was no place for me.
- Who's that? Let go...
- Kill you
and I'll be the master of this manor.
The queen loves me the most.
All of you must die!
You can have the queen.
Just take her if you want.
Just take her!
Help! Help!
Help!
- Xiaoxi!
- Help!
You all must die.
I want you to die!
Help!
- Xiaoxi! Let go!
- Little Walnut.
Let go!
Are you alright, Jianwei? Are you hurt?
I'm alright.
Please get this right, Little Walnut.
If you had come later,
I would've been killed.
Forget it.
How did you end up being brought here?
Did that old hag hurt you?
I'm all fine, Xiaoxi.
Madam Wan has been kind to me
because she thinks I'm her daughter.
Her daughter?
You?
We can't stay here.
Let's just talk later.
We should get out of here first.
Let's go. Quick.
Stop right there! Come back!
I'm going to kill you all!
My queen.
I want to see the queen!
When will you come and see me, my queen?
Little Walnut.
Where are you going?
Don't hurt them, Mother.
We didn't mean to mess with you, madam.
Little Walnut's family
has been worried about her
since her sudden disappearance.
Well, please show some mercy
and let us go.
Does that mean
the encounter at the restaurant
was a plot of yours?
Was it, Xi?
That's why. We had been looking all over
for your filthy lair.
Thus, we came up with that last resort.
What did you say? Say that again!
Sure. Your filthy lair!
Please don't hurt them, Mother.
Get up, Little Walnut!
I'll stay here for you.
Little Walnut. Little...
Please spare them, Mother.
I beg of you.
Fine. I can let them go.
Really?
Be patient. I'm not done yet.
Stop wasting our time here, woman!
You want to settle the score, huh?
I haven't settled the score with you
after taking advantage of me.
Let her finish her sentence.
Kill a person for me.
Bring his body back here,
so I can make a fertilizer out of it.
After that,
Little Walnut can go with you.
Kill a person?
Who's it?
Li Pu.
Li Pu? Wasn't he the protector general?
Isn't he dead?
What did you go? He's dead?
When was that?
Didn't you know?
He's been dead long ago.
General Li and his whole family
were killed last Chinese New Year's Eve.
None of them made it out alive.
No way. That's impossible.
It's impossible. No way.
That's impossible.
Impossible.
No way! You're lying!
He promised to come back to me!
You must be lying to me!
How could he die without my permission?
How could he die?
You must be lying to me!
He can't die without my approval.
How could he die?
It turned out
you were that treacherous man's lover.
What a shame.
He never showed up before his passing.
You're talking nonsense!
He promised to come and see me!
He promised me that.
I've been waiting him for years.
She's heavily poisoned,
why must you keep provoking her?
Because she was in cahoots
with that traitor.
- Liar!
- You...
Madam Wan!
Little Walnut!
Among the flowers,
I glance back with no desire.
Half for the Dao, half for you.
Among the flowers...
How did she end up this way?
I glance back with no desire.
Half for the Dao, half for you.
How come?
Among the flowers,
I glance back with no desire.
Half for the Dao, half for you.
Mother.
Who are you?
Are you alright, Mother?
Little Walnut?
Yes, it's me.
Stop this, Mother. I'm scared.
Little Walnut. Little Walnut.
My daughter.
No, you're not. You're not her!
Where is my daughter? Where is she?
Why is she going berserk again?
I think she's lost it.
She's lost it?
If so, why don't we get rid of her now?
I'll end her life now.
Where is my daughter? Where is she?
My daughter.
My daughter...
Listen up.
I don't want you to end up like me.
So you can't fall in love with anyone.
If not, you'll get hurt.
Got it?
I really hope you could grow up
a healthy and happy girl.
Did you hear me?
Calm down, Mother.
I... I will kill him!
Old hag. Where's my sister?
Tell me now
or I'll your filthy lair down!
Among the flowers,
I glance back with no desire.
Half for the Dao, half for you.
Where exactly is my sister,
you crazy woman?
I'm not a lunatic.
In this world,
everyone is after fame and fortune.
They're hungry for power and ambition.
All of us are crazy, no?
Cut it out. Where is she?
I can let you have her.
Want to know where Little Walnut is?
Kill him, then.
Jian... Jianwei.
Are you really going to do as she says?
Fine. Do it, then.
However, after I die,
you must bring Little Walnut home safely.
How touching!
Both of you can die together, then!
♪The soul within the dream is started,
and flames consume that soul♪
♪Beyond the dream, a friend leads the horse,
smiling, urging the journey to begin♪
♪Through the turmoil of the martial world,
who is without regret?♪
♪Heaven's will toys with innocence
time and again♪
♪When the fog settles,
who owes the deeper debt?♪
♪Clashing spear tips and flashes of blades
reflect on youthful faces♪
♪Passion masks the sorrow beneath♪
♪Side by side in peril,
life hanging by a thread♪
♪Life and death are easy,
feelings are hard to express♪
♪Snow falls on green hills,
stirring the eyes♪
♪Its sharp edge grazes the temple♪
♪Heaven and earth fall silent,
letting love and hate swirl free♪
♪But this karmic entanglement
can't be severed♪