[Park Ji Hoon]
[Hong Ye Ji]
[Hwang Hee]
[Ji Woo]
[Love Song for Illusion]
[Characters, places, organizations, and incidents in this drama are fictitious and have no connection to historical facts. The scenes with animals were in compliance with the production guidelines.]
I missed you, Kyera.
Sir Ak Hee?
Sir Ak Hee, your blade was removed.
I am glad.
I was very worried since I could not confirm before leaving.
You were worried?
Of course, you were not waking up as Sir Ak Hee. I was so worried.
You were worried, huh?
I guess you are still unwell.
It still hurts a lot here, does it not?
Yes, there is a little bit of bleeding.
It kind of- A little- No, it hurts a lot.
Still? Let me see. I will try treating it.
N-No, it is okay.
I-It is not that bad.
Kyera!
[Episode 14]
Master Yang, Ha Rang.
Are you okay?
How can you leave without even telling us?
Sorry. I made you worry, right?
Why did you do such a reckless thing?
I am sorry, Master Yang.
How did you know I was here?
His Majesty sought us out.
I have something to talk about with Kyera.
How did you know where to find Master Yang?
I-It was not me. It was Sajo Hyun.
Did Yeon Wol get this for me? To save my life?
That is correct.
But why did she leave without a word?
Why?
I know. Why would she suddenly leave?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
Where are you going?
Yeon Wol might be in danger! I must save her.
You do not even know where she went!
You cannot. This is dangerous.
Move aside.
Let me come with you.
It would be better than going on your own.
Let go of-
Sajo Hyun.
Let me see you for a moment.
Your Majesty.
What is the matter?
Are you feeling unwell again?
Come to your room right now.
Your Majesty, you are not going, right?
Tell Eunuch Neung to leave.
Take your leave.
You cannot go anywhere!
I am going to be standing guard right here.
Close your eyes now.
Eunuch Neung!
Eunuch Neung, are you there?
Did it work?
It worked. It did.
It finally worked.
Who is there?
You are- How...
How do you have my face?
Look at this. I guess you really lost all your memories.
Hey, I could not even go out because you lost your memories.
W-Who are you?
And where is this place?
Oh, this place?
I guess you can say this place is
our mind's space where we have our friendly meetings.
Me? I am you.
Me?
What a heinous evil spirit.
This is still the same even though you have lost your memories.
Evil spirit?
Wow, it is unpleasant but amazing at the same time.
How impertinent, you scum!
Hey...
stop yelling and...
come. Come take a seat here.
Answer me. I asked who you are.
I said I will answer you, so come take a seat.
It has not been long since I got that removed, so I cannot really move.
I explained the situation to Sajo Hyun in a hurry.
The urgent matters first for now.
He is smart because he takes after me.
He sure understood quickly.
Two personalities?
Confusing, right?
But you do not have the time to be doing this.
I got it. I must go save Yeon Wol first.
On your own? You do not even have Ji Jeon Seo with you.
I know where to find the man you called Master Yang.
By the way, how do I get out?
Is there anyone here who knows Yeon Wol?
If you do, show yourself! I have to say something.
Hey, Sajo Hyun, absolutely do not be kind to Hwang Ga Ron.
Get the drop on him, no matter what, okay?
Act like you saw through everything.
Absolutely do not let him know you lost your memories.
By the way, why did you suddenly come out?
You are disappointed I came out.
Should I go back inside?
That is not it.
You could have come out after we got back-
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you as soon as possible, so I asked Sajo Hyun.
For telling him how to save you, I asked him to allow me to meet you quickly.
Sir Ak Hee, your eyes are worse than before, right?
N-No.
I-I can see just fine.
That cannot be. Your focus is not right.
We are done talking. Let us go.
Thank you for helping me today.
Please help so His Majesty's memories can return soon.
You knew I was not Sajo Hyun?
D-Do I not look like a king?
We must rush to go back before sunset.
Those two are looking down on me, right?
Your eyes did get worse. You are misunderstanding them.
No, I can see just fine.
Did Sajo Hyun's memories come back?
I do not know that,
but he told off Prince Ga Ron and took Kyera back.
That man is not Sajo Hyun.
He is Ak Hee.
No way.
There is no way the blade was removed.
Even if it was removed, His Majesty has lost his memories,
so Ak Hee cannot come out.
Incorrect. Even if the one who took Kyera was Sajo Hyun,
he could not have done it alone.
One way or another, Ak Hee is influencing him.
It means Ak Hee survived.
Oh, my. This is such a letdown for you.
You thought Ak Hee had died.
If he survived, I just need to make use of him alive,
manipulating his boiling obsession and ambition.
I realized it clearly after nearly perishing for good.
I...
do not want to let you go.
I do not want to lose you to Sajo Hyun.
I have been sharing my body with such an untidy person?
He still survived even after being stabbed with something like this?
My goodness.
Wait a moment.
Anyhow, you want to save Kyera,
although you do not remember her.
That is right.
You were having a great time yesterday, being all lovey-dovey.
Wait, how would you know that?
Sir Ak Hee can read everything you experience and think.
You get to read me, but why can I not read you?
That is the difference between you and me.
The proof that I am way greater than you are.
Ak Hee gets to read my mind and my memories.
But why can I not do the same?
I can also read Ak Hee's mind.
I can read it.
Gosh, it is not working.
Goodness, I was looking elsewhere.
W-What is this?
Wait, he came to such a rundown place?
Exactly.
Yeon Wol!
Aigoo, Yeon Wol!
You left without even a word. Do you know how shocked I was?
I am sorry, Eunuch Neung. I made you worried sick, right?
Gosh, seriously.
Your Majesty, you, too.
I was guarding you all day, and you left the moment I went to take a leak.
Well, I apologize.
Sorry?
Sir Ak Hee?
You are Sir Ak Hee, right?
Aigoo, Sir Ak Hee!
Aigoo, aigoo...
What in the world? I never thought I would be so glad to see Sir Ak Hee.
What makes you think I am Ak Hee?
Come on, Sir Ak Hee.
I can tell with one glance.
What about His Majesty?
He is doing well, right?
He does not even have his memories. Would this not confuse him more?
Sir Ak Hee, as for your memories...
You recognize me, so you are fine. Right?
Aigoo, His Majesty is the only troubled one.
Aigoo, what do I do?
Gosh, everyone is only worried about Sajo Hyun.
Yeon Wol, you will not go anywhere now, right?
For a while.
Huh? Where are you trying to go now?
Even if I go, I will make sure to tell you, Eunuch Neung.
I promise.
Yes, you must do that.
Sir Ak Hee, you will have dinner, right?
What? Why?
Should I just skip dinner and go inside?
So you can see Sajo Hyun sooner?
Gosh, why are you saying that, Sir Ak Hee?
Let me treat your wound. We have the medicinal herbs, too.
What wound?
I will treat your wound.
And let us have dinner together, too.
She said she would treat me.
She wants to eat with me.
C-Chung Ta?
Why you little...
W-Wait, what is the matter with you?
Stop it!
H-Hey, hold on, stay right there.
Wait-
You bastard, how dare you stick the blade in me?
You tried to kill me!
So, you should have listened to me from the beginning.
I gave you a chance, but you did not even budge.
Oh, really? You should try getting stabbed, too.
See how much it hurts, okay?
Kyera!
You need to have Kyera.
You can have her.
You just need to get rid of Sajo Hyun.
Once Sajo Hyun is gone,
you can take over that body
and Kyera will have no choice.
That talk is already over.
You are going to disappear soon! You know that!
See? You are more or less blind now, are you not?
You forced your way out earlier. So even your power must have weakened more.
And Sajo Hyun became stronger!
Sajo Hyun lost his memories anyway.
That is why this is a chance for you.
Sajo Hyun fully trusts you right now.
He does not know who you really are.
Perform geuminsal* on Sajo Hyun.
(Killing with a metal)
You will stick the blade in him.
How about it?
Are you sure the Queen is pregnant?
Yes, you told me to confirm it, so I went to her chamber again.
Queen, guess what I brought.
They are the highest quality silk I got from the country of Jinhoi.
Take a look.
I rubbed peach skins all over the silk before taking them with me.
Hold on.
Wait, why?
She cannot fool my eyes.
She is pregnant, for sure.
Grand Prince, I did well, right?
Grand Prince, Grand Prince!
Grand Prince, you must be busy with state affairs.
What brings you here?
No matter how much I think about it,
I reckoned it cannot be overlooked. So I came running.
Did another problem break out?
It did.
And it is a serious matter.
I had a dream last night.
A large dragon was embracing the Queen's pavilion.
I had a weird feeling and asked High Priest Chung Ta.
She said it must be a highly fortunate conception dream.
Now that I see, Your Majesty, your complexion looks quite rough.
My dream is a conception dream, right?
Grand Prince, that is total nonsense-
It is.
I did not tell anyone because I was being cautious.
But as expected, you are special because you are the uncle.
What great news!
Your Majesty,
I sincerely congratulate you.
Head Minister, congratulations.
You will now become a grandfather.
Father did not know, either.
I apologize for not having told you.
Oh, yes, Queen.
His Majesty should be a part of this joyful news.
But he is fighting an illness, and it makes me sad.
Exactly so.
But still, I feel so reassured to have you here, Grand Prince.
Yes, I will protect the baby
in your womb without fail as his uncle.
As expected, I was right to bring that person.
Pardon?
To serve Your Majesty, the precious one, with even more care,
I brought a trustworthy bodyguard.
Come in.
What are you waiting for?
Come in and offer your greetings.
Officer Ji will protect you starting today, Your Majesty.
Grand Prince, this man is His Majesty's bodyguard.
Since you are pardoning him anyway, why not send him to His Majesty-
My subordinates are protecting His Majesty rigorously, so do not worry.
I heard Officer Ji was taken in by Your Majesty's family.
The baby in the womb will also be at ease
if Her Majesty is served by someone she used to know.
Aigoo, now that I think about it,
this man also found out about Her Majesty's pregnancy.
Officer Ji, you must protect Her Majesty with your life.
Do you understand?
I might as well use your room.
Did you meet Yeon Wol?
How was your talk with her?
Was she not surprised to see you?
What took you so long?
Gosh, ask me one thing at a time.
Could it be that Yeon Wol left soon after?
Yes, she sends her regards to you.
Aigoo.
She left.
Without even a farewell.
I am kidding.
She is at the villa right now.
R-Really?
I stopped her from leaving and told her to be with me.
Thank you, Ak Hee.
H-Hey, I am not fully healed here.
Anyhow, thank you.
Why thank me? I only told my woman-
What were you going to say?
You can go now.
Can I really do that?
Help the Grand Prince Sajo Yoong.
If you do, I will stick the blade in Sajo Hyun's body.
Will Sir Ak Hee yield tomorrow?
I told him the wound needs to be disinfected again tomorrow, right?
Should I not have said that?
Sir Ak Hee.
You are trying not to fall asleep, right?
Your Majesty?
It is Your Majesty, right?
Your Majesty.
I mean...
how did you recognize me when it is this dark?
Just a feeling.
♫ Even if you disappear, even if it is only for a moment ♫
I was too harsh on you at Prince Ga Ron's royal villa.
I was too shocked.
It is okay. I understand.
But still, I was able to save you because Ak Hee could read my mind.
I am really glad Sir Ak Hee did not lose his memories.
However, that is really...
Ak Hee can see my memories, but I cannot.
I heard that is how it was from the beginning.
Could it be because you thought you could not do it from the beginning?
It is because I never tried to do it?
I did try earlier.
Try harder until your brain starts sweating.
Until it sweats?
♫ So that I can feel the faint sound of you breathing ♫
Yes.
Focus your strength right here.
♫ Even if the memories get erased and become blurry ♫
♫ Your warmth remains in my heart ♫
♫ Even if you become wind and cannot hold you ♫
Your brain must be sweaty.
♫ I'll stay here and wait for you ♫
♫ Even if you disappear again tomorrow, I will wait ♫
Is it refreshing?
It is refreshing, and it is cold.
♫ So that I can feel the faint sound of you breathing ♫
How is it? Is it refreshing?
It is very refreshing.
Have some more.
They are having the time of their lives.
Just let the Grand Prince Sajo Yoong deal with the bothersome throne.
Go far away with Kyera and
live happily ever after, Sir Ak Hee.
Is this also an herb?
Oh, this is a medicinal herb good for the eyes.
Sir Ak Hee's eyes keep getting worse.
Did something get in your eye?
I think my eyes keep getting blurry as well.
I will give you some as well, Your Majesty.
Gosh, I will give you a lot.
I think dirt got in for real.
Let me see.
Open your eye.
Aigoo, stop overreacting and bear it.
I am sorry.
For what?
I am sorry for liking you this much when I have the Queen.
I am sorry-
I would like to come pick greens again tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Sir Ak Hee's turn to wake up.
Oh, in that case, the day after tomorrow?
S-Sure thing.
And also, it will be dangerous for Ak Hee to come
pick greens because his eyes are bad.
I reckon it would be better for Ak Hee to just stay in bed.
Yes!
I will make sure Sir Ak Hee stays in bed all day.
I thought you were taken by a tiger while picking greens.
You did not even gather that much greens, either.
What were you two doing?
So, where are you coming from?
The market, so I can make a delicious dinner later.
Ji Jeon!
Aigoo, Ji Jeon, you were released, huh?
You went through so much. Look how much you waned.
Your Majesty.
He is Officer Ji, who used to guard you, Your Majesty.
Ji Jeon, you did not come alone?
Her Majesty has arrived.
What?
The Queen?
Your Majesty, where have you been?
I was coming to meet you because I was worried.
What brings you here, My Queen?
What do you mean?
Would there be a reason for a wife to come see her husband?
Who do we have here? Are you not Yeon Wol?
Have you been doing well?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, the wind is cold.
It is.
I should go inside.
My Queen, are you unwell?
Yes, I am a little unwell.
I will do it.
Is she sick?
In fact, I came to deliver joyful news to you, Your Majesty.
I have...
Congratulations, Your Majesty.
Her Majesty is with a child.
With a child?
S-Sajo Yoong, you scum.
W-With a child?
I found out a while ago.
But I get to tell you now because I kept quiet since it is an important and cautious matter.
I am sorry I could not inform you sooner, Your Majesty.
Yeon Wol, why are you standing there?
The sun is hot. Come on up here.
Yeon Wol, will you congratulate me on my pregnancy?
You were once my servant.
I heard you used to be a palace maid in the royal kitchen.
Did you also serve the Queen?
Yes, she did. Only very briefly.
Congratulations on your pregnancy, Your Majesty.
Thank you.
Thank you for making this long trip.
Rest comfortably in the master bedroom.
Yes, I made this long trip because I missed you so much.
But I am actually quite tired.
Let Her Majesty rest in my bed.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- No.
Could you do it, Yeon Wol?
I am glad to see you in a long time.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Eunuch Neung.
Eunuch Neung, Grand Prince Sajo Yoong said to remember the promise.
I am sorry, Eunuch Neung.
Your Majesty.
Why are you still lingering around His Majesty?
Did you really...
bear His Majesty's child?
What?
You wicked wench!
Be careful.
You will get hurt.
It is His Majesty's child I conceived from sleeping with His Majesty.
What an idiot.
Did you think your behavior with His Majesty was love?
Did you mistake him to be sincere?
Do you think His Majesty really loved you, you lowly wench?
Get lost, you wench.
Do not ever come near His Majesty again.
If I see you one more time,
I will rip you into pieces alive!
If your pregnancy is true, consider your baby in the womb.
Such harsh language is bad for prenatal care.
What?
Eunuch Neung, did I really...
Did I really have a good relationship with the Queen?
You were kind to everyone, Your Majesty.
Are you saying I turned my eyes to another woman
when I had a good relationship with the Queen?
Answer me, Eunuch Neung.
You are the only one I can trust right now.
Your Majesty, the thing is...
The moment you spout nonsense,
your old mother, your brother couple, and your young nieces and nephews
will all be torn apart limb from limb.
I do not really know, either.
Did you used to be my bodyguard?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Is Yeon Wol still serving her?
She left just now.
Her Majesty is with a child.
W-With a child?
There is no way.
What an idiot.
Did you think your behavior with His Majesty was love?
Did you mistake him to be sincere?
Master Yang.
Have you realized everything now?
Everyone is conspiring to mock His Majesty.
We cannot let things be.
Why did you become so foolish?
Did your love for His Majesty do this to you?
What can you do by going back to that house?
What will you do with His Majesty, who lost his memories?
The Queen even became pregnant.
What are you even going to do?
I will not stand by and watch anymore.
If you will not forsake everything and follow me,
this will be the end of our connection.
Master-
What am I going to do by meeting her?
What excuse am I trying to give?
I do not have the right.
Sajo Hyun would never do that.
Once she loses all feelings of love for Sajo Hyun,
Kyera will not have any other choice.
H-How will she lose all feelings of love?
She is bound to end up that way.
This is really your final chance, Ak Hee.
That was why.
I am standing at the edge of a cliff right now.
And all my memories are gone.
What should I do?
Who should I trust?
Ak Hee, let us have a talk.
Please summon me.
Ak Hee, summon me to that room.
I cannot go there on my own yet.
Gosh, if I face this bastard right now,
I will have to lie to him.
Hey, come to your senses.
You are an evil spirit.
Guilt does not suit you.
Ak Hee, Ak Hee!
If there is no way to regain my memories,
I need to read Ak Hee's mind, at least.
I will be able to read it.
Sir Ak Hee.
I must tell His Majesty the honest truth.
Mother, I am sorry.
I am sorry, Eunuch Neung.
Ak Hee, I have to meet you this way since you will not summon me.
Looks like Officer Ji delivered my words properly.
Is it to your liking?
The current situation I prepared for you, Sir Ak Hee.
Everything exists for your sake, Sir Ak Hee.
Are you even human?
I may not be human!
I may be an evil spirit like you.
You are doing all this to become the king, right?
Wow, you are really something else.
It is natural for me to become the king.
The method is what matters.
I want a peaceful passing of the crown.
Peaceful passing of the crown?
You are scared because people are saying you are the most wicked of them all.
Those who yearn for the restoration of the Royal Family of Yeon.
Those who support Sajo Hyun.
There are even those who doubt my legitimacy to the throne.
In order to silence them at once,
peaceful passing of the crown will be best.
Will Sajo Hyun just watch, huh?
Though he lost his memories, he is very smart.
That is why I am saying I need your help.
The day you allow the passing of the crown,
Chung Ta will perform geuminsal on Sajo Hyun.
I heard it from Chung Ta.
That you will disappear soon.
So, this is really a trade that is good for you, me, and everyone else.
Use honorifics.
I am the king.
Would this not be what you call the best trade, Your Majesty?
How would I know if you will keep your promise or not?
That is the same for me as well.
Would it not also be quite fun to doubt and suspect each other
until the very last moment, Your Majesty?
I will not disappear.
You were avoiding me. So what brings you here?
I am going back to the Palace tomorrow.
Did you already come to an agreement?
Since I recovered, I cannot very well stay here forever.
Ak Hee, regarding the Queen, did you-
Am I the one who impregnated the Queen?
Tell me honestly.
Why would I?
I have a woman I love. So, why would I?
You had a woman you love?
Who is it?
Hey, Sajo Hyun.
There is something you are mistaken about.
Kyera- No.
Yeon Wol...
is in a relationship with me.
What?
I got to know her while roaming outside the Palace and came to like her.
Back then, you had your queen...
Kyera and I liked each other so much that I took her in as a concubine.
I took her in as a concubine.
A concubine?
Did I just sit back?
I did nothing when you took in a concubine-
Would you have done nothing, you ask?
You made such a scene.
You and I fought a lot.
Aigoo, when I think about back then...
There is no way.
- Yeon Wol-
- Would not have liked me instead of you?
There is no way since she was so kind to you?
Hey, she did all that because
you need to recover and get your memories back for me to live.
You cannot mistake such things.
Why are you telling me this only now?
You kept quiet all this time, so why now-
Well, it has been chaotic and...
you seemed to like Kyera.
So, I did not know how to bring this up.
But the Queen suddenly came.
So, I cannot help but tell you the truth.
I am sorry-
Well, what? What is it?
Well...
nothing happened between you two already, right
I have been sick for a while, so I could not look into the world.
I see.
Aigoo, you are too kind.
Anyhow, I am sorry.
Things became complicated because of me.
Be good to the Queen.
The Queen went through a lot because I brought Kyera as my concubine.
More tightly.
It was all a misunderstanding?
Yeon Wol was Ak Hee's woman?
Her Majesty is with a child.
Will you be able to leave tomorrow like this?
I will leave.
Go back to Sajo Hyun.
Go tell him everything, honestly
and become Sajo Hyun's concubine again.
Master Yang, how can you say that?
I do not wish to see you like this anymore.
Have you no shame to face the people wishing for the restoration of the Royal Family of Yeon?
What would they say if they found out about this?
Master Yang, I know I cannot repay you for saving my life and
taking care of me thus far, even with my death. However,
I do not want any more violence or killing.
In that case,
we will have to part ways now.
Master Yang.
Do not think you are indebted to me.
I only did my duty as a vassal of the Yeon Family.
I will no longer live for your sake now that you have changed like this.
Let us go our own ways tomorrow morning.
Master Yang.
This is a treasure as valuable as my life that I inherited from my late father.
I will leave this here.
Make sure to...
keep your promise.
Master Yang?
Master Yang, are we parting ways with Kyera like this?
You are really too harsh!
Ha Rang, go and bring Wind Knife from the western valley.
Right now.
Yes.
Master Yang.
Please be careful.
It would be great if I could read Ak Hee's mind.
Do not waste your energy, Sajo Hyun.
You are making me feel worse.
I can read it.
I can read Ak Hee's memory.
I will take your life today.
You seem fake for some reason- I am sorry.
Please take care, Your Majesty.
Master Yang?
Master Yang, what is the matter?
- Master Yang.
- Your Majesty.
Have you forgotten...
the promise you made to me?
Can you give me a chance, please?
Can you watch me take care of the wicked doings of the previous king
and build a country where the despaired people live with hope yet again?
Kill me with this sword.
- Your Majesty-
- If I do not keep my promise or
if I follow the previous king's footsteps,
do not hesitate to kill me with this sword, then.
- That is-
- It has to be you, Yang Jae Yi.
It has to be you and
no one else who will slash my neck.
What promise did I make to you? Tell me.
You told me to strike you with this sword if you go down the wrong path.
You are going down the wrong path right now, Your Majesty.
- Shut up, Master Yang!
- Officer Ji!
You only loved Lady Yeon Wol, Your Majesty.
Lady Yeon Wol offered her everything for your sake.
Please realize this fact and
do not let the Queen and Sajo Yoong deceive you.
- Master Yang!
Your Majesty, it is dangerous.
Please escape!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
Please protect Lady Yeon Wol!
You are the only one for My Lady!
Your Majesty!
Master Yang!
Do not come. Kyera!
Master Yang.
Please do not move.
Lady Yeon Wol,
I am sorry I could not do as you wished.
Please...
Master Yang.
Master Yang, Master Yang!
Master Yang!
A fake is fake forever. As expected, there is no sincerity.
You seem fake for some reason.
I know you like me, Kyera.
I clearly felt it.
That must be because I thought you were His Majesty, Sir Ak Hee.
- I am sorry.
- That is not true.
T-That cannot be.
Ak Hee, perform geuminsal on Sajo Hyun.
Would this not be what you call the best trade, Your Majesty?
Ak Hee.
He was lying.
Yeon Wol, Yeon Wol!
♫ Because I was always you ♫
♫ And you were always me ♫
♫ I see, hear, and feel you from anywhere ♫
♫ The place where you are, even if it'll only be a moment ♫
♫ Please take me anywhere ♫
[Love Song for Illusion]
We were never meant to be.
I must not look into my mind carelessly.
Who is it?
The father of the baby in your womb.
What you think is right, Grand Prince.
My memories came back.
Do whatever it takes and get rid of Sajo Hyun.
I am going to read all of Ak Hee's memories while I am here.
I will put the seal on this after I confirm Sajo Hyun is gone.
What did you do to His Majesty?
What did you do?
I am sorry, Kyera.