[Park Ji Hoon]
[Hong Ye Ji]
[Hwang Hee]
[Ji Woo]
[Love Song for Illusion]
[Characters, places, organizations, and incidents in this drama are fictitious and have no connection to historical facts. The scenes with animals were in compliance with the production guidelines.]
I am sorry.
Consort Hyo.
Did you make me lose my memories?
Why?
Was it revenge for trying to kill your father?
Is that why you still took me in, knowing I am an assassin?
That man is not the Crown Prince!
He is the evil spirit!
Or did you do it because you are an evil spirit?
Is something wrong?
You look sad.
It is fine if nothing is wrong.
Your Highness.
I will do as you said.
I will stay here longer until my memories come back.
A crown prince possessed an evil spirit.
Were you punished?
Were you the one who was punished by the heavens
for the massacre of my family?
Father!
You are now this country's only royal descendant.
Please survive and plan for the future.
Father.
Mother.
[Episode 4]
Why do I feel so uneasy?
I have a terrible feeling.
I am sure bonghamsal worked successfully.
Dear heavens, hear my prayer.
Hear my prayer.
[Ak Hee]
Is it still not over?
- B-Be-
- What?
Be respectful!
[Ak Hee]
Gosh, no way. I am sure it worked.
Yes.
What the heck? Is it Eunuch Neung?
Chung Ta?
If bonghamsal worked successfully,
he should have turned back into Crown Prince Sajo Hyun.
- Eunuch Neung.
- Your Highness?
You have come back, Your Highness!
How dare you come in here when you should be at the laundry!
T-This humble one only...
c-came to get my stuff.
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
Kyera, pull yourself together.
Get your revenge, no matter what.
Bring more alcohol.
I told you to bring more-
You are...
Yeon Poong Hak's wife.
Are you happy?
You massacred your best friend's family and
live a life of debauchery in the people's blood.
Are you happy now?
Unable to see an inch into the future,
do you feel you own the world?
H-Hear ye, is anyone there?
You are worse than a beast.
All the resentful spirits who died will take your life tonight.
Fall into hell, Sajo Seung!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
You wretched wench!
W-Why do you keep harassing me?
Why are you still roaming this world?
Your Majesty, did you have another nightmare?
It is me, Consort Cheong Myeong, Your-
Your Majesty!
Get the physician here right now!
It was a dream, Your Majesty.
It was all but a dream, Your Majesty.
Alcohol.
Bring me alcohol.
Your Majesty, it is already deep into the night.
Your Majesty, I will give you needle treatment, so rest-
Bring me alcohol! Alcohol!
Bring me alcohol! Bring me alcohol.
Your Majesty!
Bring me alcohol!
Set up the table and alcohol! What are you all doing?
Your Majesty.
I am in so much pain!
Your Majesty, I told them to set up the table and alcohol, so please wait a moment.
You will be at ease soon.
Hurry up and get to it, all of you!
You are the only one who cares about me, Yoong.
Right, Your Majesty? Grand Prince Yoong is the only one who cares.
Grand Prince Yoong is standing guard in the room next to us every night.
He is worried something will happen to you, Your Majesty...
Grand Prince, what is the matter?
It is nothing.
Ha Rang.
Master Yang.
You forgot this.
I failed my mission and even lost my memories.
I am too ashamed to face them.
I will succeed no matter what.
Even if it means I will be back as a corpse,
I will kill Sajo Seung this time, for sure.
Consort Hyo, you are prettier than you were at the installation ceremony.
The Crown Prince must be treating you so well.
Yes, Consort Hyo's face is pretty like crepe myrtle flowers.
I am eternally thankful.
I cannot believe he was a son of a concubine.
Why did he sponsor a group of assassins when he is the king's son?
Is it his resentment as a bastard child?
You did not even show your face last night.
It must not matter to you whether your father dies or lives.
- I am sorry-
- Your Majesty,
The Crown Prince had fallen weak last night-
Forget it!
What use are you as a man when you are so fragile?
You can all leave now since you greeted me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, are you feeling the pain here by chance?
From here to all the way here,
it feels like I am being stabbed by a knife.
If so, you should try pressing those spots in pain like this.
Consort Hyo, you are being rude.
How dare you speak up.
Your Highness Consort Cheong Myeong, will you help?
Consort Hyo, do it yourself.
Do you not hear me?
Consort Hyo, come over here and do it yourself.
See? It must be giving him more pain.
Come out here, Consort Hyo.
Consort Hyo!
Just endure it a bit longer, Your Majesty.
How do you feel, Your Majesty?
My goodness. Bring the physician right now-
How odd.
The pain is gone as if it was washed away.
Consort Hyo, did you study medicine?
I heard Consort Hyo has been studying medicine in her spare time
due to her vast interest since she was young.
Really? My goodness.
The skills you have studied in your spare time are better than those of the royal physician.
Our Royal Family gained a great physician, huh.
How amazing.
Crown Prince, have I had a vast interest in medicine when I was young?
I would not know that.
Since you do not remember,
I had no choice but to concoct a story.
I see.
- Thank you.
- I am the thankful one.
I scored some points from His Majesty, thanks to you.
Well, I guess the Crown Princess was displeased.
Is he the evil spirit or the Crown Prince?
By the way, what have you been pondering about since last night?
Wondering if I am the evil spirit or not?
Yes, Eunuch Neung told me that your personality changes whenever you sleep.
Well, then.
Who do you think is standing in front of you, Consort Hyo?
Not sure.
I do not know which one is the evil spirit,
but I noticed your temperatures are different.
Temperatures, huh?
One day, you are as cold as ice, and
another day, extremely hot.
In that case,
what about now?
Right now,
you are neither hot nor cold.
Really?
Interesting.
Whomever you may be, I will not forgive you.
If you are the evil spirit, I cannot forgive you for erasing my memories.
If you are the Crown Prince,
I cannot forgive you since you are my enemy's son.
Hong Gun, are you okay?
Aigoo, aigoo, stand up.
Do you think you can get up?
My goodness...
I am deeply sorry, Your Highness Consort Hyo.
I was rushing because of an urgent matter.
Not at all. It is okay.
- Grand Prince.
- Yes, Your Highness.
Never mind.
Kyera, do you have something to tell me?
All right, then.
Your Highness?
Sajo Yoong, you tried to kill me.
Why did he try to kill me?
Because I might cause harm to Wind Knife?
Be careful. Someone will come to kill you.
Did Master Yang agree to this?
Or did he do it without Master Yang knowing?
Or...
did Master Yang have a change of heart?
Young Lady Wol!
Who am I supposed to trust here?
Who is it?
Why did you come so late? I told you to tell me quickly!
So, how did bonghamsal turn out?
D-Did it succeed? It worked, right?
It did not work?
D-Damn it!
I need to run away! I need to run!
Do not tell him you saw me.
A-Aigoo, Sir Ak Hee!
Congratulations!
Congratulations on the success of bonghamsal!
Why are you shaking so much when you are happy for me?
W-Well, I was too happy to see you in good health.
I am shaking from the joy, and it is making me dance.
By the way, you are not Ak Hee, right?
You know you are not.
You are not him! Hurray, it worked!
It worked!
Hurray!
How dare you lie to me!
You dared to lock me up by plotting with Ak Hee?
N-No, Ak Hee-
That is absolutely not the case!
Can you not see how you came back?
I did everything in my power to bring you back!
Come on, talk. You should have let me know sooner!
I did not even know and was worried about bonghamsal.
I could not even sleep a bite or eat a wink!
All I could do was think about you, Your Highness.
Gosh, I freaked out at first, too.
Your Highness? You are the real crown prince, right?
Your Highness, why must you trick me like this?
Hate you...
I told him not to tell you.
Since you released me, I reckoned you can lock me up again at will.
So I have been watching you quietly.
O-Oh, I see. Lock you up again?
I can never do that.
No one can escape bonghamsal once they are locked up.
- Chung Ta.
- Yes.
Why did Ak Hee erase Consort Hyo's memories?
The thing is, I-I do not really know-
He erased Consort Hyo's memories with the sleeping incense you provided!
O-Oh, probably...
From what I assume,
Ak Hee had a crush on Consort Hyo.
So he erased her memories and made it look like they were in a passionate relationship.
There is something more than that. Spill it.
I do not really know more than that, either.
Even so, you erased that woman's memories.
Why on Earth did you do that, Ak Hee?
What can I do, then?
If I left her memories intact, she would never be together with me.
Just think about it! How can you love your sworn enemy's son?
But still! How can you defy fate like that!
Whatever. It could not be helped.
Anyhow, this is a secret only between you and me.
So, just try talking about it somewhere. Your life as a shaman will be over.
Mark my words.
I cannot tell you.
- You know what it is. Speak!
- I cannot tell you.
What did you say? Tell me.
- Spill it!
- I cannot tell you!
Huh?
What is this?
Chung Ta is using a cheap trick.
Hey, you!
Are you showing off just because you are a famous shaman?
W-Whoa-
Chung Ta?
Crown Prince, stay away from Her Highness Consort Hyo.
Let her leave.
Otherwise, your life will be in peril.
Please remember my words.
What on Earth...
Do you think this is true, Your Highness?
M-My goodness.
Your Highness, why would Chung Ta tell you to make Her Highness leave you?
Right, could it be because she has become close to Ak Hee already?
Was Consort Hyo that close to Ak Hee?
Well, Ak Hee was really quite good to Consort Hyo.
He had honey falling out of his eyes when he looked at her.
Well, then.
Did Consort Hyo like him, too?
Probably so?
I am sure Ak Hee was pretending to be you, wandering everywhere,
and fell in love at first sight when he saw Her Highness!
With your good looks as a weapon,
I am sure he made all the moves he can.
Gosh, that wicked Ak Hee!
- Eunuch Neung!
- Yes, Your Highness.
Even though Ak Hee is an evil spirit,
he had once resided in my body.
It bothers me to hear you badmouth him every time.
Aigoo, Your Highness, I apologize.
Let us go.
My big mouth. My big mouth. My big mouth.
I need to pick my words carefully!
Your Highness!
Ji Jeon!
You know I cannot get on by myself!
Consort Hyo, were you really Ak Hee's woman?
Have you returned to being a cowardly nerd?
Were you looking manly only because of your madness?
I will change.
I am going to be better than Ak Hee.
Your Majesty, though we fortified our guard,
the theft and arson by the poor are endless.
Strengthening the border is only a makeshift solution.
I reckon the wise solution is to provide additional rice for free to the poor who are causing trouble.
That is also only a makeshift solution!
Your Majesty, you cannot console your people who turned into rioters due to poverty
merely by providing free rice.
I think teaching how to make a bowl of rice is wiser than giving a bowl of rice.
Therefore, please punish the criminals by sentencing them
to working the barren lands instead of beatings.
If allowed to take 80% of whatever they make
on those barren lands, they will not commit
anymore theft or arson, even if someone were to beg them to do so.
Your Majesty, working the barren lands-
Head Minister!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Do as the Crown Prince said.
Today's assembly is over now.
Crown Prince.
What is the occasion?
Is it wrong for the crown prince to attend the assembly?
It is because you have not attended so far.
In that case, do you plan to keep attending the assembly?
If you do, I will have your spot prepared from now on-
Your question itself is wrong, Grand Prince.
An assembly is supposed to be led by His Majesty and myself, the Crown Prince.
Am I supposed to get permission from you?
Sajo Hyun!
How dare you, you half-witted nerd!
No way!
No way.
There must be a way.
A way.
The path to this location is in bad condition.
- Therefore...
- Yes.
Sajo Yoong, a secret army, too?
Stay away from Her Highness Consort Hyo.
Let her leave.
Otherwise, your life will be in peril.
Did you go for a walk?
Yes, I felt a bit stuffy in here.
You must be.
Since you are confined in the palace all day.
There is no need to feel confined anymore.
Leave the palace.
I told you I will not leave.
Why?
I want to stay by your side.
I might be the evil spirit.
If you are, you would try to make me stay.
- How come?
- Because the evil spirit is the fake one.
His greed would best his morals.
His greed, huh?
Are you talking about his greed for wanting to have you by his side?
I would say it is closer to lust than greed.
Are you also being shaken by the evil spirit's lust?
- Are you that starved for affection?
- Your words are too much, Your Highness.
Leave at once. I do not wish to see you anymore.
I cannot do so.
I am a concubine who has been officially installed.
If you really want me to leave,
please kick me out harshly yourself.
I will keep an eye on you.
I will make sure to watch with my own eyes how you realize
what a trivial creature the evil spirit you have feelings for is.
In the mountains?
Yes.
I heard Consort Hyo spends all day in the mountains.
And she comes back around sunset with dirt all over her.
Why is she doing that?
Who knows?
They said the Crown Prince does not even head toward Consort Hyo's pavilion.
So she must be mad about that, right?
It must be to discipline her mind.
I am back, Your Highness-
Gosh, I said I will do it!
I am almost done.
Why did the Crown Princess want to see you?
Oh, well.
The Crown Princess told you not to go outside starting tomorrow.
She is worried something might happen to you.
Really?
- Are you going to boil this?
- Yes.
N-No, I will do it.
- What do you mean?
- Gosh, it is okay. I can do it-
You have dirt all over your hands, Your Highness!
Do I have to keep fanning?
Consort Hyo's pavilion reeked of medicinal herbs.
It must be the concoction for the Crown Prince.
That was why she was wandering in the mountains.
W-Whoa, what do I do?
Gosh, what is this?
W-What happened?
Y-Your Highness, this is bad!
The concoction was...
What about the concoction? Did it topple or something?
How did you know?
It cannot be helped.
It cannot be helped?
You went through so much to get those medicinal herbs!
These are what you are talking about.
Aigoo, I spent all night preparing them.
Your Highness, did you expect something like this to happen?
Hong Gun, can you deliver this to the Crown Prince?
- Consort Hyo did?
- Yes, Your Highness.
Crown Prince, I will be waiting for you in front of His Majesty's chamber.
You came for me.
When will you be leaving?
When will you kick me out?
I prepared a concoction for His Majesty.
I asked to see you to present it to him together.
You will help me gain His Majesty's favor with a mere medicine?
You are doing anything to catch my attention.
Did I really catch your attention at all?
I am glad, then.
I-I am sorry.
You were that child, huh?
Your Majesty, your body and mind will be at ease if you take this medicine.
Who knows if they will be at ease or
rest in peace forever inside the coffin?
Forgive me, but I will consume it first-
Consort Hyo obtained those herbs from wandering the rough mountains.
If you will not take it, I will take it instead.
You are a fool who is head over heels for Consort Hyo, huh?
I will soon be meeting my grandson.
Are you happy now?
He will soon be meeting his grandson?
Your Majesty, it is a bit uncomfortable, right?
I am at ease.
My headache is also gone, perhaps because of the medicine I just took.
I am glad.
Crown Prince.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Would it be okay if I call over Consort Hyo like this from time to time?
Just as my physician, that is.
Will you be okay?
How could I answer otherwise? Please call for me whenever, Your Majesty.
Consort Hyo is the boss of our Royal Family.
I make a request to the Crown Prince and
the Crown Prince makes a request to Consort Hyo.
So, that would make you the true boss, would it not?
I do not deserve your graceful compliment, Your Majesty.
By the way, Consort Hyo, you look familiar for some reason.
Is that so?
You seem to take after someone a lot.
Someone I know quite well.
Right.
It is that person.
That person I know very well.
My son!
They say a married couple resembles each other.
Your Majesty, Grand Prince Sajo Yoong is here.
Come in!
Your Majesty.
I must have interrupted a lovely time you were having.
I will come back later.
No need to come back. Just cut to the chase and leave.
The Minister of Hunting just notified me
that the northern borders' boars and wolves are headed to the capital.
But it is not time yet.
He said it happened due to a fire at Mt. Baekhwa on the northern border.
I am reporting because they will pass our capital's mountains by dawn tomorrow.
Really?
We need to go out to hunt, then!
Yes, I will make the preparations, Your Majesty.
You should also join us, Crown Prince.
You showed a great performance at the last hunt, too.
The Crown Prince can stay.
He does not even seem to be in his mad state.
- Yes, that will be for the better-
- I will be attending as well.
Crown Prince, please do not overexert yourself.
I am so thankful you care for me so dearly, Hyungnim.
I will try overexerting my half-witted self at the hunt again this time.
So please give me a hand.
W-Wait, that one stung a bit.
Gosh, I am sorry.
No, no, it is okay.
I told them not to let anyone in.
Why do you only practice indoors?
Now that you got complimented by His Majesty,
do my words sound like a joke to you?
I apologize.
I do not like hearing the slashing sound of the winds.
When I am outside, that sound is too clear.
The sound of the arrow ripping the wind apart.
What are you going to do about tomorrow's hunt, then?
Not sure. Perhaps the evil spirit will help me.
The wind is just a wind.
Wherever you are, try lingering around yourself and yourself only.
Do not avert and look straight on.
The sound of the wind ripping apart will disappear.
Is your mind a bit more at ease now?
When will you leave?
As long as you are here, my mind will always be disturbed.
I feel like I could fly since I am on the hunt with my son after such a long time.
I feel the same way, Your Majesty.
There is a red boar at the western boulder!
All right, let us go!
The wind is...
just a wind.
Wherever you are, try lingering around yourself and yourself only.
Do not avert and look straight on.
The sound of the wind ripping apart will disappear.
Stop, stop!
He is down.
The Crown Prince has hunted down the boar!
Do not do this, Grand Prince. Grand Prince!
The Crown Prince has finally succeeded, huh?
Where is it?
Your Majesty, it seems the Crown Prince was too startled.
Grand Prince Yoong hunted the boar. It was not me.
Your Majesty!
I only helped a little bit because the Crown Prince almost had it.
Your Majesty.
I will pierce your forehead next time
if you mock my son again.
I am sorry, Your Majesty.
Half-wit...
Just like you,
I am also ashamed of you.
You will have to lead Asatae after me.
But what the hell is all this!
You cannot. This one is for Mother.
I am going to give it to Mother!
More than three months passed since your mother died.
Yet you have not come to your senses!
It was supposed to be for Mother.
I was going to give it to her on her birthday.
Get off me!
I know why you ordered Mother to die by poison.
It is not because Mother envied Yoong hyung's mother.
What did you say?
It is because she always said the right things to you.
You could not endure Mother's honest opinions.
So you...
What about me?
Go on.
What about your father?
Go on and say it.
What about me? Huh?
Go on and say it before I rip your mouth apart.
- Say it!
- I am ashamed...
of you, Father.
All right, let us take a shot.
Gosh! Come on now!
Aigoo, seriously!
What are you doing here?
I was passing by, and the crepe myrtle flowers were too beautiful.
I did not know there were crepe myrtle trees here, too.
All right, then.
You can stay...
for a moment if you want.
Today is the date my mother passed away.
I did not know.
No one knows.
No one is supposed to remember.
You should not...
have done it.
You massacred General Yeon Poong Hak,
your best friend, and his family.
Including his young daughter, too.
Shut your mouth!
You wicked wench.
What are you all doing? Make her drink more of the poison!
M-Mother!
Mother!
Mother, Mother!
How was the hunt today?
Square one.
Everything is completely back to square one.
I guess the evil spirit did not help you.
The evil spirit is no more.
A shaman called Chung Ta sealed him away.
You do not have to believe me.
You can resent me.
Technically, it is my fault you ended up here.
The evil spirit inside my body had feelings for you
and made you live at the palace.
If what you said is true,
how could it be your fault?
Because the evil spirit possessed me due to my fault in the first place.
Because I am a half-wit.
I told you I only use the indoor archery field
because I hate to hear the sound of the wind slashing, right?
Whenever I hear that sound, I am reminded of that day.
That house I saw when I was young.
The site of the massacre.
The swords ripping through the air,
the screams,
and the dead bodies.
The young girl who was there.
I am sure she died.
I could not save her.
Just like how I could not save my mother.
Her eyes are still vivid in my mind.
Even more so when I hear the slashing of the wind.
That is why I was punished by the heavens.
That is why.
That is why an evil spirit possessed me.
This man remembers that day.
That day has become a deep wound for him, just like me.
♫ Because I was always here, and you were always there ♫
♫ Please take me anywhere, a place, go away ♫
♫ Please hold me so I do not waver, I am tired ♫
♫ Please hug me so I can relax ♫
♫ Because I was here ♫
Be careful, Your Majesty.
I will call over a court lady.
Forget it!
My Yoong is taking care of me so well,
so, who else would I need?
I do not know what to say, Your Majesty.
Now, then. This humble one will do it for you.
Yoong!
Yes, Your Majesty.
You are a really reliable fellow.
I am thankful.
Be satisfied with what you have now.
Pardon?
I am telling you not to overtake my son.
Your Majesty...
You know very well that my bastard children are all over this country.
A bastard child is only a bastard child.
Sajo Hyun, the heir, is my only real son.
You said we should have
been switched, did you not?
You said I should have been the heir.
That I should have been the crown prince. Did you not say so?
You mean, you actually believed that?
How could you not know I was only trying to provoke my son?
That is so unfair, Father.
How much more effort and hard work
must I display for you to consider me your son?
Poor thing.
Why do you keep pretending to forget the fact you and I both know?
You are not even my real son.
Did you think I did not know?
I took you in and made you a grand prince when you are not even my blood.
I believe I have done enough as well.
Do you not think so?
I must sleep now!
Consort Hyo takes such a good care of me,
so I get good sleep, and my mind is at ease.
I told His Majesty that Yoong is his son.
He took me while knowing you are my husband,
so he just went along with it.
Good job. That way, it is beneficial for all of us.
You became prettier since becoming a concubine.
Aigoo, what is with you?
What if Yoong sees us?
You said Yoong went to play by the stream.
Do not be like that and come over here.
Grow more mustache. You look just like Yoong.
Okay, I will.
Hold on a moment.
How could this be...
She is Ak Hee's woman.
But Ak Hee is gone now.
Consort Hyo, I gave it a lot of thought.
No matter what I think, kicking you out harshly is against the rules of the Inner Court.
If you wish, you may stay here.
Stay by my side, Consort Hyo.
- Stay by-
- Your Highness!
Her Highness the Crown Princess is here-
What is the matter, Crown Princess?
Your Highness, do you know Consort Hyo's true identity?
What identity?
I heard Consort Hyo is the only daughter of General Yeon Poong Hak, who was executed 10 years ago
for plotting a rebellion, Yeon Wol.
Wait, where did you hear such nonsense?
Consort Hyo is sure to possess this dagger.
Search Consort Hyo's pavilion right this moment
and interrogate her strictly.
Calm down first, Crown Princess.
I will take care of this matter.
So, keep quiet about it for now. I ask of you.
However, she might harm His Majesty in the meantime.
Where is Consort Hyo right now?
Thanks to you, I sleep very well these days.
I do not even have nightmares.
I am glad, Your Majesty.
I do not even let the Royal Physician take care of me this comfortably.
Ak Hee is the only one who knows whether Consort Hyo is an assassin.
Ak Hee is the only one who knows what happened that day in His Majesty's bathroom.
Ak Hee, is that why you erased Consort Hyo's memories?
Did he know everything all along, then?
I am sorry.
Your Highness, there is something I must tell you.
I will do as you said.
I will leave.
Leave?
You said you will stay in the palace until I kick you out.
I did.
However, there is something I told you way before that.
That I will leave once my memories come back.
My memories...
came back.
When did your memories come back?
Not too long ago.
You hid it even after your memories came back?
You knew who you are,
but you kept it hidden from me?
In that case,
were you not sincere that day?
That day was...
Is your name Yeon Wol?
Will you say you do not know that name?
Even after your memories came back?
Did you already know who I am?
Are you really...
an assassin who came in to kill His Majesty?
Tell me.
Right now.
Yes.
Did you also keep quiet about getting your memories back
for the purpose of killing His Majesty?
Tell me it is not true.
Say it is not true.
You deceived me.
But I showed my sincerity.
Why?
Your Highness!
Your Highness, there is a terrible incident.
His Majesty has...
His Majesty...
Your Majesty.
Father.
Father!
Father, Father.
Father! Father...
Father...
Father!
How...
How could you...
How could you!
I did not do it.
[Love Song for Illusion]
♫ Never lost, I will never lose you ♫
♫ Within the darkness, open the door and look at my inner self ♫
♫ Never lost, when this darkness ends ♫
I cannot...
I cannot ever forgive you.
Who could have killed the king?
- I do not fear dying.
- Your Majesty!
I am only sad you are mistaken about me.
Sajo Hyun, you will take your own life tonight.
The Crown Prince hung himself out of severe sadness.
Sajo Hyun!
The Crown Prince has ordered the execution of the guilty.
Father, Mother.
Your daughter is coming to meet you soon.