(Mu Yinan,)
(Regret Inn)
(do you think)
(love will disappear
all of a sudden?)
♪Watching the scenery unfold♪
♪The changes feel like a sign♪
♪That we'll get separated in the crowd♪
♪Chance of love is fleeting♪
♪We brush past each other
and miss the chance♪
♪When I came to,
I realize the loneliness♪
♪Our moments are so memorable♪
♪Every little detail of the memory♪
♪Is written down♪
♪Yet somehow I hear♪
♪Regret singing a song♪
(Adapted from "Love Story of Yinan
And Xiangbei" by Sunbright Publishing House)
=Xiangbei Regret=
=Episode 13=
Stop it,
both of you!
Are you insane?
You actually hit me,
Mu Yinan.
We both need to calm down.
I don't want to see you
stuck in guilt over Xiangbei
and unable to move forward.
Look at yourself.
Are you still
the same man you used to be?
I barely recognize you anymore.
Let me say it one more time,
Mo Xiangbei
left us.
She's the one who left us!
Mu Yinan...
Yinan.
Yinan,
Mo Sang is right.
I know what I'm doing.
I don't need anyone else
making a big deal out of it.
What about me?
♪Where should I begin♪
Cherish the one
who really cares for you.
Mo Sang is a good match for you.
♪To sort through the past♪
Mu Yinan, you're a jerk!
♪I don't know how to start writing♪
♪To record our stories♪
♪And trace the marks we've left behind♪
♪The words I've spoken♪
♪Still haven't reached your heart♪
♪I don't have the courage
to say I miss you♪
♪It's just a mess of memories♪
♪Occupying every nerve♪
♪Numbing every word♪
♪I can't bring myself
to put it down in writing♪
♪Because every word connects♪
♪To my heart♪
♪ I write and erase, over and over♪
♪Turns out I was thinking of you again♪
Don't leave me.
Wanqing,
are you okay?
Let's have lunch.
Come on.
Lele,
the food is ready.
Go call Xiangbei.
Lele?
Cheer up,
or Xiangbei
will feel bad.
Okay.
Go and tell Xiangbei food is ready.
Xiangbei?
Xiangbei, I'm coming in.
Xiangbei!
Xiangbei?
Xiangbei,
why are you sitting here
when you're supposed
to rest in bed?
You might catch a cold!
Xiangbei,
let's go downstairs for dinner.
You know,
Li Munan made
your favorite tomato and egg noodles!
He wouldn't even make it for me,
no matter how much I begged him before.
Come eat with us.
You guys go ahead.
I'm not that hungry,
and I just don't feel like moving.
Xiangbei,
come on,
let's go eat together.
You've been
getting lazier lately.
Come on, please.
Come on, Xiangbei.
Here.
Put this on.
Come.
Let's eat.
Xiangbei,
come on.
Come.
Faster.
Let's eat.
Easy.
Xiangbei,
sit.
Li Munan, hurry up!
Xiangbei's here!
Serve the food!
Coming!
Where is Xixi?
Xixi?
He's probably resting upstairs.
When I went upstairs to find you,
he was there.
Here it is!
Piping hot
tomato and egg noodles.
Come on, eat up.
What are you staring at?
Yours is still in the pot.
Go serve yourself.
Xiangbei,
look at him!
Li Munan
is bullying me again!
Li Munan,
stop picking on Lele.
That's right.
Listen up, Li Munan.
You'd better do as Xiangbei says,
or
one day
I'll get her
to kick you out.
(Regret Inn)
Who's bullying you?
Xiangbei,
you're spoiling her.
Lele's just a kid.
Li Munan,
I could hear you talking bad about me
in the kitchen.
No, I didn't.
You're denying it?
When I was in the kitchen,
I clearly heard you bad-mouthing me
to Xiangbei!
Alright then,
what exactly did I say?
You...
You did it on purpose!
Every time,
you...
You're framing me.
You always make me get my own food.
You always...
Stop, stop.
Let's just eat.
Dig in.
Does it smell good?
Yes.
Tasty, right?
(Regret Inn)
My tomato and egg noodles
are the best in the world.
♪Time keeps pushing me forward♪
♪To let go of the lingering warmth
of memories♪
♪How hard it is, in a world without you♪
♪What's left for me♪
♪Drifting in memories♪
♪Only to rediscover♪
♪The galaxy in my eyes♪
♪Filled with regrets♪
♪Returning is fate's
inevitable consequence♪
♪Watching the scenery unfold♪
♪The changes feel like a sign♪
♪That we'll get separated in the crowd♪
♪Chance of love is fleeting♪
♪We brush past each other
and miss the chance♪
♪When I came to,
I realize the loneliness♪
♪Our moments are so memorable♪
♪Every little detail of the memory♪
♪Is written down♪
♪Yet somehow I hear♪
♪Regret singing a song♪