XIN cheek
Wake up
The process is too easy
Take the time to grow up
Wake up
Dad
Son
How is your life?
Are you used to it?
OK
Dad
What's up?
Nothing
Today, all three of your aunts
Come to eat at home
I heard you got into financial college
They are all happy for you
Dad is really proud
What did dad say?
You have to learn financial
Do you have to go out to learn financial?
What kind of music did you take before?
What can you do in the future?
Dad
What else?
If there is nothing
I hang up now
I have to go to the library
OK OK OK
Son, you read it carefully
You have to learn it
Grow up
One more
You are drunk, mom
Sister An
You are the best
Why do you drink so much?
I am in a bad mood
Dad
Are you OK?
I am OK
Slow down
How old are you?
Take care of your health
How is it?
I just fell asleep after a long night
How much did Xiao Chen drink yesterday?
Not much
Just four or five bottles
Four or five bottles
He shouldn't
Yes, he drank less than me
I have been tossing and turning all night
I'll sleep for a while
Don't look
You are in the room
Oh my god
Why is there no sound when you walk?
You scared me
You are not guilty
What are you afraid of?
Are you free?
Why do you keep staring at me?
Boring
You came from the inner prison
What are you doing?
You guess
I am too lazy to guess
I can't guess
Teacher
Can you tell me
the story of Chen Haoyu and Wu Wen?
Wu Wen
How do you know about Wu Wen?
Chen Haoyu told me
What did he tell you?
He didn't say anything
He said
Wu Wen is handsome
Wu Wen is a musician
and he always teaches him to write and sing
Do you want to know more?
What else do you want to know?
I want to know
what happened between them
What do you want to do?
Maybe I can help Chen Haoyu
It's been a long time
since anyone came here
This used to be
Wu Wen's studio
It's where he worked
To be precise
Wu Wen is a musician
He created a lot of songs here
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Why did he leave?
I told you
He left without saying goodbye
What about Chen Haoyu?
What happened between them?
Chen Haoyu
was brought back by Wu Wen
He was picked up
Picked up?
by Wu Wen
Yes
When Chen Haoyu was in college
he always sang on the underground tunnel
Wu Wen met him several times
and found he had no place to live
so he brought him back
Slowly
Wu Wen found Chen Haoyu
was talented in music
so he taught him to write songs
sing and compose
At that time
we knew
Chen Haoyu wanted to study music
but his family didn't allow him
Later
Chen Haoyu wrote some songs
Although it wasn't that good
it was much better
than the current songs
Since Wu Wen left
he became confused
I knew he wouldn't go to school
but I didn't expose him
I knew you wouldn't say it
I didn't know what to say
what to say
What if I made him angry again?
Right?
After Wu Wen left
Chen Haoyu stopped playing the piano
and singing
and writing songs
I knew it
You stopped writing songs?
Zheng
Can I come here often?
You can come during the day
when everyone is at work
The point is
when Susan is not here
Okay
I'm sorry
How did you know this song?
Is it good?
Are you familiar with it?
This is the song you wrote, right?
It's really good
But there's no lyrics, right?
I'm asking you
How did you know this song?
Aren't you curious
what I found in my room?
There's a Chen Haoyu's folder in this USB drive
You wrote all the songs in it, right?
It's really good
But I like this song the most
To be honest
your writing is really good
If you can write like this in every song
I think
you can be a professional musician
But Chen Haoyu
Do we need to add a lyric to this song?
Or we can form a band
There's a special band now
called Phoenix Legend
We're called Dragon Phoenix Legend
How about it?
You write the lyrics
I add the lyrics
We can definitely win
Chen Haoyu
I found the USB drive
You can record it
This song is good
Can you record it?
Master
I haven't written the lyrics yet
No need to write the lyrics
Just sing
Here
I'll start with the project
OK
Recording
耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶耶
well
a man man no son ca wrong
The truth is hidden in the old USB
The pace of the game is slower
The game is not about the suspense
The answer is in the darkness
The suspicious person
I can turn the plot upside down
The mystery appears again
The mysterious person
Whose body
Whose finger
Open the door to you when the wind and rain stop
Whose eyes
Whose turn
The road ahead makes me deeper and deeper
The end of the blurry will