YoYo English Channel YouTube
Wake up
The process is like
a world of
Sister An
Why are you back now?
Zheng hasn't eaten for a day
I brought him some food
I think I smell love
Don't talk nonsense
What are you going to do
in this dress?
Go to work
Go to work?
In this dress?
Zheng
You haven't eaten for a day
Come and eat
Don't starve
Let it go
I can't eat
You have to eat even if you can't
Hurry up
Don't think too much
It's good to be like this now
As for me
As long as the child is good
It's better than anything
You said
It's okay not to see
I saw it
It's more like my daughter
She's not with me
You said
If she met a bad person abroad
What if she learned badly?
Yang Zheng
Do you know what Su Diya
has been busy with recently?
I don't know
What's wrong?
I saw her dress like that
She went out to work
What kind of dress?
Like that
Young people love beauty
Is there anything wrong?
But one night
It's dark
She dressed like that and went out
Don't you think it's weird?
You're worried about her
What if she's in danger?
That's what I'm worried about
Did she really learn badly?
Come on, cheers
Mr. Liu, have a bite
Mr. Chen, have one too
And mine
Of course
Thank you
Susan, you're wrong
Mr. Liu has dried the wine
Do you have to drink it too?
Cheers
I can't drink anymore
Brother, what kind of person is she?
Who?
Susan
She
She's beautiful
She's a little straight
But she's nice
She's very handsome
She wants to be the best female archer in China
She can give up everything for her dream
She's good at drinking
She can't even hold two cows
Master
Can't you hold two cows?
I can't
Come and see me
It's too lively
I don't have time for that
It's hot
You're good at drinking
If you drink like this
You'll get sick
It's all Jin Zhu's dad
He has to be with her
That arrogant man
He gave up everything for his dream
And he's already bowing to Jin Zhu's dad
Don't be so over-reacting
I can't afford to drink
If I can't afford to drink, I won't have a job
Where can I get money if I don't have a job?
Money, money, money
I only know money
Where's your dream?
Thank you, dad
I'll pay you back
No, I have to be the best archer in China
I'm leaving
Dream
Dream is a dream
You have another choice
Come on
Mr. Chen
To you
Tonight
Mr. Liu, to you too
I'm leaving
Xiaosu
You're back so late
Anjie
Why are you still awake?
I
I'll pour a glass of water
Pour water
A smell of smoke and alcohol
Is it really blood?
Xiaosu
You're finally awake
Anjie
Aren't you going to work today?
I took a day off today
By the way, I cleaned up the house
Xiaosu
You're back so late recently
Get off work
Then you'll be back tonight
Is it safe?
Is there anyone to see you off?
It's just at the intersection
It's very close
Bar
I'll go to the bar
What are you doing in the bar?
Why are you back so late?
Singing
Only singing?
I drink sometimes
Then will you
Go out
Go out to drink with the guests
I won't, Anjie
I mainly sing
But sometimes the guests are happy
I'll drink more
Then you make a lot of money
Yes
If the guests are happy
I'll give them more money
Yesterday, I had a good time
Yesterday, the guests were very generous
I made a lot of money
Anjie
What's wrong with you?
Do you want to get back to work?
No
No, I mean
Do you want to change jobs?
Me?
You come back so late every day
Stay up late
It's okay, Anjie
I like singing
I like this job
Beidiao
Yes, Beidiao
You have to know every guest
You
You have lived here for so long
I know you
You mean
We know each other in Jianshan?
I didn't say that
You mean Su?
Be quiet
What about Su?
He goes out every night
with a lot of makeup
He comes back when the sun is about to rise
He comes back
He drinks so much
and goes to bed early
He wants to wake up in the afternoon
He drinks so much every day
And just now
He said he was singing in the bar
He sings in the bar
He has a little bit of smoke
It's normal to drink
He doesn't only sing
He also drinks
Guests give him money
Think about it
Why did he give him money for nothing?
He also said
A few days ago
A guest was excited
and gave him a lot of money
No, you
What do you mean?
Zheng
If Sudia is your daughter
She is now
with someone who is not clear
and not good
Are you at ease?
If she is my daughter, I
What should we do?
We have to think of a way
to help her
Come
Look
She is out
like this
Can it be assured?
It's true that it can't be assured
But
Before we investigate it
We can't talk nonsense
If it's out
It will affect the little girl
When can we investigate it?
I'll let people go to the bar
and see
Then we will know
Okay
Come, drink
Come, buy it
Buy it
Brother
Drink
Happy
Come
Cheers
Susan
You are not in a good state today
But this wine
We can't waste it
Come, buy it
Mr. Chen
Come
I really can't drink
Mr. Chen
Bosses
I am Susan's good friend
Welcome to our bar
Today
I will drink with you
Okay
Come
Sit
Susan's friend
is also my friend
Can we drink a few glasses?
Come, boss
Cheers
Come
Susan
Drink
We all drank
You are not missing
Are you here to harm me?
This sister is happy
Come
Let's drink another one
Susan
I like you so much
This sister
Good character
I like you like this
Come, cheers
Brother
You are a big business person
You must take good care of me
This sister
Sister
Don't worry
We will take care of each other
Take good care of each other
Brother looks like a happy person
In this case
Let's do another happy one
Slow down
This sister
No matter how good the singing is
The alcohol content is still so high
As long as the boss is happy
Sister Susan
Are you here today
To sign a contract with brother?
It's a good thing
Brother
Sign this contract
I will accompany you to have a happy one
As long as we are happy
We sign the contract
We are all happy
Brother
Just because of your words
I am happy
Good
So good
Little sister
What are you doing?
Brother
I go to get some wine
Little sister
What are you talking about?
Come to Guo Guo's place to drink
How can you let yourself drink?
Drink ours
Of course we drink our wine
Let you spend money
Come, come, come
Sister
You go to the bathroom to make up
I'll chase after you when I'm late
Isn't it, brother?
Yes, yes, yes
My eyes are really uncomfortable
Then you drink first
Come back quickly
Sister
You sing well
The alcohol content is still good
Drink another cup
Drink one
Come, come, come
Come, drink, drink
What do you think I said?
I just want to give you a littleQuite some
Brother
What do you want me to tell him?
Come
This is the car
I'll take the public transport
Come
When old man kill me
This is the car
Come
I want to give you one
Go
I'm going to turn on the lights tonight
The truth is hidden in the old USB
The rhythm of breathing is slower
The footsteps are slowly moving
The music is not good at showing off
Creation makes me die
The answer is in the dark
Suspicious person
I can see the plot is turning around
The mystery is solved and appears
You ask
Whose body temperature is it?
Whose finger is it?
Open the door of the city wind
Whose eyes are it?
Whose hair is it?
The mystery is solved and appears