=Lost Track of Time=
=Episode 12=
What are you doing here?
Watch out.
Why are you here?
Can't I
pay a visit
without a greeting letter?
Your Highness is joking.
Why do you look like
you are on guard against your archenemy?
Are you
terrified against me?
Is your hand alright?
A small scratch is no big deal.
I appreaciate Your Highness' generosity,
but I don't like owing favors,
especially yours.
The Chinese medical wine smells strong.
Will I
violate Your Highness' taboo?
What taboo?
Never drinks alcohol.
How do you know
I don't drink?
I haven't seen for once.
I am just guessing.
Did I
forget anything?
What does Your Highness mean?
Have we met
before I went to Su City?
Why does Your Highness ask this?
On the day before
the hair-pinning ceremony,
I met Your Highness for the first time.
But your looks tell me
we've met before.
Sis,
Mr. Xu wants to
borrow the books in the study.
I am here to...
Greet Your Highness Princess Qing.
Who is Mr. Xu you mentioned?
He is a talented man
in Su City, even in the southern Su area.
Mr. Xu is great.
So capable.
From the grass roots.
He is suitable
to be a substitute
for Minister Yan's son.
(Winning the first prize,)
(Mr. Xu was used by Mu Ze)
(and assasinated by Prince Yi)
(on the street soon.)
(If he had failed and returned home,)
(he might have been saved.)
(It's never too late)
(to attend the exam after three years.)
(Why not make use of and go with it?)
What?
You don't look like
you are willing to.
I know there is no room
for what Your Highness decides.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
It's a nice present.
Take your maid home
after the exam result is unveiled.
(Mansion of Prince Qing)
Cuicui, stop it.
Okay.
Okay. Slower.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
Leave it to me.
Get out.
Get out of there.
Take care.
Take care, Your Highness.
Take it slow.
Take care.
Look.
Those minions.
How could they be like this?
They don't take
His Highness' birthday seriously.
There can't be someone...
Someone who doesn't care about
his birthday.
Right?
Mom,
today is my birthday.
But it is the date I hate most.
Because there is never a soul
who knows your name.
There will be a day
when I put your name
in the royal ancestral temple.
Let you be enshrined by generations.
What are you doing?
Since Your Highness toils day and night,
I am always afraid that
I can't spare your distress.
And today is your birthday,
I can only
make a bowl of longevity noodles
for you personally.
Wish you live a long life
and all your dreams come true.
You should
stay in your own court.
Don't make efforts
to flatter me.
Your Highness. Your Highness.
It's not for flattering you.
When I was in the Lu Family,
no one cared about my birthday
every year.
The whole family prepared feasts
for Lu Anran.
I felt lost inside,
but I could only say I didn't mind it.
I don't know
why you don't celebrate your birthday.
So, I just put myself in your shoes.
I don't want Your Highness
to feel
a little bit of disappointment.
Even when you are showing your sincerity,
you don't forget to depreciate Lu Anran.
But Princess,
you seem to have a poor memory.
I have reminded you
to behave yourself.
Don't stir things up.
Your Highness,
what we've made has no conclusion yet.
As I married you,
I will only live for you
for this life.
But Lu Anran won't.
Her resurrection
is strange enough.
And now she comes to Hanjing,
haunting us.
What does she want from us?
Your Highness shall beware of her.
Even if Lu Anran has an ax to grind,
she is more useful than you.
You are just a concubine's child.
The Lu Family thinks you are worthless.
It's I who feed you now.
Were it not becasue you can't mess around
with the imperial marriage,
do you think
you have any chance to be pretentious
in front of me?
Do you dislike me so much?
Your princess title
was stolen from her.
If you even try to gain a foothold here,
then I
will never go easy on you.
Also,
if you dare to take it upon yourself again,
the bowl of noodles
will become the offering
on your grave next year.
Remember?
Miss.
Lu Xinran
is really unfortunate.
I fret that Cuicui may have a rough time.
She will get out of the sufferings
one day.
It's all because of you
who made me so humiliated today.
Your Highness,
it's my fault.
Please forgive me.
Keep slapping.
Lu Anran,
why are you always around me?
The Double Fish Order
is still in her hand.
His Highness will
give way to her somehow anyway.
Right.
Yun.
I got Yun.
(Examination Hall)
Brother Xu.
(Select Talents for the Nation)
Yun.
How is the exam?
The question
is set well.
We don't have to
write an eight-legged essay,
nor verses, ditties, odes or songs.
It asks us
to give advice
on the starvation
and heavy taxes
Dahan's civilians suffer.
I stated
all the panaceas
I can come up with.
So jubilant.
That is great.
Yes.
Yun.
It's my fourth times
to attend the exam in the capital.
To raise the traveling expenses
for me all this way,
my family has been destitute.
But if I can
score high this time,
I can finally
live up to them.
Brother Xu,
I heard the chief in the Imperial Academy
was once a chief examiner.
Really?
Yeah.
Let me ask him to make an assessment.
Let's go.
Go.
I didn't hear you mention it.
Ask him to
judge your answer then.
Okay.
Yun.
Why don't you visit me
since you came to Hanjing?
What brings you here?
Brother Xu,
this is my second sister.
My name is Xu Qingce.
You are Yun's friend?
If you need
any help,
you can reach me
at the Mansion of Prince Qing.
She is Princess Qing now.
Yun,
I will wait for you over there.
I will leave you
to catch up.
I am leaving.
Tell me now if you need something.
I have to take Brother Xu
to find the chief to rewrite the paper.
Yun.
I just want to tell you
that you are fooled by Lu Anran.
What are you saying?
Lu Anran told me in person.
She killed our mom.
She almost killed me.
Do you know it?
Nonsense.
Mom got a dose of her own medicine!
She failed to harm First Madam.
She still wanted to kill Big sis.
Mom did this for whom?
For you!
Nowadays, the Lu Family's property
is all owned
by Lu Anran.
She sowed discord between us.
Isn't it for
grabbing all the property alone?
Look clearly.
I am the very sister
who shares the same mother with you.
You come to me today
and sow discord between Big sis and me.
Isn't it for the family property?
Yun.
Sister.
I beg you, okay?
You have been
Princess Qing now.
You have realized
mother's dream.
Stop asking for more.
Yun.
You all help Lu Anran.
I will let you
see her real face
one day.
Go. Let's go.
How is it?
Let me have a look.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
(1st: Yan Ziyun
2nd: Wang Chudao 3rd: Bi Shengjie)
I made it.
Congratulations!
Congrats! Congrats!
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Never mind. Never mind.
If you don't win the champion,
the Imperial Scholar background
is fine as well.
Let me check it.
(The Rankings)
(Yan Ziyun, Wang Chudao, Bi Shengjie)
Miss Lu, please.
Your Highness,
Miss Lu is here.
Coming.
You hurry to here
to take your reward, right?
Whether give me or not
depends on Your Highness.
If I am right,
the Yan Family
is preparing the feast
to celebrate the first prize.
Relax.
I will do
what I promised you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Bring her in.
Lingxi.
Miss.
I am here to take you home.
Is it true?
I still have some concern.
The agreement between us before
is a wedding aggreement,
which can prove our relations.
But now we collaborate with no evidence.
How can I trust you?
How about this?
Here is an agreement.
Sign it.
If one day,
any party
betrays the other,
he or she will be punished
by the other as they wish.
How is it?
Wait.
Raise.
What are you doing?
The Mansion of Prince Qing doesn't need
a reluctant alliance.
(Lu Anran)
See Miss Lu off nicely.
Miss Lu, please leave.
Mr. Cai.
You are injured.
Your Highness.
Thank you for Your Highness' kindness.
But it's improper for me to receive it.
Please Your Highness
doesn't embarrass me.
It's normal
for me to care about you as I treat you
as His Highness' consultant,
let alone you're my friend.
I don't dare to.
If you regard me as an outsider like this,
I will be sad.
You know.
In this mansion,
there are a few for me
to extend my care.
Fine. Thank you, Your Highness.
But I don't understand
now that Lu Anran
gets closer with His Highness,
why did she prick you?
His Highness caught Lingxi
because he wanted Lu Anran
to help him cooperate with Minister Yan.
Today, the rankings are out.
Lu Anran has made contributions
to the rankings.
So, they signed
a new agreement today.
My injury
was just a result
of their tentative choices to each other.
What help?
We were looking for a talent.
Lu Anran introduced a right option,
which did Minister Yan a favor.
Then again,
he is from Your Princess's hometown.
Holly.
I am back.
Lingxi.
It's great you are back.
Do you miss me?
Yes.
I will arrange a room for you
after I clean this pillar.
What is going on?
You didn't arrange my room
ahead of time.
And why do you prioritize
cleaning the pillar?
I will arange it for you now.
Alright?
Let's go.
That's more like it.
What's wrong with your hand?
It seems that
you do care about me.
Stop it. Stop it.
Let's treat it.
It's no big deal.
It doesn't hurt for real.
What is your sad face?
Just a failure.
You don't need to worry about me.
It's me...
It's me myself.
Aimed high without the abilities.
Therefore,
I let the time of over a decade
pass in vain.
Mr. Xu,
you don't have to sell yourself short.
I promise you
the Lu Family will ensure
you are fully supported
without further worry
however times you attend the exam.
Thank you for your good intention.
I really appreciate it.
But if I agree with it for real,
my past study time
is frittered away
for sure.
Tomorrow, I will
leave for Su City.
Thank you
Yun
and Miss Lu
for your care recently.
Farewell.
A few days ago, the chief said
Mr. Xu's essay was ingenious.
He could rank third class in the exam.
How could...
Your Highness, Mr. Lu is here.
What do you call me for?
Yun.
Have a seat.
You are my only relative
in Hanjing.
Even if I ask you to stay with me,
you don't have to be loath to do it.
Big sis is your relative too.
She treated you so well before.
It's because you did
something you shouldn't.
You stay with Lu Anran
all day.
But do you really
see through her?
What do you mean?
Sis,
don't try to stir up a dispute
between Big sis and me.
Has your friend Xu Qingce
failed?
How do you know?
Isn't it weird
that Mr. Xu couldn't
make himself on the rankings
with his abilities and insights?
Ask
your good sister
if she changed Xu Qingce's paper
for that of Minister Yan's son.
No way.
Don't you buy it?
Then go ask your classmates
in the Imperial Academy.
They are all born with wealth and fame.
It's not hard for them
to get the paper of the champion
from the court, right?
Come in.
Yun.
Sis,
please do
Mr. Xu a favor.
What?
(Yan Ziyun)
Mr. Xu's paper
was secretly changed by someone.
He is supposed to be the champion.
Sis.
Why don't you say anything?
I get it.
When Second Sister told me about this,
I thought
she didn't change
and wanted to frame you again.
But I really didn't expect,
sis,
you should do such a thing!
Yun.
I will explain it to you
later.
But you can't
tell Mr. Xu about this.
Get it?
Till now,
you still want to hide it from him.
The champion now
is the son of Minister Yan.
If you make it serious,
will he stop there?
Even if it's for Mr. Xu's life,
you should pretend you don't know.
Then, why should you did this?
It would be nothing
if you didn't change the paper.
Sis, why?
Why?
Tell me.
Why did you do this?
Yun.
This is?
This is my paper.
Yan Ziyun?
Yun,
where did you get this paper?
Tell me.
It's mine.
This is...
This is the essay of the champion
shared in the court.
Brother Xu,
it is your essay.
Brother Xu.
It's my paper.
Are you okay?
Brother...
Brother Xu. Brother Xu.
Brother Xu, where are you going?
Mr. Xu.
Yun.
Brother Xu.
Mr. Xu.
Young Master.
Miss, Cuicui sent us a message saying
Lu Xinran met Young Master in the mansion.
But she didn't know the reason.
Prepare a horsecar
to the Mansion of Prince Qing.
Then, what about Young Master?
I can't stop him now.
Ask Shan Yue to watch him.
Tell me if there are troubles.
Okay.
Shan Yue.
Open the door.
A complaint to make.
A complaint
to make.
I, Xu Qingce,
receiving bounties
from my relatives and villagers,
desire to serve the country.
So, I made endeavors
to study for over a decade.
But I didn't expect someone
changed my paper with his power,
stealing my championship.
Please look up.
(Examination Hall)
The examination hall
is not
a place for the selection of talents,
but a vault for the wealth
and a grave for the poor.
What is the meaning for we the poor
to study hard for twelve years?
Yan Ziyun
won the first prize
with my paper.
The examination hall
must give an explanation today.
Open the door.
Give the first prize back to me.
You look thinner
after you work in the examination hall.
During the days when we set the questions,
I have debated with those old pedants
for some days.
Then when we scored the papers,
it's much tougher.
My body
did lose fat.
Since you are here,
have a meal together.
I ask the chefs
to make you delicious food.
Okay.
I heard Yan Ziyun
was a rich playboy.
But I read his paper this time.
His purity
and far-sightedness
are beyond my thought.
Your Highness.
Minister Yan is visiting you.
Your Highness Prince Qing.
Your Highness Prince Qi.
Minister Yan.
Ninth Brother.
Second Brother, I'll leave you.
Minister Yan, please.
After you.
Your Highness.
Someone is beating the drum
to make a complaint in front of the hall.
He said his paper
was changed by someone.
Minister Yan, please rest assured.
The issue.
I have sent someone to handle it.
Fu Yunan is smart.
It is his first time
to hold the Spring Imperial Exam.
He doesn't want to
see such a scene either
as it will damage his reputation.
What do you think?
Then,
I will go back and do something.
Otherwise, I can't feel at ease.
Okay.
I am leaving.
Princess.
What are you doing?
Hands off.
Lu Anran.
I am His Highness' wife.
I don't mind
if you usually don't respect me.
But now you disgrace me like this
in front of His Highness.
Do you respect His Highness
or not?
You know you are
His Highness' wife.
Your Highness,
Lu Xinran intended to disclose
the change of the papers to Yun.
She almost destroyed all you have done
for the examination.
Minister Yan still asked me
why Xu Qingce knew this.
I also doubted it.
But now I know why.
Lu Anran,
you slander me.
Your Highness,
don't trust her.
Just because she ruined it
and she is afraid that
Lu Yun will incriminate her,
so she smears me.
More than this,
I know one thing accidentally
that Lu Yun took Xu Qingce
to find the chief of the Imperial Academy
to rewrite the paper.
It must because
Lu Anran planned to
destroy Your Highness' plan
from the beginning.
A few days ago, the chief said
Mr. Xu's essay was ingenious.
He could rank third class in the exam.
How could...
Your Highness,
Lu Anran
is always duplicitous.
She set a trap
to let me be the surrogate wife,
then she could get out of it.
And now she ruins your plan.
Your Highness,
don't trust her.
Lu Xinran, it is because
you have a grudge against me
and you knew accidentally
about the plan of His Highness and me,
so you instigated Yun
to take Xu Qingce to rewrite the paper
and told Yun
I engaged in the change of the papers
to make it a big scene now.
For one, you made me flop.
For another, you sowed discord
between Yun and me.
Killing two birds with one stone.
You are talking nonsense.
Your Highness,
don't trust her.
Since they were both our own words,
how do you assure
I am taking nonsense?
If I did wreck
His Highness' plan,
how would you get a chance
to mess around here?
Your Highness,
now that we can't
tell the truth in a minute,
the priority is to appease Xu Qingce
and defuse the situation.
I have sent
Cai Wangjin to address it.
Since Xu Qingce
is able to win the first prize,
if Your Highness can use him,
you will get a right-hand man.
I think Xu Qingce
will consent
after evaluating the state of affairs.
I have no time
to investigate the cause of the issue.
After the situation is defused,
I will settle the scores with you two.
Lu Anran,
if the case of the chief is real,
I will leave it to you.
Forestall future trouble.
Yes.
Fu Yunan, tell me.
Why don't you look into
the Xu Qingce issue?
Prince Qi,
several powers in the capital
are watching the examination hall.
Even if the mayor of the capital
doesn't send attendants here,
other officials will also send attendants.
How can we investigate
with our tiny power?
Then you even need to look into it.
(Zhigong Hall)
If you and I
watch the Imperial Examination
falling to a place
for the power and money trade
without doing anything,
where do students
put their high spirits
for serving the nation?
How does the examination hall
select talents for the court?
If we do investigate it,
we may incriminate
some nobles in the court.
Won't it
affect you yourself?
What do you mean?
This is
all I can say.
Your Highness,
please behave yourself.
Your Highness Prince Qing, Prince Qi.
Ninth Brother.
Second Brother, I will leave you.
Mr. Xu.
I was once a student
as you are.
I really understand
your feeling now.
You won the title and reputation
after making endeavors for over a decade,
but you have to relinquish it
to the other now.
You must feel resentful.
But have you ever considered the case?
The substitute
is the son of the Minister of Personnel.
Even if you regain your title and reputation,
but you will offend him.
How will you grab a foothold
in the official circles afterwards?
If you help His Highness now,
Minister Yan will
appreciate his favor as well.
Afterwards,
it will not be a hard thing
to give you a post.
With the support
of His Highness and Minister Yan,
how will you fret that
there is no way to serve the country?
What about other students?
Who will
do the justice for them?
Justice?
Mister,
in this cage,
you still strive for the justice?
Isn't it funny?
Do you know
why you flopped again and again
during these years?
That is because of your background.
So what if you enjoy outstanding talent?
So what if you boast the reputation
in the southern Su?
Your poor background
is like rootless duckweed.
Please think about this.
On the rankings these years,
which one
isn't the offsprings of dignitaries?
It is wishful thinking
if students like you
want to stand out.
I really admire
your talents and ambitions.
But isn't it a pity
if you don't have a chance
to show your talents and ambitions?
Your are intelligent.
I believe
you will
make the best choice.
Miss went to the Mansion of Prince Qing
in order to protect Young Master?
Once Mu Ze checks it,
he will know it was Yun who told the issue
to Mr. Xu.
So, why not I made it clear
and blamed Lu Xinran
to let him think
Lu Xinran stired it up purposely.
Then, he wouldn't
do anything to Yun.
But I didn't expect
Yun would take Xu Qingce
to rewrite the paper.
If the chief
does have the paper,
will you destroy it for real?
I should end this soon.
Otherwise, if it becomes serious,
I worry about Mr. Xu's life.
Didn't Prince Qing
send someone to recruit him
as you planned?
But I don't feel at ease.
Fire.
Hurry up.
What's going on?
Miss.
The Mansion of Hanjing's Mayor is on fire.
Fight the fire.
I have seen intrigue
simmering under the peace
Ignorant of the truth
for not seeing wood from the trees
I have seen the fate
foreshadow my destiny
where I am running
around in circles feeling lonely
In this life,
if I race against my destiny
a slim figure goes
through the dark days I will see
The more thorns there are,
the more moving the struggle is
Even if more fears strike,
I will turn the tide regardless
In this life,
if I stick to what I wish
a staunch figure
withstands wild winds I will see
Time proving, what Ive made
will stay forever in my memory
Risking everything
to reach my destination however far it is
In this life,
if I stick to what I wish
a staunch figure
withstands wild winds I will see
Time proving, what Ive made
will stay forever in my memory