=Lost Track of Time=
=Episode 26=
Brother,
I heard that in the morning court today,
His Highness Prince Qi impeached you.
They said you ordered the garrison
to beat and kill tenants.
Is it true?
It's okay now.
Can't you trust my brother's men?
They took
all the blame.
As for His Majesty,
he just scolded me
for not being restrained properly.
It's just a few months' salary.
Their Highnesses have always been close brothers.
Prince Qi is so confused.
It's not like he doesn't know
that Brother is helping His Highness.
Because of this,
they have broken off friendships.
What?
It's because His Highness
indulged him too much.
That's why Prince Qi
is so unscrupulous.
It's a pity that I didn't take the chance
to kill him this time.
But Brother,
he is the prince.
Isn't it too risky?
Don't worry.
I'm not stupid.
I just want to force Lu Yun to do it,
and then find an excuse,
saying that
Prince Qi brought people to
make trouble in the army,
and Lu Yun knew that
Prince Qi injured his sister,
so he did it in a hurry.
In this way,
we can kill Prince Qi
and Lu Anran smoothly.
I see.
But brother,
don't take risks like this in the future.
If something happens,
what should we do?
Got it.
I have to save my life
to protect you.
Speaking of Lu Anran,
she has been having a hard time recently.
Not only was she stabbed
by His Highness Prince Qi,
a trusted maid also
left the mansion.
She even made a scene before she left.
It really cheered people up.
Sister,
maybe we can take this opportunity
to kill Prince Qi.
And Lu Anran.
Doctor, how is my brother?
It's nothing serious.
He'll wake up in a couple of days.
Thank you.
Fine, fine.
It's because Leader Shen
is lucky enough.
He didn't hurt the vital part.
I'll get going.
Thank you for your hard work.
Miss,
someone is looking for you outside the door.
One should be treated differently
after three days.
Who would have thought that
once a maid in the mansion
now becomes the head
here.
General Xiao, you're too serious.
It's just that my elder brother
is ill in bed now,
so I'm just taking care of some chores.
You really can't say I'm "head".
I wonder
how is Leader Shen's injury now?
General Xiao,
you and I have no friendship.
There's no need to bother
and greet me here.
If there's something, please be frank.
Okay.
Then I won't beat around the bush.
Why did Leader Shen fall into a coma?
You know it better than I do.
Girl,
don't you
want justice
for your brother?
Lu Anran stabbed my brother,
so she deserves to die.
But on that day,
who tied my brother up there
and tempted us into it?
General Xiao, do you think
I don't know?
His Highness Prince Qing
and I really want to
test Lu Anran.
However,
we didn't do anything
to Leader Shen.
If it weren't for Lu Anran
selling his friends for glory,
how could it have come to this?
General Xiao asked me to come here today.
Do you still want to
test Lu Anran?
This woman
is too shrewd,
too malicious,
and resourceful.
If she is still alive,
it won't do us any good.
Now that Miss Holly
has stepped into the world of Jianghu.
Don't you have any idea of
avenging him?
What do you want to do, General?
Although Lu Anran
did it watertight,
she
has a fatal weakness.
That is
His Highness Prince Qi.
As long as you
help me kill Lu Anran,
I promise,
for what your gang has done recently
I'll let bygones be bygones.
I didn't expect that a great general
would use his personal relationship,
and such despicable means
to deal with others.
It's really eye-opening.
Miss Holly,
I didn't say that
they had an affair.
A general can abandon
the integrity of soldiers,
but Holly can't disgrace
Qinghe Gang.
I have my own way to deal with Lu Anran.
General. Please go back.
You.
You'd better
appreciate my kindness.
I'll not see you off.
By showing me these,
what do you want to do?
I want justice.
Xiao Ying's henchmen
have been brought to justice.
Prince Yi
has been punished.
There's no need to discuss
this matter anymore.
Stop fooling around.
Your Majesty is the emperor of Dahan.
But why
do you ignore
their sufferings and grievances?
It seems that you really want
justice.
Then let me ask you.
Where is justice?
Justice is written in the law,
and in the hearts of the people.
If, as you said,
justice is written in the law,
why don't you go to the Ministry of Penalty?
Why didn't you ask the Third Division?
Why do you come to my Imperial Study?
Because you know in your heart,
justice
is in my hands.
I hope
you can understand
the real justice
is not determined by God,
but by the emperor.
You should think about it.
If you want real justice,
you should consider
taking that seat.
(Xiao)
Your Highness,
Xiao Ying is not in the barracks.
I just heard that
he went to Qinghe Gang.
The head of Qinghe Gang
is Ms. Lu's
maid,
Holly.
He went to see Holly?
But I didn't
find out the details.
The person I asked
didn't make it clear.
Xiao Ying is too selfish,
he may not be loyal.
From now on,
we have to be more careful.
Yes.
Miss,
it seems the fish has taken the bait.
People following Xiao Ying
came back and said
when he came out of Qinghe Gang,
he seemed to be very angry.
It doesn't matter.
The angrier he is,
the more he won't let it go.
But you still have to
remind Holly to be careful.
She should give in at the right moment.
Don't hurt Qinghe Gang.
Yes.
Well,
Miss.
Just say what you want to say.
Xiao Ying is a general.
If what we're doing
doesn't work out,
wouldn't it be a big disaster?
If we keep treading as on eggs,
how can we deal with Xiao Ying?
However...
Xiao Ying and Mu Ze
are already at loggerheads.
Only by making him feel that Xiao Ying
is out of control,
can we have a chance to kill him.
Although Xiao Ying holds the capital army,
if it can't be used by himself,
for Mu Ze,
he won't give it to anyone else.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
Then,
what about His Highness Prince Qi?
He stabbed me.
This time I took advantage of him.
We're even.
Brother, you mean,
they do have an affair.
That maid,
was hiding something,
but her
expression betrayed her.
However,
she didn't agree to work with me.
It makes me
admire her a little.
Brother,
don't just admire her.
What should we do next?
Although she looks like
a tough guy,
now,
Qinghe Gang is leaderless.
She's just a little girl,
as long as I use some means
she must come to me.
Brother,
you must hurry up recently.
His Highness's attentions
are on Lu Anran.
I have to show
that I am broad-minded.
I can't say anything.
It's killing me.
I'm anxious, too.
After all, Prince Qi
is still staring at me.
(Qinghe Court)
Something bad happened.
What are you doing?
Some people went to
the barracks to report that
in the name of helping people,
Qinghe Gang robbed houses,
burned, killed, and pillaged.
They are the evil of this place.
Before we figure it out,
no one is allowed to
go in or out of Qinghe Gang.
Bullshit. Who reported it?
Ask him to confront us.
Guys, let's fight with them!
Let's go! Let's go!
Don't move.
I want to see your general.
I knew you'd come to me.
General Xiao, what do you want?
I've already told you.
As long as you let me get the evidence
of Lu Anran and Mu Chuan's affair,
I'll withdraw my troops immediately.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
What's wrong?
Is the vegetable for
Ms. Lu?
Yes.
Let me see whether it's fresh or not.
There's nothing to see here.
Hurry up.
I'll get someone to move the vegetables.
Okay.
(Meet you at a private house in the western suburb at 15:30.)
They really communicate through
the vegetables
sent to Lu Anran's court daily.
What a good idea.
If General hadn't
extorted a confession from Holly,
who could find out?
Nanny,
put this letter back.
If this pair of lovebirds
don't keep an appointment,
how can we catch them red-handed?
Yes.
Your Highness.
It's been so long.
Why are you still ignorant of the rules?
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Today, the chef mistakenly
took back Ms. Lu's
vegetables.
And a huge scandal
breaks.
Your Highness.
How is Brother Shen?
He hasn't woken up yet.
But the doctor said
he's fine now.
Holly, come on.
Why are the soldiers outside here?
Xiao Ying
knows Your Highness
hasn't given up on investigating him.
So...
He surrounded this place but didn't move.
Obviously, he is trying to
make a deal with me.
Holly, don't worry.
It doesn't matter if you say it directly.
He asks you to meet him at a private house
in the western suburb at 15:30.
Take good care of Brother Shen.
I'm sorry,
Your Highness Prince Qi.
(Qinghe Court)
Shan Yue,
I need your cooperation later.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Help!
Anran!
Someone is putting incense in the room.
I'm afraid I'll be dizzy.
So I pricked myself with a hairpin.
In order to protect me,
Shan Yue fights with them.
I took advantage of the chaos to run out.
Your Highness,
there must be something fishy.
Let's go.
Go in first.
Shan Yue.
Where is the bad guy?
I don't even see a shadow.
I'm afraid he hears
the sound outside,
and jumps out of the window.
What's going on?
That's the case.
Your Highness,
Lu Anran and Prince Qi
must have a private meeting here.
Unfortunately, we arrived early.
So, they use the ruse of self-injury.
Your Highness,
I am a man who is not married yet.
It's fine for you to make up
some erotic history before.
What you just said
not only slanders Ms. Lu,
but also ignores His Highness Prince Qing's
face.
If you just say it without thinking,
it would be too disgusting.
If I wronged you before,
you should
avoid suspicion more.
So suspectable.
Your Highness,
they just can't forget each other.
Ninth Brother,
why are you here?
Xiao Ying asked me to come.
Your Highness Prince Qi,
you always think of yourself as a gentleman.
Unexpectedly,
you're such a dirty person.
Xiao Ying,
you're really in time.
Holly?
Holly,
why are you here?
Good question, Ms. Lu.
If it weren't for your former confidant,
how can we know that
you secretly collude with His Highness Prince Qi.
Holly,
why are you with Xiao Ying?
Didn't you say he wanted to
make a deal with me?
Your Highness, I didn't say that.
Ms. Lu has always been skilled,
so I specially brought Holly here today
to prevent you from denying it.
Holly, tell us the truth.
Lu Anran killed my brother.
Today, even if I risk my life,
I will reveal her true colors.
Your Highness Prince Qing,
before she entered the mansion,
he fell in love with His Highness Prince Qi.
After the Lu Family loses
power and influence,
she has no choice but to join you.
But she's still attached
to His Highness Prince Qi.
She even asked us
to use the food truck to
deliver the message for her
to deceive the public.
Your Highness,
you are too indulgent.
That's why Prince Qi
did such an immoral thing.
As for my inner disputes,
you are quite clear about it.
I dare not.
I put Lu Yun in your army,
but you made him kill ninth brother.
I'm just thinking of you.
How dare you kill my ninth brother?
You really don't
respect me.
Xiao Ying went to Qinghe Gang.
This person is too selfish
he may not be loyal.
Your Highness,
General Xiao took advantage of your suspicion
to kill His Highness Prince Qi and me.
Not only can he get rid of
His Highness Prince Qi's entanglement,
but he can also help his good sister
to kill me, her most hated person.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Holly,
you said Xiao Ying's garrison
surrounded Qinghe Gang.
He is not to make a deal with me,
but to force you
and threaten me, right?
Your Highness, isn't it strange
if Holly wants to avenge me,
why didn't she tell the so-called affair
between His Highness Princess Qi and me
on the day she left the mansion?
Instead, why does she have to go around
in such a big circle to find General Xiao?
Xiao Ying,
did you
really surround Qinghe Gang?
Yes, I did.
But,
I did it
to make Holly tell the truth.
Holly,
as long as you tell the truth,
for what happened today,
I will let bygones be bygones.
Your Highness Prince Qi,
I tricked you into coming here.
I'm sorry to you.
But I really have no choice.
Xiao Ying said that if
I don't cooperate with him,
he will kill everyone in the Qinghe Gang
with any excuse.
Your Highness Prince Qing,
the truth is,
what I said today is not true.
The food truck.
The secret affair.
It's all made up by Xiao Ying.
He asked me to say it .
He forced me to say it.
Nonsense!
General Xiao,
you failed to kill me before.
Now you're using such
despicable means to frame me up.
Do you deserve to be a general?
Your Highness, I think I have to advise you
Xiao Ying is unfaithful and unjust.
He even dares to make use of Your Highness.
In the future,
will he fight for your great cause
for Your Highness?
Lu Anran.
I'll kill you.
Brother!
Brother! Brother!
Your Highness.
You're still not going to tell me, are you?
What do you want me to say, Your Highness?
Tell me about what happened today.
Your Highness has saved Holly before,
but I falsely accused Your Highness today,
humiliating Your Highness
in front of everyone.
I deserve to die.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
Holly,
you know what
I want to ask.
You and Lu Anran
used to be so close.
Why did you act like this today?
Didn't you trust her very much?
Just because of what Your Highness said,
she sacrificed my brother
to save her life.
Okay.
It seems that
you hate her very much now.
Yes.
So you cooperate with
Xiao Ying's action today,
accusing Lu Anran and me
to get back at her?
No.
Xiao Ying coerced me.
Coerced by him.
Why did you expose him in public?
If you insist on accusing him,
you can solve the Qinghe Gang's problem,
and also revenge for Brother Shen.
Isn't that killing two birds with one stone?
Now you've exposed him.
You can't
do good for any side.
Your Highness,
I'm just a little maid.
In the face of such a situation,
how can I
be so thoughtful?
It's not that you're thoughtless,
but that you know
the one who's going to win today
can keep Qinghe Gang safe,
can keep you safe as well.
So you cooperated with her,
and put on a play.
You drove her to a desperate situation,
and then washed her out again.
My second brother's monstrous anger
must be nowhere to put it.
As it happens,
Xiao Ying has a grudge against him originally.
What's more, it's a trap to kill him today.
How could my second brother
let him go so easily?
Your Highness, don't push me anymore.
Lu Anran.
You scheme everyone.
Even me.
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
I'll ask my brother
to kill all of you!
All of you!
Where is my brother?
I want my brother.
I want my brother!
Don't laugh!
You! Shut up!
Brother.
I want my brother.
No.
Princess, don't be nervous.
I
won't do anything to you.
Tomorrow is Double Ninth Festival，
I will take you to the height
to enjoy chrysanthemums.
Look at you now.
It's a disgrace to Prince Qing's Mansion.
Freshen up.
By the way,
don't you miss your brother very much?
General Xiao
will go with us tomorrow.
Happy?
You'd better wear the hairpin I give you.
Brother.
What did you say? Brother.
Brother, say something.
Brother.
Brother, I was wrong.
Don't leave me.
Brother.
I was wrong.
Don't go.
Don't leave me alone.
Your Highness, something big happened today.
I'm sure you won't think of it.
The dam is closing soon.
Any mistakes are not allowed.
What's going on?
The dam is in good condition,
so it will be opened on time
for acceptance check.
Then what is it?
Xiao Ying is dead.
Your Highness,
why aren't you surprised at all?
Do you know how he died?
How did he die?
He climbed high and fell to his death
at Double Ninth Festival.
As a general,
he doesn't die in battle.
But he climbed a mountain and fell to death.
It makes me laugh my head off.
Who knows who will take over
thousands of troops
in the suburbs of Hanjing?
I'm afraid those two
will spare no efforts to fight for it.
(Xiao Ying tortures citizens.)
(He deserves to die a thousand times,)
(but dies)
(for such a reason.)
(How ridiculous.)
(Two people)
(whom I cherish the most in my life.)
(It's harder and harder for me to see them through.)
(How can I)
(protect what I want to protect)
(in my life?)
Chuan,
how is the water conservancy project
going recently?
As usual.
This month,
the dam will be completed.
Before the flood season comes this year,
it can be put into use.
Xiao Ying slipped and died a few days ago.
His death is sudden.
The Hanjing garrison
is leaderless.
Your two brothers
are also competing for this position.
In your opinion, who should I give it to?
Father, it's your belongings.
You should decide for yourself.
If I want you to decide,
who do you want to give it to?
Seems like you're the same as me.
You also know
what your two brothers want.
Prince Qing is close to Xiao Ying.
Xiao Ying's sister
is married to Prince Qing.
He gains everything with hard efforts,
so he doesn't want to give it to others.
And if Prince Yi
gets the garrison of Hanjing,
with his characters,
he will be more arrogant.
It seems Father has made up your mind.
You've decided
the most suitable candidate for sure.
You're the one I want.
The army is the weapon of a country.
If someone with too much selfishness gets it,
there will be endless troubles.
And you don't mean to do that,
and are eligible as well.
In my heart,
you are the most suitable one.
Your Highness Prince Qi.
Father,
as you know,
I have no intention of
getting involved in this court battle.
I just want to build my water conservancy,
and be the keeper of
Peace Granary.
Do you not want to accept
my decree?
Or you don't want
this seat
I told you before.
I know you are open-minded by nature,
and long for a free life outside the palace.
But what a person wants in his life
will not always be the same.
Chuan,
between the freedom you want
and what you want to protect,
you'll definitely
have to make a choice one day.
Well,
you can take this decree first.
You can reply to me
when you have made up your mind.
Your Highness Prince Qi.
I don't want to
wait too long.
Brother.
Brother, you're awake.
Are you feeling better?
Qing,
don't worry.
I won't die.
Why are you here?
After you were stabbed that day,
Miss asked me
to pretend to break up with her.
I can
go back to Qinghe Gang
to take care of you.
Didn't you mistake Lu Anran?
Miss is grateful to me
for saving me.
I know exactly
what kind of person she is.
That's good.
However,
Miss will not care about
whoever in the world misunderstands Miss.
But Prince Qi...
Brother Chuan?
What did he do?
On the day Miss stabbed you,
Prince Qi happened to see it.
He thought she really wanted to kill you.
He even stabbed Miss.
The sword
was stabbed at Miss's body,
also,
at her heart.
Chuan stabbed Lu Anran?
Silly boy.
Well,
Qing,
help me up.
Brother, you just woke up.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to see Chuan.
Brother,
She won't let us
tell His Highness Prince Qi.
She doesn't want His Highness to get involved.
Things have already happened.
And all of you
are self-righteous,
with a little girl's temperament.
Chuan is
a man.
How does he feel about
letting you girls
lie to him?
Besides,
can't you see
they love each other?
But I promised Miss
I won't tell him.
No buts.
You've promised your Miss,
while I take care of my Chuan.
It's not a conflict.
Brother.
Brother, don't move.
All right, brother.
Don't move.
I'll ask someone to invite
His Highness here tomorrow.
You can talk to him tomorrow.
You may all leave.
Yes.
You.
The injury...
Your Highness, don't worry.
It's just a flesh wound.
Is it really just a flesh wound?
I remember how you
got hurt.
You would say something before.
But now,
you're so calm.
Are you
completely disappointed in me?
Your Highness, if you say so
you really hurt me.
This mansion
belongs to Your Highness.
I still have to rely on Your Highness.
But I make Your Highness suspicious.
Let others take advantage of it.
This is indeed my fault.
I don't want you to be so sensible.
I know.
I suspected you many times,
and almost got you killed.
If it were Xiao Jingque,
she,
she would have turned Prince Qing's Mansion
upside down.
But you...
And your wound.
If others are in a dangerous situation,
they will cry at least once.
You're so calm,
because you've never
put hope on me,
right?
Your Highness, you know very well.
The royal mansion
is the place that torments people.
Some are tired.
Some are insane.
It's just their own cultivation.
I didn't want you to cultivate with hair
by marrying you back.
What do you want me to do?
Scold you for not
distinguishing right from wrong,
and being too suspicious,
and trying to kill me many times?
Or secretly shed tears,
lament the injustice of fate,
and cry with you,
saying that I used to
shine my heart on the moon,
but the moon shines on the ditch?
Mu Ze,
I've abandoned
what I cherish the most
and I'm willing to
be locked up in this mansion.
What do you want me to do?
What do you give me back?
You only give me endless damage.
But now,
you want me change back into
an innocent girl
like Xiao Jingque.
It is you that ruined my innocence!
It is you that ruined
my trust in you.
Impossible!
We can never go back.
Alright,
I know
you're so angry
because you still care about me.
To be honest,
among these days,
today is the happiest day,
I'm aware that
Xiao Jingque and his brother
have been hurting you.
But now I promise you,
I will let the whole mansion know
who is the mistress of this mansion.
Go freshen up now.
Come to the mansion in two hours.
I'll prove it to you.
♪I have seen intrigue simmering under the peace♪
♪Ignorant of the truth for not seeing wood from the trees♪
♪I have seen the fate foreshadow my destiny♪
♪where I am running around in circles feeling lonely♪
♪In this life, if I race against my destiny♪
♪a slim figure goes through the dark days I will see♪
♪The more thorns there are, the more moving the struggle is♪
♪Even if more fears strike, I will turn the tide regardless♪
♪In this life, if I stick to what I wish♪
♪a staunch figure withstands wild winds I will see♪
♪Time proving, what I’ve made will stay forever in my memory♪
♪Risking everything to reach my destination however far it is♪
♪In this life, if I stick to what I wish♪
♪a staunch figure withstands wild winds I will see♪
♪Time proving, what I’ve made will stay forever in my memory♪
♪Risking everything to reach my destination however far it is♪
(Lu)