Go for it.
I'm not afraid of anything.
The flowers are in the branches.
The years are passing by.
I don't know why I'm missing you.
Some people want to repay you.
But they have no power.
A lifetime of love is the best way.
The Long Ballad
Episode 18
After this event,
I also know about Lun'er's identity.
Your marriage...
Madam,
I was so confused.
I pretended to be a robber.
Just to get your approval.
But I don't know why.
I almost hurt Shao Heng and your life.
I know it's not sincere.
I don't dare to mention my marriage with Shao Heng.
I just hope you can forgive me.
Come.
Don't talk nonsense.
Those killers are so vicious.
They almost killed you.
How could they be the one you're looking for?
The four who ran away,
I hope they're the one he's looking for.
But it has nothing to do with him
who wants to kill us.
Madam.
Heng, you insisted on taking me to burn incense.
You've been acting strange all the way.
I guess you're involved in this.
Mother.
I'm not that stupid.
Lun'er is injured.
I'm afraid she can't drink water
or boil tea.
I think we should stop this tea house.
Mother.
How could you say that?
I did it to save you.
I'm just trying to save myself.
Don't blame others.
Don't worry.
My son is a little bit stupid.
He's a little bit naive.
But he's a little bit kind.
If he's not good to you in the future,
I'll beat him for you.
Mother.
You agreed?
Go get the room ready.
Right.
Remember to go to the law firm.
You kids
discussed such a bad idea.
I'm not going to marry.
Now everything is settled.
Get the wedding ready.
Thank you, mother.
I'll go get ready.
Let's go.
Let go.
You're clumsy.
I'll take care of Lun'er.
You go do your business.
Brother Mu, I...
I'm sorry.
I must have been too kind to you.
I don't know how to repay you.
You know?
I'll know if you tell me to.
If you don't want me to know, I'll pretend not to know.
But I'll keep
your kindness in my heart.
I don't want to be ungrateful.
It's good that you forget.
Anyway, there's one more thing you have to promise me.
What?
Can you two
stop playing tricks on me?
All of that is your life's gift.
Come on.
Qi Shaogeng, stop talking nonsense.
I didn't say anything nice.
I'm going to get married.
Don't you think it's like a dream?
I can give you a chance.
Feel it.
No need.
It's a great honor
to have you and Sister Luan'er married.
What a pity!
But, Brother Lu,
you only acted in a few films.
Why did you do this to us?
Qi's family is a escort company.
They have some enemies.
It's not a rare event.
I guess so.
I'm sorry.
Anyway,
your marriage is done.
Mrs. Qi has been kind to us
and didn't blame us.
She even agreed to your marriage.
Of course.
Thanks to our daughter,
she risked her life to save my mother.
Of course.
The good plan of Shi Meiguan
is also a great achievement.
Don't mention it.
I don't dare to think
about my bad idea again.
Congratulations, Mr. Qi.
You're really
in good shape.
I think so, too.
You...
Thank you, Shi Meiguan.
Please help me with the wedding.
And give me a gift of three books and six films.
Goodbye.
Wait, Mr. Qi.
I have a favor to ask you.
Our Shi family
never stole your family's money.
My parents are still in prison.
I know you're the victim.
So are my parents.
So I beg you
to tell the truth in the General's Office
and release my parents as soon as possible.
I should.
I'm afraid
those bad guys are our real enemies.
Shi Meiguan is a kind and sincere person.
I've heard about Tao Meiguan.
I'll go to the General's Office now
and make sure your family is cleared.
Thank you, Mr. Qi.
I'll go get the wedding invitation and the wedding certificate now.
Lu Xiong.
You...
You totally...
He's asking me to do these things.
Chu Dream.
My family is in prison.
How's about my family?
For lovers.
They keep the feeling of married life inside them
La pockets
any
Cross
What's wrong with you
Like you
Only you
can see
How
What do you think?
Aunt Deng,
you're so affectionate.
Don't call me Aunt Deng.
Call me Deng Shoumei.
Now I'm the Shoumei of Guanmei Hall.
I know.
If Guanmei Hall doesn't assign me a task,
I won't do it.
I can be the Chief of the Department of Justice.
Lady.
I brought what you ordered
for Lady Shi.
Lady.
Good news and bad news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Do you want to hear it now
or never?
Which one do you want to hear?
Good news is that
Tao and Shi's father
are about to be released from prison.
Bad news is that
the guard
has been forced to marry by courtiers
and has no time to do anything.
He ordered you to keep an eye on Marquis Wu'an.
Marquis Wu'an
will definitely tell the truth from Guanmei Hall.
Good news is good news.
But bad news is not bad news.
I'll definitely keep an eye on Guanmei Hall.
Brother Lu.
Ke.
What did I buy for you?
Brother Lu.
You should have a good rest.
Did Ke meet any trouble?
Brother Lu.
I have good news
and bad news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Of course I want to hear it first.
Brother Lu.
When my family was gone,
I met a good person
like you.
When my parents come back,
I'll tell them
to be your brother and sister.
I already have a brother and sister.
I don't want to have a sister anymore.
You don't want to?
That's true.
I'm a troublesome person.
I always cause trouble
and I always get people involved.
How about I remind you
my hobby?
I remember
helping people to have fun and having fun.
Brother Lu, look.
My good news is
that Deng Yi is on the post
without even looking at it.
The bad news is also
that Deng Yi is on the post
without even looking at it.
So,
what's the difference?
I just found out
that I always call him Deng Yi
but he never treats me as his niece.
I suspect that he has other motives
and has other intentions.
That's why he's so happy.
Do you trust me?
Of course I trust you.
Then don't worry about it.
I'll keep an eye on
Deng Mei Guan's every move.
Really?
Won't it
delay Brother Lu's business?
Of course not.
Your business is my business.
Brother Lu.
What's your business?
Eating, drinking, having fun,
and helping people to have fun.
Forget it.
You can talk when you want to.
I'll go too.
Brother Lu.
You should have a good rest.
You don't have to accompany me.
That's another good thing about me.
Accompany me?
Watch the fun.
Let's go.
What's wrong with me?
What am I thinking?
My face
must be red as a monkey's ass.
It's all Qi Shao He's fault.
He said he made me his wife.
I've made a promise.
Brother Lu and I are just good friends.
Don't think too much about it.
You can't talk like that.
I won't talk to you.
You'll be embarrassed.
You're a bad daughter.
The only daughter of the Liu family
was born in Liu's Mansion in the west of the capital.
Her surname is Luan Er.
She's 18 years old.
Her mother is a noble.
All right.
Don't read it.
Mrs. Qi.
Are you going to change your mind
or did I make a mistake?
Mother.
Why don't you read it?
to fulfill my wish.
Madam, just tell me.
As long as I can do it,
I'll do as you wish.
After the official marriage ceremony,
when will the wedding be held?
After the ceremony,
we'll exchange the marriage papers.
The marriage papers will be shared
and the wedding will be held
on the day of the selection.
Then the wedding will be held.
On the day of the selection?
Then tomorrow is the wedding.
The marriage papers
have been approved long ago.
You can take them today.
You can exchange them tomorrow at noon.
You can get married at night.
Tomorrow?
So soon?
Well,
isn't the official marriage ceremony allowed?
Not really.
It's just a matter of
making some seal.
But the wedding preparations...
I've prepared
the wedding gifts for over ten years.
The wedding gifts are all ready.
The wedding gifts are also ready.
You can get married
only after you marry a woman.
I don't want to
delay it for a day.
Come on.
As long as you don't break the wedding ceremony,
you can get married with a decent manner.
I don't have any other requirements.
Please.
Mrs. Qi, I...
Ke.
Since Mrs. Qi has made up her mind,
why don't we go to the teahouse
and ask Mrs. Liu?
Let's go.
Go.
The wedding is arranged by both parties.
Everything is fine.
The only thing that's not right
is that the wedding will be done too soon.
Would you like to do it?
Mr. Luo and Mr. Qi are in love.
I'm willing to do it.
Then let's
check our dowry.
Wait a minute.
Rui Ling,
The keepers'
hand-held。」
Shiathy stationed here.
This is my dreaming city啊?
Is there any
real estate?
How could his reason
spare him money
to build a grand gate?
But, I have to give her all the money to help me.
I...
Father.
I'm useless.
I'm so rich.
I don't have the guts to let her be so generous.
Father, you're sick. You should try your best to cure yourself.
I only have gratitude towards you.
Why should I feel that you're useless?
Then, what should I write in my letter?
This is a letter of etiquette.
Don't forget that the one that Madam Qi hates the most
is the one who made a fool of herself.
But Madam Qi doesn't like to lose her etiquette.
This is a letter to her.
I'm already satisfied with your approval.
I don't want to lie to deceive you.
I'll ask the guard to write a letter of etiquette.
My family background is like this. You don't need to change it.
You don't need to cover for me.
I didn't marry or beg for the marriage of the Qi family.
I only ask for the true heart of each other.
Brother Lu really helped me fix it.
My ancestors, I came in through the wall.
I ask the ancestors to help me.
The Qi family is so rich.
They gave me a gift that is longer than me.
But in Sister Lun'er's house, there is only 7 taels of silver.
There is only 7 taels of silver.
Not to mention that the door is right.
Even the son of the Ban family can't stand on the edge.
But Sister Lun'er is a good girl.
When I was exchanging the gift, I said how to operate it.
It can either ruin the reputation of the Qi family
or make Sister Lun'er not lose face in the family of the woman.
It can make this marriage happen.
Ake.
Brother Lu, why are you here?
I brought food for you.
I'll leave with your family first.
Brother Lu, let me ask you.
If you also like a girl like Sister Lun'er,
a poor and unmarried girl, what would you do?
What I like is a person.
What does marriage have to do with her marriage?
Also, if you like a person, but she can't get a dowry,
will you marry her?
Yes. I have promised my little brother.
As long as she appears and has no dowry,
I will follow the agreement.
I only ask for one person.
Whether she has a dowry or not, I will not leave her.
That's good.
That's what I think.
But a woman doesn't have a dowry.
Even if she is a thousand years old, she can still kill Sister Lun'er.
And Madam Qi has already let her in.
She only has one request. She wants a dowry.
Just like this cake.
We'll buy it for you.
When you eat it, I'll open it.
Do I still want your money?
You give me a cake. I'll open it for you.
I understand.
Sister Lun'er, don't be so modest.
And don't marry Qi Shaohe.
We can exchange our gifts for equal things.
The most equal and the most unmarried in the world is the one who is the most beautiful.
If a person's heart is sincere, and a person's heart is pure,
it is the best way to be together.
Ake is indeed smart.
He is very smart.
Ake! Ake!
Where are you?
My parents are back.
Brother Lu, you go first. I'll go find you later.
I'll go find you later.
No, no.
Is Ake in there? Let's go take a look.
Ake! Ake!
You're back!
My precious daughter.
Let me take a good look.
Daughter, I feel like you've lost weight or...
You've gotten taller.
Really?
Don't be so blind.
You're the one who's lying.
Ake isn't thin or tall.
He's just pretty.
Brother is right. Our Ake is even cuter.
Mother.
Mountain Master, I received news.
Marquis Wu An's steward just went to the General's Manor to meet Li Ang.
Then he went to Guanmei Hall.
It seems like he's trying to force Deng Weiguan to do something.
It's Li Ang again.
I think Marquis Wu An should stop chasing Qi Shaoheng.
And go find Li Ang to be the new head of the law.
It seems like he's going to do something new again.
Mountain Master, you know that too?
Continue to investigate the news.
Report to me as soon as you get any news.
Yes.
I'll keep an eye on Guanmei Hall.
He's obviously trying to keep an eye on the missing girl.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Mother, the General's Manor has released you.
Tomorrow, can you go back to Guanmei Hall?
This is a report for the future trial.
You don't need to report after the escape.
But before the case is solved,
you need to be confined to the capital. You can't escape.
If you have any clues,
you can come to the General's Manor to assist the investigation.
We were innocent.
Sir, you don't need to pay us back.
You even detained us in the capital.
How can you call my wife a rebel?
Let me tell you, we can't sign this document.
Innocent?
You're only called innocent after you've investigated it.
As for when to investigate, I don't know.
You can sign it.
Then send this to the bottom.
General, wait.
I'll sign it.
Madam, you can't be so muddled.
If you sign this document,
you're a suspect.
You're the one who's in charge.
Husband,
all three of our children are waiting for us to go back.
Especially Ake.
He's a girl and he's out for so long.
I'm really worried.
Madam.
Ake, I just got back.
I want to rest for a few more days.
I won't go to the hall for now.
But I really didn't expect
you would protect the ancestral hall so well.
Yes.
I'm really happy.
I thought the ancestral hall might be ruined by those people.
It's really good.
Mother, this is what I should do.
You said I'm the best heir.
By the way, mother, look.
When did you send the snacks?
We three have been bothering the He family for so long.
We should thank them.
No.
Brother Lu has been with me.
But how can we say that?
Forget it.
I'll find a chance to invite him to our home and tell him in person.
Qi Shao Heng?
Yes, mother.
I've made Qi Shao Heng's beauty.
I asked him to go to the General's mansion to talk to you.
Now it's time to say goodbye.
You did a good job.
I'm proud of you.
Mother, you should rest well.
Before you go back to the temple, I'll do my best.
I won't let you down.
You guys can leave now.
I have something to talk to Ake alone.
No.
Okay.
Let's go.
Go.
You guys go too.
Brother, the snacks are not from He family.
Not from He family?
So there are outsiders coming to our home recently.
Yes.
Who could it be?
Ake.
I won't go to Guanmei Hall anymore.
From now on, this ancestral hall
and the most beautiful name in the world
will be entrusted to you.
Mother, why is that?
I've already signed the contract.
I won't interfere in Guanmei Hall's affairs for now.
But don't worry.
No matter what you do, I will support you.
I will support you.
Mother.
Come, open it.
Mother, this is...
This dress
was originally intended to be passed on to you when you are the best in the world.
Then maybe, it's that time now.
You wear this dress
and host the wedding for Qi Shao Heng.
Mother, I will definitely not disappoint you.
I will definitely not disappoint you.
So beautiful.
So beautiful, right?
Give her a round of applause.
Brother Lu.
Ake, you look really good today.
Really?
Thank you, Brother Lu. My mother is back.
I plan to invite you to my house to be a guest
and introduce you to my family.
Really?
You are my savior.
I plan to tell them about the matter of the General's Office.
I also plan to say...
So it's about this matter.
I know.
It's not good for too many people to know about the General's Office.
Brother Lu, let me ask you again.
You really don't plan to be my sworn brother?
I don't want to.
I'll just pretend that you didn't say it. I'll pretend that I didn't hear it.
What did I say wrong?
What's wrong?
Your two brothers are here.
Oh no, my two brothers have a bad temper.
You are just thinking about my family's future. You won't listen to anything I say.
You are just going to fly away.
Who are you?
I am Lu Chi. I live next door.
Come and help me.
Helping by the wall?
That's not necessary.
Ake, how do you know such a little, little disciple?
Brother, you are fierce.
Ake, I am not fierce to you. I am fierce to him.
This kid is so sneaky. He's not a good person at first sight.
How do you know he's not a good person?
In the days when you were not here, he was the one who helped me fix the hall.
He was the one who got the marriage of Qi Shao Heng and saved me from the bad guys.
Look at his wound and you are talking.
You guys are still following the rules.
You can't help me with anything.
I am the only one who is handling the family affairs.
Ake, your two brothers are helpless.
They didn't mean to.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
Brother Lu is still speaking for you.
It's all my fault.
It's all your second brother's fault.
Your second brother's fault.
I will let you go today.
Brother Lu, I am going to the He family now.
Please go to the Xibao Pavilion and ask Manager Li to come.
We will meet at the door of Qi Shao Heng's house.
Manager Li? I can also go?
Brother, go to the He family and ask Tian Tian to come to help us.
Okay, I will go to the He family now.
Let's go.
Brother Lu, I have a door.
I can go through the door.
Okay.
Seeing how my second brother is looking, I have already done half of it for you.
You are not going to embarrass Tao Yi.
Of course, I won't.
I know that our Tian Tian is the best. Thank you.
Dear fellow villagers,
Miss Lu Er has specially invited the He Ji Bings to distribute sweets and cakes.
Everyone can also invite some friends and relatives to enjoy the family's happiness.
A'Kao, did you invite me here?
Why did you become Lady Liu Xia?
What do you want to do again?
This is a wedding. Even though it's a long distance,
Brother Xian, I invited you here on behalf of Sister Luan Er.
Your family's wedding sweets and cakes are the best in the capital.
Anyone who marries can get your exclusive
I'll take 20 taels from him.
If this continues,
our He Ji will soon have a day to feed A'Kao.
Tian Tian, I gave my second brother to you.
What else do you want?
My second brother is willing to help me.
Tian Tian, money can't be given to A'Kao.
I'll do whatever A'Kao asks me to do.
He has his own reason.
Why do you ask so many questions?
Which ones do you want?
These ones, right?
The Jin family's daughter, Liu Luan Er,
invites everyone to eat cakes.
Come, come, come. We all have some.
Liu Luan Er, I know her.
She's a very gentle lady.
Please give her a few more beautiful words.
Of course.
Everyone, don't be shy.
Slowly, slowly. We all have some.
Brother Lu, Sister Pan Er, you're finally here.
I have one more favor to ask of you.
What is it?
When Mrs. Qi comes out later,
please help me praise Liu Luan Er and Mrs. Qi.
You must make Mrs. Qi happy
and make her feel proud.
I'm at your disposal.
I'll do my best.
Come, come, come.
Sister Pan Er, my parents are back.
If Brother Lu is in your Xibao Pavilion,
and he can't get any money,
don't make things difficult for him.
Come find me. I'll help him.
Little lady, when Brother Lu is free,
he often comes to Xibao Pavilion to help me.
I'm willing to help you.
There's no need for us to see each other.
Who's talking behind my back?
You're so annoying.
No, no, no.
Why is this?
Find an outsider to come here.
Who's an outsider?
This...
What happened?
Why aren't you going to marry him?
Guan Mei Ting, Mei Guan Shi, and Fa Ke came to his house today.
They're going to send a message to the young lady.
They're going to return all the betrothal gifts.
He won't take any of them.
Return? Why?
But Luan Er thinks there's too little betrothal gifts.
If he has other demands, I'll just accept them.
Don't worry, Madam. Let me explain.
Sister Luan Er said that as long as he wants the same betrothal gifts,
if he gets the same betrothal gifts, he won't take any of them.
Junior Mei Guan, what does Luan Er want?
I'll immediately send a message to him.
You want another one?
Could it be that Luan Er hates me for being a fool,
so he deliberately...
Sister Luan Er said that
as long as he truly loves you,
he'll accept any betrothal gifts.
I knew it.
Luan Er is a kind-hearted young lady.
How could she be so greedy?
So it's for your true feelings.
I've always had true feelings.
I've already written the betrothal gifts.
If you're willing to sincerely ask for the betrothal gifts,
just put the handprint on it and the betrothal gift will be done.
Okay.
Is Junior Mei Guan joking?
If you're willing to sincerely ask for the betrothal gifts, how can she be reasonable?
That's right. If a man is willing to sincerely ask for the betrothal gifts,
then a woman should be reasonable to be able to match him.
Sister Luan Er said that she's willing to sincerely ask for the betrothal gifts,
she's kind-hearted and loyal.
She's willing to entrust her whole life to you and Childe Qi.
We'll share our life and death together. We won't change.
Oh my god. Mrs. Qi is a kind-hearted and compassionate person.
She deserves such a kind-hearted daughter-in-law.
She doesn't look down on her family and her money.
This is a great fortune for the Qi family.
Am I right?
Yes.
Mrs. Qi is the kind-hearted and compassionate person.
She will be happy to have a father like her.
Congratulations, Mrs. Qi, you have a father like her.
Thank you. Thank you, everyone.
As everyone said, my son and Luan Er are a perfect match.
Son, what are you waiting for?
Hurry and go get Luan Er back.
I'll wait for you to win back our new wife.
Great!
Congratulations.
You worked so hard!
We'll support sadness one day.
It must be a concert in A Year Green throat
akeeper
A closes
a closes
hand
a key
point
So
The groom is Qi Shaoheng, the bride is Liu Guan'er.
Hurry and get married!
Luo'er, I'm here to pick you up.
Xiao Hoo, you say that I'm質ocratic?
We aren't.
You're just begrulous!
Xiao Hoo,
I love you more than anything else in this world.
Open your eyes!
Open them!
What is it?
bright
right
let's do it
They definitely have a distance
I'll tell you
let's go
Light
So embarrassed
do it
Shimei Guan, now you can really take responsibility
for the reputation of the eight words of the word
to make a match and to make a match.
I can really take responsibility.
How can I complete it if I can't make it in several times?
How can I complete it if I don't believe in the conscience of the heaven and the earth?
Yes, although Shimei Guan is a wise person,
he has the style and ability to handle the match.
The world's number one match, even if you can't make it today,
you will definitely make it in the future.
Ok, ok, ok.
For getting back,
I
want to beALLkeeper
Way
What way
Brother He is drunk.
Send him back.
Yes.
Brother He.
Let's go, Brother He.
Don't pull me.
Don't.
What?
Call Brother He here.
I'll wait for him over there.
Brother He.
Brother Lu, it's fun.
He's drinking here secretly.
Where's Brother Xian?
He asked me to come here.
Why is he gone?
Ke.
You're drunk, right?
Brother Lu.
Do you know?
Everyone praises me.
They say I'm the most beautiful girl in the world.
I'm not happy.
How can I be willing to give up?
Ke.
You look so beautiful tonight.
Really?
Yes.
No.
You don't have to help me.
I can stand.
Brother Lu.
Look.
My clothes look good, right?
My mom gave it to me.
From now on,
I'm the best of the family.
Are you happy now?
Of course I'm happy.
I've never been so happy.
I'm happier than I am when I bought Mr. Lin Yuan's painting.
It's so happy to be a good matchmaker.
Why didn't I feel it before?
I wasted so much time.
I should have done so many makeups.
Brother Lu.
Cheers.
Come on.
Ke.
You...
I've decided.
From now on,
I'll be a good matchmaker.
I'll be the pillar of the Shi family.
I'll make all my friends
be loyal to me.
I'll find happiness.
Brother Lu.
Come on.
Drink it.
I've had it. Be good.
Ke.
Brother Lu.
I have a question.
Does Ke like you
so much?
He won't.
Why?
Because
I'm his father.
You're the
distinguished person of Bai gaps.
I'm the owner of the house.
My neighbor is a rich man.
Brother Lu is so rich.
How can I repay you?
Brother, drink.
I never want to be a man.
You don't want to be a man.
I want to be a man.
Today, no one can stop me.
I want to be a rich man.
I don't want to part with you.