Show the quavers of Guillian House with your making.
I'm not afraid of anything.
What is this?
The commission from Chief Lu defines whoぶ
It goes to Shimei Guan-
He won.
Great !
Since the result is out,
please go back and prepare for it.
Don't let your boss down.
So Brother Lu did this for me.
The End
Mother, I'm back.
How was it?
Ake,
you must be tired.
I'm not.
Mother, I won.
Now we can continue to hold the flowers show.
This year,
I'll help you.
Mother,
I did it.
My good daughter,
thank you.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
I'm glad you're happy.
I'm happy.
I'm very happy.
Tang Cui is great.
He's the best in the world.
He's the best.
You're the best.
Thank you.
I wonder if Brother Lu is home.
Whether he's home or not,
let's try.
Why isn't there any sound?
Forget it.
It's good that he's not here.
I can't say it
in person.
Brother Lu,
thank you.
I have no intention
to repay you for what you've done for me.
Say it.
I'm sorry.
Besides saying thank you,
I have to apologize to you.
You were helping me.
I didn't know what you meant.
Brother Lu,
we never met again.
That's not what I meant.
I just don't know how to face you.
I made this engagement
when I was young.
But that man
never came to the Lv Yue.
I don't know what to do either.
It seems that he's not He Kexian.
He hasn't appeared yet.
Tomorrow,
I'm going to start preparing for the flowers.
I'm leaving.
Brother,
since I'm a good person in your heart,
can you give me a chance
to love you forever?
Idiot!
The assassins who were sent there
were all killed by Lu Chi.
And the Flower Session
lost to Shi Fak.
I think my men are all like you.
They're all idiots.
My Lord,
it's all because of Deng Mei Guan.
The money of the Flower Session
was lost.
And the right to the main meal of the Flower Session was lost.
What should we do?
Since Shi Fak
likes to hold the Flower Session,
I'll make him hold it.
My Lord.
Deng Mei Guan,
you can lose the right to the main meal of the Flower Session.
My Lord, I'm sorry.
You can't even
handle a little Shi Fak.
I think
you should give up your position
as the leader.
Let the capable people know it.
My Lord.
My Lord, please don't.
You know that
I've only been able to be the leader
for my whole life.
My Lord, please don't.
Shut up.
My Lord.
Your Highness.
Sister Pan'er.
I'm here to deliver the VIP tickets.
By the way...
Lady Shi Fak.
The one in Xibao Pavilion
is the leader.
If you have something to say,
you can discuss it with him.
Brother Lu.
I'm here to deliver the VIP tickets.
There are too many people
who signed up for the ceremony.
Only when you get the tickets
can you discuss it with Lady Shi Fak.
Everyone can come to Xibao Pavilion to get the tickets.
It can also increase the popularity
of Xibao Pavilion.
Okay.
I'll tell Manager Li
to take good care of everyone.
I'll send someone
to send the money to your Guanmei Hall today.
So much money is put in Guanmei Hall.
It might cause trouble.
If there are goods in Xibao Pavilion,
we can go to sell them.
If there are none,
we can ask the official to buy them.
Then we can ask Brother Lu to sell them.
What do you think?
It's better to think about it in the Ake Temple.
Then Brother Lu,
please sit in Guanmei Hall for a few days.
It won't be a trouble.
Let's go.
What?
Although the Flower Session is run by Shi Fak,
I'm the handmaiden.
All the accounts
should be checked by me.
You don't have to
bother about the accounts.
This time, the news is true.
All the things I bought
are checked by Xibao Pavilion
and the number of tickets.
Then we can compare the balance and the price of the goods.
This can prevent corruption
and save people's lives.
Shi Fak, you...
Handmaiden,
you don't know
the accounts of the Flower Session.
You don't have to bother about it.
What did you say?
Colleagues,
if you buy the goods,
please take out the balance.
After we get together,
we can go to Xibao Pavilion to get the money.
Thank you for your efforts for the Flower Session.
I won't treat you badly.
Anyone who goes to Xibao Pavilion to get the money
will get free tea.
Thank you, Chief Lu.
Come on.
Wait a while.
Airy and not greasy.
Your good luck is unparalleled.
Good for you.
Just buy the 280 catties.
Tiantian,
my brother has covered the hard drive.
I'll just go to Xiebao Pavilion and get the money.
So much money?
This is what I deserve.
I can't let you spend money again and again.
You're so generous, Chief Lu.
Young Master, what book are you reading?
We have four books here.
All of them are from the ancient times.
Boss, which one of your books
is the best seller?
Speaking of books,
it should be the one next door.
But he hasn't released a new chapter
in the last month.
The reader is waiting for a hard time.
I'm also involved.
I've burned a lot of bricks.
It's hard indeed.
I'm suffering because of the important things.
I'm suffering,
and so are the people.
You're a crazy person
waiting for the book of the next door.
Boss, are the new chapters here?
Little nun, why are you here in person?
Just write a list of books you like
and send it to me.
I can send it to my house.
Boss, I haven't read the book
of the next door for a long time.
I read some of the books
and I only think about the new chapters of the next door.
The next door
has to be published in a month.
How about this?
It's a book of the next door.
It's good.
No need.
I only read the book of the next door.
Boss, if the new chapters are here,
send it to my house.
Don't worry.
As long as the new chapters are published,
I'll send it to the house of the next door.
Let's go.
Take care.
I didn't expect this little nun
to be so beautiful
and have such a good taste.
Look.
This is real.
Yes.
It's worth it.
Look, this color is so beautiful.
It's really good.
Go and ask around.
I haven't seen it.
This is really good.
It's really good.
It's also sold out.
I'm so relieved.
This is really good.
It's really good.
Young Master,
would you like to see
the new products of our Xibao Pavilion
and send them to your family?
Pearl, jade, jade, and jade.
Send them to the young lady.
Earrings, necklace, hairpins.
We have everything we need.
Your Master...
That's not a coincidence.
Our Master is not here.
If you have something important,
you can keep your name.
It's good that he's not here.
Shopkeeper Li, go ahead.
Make me some good tea.
I want the
snow-covered cold drink.
You know who the Master is
and you're not afraid of him?
You know my surname is Shen Ming Shui.
But I'm not his face.
The snow-covered cold drink
was delivered three days ago.
In the capital,
other than me and the Master,
even Lu Yi might not know.
Who is this person
in front of me?
Who is this person?
Oh no.
I saw the snow-covered cold drink
in the secret report.
I accidentally
lost my mouth.
So, the Xibao Pavilion
doesn't have such good tea.
It's said that
Xibao Pavilion has countless rare treasures.
It seems that
it's true.
That's not true.
But
even if the Master wants to drink it,
he has to be the Master.
What do you mean?
I have many people.
But I can't guess
the snow-covered cold drink.
After all, there are often
people from Xibao Pavilion
to make trouble.
But
the jade belt
is made by Xibao Pavilion.
There are two pairs in total.
One for the Master
and one for the Master.
Master,
you went down the mountain without permission.
Does the Master know?
Manager Li,
please don't say that.
Of course, my brother doesn't know.
I haven't figured out
how to tell him.
I came here
to find out the truth.
I don't know what happened.
Brother, how are you?
Tell me.
Why did you go down the mountain without permission?
I can't see you on the mountain.
I'm really worried about your safety.
So I went down the mountain to find you.
It's only a ten-day journey from Mount Qianya to the capital.
Why did you show up today?
Brother,
the capital is so prosperous
and fun.
It's beyond my expectation.
I was delayed for a few days.
Brother, I'm here.
I...
We don't have to separate anymore.
Master,
the jade light used by the Flower-picking Society
is a sample.
Lu Yi?
Long time no see.
It's from the Second Master.
Lu Yi, why are you hiding?
I finally escaped from
this evil hand of the Xiao Clan.
The Flower-picking Society?
What is the Flower-picking Society?
The Flower-picking Society
is a garden party held by the Guanmei Hall
for single men and women.
Manager Li,
say it again.
Xibao Pavilion
is going to inaugurate the Flower-picking Society this year.
By then,
the young ladies and gentlemen of the capital
will come to the garden to play
and hope to find someone in their dreams.
What is the jade light for?
The jade light is customized by the Shimei Pass
for the Flower-picking Society.
It's for the Flower-picking Society.
The Shimei Pass?
Who is the Shimei Pass?
The Shimei Pass is...
The Flower-picking Society
sounds like a fun place.
I want to go too.
Stay here and reflect on your mistakes.
You're not allowed to leave this place.
I don't want to.
Brother,
I want to go to the Flower-picking Society.
The jade light is sent to the garden.
It will be sent to the garden in a few days.
Shimei Pass,
this is our master.
He asked us to make it for you.
That's great.
This is exactly what I want.
Brother Lu,
you really did it.
It's good that A'he likes it.
Our master not only did it,
but also did it in such a short time.
I wonder if the intention behind it is...
Manager Li.
Brother Lu,
thank you so much.
I've already tried the jade light.
I'll have to trouble Sister Pan'er
to send it to the manor.
But the jade light is broken.
It's crowded and busy.
I have to find someone who is reliable and considerate
to help Sister Pan'er.
Who do you think is reliable and considerate?
Speaking of someone who is reliable and considerate,
it's my brother.
But the government is busy.
I wonder if he...
I think so too.
I think
Brother Lu will definitely help us.
After all, it's all for the flower show.
Then I'll ask my brother to help us.
Thank you, Sister.
I suddenly remembered
that there are other things in the room.
I'll get back to work.
Brother Lu.
Do you think Sister Pan'er...
Ke.
Actually, that day,
I...
Chief.
Chief, it's me.
The wedding cake at He Ji has been prepared.
That's great.
Brother Xian has helped me a lot.
And He Ji has prepared
so many wedding cakes in a few days.
Brother Lu.
This is the VIP ticket for the flower show.
I left it for you.
I'll go check the goods first.
Take it.
Really?
It's for me?
Thank you, Chief.
I can go to the flower show too.
Chief, this is mine.
Give it back to me.
You can take it if you want.
I won't.
Give it to me.
Brother.
Recently, the flower show has ordered a batch of jade.
It's easy to break.
I want to invite you to Xibao Pavilion tomorrow
to help Manager Li.
Are you free?
I... I'm free.
It's my sister's order.
I must do it well, right?
Brother Xian is busy with the flower show recently.
I don't think he can make it.
I'll go help him tomorrow.
Brother, you're not right.
Mother usually tells you to work,
but you just run away.
Why are you so active today?
Brother and Sister Tang.
Uncle and Aunt asked you why you're still awake.
Sleep.
I'll sleep now.
I'm going to Xibao Pavilion tomorrow morning
to help Manager Li move things.
You should rest early too.
Ke.
I'm going to sleep too.
Sister Tang, you should rest early too.
did not emoji
R riots, do검
Really?
Ever since I became the organizer for the flower show,
every moment
feels like a dream.
It's różnych that solely making troubles within life
and the world watching this one esaase the heart.
These are things that should not be knew.
Why are you still awake?
Mother, I'm praying for the ancestors' blessings
to make the flowers come back to life.
Do you feel
uneasy now?
You're even in a daze.
You're like dreaming every day.
Mother, how do you know?
I'm also from the same family.
My daughter is the most obedient
and the most excellent rose.
You're very generous
and you know how to change.
I believe
you can make the flowers come back to life.
Mother, I understand.
I'm the organizer of the flowers coming back to life.
I owe it to the people who helped me.
Brother Xian,
Tiantian,
Manager Li,
and...
Brother Lu.
You helped us before.
You should thank them.
You'll finish your work tomorrow
and come back early.
We'll hold a ceremony to thank them.
Then we'll invite Keqian, Ketian,
Chief Lu, and Manager Li
to come to our house.
After the ceremony, we'll have a meal.
I'll express my gratitude
on behalf of the Shi family.
Okay.
Miss Huarui,
here's a bouquet for you.
You are very beautiful.
I can smell the fragrance from your breath.
It's delicious.
And now I just need a little bit more.
And I'll check again.
No problem.
So easy.
I... I'm going to clean up now.
Thank you.
That's good.
Hey.
You have to take the drug.
What do you want me to do?
I need to clean up.
I'm sorry.
Brother Lu,
have you known
my brother and Sister Pan'er long ago?
I only got a few points
from Manager Li's expression.
So I asked Brother Shi to help me.
When Brother Shi came,
I only went to the others
to give them some opportunities.
But whether it can be done
depends on them.
Brother Lu,
you're really a good girl.
Sister Pan'er is pretty and capable.
She's a good match
with my silly brother.
If they're interested,
I'll definitely help them.
All these years,
Manager Li has been
managing the Xibao Pavilion alone.
I also hope
she can find a good family member.
Brother has found me.
Brother has been acting strange lately.
He's always been running to the He family.
Brother is smart and interesting.
He's a good man.
He's a good match
with Lady He.
No, no.
Brother Lu,
Tian Tian has a engagement.
Don't make any mistakes.
Have you asked Lady He
if she really likes him?
Does she have an engagement with him?
Does she know him?
Does she want to
marry Lady He?
It's an urgent agreement.
How can the engagement
be changed at will?
It's just that if they meet someone
who's more suitable, they'll break off the engagement.
Tian Tian can't do that.
What about the one who has an engagement with you?
Do you know each other?
Do you like each other?
I...
I'm going to get Tian Tian married
and then help two brothers
marry their sister-in-law.
I'm not in a hurry.
I'll wait for that man to come to the engagement.
Brother Lu,
don't talk about me.
The Baihua Society is in a hurry.
The official business is important.
Today, our family worships our ancestors.
My mother was invited to a banquet
and asked me to
invite you and Manager Li to come.
I want to thank you.
I'll go prepare some gifts now.
I'll definitely visit you on time.
Okay.
Brother, do you like him?
Is it that obvious?
You almost got a red envelope
and everyone knew it.
But Ake didn't know.
Then you have to listen to
my good words.
As a woman,
you should first take the initiative
and be decisive.
Then,
you have to show yourself.
Thirdly,
you have to seek help from others.
What should I do?
You have to seize the opportunity
to go to dinner this time
and please your parents-in-law.
Let them care about you.
Besides,
talk about the official business more when you eat.
This way,
you'll be more stable
and reliable.
Really?
Yes.
Boss,
the Junshanji from the next mountain,
have you got the goods?
How's the sale?
The Junshanji is in stock.
The Book Service only sent the goods this morning.
How did you know?
Are you...
I'm...
A colleague.
I guessed right.
You're a colleague.
Listen,
colleagues are enemies.
Don't steal my business.
Boss, I'm here to get the books.
Don't call me a double.
Come on.
Follow me.
I'm here to buy the books.
I heard that the Junshanji is in stock.
I don't know when I can buy it.
You like the people from the next mountain?
I like your books the most.
I'll read them all over again.
If the Junshanji arrives,
I'll buy a lot of books
and keep them at home.
Do you like the people from the next mountain?
I'm...
Miss,
we've paid the money.
Let's go back.
Uncle, auntie,
I'm here to give you a gift.
Don't laugh.
Is this for me?
Uncle,
I...
I'm Mengmeng.
Brother.
Thank you.
I have one, too.
Happy now?
Take a breath.
Hi, Brother.
We've moved tickets.
How's the shooting?
Great.
You have a large allotment.
Do you want money now or later?
No.
I don't have money.
Please
Brother, sit here
Come, sit
I want to thank Master Lu and Shopkeeper Li
Xian and Tiantian
are all invited to the flowers show
Shopkeeper Li is working hard for the show
Xian and Tiantian are also doing their best
I'm so grateful for their support
We have nothing to repay them
Come, let's have a drink
I want to thank you too
Thank you, Xian and Tiantian
And Lu
Master Lu
You are so generous
You are the host of the flowers show
You have done so many glazes in a short time
Thank you, Xibao, Pan'er and Lu Yi
They are all helping me
Just for the show
Thank you
Thank you, Aunt Tao and Ake
Ake is leading the show
He is the host
It's my pleasure to meet Ake
I'm so grateful for your appreciation
Xibao has to thank the guards
for promoting us
Ake is so smart and thoughtful
I'm afraid that the flowers show
will be too lively and exciting
Brother Lu, thank you again
I want to thank Brother Lu
for giving me the privilege
to be the host this time
Manager Li, you have worked hard this time
I heard from the boss
that you arranged the flowers show
I didn't expect that
you are not only beautiful
but also capable
Brother Shi is steady and capable
Thanks to him, Xibao
has helped me a lot
He did all the dirty and tiring work
I'm not tired
Brother Xian, Tiantian
I know
If it weren't for you
Ake couldn't have done
such a big thing
Come on, I thank you
Aunt Tao, you are too kind
Ake grew up with me
He is like a family
Ake's business is my business
The Shi family's business
is also the business of our He family
Okay, let's eat
Don't be polite
Yes
Ake, this is your favorite
I'll put it here
Thank you, Brother Xian
Brother Lu, try this
It's delicious
Thanks
Tiantian, try the fish
Brother Xian, don't you like fish?
Tiantian, eat more
Manager Li, this is very delicious
Try it
Thanks, Brother Shi
Manager Li, I'm sorry
You are young
and beautiful
Do you have a match?
Thank you for your concern
I...
To be honest
Xianfu has died for many years
He has never had a match
in these years
I'm a matchmaker
But I don't think
women are only meant to marry
As long as they don't indulge in old-fashioned business
No matter you marry or not
as long as you feel happy
Of course
Manager Li is kind and beautiful
He will be happy
Yes, Sister Pan'er
Life is impermanent
If you meet someone you like
you will be happy
I'm not a woman
I'm a woman
If you meet someone you like
you will be happy
Thank you for your gift
I know the reason
But it's not easy
Manager Li
I think Ake is right
You are kind and beautiful
You will find your happiness
I...
Brother Xian
I also left you
the VIP tickets for the flowers show
You can check
if you have a woman you like
I...
Ake
I don't need the VIP tickets
because they are limited
You are old enough to get married
You should think about it
Ake
My brother won't
go to the flower show to find someone
He...
Since it's from Ake
I'll take it
Thank you, Ake
By the way
Brother
I'll give you a toast
Thank you for taking care of Sister Tianting
these days
Brother Xian, you're welcome
I should do this
I should give you a toast too
Thank you for your help
I know
You've always
treated me like your own sister
No
Yes
Why is Brother Xian so weird?
Everyone
I believe Ake
can hold the flower show
successfully and successfully
Let's make a toast to him
Come on
Thank you
A toast to Ake
Okay
Don't just drink and talk
Eat more
Come on, eat
Thank you
Brother
Why are you still up so late?
Did I wake you up?
No
I couldn't sleep
It's probably because
the weather is too hot
You always say
you want to eat mung bean cake
Well
I'll make some
Then you can eat some
and send some to Aunt Tao
Okay
Thank you
Send some to Aunt Tao
Okay?
Brother
Actually, we can see
what we've done today
Aunt Tao and Uncle
treat us like their own
Especially Uncle
Yes
Aunt Tao and our He family
have been friends for decades
It's not like Lu Chi
can win the country
with some money
It's just
Look at the situation
Ke seems quite close
with Lu Chi
Brother
You grew up with Ke
講婚價之事呢
It should be
taken from the elders
Of course they can choose
a perfectly man to be their wife
How about shameful parents?
In our times
even though
we had brothers from the Family Si
before the relationship
they still promised
to get married
under the terms of
a relationship
We all know
I just want to be a scholar
and hope that I can join the Shu Xiang family.
Even if I don't want to,
I still have to listen to my parents.
I know.
I know that Uncle and Aunt Tao are very protective.
The marriage arrangements arranged by my parents won't be wrong.
I also believe that Uncle and Aunt Tao
will choose a family that knows the roots and the roots.
Okay, Tian Tian.
Hurry and rest. It's getting late.
When you wake up tomorrow morning, you'll have good food.
Okay.
Then you should rest early too.
Manager Li, I think what Aunt Tao said today is very true.
You've worked hard to get the Xibao Pavilion for so many years.
It's also good that I asked Ake to find you a loyal person.
Thank you for your consideration.
It's just that I don't know if I can still meet someone who is loyal.
This loyal person, is he loyal to me?
If fate has brought us together, I will definitely go and disturb Junior Sister.
I believe that you will definitely meet her.
Why don't you look at the people around you?
Chief, I'll go back and rest first.
Luo Yi, you are crazy!
Brother.
Luo Yi, you are not a maid. Why are you being so pushy?
Brother, how is the food?
It's not good enough that the He family is also going.
Oh.
So, you didn't see your father-in-law alone.
It seems that the Shi family is thankful to you,
but if they treat you as their son-in-law, I'm afraid that there is still a gap.
You are not the best candidate for being their only son-in-law.
Brother, you must work harder.
Do you have any method?
The best way is to just give it a try.
The Flower Session is the most important thing for Auntie Tao.
You must help Shi Mei Guan to hold the Flower Session well.
You must do it with a different mindset.
Naturally, you won't be able to get the love of your future mother-in-law.
And then?
You must be more proactive. You must be able to make a decision.
Of course. If the Flower Session is held well,
and Auntie Tao still doesn't like you, then...
Then what?
Then... it's just that she simply doesn't like you.
What I mean is that a mother should look at her son-in-law more,
and compare him more, and make a more careful decision.
But what is done is done.
I believe that you will be able to successfully move your future mother-in-law's heart.
Really?
Don't worry, Brother. I will definitely help you marry Sister-in-law.
Come.
This is so beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
Come here.
Little Madam Wang, please come in.
Welcome.
Mr. Zhang, please come in.
Please come in.
Thank you.
It's all in.
Please come in.
Little Ladies, you all dressed up today.
It's so beautiful.
Yes. Let's go. Let's go over and look for him.
Little Ladies, you're here.
Little Ladies, you're so beautiful today.
Little Ladies, you're also beautiful.
Come. Let's go.
I was a Taoist. Now, I'm a Shifang.
Can I never truly have Guan Mei Ting?
I can never win her over.
Thank you.
Little Ladies, you're here.
Please come in.
Grandfather.
Young Master, please come in.
Please come in.
Thank you for coming, Little Ladies.
You're welcome.
Ah Ke, your dress is so beautiful.
And your hairstyle is very trendy.
I feel like you're different from before.
Am I?
Grandfather, your dress is also very pretty.
It's not because I listened to you.
I was asked to go to Xibao Pavilion to customize it.
Oh, right. After I mentioned your name,
Head Li even gave me a discount.
Speaking of this, I have to thank you.
Where's Tiantian?
Brother Lu.
This is...
This is my younger brother, Lu Zhu Xi.
This is the organizer of the Flower Session, Shi Mei Guan.
Oh? You're Shi Mei Guan?
I know this encounter is the secret of fate
Every time I see you, I only have a lovely stubbornness
Although I can't remember every single word
I can't remember every single word
I never forget the first time I saw you
Even if there's no star, no sky, no sun, no night
It doesn't matter if it's windy or cold
As long as you're never afraid, never shy, never worried
Never worried about the
No matter in this world or in the other
Whether there will be any border
I'm willing to protect you with my life
Even if I can't remember every single word
No matter in this world or in the other
I'm willing to protect you with my life
The sky is always looking at you
Even if the sky is blue or blue
It doesn't matter if it's the same as before
Please remember the youth that was once so pure
From now on, I don't want to part with you