Chinese TV Series Exclusive YouTube
I'm not afraid of anything.
The flowers are in the branches.
The strange years.
I don't know
I don't know if you have a care.
Some people
If you want to repay
But there is no way to do it.
A lifetime of love
Is the best way.
A Long Time No See
The Legend of Qingcheng
Episode 1
A-Kong, it's okay.
I'm here.
I didn't save Danyi.
I'm sorry.
You've done your best.
Don't blame yourself.
Brother Lu.
And Yan Yan.
Let's go find them.
Don't worry.
Zhou Xi hasn't come out yet.
But she's innocent.
Maybe she has found
Zhu's wife
and went to a safe place.
Where are they?
I'll take you to find them.
Hurry.
Come on.
Let me carry you.
Mr. Lu.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
I'm fine.
Where is this?
Will the fire
burn over in a while?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
I'll carry you.
Go ahead.
You should be able to get out soon.
Brother Lu.
Thank you for today.
Without you,
I don't know
how things will develop.
Your responsibility
is to protect the people
who attend the meeting.
And my responsibility
is to protect you.
I'll be with you
and protect you.
Don't look at me.
I look ugly when I cry.
If you don't look ugly,
I'll treat Ake
as the most beautiful person
and my favorite person.
I'll protect you
and keep you from getting hurt.
I'll let you live a peaceful life
and live a happy life.
Why are you saying these?
I'm not saying these out of the blue.
I've been telling you all the time.
Yanyan.
Ake.
Brother Lu.
Yanyan.
You're okay.
That's great.
I'm so scared.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't move.
Be careful not to hurt your wound.
I'll take you to the doctor.
Let's go.
It's okay.
He's out.
Brother Lu is out.
Ake.
It seems to be fine.
Brother Lu.
Sister Tao.
Are you okay?
Master.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
We're fine.
Ake.
Did you see Deng Meiguan?
He's the only one left now.
I've been looking for him everywhere.
He's not here.
I can't find him anywhere.
Deng Yi is
no longer here.
We went to the fire station to save him.
But it's too late
to check on him.
How could this happen?
Master.
I've checked on him.
Except Deng Meiguan,
all the other people who met him
have escaped.
Thank you.
Thank you, Master.
Thank you for saving us.
You're welcome.
As long as you're safe.
Go.
Take Shifak away.
Yes.
I...
General Li.
What do you mean?
The smoke is so strong here.
It's a big fire in the city.
Shifak.
As the organizer of the Flower Session,
you're here to kill someone.
Shouldn't you be obedient?
General.
The Fire of Flower Session
is to catch the person who set the fire.
But you caught an innocent Meiguan.
It's not reasonable.
How dare you talk like that?
General Li.
I'm hosting the Flower Session
when the fire happened.
Everyone here can testify for me.
What evidence do you have?
I'm the one who set the fire.
There must be a reason for the fire.
You're lying.
It's better to lie than to be guilty.
You'll know it after you go back
and take the investigation.
I'm not afraid of the shadow.
I've never done it.
I can take your investigation.
But I'm telling you.
If you dare to hurt anyone here,
I'll sue you to death.
General Li.
There's a court case.
The security of the guards is under investigation.
Why did the General's Office
send soldiers to catch the person?
Are you going to ignore the rules
and take the responsibility?
Lu Chi.
Shifake.
The Flower Session has a big mistake.
As the organizer,
shouldn't you take the responsibility?
The Xibao Flower Session
is funded by the Xibao Pavilion.
Lu Chi.
You're also guilty.
Yes.
I'm the organizer.
I do have a responsibility.
I'll go back with you for the investigation.
Ke.
No.
Since you said so,
come on.
Take her away.
Who dares?
I'm a witness.
I can testify for Ke.
Yanyan.
I'm the granddaughter of Prime Minister Zhu,
Zhu Yanyan.
I saw it with my own eyes.
It's the fire of Deng Meiguan.
I can prove that it has nothing to do with them.
You...
It's not fair.
It's not enough to prove.
This waist is
from Deng Shoumei.
I witnessed her burning the Flower Session.
I can testify.
I saved Madam Zhu from the fire.
Where is Deng Shoumei?
Tell her to come out and confront.
Deng Shoumei
has been buried in the fire.
Are you trying to blame
a dead person?
You...
I think Deng Shoumei's death
has nothing to do with you.
What's the truth?
We'll talk about it in court.
Guards, take her away.
Yes.
You can't take her away.
Grandfather, what are you doing?
Grandfather.
You can't take her away.
What are you doing?
Get down.
Grandfather.
Yanyan, are you hurt?
I'm not hurt.
Grandfather,
help Ke to justice.
I saw
Deng Shoumei
burning the meeting place.
General Li
insisted on asking Ke for justice.
Yanyan, don't worry.
Prime Minister Zhu, take care.
General Li,
this case should be handed over to Fuya.
Which law
do you follow to take the body away?
Guards, take her away.
Prime Minister Zhu is right.
I was too hasty.
So this case
should be handed over to Fuya.
Let's go.
Great.
It's okay.
Grandfather is here.
Thank you, Prime Minister Zhu.
Thank you all for
helping me
when I was in danger.
Thank you for your kindness.
Please go back and have a rest.
Thank you.
Thank you, Chief Guard.
Brother, I have something to do.
I'll go first.
You...
Slow down.
Ke, don't be sad.
Liu De and Qingshan are here.
It's not a lie.
This is my first time
hosting the flowers show.
Ke,
we'll hold
a bigger one next year.
Yes.
I'll go every day.
I support you.
Okay.
It's a deal.
Brother, if you're tired,
send Officer Li back to have a rest.
Okay.
Brother, your foot is injured.
I'll send them back first.
Luo,
if you send Tiantian,
who will send Ke?
I'll send him.
Brother, look.
They'll send me back.
Don't worry.
Officer Li, please.
Let's go.
Brother,
your leg is badly injured.
You need to be treated.
Luo,
send Boss He back to have a rest.
The best doctor will take care of him.
No need.
I can send Ke back.
Boss He, don't force yourself.
If you don't treat your wound in time,
you'll get sick.
Brother,
Luo is right.
You need to be treated.
If you're free,
I'll go to Heji to see you and Tiantian.
Don't worry.
Qin, Luo,
please.
Go.
Sister, don't worry.
I'll go.
Let's go.
Brother Luo,
we're walking so slowly.
When will we get home?
Not yet.
The slower, the better.
Brother Luo,
thank you.
The more beautiful the flowers are,
the less regretful I'll be.
I see the flowers in the branches.
Brother Luo,
you're injured.
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
I'll go.
What's the matter?
Brother Luo,
from now on,
I'll be with you,
protect you,
and be with you.
Luo,
thank you for bringing my sister back.
It's getting late.
I won't invite you to tea.
Brother Luo,
Tiantian is waiting for us.
Don't worry.
Go in.
Go.
Don't let anyone else worry.
I'll go in first.
I wonder how he is now.
Who is it?
Lian Yan, it's me.
Are you okay?
Every time I meet you,
I can be a flower in the wind.
I'm also recalling
the fear you've unleashed.
I thought I was not meant to be.
Our fate has been destined.
Why are you here?
I secretly escorted you back.
I'm worried about you.
I'm waiting at the roof.
I'm a little worried about you.
So you...
You've been at the roof?
Did you walk too fast?
Did you get a cold?
I'm fine.
Are you hurt anywhere?
How's your injury?
I'm fine.
I'm afraid you were scared last night.
I'm a little worried.
So I came to ask you.
You're so silly.
This is the medicine for my special injury.
Here you go.
You prepared the medicine for me?
Hurry up.
Remember to apply the medicine on time.
Okay, I'm leaving.
You're useless.
How can you forgive me for my incompetence?
I'm killing you now.
Can you solve the problem?
It's all Zhu Xiangyang and Zhu Yan Yan's fault.
If so,
who blocked your way
should pay the price.
Do I have to teach you this?
Yes.
I understand.
I'm so angry.
It's here.
It's Deng Mei Guan who set the fire.
He didn't do anything good
but set the fire in the department store.
Is he crazy?
I've been working with him
in the official media office for more than ten years.
I know he's very angry
with me and the world's first Mei.
But I didn't expect
he would be so confused.
He wasn't a big villain.
He was just too stubborn
and he didn't do anything right.
Congratulations.
I envy you.
You're so lucky.
Shu,
what do you mean?
Nothing.
I just envy you.
I envy you for being born in the world's first Mei
and studying in the Cloud Garden.
We Mei Guan
can't compare to you in our whole life.
Shu,
it's just a responsibility
to be the Mei Guan.
It's about leading the Mei Guan
to fulfill the wishes of the people.
Well said.
I wonder
if I'll be able to do that
in my whole life.
I look ugly when I cry.
Not ugly.
I think Ake is the most beautiful person
and my favorite person.
I'll always protect you
and keep you safe
so that you can spend your whole life
in peace and happiness.
Ake,
from now on,
let me be with you,
protect you,
and be with you.
Shu,
you...
Ake,
you must be tired.
Go back to your room and rest.
Daughter,
are you scared?
Why are you laughing?
You two little rascals,
where are you going?
Where are you going?
We're not going.
If you don't come back with Ake,
how can I tell you?
Father,
don't scold them.
I asked Brother to send Manager Li.
Tian Tian and Brother Xian got hurt.
Ake also went to send them.
They've been working all night.
Father and Mother,
you should rest.
We'll go to rest too.
Go, go, go.
You two little rascals,
you're not familiar with each other.
I'm here.
Come on.
I'll go and get you some food.
Go.
What are you doing?
Mother.
I cannot rest assured of you. I came to visit you.
Today, I made you feel wronged.
There are so many people talking for me. I won't feel wronged anymore.
Mother, in the past, I wanted the label the most,
Because when I saw you wear it, you were very bright.
But now I know that the world's first beauty is not only honor,
but also responsibility.
The beauty is done. The beauty is done.
I only wanted you to remember these eight words first.
When you grow up,
you will understand and shoulder the responsibility.
I didn't think you would understand so quickly.
Ake, if you want to continue walking down this path,
you will surely meet people of all kinds and dangers.
If that's the case, are you still willing to continue?
I am your daughter and the most important successor in the world.
Even if there is no way, I will still find a way.
You are good at saying big words.
But on this path, your father, mother, big brother, second brother,
we will all accompany you and continue walking together.
Yes. And Brother Lu too.
He will accompany me and protect me and help me solve all kinds of problems.
Is that so?
Mother, actually Brother Lu has been helping me.
Yesterday, the flowers were so big.
Ake, you must be hungry.
I will tell them to make you something delicious.
Mother.
Jin hall
You came out after getting hurt?
I just hurt my head.
Your back injury has not been healed yet.
Just rest for a few days.
I've asked Lu Yi to go to the pharmacy
to get the medicine for a fever.
Thank you, brother.
Master.
Come in.
Master, are you okay?
I'm fine.
The fire of the Hundred Flower Society
is not a small matter.
Now that Deng Meiguan is dead,
the Queen of Five will certainly find another way to deal with it.
Ake has repeatedly destroyed his plan.
The Queen of Five will definitely not let him off.
Lu Yi,
keep an eye on Ake
and ensure his safety.
Yes.
At this time,
I have to remind that person
to make an early decision.
Brother,
there are so many medicines.
I can't finish them all by myself.
This bottle is for you.
I'll send the rest to Ake.
You...
You're so
I can only say it
to make him more worried.
It's not my nature.
This Wan Hu Lu.
It seems that I have to help him.
Zhu Xi.
Don't be a fool.
I'm not.
Brother, don't wrong me.
Brother Lu is so good to me.
I'm also very happy.
I can't just be distracted.
I have to find the person who has an engagement with me first
and explain it clearly.
Brother Lu.
Could it be Brother Lu?
Ake.
Brother Lu.
How many young concubines did Brother Lu
meet by tão time
to greet you at the LOL meal?
I don't want to talk about them carefully.
But I'm afraid that I'll be re eighth to
meet you in person.
If it was our sometime long time ago,
I wouldn't be able to meet Ake at all.
Why don't you get in first
since I don't want to make things worse.
I'm here to deliver your medicine.
You must have absorbed a lot of opium
in your fire field today.
There are some medicine for the lung,
some medicine for the heat,
and some medicine for calming your mind.
So many medicines?
Thank you, Brother Lu.
You're so nice to me.
Ke.
I'm sorry.
Actually, today I still...
Brother Lu.
I...
I have a doubt.
What is it?
Yesterday, Deng Yi said
he was involved in the trap.
It means someone instigated him to set fire.
That's right.
Who could it be?
He's so ruthless.
He instigated Deng Yi to set fire.
And why did he stay in the fire
after he set fire?
Actually, I met a man in black yesterday.
I think
it's the chief behind the scene
who sent someone to kill Deng Mei.
Then,
who's behind the scene?
Wu An Hou.
Wu An Hou?
My mother rejected his request before.
Is this the bad news?
Tao Shou Mei is the best in the world.
She has achieved countless wishes.
You should have known it
when you were in the base.
I was so worried.
I knew
that no matter how many officials
would come to the door
to congratulate Tao Shou Mei's daughter.
That's the wish
my mother has made countless times.
Does Wu An Hou
want to control Guan Mei Ting
through my mother
and control the marriage
of these people through Guan Mei Ting?
Yes.
He wants to grow up
his career
through Guan Mei Ting.
He pulled Tao Shou Mei's tail
and helped Deng Mei.
But you broke his plan
again and again.
He was so cruel to you.
Even if he can't burn you to death,
he can make you suffer.
It's so horrible.
No wonder my mother said
this road is not easy to walk.
So that's what it means.
Ke.
Are you afraid?
How can I be afraid?
I want him to see
that the first few bones in our world
are not so easy to be cut off.
I won't allow Guan Mei Ting
to be sacrificed by others.
Ke.
You are so brave.
I will protect you.
Thank you, Brother Lu.
Actually, I...
Tang.
Are you asleep?
Come on.
Hide.
This way.
Hurry.
Tang.
I'm here.
Aunt made some ginseng soup.
I'll bring it to you.
Just leave it there.
I'll drink it later.
Tang.
Why are you standing by the window?
I'm hot.
I'm cool.
Go to have a rest.
Lu...
It's too late.
You should go to bed early.
You should go to bed early too.
See you tomorrow.
Close the door.
Don't get cold.
Okay.
I'm drunk.
Ke.
You came early to clean up?
Deng Yi used to come early.
He used to clean up.
Now Deng Yi is gone.
I'll clean up.
It's a pity that Deng Shoumei
is so smart.
But he doesn't understand.
I've been in Guanmei Hall for years.
I know he doesn't like your mother.
But I didn't expect
he could do such a stupid thing.
Forget it.
He's gone.
My mother was sad for him last night.
Ke.
You and your mother are good people.
By the way,
Zhao Meiguan.
This is the official document from the government office.
The protest is about to start this year.
Don't waste money.
The government office will register all men
who are not married yet
at their age.
If that's the case...
Guanmei Hall Lawyer, please take the invitation.
Yes.
Why did he take it?
It's so early.
What's the matter?
Ke.
This is yours, too.
Here you are.
Ke.
You're the famous person in Guanmei Hall now.
Everyone.
I have a favor to ask you.
So many invitations to Shoumei Hall.
I can't do it alone.
If I do it alone,
I'm afraid it will delay the wedding of Xi Ke.
Our Guanmei Hall is a whole.
I hope everyone can get a invitation
and explain the situation clearly.
Then record the situation in Xi Ke's house
and the requirements.
We can do these invitations together.
We can share the money together.
It's great.
Thank you, Ke.
Here.
Take it.
It's yours.
Here.
So beautiful.
Mr. Shen.
I want to ask for your name.
We can share the name together.
This is my address and your name.
Please take care of the wedding.
Mr. Shen.
I like a young lady.
Mr. Shen, can you ask for my name?
Okay.
I want to ask you to do it for me, too.
I want you to do it for me, too.
Let me do it.
Everyone.
Listen to me.
Thank you for your kindness.
But there are so many plum trees.
I can't run here alone.
I'm afraid I'll be late for your wedding.
I've received your requests.
From today on,
we, Guanmei Tian,
will send an excellent plum official
to your house to record the wedding.
I'll be ready
to take you on a blind date.
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Give it to me.
Okay.
Ke is the most popular plum official
in the capital.
Brother Luo.
I've received so many requests for plum.
How do you plan to clear it?
I'll have two pieces of sweet and red bean paste every day.
Ke is now a backup.
When the plum is over,
the plum position is vacant.
Now you're one step closer to your dream.
Mr. Shen.
You're so young and so benevolent.
I think you're the only one
who can take the plum position.
Mr. Shen, please ask for my name, too.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Shen.
Is it plum?
Brother Luo.
Actually, I've thought about it.
It's not important
if I can be the plum.
Everyone loves to take care of our plum court.
Relying on us plum officials
is what makes me happy.
My dream
was to guard this plum court for my mother.
But now,
I want to guard this plum court
for myself and all the guests.
As long as I'm in the plum court,
I'll take the responsibility
and tell everyone
to guard this plum court.
Brother Luo.
I have work to do.
Wait for me.
Okay.
I'll go buy some sweet and red bean paste.
Come on.
Mr. Wang's marriage is so hard to say.
His information is...
Shi Wa Ke.
They're all here.
Is Shi Wa Ke here?
Shi Wa Ke.
Come here.
Come on.
Look.
They're all here.
Mr. Zhou.
What's the matter?
Tell me.
Well.
My marriage with Tiantian
is coming soon.
I saw the flowers show
you hosted.
It's good.
Not bad.
So I want you
to host the wedding for us.
Tiantian told me
you're best friends.
So she must be willing to host the wedding.
About the money,
you're in this relationship.
We're still talking about money.
Right?
You've been studying for more than ten years.
You're still young.
You're going to marry Yao Yi without a name.
What a coincidence.
The government is fighting for Yao Yi.
You're going to marry Tiantian.
I'm afraid no lady is willing to marry you.
That's why you're marrying Tiantian
to avoid Yao Yi, right?
So what?
We're engaged.
I can marry him as I want.
In that case,
I've prepared a marriage certificate for you.
Please sign it.
Here.
You're thoughtful.
Marriage certificate?
Who wants to get married?
Mr. Zhou.
I prepared this marriage certificate for you.
After you sign it,
you'll have nothing to do with Tiantian.
From now on, you'll be married
and have a good life.
Bullshit.
I'll never cancel the marriage.
I told you to cancel it.
Cancel it.
Fine.
Mr. Zhou.
You don't know the rules of our Guanmei Hall, do you?
You...
The marriage certificate of canceling the marriage
is as effective as
the official document of the Guanmei Hall.
I asked you to sign it to save your face.
Shiba Ke.
I'm here to teach you a lesson.
You think you can talk like a pig?
You...
A man
can't do that to a woman.
Let go of me.
Who are you? Let go of me.
Shi Meiguan.
How do you deal with this crazy man?
Cut his hand
or cut his leg?
Well...
I have to think about it.
Cut his hand
or cut his leg?
It's so hard for me to choose.
Say it.
We're all friends.
Shi Meiguan.
I know I'm wrong.
I'll sign it now.
Mr. Zhu.
Won't it be too hard?
No, no.
I'm willing to do it.
You just let him let me go.
I'll sign it now.
Take it away.
Sign it. Sign it.
I'll let you go.
Hurry.
Where's the pen?
You can bite your finger.
Let's press it together.
I...
No, no.
It's hard to bite my finger.
Hurry up.
I...
I'll bite it.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, Mr. Zhu.
When I sign the other one,
I'll send it to your home.
Get out.
Okay.
Thank you for your help.
By the way,
I'm going to send this to Tiantian.
Or you can go with me.
Okay.
Let's go.
Tiantian.
I'll help you with the engagement.
You're a beauty in the middle of life and death.
When Zhu Yizhi was in a big fire,
he left you alone to escape.
He's so cruel.
The engagement is important.
But the one who marries a woman who loves you and treats you well
is the most important.
I didn't expect that I couldn't keep my parents' engagement.
Tiantian.
I'll make the decision for you this time.
The happiness of your second half is the most important.
I hope
you can find someone you really like.
Brother.
I and Zhu Yizhi will break the engagement.
From now on,
I'll never be a part of this engagement
and neglect my happiness.
Tiantian.
Don't be afraid.
I'll find you a good wife.
I'll help you.
Okay.
I'm not
being controlled by an empty agreement.
Brother Lu.
People
shouldn't be so cold-hearted.
They should look at the people around them.
Come with me.
Okay.
Brother Lu.
Do you know why I brought you here?
This marriage tree is famous in the capital.
Rumor has it that the two names
are engraved on the stone
and the ribbon is hung on the tree.
Then it becomes a beautiful marriage.
I know this meeting
is the grace of fate.
Every time I see you,
I only feel the love and stubbornness.
Although I can't remember
every difficult day,
I never forget the first time
we met.
Even if love is endless,
never-ending,
no matter the wind or the moon,
as long as you are never gone,
I'll always be with you.
No matter the world or the fire,
I'll protect you with my life.
I used to be a human being
and I promised to follow my dream.
But now I know
marriage is not only about promises,
but also about love and hate.
There's fate and fate.
So today,
I'll return the marriage
between me and my brother to you.
No matter the world or the fire,
I'll always be with you.
Please remember the youth
I used to have.
I'll always be with you.
A man should not be left alone.
He should look at his surroundings.
So today,
I'll return the marriage
between me and my brother to you.
Brother.
It's been an hour already.
Did you make your promise?
What did I say?
Bloody!
Brother was infections for half an hour
before opening and servers are finished.
laf touches your hip as long as there are two hands,
that's enough for me.
YourJing Yu
fell into a meltdown.
Greetings, Bad Brother.
You can just know each other
Don't do this
That's not what I mean
You and my wife have experienced a lot
To determine each other's feelings
Such a big thing
Of course, there must be a clear expression
My wife
The one who cares most
But it's the person in my heart
Precious to myself
These are all in my sketchbook
It makes sense
Manager Li
This is
Remember
This card
what
What are you talking about?
You're indeed going to tell my father.
I've been paying attention for you so many times.
Let me mention it first.
Do you know about the
work cancelling activity in thistalismans in my customs?
I'm just saying that Lu Zhuoxi is not reliable.
She said that she's a trickster and a traitor.
Could she also say that
the young lady likes to play the flute?
I shouldn't have believed her.
No.
I came too early.
Brother Lu!
Ke, you're so cool.
Ke!
I know this meeting is the grace of fate.
Every time I see you,
I only feel the love and stubbornness.
Although I can't remember
every difficult day,
I never forget the first time
I saw you.
Even if this love is heartless,
silent, day or night,
it doesn't matter if it's a stormy month.
As long as you are never afraid,
never afraid of worries,
and never afraid of worries.
No matter if this world is on fire,
or if there will be any changes,
I'm willing to face it with my own hands.
Even if I can't see you as I see you,
in front of me or in front of me,
I'm still wholehearted.
I only miss you all day.
Even if the sky is blue or the sky is blue,
I don't care about the past.
Please remember the youth that once
was so bright.
From now on, I don't want to part with you.