=My Sweet Professor=
=Episode 2=
Hello, Mr. Huo.
I'm your attending doctor,
Gao Yuan.
Eh?
You don't recognize me?
If you need anything, ring the bell.
A nurse will come over.
We're going to have a quiz.
The purpose is to test
what you've learned
in the last two years.
Don’t cheat.
Read the questions carefully.
Hey.
Guess who I’ve just seen?
Huo Shang.
How do you know?
That's right.
He's in your neurosurgical ward.
He seems to own a business now.
He's even got an assistant.
Can I talk to you about something?
He has a fracture in his arm.
The nerve is not impaired.
Um...
Just tell me what you want.
Your Orthopedics should take over him
from now on.
No.
I give you this topped-up
canteen service card.
Oh.
Well...
Mr. Huo,
how do you feel today?
Not bad.
Oh,
your BP is a bit low.
(President Gu)
Hi, President Gu.
OK, sir.
I'll switch back with Huangfu Ren
tomorrow.
Good night, sir.
Mr. Huo,
do you feel better today?
Yes.
It'd be better if someone didn't pretend
to be a stranger.
Dr. Gao, we were friends in school.
Am I that scary?
You are getting a lot better
and can leave the hospital in days.
I have a headache.
I feel nauseous
and sick.
You're totally fine.
Maybe it's a mental problem.
Get well.
Call the nurse if you need anything.
Is this how you treat your old friend?
That really hurts,
Gao Yuan.
I thought
you'd hug me, crying,
since we hadn't met in years
and ask me how I had been.
Hey,
give me your phone number
if you don't mind.
=My Sweet Professor=