Joonhee.
Did you see it?
What is all that?
It's not...
What is that? Why are my photos...
Photos of all our neighborhood women?
It's for my next project.
What?
I'm a web-comics writer...
This movie was based on your comic?
Yeah... It's was a while ago.
I took time off to take care of Noeul.
I'm preparing for my comeback piece.
Oh, I see.
It's my first time writing from a woman's perspective.
I'm terrible at drawing women.
Noeul did her best to support me.
She took photos of everyone for me.
Were you surprised?
But why... is my photo in the center.
You're my main character.
Shouldn't main characters be beautiful?
You are beautiful...
Want to see?
It's a still cut, I even colored it.
Do you like it?
Hello.
- Oh, good morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
What? You think I don't wash?
Uncle, what's wrong? What's going on?
I just exercised, exercise, exercise!
Oh my god!
What, what, what!
Put some pants on.
Mom, he was exercising.
People die when they suddenly change.
Don't ruin my vibe, old lady.
I'm going to live forever.
Water in the morning is healthy.
I want to tell you about our family's new goals and direction.
Since I destroyed the Momvelies and their plans,
they will be coming after all of us.
So how do we prepare?
Survive. Our goal is survival.
If they hit you? Just say "ouch." Walk away.
If they spit on you?
Just smile and wipe it off.
We will become a family of boars that can't be phased.
Family of boars? Terrible naming.
I'm not joking around.
Sorry.
Now, again.
Don't ever talk about moving schools like a loser.
So what if the school changes?
Why can't you do music?
Those are all weak excuses.
I never had music education.
If it comes down to it, I can teach you music myself.
You'd be learning from a top 1% musical genius.
Okay.
Why aren't you excited?
- Yeah...
- Okay.
Let's cheer together for our new future.
Come on, bring your hands in.
Let's go family!
- Let's go family.
One more time. Where's the energy?
Again, louder.
Let's go family!
Enjoy breakfast!
It was you! You gave him the audio recording.
Are you crazy?
Why would I do that? Why?
You've been siding with him! Know your place.
My place?
How dare you talk about "place" to me?
I'm a beauty pageant winner and my husband's a doctor.
Some second-tier plastic surgeon? Not impressive.
Well, you must be so happy. Right?
Living with a cheating car wash owner.
My husband is an incredible doctor,
the problem is with your ugly face. It can't be helped!
The reason you can't have a son is because you're rude!
I curse you!
I'd rather have no son than a son like yours.
Why you little!
I will always do whatever it takes for our goals!
If you don't like it, you can leave right now!
You are all my proud Gold Momvelies, we cannot have conflict from within.
Let's forget about what happened, and move on.
We can't just move on.
Jihoo's uncle is responsible for all this mess,
he should be our target.
I don't want to think about him anymore.
The school system change will happen in due time.
I'll proceed with our plans with the congressman.
You should focus on the big picture, we'll take care of the rat.
That's our specialty, isn't it?
She's right! We can handle him!
This month's Gold Momvely Member Package.
Good job, everyone.
VVIP tickets to the Grande department store fashion show.
19th Century Black Pearl Wine Coupon from the Olcanta Shell Rose family in France.
Oh, how I love being a Gold Momvely, Sis!
I prepared one more thing, what could it be?
15-year-old wild ginseng from the Sobaek Mountains.
For your husband, he'll give you another child.
And one more.
The Fond d'Amore restaurant in the Fantastic City Hotel,
has invited Gold Momvelies for a tasting dinner course.
What? What's the good news? Congratulations!
What's the good news? What's the good news?
Speak of the devil...
Not the devil, a rat.
You guys seem happy.
I thought you'd be fighting each other to catch the spy.
What can I help you with?
I'll be here every day.
I'm stuck to you like a leech.
Just in case all of you plan something terrible.
Code "Won't get backstabbed."
Our meeting has come to an end.
Please text for important matters.
Okay! Good job, everyone.
Goodbye.
Oh right, Diamond?
Can I work part-time?
Why are you asking me?
I don't want you to get angry.
I need your blessing for everything now.
Can you take care of this?
Part-time? Go ahead. Let's see if you can.
Thank you so much! I'll buy dinner when I receive my first paycheck!
Bang, bang! Bang, bang!
If you're finished, please close the windows.
I'll make sure to wipe them clean!
Please be careful of the water! 1, 2, 3...
I reported him for watching me change, he got fired right away.
Nice.
- Hello?
- What?
Fried chicken delivery! 2, 3 chicken... And 3 beers…
A lot of beer... It's for the two of you?
Excuse me, we ordered 3 chickens, there are only 4 legs.
I think the delivery guy ate them!
I'll begin to wash your hair.
Let me know if it's too hot.
Oh, it's so hot!
I'm so sorry, my apologies.
You did that on purpose!
Do-Anything services! Did you need dinner?
What are you doing here? You're terrible at everything.
Excuse me?
I'm really good at cooking.
My in-laws are coming, you'll ruin everything!
I'm really good.
What?
I'm not satisfied.
With this?
So why'd you do it?
What?
You sent me the recording.
I don't know what you're talking about.
How sweet of you!
Don't tell anyone! You got it?
All right, all right. Don't worry.
How long can you keep this up?
They'll always get you fired.
They can try. I'm just living my life.
Let's see who wins...
I'll be the last man standing.
He's driving me crazy!
I went for a haircut, and there he is!
He's also the bus driver.
How do we get rid of him?
He's not a rat, he's a cockroach.
Cockroach pest control! Cockroach pest control!
- What are you doing!
- Do it later!
Sorry, no can do. As a professional,
I just finished the other rooms, they'll all swarm over here.
I'll protect you.
Not on us!
Oh, there's one!
Cockroach!
What the heck?
I thought it was a cockroach.
Sorry, my apologies.
You're going to get fired today.
Then I'll just find another job.
I'm leaving now, sorry.
Anyeong, goodbye, sayonara, zaijian!
(In Korean, English, Japanese, and Chinese)
Get him fired now!
That's why I told you to just leave him alone.
You can't get rid of cockroaches by stepping on them.
Just leave him, okay?
She's an alcoholic...
Hey, soft eyes.
Hello.
Why am I "soft eyes"?
You're always about to cry.
I'm Chaeyoung. Shin Chaeyoung.
Here, I washed it.
We have similar counseling times, so I waited for you.
It's really old.
But still, it's really important to me.
I'll let you borrow it. Give it back when you're okay.
Thank you.
But... what made you so sad?
My boyfriend left me.
I really loved him. We promised to get married.
And?
He changed... when I got pregnant.
He blackmailed my mother, took her money and left.
What a piece of trash.
You look happy today.
I got a lot off my chest.
To the doctor?
Huh?
Yes.
- Hello!
- I like your braids.
- Hello.
- Hello!
Oh, hello.
Hello, Teacher.
You're security here?
You look really good in a uniform.
Thanks.
Hello.
Thank you for getting my job back.
- And the letter.
- Yeah.
Kids, be careful!
Come here, excuse us.
- Hello!
- Hello there.
- Hello.
- Yup.
Are you here for me?
I had something to tell you...
I was just about to go see you.
The kids are on a field trip, I'm free all day.
I actually prepared something to show my gratitude.
But I couldn't finish it, I've been so busy.
But don't worry, I'll complete it this week.
It's okay.
Don't give me anything.
Is there something wrong?
We shouldn't talk anymore, it's best for you.
With all the parents and even the kids.
Everyone is paying us a lot of attention.
I even considered turning down this security job.
But I really need the money.
Got it, got it.
We're playing it cool! This will be fun!
All right, I'll leave first.
I'll just text you now for bluebird work.
Stop carrying around the keyring.
Okay, I'll take it out.
Can you stop it now?
I won't. I'll just leave it at home.
No, stop being my fan.
Can you please stop being my fan?
I don't deserve to have fans.
I'm nothing now.
Jihoo said everything was an excuse...
I want to stop blaming my luck and others.
I'm going back to the beginning, when I was focused.
That's why...
I'll be by your side and cheer for you.
I'm your one and only, biggest fan...
To yourself then.
Just keep it to yourself, Teacher.
I'm sorry.
I don't deserve any of your support.
Sorry.
You're so cool. J. King is the best.
You won first place,
yet you're going back to your humble beginnings...
That's so cool.
All right then, I won't be your fan.
I don't want to get in your way.
I'll support you but keep it to myself.
Thank you for everything.
♫  I think it will take a long time  ♫
♫  To erase you from my memory  ♫
I hope J. King gets back to his music.
I'm sure others are waiting for it too.
I'll be your fan and be by your side.
Forever.
♫  Instead of talking with those sad eyes  ♫
♫  We laughed a lot  ♫
♫  While we were in love  ♫
♫  I will miss that smile  ♫
♫  In the distant future  ♫
♫  When time passes, someday we'll forget each other  ♫
♫  You must be happy  ♫
♫  Forget the ugly me  ♫
♫  Now it's time to say goodbye  ♫
Was that bad?
I like it.
It's the most emotional song you've done.
Bravo!
Bravo, bravo!
Losing someone is the best inspiration!
You never even dated her...
It was deeper than dating.
You didn't write such a lovely song when we broke up.
Your relationship wasn't deep, baby.
Think however you want.
Uncle, do you know SoriCloud?
The music-sharing website?
Yes. Can we upload it there?
This is amazing!
Is this what you've been learning at MIDI lessons?
We can record your songs, and upload them on SoriCloud.
Let's hand out USBs to labels, too.
They're always looking for new talent.
Why haven't you done this for me earlier?
You didn't have any good songs.
You don't have any MRs, right?
(N/T: Material Records)
MR? Everything is analog for me.
Busking around, doing live gigs.
I've recorded a live set and sent it to labels before.
To just any label?
All music labels have their own taste.
How do you know all this?
How do you not know any of this?
What could you possibly teach me?
Right leg, right leg. One, two, three, four... Left leg, left leg.  One, two, three, four...
Left hand, right hand...
So many of you got it wrong.
Everyone must memorize it by next week.
Yes.
If you have a hard time, please come find me.
Why aren't you dancing?
I memorized it. I'm smart.
What do I do when the boy I like, likes someone else?
If they're happier with someone else...
There's not much to do...
- Just let...
- Kill her.
- Kill him.
Stop watching dramas.
Should I make you a voodoo doll?
You can stab it every night.
No thanks! I don't like murder...
Who do you like?
It's boring now, I quit.
Kids these days are so cool.
Now let's try dancing to a new song.
Let's all stand in a circle.
Yes.
Tell me everything!
I'm going to watch a movie with Youngah.
How are you still so strong? Take it easy.
Were your hands itching, since Jihoo's mom left?
Mrs. Jang, stop stalling. It'll get worse for you.
I'll find them in time.
Just tell me where they are.
If you just tell me, I'll forgive you this once.
Shouldn't you still be here when Jihoo comes back?
It's tough for a young child to live, after losing his mother.
I will make sure Jihoo's mother is found dead.
- It's healed now.
- That's good...
You want to have dinner today? With the kids?
Pardon?
I can't cook due to my injury.
You're fussy.
Look.
Do you have other allergies, besides peanuts and kiwis?
Tuna and peaches.
Okay, what burger does your mother like?
I don't know.
All right.
What would she like?
I didn't know what you liked so...
Did I do something wrong?
Did a burger-loving ghost possess you or something?
I think it's cool. Burger flexing.
Well, don't flex twice, we can't finish all this.
- It's really a lot of food.
- We can take it home.
Exactly, we can just do take-out.
Okay.
- Let's eat.
- I want this one.
I want this.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Seriously, he basically told me he liked you.
Jihoo, what do you think?
Do you think Noeul's dad likes your mother?
Did you seriously wear that to a date?
It wasn't a date.
Can't you make an effort? Do you only have one shirt?
Do you only have one eye? I have a lot of clothes!
No, you don't.
You don't even have proper shoes or a bag.
I thought you married rich, didn't you bring anything?
I brought my son!
Anyways, just make an effort, when you meet him.
You look terrible.
You think I won't beat you anymore?
Dress up when you take him to school, too.
I don't want all the other women to feel bad.
You guys are the same when you argue.
Hey.
What?
Why are you offended?
You should be thankful.
See, exactly the same.
Can I sleep next to my son tonight?
Do you like Noeul's father?
I've been watching him, he's not bad.
By chance, if you need my permission,
you have it.
You have my blessing.
I know he really likes you.
100% green light.
Turn your lights off, and sleep, sir.
You like him, right?
No.
You do. I haven't seen you smile like that.
How did I smile? Was it ugly?
Pretty.
It's okay, Mom.
You can smile and be happy.
Go to sleep.
I'm not following, just go with your mom.
Then, why are you dressed up?
I'm a natural fashion killer.
Just go, we need one more person.
What if we lose because of you.
Even if I go, you'll lose.
You know how terrible I am at those things.
You just don't want to see Teacher, right?
You don't know what you're talking about.
Quitting your security job? Not doing bluebird work?
It's out of sight, out of mind.
Being away won't change anything.
You have a point.
Let's go.
Wait for us.
- Hello.
Put this on your chest.
Hi, Shiwon.
Hello, Father.
Greetings.
Ms. Diamond!
Hello.
Diamond, the rumors aren't true. Right?
Did the Momvelies forge consent forms?
There's no way! It's just some strange rumors.
How about a glass of wine after this is over?
Our whole family?
Sounds great.
Call me.
So annoying, you have to deal with all these moms.
It must be stressful, having to invite all these people.
What can we do? It's better than losing face.
There they come.
Are you inviting them, too?
They're in the same class, how can I not?
Why are you always complaining?
What?
What should we do?
Hello.
I've invited everyone for drinks tonight,
will you join us?
Are renters allowed? Why all of a sudden?
Let's just call it a kind gesture.
If I were the Diamond, we'd offer you nothing!
I don't need much.
Go have fun, let's go.
I want all Berry classroom parents to get along.
Let's put our differences aside, for our kids?
Thank you for letting me work at Cook Mom.
Thank you for the invitation.
Oh, it must be difficult for you.
Since you can't drink.
Pardon?
Why not? I remember her chugging wine at Mingi's party.
She's being treated, she's an alcoholic.
Really?
No way! Are you an alcoholic?
Is that why you got divorced? How unfortunate!
Hey!
I hope the treatment is working for you.
You should stay away from drinks.
Don't drink because of stress like last time.
We're moms, aren't we?
I think there's a misunderstanding, what're you talking about?
Oh my, was it a secret?
Oh no, I'm so sorry.
I was just worried, I guess I shouldn't have said anything.
- Why are...
- Hey, let's just go.
Noeul's Father, join us later.
Please, join us.
I guess you don't step on cockroaches, you burn them.
Did you see her face turn red as she ran away?
That felt great!
But, Sis, how'd you find out?
Someone told me.
Did you meet anyone at the hospital?
No...
I think she's looking into your past.
Please give a round of applause for our Berry class!
Thanks to the parents too!
Now, it's the mothers' turn!
So annoying. You're terrible at everything.
Take it easy, we're here for the kids.
You know this is a kid's sporting event, right?
I had the most difficult position...
- Let's go!
Ready.
Why aren't you running?
...two, three...
How did she...
She's the athlete of the family.
Isn't my mom so cool?
She's the best, Jihoo.
Best! Best!
Let's go!
In position, please.
Hey!
Take photos!
Blue team wins!
Uncle, have some.
- The desert is good!
- Is it?
Did you cook all this?
- It's the best!
- Eat some more.
Why does Noeul's father spend all his time with them?
I think he's friends with Jihoo's uncle.
Yeah, there's no way he's interested in Jihoo's mom.
You never know.
What if she's doing her best to seduce him.
She can try her best.
He won't be interested in her.
How dare an alcoholic take a shot at him.
She's so unsophisticated.
Do you think she used to be a street walker?
Did you see all the men look at her body?
Wasn't it just your husband?
At least we don't sleep in different rooms like you.
You don't need a separate room, he doesn't come home.
- Hey!
- What?
Stop it!
If Jihoo's mother and Noeul's father get married...
She won't be a renter, then she could join Gold Momvely?
Sounds like a nightmare.
That's the worst!
Hey, don't even mention it.
She better not!
I'll chase him around everywhere and stop him.
Hey, Sis, when is your husband coming back to Korea?
I heard his business is flourishing in Dubai.
I'm so jealous of you.
Me too.
Jealous? He just wants to be with the kids.
He pesters me to send pics and videos all the time.
Take me to Dubai, too.
Do you possibly know a cool place?
For my first date with your mom.
Can I go out with her?
The ocean!
She likes the ocean.
But she's never been.
Really?
Thank you. For liking my mom.
Thank you for accepting me.
I'll see you outside.
Excuse me... Do you hate me?
What?
You quit your job here and always evade me.
It's because everyone's watching us.
The Momvelies are looking for a reason to mess with us.
If they see us together, they'll come after you.
All right, all right. Just go your way.
Teacher... Teacher...
Are you mad at me?
I'm not mad.
I understand why you're doing this but...
I'm just not used to this.
It's like the Young Prince and the Fox.
Teacher...
You can't say things like that.
I'm not a prince. How am I a prince?
I understand that you're my fan, but I'm no prince.
And you aren't a fox.
Who called you a fox?
No, I'm talking about the French...
You're just used to seeing me all the time.
And now that I'm gone, it's awkward for you.
That's what I've been saying...
You just haven't seen me in a long time.
You'll be fine, once I'm gone again.
How do you know?
I'm not a prince.
Take it easy! You'll get hurt!
Mingi and Jihoo are fighting!
- Stop! I said stop!
- Jihoo!
Stop!
Jihoo! Jihoo! Hey, stop!
Mingi!
Mingi, are you okay?
What happened?
Open your mouth again!
See what happens next time!
Hey!
Are you crazy!
What's wrong? That's enough!
Sis, Mingi's bleeding.
Hey! This isn't over! I'm coming for you!
- Is he okay?
- Take him to the hospital...
- You're okay?
- Its okay, leave it.
Don't be so rough, what if his nose is broken!
I don't think it's that bad, his hand's fine too.
- Better now?
- Leave him.
- We called an ambulance.
- You did? Good.
It's not that bad...
What happened? Why did you do that?
What did I just see? He's actually good at fighting.
Bam! Bam! Those were good hits...
You can't let him get to you.
Let's go, go! You have to apologize.
No.
Min Jihoo!
Did they seriously call an ambulance over a bloody nose?
I knew this would happen.
We should've opened a bullying case when he hit my son.
We can now.
Exactly!
Does this really constitute as a bullying case?
Your husband knows doctors here, right?
Let's get a strong diagnosis.
He does but...
You don't want to?
Why wouldn't she want to help!
We have to stop them before others get hurt too.
Of course, Sis.
It'll happen again if we leave it this way.
My husband's a plastic surgeon.
I'll look into it.
No, don't bother.
Hello, Congressman.
We can get rid of the entire family, if we get Jihoo expelled.
We won't have to deal with his uncle and mother ever again.
It's a win-win.
- 8 weeks?
- For a bloody nose?
How can a bloody nose get an 8-week treatment diagnosis?
He can't go to school until the bullying case ends?
Mingi's mother requested for Jihoo to be removed.
I'll mention the shoes and the peanut incident.
But no matter what I say,
if worse comes to worst, he might be asked to transfer.
Forced transfer?
Is there any other way?
Focus on apologizing and reaching a written agreement.
Okay.
He can't even go to school?
Let's go! We have to apologize.
- No.
- No?
Let's just deal with it.
Why are you so stubborn?
What did Mingi say to you?
It doesn't matter what he said.
You hit him first.
Get up, let's go apologize.
No, I don't want to!
Min Jihoo! Are you going to disappoint me?
Don't get angry, let's just talk nicely.
Get up now.
Will they dismiss the case?
Just apologize because you're sorry.
We still have to apologize and do our best.
Don't beg. Uncle, don't beg! Mom, you too!
Don't beg on my behalf!
Begging is also a way of standing strong.
Did you forget our family plan?
Giving up is losing.
What's wrong with losing? You can lose.
What's wrong with giving up?
It's too much, I want to give up.
You want to move schools?
Let's go.
Do you have money?
Mrs. Jang helped us get this apartment. I don't have money to move.
Which school would you go to?
We found you a school with a music program.
Your uncle did so much so you could stay here. You beat up people and you don't want to apologize, so you want to give up?
You can give up over an apology?
How can you hit someone because they said mean things?
That makes you the same kind of person as your grandmother.
Are you really my son?
I guess I'm my father's son.
- What?
- Oh okay!
Don't say such things to a child!
Go calm down.
You too! Don't be rude to your mother.
Everyone go look at the Happiness Rules.
How could you do this to me?
You don't want me anymore? Should I go to dad?
What?
Stop it! Go to your room!
Do 5th graders go through puberty?
Get in your room, you little brat.
Do you regret leaving with me?
Just stop.
Yeah, I do.
If I didn't exist, you would be happy.
Sure.
If you didn't exist I would be, right?
Hey, stop...
If you want to leave, go back to your father!
Stop that! What're you saying!
- Excuse me.
- Oh my!
Are you crazy?
I waited so long.
Me? Why?
We need a way to meet up.
- What're you saying?
- Hey, hey.
If you don't help me, I'll tell everyone the truth.
The Momvelies will probably murder you.
So annoying. What do you want?
How did he get an 8-week diagnosis?
Is Mingi actually hurt?
No, just a nose bleed.
I knew it.
Did a doctor help you?
I'm not surprised at all.
Exactly.
You can never beat her.
I have before.
She's won't let this go. No one can stop her.
She always controls situations and lies.
She's a professional at making things up and controlling.
She's extremely well connected.
Just give up.
I didn't call you over so that you can brag about her.
Give me something to work with; you're my spy!
There's only one way.
The truth?
Are you stupid?
You can't beat her with that.
Money?
Evidence.
You can only win with hard proof evidence.
Is that why you're always recording things?
What evidence could there be for this bullying case?
I don't know. Figure it out.
- It's Sechan's mom!
- Where, where!
Is it not?
Throw it out.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
You still have to study.
Your English teacher will be here at 11:00.
This is uncomfortable, I want to go home.
You can tonight.
I have to go home, then see your sister.
Finish all your math homework by then, okay?
Huh?
Mingi, I can't contact your sister.
Can you tell me her new number?
She doesn't have a phone.
How do you call her?
You must call her since she's studying abroad.
Studying abroad?
She didn't leave Kor...
She didn't leave, huh?
Mom told me not to tell anyone.
Hey, just tell your uncle. What did Mingi say?
Is your mouth sewn shut?
Yup, it is. This is so frustrating.
Did anyone see the entire situation? This is so frustrating.
Hey, what're you going to do?
She's never been that mad with me before.
What happened to the loving mother and loving son?
Stop.
Get him, Dad! Get him!
Huh? Yeah.
You're at half health. Try harder!
I'm doing it.
Die. Die. Why aren't they dying?
Did you see Jihoo and Mingi's fight?
Yeah, yeah.
You died again, you're really bad.
What did Mingi say to Jihoo?
I can't say.
Why?
Jihoo said so.
He said he'd beat anyone up.
He won't find out if you tell me.
But I'll know.
I don't want that on my conscience.
All right, I won't ask.
I guess Jihoo will transfer schools now.
But you know...
He said don't say it, he never said anything about writing.
The number you have dialed can not be conn—
- Hyeok...
- Why are the lights off?
Have you seen Jihoo?
Why? Did he got somewhere?
What's wrong?
You think he ran away or something?
- Hyeok, do you think...
- What?
He went back to his father?
Back to his grandmother!
There's no way he would.
Would he?
Call him!
It's off. What do we do?
Why did you push him into a corner!
I went too far! What if he actually went back.
Why would he! He wouldn't, right?
Noeul's father might know something.
Excuse me, how do I get here?
Walk down the big...
There's no way... How do I sneak in?
How do I open this? Think, think...
Open sesame?
I'll go in and take a peak.
What? Another door?
Hello? Who is this?
Who? Min Jihoo!
Where are you?
Think whatever you want, Mom.
Stay right there, I'll come and get you.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
I'm really smart.
What? Who's there?
Who could it be?
Wang Joonhyeok?
It's you, right?
So stressful!
Let's get out together.
Have you seen...
Welcome. He's sleeping over there.
You found him? Where?
Okay, hurry over.
Yes, Noeul's father.
No, I called you.
Sorry, Jihoo was missing.
We found him.
Noeul has a video, you should probably see it.
Hey, your mom and Noeul's dad are dating?
The moms would love to hear this, I'm going to tell them.
Don't, just don't.
Piss off.
A pathetic alcoholic?
Trying to get married to a rich guy and move out of rentals?
Your mom's a determined gold digger, huh?
Don't talk about my mother like that!
Don't get in the way of my mother's happiness!
What are you doing Mingi?
- Stop! I said stop!
- Jihoo!
Stop!
Jihoo! What are you doing?
Mingi, are you okay?
Open your mouth again!
See what happens next time!
I'm sorry, Mom. I messed up.
You broke your piggy bank to buy an apple?
Uncle made fun of you because you don't have a bag.
- Your change.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
He ran out of money and couldn't get on a bus back.
His phone ran out of batteries, so he used the fruit shop's.
He didn't run away. Don't be mad.
She doesn't like it.
No, she loves it.
I looked it up on the internet.
It said a bag is the best way to make a woman feel better.
Just forgive him already.
I didn't ask for this.
Come on, stop!
I don't need any of this, I just want you to behave.
I don't have to go back to grandmother?
You're not going anywhere!
I don't want to go.
You can't! I'll never let you go.
Really? You promise?
Never! I can't live without you!
Really? That was a quick change of mood...
I'm cringing. Sort of annoyed.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'll go and apologize to Mingi.
Don't apologize. You did nothing wrong.
I'm not going to let them do this to you!
I'm sorry.
You rode the bus alone?
I'm so proud.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Dad lives close to the hospital, but he doesn't even visit.
Even if you divorced, he's still my dad...
You're not really hurt.
He even came to your birthday party.
You have to speak well for the bullying case.
If they mention the peanuts or shoes, just say you don't know.
They don't have CCTV evidence anymore, just lie about it.
Aren't you curious as to why I did all that to Jihoo?
Why did you?
He annoys me.
He might get a new father.
He already has an uncle that comes to his rescue.
So annoying.
You have the Momvelie aunties.
Them? They're not on your side.
That's why you keep secrets from them.
Secrets about dad and my sister.
Let me get you some food.
Have some treats.
I'll be right back.
Chaeyoung, it's me. Let's talk.
Chaeyoung.
How'd you find me?
Why are you here?
Why'd you change your number? Why'd you quit school?
I've been looking all over for you!
How dare you look for me!
You left because I got pregnant!
What?
Why'd you come?
You want to threaten me too? You piece of trash.
What did you just say?
Pregnant?
What?
Acting like you don't know?
How could I know?
You never told me, how could I know?
My mother told you.
This is the first time of hearing of it.
Our baby is in your belly right now?
What? What're you saying?
You wanted me to erase him!
Feeling sick? Is she laying down?
I'm really busy today.
I'll go as soon as I can.
Don't worry! You have me and your mother.
We will be victorious today!
Why? We have Noeul's phone. Undeniable evidence!
Don't worry about anything.
You have it? Her phone?
Why did you give it to uncle?
Oh no.
He said it was important, that he'd protect it.
Wait, wait.
We're late.
Why?
I have to poop.
Just go ahead without me.
I can't hold it. Just go.
Oh god, what do I do?
Please turn on, please.
Excuse me.
Water got into it,
I need you to get the data out of it!
You can't? Okay, sorry!
Service center? Okay! Water, water got into it...
Taxi! I have to get to a service center! Please!
To the service center!
Like mother like son.
Don't give them attention.
Weren't you just on your knees recently?
I heard you didn't even apologize to Mingi.
Prepared for a forced transfer?
Let me say farewell in advance. Goodbye.
You should raise your child properly.
The son of an alcoholic single mother and renter.
That's who they'll blame if your son lives like that.
Go over there with Noeul and her dad.
What? How dare you? Do you have something to say?
It's too late for apologies.
I'm not going to apologize.
Yeah, I'm divorced.
I do live in a rental, and I was an alcoholic. Facts.
Say whatever you want. I really don't care but...
Don't mess with my kid.
My son is growing up to be a fine young man.
You should all be ashamed.
You lie and steal, causing harm to others.
Your children do exactly as you do. They learned from you.
Now that you're forced to move, you have nothing to lose?
How dare you speak to us like that!
Please, stop now.
Why are you here?
Noeul will stand as a witness.
What witness?
Noeul do you have something to say?
Mingi ordering Sechan to steal Ji-hoo's shoes.
Spraying water on his pants and attempted murder with peanuts.
Mingi hit Ji-hoo first,
then constantly insulted his mother.
Noeul's father, I suggest you stop your daughter.
You know rumors are spreading in our neighborhood?
Nothing good will come if you take a renter's side.
What's there to lose?
I'm not taking a renter's side, I'm taking Jihoo's side.
What?
I don't want him to move schools, or his family to move.
I'm doing my best to look cool in front of Jihoo.
I am very attracted to Jihoo's mother.
What the hell did I just hear?
From now on, please watch your mouth when speaking to her.
It's really pissing me off.
No way!
Where can she even go?
Look around, I'll be right there!
You can't leave, I just fixed this.
The case is about to begin, let's go inside.
Wait!
Isn't that the robber kid?
Did you meet her? Did you meet my daughter!
He has a knife! Careful! Be careful!
What are you doing? Stop this, at once!
I'm going to cut your tongue out, so you can't lie anymore!
Hey, stop! This is dangerous!
Stop that!
How could you do that to your daughter? It's all your fault!
You ruined Chaeyoung's and my relationship!
Why is that my fault? It's all your fault!
Stop talking!
You too! Put the knife down!
Are you okay?
You're the devil!
I have to get to school.
The kids are waiting for me...
What do I do...
Hey!
Please call 911.
Just a sad life of hardship and debt.
Never having the chance to get married.
He tried to stab me but someone else got hurt.
It's all lies!
It turns out the culprit was the son of a security guard here.
The person who was stabbed was Jihoo's uncle.
So take some rest, and wake up tomorrow.
Now that he's hospitalized, you won't even visit?
Are you trash?
I want to go and it's driving me crazy!
Why'd you avoid him?
He might take Jihoo away.
We're always terrified of getting caught.
Find him before the police get him!
- Oh?
- Do you live here?
Destroy all the files.
No one can find out about this.