- How do I look?
- Perfect!
My son is looking incredible!
Who's son are you?
Wait!
What?
Just wait.
Mom, this... feels weird.
Why? Does it hurt?
Have you been taking your pills?
It doesn't hurt, it feels weird.
What! Explain it to me!
I never felt this before.
Could this be happiness?
You little...
Yes, this is happiness.
You look really cool.
Hey!
This feels weird.
You can't wear that.
- You haven't changed?
- This is it.
What about your hair?
This took me an hour. His hair is bad.
Don't touch my hair!
Hey! This took me an hour.
Seriously don't!
It was a perfect day.
Congressman.
The Diamond isn't what it used to be.
Congressman ignores you, Momvelies are losing members.
Just get out of...
Hey!
- I was talking...
- I'm worried about our Momvely.
- That's it?
- I couldn't recognize you. You look so pretty.
- Why?
- Nothing.
I thought I saw something.
Everyone's here, the parking lot was full.
A lot of people came.
♪ Relax and take a breath ♪
♪ You can cry if you want ♪
♪ You're perfect to me ♪
♪ Although we are small and weak ♪
♪ We can accomplish anything ♪
♪ We can fly like butterflies ♪
- You look great.
- Greetings, I'm the principal.
What an amazing opening from our choir.
Absolutely amazing.
Great job!
Noeul's magic show is up soon.
Really? I should go and cheer for her, I'll be right back.
It's like you were born for the stage!
It was better than the rehearsals.
One of our school's biggest, newest supporters...
I present to you, the president of Gangto Money.
- What?
- Wow! Great!
- Honey, did you know?
- No.
I wanted to remain as an anonymous supporter. But the principal...
Oh my...
What do we do?
I am the president of Gangto, Shin Hwaja.
Watching all the children perform so well
reminds me of my grandson. I feel warm inside.
Oh my god! Let's get out Jihoo!
I will help children grow their dreams.
To become...
Hurry! Hurry!
Jihoo, are you okay? Come to your senses!
Are you okay? Did she know we were here?
Where's the car? Hurry and get the car!
- Wait!
- Oh my!
What? Move aside.
This is a school.
Wang Joonhee? The president wants to see you.
Mom, no!
Security! Security! Here, help, here!
How dare you hit a child!
- Are you crazy?
- Is there a problem?
This stranger suddenly hit our child! Take them away!
- How dare you!
- You animals...
You should know better!
How could you hit him?
Don't move!
- Oh!
- What do we have here?
Get out! Hey! hey!
Chase them!
What do we do? Where are we going?
How did they figure out where you were?
- Listen to me carefully.
- You have a plan?
The number you have reached is unavailable...
Step on it!
Faster!
What the hell!
For Christ sake!
Cut through them!
If you have eyes, drive better!
Where'd they go?
Cut through them!
Damn it!
Hey! I warned you to stay away from them.
I've got back up.
How'd you find us? How'd you know where we lived?
- You aren't in the position to ask.
- Well, I am!
You loser, I saw Jihoo playing the piano on YouTube!
If you wanted to hide, you should've stayed hidden.
I'm not letting you take either of them.
I don't know where they are.
Kidnap me, kill me, do whatever you please.
- I'm not telling you anything.
- So dramatic, I just want to chat with you.
I don't believe you, I know what you people are.
Just stop running away!
You ran away like a scared dog.
It was fun. Thrilling.
Are you actually crazy?
I seriously just want to talk.
My mom has something to say.
Huh?
You're just leaving? Don't bother running.
I know all of Joonhee's plans.
Mrs. Jang snitched.
Oh hey. Well, I'm at the...
Yeah...
I don't know...
Oh wait, there!
Joonhee! Why'd you turn your phone off!
They knew my number. They might track me.
Sodam's mother, please take care of Noeul today.
Something urgent came up, sorry.
Thank you.
What was that about? I was right next to you!
You were just planning to just disappear?
I was going to contact you after relocating.
Do you know how worried I was?
I'm sorry.
They're from Gangto Money?
If they keep chasing you,
we can threaten to publicize their domestic violence.
There's no point.
They're powerful enough to bury the evidence.
Do you not trust me? I'll do it, I'll protect you.
Sorry to interrupt but...
Who's Mrs. Jang?
He said she snitched all of your plans.
- There's no way...
- What are they planning?
I thought they would kill me, but they just left.
He said he just wanted to talk.
I don't understand anything!
Incheon port?
Why?
I'll be there, let's talk.
Don't worry.
You look good.
You've got a man.
What did you do to Mrs. Jang?
What could I do?
You still trust her.
Foolish...
Money rules over any secret.
I'm not going to take Jihoo away.
Stop running, continue with your life.
We've been watching you for quite some time.
Even if we took him back, he'd run straight back to you.
I'll wait until he grows up. He'll come to me.
When he's older, he'll know what he walked away from.
He'll regret leaving us.
Do you expect me to believe you?
I'm running for Seongjak congress.
I don't play games, I just win.
My district is controlled by 4 congressmen.
But here it's different. Also, my grandson resides here.
So watch your mouth.
Don't tell anyone about your past, or I'll come after you.
Understand?
I've asked around, she's telling the truth.
She'll publicly announce it tomorrow morning.
She's going into politics, she can't do terrible things now.
She was just afraid that her past would interfere.
Sorry, for scaring you.
Yeah.
Get some rest.
The number you dialed is not available. Please check again and call back later.
Joonhee, how are you? How about Jihoo?
Never mind, don't answer anything.
Don't contact me. Stay hidden, okay?
The principal didn't know she was Jihoo's grandmother.
They'll be speaking about it tomorrow.
Thank you for looking into it.
I understand. I'll be extra, extra careful!
But don't scare the child, don't let him notice.
Just like that one movie...
Locked, okay.
Oh my g—!
You slept here?
Hey!
You've never served in the military.
Soldiers are trained to withstand sleep.
Don't be scared. Going to the toilet?
- Yeah...
- That way.
Take a right, it's the first, no second door.
It's too early for this!
Sechan wake up, time for school.
Gangto's president, what?
Running for congress? That's crazy! Oh my goodness!
Hwang must be pissed! He thought it was over.
Now he has an incredibly powerful opponent!
I don't care, I don't think he'll side with us anymore.
Why don't we link up with Gangto's president?
I am so smart.
Put it around your neck.
Blow it when in danger.
It's in the news. She's really doing it.
President Shin Hwaja, known for philanthropy...
Decides to dedicate her life to the people and society.
What a load of crap.
Scary old hag.
Just eat.
Hey, wait!
It might be poisoned.
- I cooked the rice.
- What about the ingredients?
They've watched us for months.
They could've snuck in and poisoned everything.
Don't eat anything strangers offer you.
I'll eat it first, just to be safe.
What if it's poisoned, Uncle!
It's too late now.
Still alive?
No poison. Jihoo, eat.
- Going to work?
- Of course.
Mom, stay. Just stay at home, please?
It's okay, we have the CCTV and all our neighbors.
You stay home, just in case.
Why're you going so early?
I have to meet the principal.
Hey, take this!
- She never listens.
- Phew!
Chungshin Security. A requested personal protection.
Who...
I was worried. Get to work safely.
I'm sorry.
It was an anonymous donation, introduced by Congressman Hwang.
I didn't know she was Jihoo's grandmother.
Jihoo went through a secret transfer, I would've told you.
My sincerest apologies.
Why are you speaking with the principal?
Oh, Jihoo's mother?
Send me beansprouts, anchovies, and spicy soup.
Oh, I want some warm and fresh egg rolls.
- Excuse me?
- Is your pride hurt? Then forget it.
An employee is right here, why would I bother calling?
I was just trying to help with sales.
Is that offensive?
How many portions of each?
- 1 that feels like 2, got it?
- Got it?
She's polite but rude, it's strange.
How dare she, I'm the Diamond.
So principal, what I'm trying to say is...
Just connect me to Gangto's president.
Momvelies are always looking for the school's best interest.
Weren't you ecstatic when Gangto donated?
We want to approach Gangto and show appreciation.
For the school, our district, and our children.
Then speak with Jihoo's mother.
What?
Why her?
She's Gangto's daughter-in-law?
Oh my goodness!
Jihoo is the grandson? He's a billionaire?
That family was probably laughing at us this whole time.
So what! They're divorced and living as renters.
Why'd you have to be rude and order from her!
You ordered too!
Yes, Congressman Hwang.
You heard Shin Hwaja is running for congress?
Yes.
Then why didn't you contact me!
I just heard it now.
Come to my office for a meeting now!
Yes, Congressman, but...
We're on his side, I guess...
Go meet him. We need to grab onto someone.
Guys! Jihoo!
- Jihoo?
Hello.
Where are you? Why is it all red?
I'll tell you later, bye!
You can find hidden cameras with that?
That's what they say... Look for a light...
- Here!
- It's me!
Okay.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- It must hurt.
Thank you. You're excused.
Thank you.
I spoke with security.
They're watching out for strangers and unknown vehicles.
We've broadcasted warnings and put up signs.
You said it'd be fine.
I said I'd make it fine.
- You look tired.
- Huh?
I was busy figuring things out...
I couldn't sleep either.
You ran away in my dreams, I was chasing you down.
I'm sorry. I won't do that again.
Then live with me.
What?
I wanted to give you an extravagant proposal but... I'm sorry for saying this.
What are you saying?
1 year into our marriage, I can be Jihoo's legal father.
I want to protect you both.
You don't have to answer right now.
Just think about it!
All right.
Don't close your eyes! Don't close them.
Keep them open. 1, 2...
1, 2, 3, 4... As fast as possible.
1, 2, 3, 4...
It's a scare tactic. It's all about looking fierce.
If you're in a sticky situation...
You can defeat 3 to 4 adults with this technique.
- Aren't you scared?
- Never.
If I have these, nothing in the world can scare me.
Huh?
- Mom, you okay?
- Yes.
What're you doing?
Self-defense training.
Go change into sweats.
I'm okay.
Now!
I'll teach you something else!
Focus!
Eyes closed... Close you eyes.
Just in case of danger...
In order to defeat your fears, you must train!
I will teach you the technique of forgetting traumas!
First...
Before we begin, give your gratitude to Song Hwaeum by clapping three times.
First: hug technique.
If I begin to feel fear inside
about someone from my past attacking me,
open your arms and hug yourself.
Then pat yourself like this...
It's okay...
Try it. It's okay...
- It's okay.
- Once more.
It's okay. Everything will be fine.
- It's okay. Everything will be fine.
This technique works incredibly well.
This'll help for the rest of your life.
Especially you!
If you want to be a musician, you must prepare with this.
Even when you approach the public with open arms,
not everyone will show you the same affection.
I was attacked from all directions.
He's got a weird face, his voice sucks...
All of these hurtful lies.
If I let all that negativity get to me,
it's only my loss.
I must learn to love myself, and to protect myself.
My mentality is the most important!
Open arms, hug yourself... I'm okay...
It's okay. Everything will be fine.
Second: Sealing technique.
Negative memories, emotions, things you want to forget...
Write them all down.
You can draw them, too.
Good, good, good.
Now...
We've just sealed all that negativity in here.
It can never come back out.
It's practically gone, okay?
What are you doing?
Mom, I think I can go to school.
Yeah, you can't hide forever, right?
Wait, Jihoo.
- What do you think of him?
- What do you mean?
He wants to protect us.
He already is.
He wants to become your father.
Is that possible?
Is that okay?
I like that! No... I love it!
I love it! I love it!
What!
Uncle!
- Why?
- Don't!
- What're you doing?
- I'm a bodyguard.
Can't you tell?
A bodyguard must wear an all-black suit.
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
Something could be inside!
A poisoned needle with a deadly infection on it!
How can I overcome my fears, if you scare me like this?
I'm not trying to scare you, just want you to be careful.
Haven't you heard?
You must lose a cow before building a fence.
You stand out too much.
No, no.
Wait! Which apartment? Which room?
- What?
- Apartment and room number?
- You've got 5 seconds, 5, 4, 3...
- Apt. 3512 Room 403.
You must be new.
We're just role playing.
It's a school project...
Jihoo, let's go.
Use each of these cards, one time each.
Out of the four possible digits,
find the largest number rounded to 6,000 and
also the smallest number.
We've studied and practiced rounding up,
I will give you 10 minutes.
Solve it by yourself.
After 10 minutes, we can solve it together.
Yes!
He's so annoying.
- Uncle, wait there.
- Okay, okay.
What's your uncle doing?
This is a toilet.
Sorry.
Jihoo.
I heard you were the grandson of Gangto Money.
I'm just me.
How'd the trauma lessons go? Did they help?
I'm doing everything you taught me, but I'm not sure.
I hope it works.
He almost faints when seeing any grandmother.
I understand that you can leave such a rich family.
But the least they can do is give you a store or a lot of money.
You live as a renter, working for someone...
I seriously can't understand your logic.
Tell me.
Did something happen?
It's obvious.
You took Jihoo, so they must've done something terrible.
I can't speak of it, we can get hurt.
What? Something really happened?
Okay well... We aren't that close, I guess...
But I don't have friends anymore, you can tell me if you want.
I'm sorry.
The Gold Momvelies are frantic.
I regret leaving for the first time, I want to see them panic.
What's wrong with them?
After Mingi's mother left, their reputation hit the floor.
Even Congressman Hwang tried looking for other mom cafes.
Sechan's mother is probably trying so hard to
suck up to Gangto's president.
She must be shocked, hearing you're the daughter-in-law.
Why are mom cafes obsessed with politics?
Moms only care about education and apartment prices.
The more members you have, the more power and influence.
Congress and mom cafes work together to win-win.
It creates selfish people like Mingi's mom.
It's our reality.
Congressman Hwang is moving to another mom cafe?
He said he will if we don't get our members back.
So annoying!
Why is everyone leaving us?
We don't offer any benefits or developments.
Would Gangto's president want us?
After everything we did to Jihoo's mother?
We voted for the worst Diamond...
Hey, seriously!
Is the Royal Momvely Diamond here?
Yes.
As you know, this is my first time running.
I'm independent, but I need help.
I know you've sided with Congressman Hwang, but
how would you like to partner up with me?
I can provide generous sponsorships and support.
Ms. President I have a question...
Honey, what are you doing?
I'm just curious why Jihoo's mother divorced...
Our members will be curious, too.
For us to protect you, we'd need to know why...
It's all my fault.
Jihoo is our only successor.
I was very strict with successor training.
But as you all know, Jihoo is only interested in music.
He rebelled.
In a moment of anger...
I hit him.
It angered my son and daughter-in-law.
We argued about the schooling system.
Things just got worse and worse.
We split as a family.
It happens to everyone, while raising a child.
Child violence is not okay...
I am a human that made a mistake.
I hope you can understand.
Older generations can do that.
I regret and repent my actions.
You're very down to earth, Mrs. President.
Absolutely.
I hope I get a chance to mend my relationship with Jihoo.
And also his mother.
Yes, you should. It'll help with your polls and votes.
Well then...
I trust that you'll help me.
Don't worry, Mrs. President.
Jihoo's mother is my best friend.
Jihoo and my son Sechan, are best friends too.
I'd like to invite everyone to my house.
Oh, Mrs. President! We'd be honored!
Don't be nervous, we knew this was coming.
Sealing technique activate!
You buried your fears in the dirt.
Take a breath.
If it didn't work, use the hugging technique...
It's okay...
Right, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
Look at her. She's just a small old lady.
She's not scary.
She's not scary. She's not scary.
You'll be bigger than her soon.
Let's go.
Jihoo, say hi to your grandmother!
Excuse me? Stay out of it, okay?
- Jihoo's uncle...
- Jihoo.
I'm sorry.
It breaks my heart, thinking about the past.
It's all my fault. Will you forgive me?
I can't right now.
Please leave this neighborhood.
Don't hurt my mother ever again.
Then, I'll forgive you.
You've become strong, my little Jihoo.
If you need anything, just call me.
I don't need anything.
All I need...
I already have.
Great job! Great job!
Jihoo.
That was amazing.
Since then, my grandmother never came near our home.
And not too long after, something surprising happened.
After discovering your music online,
I couldn't believe my eyes or ears!
How is it that after all this time, your voice didn't age?
I used to be a huge fan.
- Really?
Right! After military service, I struggled to figure out life.
That's when I heard "Your Dream."
Oh my! That's my favorite song.
♪ When you feel all alone ♪
♪ You can take my hand ♪
♪ I'll be by your side ♪
Wow, you've got an amazing manager.
- I was a huge fan too.
- There isn't a hidden camera, right?
- Where's the hidden camera?
- No, no way.
- Here's the contract, please have a look.
- Thank you.
- One for you.
If we sign it, Uncle will release an album again?
Of course!
Our company focuses on finding new talent, but
we also find artists who couldn't reach their potential.
To be honest, our CEO doesn't know J. King.
But I strongly recommended you.
Your music sense and creativity.
I believe you can be one of our main artists.
Thank you.
Uncle! There's a signing bonus!
I'm sorry.
He's my nephew, I've been taking care of him.
We're stuck together 24 hours a day. Is that okay?
Sure, why not?
How much is 50 million won?
How can you not count? It's 5 million, right?
It is 50 million.
Really?
Now, now, now. A future celebrity is buying
It's the highest grade beef!
Noeul, why aren't you eating?
You have to be careful people who buy you beef.
The cut line for pure gifting is pork.
That's not true, if the person buying is family.
Don't go back on your word.
Noeul! Just say thank you, and enjoy the food.
- Jihoo too.
- It's so good.
Congratulations. I'm happy for you. Can I have your autograph?
I'll be too busy in the future, I'll give you one after we eat.
Can we really use this money?
Did you read through the contract?
I did it for him. There's no problem.
Only you don't believe in me. I deserve that amount.
You've been scammed and tricked many times.
I just have to be careful of you.
What does that mean?
It's nothing.
She stole 100 million won from me.
- Hyeok?
- 100 million.
Just eat, enjoy the beef.
- We don't have to share that.
- Okay, fine.
Be careful of your wallet.
Uncle, Mom didn't do that.
Son, just eat.
If it wasn't her, then who did it?
Whomever it was, it's been 10 years. ight?
Hey, I'm petty, extremely petty. I'm Petty King, so what?
Hey, just quit it!
She's angry. You saw that?
She got mad at me.
Big Brother! This is her true face!
How nice. An argument to complete the day.
When family gathers, there's always a fight.
Exactly! We're arguing because we're family!
Oh, Joonhee. When will you give me an answer?
Don't bring it up now.
Jihoo and I already said yes.
Your the only one left.
What? What about me? What's going on?
Really?
I like the idea.
Yay! Yay!
What is it? Big Brother, what is it?
We've decided to live together, like a real family.
I see...
Why don't I know about this?
How come no one told me?
- Just be quiet, let it go.
- Why didn't...
Joonhyeok, you'll be a famous musician now.
I'll protect Joonhee and Jihoo.
Don't worry about them and focus on your music.
This is great timing.
The record label wanted to provide me with housing.
That's so cool! Let's be friends.
We are friends. We're more than friends, we're family.
Since we're family, call me "uncle."
Sure, you even bought dinner.
Uncle!
Shall we cheers as a family?
Sure!
Cheers! Cheers!
- Jihoo is that soju?
- No!
Look where you're going!
Aren't you spending too much?
When can I ever spend like this?
It's my class.
Can I see that one? The one on top.
It's your birth ring. I've always wanted to get you one.
- You've bought me plenty.
- Try it on, it's my heart.
All of this is thanks to you.
You told me to record.
You posted it online.
You sent my music to labels.
Come to think of it, it's all your doing.
I'm just thankful to you, so just accept it.
- I look like a gangster.
- You look tough.
That's what it is!
Gold is timeless.
Gold prices will never drop. They'll only rise.
Don't ever sell it.
And never forget this.
This ring will help you in tough times.
We'll take it.
Thank you.
Uncle, thank you.
Yeah!
Boom!
Bam, bam!
What's that?
- For me?
- Nice!
- What?
- It looks good.
Stand still.
- What is it?
- How did it work again?
Oh? I know.
Like this.
You're getting old, take care of yourself.
- This is nice.
- You should wear it out too.
Thank you.
It's pretty; go wear it outside too.
You're really cool.
Gifting an ex too? You're like Hollywood classy.
He didn't get you one because he likes you, he likes giving.
How'd you know?
This is the difference between the rich and the poor.
When rich people gain money,
they worry about where they could invest it.
When poor people gain money,
they wonder where they could spend it.
What do you mean poor?
I'm about to be rich and famous.
You should learn to be humble.
Flaunting and bragging won't get you anywhere.
Oh my, oh my.
Suddenly you're parenting?
I'm just happy for you!
I'm glad you finally got your chance.
I'm about to cry.
I love it! It's so pretty.
The company car is for you, why're you giving it to me?
I haven't driven in ages.
I guess it was worthwhile raising you.
- That?
- Tada!
Not that...
Two over...
Next to it.
Tada!
Are you kidding me?
That's not all.
Surprise!
Seriously?
Thank you for raising me!
Don't cry.
Take the keys.
This is pretty bad.
- What do you mean?
- Mom!
She has to be comfortable!
She's a beginner, she should start with something like this.
A brand new car would just stress her out.
Clean that right off!
Tada!
Yes!
It's a steam iron.
A necessity for a fashionista.
Oh and this! An electric toothbrush.
It's for me since you don't brush your teeth.
Why didn't I buy this for myself before?
Mom, don't be mad.
What was that necklace earlier?
Necklace, necklace...
Tada!
Pretty right?
It's not for you.
Who? Teacher?
Don't tell anyone.
I'll give it to her at the perfect place at the perfect time.
Now!
Here.
It's not for me again?
Hey, how'd you know?
This one's for Noeul, and that's for Big Brother.
They'll be so happy.
I never expected anything, but I'm upset.
Look at all that!
What?
What's what?
I bought this and that, got matching attires with Jihoo...
Bought some necessities, I've spent 11,264,000 won.
I also took out emergency money and paid my credit card off.
Why should I hold this for you?
You aren't holding it, it's yours.
That's enough for public or private college tuition.
Why? What!
An uncle is allowed to flex for his only nephew!
Think of it as a wedding gift. I'll earn and get you more.
You're emotional? You too?
Stop that.
I'm glad you're happy. Is this the taste of success?
Jihoo, just wait. When I make it, I'll do more for you!
How sweet.
That's right. It's yours, tada, tada.
I almost forgot.
Our family car.
- Drive safe.
- It's mine?
I knew it! I knew you were messing with me!
Even the key is fancy.
It even has airbags...
- Can I press this?
- Don't! It's loud.
Where should we go?
Let's go for a drive in the morning.
♪ I don't know how but ♪
♪ If it's all right with you ♪
♪ I'll always protect you ♪
♪ If it's alright with you ♪
I think "Bluebird" is better for his vocal range.
♪ I'll always be on your side ♪
Hello.
Oh, hey.
Have some snacks.
Jihoo too.
Let's do one more. According to Jihoo,
your vocal range is better with "Bluebird."
Okay. I'm more comfortable with that song.
Your nephew is basically a producer!
He's good at producing and singing.
I want to duet with him.
- That's not up to you!
- It is!
Well... No...
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Okay then. I'll try and speak with him.
- Umm...
- Why? Is there a problem?
He heard your recording. He wants to delay our album.
- What? Why?
- Why...
Because...
He urgently wants a mini-album, and a showcase!
A showcase?
Starting on stage?
Yes, live on YouTube.
He's excited and wants your comeback to be awesome.
You had an upset expression.
It's because now I won't even have time for a vacation!
- Jihoo, you're excited, right?
- Yes.
- When's the showcase?
- Two weeks from now?
Two weeks?
It's really soon. What should I prepare?
Your outfit styling,
dieting, and skin care.
All right.
It begins.
- Congratulations, Uncle!
- Yes!
My partner!
We don't have much to take.
- When are you moving?
- After your showcase.
Is that okay?
You seriously aren't having a wedding?
Wedding?
It's the second time for the both of us.
You didn't have a wedding on your first.
Let's have a small one.
Yeah, Mom. You haven't had a wedding dress.
I don't like that stuff, none of it matters.
Give me some.
- Hey.
- Move!
- Did you hit me with a rock?
- Whatever.
Does this even work?
Anything would work on your skin.
You're aging at an incredible rate.
Son, be nice.
You have to get prettier.
This is nice.
We laughed like this over the smallest things.
I thought only happiness was waiting for us.
These were the days, we had no doubts.
Look pretty!
The password is my birthday.
319...
It's passed.
This year it has. But there are many more with you.
- Okay.
- After you.
It used to be a storage, but I'll redo the walls.
Is it okay for Jihoo?
What should I prepare?
Don't prepare anything. Just bring yourself.
Shouldn't I at least buy blankets? Or dishes?
Then let's go shop for them together.
I feel burdened, you're providing everything...
Don't think like that.
I have something for you.
- Insurance?
- You don't have any, right?
Anything can happen.
At our age, we need at least one of these.
The monthly fees are very expensive. It's quite burdensome.
Every month I'll deposit the amount to your account.
- Why?
- It's a gift.
A lot of people gift insurance these days.
You said there was something I had to do.
Sign it.
You're funny.
Here.
Reporter Song! I didn't molest anyone!
That was years ago!
Get the article down, now!
- Congressman.
- What?
The construction site assault case from 8 years ago...
A public petition was filed.
The bereaved family reported that you threatened them.
What?
- Why are you doing this?
- Doing what?
It's not like I didn't know you were interested in politics.
Your grandson lives here, I understand.
I even understood when you took the mom cafe from me.
Buy why are you going after my flaws and mistakes?
Congressman, I think you have a misunderstanding.
I do not know anything about your past.
Okay. Of course, you don't.
But I know who does.
- Is it Park Hyeryeong?
- Who?
The previous Momvely Diamond.
Isn't the previous Diamond in prison?
Do you believe that only one person knows your weaknesses?
You should get going, I have a busy schedule.
I'm nervous.
How long has it been?
We have a lot of time to rehearse. Don't be worried.
I urgently found this stage, isn't it too small?
What do you mean? No one will come anyways.
We have to fill it up.
If you're done here, want to get a drink?
Jihoo, your uncle's favorite bar, is Hot Bar. Right?
- Yes.
- I'd like to but...
I don't want to take Jihoo out drinking.
I'll ask Mom to pick me up after work.
Yeah? Should I invite your teacher?
Yes!
Okay, let's go.
She hasn't called back?
She must be busy, she's not picking up.
Where's your manager?
How will we fill up the entire audience?
It would have been nice if you had fans.
You might have hidden fans, like me, around the country.
There are so many musicians, no one would remember me.
I have no fans.
J. King! Again!
Yeah, surprise!
What? You knew about this?
You planned with Jihoo?
Tada!
Teacher!
Your manager did everything.
You surprised me!
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Did you know?
J. King's fan cafe manager J. Queen was her!
Really? You're so sweet.
We e-mailed all your fans individually.
Thank you! Thank you!
Uncle, blow them out.
1, 2, 3!
Now, now...
Our star! Our bright shining star!
Voice Audition 1st place winner, J. King's fan meeting...
will begin!
J. King! J. King!
Hello.
I'm on my way home.
You should've told me. I wouldn't have made other plans.
It was really urgently prepared. I just found out today.
Yes, okay. I'll tell him for you.
Busy?
Where are you going?
- Why are you here?
- Let's talk.
Don't get near me, keep your distance!
I'm Jihoo's father. I used to be your husband, too.
You might've married me because you got pregnant but...
I was in love with you. You knew that.
Seriously...
Well, anyways... I'll cut the crap.
Let me get to the point.
Isn't he strange? Ju Gyeongil?
- What?
- He's suspicious.
He's handsome, smart, and wealthy.
Why would he choose you?
So I looked into him.
- Are you crazy?
- Crazy?
- You almost died!
- What are you talking about?
He's a murderer.
What?
He murdered his wife for insurance money.
He approached you with bad intentions.
You're his next target. You understand?
Don't be a fool. Get your head on straight.
Surprised?
You really didn't suspect anything.
Stupid.
It's easy to trick innocent and kind people.
Easy to trap...
♫  Should I be brave?  ♫
♫  Even if I have nothing  ♫
♫  My racing heart whispers  ♫
♫  Telling me to fufill my dreams  ♫
♫  My dream is to be the bluebird, I'll become the bluebird  ♫
♫  I don't care if I fall forwards, as long as I'm moving forward  ♫
It was a perfect day.
♫  I don't care if I fall backward, then I'll be able to see the stars  ♫
1, 2, 3!
♫  Towards the skies  ♫
♫  I will fly  ♫
Jihoo!
Jihoo, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Jihoo, wake up!
What did he eat?
What's wrong with him!
Call 911, 911, Call 911!
Jihoo!
He's unconscious! Help us!
I don't know what he ate. I didn't see what he ate.
Don't let anyone speak badly of you.
If you don't mind your own business, I'll make you regret it. Got it?
What's... Where'd you get this?
Mingi's mother moved into the penthouse!
I am an expert at controlling those women.
I'll return to your home.
But I have a condition.
How can you call yourself his mother? Why would you send him there?
Don't take him away from my sister because of me.
I swear... I'll never show myself to Jihoo again.
A special person in my life supported me and gave me courage.
My loving nephew, I'm grateful for helping me come back.
If you know their weaknesses, we are indestructible.
You are under arrest for drug-related crimes.
This is my stage!