A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
EPISODE 2
I beat the Green Crocodile Pineapple Head.
That narcissist.
As if he scares me.
That girl called Dong Shancai
is quite something.
Si deserved a beating.
Dong Shancai just carried out
the will of the gods.
Today is worth celebrating.
I'll record it.
This is Meizuo reporting from Egypt
on an amazing discovery of a mummy.
There's a bump on his head
from a girl's flying kick.
What we have here must be
the unluckiest man
in the 21st century.
Lei, do you want a picture with the mummy?
This is the report
of Daoming Si's first knock-out.
How embarrassing.
If I were Si, I'd stop going to Mingde.
If I were Si,
I'd disappear from Earth. What time is it?
What the hell?
You fainted.
We brought you back here.
I remember.
That crazy girl actually kicked me!
I'm going to knock her head off.
Si.
Did you know that Shancai
was harassed by two guys
on her way back
after delivering your order?
What? You saw her?
Is she okay?
That's why she was angry and kicked you.
You deserved it.
What does that have to do with me?
Besides, those two guys
must be stupid to pick on her.
Fine. Since you're awake,
we don't have to stay here.
Let's go.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, at least untie me!
FOOD NUTRITION CLASSIFICATION STAGE 1,
LI ZHEN
Hey.
Wow, your notes are incredible.
I want to be in your group.
Zhen and I did a lot to make this.
Hey, Xinhui.
Here's the data Zhen and I prepared.
Give me your email addresses
and I'll send them to you.
Hey, Shancai.
You know very well that Xinhui likes Si
and yet you still flirt with him.
No, I didn't.
Xinhui, I'm not interested in him at all.
Hey, Shancai.
You're the most famous new kid
in Mingde University right now.
First, you attacked the VIP, Mr. Bobbit
and then you went and kicked
the most popular senior, Si.
You could've done something else
to stand out, right?
That's not Shancai's fault though.
Who told Si to step on Shancai's phone?
Actually, it's my fault.
I pissed Si off.
It might seem like I'm the bad guy here, but Si basically ruined my life.
He even sent me a Joker card,
challenging me to Poker.
Should I just let him walk all over me?
What?
You actually got a Joker card?
Why did he give it to you?
Do you even play Poker?
What are you betting against F4?
When?
Where?
I don't know. I don't know anything.
But I'm not giving in.
If the situation becomes worse,
I won't go.
Hey, if you don't want the Joker,
can I have it?
Do whatever you like.
I can't stand that guy, Si.
Shancai.
Why don't you go after
the guy you like then?
But as a new student in school,
besides getting along with other students,
you should also respect
the school's seniors.
Sorry.
I interrupted you.
What is it?
I came to return your handkerchief.
Keep it.
I don't usually take back
what I've given away.
Also,
I received the Joker card from F4.
Yeah, all the best.
Hey.
Thank you
for what happened.
If you hadn't shown up,
I would've been in big trouble.
Don't misunderstand.
I only freaked out
because I couldn't stand it.
So
can I look for you
at the rooftop again?
Then I won't go there again.
Hello.
Ms. Dong.
Mr. Daoming wants you to get in the car.
Why should I?
He wants to see you.
He'd like to pay for your phone
and apologize for what happened.
You must be kidding.
Ms. Dong, please.
Help!
What are you doing?
Who are you guys?
Hey!
Help me! That tickles!
Save me!
She has a round face.
An airy bang doesn't suit her.
She's got baby fat.
A center part will make her face look big.
Stop disagreeing with me.
It's impossible to make
your face shape nicer, okay?
What are you guys talking about?
-Shut up.
-Quiet!
Let's get on it.
First, I'll cover up the blemishes
on her radiant skin using CC cream.
This is more fashionable. -Fix her bangs.
-Cover the blemishes.
Like that.
Is she done?
Yes.
She looks much better now.
Ms. Dong.
Please follow me.
Please wait here.
Si will be here soon.
What does he want?
Don't worry, Ms. Dong.
Si is a very nice guy.
He won't do you any harm.
Hey.
Could this be F4 when they were younger?
So Lei has always been cute.
You're finally here.
Where's my phone?
I want to go home.
Hey.
Do you like Lei?
Listen.
You can't like Lei.
Why do you care?
What is this place? My house.
Why did you bring me here?
And why did you dress me up like this?
Well?
Isn't it nice to be pampered like this?
You know what?
If you listen to me,
I'll let you be my girlfriend.
No matter where I go, you can be with me
within a one-meter radius.
When I eat, you can sit with me.
Even better,
you can find me anytime you want
and be with me immediately.
I can take you to and from school
once a week.
I can give you good snacks at school.
I can help you with homework
if you need it. We can go to the best restaurant
in Shanghai on your birthday.
When we play games,
I'll let you beat me.
We'll take a trip overseas once a year.
Of course,
I can get you a new phone
to replace the broken one.
You must feel really happy now.
Happy?
You must be kidding me!
Where are my clothes?
-I want to get changed.
-Hey, you...
What are you doing?
Daoming Si.
I'm not sure if you're crazy
or if you're dumb.
I don't know
why you said all of that to me.
I don't need your charity
or some special treatment.
I also don't need your money
or a new phone.
I want to go home!
Hey, listen to me.
You'd better not come back crying.
There's nothing in this world
that I can't have.
Who do you think you are?
I don't give a damn.
Well?
You can't have me even
if you give me everything in the world.
Listen.
I, Dong Shancai, simply won't
date a narcissist like you.
What you just said is as stupid
as your pineapple head.
Goodbye!
He brought me to his house to show off?
What an unbelievable guy.
But then,
if I could exchange
with anything in the world,
what would I wish for?
I think I know.
Shancai, you seem
a little different today.
Really?
Is there something on my face?
Your pores are invisible.
And your brows are trimmed.
Did you go to the beauty salon?
Of course not.
Hey, I think Si was looking
at you just now.
Whatever.
Did you guys know
that Shancai is infatuated with me?
You mean the girl that
knocked you out with a kick? Hey, stop laughing. You don't believe me?
I believe you.
I knew nobody could say no to my charm.
That girl says one thing,
but means another.
Even I can't say no to Si's angelic charm.
I have an idea.
We'll hide in the girls' bathroom
wearing a wig and pretending to be ghosts.
We'll jump out at Shancai.
I bet she'd be scared.
Come on, man.
You're asking us to sneak
inside a girls' bathroom.
Have you lost your mind?
Then what should we do
inside a girls' bathroom?
First, four guys sneaking into
the girls' bathroom
is already embarrassing.
Also, you're asking us
to pretend to be ghosts.
We might just end up
looking like perverted ghosts.
Don't worry. We just need to stay alert.
No way. Leave me out of it.
Si just doesn't really understand women.
Lei.
I won't be a ghost. Forget it.
Si, it's not that hard to hit on a girl.
Who said I'm going to hit on her?
I just want
to pull a prank on her.
Are you sure?
-I won't help you, then.
-It's okay.
Yan isn't a good friend.
I'll help you get her.
That's great!
I said I don't like her.
Sure, you don't like her. Neither do we.
Hey.
What about getting some fake cockroaches
and planting them in her bag tomorrow?
Imagine her opening the bag and...
That's something a child would do.
What?
Too lame?
We could buy some onions
and paint them red.
Make them look like they're apples.
Hey, Meizuo.
Give them to her tomorrow.
She'll be eating it
with tears in her eyes.
I can just imagine it.
Hey, Si.
We're too busy to be pulling pranks.
What are you busy with? He forgot.
We need to see the professor
to discuss our graduation project.
Oh, we can go tomorrow.
By the way, Lei,
you're majoring in music.
Why are you coming with us?
I'm just taking a free ride.
It's more environmentally friendly.
Who can tell me
the nutritional content of a banana?
-No idea.
-Yeah.
I know, sir!
A banana contains calcium,
sodium, magnesium, manganese,
zinc, potassium, iodine,
selenium, iron, copper.
Vitamins A, C, E, B1, B2.
Protein and dietary fiber.
Excellent.
How did you memorize all that?
I come from a family of banana farmers.
One year, we had an enormous harvest
so we opened a food processing plant
to make banana cakes.
The same year, our sales hit the roof.
Then we opened ten more factories.
So does your family often step
on banana peels and fall?
You're wrong about banana peels.
People don't fall from banana peels.
A fresh banana peel has friction
and won't cause people to trip.
Really?
How about a demonstration?
Watch.
Be careful.
But if the banana peel is not fresh,
you'll easily fall.
-Do it again then.
-Yes, one more time.
-Do it again.
-Again.
This new batch of Nutrition students
has got some interesting people.
They all have amazing legs.
They can step on banana peel
and kick Si too.
Shut up.
We should go for a visit someday.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
You received a Joker card
just after you started school.
A flying kick,
an attempt at reconciliation
and a request to be his girlfriend.
What a gripping story. Full of ups and downs.
So is that Daoming Si guy
interested in you?
Don't be ridiculous.
He just wants to make my life miserable.
I'll never let him win.
Shancai, don't worry. F4 or whatever,
whoever bullies my friend is a bad guy.
I'll stand up for you if I see them.
Thanks a lot.
But after listening to your stories,
it seems like Si
is the ultimate troublemaker.
Are his friends annoying too?
You could say
that one of them is different.
How so?
I can't really explain it.
Maybe he's a little less annoying.
A handsome guy. Welcome.
So you work here on weekends,
Ms. Flying Kick?
How hardworking.
Just order what you want
and don't disrupt our work.
Hi, Ms. Milk Tea. Hi, how are you?
I want two drinks.
Shancai. Shancai?
Shancai.
Two drinks.
Yes, two drinks.
Our best-sellers are White Jasmine
and Red Royal Peach.
Which one would you like?
I'll take both.
Okay.
I don't remember you liking milk tea.
I don't really like it.
But these drinks have interesting names.
PLEASE PAY
Shancai, who are they?
They're two of the guys in F4.
Really?
They're ready.
TALENT'S TEA SHOP
Thanks.
We're going. Bye.
Bye, Ms. Milk Tea.
Bye.
What?
Who are they?
He's called Huaze Lei.
The other one?
The other one isn't important.
So he's the one that's different?
Did he come here just to see you?
-Why are you blushing?
-What?
Where?
I'm not blushing. Okay.
You're not.
This is Asia.
This area looks like...
Is it Shanghai?
EAST LONGITUDE 2.21 NORTH LATITUDE 48.52
So this place is...
North latitude of 48.52 degree.
East longitude of 2.21 degree.
Where is that?
It's Paris.
Do you know the time difference
between Shanghai and Paris?
I'll check. Seven hours.
Shanghai is seven hours ahead of Paris.
I wish time could fly by faster.
I have a classmate named Time.
I'll tell her to come here now.
Was that not funny?
You really are a weird girl.
Look. This red bag goes well
with the leather jacket.
Yes.
I heard it's the most
trendy design this year.
Really?
-Bye.
Wow, Shancai.
You got together with Lei quickly enough.
I was just talking to Lei on the rooftop.
Yeah, right.
Anyone could tell from your smile
that you're in love.
You like Lei, don't you?
We're all classmates. I'll do you a favor.
Lei already has someone he likes
since a long time ago.
Look.
This is the goddess of Mingde,
the senior Teng Tangjing.
Well?
Aren't they a match made in heaven?
You probably don't know.
Jing will finish her studies
in France and come back here soon.
Shancai.
You're so cute today.
Hey.
Hey, Si.
It's you.
What happened to your pineapple head?
What's wrong?
Is it that big of a deal
just because I changed my hairstyle?
Let me tell you.
I wanted to try a new hairstyle.
I didn't change it because of you.
Oh.
It suits you.
With an incredible face like this,
regardless of my hairstyle,
I still look dashing, don't I?
"Dashing" is used to describe a gentleman.
And you're not.
How am I not?
Nothing about you is dashing at all.
Are you making fun of me?
Say that one more time.
I will.
Good morning, Shancai.
What are you laughing about?
I'm laughing
at someone's who is so full of himself.
What are you talking about?
I really am a dashing guy.
Si.
-Jing is back.
-What?
Jing is back.
Who is Jing?
Welcome back.
Lei, I'm back.
I've missed you.
That senior, Jing, is so pretty.
Is she the girl Lei likes?
She's clearly
in a totally different league.
I still think it's funny.
This place hasn't changed. But you guys...
After three years,
you're no longer high school students,
but university students now.
Luckily, you guys haven't changed.
I'm glad.
Hey, the five of us grew up together.
You can say we're childhood friends.
Si hasn't changed.
You're still the jokester.
You're wrong. I'm more amazing now.z
I'm doing my own investment.
I'm paying for my own tuition fees.
That is pretty amazing.
Your sister must be proud.
I haven't seen her in a while. How is she?
She got married last year.
She's moved to England with her husband.
I know you're really close
with your sister.
Without her here,
you must feel very lonely.
Jing, don't worry about that.
There's a girl who's got
all his attention now.
Her name is...
Dong...
-Something...
-Dong...
You two.
You can't compare her to my sister.
My sister is out of her league.
Lei, why are you so quiet?
Yeah.
You're even more quiet with Jing around.
I know. He's always been this way.
He becomes really quiet
whenever he's happy.
He doesn't say a word,
but his heart beats really fast.
Lei will never change.
Jing, we've grown up.
So has Si.
Yes.
Unlike Lei,
who's always such an introvert.
Look at him.
He's still the same Lei from the past.
He's still very amusing.
Come on.
Let's have a toast
to the never-changing Lei.
Cheers!
I'm not!
Lei. What's the matter?
Jing.
Why did you take those vulgar photos?
That's not like you at all.
Is Lei acting like he's jealous?
I think those photos came out pretty well.
Don't you like them, Lei?
I don't like them at all.
You're not like those vulgar girls.
I knew you cared about me the most.
That's why I like you the most.
Wow!
-Give me a kiss too.
-Me too!
-Come on.
-One here.
Give us a kiss too.
Come on.
Jing.
Dong Shancai, wake up!
That guy will never belong to you.
Starting tomorrow,
I have nothing to do with F4.
I will study hard
and be my cheerful self as usual.
I'll buy you lunch. My treat.
My mom made me lunch.
-Really?
-Yes. Awesome.
I think we were meant to meet again.
We meet again in this school.
We'll study together.
-Si, I need to talk to you.
-Step aside.
Dong Shancai,
I want to talk to you. Come here.
What's so important?
It's important that I see you.
Why do you want to see me?
Do you want to tell me
some weird stuff again?
No, thanks.
You're free anyway.
Just come with me.
Who said I'm free?
I have a lot of things to do right now.
Like what?
I am going to eat the lunch my mom made me
with my best friend, Qinghe.
I don't know about you,
but this is my kind of fun.
Rich guys like you won't understand.
I totally enjoy spending time
with Shancai.
Let's go.
-WHAT DO YOU WANT?
-I'M NOT TELLING YOU.
Mrs. Chen, you're incredible.
Who's Mrs. Chen?
You are.
Isn't this you?
Do you remember the time
the beehive fell from the tree?
Everyone ran off,
but you dragged me there.
Of course, I remember.
Back then,
-your face swelled up this big!
-You're terrible.
You're awful!
Listen up, girls.
A ripe banana peel
will still make people fall.
I still can't pass this damn level.
Qinghe, are you okay?
Shancai, look.
I got a Joker card too.
I bet F4 members think
I've got the potential
so they want to be friends with me.
It'd be rude if I don't accept it.
Right, Shancai?
To hell with them.
They're bothering my best friend now?
Shancai, where are you going?
Daoming Si!
What is this?
Tell me if you've got a problem with me.
Why are you bothering my friend?
What do you really want?
Why?
Are you pissed off
because of that farmer dude?
"Farmer dude"?
He's my best friend.
I won't let you bother him.
Are you serious?
What's wrong with your taste?
What's so great
about a lame friend like him?
He's a million times better
than an annoying guy like you.
Being with him makes me feel 1,000 times,
10,000 times better!
Fine.
I wish you two 1,000
and 10,000 times happiness.
Si, thanks for your Joker card.
My mom made me soy milk. You can have it.
Go back and do your research.
Remember.
"Non-fat milk."
QQ MESSAGE FROM DAOMING SI
Look. "Chen Qinghe.
Your Poker game with F4
is arranged for next Monday at 6:00 p.m.
Please prepare yourself and be on time."
Stop! Ignore him.
Hey, Daoming Si.
You'd better stay away from us, jerk!
Done. Read this.
Don't be scared, man.
It's an honor to receive the Joker card.
Just be careful not to lose too badly.
Thanks for your concern.
Shancai, read this.
"Freshmen Chen Qinghe and Dong Shancai
received the Joker,
but too afraid to accept the challenge.
They're nothing, but...
cowards"? Are you blind?
Watch where you're going.
-So sorry.
-I'll let you go this time.
You'd better watch it.
Shancai. Being with Qinghe
makes you 100, 1,000,
10,000 times happier, right?
So you must be really happy now.
Daoming Si.
Why are you picking on us?
Do you really enjoy doing that?
I do.
It makes me so happy
to see you fall on your face.
Shancai.
You look like you love to eat
all kinds of vegetables.
-No wonder you're called "Shancai."
-Let go!
What's wrong?
Go ahead and hit me.
Si, you're crossing the line.
Have you had enough?
Lei, do you know what you're doing?
Si, enough is enough.
Don't tell me you like this crazy girl.
Stop it.
If you're my friend, let go.
You...
Let go!
-No.
-Let me go! You're hurting me!
If you leave with her now,
don't talk to me ever again.