Little grudge girl
Little grudge girl, come out here!
Where are you?
You run away whenever something happens, huh?
Come out here!
Zhang Yi, what are you doing?
Hey!
You—
You pervert!
Me?
You—
Taking advantage of me!
I'm taking advantage of you?
You're dressed like a ghost in the middle of the night!
Me—
My makeup just got smudged.
What do you know?
Why are you acting so arrogant?
I came here today
to get an explanation for Sister Jingqiu.
Let me tell you, little grudge girl—
You—
Why are all of you
taking Jingqiu's side?
What's so great about her anyway?
Hey.
Don't cry.
If someone sees this,
they'll think I'm bullying you.
Aren't you just here to accuse me?
Yeah, I guess so.
Say whatever you want to me.
Jianxin is already mad at me anyway.
One more person doesn't make a difference.
I'm the bad guy.
I'm a jerk.
Are you satisfied now?
Danniang.
Danniang, right?
Stop crying.
About what you did,
you really
went too far.
It wasn't right.
But if you can admit your mistake and change,
there's still hope.
Even though you have a lot of flaws,
and some are pretty serious,
but
you also have many good qualities.
For example,
you go to a good school.
No. 2 High School is so famous.
And also,
you're good at sports.
You're a champion.
And
you're good-looking too.
In a crowd,
you stand out right away.
And you have a good heart.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't be this upset.
Alright,
don't cry, don't cry.
So Jingqiu,
what kind of person is she, really?
All these years,
Jingqiu has been studying and working at the same time.
She gets bullied outside and doesn't even mention it.
At home, she still has to take care of Teacher Wang.
It's really tough for her.
As for me,
I've never met my real parents since I was little.
So
I really hope
to have a family like Jingqiu's,
a proper home.
After my dad passed away,
I felt like the world was too harsh to me.
It was just too unfair.
Before my dad left,
he took me to see Uncle Sun.
Uncle Sun was really very kind to me.
But deep down, I felt
that when others were good to me,
it was something I deserved.
It was what fate owed me.
Jianxin was also especially good to me.
Jingqiu,
I'm sorry.
Oh.
It wasn't the two of them who forced me.
I truly felt
that I went too far.
I was too immature.
So I wanted to apologize to you.
I believe you.
Come on.
Today is worth celebrating.
Jianxin,
That day, I...
I...
Thank you, Jianxin.
This place is really beautiful.
Let me tell you all,
there are so many fish in this lake.
You can scoop up four or five at a time.
What are you laughing at?
Ouch.
Slow down.
Come on, come on.
Let me, let me.
Take it easy, take it easy.
Ouch, Jingqiu.
Here, put it down.
I'll do it.
Jingqiu, let me tell you.
Why do you work like you're risking your life?
I'm fine.
It's just that
I missed mealtime and forgot to eat.
You...
Wait here.
Here.
Take it.
You do such heavy work,
if you don't fill your stomach,
if something happens,
I can't take responsibility.
Thank you, Brother Wan.
It's nothing.
Oh.
By the way,
Jingqiu,
do you want
to earn more wages?
Yes, I do.
But I...
You must keep this news a secret.
At the factory,
there's an opening for a full-time worker.
Really?
Yes.
Then...
Can I apply?
You,
you work efficiently,
and you're hardworking.
Not like those temp workers
who all day long
just try to slack off.
All this,
I've noticed.
Don't worry.
This position
should be yours.
Thank you, Brother Wan.
No problem.
Well then,
I
how can I apply?
I'm a bit busy today.
Let's talk about it in detail tomorrow.
Hurry up and eat.
Eat first, then get back to work.
Alright.
Mm.
Hey, let me take a look.
Are you on the list?
Dongmei,
you're on it!
They say there will be more spots to stay at school this year.
But why is there still no news?
I heard that those who got the "Three Good Student" award in previous years
have a better chance of staying.
This year, you'll definitely make it.
Hey,
we don't really know.
But some people
have been running errands for Teacher Luo all the time,
yet they didn't even get the "Three Good Student" award.
Not even that.
Exactly.
I guess
staying at school
is probably not going to happen either.
You really don't need to worry.
I've already let it go.
Besides,
even if I did everything Mr. Luo said,
in the end,
I still might not be able to stay at the school.
So in the future,
do you have any plans?
I'll work part-time to earn money
while writing articles.
I'll submit them
to big newspapers,
small newspapers,
major magazines,
and minor magazines.
I'll submit to all of them.
As long as there's a glimmer of hope,
I'll keep writing forever.
Manuscript paper
and ink—
I've got plenty of both.
When you become a famous writer,
just don't forget about me.
Distinguished leaders,
colleagues,
today,
I am honored to be here
to receive this honor.
I sincerely want to thank someone.
You skipped a meal again, didn't you?
Today's shift didn't work out.
I didn't have time to eat.
No matter what happens in the future,
make sure you eat first
before doing anything else.
Okay.
Jingqiu
You're here.
When you start working at the factory,
you'll be doing this job.
This inventory checking
requires attention to detail.
It's perfect work for a girl.
It's much better than doing odd jobs.
Not only is the pay higher,
there are also benefits.
Thank you, Brother Wan.
Here.
Take this.
Get familiar with it.
Come.
This way.
Keep going, keep going.
Jingqiu,
when checking inventory,
you have to go item by item.
Make sure everything is clear.
You can't have one more or one less.
You need to keep track in your mind.
There are some tricks to this.
I'll teach you later.
Hey, don't move.
I'm just checking
if you've trimmed your nails.
Brother Wan,
I never let my nails grow.
Oh,
I didn't notice.
Your hands
do so much work,
yet they're still so soft and delicate.
Oh,
Jingqiu,
I'm just looking out for you.
Can't I even touch your hand?
I'm not going to work at the factory.