♪Time once stopped everything♪
♪There's someone special♪
♪I flip the eternity dictionary♪
♪And uncover the suspense
that makes my heart beat fast♪
♪At this special moment
we run into each other♪
♪As unconsciously as we breathe♪
♪Holding hands over a long time♪
♪Means more than any word♪
♪Among a sea of people♪
♪I hold the umbrella for you♪
♪You hold the umbrella for me♪
♪I'll be special for you♪
♪You shelter me from the rain♪
♪Don't be afraid♪
♪Your love gets me through the haze♪
♪You'll have me♪
♪I'll search and wait♪
♪For the love of our lives♪
♪The future spent with you♪
♪We shall no longer linger♪
♪Is the best arrangement of love♪
♪The best arrangement♪
=The Oath of Love=
♪Is love♪
=Episode 8=
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
I'm not going to the seminar. Sorry.
Han Han.
Do I look like
a real cellist today?
No audience could see you from far away.
You mussed up my fringe.
What? Do I look okay?
You laughed at me before.
You also care about your fringe.
This is a special day.
It's the first time
that I play the cello
at such a concert.
I must care about every detail.
Do a good job, then.
If you perform successfully,
I'm afraid you no longer need
to play the triangle.
Of course. I must prove myself today.
Come on.
Is everybody ready?
Yes.
Let us
only practice one part,
from Bar 48 to 56.
- Okay.
- Only this part.
- Get ready for it. Tune the instruments.
- Okay.
(2019 Huaqing University
Orchestra Concert)
(Cellists: Han Han,
Lin Zhixiao, Sun Yang)
(Concert hall)
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
Stop.
What's wrong, Lin Zhixiao?
Why is your hand shaking so violently?
Did you practice too much?
Have you been practicing all these days?
Go take a rest.
Immediately!
Don't lose the greater for the less.
Don't ruin your career
for only one concert.
Mr. Jin,
I was okay this morning.
Give me a second chance.
- I can do it.
- Say no more.
Don't force yourself, all right?
Go take a rest.
Cao,
go get Fang Zhou here.
Fang Zhou, get your cello
and take her place.
All right.
Okay, the rest of you, get ready.
Zhixiao, Zhixiao.
Let's take a photo.
We haven't taken a photo together yet.
Just one photo
in the center of the stage.
Lin Zhixiao!
Sorry, Tongtong.
I accidentally knocked it down.
I'm sorry.
Gu Wei?
Sir,
long time no see.
Gu,
I didn't expect you to come
and watch the concert today.
Come on.
This is my daughter Han Han.
She's the chief cellist
of today's concert.
Hello, Mr. Gu.
Why do you not let it go?
- Who's your partner?
- Nice to meet you.
The concert was a success.
Thank you.
Who wants to enjoy
your poor performance?
I do.
You want to enjoy
her triangle performance?
Yes, I do.
And I think
Lin Zhixiao's triangle playing
can be the punchline of the concert.
Just now, I heard
that you asked her to pay
for the damage.
But as I can see,
your cello isn't damaged at all.
If you insist on asking
for compensation,
I guess you need
a professional institution
to confirm the damage condition
and the amount of compensation.
If it's really damaged,
I'll pay for that.
Who are you?
- I...
- He's my fan.
My fan.
Yes.
Look.
My fan.
You're my fan from now on.
Give me your hands.
Why?
You touched her cello.
Your hands should be disinfected.
Thank you, Dr. Gu.
But why did you come today?
As I said, I came to watch the concert.
I saw you talk with the principal.
He invited you, right?
- I...
- It's okay.
Even if you didn't come for me,
I still want to thank you
for helping me out.
I have to say
that you looked amazing
when you leaped to my defense.
You're like 1.8m tall.
I'm 1.836m tall, actually.
You have a good sense of humor, Dr. Gu.
Thank you.
Come on.
Let me walk you home.
Okay.
Uncle, Aunt, I'm full.
Have you enjoyed the meal?
Yes.
Gao,
how's the work of your team lately?
Thank you for your concern.
With Gu Wei there,
everything goes smoothly.
I had wanted him
to come back for dinner with you.
But he couldn't, for some business.
Xi,
do you know what he is busy with?
Aunt,
I don't understand him very well now.
I think he's been weird lately.
When I called him today,
he said he would watch a concert
and wouldn't come back for dinner.
Do you know about it?
Actually, I invited him
to attend today's seminar with me.
It was a rare chance.
But he said he couldn't come
because of some emergency.
It's just not like him.
He seems to be distracted recently.
Whose concert did he go to?
The concert of a patient's daughter.
Dr. Gu,
what are you doing?
What do you expect?
I...
I expect nothing.
Your wrist is obviously swollen.
Because of excessive practice, right?
Excessive friction of the tendon
for a long time
will lead to traumatic inflammation
of tendon and tendon sheath,
namely tendonitis.
It's an arthritic problem.
You'd better see an orthopedist.
Thank you.
Your hands are cold.
Put my suit on.
No, thanks. I'm strong enough.
I'm okay.
I'm a doctor.
My duty is to prevent disease.
I'm home.
Well...
Go back home.
I'm going then, Dr. Gu.
It's okay. It's okay.
I... I'm going back home.
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
Did you invite Gu Wei?
I did.
I'll go give him the ticket.
How about this? Leave the ticket to me.
I'm just on my way to see him.
Well, thank you, Dr. Gao.
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
♪Pass by the bustling scenery♪
♪Fascinated by a raindrop♪
♪Watch it glide on my fingertip♪
Why haven't you left yet?
Because you just turned on the light.
Dr. Gu,
thank you.
Thank you for helping me out today.
You're welcome.
I forgot
to return your suit.
Give it back to me next time.
♪Later I smiled and remembered,
leaning on you♪
It's already late.
You have to work tomorrow morning.
Good night.
♪They show love
by slowly getting closer♪
♪Secretly glad how incredible it is♪
♪One likes another♪
♪Leave all care♪
♪Without a trace, without reservation♪
♪All myself to you♪
(Friend Request,
Reject, Accept)
(Accept)
(Note: You have added him.)
♪They show love
by slowly getting closer♪
♪Secretly glad how incredible it is♪
Dr. Gu,
I'll return your suit after I wash it.
♪One likes another♪
♪Leave all care♪
You don't need to.
♪Without a trace, without reservation♪
♪All myself to you♪
♪One likes another♪
♪They show love
by slowly getting closer♪
(Gu Wei)
(Study on the Effect of PD-1 Inhibitor
in Stomach Cancer)
(Notice of Doctors' Consultation
of Huaqing University First Affiliated Hospital)
(Fresh Development of the Study
on Stomach Cancer-related Genes)
♪Leave all care♪
♪Without a trace, without reservation♪
He's indeed a doctor
and a straight-A student
that I'm inferior to.
Dad, Mom, I'm back.
- You're back?
- Mm.
Be seated.
We have something to tell you.
What is it?
What a poor attitude!
Sit.
Gu Wei,
you're no longer young.
A man gets married and has a job.
Now that you have a job,
time to get married.
Gao Xi is a good girl, I assume.
You were classmates for years
and you know each other very well.
In terms of family background
and personal record,
you make a perfect couple.
Dad,
could you stop making a choice
for me?
Gao Xi and I are only colleagues.
Let me make it clear.
I don't plan to get married yet.
How old are you now?
You still don't plan to get married?
Think about it.
In your hospital and our hospital,
most doctors get married
with doctors.
Why?
Because they can easily communicate
and understand each other.
Isn't that perfect?
A doctor should
have professional ethics.
He should particularly distinguish
patients from friends.
You're a good man,
but you're just too sentimental.
Gu Wei,
don't let us down.
(58. com, Property)
(The whole apartment to rent,
Fully furnished)
Dr. Gu,
here's the record of Bed No. 37
you asked for.
Put it there.
Why are there so many things?
I brought them from home.
I'm not going home for a while.
You're indeed busy
whenever you apply for a research fund.
I'll leave you alone, then.
Mm.
(Harrison's Gastroenterology
and Hepatology)
By the way,
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
have you received
(Harrison's Gastroenterology and Hepatology)
the concert ticket?
I requested Dr. Gao to take it to you.
(Huaqing University Orchestra Concert)
Do come and watch the concert.
I forgot
to return your suit.
Don't bother to wash my suit!
Take it to the hospital today.
Ms. Li!
Ah?
Come over, please.
What...?
What happened?
Look, look.
Why is it discoloring?
That's for mopping.
You have to dilute it.
What?
And this is for laundry.
What a trap!
They look the same, don't they?
You don't even wash clothes.
How can you distinguish them?
Besides,
a suit must be dry-cleaned only.
Why did you wash it?
I...
I think washing it with hands
can express my sincerity.
Sin... Sincerity?
Mm.
It's not your suit, is it?
It's so big.
It's mine.
It's the popular style of the season.
Oversize.
Over what?
You don't understand. Never mind.
I'll take care of it.
Get back to your business.
I'll solve the problem.
Just go. Go.
Shall I help you with it?
No, no. I can handle it. Off you go.
Wait a minute.
She's the family of my patient.
Dr. Du.
Go on with the ward round.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Hi.
Let's go.
Mm.
Dr. Gu, would you like some Pepsi?
Pepsi in the day?
You can also drink it at night.
When I received your message,
I came to see you.
I've got something to tell you, too.
Let's talk in my office.
Mm.
Dr. Gao. Dr. Gao.
Come over, please.
I'm sorry, Dr. Gu.
Punish me as you wish.
It's tie-dyed?
Is this the popular style recently?
I'm sorry. Terribly sorry.
How about this?
I'll buy the same suit for you
as compensation, okay?
Show me your right hand.
Ah?
Why?
Turn it over.
Seriously, Dr. Gu?
Will you hit my hand to vent your anger
just like Mr. Lin?
We're already in modern times.
Why do doctors still punish people?
Doctors in our hospital do research,
teach students, and give operations.
I can also be a teacher.
Terrific.
Give me your hand.
I failed to check carefully
under the streetlight last night.
You indeed need
a professional orthopedist
to check on your wrist.
But...
Your wrist is more important
than my suit.
(Register with an expert orthopedist)
Register with an expert orthopedist.
Dr. Gu,
did you line up for a long time
to register for me?
I didn't.
Dr. Du did.
He lined up for you
after his night shift.
You must have asked him to.
Or he wouldn't know
there was a problem with my wrist.
Fine. I know you want to help
without letting me know.
Thanks, Dr. Gu.
In this case,
go get a cup of water for me.
After saying so much,
I'm thirsty.
Got it. Be right back.
Wait a minute.
Wash the cup carefully.
Yes, sir.
(Apartments to let)
Take the temperature of Bed No. 15.
Okay.
Hello, Dr. Gao.
Wait.
Is it Gu Wei's cup?
Mm. I got some hot water for him.
Miss Lin Zhixiao,
I have to remind you as a doctor.
Your father is already discharged.
Don't often come here
unless you have to.
We're quite busy.
It fell to me to take care
of your father's chemotherapy.
Come to me if you have any problems.
As for some other doctors,
you'd better keep your distance.
Or it would create a bad influence.
Dr. Gao, you get me wrong.
I came to see Dr. Gu because...
You don't need to explain to me.
I saw you come in a hurry.
I guess you have something else to do.
I'm on my way to see Gu Wei.
Leave the cup to me.
I'll give it to him.
You may leave.
But...
Come on in.
Thank you.
What's wrong with her?
I haven't finished yet.
My bag is still in the office.
Dr. Du.
Miss Lin, what are you doing here?
You came to see Dr. Gu?
Knock at the door and get in.
But Dr. Gao is in the office now.
They keep the door closed?
Dr. Du.
Have you noticed
that Dr. Gao doesn't like me?
You bet.
I guess she likes no one,
but Dr. Gu.
When Dr. Gu is away,
I've never seen her smile.
I get it.
I'll get to my business.
- Bye-bye.
- Okay.
What's the look on your face?
You don't want to see me?
You're wrong.
I just met Lin Zhixiao.
She has something urgent to do.
Then I brought the cup to you.
Something urgent?
Not very important, I'm afraid.
After all, it's her privacy.
I shouldn't ask too much.
Mm.
Well, what can I do for you?
It's the paper of our application
for the research fund.
Review it.
Your eyes will be hurt like this.
I've got the printed paper.
Here. Read this.
Yesterday, I happened to
read a new paper
with basically consistent viewpoints.
It can be used as our new quote.
But I think we should
confirm the paper content more strictly
before we quote it.
It'll be less risky.
Well...
(Pepsi)
Looks like
you get along well with Lin Zhixiao.
Mm.
We get along well.
That's good.
Any more questions?
No.
I'll go see Dr. Du.
Mm.
Tell me the result
after you review the paper.
Okay.
Come on. Help me.
I'm dying.
I'm dying if nobody helps me.
Help me.
Oh.
Dr. Gu.
What took you so long?
Did you really have so much
to talk about?
You've been waiting for me here?
Where else could I go?
Thanks.
Now that you've waited for a long time,
shall I treat you to lunch?
Sure.
Let's go.
I don't need room cleaning!
Son, open the door.
It's me, your mother.
Hurry.
Wait a second.
Be right there.
- Son.
- Mom.
Get packed and go home.
Be quick.
Where's your husband?
Your father has gone abroad
for business.
He won't be back soon.
Oh, my dear son.
It doesn't feel good
to live in a hotel, huh?
Look, you're thinner.
I'm not.
Mom.
What?
I know why I'm thinner.
Lately...
Lately, I don't eat well
or sleep well.
I'm exhausted.
What happened, Son?
Tell me about it.
I'll try to help you.
It's just because my father
looks down on me!
To prove myself,
I've been working hard
on doing business.
And I've found
a great business opportunity.
Everything is ready,
but the investment fund.
It hurts, Mom.
Mom,
give me some money.
I'll make you a shareholder.
Go away.
You want some money again.
Could you stop
wasting your father's money?
Come on.
Why do you think I'm wasting money?
I'm starting business seriously.
Mom,
trust me this time.
This time?
I trusted you so many times.
You want me to trust you again?
How can I?
Mom,
stop packing things.
Do you want my father
to look down on me forever?
Mom, be seated.
Be seated, please.
It's okay that he doesn't trust me.
But Mom,
you have to trust me.
I'm borrowing money from you
one last time.
I'm serious.
I promise.
You will?
I promise
I will do business seriously
and surprise my father.
When I make money,
I'll buy presents for you.
Fine.
I'll trust you one more time.
I'll transfer some money to you
from my private fund account.
Really?
In this way,
your father won't be aware.
But I'm warning you.
This is the last time.
Yes.
And you mustn't be on the tiles anymore.
Got it?
I won't be on the tiles anymore.
I love you, Mom.
Come on, you're no longer young.
Why are you still childish?
However old I am, I love my mother.
All right. All right.
Go get packed.
And let's go home.
Hurry. Look how thin you are now!
(Sansan)
Shall we meet tomorrow?
Why are you playing
with your phone again?
I'll stop. I'll stop.
Get packed and let's go home.
I'm on it.
Dr. Gu,
what are we going to have for lunch?
It's up to you.
How about the hot pot?
Barbecue or crawfish?
What?
(Healthy porridge)
Those kinds of food
will easily accumulate heat in your body
(Healthy porridge)
and cause gastrointestinal illness.
You'd better have
less greasy or spicy food.
As a gastroenterologist,
I suggest a bland diet.
Check the menu
and see what you would like to eat.
Less salt and oil?
Normally, no oil is used in porridge.
You know quite a lot, Dr. Gu.
Here's our order. Thank you.
Okay. Please wait.
Is it appropriate?
Well, thank you, Dr. Gu.
Your hands will be cleaned then.
Okay.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Dr. Gu,
you're not a big eater.
You don't like the food?
Shall we go to another restaurant?
No, no. I'm just having a free lunch.
I don't have the nerve
to request anything.
It's good. Good.
It's healthy food.
You're right.
Didn't you say you would compensate me?
Right, right. I will.
I'll buy a new suit for you.
Not a very expensive one, okay?
Don't bother. Compensate me with labor.
I plan to move out.
Check the apartments for me.
Oh, no problem.
You should have told me.
I can help.
When will you be available?
Shall we make a date
to check the apartments together?
Seriously, Dr. Gu?
How old-fashioned you are!
When you want to check an apartment,
you can do it online.
Don't get me wrong.
I don't mean to laugh at you.
I just think...
Oh, I know. You're a serious guy.
And you don't often surf the Internet.
I get it.
Count on me.
You'll be satisfied.
Have some porridge.
Okay. Okay.
Enjoy your porridge, too.
Hello. This is your milk.
Thank you.
You came to me so early in the morning.
You're more punctual
than you are at work.
I have some good news for you.
I've rented the shop you fancied.
The one in the downtown?
Aren't you afraid
that you can't recover your costs?
What am I afraid of?
I'm Gu Xiao,
from a rich family.
I can do whatever I want.
Just think about it.
Think about the name of our café.
Name?
Enjoy?
Tasty?
Enjoy and tasty?
Mm.
Sounds good.
But a little bit
uninspired.
Uninspired?
Why don't you think of one?
I indeed came up with one.
San Gu Cafe.
Our names are in it.
In memory of our meeting.
What do you think?
San Gu?
What makes our meeting
worth remembering?
What are you talking about?
Our meeting isn't worth remembering?
Think about it.
How did we meet?
It was indeed an unusual meeting.
But it was also interesting.
Shall we do it again tonight?
Go away.
Why can't friends warm each other?
I don't need it.
Let me know when you need it.
(In-patient)
Dr. Gu.
What did the director say?
He asked me to rest for half a month.
In this way,
don't practice the cello
during that time.
Oh.
Goodbye, Dr. Gu.
(Symphony Orchestra)
You all did a great job at the concert.
I'd like to heavily praise Fang Zhou.
When she was assigned the mission
at the last minute,
she performed wonderfully
and cooperated perfectly
with other students.
She's awesome.
Thank you, Madam.
Fang Zhou is really great.
Zhixiao,
why haven't you slept
at this time of night?
Can you hear me, Zhixiao?
Hello, Dr. Gu.
Hello, Aunt Li.
I'm sorry
to call you at this time of night.
I was just off work.
I'm calling to check
Mr. Lin's physical condition.
It's so considerate of you, Dr. Gu.
He's recovering very well.
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way,
is Lin Zhixiao
still playing the cello?
Even you heard it?
Yes, yes.
I don't know why,
but since she came back home,
she's locked herself in the room,
playing the cello continually.
I called her, but she ignored me.
Actually, playing the cello
for a long time
and sitting with one pose
will be particularly bad for health.
She isn't in a hurry for the practice.
She should rest regularly.
Okay. Thank you for reminding me.
I'll try to stop her.
- Goodbye, Aunt Li.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
Zhixiao, it's getting late.
Get to bed early
and play the cello tomorrow, okay?
Zhixiao.
Dr. Gu.
Mm.
How's your wrist recovering?
Have you taken enough rest
as the doctor asked you to?
I have.
I've been resting.
I haven't played the cello.
Oh, really?
Now that you've taken enough rest,
please do me a favor.
You promised
to check the apartments for me, right?
I've been very busy lately.
So, could you please
sort out a file of apartments for me?
In the file,
there should be
more than a hundred apartments.
Email it to me tomorrow morning.
What?
A hundred apartments?
I want more alternates.
I'll count on you, then.
Dr. Gu, Dr...
What on earth is going on?
A hundred apartments?
What a cheap labor
to compensate him!
For Mr. Lin,
I'll bear with it.
(58. com, Apartments to let)
I'm not compensating him.
He's exploiting me instead.
(Evil Capitalist)
(Done)
(Evil Capitalist
Name: Gu Wei)
(58. com, Apartments to let)
(The mail has been sent.)
♪Look at that pair of eyes♪
♪Suddenly feel at ease♪
♪Gentle as pure white coat♪
♪Covering all the sadness♪
♪Wounds are healed in an instant♪
♪Warm the heart bit by bit♪
♪You asked me how to describe you♪
♪Empty words are not worthy of it♪
♪I haven't finished
telling you my heart♪
♪I'll prove it for the rest of my life♪
♪Only give you the best view♪
♪Only give you my greatest love♪
♪Seriously My girl♪
♪I want others to♪
♪Want them to♪
♪Envy you♪