I, Tong Xin,
want to be best friends with An Ning for life.
Forever and ever, may our friendship last.
An Ning?
Why is it you?
Aren't you Tong Xin's best friend?
Who said she's my friend?
Besides,
there are no forever friends in this world.
Rather than calling her my friend,
I'd say
she is now
a common enemy to both of us.
This is Tongxin's most precious thing.
I think
you'll use it
where it's most needed.
Dr. Wang, your case file.
Good, thank you.
You're welcome.
Dr. Jiang.
This is Anning's case file.
The director asked if you could take a look at it.
This young lady's condition
keeps fluctuating
and she doesn't cooperate with treatment.
Medication treatment prescription...
Is there a problem?
Her?
She has some serious issues.
Dr. Jiang,
I didn't expect you to ask me out.
The medical advice says
you should avoid cold and spicy food.
I only follow Dr. Jiang's medical advice.
Try the vanilla flavor.
If you want me to behave,
then be my attending physician.
But I have one condition.
Starting today,
you cannot appear in front of Tongxin.
You cannot disturb her life.
You cannot affect her emotions.
Why are you making it sound
like I'm the bad guy?
I'm the victim here.
I promise you.
I have matters to attend to at the hospital.
I need to go now.
When I was feeling down as a child,
I would come here.
Because I grew up in a single-parent family,
I had to listen to my mom about everything when I was young.
Bufan, what do you want to eat today?
Bufan, what should you wear today?
I had no say in anything, big or small.
Sometimes I even wondered
if I was my mother's son
or just her doll.
I thought things would get better when I grew up.
But now she
even wants to meddle in my marriage.
She's already picked out someone for me to marry.
I couldn't take it anymore,
so I came back to stay with my brother.
Who knew her reach would be so long?
From across
the ocean, she's still sending people to catch me.
Can you understand that?
Your mother...
Stop.
Don't give me that
'your mother only wants what's best for you' speech.
Do you even believe that?
I'm sick of hearing it.
What I want to say is
your mother has her perspective,
and you have yours.
Conflicts and misunderstandings between people
are completely normal.
What's most important is
how you find yourself in all this
and stay true to who you are.
Then give me some advice.
Make money.
Only when you're financially independent
can you be emotionally weaned.
So I need to be rich after all.
When are you going to give me a raise?
The company offers raises twice a year.
It depends on your performance.
That's strict.
I'll do my best.
What's wrong?
You're bleeding.
It's nothing. Just put some iodine on it later.
When I was little, my mom
would treat my small wounds just like this.
It'll be better soon.
Hello everyone, I'm Xiaoxin.
Today I'm bringing you a song
'It's Raining All Over the World'.
I hope you'll enjoy this song.
The sudden downpour.
Yet I don't want to hide.
Nowhere to go anyway.
Remnants everywhere.
Recording the past
all about you.
Rain turning the city upside down.
Hello everyone.
My name is Tongxin.
I'm bringing you a song today.
The sudden downpour.
Yet I don't want to hide.
Nowhere to go anyway.
Remnants everywhere.
Recording the past.
What's wrong?
It's so frustrating.
Whenever there's a camera pointing at me
or a bunch of people watching me,
my throat feels like it's stuck
and I can't sing at all.
It was the same when I participated
in that campus singing competition.
You're going to be a big star someday.
You'll have to perform on stage.
How can you be afraid of cameras?
By then, not just on stage
but even off stage,
there will be many cameras following you.
If you're nervous,
I have a little trick.
Have a mint.
It'll help with the nerves.
I don't want it.
How would this help?
Just try it.
How does it feel?
Cool and refreshing.
It does seem better.
If you're really scared,
I can point the camera at you
but I won't turn it on.
After you get used to it,
we can film something, okay?
The sudden downpour.
Yet I don't want to take shelter.
There's nowhere for me to go anyway.
Everywhere are remnants.
All memories recorded are about you.
The whole world is raining.
I hope you won't get wet.
Nostalgia is a stubborn disease.
I can't help wanting to care for you.
What role must I play to hear your voice again?
If memories are this heavy rain.
I still don't want to escape.
After all, I've already...
What's going on?
Sing!
You forgot the lyrics?
Forgot the lyrics.
Anyway, I have nowhere to go.
Everywhere are remnants.
All recorded memories are about you.
The heavy rain in this upside-down city.
Has someone replaced me?
No more news from you,
never meeting you again.
Perhaps you've
escaped the gravity of longing.
The whole world is raining.
I still think you're by my side.
Regret has its own inertia,
I still save half the umbrella for you.
Last time you said you wanted to isolate yourself to prepare for the album.
How's the preparation going?
Are you doing okay?
What is it? Got new work?
No.
I'm just worried about you.
Afraid you're keeping things to yourself.
What are you worried about?
Worried I can't sing anymore?
That's not what I meant.
It's just lately...
As it turns out,
what you all worry about will never happen.
What role must I play to hear your voice again?
If memories are this downpour,
I don't want the sky to clear.
Congratulations.
You've been recovering well lately.
This is a small gift.
Wishing you happiness every day.
I believe it won't be long
before we can hear you singing on stage again.
Thank you.
It's also thanks to your patience in communicating with me
and listening to what I have to say.
I've been getting to know your work recently.
Now I'm one of your fans.
By the way,
I bought tickets to your concert.
You should have told me earlier.
I could have given you front section tickets.
I couldn't possibly accept that.
I genuinely love your music.
I wonder if you could give me an autograph at the concert?
No problem. That's easy.
Actually,
we can
open up to each other
and talk about anything you want.
There's something recently
that's been confusing me.
Why don't you tell me about it?
When I was in high school,
someone did something that hurt me.
I was very upset
and hated him for a long time.
Until recently when he appeared in my life again
and suddenly became very nice to me.
I don't know if he's trying to make amends
or if it's something else.
I'm resistant
yet I can't push him away.
Many times,
hate and love can transform into each other instantly.
You could say
that hatred is also a form of love.
From what I'm hearing,
I feel like you still care about him,
you're concerned about him,
and that has never changed.
Maybe.
But I don't want to make the same mistake again.
You need to face it honestly
so you can move on.
Why not carefully consider your true feelings?
But as Jiang Yinchuan's friend,
I can only tell you
that he's usually a very cold person
and wouldn't act this way toward just anyone.
Who said it was Jiang Yinchuan?
You're always so busy with work
how come you have time for afternoon tea with me?
I asked you here for work reasons too.
Our company is collaborating with Qingyuan's new scenic area
on a resort project.
We're looking for someone with the right image and temperament
to be our spokesperson.
I thought you said
you didn't support my entertainment career,
but you still think of me when there's an opportunity.
Stop joking around.
I honestly believe that among all the female candidates,
you're the most suitable one.
Good taste.
By the way, tomorrow's Friday.
You should meet with the shareholders and the scenic area managers
to finalize this deal.
I've sent the address to your phone.
Don't forget to check it.
It's not confirmed yet.
There's another round of interviews.
Of course.
You're not the only one who wants this endorsement deal.
Who else is there?
Well, there's
that Yiyi you hate so much.
Her?
Alright, prepare yourself well.
I have another meeting. I need to go.
Bye.
Remember to check it.
The folder.
I haven't deleted it for her yet.
I'll delete it now.
I lost my lyric notebook long ago.
How did it end up with her?
Remember this? I've taken a look at it.
Many of the songs in it are quite good.
There's one that's not finished yet.
Seems like you wrote it for your first love.
Who gave it to you?
Do you want it back?
Come get it from me tomorrow.
If you don't want it, I'll burn it.
Ziran
Shouran