The water clock ticks as mist lightens the window,
Green lamp and jade brush stand ready at my desk.
Crafting words and phrases, plowing fields of ink.
Moonlight prints between verses where plum shadows thin,
Wind caresses the jade flute, its soul whispers light.
Years spent in study, seeking scholarly glory.
A lone traveler crossing thousands of miles,
Why fear the rain that lies ahead?
As long as we dare to try,
And boldly take the first step.
We'll discover that
Many things aren't as difficult as we imagine.
Fear is a reaction.
Courage is a decision.
Jiang Yinchuan.
I like you.
I can feel it.
You like me too, don't you?
Don't bother me anymore.
You're being
so cheap.
So that's Tong Xin, the sophomore boss.
What boss?
She's just Jiang's lapdog.
Jiang didn't even turn off his mic when rejecting her.
So what if he's her family driver?
She was the one confessing to Jiang Yinchuan in the broadcast room just now.
But Jiang Yinchuan likes her best friend instead.
It's disgusting. Acting so close with An Ning on the surface,
while trying to steal her boyfriend behind her back.
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
The doctor said you fainted due to extreme stress.
Are you feeling better now?
You little troublemaker.
Do you know what people are saying about you online?
See for yourself.
If you had answered my call yesterday,
and discussed this with me,
we wouldn't be in such a passive position now.
Your concert is coming up soon.
What should we do about this situation?
Xinxin, you've never been like this before.
What's really going on?
Is your throat injured?
I'm too exhausted lately.
I'm not in a good mood either.
I don't want to work.
Please help me reschedule all my appointments.
I want to isolate myself
and focus
on revising my concert album.
Those appointments were scheduled in advance.
They've already paid deposits.
How can we just cancel everything?
Oh dear, we—
Director Xie.
Maybe we should listen to Xinxin.
After all, the concert is the most important thing right now.
It might be good for her to focus in isolation.
It's a perfect chance to lay low
until this wave of public opinion blows over.
Fine.
Xinxin, get some good rest.
We'll be going now.
Let's go.
Remember to go to the hospital for your follow-up tomorrow.
Anan.
Finally seeing you again.
I'm sorry.
Anan.
When did you come back to the country?
What's wrong?
Don't want to see me?
How could that be?
After what happened back then,
I've been trying to contact you.
I sent you so many messages
and made so many calls,
but you never responded.
You ruined my life.
That's right.
I am that rat in the gutter you talked about.
I've been watching your life from the shadows.
But everything you have now
should have been mine.
You've become a big star now.
You're living the high life, collecting awards everywhere.
And you have the nerve to ask me how I'm doing.
Do you know?
Every song you sing now,
every lyric, every melody,
is a knife killing me.
All your achievements
were built on my flesh and blood.
It's not like that.
Get out! I don't want to see you! I don't!
Tong Xin in another scandal:
Intimate behavior with greasy 50-year-old tycoon,
Pair photographed entering hotels multiple times.
Where do they dig up all this old dirt?
That happened ages ago.
And they still bring it up.
That greasy 50-year-old man is my father.
Who else would he support if not me?
Then I'll issue a statement to clarify.
The headline will read:
'Tong Family Heiress Ventures into Entertainment'
No.
When I debuted, I promised my sister
not to reveal our family situation.
The public opinion is extremely unfavorable to you now.
If we don't find a way to divert attention,
your career will be completely ruined.
There's only one solution now.
Xinxin, you need to date someone.
You must be joking.
I haven't dated anyone in my ten years since debut.
Where would I find a boyfriend now?
I don't mean a real relationship.
Just pretend.
If you want to suppress this scandal about being kept by a rich businessman,
you need to release even bigger news.
Fight fire with fire.
Yes, exactly.
People nowadays don't care about the truth.
They just want gossip.
No matter how you clarify, nobody will believe you.
Look, I've always done everything your way before,
but this time you really can't be so stubborn anymore.
Look at my dark circles.
And look at Director Xie's.
Look, look, look.
The company has been incredibly busy
preparing for your concert.
The PR team
has been working overtime to manage public opinion for you.
Please have some mercy on us
and stop making everyone worry so much, okay?
Fine.
I'll date him for one month.
One month isn't enough.
That's too short.
At least six months.
You don't need to post about it every day.
Just check in occasionally when you have time.
Xinxin.
Three months.
Let's meet halfway. Can't be any less.
Fine. We'll break up after three months.
What are you all doing?
No noise in the hospital.
Hurry up! Follow me! Quick!
Let's go! We need to run!
What are you doing?
I'm warning you.
Your behavior right now
is seriously disturbing the patients' rest.
If you don't leave,
I'll call the police to arrest you.
Let's go. Come on. Go.
Everyone get back to work. It's over.
You're fine too.
Pretty clever.
How did you recognize me?
Me? Tong Xin?
You recognized me even though I'm all covered up.
Tell me, are you my fan?
Aixin.
Thanks for your help just now, little Aixin.
Remember to keep it a secret.
Didn't I just give you an autograph?
Why are you still following me?
I'm warning you.
If you keep sticking to me,
Hey! Hey!
I wasn't finished speaking.
My fans are truly excellent.
Your examination shows no issues at all.
Then why can't I sing anymore?
There's no physical abnormality in your throat.
The first time
you lost your voice while singing,
the most likely cause
is psychological.
That's impossible.
My mental health is perfectly fine.
Jiang Yinchuan
I like you.
I know.
So let's be together.
I can feel it.
You like me too, don't you?
Otherwise, why are you so nice to me?
Helping me with my studies and my singing.
Also because...
Also because my father is your family's driver.
I can't afford to offend Miss Tong.
Then why do you keep my hair tie
on your wrist?
You're not the only one with this hair tie.
An Ning has one too.
I thought you two didn't get along?
How is that possible?
She hates me,
but why can't I like her?
I know you two are good friends,
but you really don't compare to her at all.
Stop bothering me from now on.
You're being
so cheap.
What are you two doing?
The whole school can hear you.
You turned on the microphone.
Jiang Yinchuan.
You hurt me so badly back then,
I've remembered it for all these years.
Now
you dare to come back to the country acting like nothing happened.
I thought we would never see each other again.
But I never expected
that you would
dare to show up in front of me like this.
Mr. Jiang.
I'll take you somewhere fun.
Let's go.
I wonder how you've been
all these years.
Hey, bro. You're back in China.
What do you want?
Did you get into trouble again?
My mom wants to arrange a marriage for me,
and the woman is several years older than me!
You have to save me!
I can't help you with this.
If you don't like it, tell your aunt yourself.
She won't listen to me.
Anyway,
I'd rather die than marry an older woman.
Don't be so absolute,
or you might regret it later.
Then do you
regret it?
Ziran
Leran
Shouren