Xinxin, it's all set.
Xinxin.
It's just a school competition.
So what if you didn't make it?
You just didn't perform your best.
Xinxin, we've grown up together.
We share the same dream.
We'll debut together in the future.
Let's try again next time, okay?
Anan.
This must be Jiang Yinchuan's vote for me.
He's the only one in the whole school who voted for me.
It's an anonymous vote.
How do you know it was him?
Look. This is his draft.
Isn't the handwriting identical?
So what?
Do you like him that much?
He has good grades, good character, and good looks.
And the only vote I got was from him.
It shows he approves of me too.
How could I not like him?
His father is your family's driver.
The gap between you two is too big.
What's wrong with being a driver?
Professions aren't hereditary.
Jiang Yinchuan
Why didn't anyone pick you up today?
Your dad is busy today.
He can't take me home.
So now you're being requisitioned.
You could take a taxi.
I don't want to.
I can hold an umbrella for you if I sit behind you.
Not everyone gets this special service.
Jiang Yinchuan.
Did you vote for me in the last competition?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't pretend.
I recognize your handwriting.
Tell me honestly, do you like me too?
You're just too shy to admit it.
Get off.
What's wrong?
I was just kidding.
Why do I keep thinking about the past lately?
Maybe
I should really do as he said
and meet this friend.
Break up immediately. Break up immediately.
Your love won't last.
Your union is impossible.
Who's the crazy guy
making a scene at my door so early?
Alright, alright, alright.
Alright my foot!
Watermelons, 5 yuan for 3 jin,
guaranteed ripe and sweet!
guaranteed sweet! I'm Lin Bufan.
If you have a death wish
Go to hell.
There are many ways to die.
You don't have to die by my hands.
Dr. Jiang as a fiancé
is really putting on a good show.
She doesn't usually eat breakfast.
I brought her something.
Jiang Yinchuan.
What exactly are you after?
Why are you still showing up around her?
You hurt her so deeply before.
Now you want to pretend nothing happened?
I don't have any ulterior motives.
I just want to help her.
That might fool Xinxin.
But unfortunately,
I'm not falling for your act.
Because
I regret it.
See? People are just like this.
Always gluttons for punishment.
I couldn't protect my sister when I was studying abroad.
But things are different now.
Let me tell you, Jiang Yinchuan.
Whatever you're scheming in your mind,
you'd better drop it right now.
I won't let you hurt her again.
Tongxin, let me tell you.
As long as you don't break up with my brother,
I won't move from here.
I'm staying right here.
I'll blast my speakers every day.
I'll make sure everyone in this neighborhood knows.
Your love
won't last.
Your relationship is doomed to fail.
Hand it over.
Let me tell you, I'm not afraid of you.
I'm not afraid of you at all.
He hit me. What are you doing?
Lin Bufan.
Didn't I tell you to go back to my place?
Why are you here again?
It's you.
That rude lady.
Are you crazy?
First thing in the morning, without even brushing your teeth, you're attacking people.
This is my sister.
Who are you?
I am...
I didn't notice.
I really didn't notice.
What's wrong?
Mr. Tong, the scratch on your car door is long and deep.
Fine.
You accused me of scamming.
Called me a gold digger.
And now you've forgotten all about it?
You two are really in cahoots.
Lin Bufan.
Stop making a scene here.
Go back quickly.
You two brothers are really
quite the characters.
One's a clam,
the other's a loudspeaker.
I, Tong Xin, must have owed you both in my past life.
Xinxin.
Watermelons, 5 yuan for 3 jin,
guaranteed ripe and sweet!
Watermelons, 5 yuan for 3 jin.
Guaranteed ripe and sweet!
Xinxin!
Breakfast.
- Get out!
- Xinxin!
Xinxin.
Lin Bufan.
If you keep making trouble,
I'll call your aunt right now and have her take you back.
Do you hear me?
She called you a clam.
So what if she called me names?
Would it kill you
to show some backbone?
You, go back.
You're completely clueless.
Why can't you have just a little dignity?
Gourd Baby.
Xinxin.
Open the door, please.
Miss.
Tong Xin's sister.
Can't you hear me?
You got away last time,
but don't think you'll escape this time.
Add my WeChat.
Kid, I don't have time to play with you.
Miss, I'm not interested in you.
I'm not some player trying to hook up.
I'll pay for the damage to your car.
I don't need your money. Run along now.
Stop treating me like a child.
I, Lin Bufan,
am an honest and upright person.
No, I mean, I, Lin Bufan,
am a person of integrity.
am... am honest.
Just tell me how much and I'll transfer the money.
Seriously.
Here's the repair estimate.
A total of 30,000 yuan.
30,000?
Are you trying to scam me?
I have the insurance company's number.
You can verify it yourself if you want.
If you dare to do it, you must dare to face the consequences.
Pay up.
It's just 30,000.
I wouldn't have batted an eye in the past.
But now...
Recently,
I have to pay for this car.
Don't look down on me.
What are you going to pay with?
Can't I pay in installments?
How about this? Come work as my driver.
My driver just went on paternity leave.
Work as my driver for a month,
and we'll call it even on the 30,000.
Me, be your driver?
What's wrong?
Can't drive?
Are you kidding?
Driving is so simple.
Wait.
Someone as talented as me,
working as your driver?
Kid.
Think about it. You can't find
a more suitable job than this anymore.
Or would you rather call your mom
to come and pay for it?
It has nothing to do with her.
One month means one month.
I haven't even started making money
and now I'm losing a month of labor?
Tong Xin.
Are you...
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I just got rid of the reporters.
Yinchuan has already told me about your situation.
I'll help you overcome your psychological issues
so you can sing again.
I have a concert coming up soon.
I'm afraid there's not enough time.
If you fully cooperate with me,
I think it won't take long.
By the way.
Yinchuan and I are good friends,
so you can trust me completely.
As you know, I'm a public figure,
so this matter
cannot be known by anyone.
Of course.
Including Jiang Yinchuan.
Absolutely.
They're pushing us again.
Is Tongxin's theme song recorded yet?
She couldn't finish recording last time.
Probably still traumatized by what happened before.
This theme song,
she probably won't be able to sing it.
What do you mean she can't sing?
Xinxin said she'll pay the penalty herself.
Is this just about the penalty?
'Princess' is
a Golden Eagle Award-nominated film.
It's definitely going to be a hit!
She's just giving up such a great opportunity?
Besides, the concert is coming up soon.
If she can't sing,
what about the album?
If worst comes to worst, let's find someone else to sing.
We can't give the movie theme song to someone else.
Mr. Xie, Xinxin won't agree to that.
This won't work, that won't work.
If she keeps not being able to sing,
how is my company supposed to survive?
Mr. Xie, we've found the person you wanted.
What do you want to ask?
Dr. Jiang, is Tong Xin really your fiancée?
Didn't you say you weren't a fan of celebrities?
I'm not a fan of celebrities.
But I am a fan of my wife.
When did you two meet?
Did you...
Have you done your rounds today?
Not yet.
Then what are you waiting for?
Go do your rounds now.
The theme song for the movie 'Make Way for the Princess'
was released at 8 o'clock.
It's performed by popular singer Tong Xin.
Congratulations, Dr. Jiang.
Your fiancée has released a new song.
She's so beautiful.
Bluestone paved street,
a touch of slanting sunset.
Memories drifting away.
Xinxin, why are you here?
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I could have sent a car to pick you up.
Who did you get to sing the 'Princess' theme song?
I've already said I won't accept a ghost singer.
Doing this will destroy your reputation.
My tenth anniversary concert is coming up soon.
It should be my gift to the fans.
There absolutely cannot be someone else's voice in it.
You know the current situation.
Using a ghost singer is our only option.
It's the only solution we have.
Yes, and that girl who's singing for you,
she's your fan.
She really admires you.
Don't worry about confidentiality.
The company will handle everything.
Yong
Ziran