Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I can't believe Xuanze would do such a thing.
I'll definitely make him pay for this.
Let it go, sis.
It's all in the past.
I don't want to dwell on it anymore.
What are you going to do about your new song?
I'm going to rearrange it.
'Heart Gravity' will be even better.
We really owe Jiang Yinchuan for this.
Otherwise who knows
where Xuanze would have taken you.
Xinxin, have you made up your mind?
Are you really sure about being with Jiang Yinchuan?
He is my one and only choice, without a doubt.
He hurt you so deeply before.
Now that he's getting close to you again,
I can't help but think he has ulterior motives.
But now it seems
he really does love you.
Seeing my Xinxin so happy
makes me really happy.
Sis, it can't just be me who's happy.
You need to be happy too.
What's going on between you and Lin Bufan?
Him and I...
It's impossible.
Why?
When he first got together with you,
he was so proud and happy.
Why did it suddenly change?
We were never together.
That was just his imagination.
Besides,
we're not right for each other.
Don't talk about compatibility first.
I just want to ask you one question.
Do you like him?
What's the point of liking someone if you're not compatible?
We could never end up together anyway.
Xinxin, in this world,
not everyone is as lucky as you.
To meet someone you like who's also right for you.
Most people
are just settling.
And
life can't be sustained on feelings alone.
If you thought this way from the beginning,
why did you give him hope?
What happened between us was an accident.
Sometimes you're just too clear-headed and rational.
This actually makes it harder to see
what you truly want.
Thank you for ordering our couple jackets.
The customization process takes some time,
so thank you for your patience.
Wishing you both sweetness and happiness,
lasting love and a lifetime of joy.
If these custom items weren't non-refundable,
why would I put up with this?
They say love doesn't stay fresh,
but who knew it would spoil so quickly?
That heartless woman
completely shattered my heart.
She still leaves traces in my life even now.
Whenever I think of her,
I just feel a burning rage inside.
By the way,
there are still all her photos in my phone.
Delete them.
Go ahead
and get married.
Who else could take care of you?
Who else could be your driver?
Find someone old and ugly to spend your life with.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying, Fanfan?
It's my fault.
Mom apologizes to you.
I shouldn't have ignored your feelings.
If you don't want an arranged marriage, I agree.
Mom,
you're the best.
What's really going on?
Are you homesick?
If you miss home, just come back.
Okay.
Huahua.
I knew you'd come back to me.
After all, you're as smart as I am.
We're both at marriageable age.
Within our available options,
you and I are indeed the best choice for each other.
Since we've reached an agreement,
let's set the wedding date soon.
We'll fulfill our parents' expectations of this life milestone
and satisfy our families' wishes.
Afterward, we can live more freely.
So what's your plan?
My family has a hotel on Xiji Island.
To make it convenient for both families to attend,
we can hold the wedding there.
After marriage, we'll each focus on our own work.
Look, I found a really beautiful place.
I heard the food there is delicious.
I'll take you there sometime.
You'll definitely like it.
You're back so late.
The food and I have been waiting for you for ages.
It'll get cold if you don't eat now.
Hurry up.
I made your favorite beef brisket burger.
Household matters can be left to the housekeeper.
I've mentioned to you before.
During our marriage,
we can completely live our separate lives.
You don't interfere with me,
and I won't interfere with you being with others.
As long as we don't cause any trouble,
I hope our marriage can be open
and inclusive.
How can that work?
Loving someone means being completely devoted.
What's the point of having one foot in two boats?
Are you worried I might cheat?
Impossible. I, Lin Bufan, from head to toe,
inside and out, belong only to Tong Hua.
If you have any concerns,
we can sign a fair prenuptial agreement.
Here's to a pleasant marriage partnership.
Your ring is a couple's style, isn't it?
Do you like it?
I can buy one for you too.
You keep saying
that after marriage we can live our separate lives.
But let me be blunt.
When a child says they need to pee,
they've actually already wet themselves.
You're right.
I do already have someone I like.
But she's not the best marriage partner.
Does this bother you?
You shouldn't ask if I mind.
You should ask if the person you love minds.
Lin Bufan.
Can you turn up the temperature?
I'm freezing in here.
Yes, boss.
Lin Bufan.
We're just not compatible.
Your life is full of unknown possibilities.
Your life is like an adventure.
Because you're young,
you can afford to be reckless.
But I can't.
I need a clear future
and a suitable partner.
How are we not right for each other?
Tell me.
I can change.
What you feel for me now is just a momentary impulse.
You're willing to accommodate me now,
following my pace.
But what happens when the passion fades?
Lin Bufan.
I'm the foolish one.
I'm not brave enough,
too afraid to face my true feelings.
Why don't you go see him off?
Do you want me to go?
Of course I don't.
But he is your friend after all.
If you want to say goodbye to him,
I can drive you to the airport.
Xuanze and I
have already taken different paths.
Living our separate lives well
is the best choice for both of us.
I never realized before
that Xuanze had those kinds of feelings for me.
Jiang Yinchuan,
tell me,
am I too slow to notice things?
I think
it's not that you're slow.
Before, your heart only had room for one person,
so you couldn't see anyone else.
Who? I don't know what you're talking about.
Really don't know?
No.
Do you know now?
Still don't know?
Jiang Yinchuan, I'm back.
My song 'Heart Gravity'
won the Best Original Song Award.
Jiang Yinchuan.
I didn't expect Dr. Jiang to be so romantic.
It's a bit cliché.
But I really like it.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Don't move.
There's a small bug on your shoulder.
Where?
Let me catch it for you.
It looks like a small spider.
Jiang Yinchuan, you...
Got it.
Xinxin.
I'm so happy to be part of your youth.
And I'm grateful
that I can still be with you at this moment.
You're like a warm sunshine
that brightens and warms my life.
In the days to come,
I want to be with you every single day.
Xinxin,
will you continue this journey with me?
That's so sudden.
Aren't you afraid I might say no?
I've waited all these years.
If you don't accept,
I can keep waiting.
Until you accept me.
Not a bad attitude.
Then I'll
say yes for now.
Later,
I'll see how you perform.
My third wish
is to be with Jiang Yinchuan.
I hope all of Tong Xin's wishes come true.
Mom said no pressure. We won't force you.
But that girl is really outstanding.
Even if you don't date her,
couldn't you at least be friends?
More friends means more opportunities.
I'm already preparing to go to the airport.
Mom knows, but she's also in China.
I heard she really wants to see you too.
Since you have time, why not chat with her?
Alright then. Send me the address.
I'll go meet her.
I've sent her the address.
She'll pick you up.
This is the same model as Tonghua's car.
So all these rich people like the same car.
Hello, I'm Lin Bufan.
Why are you here?
Get in.
Get in what car?
I won't.
I'm not getting in.
I suggest you drive away now.
My fiancée will be here to pick me up soon.
Don't let her misunderstand.
So you have a fiancée?
Yes, I do.
My family arranged it.
What's it to you?
My fiancée and I are a power couple.
We're perfectly matched.
You think you're the only one who can find someone suitable?
I'm even better at it.
Do you like your fiancée?
Of course I do.
I like her very much.
We fell in love at first sight.
We're inseparable.
We're...
We're about to have a shotgun wedding.
Excuse me.
I need to go.
I'm afraid you don't even know your fiancée's name.
Or what she looks like.
How is that possible?
I know very well.
Let me tell you.
Her name is...
Her name is Tong...
Hua.
You're the fiancée my mother arranged for me?
That's right.
I just found out too.
I was very reluctant before.
But now I'm quite satisfied.
Get in the car, my fiancé.
I refuse to be your fiancé.
I don't agree to this marriage.
I won't accept this arrangement.
Ziran.
Yangran.
Keying Temple.