[Love in Pavilion]
[Episode 1]
Demon Lord,
the Star-Picking Tower
will be completed in 10 days.
Ten days?
I must see
the tower completed in five days.
Do you understand what needs to be done?
Yes, I will go capture some humans right away.
[Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord from Nanchui]
Huaizhu,
when we came to this town last year to gather herbs,
it was still very lively.
The whole street was
full of foreigners speaking gibberish.
Why is no one here now?
I heard that great demons have been coming here recently.
It's not peaceful.
But this inn is still here,
which is somewhat surprising.
You need to be careful.
Don't worry.
With your Demon-Slaying Fire,
I'm not afraid of those evil demons.
Demon-Slaying Fire?
What are the people from Divine Fire Villa doing here?
[Muyue Inn]
[Dongfang Huaizhu from Yiqi Alliance]
[Dongfang Qinlan from Yiqi Alliance]
Innkeeper!
Sir, two bowls of rice noodles, please.
Coming.
Waiter!
Two bowls of rice noodles.
Ladies,
have some tea first.
Sir,
are those demon-warding bells hanging up there?
I think they rang just now.
They were all left by the great demon hunters from before.
Sometimes they work,
sometimes they don't.
Where have all the villagers gone?
When my sister and I came to gather herbs last year,
this place was so lively.
You two don't know,
but Nanchui has
demons causing trouble recently.
They've kidnapped many people.
The villagers who could
escape have all done so.
What kind of demons
are this bold?
They're spider demons.
Then why are you still staying here?
If I left,
where would the demon hunters stay?
Don't worry, ladies.
The demon hunters
left me a lot of magical artifacts.
This inn is safe.
It's safe.
Walking so stiffly,
you must have just taken human form recently.
Indeed, you're not an easy one.
Fortunately, I was prepared.
It's a ghost-faced spider?
Interesting.
That's the real innkeeper.
Qinlan!
Drop the flute,
or I'll kill her.
Huaizhu!
How dare you play dirty tricks?
Shameless!
Such strong sword energy.
Where...
am I?
Hello, miss.
Are you
alright?
A mask.
A sword.
Could he be
the legendary Sword Master?
[Sword Master from Mask Group]
There was poisonous mist on the streets.
I took the liberty
of bringing you to this more open area.
You...
Can you turn your face away?
Should I thank you then?
That's not necessary.
But I have a favor to ask.
I saw you fight with Divine Fire,
so you must be Miss Dongfang.
What do you want?
I was hoping to...
It's a bit difficult to say.
How about...
Sorry about that.
I have an urgent need
I cut off a lock of your hair today.
I will repay you duly in time.
Stop right there!
Are you here for
the great demon who's been abducting people in Nanchui?
If so, do you know the demon's whereabouts?
I have a general idea.
It's in the mountains ahead.
My sister and I often come here to gather herbs.
Lilu Mountain stretches for a hundred miles.
She has already pointed out the location to me.
And it's quite precise.
I assume you need my help.
You just cut off some of my hair.
You must have a plan to defeat the enemy.
How about we work together?
Alright.
But before we go, I have three conditions for you.
That's fine.
One,
you can't attack.
Two,
you must stay within 10 steps from me.
Three,
hold onto my scabbard
and never let go.
It's a deal.
Someone kidnapped a beautiful young lady!
Help!
Huaizhu?
This is where they built the Star-Picking Tower.
My sister is here too.
Remember our three conditions.
When the battle starts,
you must not be more than 10 steps away from me.
Can you keep up?
As long as you don't turn to face me,
no problem.
But the area below the clouds
has been sealed with a poisonous barrier.
How will you get down there?
Naturally, I have my own methods.
You broke through the clouds with one strike.
Who exactly are you?
I'm just a swordsman who likes cute masks,
nothing more.
[Cave Prison, Nanchui]
Qinlan!
Huaizhu!
I'm here!
Huaizhu, what took you so long?
I waited for you for ages.
Stop right there.
[Members of Nangong Family, Yiqi Alliance]
You're from the Mask Group?
Indeed.
The Mask Group looks down on the Yiqi Alliance.
This lowly group
is practically a cult.
Running into us today,
you're out of luck.
Not exterminating demons when encountering them
is considered being in cahoots with them?
[Li Zizai from Mask Group]
This makes us
an illegal organization in the Yiqi Alliance's book?
[Li Quzhuo from Mask Group]
I think this Yiqi Alliance
is the most tyrannical and unreasonable.
Third Brother, Fourth Brother,
these three noble scions say
we're in trouble if we run into them.
Masked brothers,
they also said
they're going to attack Nanchui.
That's utter nonsense.
We're from the Nangong family.
If you dare to oppose us,
you'll be sent to the Inspection Bureau
to die!
The abducted civilians should all be imprisoned here.
Lock these three up.
Rescue the rest of the people.
Alright, Big Brother.
Where's the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord?
Take me to him.
No problem.
I'm just afraid you'll have the luck to get there
but not to return.
I'll go with you.
I can't be more than 10 steps away from you.
That works.
What are you up to now?
[Lady Poison from Nanchui]
I promised you, my dear,
that after you recovered from your injuries,
I would give you a gift.
We're not even married.
Who's your dear?
If you see this gift,
you'll surely agree to marry me.
[Star-Picking Tower, Nanchui]
I've only been to your home three times.
I couldn't remember all the details.
But I found
the blueprints of your family's building.
This Star-Picking Tower
should be exactly the same as your home back then.
[Nangong Chui, Young Master of Nangong Family, Yiqi Alliance]
Kill!
You're remembering painful memories again, aren't you?
Our clan leader was obsessed with building towers.
Sometimes he would steal timber from the Nangong family.
But we never killed any of them.
I don't understand...
Why did the Nangong family
exterminate our entire clan?
Let me show you something.
I captured people from the Nangong family to build the Star-Picking Tower.
After it was built,
I killed them all
and used their bones and weapons
to make bone bells.
Do you like it?
You killed so many people from the Nangong family.
There are even more on the cliff outside the tower.
Nangong Ye's head
will hang up here too one day.
But won't doing this bring trouble?
Of course it will.
So you are the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord?
Who are you two?
How dare you trespass Nanchui's forbidden area?
Your skills are quite impressive.
You're from the Yiqi Alliance.
You dare to hurt Lady Poison?
You really must be tired of living.
Hundred-Eyed Barrier?
Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord, the Spider Demon King of Nanchui,
has a body full of golden eyes.
Each golden eye has 100 years of cultivation
and has strong demonic energy.
Able to seize souls,
he dominates Nanchui.
But today, the descendant of the Dongfang Divine Fire is here.
Your kryptonite has arrived.
Demon Lord!
What magical artifact did you use
to destroy my thousand-year demonic eyes?
It's just a handful of Miss Dongfang's hair.
Dongfang Divine Fire...
Take care, everyone.
We do good deeds without leaving our names.
If you insist on remembering our kindness,
just remember to spread the word about the two young heroines from the Dongfang family.
Thank you, thank you.
It's nothing.
We saved all these people.
We dealt with all those bad guys.
Masked brother, are you trying to steal my credit?
You...
No.
Of course, the young heroine from the Dongfang family deserve all the credit.
See?
This masked brother has a beautiful heart and face.
Let's stay here
and wait for my sister and your big brother to return.
We'll wait patiently.
Let them face the enemy together
and give them a chance to develop their feelings.
The Demon Lord built this Star-Picking Tower for me.
If you insist on paying with someone's life,
then take mine.
Lady Poison.
Humans are the most cold-blooded.
Talking to them about loyalty and reason
is futile.
Even if you have a long-standing grudge against the Yiqi Alliance,
those civilians you kidnapped
were innocent.
Innocent?
Do you know how many of my people
originally lived in this Star-Picking Tower?
Four thousand eight hundred and seventy-one.
During that massacre,
fire burned for seven days.
Their bodies were completely destroyed.
Were they guilty?
Sister,
go!
My parents,
and my brother who had only transformed for 10 days...
Were they guilty?
What crime did we commit?
Our crime
was merely cutting down
one of Master Nangong's Golden Nanmu tree.
It was his precious wood for making coffins.
It's just a box for the dead,
yet it cost us 5,000 lives.
In the eyes of you humans,
being born a demon
is our crime.
When I kill humans,
I'm cruel.
Lady Poison's clan was peaceful
and was slaughtered.
If I have to choose...
I'll choose cruelty.
When the Yiqi Alliance attacks Nanchui,
and the demons in your territory die miserably,
can you truly bear
such a heavy price?
[To the Yiqi Alliance Leader]
This is Nangong Ye's
[Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord of Star-Picking Tower in Nanchui led his demons to kill and capture Nanchui civilians]
request to the leader of the Yiqi Alliance
[Alliance Leader, please allow us to mobilize the forces of Yiqi Alliance to attack Nanchui and purge the demons. From Nangong Ye.]
to attack Nanchui?
The Nangong family, for the sake of a coffin,
massacred Lady Poison's entire clan.
You've killed so many of his people.
Do you think this
isn't enough for all of Nanchui to pay with their lives?
Who exactly are you?
And where did this document come from?
That's not important.
What's important is whether you believe it or not.
The Nangong family has absolute power in the Yiqi Alliance.
Every word in this document
will become reality.
You may not be afraid of the Nangong family,
but what if the entire elite force of the Yiqi Alliance comes?
You came to find me
just to say these things?
No.
I came to kill you,
Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord.
If I were to use your demon core to save your Nanchui,
would you
dare give it t ome?
How could a human possibly save demons?
The Nangong family is not innocent,
and neither are you, Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord.
The ones I want to save
are the innocent ones mentioned by Lady Poison.
I hope their brethren,
their parents,
their younger siblings who have just transformed,
won't die.
Although I am human,
not every human
is like Nangong.
Audacious humans,
how dare you cause trouble in my Nanchui territory?
Have you considered the consequences of being obliterated?
This demonic energy is far stronger than the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord's.
It's the Nanchui Poison King.
Quickly, leave the building!
[Huandu Qingtian, Nanchui Poison King]
With such demonic aura,
may I ask if you are the Nanchui Poison King,
Huandu Qingtian?
Causing trouble in my Nanchui territory,
you even dared to touch my nephew, the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord.
You,
and you,
must all die.
Such strong demonic energy.
Is this the Hundred-Eyed Demon Lord?
Is he this powerful?
Miss Dongfang,
please stay here.
Be careful!
Dongfang Divine Fire!
Let me borrow your Divine Fire.
Young one,
you have some skills.
But compared to me,
you're still two
or 3,000 years of cultivation and experience short.
Retreat quickly.
You can't take my nephew's demon core away.
Come out now, or are you seeking death?
Coming!
Fourth Brother,
the swords you make are getting worse.
Big Brother,
be reasonable.
This sword could block one attack from old Huandu.
It's good enough.
This Nanchui Poison King's toxic miasma has been refined for 1,000 years.
It's indeed formidable.
If that's the case,
let's fight our way out.
Such big words.
Let's see
if you can break through this move of mine.
Third Brother, help me out.
I'm coming!
Freeze!
As expected.
Even with a body of all poisons,
it still operates on the basis of qi circulation.
As long as we lock the qi channels,
we can temporarily restrain the old demon's attacks.
Old Huandu,
what other tricks do you have?
Ignorant fools.
Again?
How many more tricks do you have?
Fourth Brother, draw your sword!
Seal!
Break!
Spirit Shell,
open!
Big Brother, catch the sword!
This is good.
It'll be my main sword.
Big Brother,
here's a bottle of wine.
You understand me.
Miss, stay calm.
Although I don't know if it will work,
let me give it my all first.
The spirit swords have merged.
Just one more breakthrough to go.
Then I'll break through your Xuanwu position first.
Third Brother, Fourth Brother,
take the lady and leave first.