[Love in Pavilion]
[Episode 29]
Father.
You've finally found me.
Are you really beyond the Boundary?
Tell me where you are.
I'll come save you.
All this time,
I've been communicating with you
through dreams, using my consciousness.
Father.
Let me tell you
why I came here first.
When you turned sixteen,
your uncle Yang He,
Yitan's father,
saw something terrifying.
He said
through some unknown means,
the Black Grief Tree beyond the Boundary
had connected with the Tushan Grief Tree.
Through the Tushan Grief Tree,
the Black Fox was frantically absorbing hatred from within the Boundary.
Yang He used all his spiritual energy
to forcefully activate his Clairvoyance
and saw the weak point in this connection
beyond the Boundary.
So I came here with the Wangquan Sword.
Who's that? Speak!
After severing the connection between the two Grief Trees,
the Black Fox discovered my whereabouts.
I realized I was no match for her.
I could only hide in the shadows,
concealing myself
and communicating with you through dreams using my consciousness.
But my willpower is limited,
so I can only
speak to you briefly each time.
Yang He said
during the solar eclipse,
the Black Grief Tree's hatred peaks,
so it's most likely
to connect with the Grief Tree within the Boundary.
There's one coming soon.
You must be vigilant.
You cannot let her succeed.
I understand.
The Black Fox is terrifying powerful.
She can control others.
Without thorough preparation,
never rashly venture beyond the Boundary.
But Father...
No buts!
Don't let my efforts be in vain.
Don't let everyone's efforts go to waste!
Unless you're sure you can kill her,
you mustn't rush to your death!
Yes, Father.
Hongye,
kneel down.
Kneel down.
♪ A sudden storm fills the night ♪
♪ 3,000 mayflies plunge into the dark river ♪
♪ The relentless march of time ♪
♪ Sweeping away the young you and me ♪
♪ I open my eyes ♪
♪ To the color of the night ♪
♪ With a wave of the sword, the mountains and rivers are ravaged ♪
♪ In an instant, I shelter myself in this fleeting life ♪
♪ Countless times we traversed cliffs and abysses ♪
♪ Side by side ♪
The coming-of-age ceremony is complete.
♪ I remember every moment as clear as daylight ♪
From this day forward,
restrain your willful nature,
uphold the virtues of our ancestors,
♪ This heavy snowfall brought by fate ♪
and strive for self-cultivation and world peace.
♪ This hopeless struggle ♪
♪ Is it insoluble? ♪
♪ Your warmth ♪
♪ A trace alone breaks down my heart's defenses ♪
Although I'm not bright,
♪ Across countless withered bones and fallen leaves ♪
I respectfully accept your blessing.
♪ Watching a blood-red sunset together ♪
♪ I thank the heavens ♪
♪ I get to brave the blizzard with you in this life ♪
♪ With the wind ♪
My son, Hongye,
♪ Comes countless farewells ♪
you have come of age.
♪ Whose lashes ♪
Remember my words.
♪ Are dyed red? ♪
Once you grasp the essence of the Unparalleled Sword,
♪ Even if a single sword ♪
♪ Turns love and hate to ashes ♪
the Wangquan Sword
♪ You still come to me ♪
will come to you!
♪ Fulfilling our destiny ♪
I finally know where my father is,
and that the final battle with the Black Fox is imminent.
♪ With a wave of the sword, the mountains and rivers are ravaged ♪
This battle
is not just for my father
♪ In an instant, I shelter myself in this fleeting life ♪
but also to change the fates of all humans and demons.
♪ Countless times we traversed cliffs and abysses ♪
My comrades in the Mask Group
♪ Side by side ♪
are also working to unveil the mask
♪ I remember every moment as clear as daylight ♪
of this world.
♪ This heavy snowfall brought by fate ♪
♪ This hopeless struggle ♪
♪ Is it insoluble? ♪
♪ Your warmth ♪
♪ A trace alone breaks down my heart's defenses ♪
♪ Across countless withered bones and fallen leaves ♪
♪ Watching a blood-red sunset together ♪
♪ I thank the heavens ♪
♪ I get to brave the blizzard with you in this life ♪
♪ With the wind ♪
♪ Comes countless farewells ♪
♪ Whose lashes ♪
♪ Are dyed red? ♪
♪ Even if a single sword ♪
♪ Turns love and hate to ashes ♪
♪ You still come to me ♪
♪ Fulfilling our destiny ♪
♪ The rain falls ♪
♪ Tearing apart the long night ♪
♪ Unraveling ♪
♪ My suppressed tribulation ♪
♪ Flowers on the distant end bloom ♪
♪ So near yet so far ♪
♪ Get dead-drunk again, with no care of the passing of time ♪
Your Highness.
The solar eclipse is approaching.
The Grief Trees will be reconnected.
Your Highness is mighty.
Connecting the Grief Trees is crucial.
Do you think Lord Jiuhuo alone
can handle it?
[Unparalleled Sword]
So Uncle Shouzhuo
went beyond the Boundary alone to sever the connection
between the Grief Trees?
At my father's request, your father
exhausted his spiritual energy to activate his Clairvoyance
and saw the weak point in the connection.
That's why when Uncle Yang
fell gravely ill...
Yitan.
I'm sorry.
What for?
In this life,
I've found a true confidant
to celebrate my happy moments
and brave hardship together.
I'm beyond lucky.
When my father passed,
I was by his side.
He left with a smile,
so I guess he had no regrets.
Right, Hongye,
you just said that
around a solar eclipse,
the two Grief Trees are most likely to connect.
Based on celestial signs,
there will be a solar eclipse soon.
I'll keep watch near Tushan.
Okay.
Get Zui to go with you.
[Unparalleled Sword]
We need fresh flowers for the memorial.
And...
I'm sure your mother loved
looking beautiful.
You didn't have to come.
You could've just waited for me at Tushan.
Do you know what this means?
I do.
We're family now.
I shouldn't be too polite.
That's more like it.
You're here, Miss Wangquan.
Hello, Grandpa.
We've just made some date cakes.
Want to try some?
Sure, I'll go try it.
I'll leave you two to have a good chat.
Why do you suddenly want to
go see your parents?
Yitan.
I've made many mistakes in the past.
Anyway, the Yang family is in your hands now.
I have no more regrets.
Grandpa.
I know the cause of my father's death.
That's what happened.
Grandpa.
My father and Uncle Shouzhuo
protected both the human and demon worlds.
If it weren't for them,
the Eternal Night might've already descended.
Wangquan Shouzhuo discovered
the rapid increase of resentment beyond the Boundary.
So he asked He to activate his Clairvoyance.
Yes.
On what grounds?
Wangquan Shouzhuo is the leader of Yiqi Alliance.
In his pursuit of fame and glory,
what right does he have to take away my He?
Grandpa.
What?
Am I wrong?
In this world,
who'd risk their life just for fame and glory?
Because within the Yiqi Alliance,
his Wangquan family has immense wealth and status.
Of course he can risk his life to protect it.
But what does our Yang family have?
We have nothing!
Life isn't just
about fame and fortune.
Without money
and power,
humans are worse off than livestock.
You'll see all the ugliness in this world.
Is Wangquan Hongye still
planning to investigate the Black Fox matter?
Don't risk your life with him.
You're the last hope of our Yang family.
I can't ignore it.
Grandpa,
you should rest early.
Yitan!
I've sworn on behalf of our family
to stand with the Wangquans through thick and thin.
I'm in charge
of our family now.
Grandpa,
just enjoy your golden years.
[Tomb of beloved son Yang He and virtuous daughter-in-law Ye Yuwei]
I heard you arguing with Grandpa.
I thought
he'd understand my father.
Now I realize
my father knew my grandpa too well.
That's why he kept it a secret.
The Yang family...
is really a mess.
Uncle Yang He,
Aunt Yang Yan,
and you
are all brilliant like pearls.
How's that
a mess?
I'm fine.
You don't have to cheer me up.
Father-in-law,
Mother-in-law,
let me introduce myself.
I am
Wangquan Zui.
From now on, Yitan will be
under my care.
Rest assured.
I have a fierce temper.
I'll deal with anyone or anything
that upsets Yitan.
Master,
here you are.
These are the jewelry sent from Ruyi Pavilion.
Please choose a few pieces
for use at the grand wedding.
Don't call me Master anymore.
Put the things down and leave.
Long time no see.
You think your family will rise to prominence
by Yang Yitan marrying Wangquan Zui.
You sure are foolish, Yang Huanzhou.
Yang He died because of the Wangquans.
Yang Ying is gone for good.
Yang Yitan will also soon embark on this path of no return.
Our Clairvoyant Yangs
are just sacrificial pawns for the Wangquans!
Now you get it.
By marrying Wangquan Zui,
the Yangs will
completely become a vassal of the Wangquans,
until they've squeezed you dry.
[Tushan]
Take a look.
Look.
They say the Grief Tree is magical.
Yeah.
Yitan, look!
The Grief Tree!
So beautiful.
If only the Grief Tree could also grant humans
with renewed love
in their next life...
Humans only have one life.
It's enough to live without regrets.
So unromantic.
You're right too.
Are you two interested
in our Tushan red love knot?
I have it already.
Want one?
No.
We bought from him before.
Sir, Miss,
would you like
a pair of our Tushan red love knot?
They're very effective.
What knot?
The Tushan red love knot.
They've been blessed by our Tushan leader
personally.
It's super effective.
I didn't know the Tushan leader was in this business too.
Of course!
Listen...
Come, come closer.
Do you see these red threads?
It's super red
because it's dyed
with the juice of the flowers
from the Grief Tree!
I don't tell this to just anyone.
Take a look.
Have a look.
The love knot.
Tushan forbids humans from entering.
How'd you get the flowers
from the Grief Tree?
Um...
The wind blew them here.
Yitan.
What's with the interrogation?
They're just doing business.
Yes, yes.
Pay him.
This is called...
The Tushan red love knot.
The love knot.
Right, right.
We'll buy it.
Thank you, Miss. Thank you.
Pay him. Quickly.
Thank you, Miss.
Thank you, Sir.
Enjoy, you two.
Wait,
you believe in
such nonsense?
They're selling a sentiment.
A story.
We're selling a story.
When you get home,
you must not cut these red threads.
If you two can hold hands
and spend the night with it,
I guarantee your love will last
forever.
Got it?
Your love will last forever.
Forever and ever!
Got it?
This sells the best.
You believe in such scams?
It's better to be safe than sorry
in matters like this.
Yitan,
don't go anywhere tonight.
Stay here with me.
Sure.
♪ Has there been a dream ♪
♪ Where you cried and chased after someone's back? ♪
♪ Your face is streaked with tears when you wake up ♪
♪ Memories are like wind ♪
In this life, my heart
♪ Traveling a long journey ♪
is full
♪ The sun sets and the moon rises ♪
with you.
♪ You're a wavering candle flame ♪
♪ Shedding light on our past ♪
♪ How do I ♪
♪ Tell you ♪
♪ I love you? ♪
♪ How do I ♪
♪ Tell you how much ♪
♪ I miss you? ♪
♪ A parting is like a tree's growth ring ♪
♪ The rings are trapping ♪
♪ All the lovesick souls ♪
♪ No words are needed when our eyes lock ♪
♪ No words are needed when our souls connect ♪
♪ Turn around, love is like falling petals ♪
♪ How to grow roots? ♪
♪ No words are needed when we brush shoulders ♪
♪ It goes without saying that we yearn for each other ♪
♪ We missed out on each other ♪
♪ We're waiting for a reunion ♪
I went to check on the Grief Tree.
I didn't want to wake you.
Send a letter if you need me.
I only removed the red thread after dawn.
Grandpa?
Zui?
Zui!
Zui.
Yitan.
Who are you?
Grandpa?
During the solar eclipse,
if the Black Grief Tree beyond the Boundary
and the Grief Tree within exert their power simultaneously,
the two giant trees will connect.
Then I'll absorb the power of the Grief Trees,
and breaking the Boundary will be possible.
Black Fox's demonic aura.
I offer my flesh and blood as a sacrifice,
summoning the world's evil thoughts
to destroy all light!
Grandpa!
I heard from Hongye that
the person who released Jiuhuo in the dungeon
used this technique.
Yitan,
submit to the darkness with me.
Lady Black Fox will give us everything
and share the world with us.
Kill Wangquan Zui.
Don't be a slave to the Wangquans anymore!
I offer my faith as a sacrifice,
summoning the world's light
to destroy all darkness!
Why are you...
doing this?
It's all for your own good.
When have you ever done anything for my good?
You're greedy and vain.
Was squandering our family fortune for my good?
You put me in danger.
Was forcing me to activate my Clairvoyance for my good?
Was driving my uncle to death
and driving my aunt away for my good?
And now,
you want to kill the one I love.
Is this all for my own good?
The Clairvoyant Yangs
should never have been under the control of the Wangquans.
They killed your father,
drove your aunt away,
and now they want you to be their lackey!
That's still better than
living in this messed-up Yang family
and looking at your ugly, vicious faces!
So there is hatred in your heart after all.
But this hatred
is far from enough.
Why don't you kill me now?
If you can't kill me,
I won't spare Wangquan Zui!
Zui.
You're a Yang daughter-in-law.
Today, please help our Yitan.
Yitan.
This is the power of hatred.
What use is love?
Love will only be a handicap.
Only hatred
will give you endless power.
Yang Yitan.
Kill him to save your Wangquan Zui.
Kill him,
and you'll be the strongest being in the Yiqi Alliance.
Yang Yitan.
You've finally become what you were meant to be.
Yitan.
Today, I sacrifice myself
to awaken your limitless power.
There will come a day
where those who looked down on us Yangs
are trampled
under the Yangs' feet!
Grandpa.
Zui.
Lord Jiuhuo.
I'm here.
Even if I die today,
I must take this step for Jia Lan.
Yitan.
Yitan!
Zui.
Zui!
The sky...
The Grief Tree!
[Libation]
[Memorial Tablet of Grandfather, Yang Huanzhou]
Young Master.
Everyone who came to pay their respects have been sent away.
Young Master Wangquan is staying overnight
to take care of Miss Wangquan.
How is Zui?
She's fine.
They say she can return to Wangquan Manor tomorrow.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
[Libation]
Hongye.
Yitan.
I'm bidding him
a final farewell.
[Memorial Tablet of Grandfather, Yang Huanzhou]
Yitan.
I can now do what needs to be done without hesitation.
I want to thank you.
As you know,
other families started seeking revenge
since my father's disappearance.
My sister and I have been on the edge the whole time.
Following me,
she endured endless hardship.
She is my only concern.
For my sister,
I can do anything.
However,
everything changed
after meeting you.
My sister started smiling more.
She also gradually stopped
coming to me in tears.
Since then, I knew
that in this world,
there was another person who loved her as much as I do.
Later,
you not only became my comrade
but also my family.
You helped me achieve my dream
of forming the Mask Group,
and we gained new comrades.
So, Yitan...
I want to thank you.
Remember,
no matter what happens,
don't be afraid.
I am your family.
I'll always be here for you.
Zui is here.
Don't make her worry.
It's chilly.
Go back early.
Zui.
I'm sorry.
I don't blame you.
But let's make this clear.
When I get better,
you owe me several jars of good wine.
Drink with me then.