[Love in Pavilion]
[Episode 32]
Qingmu Yuan.
Let me take you to Zhang Zheng.
Yuan.
Yuan!
What's wrong?
Don't you know whose grave this is?
Don't you remember? You buried him with your own hands.
You took everything from him yourself—
his identity, his reputation,
and even the woman
he loved most.
You are truly wicked.
What you're saying...
isn't true!
Look, your crimes are already
engraved on this unmarked tombstone.
[Give Me Back My Life]
Was it you...
who killed him?
Yes, I killed him.
You don't really think
Qingmu Yuan loved you, do you?
How could you kill such a good person like him?
You've been scheming to become him,
but you'll always
just be a dirty, lowly stray dog.
Your only way out
is submitting to the darkness.
Anaran, be true to yourself.
The Dark Sword became famous through malicious energy.
Forget all about being
friendly and loving.
Come with me and kill them all.
Anaran,
come with me to kill them.
Young Master lived an upright life,
carefree and unrestrained.
He won't blame me.
As for me...
I've never been anyone else.
A gentleman should be like an orchid.
How could I, Zhang Zheng,
possibly associate with the likes of you?
You presumptuous idiot.
You think you can fight me?
Look who I've brought with me.
Yuan!
Yuan.
Wake up!
A dirty, lowly stray dog
still dreaming of making a name for itself.
Qingmu Yuan,
kill him.
Classmate Zhang.
Zhang Zheng.
Dying at the hands of Qingmu Yuan
is the best end for you.
As long as you die,
Qingmu Yuan's heart
will also remain in the darkness forever.
Classmate Zhang.
I don't want to...
say...
goodbye to you.
Yuan.
Black Fox.
Don't even think of getting your hands on my Yuan.
No...
Yuan.
Don't be afraid.
I'll get you out of here.
♪ How can the wind stop? ♪
♪ How can clouds stop for us? ♪
♪ The vicissitudes of life never cease ♪
♪ The time we spend together is too short and unreal ♪
Don't be afraid.
I'll get you out of here.
♪ You blur into a shadow near me ♪
♪ We're fully committed ♪
♪ We're wholly devoted ♪
♪ Love has us spellbound ♪
Some things from our youth
♪ We're lost in a wasteland ♪
last a lifetime.
♪ A lonely boat lies around ♪
I like it.
♪ To the moon I tell how much I miss you ♪
What do you like?
I like Qingmu Yuan.
♪ My passion for you never fades ♪
♪ It's a guardian angel ♪
♪ Hovering high in the sky ♪
♪ Time goes by ♪
♪ Stars twinkle and dim ♪
♪ But our love remains still ♪
♪ I'll give away my everything ♪
♪ In exchange for a life of joy for you ♪
♪ There can be many new chapters in my life ♪
♪ But everywhere I see ♪
♪ Your image sticks around ♪
♪ Holding your hands, I can't speak a word ♪
I don't blame you.
I really don't.
But Yuan,
you must remember...
♪ We're fully committed ♪
never be controlled by her again.
♪ We're wholly devoted ♪
♪ Love has us spellbound ♪
We...
♪ We're lost in a wasteland ♪
♪ A lonely boat lies around ♪
will definitely win.
♪ To the moon I tell how much I miss you ♪
Right?
♪ My passion for you never fades ♪
♪ It's a guardian angel ♪
♪ Hovering high in the sky ♪
♪ Time goes by ♪
♪ Stars twinkle and dim ♪
♪ But our love remains still ♪
♪ I'll give away my everything ♪
♪ In exchange for a life of joy for you ♪
♪ There can be many new chapters in my life ♪
♪ But everywhere I see ♪
♪ Your image sticks around ♪
♪ Holding your hands, I can't speak a word ♪
Qingmu Yuan.
You even killed Zhang Zheng.
What's left
in this world for you?
Come with me to kill the rest of the Mask Group.
♪ I'll give away my everything ♪
Let's destroy this world.
♪ In exchange for a life of joy for you ♪
♪ There can be many new chapters in my life ♪
♪ The past vanishes ♪
♪ Like a dream and a whiff of smoke ♪
♪ I hope to see you again in the next life, if there is one ♪
What?
Even you want to defy me?
Today, I, Qingmu Yuan,
will fight you to the death to set things right.
Like a mantis trying to stop a chariot, you're destined for destruction.
You actually used your life force to empower the magical artifact?
Do you have a death wish?
Your deaths are completely worthless.
Idiots.
Classmate Zhang.
I'm coming.
Zhang Zheng, am I beautiful?
Do you like me?
Why do you like me?
When did you start liking me?
The woman traveling with me
is beautiful like a hibiscus.
Her body light as a flying bird,
her jade pendants jingling pleasantly.
Oh, beautiful girl,
your reputation is unforgettable.
Zizai, where are we?
How did we get here?
Have you found where everyone is?
This way, I think.
Okay.
Quzhuo, what are you doing?
Coming!
Quzhuo, careful!
Quzhuo!
Quzhuo, come out now!
Zizai.
Zizai!
Old fox demon.
Where's my brother?
Just like you,
he's trapped in another illusion.
You'd better worry about yourself.
Li Zizai,
your resistance is futile.
You two must die here today.
Li Quzhuo.
The magical artifacts Zizai made back then,
how do they compare to yours?
Your magical artifact is already perfect.
Impressive.
It's still not as perfect
as the purple-gold gourd you made.
Your magical artifacts
are unparalleled!
Li Zizai's magical artifacts are the best in the world,
yet he suddenly chose talismans.
Was it really because he liked them?
Li Quzhuo,
you secretly joined the Mask Group,
claiming to have a chivalrous heart.
But do you really have the ability to save others?
You were almost killed by the Rakshasa bird demons.
Have you forgotten?
Servant, is the medicine here?
Coming!
Move aside.
Move aside!
Quzhuo.
Zizai...
Where are you hurt?
I...
Today, alone...
fought against the entire Rakshasa bird demon clan.
The Rakshasa bird demon poison...
Li Quzhuo, do you know
who ultimately cleaned up after
your so-called heroic acts?
Do you know what price he paid for this?
What price?
Hand over the antidote,
or I'll raze your Snow Ravine to the ground.
Kill me, and your brother must die.
You should have a taste
of losing a loved one too.
What will it take for you to save him?
If you want to save your brother,
you'll have to trade it with your most precious possession.
Eldest Son of the Li family,
your magical artifacts are unrivaled.
Your most precious possession
should be your hands, am I right?
Your brother exchanged his right hand
for your life.
What he loved most in his life were magical artifacts.
He gave up his lifelong pursuit.
How agonizing must that be?
Li Quzhuo,
you really deserve to die.
you only drag others down.
Who needs a loser
like you?
like me?
Li Quzhuo,
your brother lost his right hand because of you.
Don't you think you should give him something in return?
Yes.
What I owe my brother...
I'll repay it.
Quzhuo.
Wake up!
Zizai!
Quzhuo!
Li Quzhuo.
Li Zizai.
You've always wanted to protect your brother.
I'll let you witness him die
in front of you today.
Zizai. Zizai.
Quzhuo.
Zizai.
My legs...
Quzhuo.
I promise I'll get you out of here.
Li Zizai.
Do you still think you have a way out?
Can you take
your crippled brother out of here?
Dream on.
Just stay here with your useless brother
and die here.
Zizai.
Zizai!
I said...
no one...
can mess with my brother!
You're as useless as your brother.
Zizai.
Didn't you say
that in this world,
talismans are yang, vessels are yin,
and humans are vessels of heaven and earth?
♪ Like a dream, like reality, like a fantasy ♪
If I use my body as a vessel
♪ At dawn and dusk ♪
to refine all your talismans,
♪ One person, one glance, one instant ♪
we'll be
♪ Stop time in the beginning ♪
able to beat her with the yin and yang of heaven and earth!
♪ Time interlaces or somersaults ♪
What do you mean?
♪ Despite ups and downs, I'll never let you down ♪
Zizai!
♪ Follow the shadow and look out for each other in the clouds ♪
You must get out of here alive.
♪ There's infatuation, there's love, there's hate ♪
♪ Lies are hard to understand ♪
I said before...
that I can protect you too.
♪ We won't argue ♪
♪ Faintly reflecting the beginning ♪
♪ Burn out the chains of darkness ♪
♪ In this life, I will do all to face it with you ♪
I'm already crippled anyway.
♪ Having agreed to grow old together, we now head home ♪
There's no point in getting out.
Today,
let's draw upon the power of heaven and earth
and fight violence with violence!
♪ The long-cherished wish of this lifetime ♪
♪ The meaning of the world ♪
♪ Follow the light, changing with the stars ♪
♪ No regrets about my fate; resolute joy ♪
♪ To search for the edge of the world ♪
Quzhuo!
♪ Born of affection, sustained by love ♪
Zizai!
Come on!
♪ Our vows will never fade ♪
♪ My heart will never change ♪
One begets two,
two begets three,
three begets all things.
All things and all living beings,
merge!
You think self-destructing your spirit can hurt me?
How dumb.
♪ There's infatuation, there's love, there's hate ♪
♪ Lies are hard to understand ♪
♪ We won't argue ♪
♪ Faintly reflecting the beginning ♪
♪ Burn out the chains of darkness ♪
♪ In this life, I will do all to face it with you ♪
♪ Having agreed to grow old together, we now head home ♪
♪ The long-cherished wish of this lifetime ♪
Turn evil into good
♪ The meaning of the world ♪
♪ Follow the light, changing with the stars ♪
like dust with light.
Break off all the stars in the world.
♪ No regrets about my fate; resolute joy ♪
♪ To search for the edge of the world ♪
Zizai, leave!
♪ Born of affection, sustained by love ♪
Descend!
♪ Our vows will never fade ♪
♪ My heart will never change ♪
♪ Memories float up ♪
♪ Clearly illuminated ♪
♪ Follow the light and bid farewell to meet again ♪
♪ The passion unchanged, the devotion unbroken ♪
♪ To break through the dark boundary ♪
Zizai...
♪ The deep love is like fire ♪
♪ Swear to reverse the prophecy and ending ♪
♪ My heart will burn through the eternal night ♪
♪ My heart remains bright for you ♪
I need a drop of your blood
to make a new talisman.
You must swear
to wear this talisman every day,
never taking it off.
Was I too reckless?
Did the Rakshasa bird demon give you trouble?
Indeed, you were rash.
But in this world,
if it weren't for you, the reckless hero Li Quzhuo,
all those villagers
would probably be dead by now.
Zizai.
We just sacrificed some magical artifacts and talismans.
Our family's wealthy and prosperous.
We can afford it.
Besides, who am I?
A petty demon
can't do anything to me.
Really?
If I make the vow,
will you join the Mask Group with me?
I, Li Quzhuo, swear
I'll keep this life-saving talisman
with me at all times, never letting it leave my side.
How's that? Am I clever or what?
Life-saving talisman!
I guessed it right!
This isn't a life-saving talisman.
It's a life-exchanging talisman.
Silly little brother,
go ahead and protect this world.
Descend.
I'll protect you.
Zizai...
Zizai!
Black Grief Tree?
Yitan, Zui,
it's me!
Qiyue!
My brother's paper crane.
Let's hear what he has to say.
Yitan!
Stop, Yitan!
What's wrong with you?
You promised to go bird egg hunting with me,
but you stood me up.
Is composing couplets
with the teacher that fun?
Taking bird eggs is wrong.
A gentleman should be upright and proper.
We shouldn't steal eggs from mother birds.
Besides,
Cousin doesn't care that much about his face.
You...
Look at him! Who did he learn all this from?
Ignore what your mother said.
Go on, go play.
Thank you, Daddy.
Why'd you take a book?
Is it sweet?
Yes.
So from now on,
will you still argue with me?
Of course not.
Oh, right.
Where's my little nephew?
Why haven't I seen him today?
Who knows?
He's probably off playing somewhere.
What about my father and brother?
At this hour...
Practicing swordsmanship in the back mountains?
Here.
These grapes are really sweet.
I hope
this dream never ends.
Weird.
Why did I say this is a dream?
Wait.
My father is already gone.
Zui.
This is not a dream.
This is our future.
Yes,
this is our future.
The future I've always dreamed of.
Even if the whole world betrays you,
I, Yang Yitan, won't.
Wangquan Zui, wake up.
This is all an illusion.
Yang Yitan.
When did you fall
under the Black Fox's spell?
When I killed Yang Huanzhou
to save you.
Because of my immense hatred,
the Black Fox's power
entered my Clairvoyant Eye.
So...
you became like this
because of me?
Yes!
Justice and righteousness?
They're all fake.
Only the strong decide the fate of the weak.
That's the truth of this world.
Why should we sacrifice ourselves?
Why should we go against fate?
Let go of me!
Instead,
let's conquer this world.
Who cares about right or wrong, good or evil?
Let's do whatever we want
and get...
whoever we want.
Who are you, really?
Have you forgotten
why he activated his Clairvoyance in the first place?
It was because you were in danger.
Why did he kill his own grandfather?
It was also because of you.
From beginning to end,
it's all because he chose you.
Wangquan Zui,
you're flawless and pure.
But think about it,
who has been protecting you so you stay that way?
Do you regret it?
Do you blame yourself?
How many people in this world love you as he does?
He can't turn back now.
Why don't you join him?
Qiyue!
Yitan, I need to save Qiyue!
Daddy.
Qiyue!
Deng Qiyue,
your daughter
will never see you return as a hero.
Qiyue!
No!