[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[theme song]
[music with a sense of tension]
[Birdsong]
(Student 1) I didn't look at it
(Iljin 1) I looked at you
- (Student 1) I didn't look...
- (Iljin 1) Hey
Who are you to look at me like that, huh?
(Iljin 2) Hey, do you want to go?
Instead of saying 'I'm sorry', say 'why did you look at me'
- sorry...
- (Iljin 2) Oh, sir
[Sigh of Iljin 3]
(Iljin 3) Why did you look at me?
(Student 1) Oh, I didn't look.
I looked at you
(Iljin 3) Hey, if it were you
When a nerd like you looks at me
Do you think it will feel good?
uh?
Korean food makes me feel dirty
[thud sound]
- Sorry
- (Iljin 1) Come to your senses.
- (Iljin 3) AC
- (Student 1) Sorry
(Iljin 3) Why did you look at me? Huh?
(Iljin 1) Hey, are you crazy? Are you crazy?
(Student 1) I'm sorry.
(Iljin 3) I see
Don't say sorry
[Iljin1's laughter]
(Student 1) I'm sorry.
(Iljin 3) Oh, this kid, for real!
(Iljin 1) Hey, do you want to die?
(Iljin 3) Do you want to die?
[The bullies' surprised gasp]
Oh, sir
(Rider) What are you guys doing?
(Student 1) Please help me.
what?
help
(Rider) The person who will help you
There's nobody
Just you
you
Do it yourself
[sigh]
[Iljin 2's awkward breathing]
effort
[laugh]
(Iljin 1) What is this?
- (Iljin 2) I see
- (Iljin 1) Are you crazy?
(Student 3) Hey, what is that?
You're going to stab me with that?
(Student 1) What?
"Please help me"?
(Iljin 3) Hey, try stabbing me.
- Try poking me
- (Iljin 1) You haven't been hit yet?
- (Iljin 3) Try stabbing him
- (Iljin 1) Hey
(Iljin 3) Try stabbing him
(Iljin 1) Bbaengsin-i
Can you stab me?
(Iljin 3) Try stabbing him
You loner kid
[Student 1's heavy breathing]
Stab it, stab it
[thumping sound]
(Student 1) Huh?
- Hey, Joongil!
- (Iljin 2) Joongil-ah
[The groans of Iljin 3]
(Student 1) Hey, Joongil!
(Iljin 2) Hey, Jungil
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, you're bleeding!
[The rider's exhaled breath]
[heavy breathing]
[Giyoon's moans]
(Yi-gyeom) Because I bully weak kids
You seem like something, huh?
[heavy music]
[groaning in pain]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[Giyoon's moans]
[Giyoon's powerful voice]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
(Giyoon) Save me
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
(Yi-gyeom) What?
[Yi-gyeom's empty laughter]
- (Giyoon) Save me
- (Yi-gyeom) Okay.
I'll save you
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[Yi-gyeom's spirit]
[Giyoon's moans]
[The moans of the bullies]
[Giyoon's labored groans]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[Giyoon's moans]
[heavy breathing]
[intense music]
[groaning in pain]
[heavy breathing]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
(Dabin) Stop it!
[forceful sound]
[groaning in pain]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[Giyoon's moans]
(Yoongi) Hey, hey, hey!
[Yi-gyeom's angry voice]
Stop it, hey
[labored breathing]
stop!
(Yi-gyeom) Get out of the way
(Yoongi) Ah, stop it.
Oh, sir
Stop it, you punk
[Yoongi's heavy breathing]
These kids should be killed
uh?
(Yoon-gi) Hey, Kim Ui-gyeom, hey
Okay, that's enough.
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
What? What is enough?
These kids get beaten up so bad
I have to kill him halfway to get his mind...
Stop it! Come on, shit
[Yi-gyeom's laughter]
[heavy breathing]
- (Yoongi) Hey
- (Yi-gyeom) Get out of here
(Yoongi) Oh my
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[sound of metal pipe being pulled]
[tensing music]
[groaning in pain]
[heavy breathing]
[Giyoon's labored groans]
[Creating music]
[Yi-gyeom's spirit]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[heavy music]
[Sound of metal pipes crashing]
[heavy breathing]
[labored breathing]
(Yoongi) Yeah
Still we
It has to be different from these guys
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
(Yi-gyeom) Hey
Have you ever smoked a cigarette?
A few times in middle school
I can't smoke
My throat just hurts
(Yi-gyeom) What do you think? What if I smoke?
[Yoongi takes a deep breath]
a moment ago
I just wanted to smoke one cigarette
'Is this why people smoke?'
I want to too
hey
[heavy music]
You were too harsh earlier
(Yi-gyeom) What?
I almost had an accident
You were so excited
He got his weapon first
(Yi-gyeom) That kid is always
I don't think the kids would have been hit like that
(Yoon-ki) We're with those guys
Would it be okay if they were the same?
Different
we are
Because I only hit bad guys
why?
Hey, Kang Yoon-ki
You told me to do it
(Yi-gyeom) What you wanted
Wasn't it something like this?
[cell phone vibrating]
Hey, Yi-gyeom, just a moment
I'll go and answer the phone.
(Yoongi) Yes, Mom
Are you Ji-seong?
Yes, yes, yes, I understand.
I, I will go right now
yes yes
Uigyeom, hurry, hurry
Me now
I have a place to go
Let's go quickly, I'll change clothes.
Go quickly
Let's go quickly and change clothes.
[sigh]
[Calm music]
(Student 2) Hey
Did you do well on the mock exam?
(Student 3) No, did you see it well?
(Student 2) Oh, sir.
Hey, what's that final answer?
(Student 3) Isn't it number 4?
(Student 4) Hey, hey, hey, hey
Look at this, this
I heard the Kyungwoon High School bullies got robbed?
'Masked duo'?
(Student 3) What is it? Hey, look.
(Student 2) Hey, I know this.
At our school
There's a kid who goes to Seomun High School
The kids at Seomun High School
I got completely robbed by two masked men
I can't even write now
(Student 3) What are these guys?
Aren't you a youtuber?
[Students laugh]
(Student 4) Hey, then
Come to our school too
I wish the bullies would just get beaten up
(Student 2) [sighing] Really
Should I post something?
Let's kill all our bullies
Hey, good, you uploaded it
(Student 4) Where should I put it?
Just upload it anywhere
Anywhere?
But the bullies see that
The mask that was supposed to come doesn't come
The bullies just came
[Student 3 laughter]
(Student 4) Oh, this kid is really
You're talking nonsense, dude.
[Yoongi's urgent breathing]
Yoongi is here
- (Ji Sung Mo) Come in
- (Yoongi) Hello
[Yoongi's heavy breathing]
(Yoongi) Hey, Jisung
Me, do you know who I am?
[Jisung Mo's trembling breathing]
[sobbing breath]
thank god
Oh, that's really fortunate
[gentle music]
(Ji Sung Mo) Our Yoon Ki
I was really worried about you
Once or twice a month
I came to find you
[weeping]
Why do you sleep so long?
[sobbing breath]
kid...
[Yoongi's crying]
That's really fortunate, sir.
[Yoon-ki's sobbing sound]
(Yoongi) Jisung, thank you.
Seriously...
thank you
[Yoon-ki's sobbing sound]
[Angering breathing]
Two left, two left
I won't leave these kids alone.
(Dabin) Yes, it's gotten a lot better.
Yes, sir
I'm going to start working now
Starting work next week
I think I can do it
[Door lock operation sound]
yes
Oh, over there, sir
The child's father is coming in now.
yes
See you next week then
[Door lock operation sound]
yes
[Dabin's sigh]
At lunchtime tomorrow
The laborers will come and clean that room.
That room?
[Clanging sound]
(Dabin) Which room is that?
say it
Whose room are you talking about?
(Seok-tae) Because of that room, Ui-gyeom
I don't think I can concentrate
[The sound of pouring alcohol]
[sound of a bottle cap closing]
It's right to clean that room
(Dabin) That's why I asked
Whose room is this?
Whose room is that?
Why can't you say it's Soo-gyeom's room?
Why is the name Soo-gyeom?
Can't you even put it in your mouth?
[heavy music]
[Seok-tae's sigh]
we
I've suffered enough
Now it's time to focus on Ui-gyeom
What's different about Ui-gyeom these days?
Did you know?
I have scars on my face every day
[Sound of documents being closed]
What does that mean?
Can't you see that in your eyes?
I can't see anything but grades
(Dabin) Soo-gyeom
I'm stressed
Like hitting Ui-gyeom
Even Eui-gyeom is stressed
I'm fighting
[Door lock operation sound]
[Sound of a door opening]
[Sound of door slamming shut]
[Door lock operation sound]
(Yi-gyeom) I'm back
Kim Ui-gyeom
Uigyeom, go into your room quickly.
yes
[sigh]
You bring that cassette
[Meaningful music]
why?
If you tell me to bring it, I'll bring it
Carrying around something that's all broken
What are you doing?
Are you protesting to your dad?
Uigyeom, come in quickly, quickly
Kim Ui-gyeom!
(Seok-tae) Bring the cassette
[sigh]
dad
This is something my brother treasured.
He told me to be like my brother
(Yi-gyeom) Why?
Oh, what's wrong?
Dad
Why did my brother like this?
Do you know that?
what?
If you wear headphones
To a place without dad
He said I could go
[Dabin's trembling breathing]
[Absurd gasp]
So, kid
Because I was so weak
(Seok-tae) I...
That's what happened
[sigh]
I can't stand it
I can't stand it!
[heavy music]
[sobbing sound]
Dad
I killed you
[Dabin's surprised gasp]
Yes, yes, yes
dad
really
I wish I could be like my brother.
Come to your senses, please
[Yi-gyeom's trembling breathing]
Uigyeom-ah
My mom is the same
Mom, Dad
I killed my brother
[Yi-gyeom's painful groans]
[Man's trembling breathing]
[Yi-gyeom's struggling voice]
[trembling breath]
[groaning in pain]
[airplane engine sound]
[belch]
[tensing music]
(Yoon-gi) Daenam High School 2nd year student, Pido-il
The second floor is a closed down bar.
I'm in there now
You shouldn't do that like last time.
why?
Those kids are bad kids.
We have to be different from them
and
You look a little dangerous these days
don't worry
Because we are different
[exciting music]
(Yoongi) Oh my
Everyone is gathered here
The bullies at Daenam High School
(Doyle) Wow, this kid.
Hey, you're really here
[The bullies laugh]
You guys? Masked thugs
Namhyeop is the one who wins, and Giyoon is the one who wins
[music with a sense of tension]
What, is it my turn now?
Who are you guys?
Our Gwangpal is gently twisting
Did you find out we were here?
But what should I do?
The madman asked me to put in a map
You guys are all talking about it
Right, Gwangpal?
[Doyle laughs]
[awkward laugh]
- Are you laughing?
- (Gwangpal) Huh?
(Doyle) Are you laughing?
[Gwangpal's groan]
[Gwangpal's weary groan]
If you can run away
Run away
[Exciting music]
I think something is wrong with this
(Yi-gyeom) Are you scared?
(Yoon-ki) [laughing] Me?
[Ringing metal pipes]
Come here!
[Yoon-gi, Ui-gyeom's spirit]
[The spirit of Iljin 4]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[The groans of Iljin 5]
[Sound of metal pipes crashing]
[Iljin 6's pained voice]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[Yoon-gi, Ui-gyeom's spirit]
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[The spirit of Iljin 7]
[The groans of Iljin 7]
[The sound of Iljin 8's struggle]
[Iljin8's pained voice]
(Yi-gyeom) Get out!
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
[Yoongi's spirit]
[The moans of the bullies]
[The spirit of Iljin 9]
[The groans of Iljin 9]
[The spirit of Iljin 10]
[Scream of Iljin 10]
[Yoongi's spirit]
seed...
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[groaning in pain]
(Yoongi) Uigyeom!
seed...
[Yoongi's spirit]
[The groans of Iljin 11]
[The spirit of Iljin 12]
[The groans of Iljin 12]
[groaning in pain]
[heavy breathing]
[Rumbling sound]
[The groans of Iljin 13]
[Yi-gyeom's spirit]
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[The bullies' spirit]
[The moans of the bullies]
[Yi-gyeom's labored breathing]
(Yoon-gi) Eui-gyeom, are you okay?
(Yi-gyeom) Oh
[The spirit of Iljin 14]
[Yi-gyeom's spirit]
[Yoon-gi, Ui-gyeom's powerful voice]
[The spirit of Iljin 15]
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
[The groans of Iljin 15]
[The spirit of Iljin 16]
[thud sound]
[The moans of the bullies]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
[Yoongi's spirit]
[The groans of the bullies]
[The groans of Iljin 17]
(Yoongi) Get up
[Yoon-gi and Ui-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[tensing music]
(Doyle) Hey, you fight well.
red mask
Let's sort it out
[Music that heightens the mood]
[noisy fighting sound]
[Yoongi's sound of pain]
[Yoon-ki's labored groan]
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait
Wait, wait, wait
[Yoongi's heavy breathing]
Who are you, man?
what?
Kangyoon?
[Laughing] This bird...
Loner kid
This is ridiculous, isn't it?
[laugh]
hey
[Yoongi is cheering]
What are you?
Are you taking revenge on us? Huh?
Oh, because of Ji-sung's kid?
(Yi-gyeom) Let go of this, you little shits.
[Yi-gyeom's painful groans]
(Doyle) What is this?
[angry gasp]
Hey, listen, stay still.
[Yi-gyeom's heavy breathing]
Hey, what are you?
High school superhero
This kid
[forceful sound]
[Doyle's groan]
[The groans of Iljin 18]
(Iljin 19) This kid
[Yi-gyeom's spirit]
[Yoongi's spirit]
[Doyle's Roar]
[heavy breathing]
Come on, Pidoyle
Kang Yoon-ki
Are you back?
[Yoongi's spirit]
[Yoongi's moans]
[Doyle's encouraging voice]
[Crash crashing sound]
(Doyle) [shouting] Ugh!
Oh, me, this kid
How is it George?
[Doyle's encouraging voice]
[Doyle's groan]
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
(Yi-gyeom) Hey, come out
Come out! Fuck!
[The bullies' surprised cries]
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
[Yoongi's spirit]
[exciting music]
(Yoongi) Uigyeom!
(Yi-gyeom) Come and see me
Come to work!
[noisy]
(Doyle) Hey, catch him!
Come quick, sir
[Yoon-gi's powerful voice]
[Yi-gyeom's powerful voice]
(Doyle) Come out
hey!
[Doyle's encouraging voice]
[The bullies' encouraging voice]
[Car horn]
(Yoongi) Hey, run!
[Exciting music]
[Car horn]
[Yoon-gi and Ui-gyeom's heavy breathing]
[The heavy breathing of the bullies]
hey!
(Doyle) Stop right there!
[Doyle shouts]
Catch it!
[Doyle's angry shout]
Wow! That's so fucking fast!
[angry shouting]
[The bullies are shouting]
[Doyle keeps shouting]
(Doyle) What, what, what?
- (Yi-gyeom) Oh, Kim Seung-jun
- (Doyle) Hey!
Ask for help
(Doyle) Motorcycle
Grab the motorcycle!
(Yi-gyeom) Go to the side
- (Yoongi) Go, go, go!
- (Yi-gyeom) Go, go!
[The bullies are shouting]
[forceful sound]
[The angry voices of the bullies]
[screaming sound]
[Yoongi's tired breathing]
Go away, I'm working part-time
(Yi-gyeom) I'm sorry
tooth
This motorcycle
I saved you today
Go, Inma
I don't owe you any more.
(Seungjun) I have to deliver.
thanks
(Yoongi) Uigyeom
I have something to say
what?
Revenge again?
Hey, Kang Yoon-ki
You saw me do that earlier
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Hey, Kim Seungjun
Hey, let me ask you one favor.
Let me sleep in today
If I go home like this, there'll be chaos
[sigh]
Please do me a favor
(Seungjun) I'm sorry
Put me to sleep at the gym
[Yi-gyeom's labored breathing]
(Seungjun) But
If you go to my house like that
There's chaos at my house too
My dad
I made up my mind
How much do you like it?
(Yi-gyeom) Hey
Are you good at boxing?
[Seungjun's empty laughter]
I am a human being
Choi Ji-hyeok and Choi Hong-il
We didn't get into any accidents while we were together, right?
At Taereung, the Asian Games are held
I was preparing
(Seungjun) There's this asshole
I was the top in my weight class in middle school.
[cell phone vibrating]
As soon as I entered high school
After the first game, he was on top again
[Yi-gyeom's sigh]
[Sound of hitting a sandbag]
Are you acting weird right now?
Don't fight
Yoongi, don't hang out with that kind of guy.
[Seungjun's empty laughter]
Wearing headphones like before
Go study, Inma
[Yi-gyeom's groan]
A guy who studies well and comes from a good family
What are you worried about?
While going to school
I've never fought before
There are a lot of kids graduating
And this fight
Once you've done it, keep doing it, okay?
[cell phone vibrating]
Why don't you accept it? Isn't it your home?
(Yi-gyeom) I don't want to accept it
[Seungjun's laughter]
[Yi-gyeom's groan]
(Seungjun) Beomsaengi
I had a big accident today
[Yi-gyeom's struggling voice]
There was a time when I first started boxing.
What, you hit someone in the face and get hit in the face
[Seungjun's powerful breathing]
That's so scary
The fight is the same
It's difficult at first
Hitting and getting hit in the face
And then you lose your fear?
From then on the fight
It becomes very natural
It becomes a habit, a habit
For some reason
It's not a fight
Make up a reason
Because it's a habit
[laugh]
(Yi-gyeom) Hey, Seung-jun Kim
You speak well.
It's unexpected
[Yi-gyeom's laughter]
What have you been up to?
I'm just being childish
Well, I was just holding onto Fukashi
You should just learn boxing instead.
[cell phone vibrating]
(Seungjun) Ah, don't do things like fighting, do boxing, Inma.
[sigh]
Hey, take that
Your parents will be worried
[sigh]
[heavy music]
[Seungjun's tongue clicking sound]
[Yi-gyeom's sigh]
(Yi-gyeom) I'm going to sleep over at my friend's house.
- Hey, teacher.
- (private tutor) Yes
Today my child
I think I'll be late
- sorry
- (private tutor) Ah
Hey, it's okay
Then I'll come back tomorrow
(Dabin) I'm sorry, my child
This kid has never been like this before
(Tutor) Oh, yes.
Oh, don't come out
Yes, see you tomorrow.
- (Dabin) Take care.
- (private tutor) Yes
[Sound of door opening]
[Door lock operation sound]
[Seok-tae's sigh]
[rider's laughter]
Kangyoon?
Is this the Kang-Yoon we know?
(Doyle) That's right
Then who is the kid next to you?
(Rider) Oh, this kid is funny.
(Doyle in the video) Hey
Who are you?
[heavy breathing]
High school superhero
This kid
[rider's laughter]
'High School Superhero'?
He's a kid I don't even know
(Doyle) He's a guy that Namhyeop knows.
(Namhyeop) I don't know much about it
I saw him briefly at my father's alumni association.
He's a guy who has nothing to do with us
Hey, anyway
You're saying you got hit by him too?
Lee Ki-yoon
[rider's laughter]
(Rider) Oh my god, you guys, really
Oh, hello, my middle school kids
(Rider Friend 1) Hello
[Rider's Sigh]
(Rider Friend 2) Oh, but
Where are you going like a fool?
I came here after getting hit
Are you here to meet Gisu now?
[Laughter from the riders]
- I see
- (Rider Friend 1) Bbaengsin [dark music]
[Coughs from the riders]
(Rider) But what can I do?
Even though we're like idiots, we're still friends
[The rider's empty laughter]
So what do you want me to do?
Arms? Legs?
where?
[Cue rubbing sound]
Do it yourself
But Hyeop-ah
You are a commoner at Seomungo
What are you doing here?
(Rider) Dad told you to study
Didn't you send it to Seomungo?
Follow your father
I need to become a doctor quickly.
Then I can help you later
Lee Ji-seong woke up yesterday
who?
(Rider) Ah
That little bastard that fell off on his own?
[heavy music]
so?
What is that?
Because of that kid's grades
Didn't you fall alone?
uh?
Your dad
You know best, kid.
[Namhyeop's absurd breathing]
Hey, but seriously, your dad too
Great, great
[snickers] That's it
Two years ago? Three years?
Are you still looking into it?
[Laughing] Hey, sir.
It's annoying, it's annoying, huh?
scary
Hey, that's about it
I'm a doctor
[Laughter from the riders]
[rider's laughter]
So, did you find out about school?
Even in middle school
I asked the kids below
I heard you're in love
ductility?
This kid ran away to the next neighborhood?
I'll go tomorrow
Can I just do it myself?
But Hyeop-ah
Give me more money this time
Oh, we're friends
You only come to me at times like this
(Rider) I'm very sad
Give me more pocket money this time
uh?
[Laughter from the riders]
(Seungjun) Everyday
What do you see here?
Like a fool
Can't you see?
- what?
- (Yi-gyeom) Airplane
(Seungjun) Oh, I see that
That's what I said
[airplane engine sound]
[Calm music]
But can you hear everything even after writing that?
this?
It's broken, it doesn't make a sound
[laughs]
Now, this civil revolution
(Teacher) Citizens' freedom and
suppressing rights
Cut off the king's head
This is a civil revolution
After the introduction of the civil revolution
Civil society comes in
The image of citizens becoming the masters
The most representative example is
What could there be?
(Students) Democracy and republic.
(Teacher) Right
And then there is the constitutional monarchy.
[tensing music]
[Deep breath]
(Rider) You really don't know?
[Student 5's trembling breathing]
I don't know
(Rider) Hey, just
Answer if you know, okay?
[Yawning sound of Iljin 20]
Oh, you guys?
What are you?
Aren't you Kang-yoon?
(Rider) Oh, this kid
You keep saying you don't know
what?
No, you're not Kang Yoon-gi
Bring Kang Yoon-ki here.
[laughs]
Me for free?
Hey, how much is it?
(Seungsik) Hmm
[laugh]
50 thousand won
okay
Let's get 50 thousand won worth once
[Seungsik's groan]
[tensing music]
[Seungsik's heavy breathing]
(Seungsik) I see
[pick laughing sound]
[Seungsik's powerful voice]
(Rider) Oho
[Elasticity of the rider]
[The rider's powerful roar]
Let go
[Seungsik's groan]
[Seungsik's labored breathing]
[Seungsik's heavy breathing]
(Seungsik) Ha, sir
[snickers]
(Rider) Come and see
Aren't you coming?
If you don't come, I'll go.
[The rider's threatening voice]
[The spirit of the rider]
[Seungsik's groaning in pain]
hey
What, it's over? Huh?
[Seungsik's groan]
Are you done? Huh?
Ah, wake up, sir, wake up
Uh, uh, uh, what is it?
[Seungsik's spirit]
Hey, what is it?
[Seungsik's powerful voice]
[Rider's Scream]
Oh my, man, it hurts
Oh my, it hurts
[Seungsik's powerful voice]
It hurts, it hurts, oh my
Didn't I say I was sick?
[Seungsik's groan]
Huh? You're sick, huh?
[groaning in pain]
uh?
[scared gasp]
[The rider's powerful roar]
What, is this how you do it?
Huh? Does it hurt?
[Seungsik's scream]
Oh, it hurts when you do this
Hey, hey? Hey
[Seungsik's urgent voice]
Is this a match, tap tap? You idiot
[Seungsik's scared voice]
Grit your teeth, huh?
[The rider's powerful roar]
[thud thud]
[Seungsik's scream]
[painful scream]
It breaks easily
[heavy breathing]
[sound of pain]
[Struggling sound]
[The rider's voice in pain]
I see
I'm sick
[Seungsik's groan]
[sound of thumping]
I told you it hurts, it hurts!
I told you I was sick, y'know?
[Seungsik's groan]
Oh, sir
Oh, what a piece of shit, y'know
It's making me feel weak
[groaning in pain]
Hey, go and bring Kang Yoon-ki.
[Rough breathing of the rider]
[thud thud]
[scream]
Bring it
[Students talking]
[music with a sense of tension]
Hey, Kang Yoon-ki
(Iljin 21) Who came to see you?
(Yoongi) Who?
I don't know either
(Iljin 21) I'm looking for you and Ui-gyeom
Hold on tight, you guys
Seungsik was fired
If you guys get caught, you're in big trouble.
[interesting music]
[sigh]
[Clanging sound]
(Rider) Oh, Kangyoon
Long time no see
What are you?
High School Superhero
(Rider) Oho
What is this? Concept?
Ha, that's funny
You talk a lot
Hey, break time is short
[sound of a thud being set down]
(Yoongi) Uigyeom
You're out, this is my job
[dark music]
Stay out of it
Hey, Choi Gi-su
You have to fight me
Why? I'm more curious about him.
(Rider) Oh, what, childish
Is this what revenge is?
uh?
[rider's laughter]
[sound of swallowing something]
[The rider's spit-out sound]
Aren't you running away today?
I have to go when you send it
uh?
[Yoongi's moans]
[Creating music]
[intense music]
[heavy music]
[tensing music]