I'm not sure if I can get the key to the door.
I'm not sure if I can get the key...
...on the door.
I'm not sure if I can get the key to the door.
produced by E einer
You were not struggling to sustain the economy.
The Thanh Thai is always other members of the Single Saiyan
You did praise a lot Miss Ji
You are prevail可是 conflicts with the government
Especially your foreign-owned competitions
Also, you won the award for a special mahjong
Miss Ji requested a special dialyce
And we also love when a good student like you comes in.
This place is different from the Seomun High School.
There are more students, so the atmosphere is different.
Do you know what I mean?
I'll get used to it.
Everyone is a good student.
Right?
Yes.
Everyone, sit down.
Hello.
Today, our classmate is here.
Kang Hyunki, you're early today.
That's right. I'm not in the subway today.
What's wrong? You're not in the subway?
I'm going early.
Okay.
Kim Woo-kyum, do you want to introduce yourself?
I'm Kim Woo-kyum.
Is it over?
It's short, so it's good.
I'm sitting down.
This is a plan for the class.
Write it down and submit it tomorrow.
Kim Woo-kyum said that he won the first place in the school.
Be a good student.
Help your school life.
Yes.
Don't get sick or get sick.
Choi Hong-il.
Yes.
Okay?
Why did you come to the first place?
I'll come.
Don't get sleepy during class.
Don't do anything else.
Okay.
Yes.
Let go of me.
I'm going to sleep.
You're going to sleep as soon as you see this bastard.
Let go of me.
Don't touch me when you're in school.
I'm going to sleep.
Let's look at page 3.
What's the result of all the mistakes?
I'm a little late today, so I'm sending you the pictures I took in the academy.
I'm studying.
Go home soon.
I'm going to sleep.
Good morning.
Oh, are you here?
How was the new school?
It was okay.
This school uniform is prettier.
Do you need anything?
Mom.
Yes.
Can't you try the medicine that your mom is taking?
Why?
Why do you need medicine for a student?
No.
I'm going to sleep.
Where are you?
How many pages are there?
178 pages.
I drank a little with dad.
The doctors are all bad guys.
I'm going to get a doctor's license.
The doctors think that their children are the best.
I'm going to sleep.
Kim Hyuk-yong.
Do you want to focus?
Focus.
I'm sorry.
It's not something I'm sorry about.
Again.
That's right.
You can do it.
Why do you keep falling into the same trap?
Focus.
Next.
Mom.
What's wrong?
You're crazy.
Did I tell you to go to the desk?
Come here.
You're not getting hit these days, are you?
I can't focus because I'm not getting hit.
Get up, you bastard.
I bought you a bread.
I'm starving.
Did you eat?
Yes, I did.
I'm sorry.
Mom, make it delicious.
It's going to be good.
I'm starving.
Hey.
How much is it?
2,000 won.
2,000 won?
Do you want to make it 2,000 won?
I'm hungry today, so I can't eat all day.
Can you do it?
Did you give it to me at school?
Why?
You didn't use your hope yet.
What are you doing?
I should start over.
Stand up, you bastard.
Hey, you bastard.
What are you doing?
1,000 won.
You're going to get hit.
You're not going to get hit.
Hey, you bastard.
Why are you so stupid?
Hey, you ate your lunch.
Stand up.
What did you do yesterday?
Did you see my money yesterday?
No, I didn't.
No, bastard.
Why are you so stupid?
You bastard.
You said you didn't eat your lunch.
No?
You bastard.
What did you do to me?
Hey, you bastard.
You bastard.
What are you doing here?
Stop it.
You bastard.
Get up, you bastard.
Stop it, you bastard.
Okay, I won't hit you.
I won't hit you.
You got hit, bastard.
Get out of here.
Are you not going to wake up today?
Do you want to do more?
What are you doing, you bastards?
Get out of here.
You bastard.
I'm just a man.
What's this?
Are you crazy?
You bastard.
Get out of here, you bastard.
I'm sorry.
Actually...
Yeah, yeah.
I was out of my mind.
I'll fix it slowly.
I'll make some money.
Money?
You're a bastard.
You're in a bad mood.
Because of you.
You're right.
Was that a gold coin?
Was it?
Do 10,000 won.
Why do you give 10,000 won?
Take your phone out.
Why?
You're a bastard.
You're trying to take my phone number.
You should have taken my phone number.
No, that's not true.
You mean it?
Yeah.
Hong-il,
if I talk, you'll check it in 10 seconds and answer.
Yeah.
When I was in school and when I was studying at home,
I already...
If you don't answer in 10 seconds,
it's a one-second time.
Go.
Do you want to go to the karaoke?
I don't think you're scared of the devil.
You're really scary.
Didn't you see the bubbles?
You didn't see it.
I didn't see it.
I'm sorry.
I called from the academy.
If you don't get a good result in this exam,
you have to go to the Chinese class.
I told you that I would never do that.
Go to my place and buy bread.
I'm sorry.
Why do you need my phone?
Hey you bastard,
are you laughing at me?
I gave you bread.
Do you want to die?
Sorry.
I forgot.
I'll forget it.
Did you have breakfast?
Yes.
Did you make mom eat it for you?
But this bastard is talking about music,
and he's holding a phone.
What? Why isn't it coming out?
Didn't you say it was a bug?
How did you turn it on?
Give it to me.
What?
A replay?
It's not coming out.
What?
Huh?
Oh, I like it.
Hey, Chae Hong-il.
What is this?
Give it to me.
What?
I want to hear it.
Are you crazy?
It's an important class for me.
I'm not a student.
Give it to me.
I don't want to.
It's mine from now on.
Hey.
I'll ask you.
Give it to me.
I'm so scared.
If it's that important, I'll tell you seriously.
It's a human-like bastard.
I'm scared.
Take it.
Hey.
I told you it's important.
So?
What do you want?
Huh?
Hey.
Don't you want to call the police?
Do you want to get a call?
You just want to be a pig today, right?
Huh?
You bastard.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I don't have any problems.
Hey.
Give me the car.
I'm really going to kill you today.
I'm going to kill you today.
Okay.
I'll kill you.
Stop.
Hey.
What?
What do you want?
Damn it.
You crazy bastard.
It's 1 to 1.
You can't get him, right?
What the hell are you doing?
Me?
The judge.
What the hell are you doing?
I told you I was important.
Why did you take him to the police station?
Come here, you bastard.
Can you be my wife?
Hey.
Nice soup.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Kim Yu-kyung.
Hey, Kang Yu-kyung.
You're the same age as me.
You were good at fighting.
What kind of exercise did you learn?
I didn't learn.
Okay.
Fight is talent.
So how are you going to fight tomorrow?
What are you saying?
How are you going to fight tomorrow?
I'm not going to fight.
You have to fight.
You're the best.
You're not going to stay still.
I don't want to fight.
Hey, leave it.
It's starting tomorrow.
Goodbye, Kim Yu-kyung.
I'm sorry.
Oh, my.
You're so slow.
You started the test.
I'm sorry.
I'll check it out.
Okay.
Take care.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
I'm back.
Go wash up.
Kim Yu-kyung.
Why did you get up late today?
I thought I forgot to give you a ride.
I'm sorry.
I know that if you don't get a good result this time,
you'll be in the middle of the game.
Okay.
I'm not talking.
I'm sorry.
Study hard.
Just look for this and go back.
Okay.
Hey.
Listen to this.
How is it?
It's good, right?
This is real.
It's real music.
You...
Yu-kyung.
Don't listen to it with your ears.
Feel it with your heart.
I'm sorry.
This is not music.
It's real.
Real life.
Yu-kyung.
Why are you standing like this?
How old are you?
193.
I'm 193.
Is this for me?
Did you sleep well last night?
I couldn't even sleep because of you.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
What?
You're such a fool.
Sorry?
Yes.
I'm really sorry.
You're such a fool.
Let's meet later.
What's wrong with him?
He's so cute.
I can't think of anything to think about.
Did I tell you?
It's starting from today.
I think it's Kim Soon-jun.
He's a great guy who works hard for boxing.
He's not that great.
The fight is starting.
If you stand on the punch line, you'll be crushed.
You'll be stuck.
And you'll be cramped.
You're stronger.
I think so.
Don't fight with me.
And...
I'm not going to fight.
You're not going to fight?
You're such a fool.
Get out.
Get out of here.
Get up.
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Are you not going to fight?
Me?
Guk-young.
Are you going to die?
It was so much fun yesterday.
Are you okay?
I was just going in the right way.
I just got stuck.
You're a crazy guy.
I'll call you.
You're not going to fight with those crazy guys.
You're a crazy guy.
You're a bad guy.
Are you going to die?
Oh, hi.
Hey.
What's wrong with you?
Did you tell Hong-il?
I apologized for what happened yesterday.
And your friend...
What?
Are you kidding me?
Guk-young.
Why me?
It's the last time.
Guk-young.
I'm going to kill you.
What's wrong?
Guk-young?
Are you bleeding?
Hey, Seung-joon.
Did you hit him?
You're so curious.
What are you going to fight with, you bastard?
You bastard.
I'm going to go.
Okay.
Hang in there.
Take Guk-young to the nursing room.
Okay.
I'll talk to you in the office.
Hey, Seung-joon.
Are you a gangster?
If you do anything because you're working out,
you're a gangster.
What do I do with you?
What if I hit you with a fake phone?
You bastard.
You can't even contact your mother.
Do you know where she is?
What does that have to do with you?
What does it have to do with you?
You bastard.
You bastard who worked out.
You're not the first one, are you?
You said you were going to punch me, right?
I told you to punch me.
I told you, you can't punch me like this.
You have to stick it on.
You have to hold it.
You said you were going to punch me.
You're so mean.
You're a bastard who works out a lot when you get my coaching.
I don't fight.
I don't think he's a bastard.
Please.
Can you stop talking to me?
I'm sorry.
Hello?
What is it?
You're out of your cassette?
Did you take it?
You're out of your cassette after you got the other one.
Choi Young-il, where are you?
You bastard.
You're the first one in the gold market.
You're a bastard who works out a lot.
Where are you?
You're the one who's going to punch me.
I'm sorry.
Kim Mook-hyun!
Hey, Kim Mook-hyun!
What are you doing?
Don't run.
You're going to get hurt if you lose your strength.
If you touch this, you're going to turn around, right?
You're going to get completely blinded.
You're a crazy bastard.
You're going to get hit on the head and bite your neck.
You might bite your teeth.
Be careful.
I'm on my way home.
I think I'm on my way home.
But I guess the cassette is important.
It's yours.
Yours?
I borrowed it, so be careful.
Oh, it's yours.
I guess the guys here are not kidding.
They've been hitting you since you took off your shoes.
They're here to get you.
I guess...
You're here.
Kang Yong-gi!
Hi.
Wait here.
If Kim Minkyeom is done, I'll have to make him pay for his personal training.
I'm sorry.
I'll be back.
You're a crazy bastard.
Take this.
Go and bring it.
Before you talk to Park.
Keep going.
Keep it.
Don't kill me.
Give me my Walkman.
Who's not giving it to me?
I'll give it to you.
If you win with me, it's easy, right?
Why should I fight?
Take off your bag.
I said I didn't want to fight.
I feel very dirty today.
Stop it.
You're a total bastard.
Stop it!
Stop it.
Are you having fun because you're a human?
Do you have something to say now?
Hey, Kim Seung-jun.
You guys are the ones who started the fight first.
And you guys are the ones who took my Walkman.
Damn it!
What did I do wrong?
Did you do something wrong?
You should've brought it to me.
We're just a bunch of fools.
Are you guys going to fight?
Give me your hand.
I'm sorry.
You're a big-hearted person.
Let's try.
What should I do?
Try again.
Should I give you a try?
Faster.
Stop it.
What's wrong with you?
You're a total bastard.
Stop it.
It's time.
Then I'm lying.
It's over.
I'm sorry.