♪In the darkness, close your eyes♪
♪And listen to the heartbeat's outcry♪
♪Turn around and return to this world♪
♪In this ruins, open your eyes♪
♪To the heat wave and flames♪
♪Move forward against the wind♪
♪Life and death
happen in the blink of an eye♪
♪When everything is no longer♪
♪Like it used to be before♪
♪I'm still in love with this world♪
♪There's a light shining♪
♪Upon my lonely heart♪
♪Crossing the raging fire♪
♪While memory is fuzzy♪
♪Among the unfamiliar sky♪
♪I'm still in love with this world♪
♪Your light shines on me♪
♪Never once wavering♪
♪Conquering the raging fire♪
=A Date With The Future=
=Episode 24=
(Is This Something A Woman Should Tell A Man?)
Come up.
Why are you asking me to come up?
Let me introduce her.
Her name is Xu Lai.
She is my family member
and an amazing reporter.
At times, as a firefighter,
I will often face different kinds of danger.
For her,
as a reporter in the front line,
she will always be fighting alongside me.
Not only is she my lover,
but she is also my partner
and my comrade-in-arms.
When I injured my leg,
I once thought I'd never be able to stand again.
It was all because she was with me, encouraging me,
staying by my side and giving me strength.
To the world, I might look like a hero,
but in my heart,
she is the heroine who saved me.
(Fire Prevention and Safety Talk)
(Prevent fires for safe families)
Why did you ask me
to go up there just now?
I was so embarrassed.
If I didn't ask you to go up there,
and a woman confessed to me,
would you be jealous?
Of course, I would.
I want the whole world to know
that I have a family member
and the others have no chance.
Dating a firefighter is such a happy thing.
What's wrong?
I'm wearing my uniform.
I'm not working tonight.
What do you want to eat?
Hotpot.
You're skillful with the knife.
It seems like I've found a brave warrior
who can also cook as my boyfriend.
There's no choice.
It's so that I can feed you well.
I can't just let you feed me.
Do you know?
It was the first time I made the chicken soup
by learning from the recipe.
Why don't you teach me?
Okay.
Show me.
Sure.
Not like that.
Your knuckle
is supposed to be against
the back of the knife.
That's right.
Yes. Just like that.
Are you all right?
Where did you get hurt?
You little liar.
See how I punish you.
Don't run!
Dad. Mom.
Why are you here?
Preserved vegetables.
Your mother made
some preserved vegetables for you.
We would like to give it to you
since we are passing by.
Don't just stand there. Sit down.
Sit down.
Here.
Introduce him to us.
Who is this young man?
This is my boyfriend,
Jin Shichuan.
Hello, Mr. Xu. Mrs. Xu.
Boyfriend?
Why have I not heard you mention it?
Sit. Sit down.
Okay.
Jin, right?
How old are you? Where do you work?
I'm 30.
I work at the fire brigade.
Jin Shichuan is
the captain of
the Emergency Response Unit.
Emergency Response Unit?
The Emergency Response Unit is
in charge of
major rescue situations.
Isn't that very dangerous?
A little.
This...
You prepared so much food.
There's even hotpot.
Yes.
We're having hotpot.
Mr. Xu. Mrs. Xu.
Have you had dinner?
Why don't you join us?
Sure.
Let's eat and talk.
I don't have an appetite.
Allow me.
I forgot.
I have some work at the brigade.
Why don't you eat first?
I'll go back now.
Sorry. I forgot my clothes.
Goodbye, Mr. Xu. Mrs. Xu.
Mom.
What are you doing?
He's here to eat.
You made it all awkward now.
How dare you say that.
If your father and I didn't see this,
how long would you hide this from us?
I wasn't trying to hide it.
We just started dating.
I just didn't get to tell you before.
Great.
I don't think you're right
for each other.
Break up with him.
What do you mean to break up?
No.
Why should I listen to you?
He's a firefighter.
It's a dangerous job.
I disagree.
I'm the one who is dating him, not you.
Is that how you talk to your mother?
You're taking his side
right after you're in a relationship.
Anyway,
I just feel that Jin Shichuan and I
are good together.
There's no one else in this world
who is a better match for me
than Jin Shichuan.
I don't think you two
should be together.
No matter how good you think he is,
I will not agree.
All right.
Stop arguing.
Calm down.
Calm down, okay?
Xu Lai.
Your mother cares about you.
Look at it this way.
This is your first boyfriend.
We have to see if he's good enough.
Right?
You too.
You shouldn't be
getting angry for no reason.
This is only the first time we're meeting Jin.
We must get to know him
before we decide, right?
Well,
since tomorrow is the weekend,
let's invite Jin
over to our house for dinner.
What do you think?
I'll check with him
to see if he has time.
If he doesn't even have time
on the weekends,
do you think he'll have time
to look after you in the future?
All right.
Tomorrow at 6:30 pm.
Invite him over for dinner.
Okay.
(Obey The Rule, Safety First)
Captain Jin.
Didn't you go to the campus
to give a talk?
Why did you come back so late at night?
I went to Xu Lai's house.
Xu Lai?
Do you have any cup noodles left?
Make one for me.
Wait.
Why didn't you eat with Xu Lai
since you went to her place?
Her parents showed up suddenly.
You've met her parents?
How was their first impression of you?
He looks terrible.
His first impression
must have been bad.
He didn't even have a meal together.
He is worse than I am.
(Hello.)
Hello.
(Are you back at the station?)
I just did.
I didn't have time to report to you.
My parents just left.
I'm sorry.
Don't take my mother's attitude to heart.
It's fine.
Why would I?
I can understand her,
since my job is something that concerns them.
I'm glad.
I was actually worried before I make this call.
What is it?
I was worried
that my boyfriend
would run away because of my mother.
I don't get scared easily.
You are underestimating me.
Do you think I can't take a challenge?
All right.
You should prepare
for the next challenge.
My mother invites you over
for dinner at my house tomorrow night.
Tomorrow night?
If you don't have time,
we can do it another day.
No.
It's fine.
I didn't expect
the challenge to come so soon.
Don't panic.
I'm here.
I'll look after you.
I'm a man.
I don't need a girl's protection.
I can even run into the fire,
let alone your home.
It's fine.
I will do well tomorrow.
It's decided.
Tomorrow at 6:30 pm.
See you at my place.
Don't be late.
My mother hates it when people are late.
Bye.
Did he get into a fight again?
Look at him being serious.
What is up with Captain Jin?
Did he have a fight with Xu Lai again?
No way.
They just made up a few days ago.
All right.
Let me ask.
Captain Jin.
Did you quarrel with Xu Lai again?
It's all right.
We are experienced.
Let's help you come up with an idea
to win Xu Lai over.
Yes.
I have more important people to win over this time.
Who is it?
Xu Lai's parents, especially her mother.
Mother-in-law?
Listen to me.
This is my first time
going to her house for dinner.
It is my first time meeting her parents.
I have no experience.
Help me out.
Hello, Commissioner.
Shichuan.
There's going to be a major celebration
in the city.
Our response unit
received an urgent order to help out.
Come back now for a meeting
and deploy the execution plan.
But...
This event is very important.
It involves fireworks and explosives.
We must ensure the safety of the citizens.
Okay.
I'll return to the brigade later.
Do you need help?
No.
There's no need.
You don't know.
You can teach me.
I want to learn anyway.
Why are you learning?
Are you making it for that brat?
I never let you cook since young.
I didn't raise you up
just to serve a man.
This misfortune is enough for me.
Not my daughter.
A misfortune?
I'm right here listening.
I said it because you were listening.
This is done.
Check the taste.
Your mother has a soft heart.
She said she doesn't like Jin
but she went to the market
early in the morning.
Look at the groceries she bought.
She's been busy the whole afternoon.
Hello. Are you arriving?
Sorry.
I received a call to return to the brigade.
I will try my best to get there
before dinner.
What is the urgent mission?
(An urgent meeting.)
(It shouldn't take too long.)
(Please explain)
(to Mr. Xu and Mrs. Xu.)
I'll come over soon.
Try to come soon.
I'll wait for you.
(Okay.)
(Culture Centre Plaza, Metro Station)
Well.
Give Jin a call.
See if he has left the brigade.
I called him just now.
He said the Emergency Response Unit
called for an urgent meeting.
He'll be late.
Late for two hours?
He has no choice since it's work.
He said he'll be here
as soon as it ends.
That's okay.
Work is more important.
It's understandable.
Let's not wait.
Tell him he doesn't need to come.
This is his first visit.
Is this person even reliable?
I told you not to date a firefighter.
It'll be just like your father.
They always give up their family
for others.
Why are you talking about me again?
Seriously.
Mother.
Think about it this way.
He's serious about his job
which means he is responsible.
His sense of responsibility is
to his work
and not to the family.
A woman's happiness is to find someone
who can stay by her side to protect her.
Do you understand?
I can tell you right now.
I disagree.
Mom.
Can you not be extreme in your thoughts?
He really has something to do.
What do you know?
I'm telling you, Xu Lai.
You must break up with him.
Otherwise,
you can stop calling me your mother.
No. What is wrong with you?
Do you have to do this?
Why do you have to be the one
to decide everything?
You've never asked me in any decisions you made
including your divorce.
You only informed me about it.
Do you even care about what I want?
I'm doing this for you.
I cannot let you walk my path.
Know that?
It won't be the same as you.
You have a failed marriage.
Not for me.
Enough.
It's not easy to sit together
for dinner as a family.
What are you doing?
Do you have to turn it into a mess?
I'm leaving.
Xu Lai.
Xu Chengyun.
I'm telling you...
Listen to me first.
Our girl is not a child anymore.
Why do you want to plant your thoughts
into her mind?
Why?
I'm telling you this, Xu Chengyun.
You have no right to say this to me.
If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have been who I am today.
Everyone, got it?
- Yes.
Okay. Dismiss.
(Huaigang Fire and Disaster Relief
First Brigade)
Your captain is in a hurry.
Where is he going?
He was supposed to be at Xu Lai's house
to have dinner with her parents.
He was going to have dinner
with her parents?
It's late now.
Xu Lai's parents didn't like it
when they're together,
because being a firefighter is too dangerous.
Judging by the time,
I think it's going to be late.
Xu Lai's parents must have a bad impression of him.
Thank you, Commissioner.
(Jin Shichuan)
Hello.
(Huaigang Fire and Disaster Relief
First Brigade)
I'm sorry.
I just got off work.
I'm on the way to your house now.
Is Mrs. Xu really mad?
No.
I explained to them.
They can understand.
(I was worried that
they'd wait too long,)
(so I told them to eat first.)
(What a waste.)
(You don't get to try
my mother's cooking.)
Maybe next time.
Why does your voice sound hoarse?
Are you crying?
No.
You're not at home. Where are you now?
(I came out from my parent's house.)
(I don't know where I am now.)
Send me your location.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm coming to you.
What happened?
You don't have to be strong
in front of me.
I was prepared
that my mother would not acknowledge us.
But I never thought
she would disregard my feelings like that.
It's all my fault
that you're going through this.
Thankfully, you weren't there.
Even if you were,
my mother would not acknowledge
our relationship.
It will only make it difficult for you.
I thought about it.
Even if she disagrees,
I will fight to the end.
No.
I don't want you to argue with them
because of me.
I want them
to acknowledge our love.
I will try my best
to have them acknowledge me.
It's going to be fine.
Mrs. Xu.
I'm here to apologize.
Can you still read?
He's already at the door.
Do you think it's right
to not let him in?
What will the neighbors think?
Whatever.
I'm not meeting him no matter what.
Let's eat.
I'm not eating.
You're heartless.
The kid is still at the door.
He's been there the whole morning.
If he wants to stand there, let him be.
Do you want our neighbors
to make fun of us?
Tell him I won't meet him.
Mr. Xu.
Jin.
Don't wait here.
Go home.
I know her attitude.
She's not going to see you today.
Listen to me.
Go home now.
It's okay, Mr. Xu.
I just want to use my actions
to show her my sincerity,
so she will know
that I can look after Xu Lai.
I hope that Mr. Xu and Mrs. Xu
can give me a chance to be assessed.
We must be cautious about Xu Lai's future.
Right?
Yes.
Why don't you go back today?
Come back when she is in a better mood,
all right?
Okay.
So, I'll...
Look at you.
I'll leave them at the door.
Leave them here.
Goodbye, Mr. Xu.
(Brave Dangers and Serve the People)
(Train Hard)
(Government Purpose Vehicle)
Hello.
Is there anything?
Nothing.
I'm looking for someone.
Who are you looking for?
The captain of the fire brigade,
Jin Shichuan.
You're looking for Shichuan?
You are...
I'm Xu Chengyun,
a friend of Jin Shichuan.
You must be his leader.
I'm the commissioner of
Huaigang Fire Department's
Emergency and Response Unit.
Commissioner.
Hello.
Shichuan is over there.
Let me call him here.
It's okay.
I don't want him to know that I'm here.
I just wanted to come here
to have a look
at how Jin is doing
in life, at work,
and how he is getting along with others.
Do you think Jin is a reliable person?
Of course.
Definitely.
Shichuan is a good captain.
He's also an ambitious young man.
Shichuan is responsible.
He is excellent at work, trustworthy
and values friendship too.
There was a female reporter.
She has the same surname as yours.
Xu.
Ms. Xu was kidnapped and Shichuan was the one
who saved her with his life.
Did you say the girl called Xu
whom he rescued was kidnapped?
Yes.
At that time,
Shichuan's leg was injured
and it was pretty bad.
But when he knew about it,
he ignored his injury
and rescued the girl with his life.
What do you think about this kid?
Good.
I think Jin is not bad.
He's a responsible person.
You see.
I could already tell
when he came to our house
to show his sincerity.
He is patient and determined.
Just like how I was back then.
He is kind and upright.
I think
we can leave our girl
in his hands.
Why don't we give him a chance?
Observe and understand him.
What is there to understand?
I've understood you well enough
for the many years being with you.
This...
We're talking about our daughter.
Why are you talking about me?
It's because he's just the same as you.
You left me alone when I was pregnant for months.
You didn't even call me.
I can't let my daughter
marry someone like you.
You have no time for family,
and your work is so dangerous.
If something were to happen,
Xu Lai would be the one to suffer.
Yes. It was my fault
but this is between the two of us.
You can't affect the kids' happiness.
I have been trying to make up
for what I owe you.
When are you going to
stop digging into the past?
Make up?
Can you really make it up?
I'm telling you, Xu Chengyun.
I will never forgive you
for what you did back then.
Move aside.
I'm watching TV.
You...
You're being unreasonable.
Go away if I'm unreasonable.
Why are you waiting here?
Go!
Get out of my sight.
You are always asking me to leave.
Do you think I won't?
Leave.
I'll leave today!
Go!
(Huaigang Medical University Hospital)
(Dr. Zang, please go this way)
Dr. Zang.
What are you doing?
Let me show you some magic tricks.
Look at my ring.
Do you want to touch it?
No.
I have another trick.
Watch this.
Nothing here, right?
Nothing.
How is it?
A heart.
That's so childish.
You're crazy.
Liu.
This is useless.
I'll deal with you when I get back.
I'm so mad.
Wait. Let me answer a call.
Hello, Mom.
What?
Okay. I'll look for him.
Calm down.
What happened?
My parents fought again.
My father left the house and didn't return home.
His phone is off too.
Don't worry.
We'll look for him together.
Could he be looking for me?
Dad!
Mrs. Xu.
Where is he?
Xu Chengyun.
Not bad.
Do you think you are mature?
How dare you run away from home
and not come back last night.
How is this my fault?
You were the one who chased me out.
Now you're blaming me.
I told you to leave and you went ahead.
Don't come back ever again
if you're that good.
Sure.
I won't be going back.
It's been 20 years
that I've been listening to you nagging.
Today, I'm a free man.
From now on,
I'll stay at my daughter's place.
Are you rebelling now?
What is the matter with you?
You took my daughter
and now you are taking
my husband with you.
What drugs did you give them?
What has this got to do with Jin?
Of course, there is.
Move aside.
If it wasn't for him,
the two of you
wouldn't have been against me today.
Mom. What are you trying to do?
Mrs. Xu.
Calm down.
Please don't argue with them
because of me.
Mr. Xu.
Go back with Mrs. Xu.
Are you staying here?
Fine.
I'll stay too.
I'm not leaving.
I'll stay here.
I'll watch you
so you can't be with this brat here.
I'm telling you.
Xu Lai. Remember this.
As long as I'm here,
don't even think about being with him.
You're unreasonable.
You want to stay here, right?
Fine.
Both of you stay here.
I'll leave.
Let's go.
Come back!
Are you done?
No!
Leaving like this
is going to make your mother angrier.
Why don't you go back?
I'm not going back.
You heard her.
She said she's going to watch me
so we can't be together.
This time, I will stand firm.
I will not give in.
Think about it.
If you leave like this,
it's only going to make things worse
for you and your mother.
Staying there will make it worse.
With my mother's temper,
we'll start arguing again.
Besides, if I am there,
my parents will not make peace.
I'm giving them a chance
to spend time together.
It sounds reasonable.
But I just don't think
this is a good way.
I know my mother's temper.
She won't listen to anything at this time.
So, we need to change our strategy
and go on the offensive.
When she comes to us,
we'll have a chance to talk.
We can then convince her
with sincerity and facts.
Perhaps it'll make things easier.
Why do you have so many ideas
in this little head of yours?
You're even using strategies
on your mother.
This is wisdom.
How else do you think I could get you?
Get me?
All right.
If you won't stay here,
where will you be staying at?
I can only stay at your house.
My house?
I don't have anywhere to go now.
If you're not going to take me in,
I think I'll have to
live on the streets.
There's nothing I can do with you.
I'll take you in.
Let's go.
♪When the sky hesitates to blue♪
♪When the snood they have no clue♪
Is this pretty?
Couple towels.
♪Wake up at noon, undo, fine♪
We only need one.
Let's go.
We need two pairs, right?
Couple slippers.
Couple chopsticks.
Wind in March, and the rain of April.
The sun that never sets.
The best of you.
♪Am I going crazy? Am I losing gravity?♪
Come.
♪Why the fishes, are in the sky♪
♪I don't want to be just another guy♪
♪Why don't you have another look
inside of me♪
♪Flowers in the sky,
clouds and butterfly♪
♪That's when I day dream about you♪
♪I don't want to be another guy♪
♪Why don't you have another look
inside of me♪
Here. Try this.
Be careful.
♪It's a daisy as it shines♪
♪Like kiddos and their bike♪
♪That's when I day dream about you♪
It's just a movie.
Why are you crying like that?
It's so touching.
I'm so jealous of
their never-changing love.
You don't have to be
jealous of other people's love.
We can have it too.
(Mom)
I'll go take a shower.
I'm done.
Sleep early.
I'll sleep in the living room.
Call me if there's anything.
Why don't you
sleep with me tonight?
Don't worry.
We won't do anything.
Just hugs.
Is this something
a woman should tell a man?
Are you too daring?
There's no difference
in gender when it comes to this.
I'm only being honest
about how I feel.
Aren't you worried that
I can't hold back?
Inviting a man to bed
is a very dangerous thing to do.
I changed my mind.
It's okay to sleep alone.
I changed my mind too.
Let's sleep together.
I promise.
Just hugs.
(Xu Lai.)
(I have something to tell you.)
(Let's meet up, okay?)
You've worked hard today.
Are you tired?
Let me bring you to eat something nice.
Let's go.
♪Pretending to be strong
in front of the crowd♪
♪What should I do
when the crowd is gone?♪
♪I thought time can heal the pain♪
♪Memories spark at night♪
♪How do I deal with
the sparks hitting my heart?♪
Open the door!
Huo Yanzong. Open the door!
♪I can't say all the greetings
in my mouth♪
I know you're in there.
♪I want to ask you later
if you really did let everything go♪
Huo Yanzong, open the door!
♪Do the wounds
from the past still hurt?♪
Open the door!
♪The words that are not true♪
If you don't open the door,
I will keep knocking.
♪Still punishes the ears♪
♪Tears are the delayed answer to love♪
Open the door!
Huo Yanzong, open the door!
♪Is the answer still the same
if we go back in time?♪
Open the door!
I'm telling you. I'm not going to leave.
If you don't find this annoying,
then don't open the door.
♪We are in each other's hearts♪
Huo Yanzong, open the door!
♪But we only care about
leaving on our own♪
♪It's my fault for missing out
on so much about you♪
What are you doing here?
♪Am I too late?♪
Why do you close the curtains
during the day?
♪The light in the flame♪
♪It's where time sinks in♪
♪It guides me in♪
♪I wish to tell you my woes♪
♪So my faith can be whole♪
♪I stand unwavering right next to you♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To show you the path♪
♪Overcoming the perils that come to pass♪
♪Searching for the traces you left behind♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To find a way into your heart♪
♪Fearlessly, I run toward you♪
♪Through the crowds♪
♪The shine in those eyes♪
♪It paused time♪
♪It guides me in♪
♪I wish I could tell you my woes♪
♪To have things I can hold onto♪
♪I stand persevered right next to you♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To show you the path♪
♪Overcoming the perils that come to pass♪
♪Searching for the traces you left behind♪
♪You're the light in my life♪
♪That is shining so bright♪
♪Life goes on, my search continues♪
(Adapted from the novel "Shi Guang Ru Yue"
of Jinjiang Literature City by Xiao Lu)
♪I run toward you♪