♪In the darkness, close your eyes♪
♪And listen to the heartbeat's outcry♪
♪Turn around and return to this world♪
♪In this ruins, open your eyes♪
♪To the heat wave and flames♪
♪Move forward against the wind♪
♪Life and death
happen in the blink of an eye♪
♪When everything is no longer♪
♪Like it used to be before♪
♪I'm still in love with this world♪
♪There's a light shining♪
♪Upon my lonely heart♪
♪Crossing the raging fire♪
♪While memory is fuzzy♪
♪Among the unfamiliar sky♪
♪I'm still in love with this world♪
♪Your light shines on me♪
♪Never once wavering♪
♪Conquering the raging fire♪
=A Date With The Future=
=Episode 25=
(Team Effort Wins Parental Approval)
Did you stay up all night?
That has nothing to do with you.
Get up.
What are you up to?
I'm free today.
My assistant isn't around too.
I need someone to keep me company.
I'm borrowing you.
Get up.
Nope. Go away. Don't annoy me.
You don't get to choose.
Get up! Let's go!
Get up!
Yu Shishi, what are you up to?
Come on!
Let's go.
Get up! Let's go!
Why did you bring me here?
I brought you here for facial treatment.
A man needs to maintain his appearance too.
Moreover, you have a face I like.
I'm not willing to let you
suffer for the sake of other women.
I'm not doing it.
I don't care if you like it or not.
Come on!
Yu Shishi, have you lost your mind?
Everything is ready. Come on.
Stop pushing me.
Please give him a soothing treatment.
Don't wake him up.
Okay, I'll get the scented candles.
Thank you.
(Amy)
I left the set because of you.
I'm sure my agent is going crazy now.
Why am I so nice to you?
I'm even touched by my own actions.
Even so, you didn't react to me at all.
Why are you hurt?
You never learn to protect yourself.
Sleep well.
When you wake up,
you should forget about
the person who broke your heart,
okay?
Not bad at all.
You became handsome again.
I spent a lot of efforts
just to help you become handsome again.
How do you plan to thank me?
Why are you looking at me?
Are you touched by my actions?
(Amy)
Get back to work.
Don't look for me again.
What do you mean by this?
You're chasing me away after waking up?
Our deal is already over.
Aren't you afraid
that I'll tell the reporters
about our fake relationship?
If you wish to do so,
you can go ahead.
Are you angry?
I was just joking.
Don't be mad.
I told you this on the first day we met.
I don't like to joke around.
You breaking our promise
has already disrupted my plan.
I'm already showing you mercy
for not holding you accountable for it.
Huo Yanzong,
do you even have a human heart?
I do.
But it's not for you.
No matter how much you like Xu Lai,
she'll never choose you.
How would you know she wouldn't?
Stop wasting time on me.
My business has nothing to do with you
from the start.
You're just inviting trouble
upon yourself.
It's impossible between you two.
It's impossible between us too.
Are you done?
Leave when you're done.
Do not bother me again.
Don't you understand human speech?
Just leave.
Huo Yanzong, you jerk!
I hate you!
Hate me then.
It's better than loving me.
(Mom)
Here, drink up.
Back then, I allowed you to stay here
because I didn't want the tension
between you and your mother to escalate.
However, you can't solve
the issue by avoiding it,
am I right?
It's time to go home.
I'm not avoiding her.
This is my tactic.
Timing is vital in negotiations.
I intend to wait for two more days
before I let my mother know about
my determination.
This way, she will soften up.
Besides,
I want to use this chance
to spend more time with you.
Don't chase me away.
No one is chasing you away.
But think about it.
The relationship between us
is already terrible.
If your relationship
with your mother worsens,
she'll think
that I'm abducting her daughter.
What should we do by then?
If so, my relationship with her
will never improve.
Am I right?
But I...
No more buts. Think about it.
Think about my relationship
with your mother.
Can you consider my feelings
for a second?
Can you please consider it?
Alright then.
For our sake,
I have to deal with my mother.
Good girl.
When you go inside,
you should communicate
with your mother properly.
It all depends on you whether or not
I get to marry into your family.
Do you want to get married
into my family that badly?
If I want you
to be a part of my family officially,
first, I have to pass
your parents' test.
Your mother is my future mother-in-law.
I cannot afford to offend her.
You're already calling her
mother-in-law, huh?
Jin Shichuan,
I realized you've gotten bolder
after you started dating me.
It's all because of you.
Fine then.
For the sake of our future,
I will accomplish my mission.
If so, don't you think you should
give me some energy?
See you.
Break a leg.
Don't throw a tantrum, okay?
Control your emotions.
Don't worry.
Dad.
Our baby girl is back.
Where's Mom?
Our girl is back.
You still remember
where your house is, huh?
Mom, I'm sorry.
I was too impulsive last time.
I shouldn't have talked back.
This isn't about you talking back to me.
Xu Lai,
when it comes to getting a boyfriend,
you have to listen to me.
When you find a partner,
you need to find one
with a stable and safe job.
And, he needs to
take care of the family...
Jin Shichuan will be the one for me.
I don't care if you like it or not.
He will be my other half.
What do you mean by that?
Why are you so sure that
he's the one for you?
What gives him the right
for you to lay down your heart for him?
It's because he saved me ten years ago.
Ten years ago?
Explain yourself.
What's going on?
When you guys got divorced
ten years ago,
I went to Huining to take a breather.
In the end, I was met with
an earthquake.
I was trapped in the ruins
for one full day and night.
Did you guys know that?
No, you guys didn't.
I would've been dead
if it weren't for Jin Shichuan.
He was the one who rescued me
from the ruins.
If so...
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
What's the use of it?
You guys only knew how to argue.
You guys never cared about how I felt.
What's the use of telling you?
You only care about the military!
You don't care about your family!
Listen.
Let's get a divorce
if you don't want to stay.
First, the nation. Then, the family.
Am I right?
Don't lecture me!
I don't care about that!
I just want to lead a normal life!
Do you know that?
Now,
you're being unreasonable.
I am the only one
who cares about our child.
I even gave birth to her alone.
You weren't even by my side.
You have no right to tell me off!
Do you want to stay here?
If not, let's get a divorce!
What's wrong with you?
You're complicating things.
I'm hurt.
I'm complicating things?
How am I complicating things?
I want to lead a normal life.
I wish to come back too.
I only want a normal life.
I want someone to care about me
and our child!
Do you know that?
I can't count on you for anything!
You're still
lecturing me here!
Just stop!
Lai,
we've decided to get a divorce.
That's pretty good.
This way,
I'll have two shares of living expenses.
I think
you two don't need to argue
when you see each other.
Our child is all grown up.
I think
we should hear her out.
We should respect her choice,
am I right?
All mothers wish the best
for their children.
I was just afraid that
she might make the wrong choice.
I want to protect her.
I never expected
Jin Shichuan to be the one
who rescued our daughter ten years ago.
We should treat him well.
After all,
he did save our daughter twice.
Twice?
I went to the fire brigade
in secret once.
I wanted to know more about
Jin Shichuan.
After that, I encountered
their commissioner there.
He said
our daughter was kidnapped some time ago.
Jin Shichuan risked his life
to save our daughter.
What exactly has Lai experienced?
Why do I know nothing at all?
I was just afraid that
you might be worried and upset.
That's why I didn't tell you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I know.
You care the most
about our daughter.
However,
everyone has a different perception.
Even if you think it's good for her,
it might not be what she desires.
Your so-called happiness
might be a shackle to her.
We can't make decisions for her
based on our life experience.
Don't you think so?
I just don't want her to
follow in my footsteps.
I'll say the same thing.
Our child is all grown up.
Let her pursue the path she desires, okay?
Besides,
what's wrong with
following in your footsteps?
It's not necessarily
the wrong path for her.
I'm still here for you
ever after all this while.
It's not the end yet.
How could you know
that I am not your best choice?
It's all your fault.
Yeah, it's my fault.
I know that.
What do you know?
Look at you.
You're throwing a tantrum again.
Stop crying.
I know we need to care
about our child.
However, you need to set her free.
I thought you went home?
I didn't accomplish my mission.
I messed things up again.
When I went back,
I said a lot of mean things.
But I regretted it immediately
after that.
I knew that I'd break my mother's heart
when I did so.
Do you know something?
When I was young,
I hated it the most
when my parents argued.
But after I grow up,
I end up doing
the thing I hate the most.
However, I cannot control
my emotions.
Tell me.
Why do people always
show their worst side
to their dearest kin?
Maybe it's because they're too close.
That's why they don't
hide anything from them.
I think you two
lack communication.
Sometimes,
it's better to clarify things.
Only then, your mother
will understand how you feel.
I hope so.
What? Are you troubled by something?
Grandpa,
how did Mom get married to Dad?
Why are you asking me this
all of a sudden?
I remember Grandma
told me about this when I was young.
She said she was against Mom's decision
to marry Dad.
It's because she thought
Dad's job was risky.
But I don't know what Dad did
to make Grandma change her mind.
Why did you drag your Grandma into this?
Is it about you?
Is Xu Lai's family upset about
your relationship with Xu Lai?
Yeah.
Is it her father or mother?
Her mother.
She's worried about
the nature of my job too.
She thinks it's risky.
She doesn't hope that Xu Lai
will get together with me.
I can understand
her feelings completely.
Being a firefighter
means you have to be ready
to risk your life 24/7.
They're not the best choice
if you want a partner.
All parents
want their children
to lead a stable life.
Don't you think so?
Yeah.
But I don't want them
to argue because of me.
I feel like I'm letting down Xu Lai
and her mother.
Silly boy.
You don't need to feel sorry.
Let me ask you this.
Do you still want to
be together with Xu Lai?
Of course.
Alright.
Did you know how your father
managed to marry your mother?
I don't know.
Silly boy. Just you wait.
Seems like
I have to do something
this time.
Hello.
Hello. You are?
You must be Xu Lai's mother.
Yes.
I'm Jin Shichuan's grandfather.
Okay, thank you.
I heard that you were a soldier.
Yes.
I was a soldier all my life.
That's good.
All three generations of my family
were soldiers.
Me, my son,
which was Shichuan's father, and Shichuan.
Back then, we were known as
armed police firefighters.
Today, we know them as firefighters.
Since both of us were soldiers,
I was thinking
that we should chat like soldiers.
Let's cut straight to the chase
without beating around the bush.
Okay.
I'm here today
because I know that you two
have opinions regarding
Shichuan and Xu Lai's
relationship.
I just want to ask
whether it is because
he isn't refined enough.
Or is it because of the risky nature
of his job?
What's the reason?
I do respect firefighters.
However, as Xu Lai's mother,
I do have my concerns.
I divorced her father a long time ago.
I feel like we've let down our child.
Therefore,
I take her marriage seriously.
I understand.
I understand your feelings completely.
I just want to tell you
about my experience
and how Shichuan grew up.
Have you regretted
being a soldier?
I did.
I regretted it after divorcing her mother.
I never regretted it.
I never regretted it,
even when my son sacrificed his life
during a rescue mission.
I never regretted it before.
It's because I know that
I belong to the country
once I wear the uniform.
I have to obey the country
and its people.
However,
when Shichuan
wanted to be a firefighter,
I objected to it.
It's because I know
this occupation is too risky.
Back then, I had much more concerns
than you guys.
I was afraid
that I might lose my grandson.
He is the core of our family.
He's my only kin.
However, Shichuan kept trying
to persuade me.
My mindset
was transformed gradually.
I think Shichuan is right.
We are able to live in peace
only because of their existence.
This occupation
should be respected by society.
However,
they cannot pursue love
like ordinary people do.
They cannot ask for love,
love others,
or establish a family.
I think
that's pretty unfair.
I came here today
just to ask you guys
to give Shichuan a chance.
Give him a fair chance.
Give him the right to love others.
Give him the right to accept love.
Give him the right
to establish a family.
I'm not eloquent.
I don't know
if you guys get my point or not.
I came here abruptly
without notifying you guys.
Sorry for the interruption.
I...
As a retired soldier,
let me give you a salute.
Thanks.
Sorry for the interruption.
Go back.
Again!
Nice shot! Again!
Come!
I...
Why didn't you tell me
that you were coming?
I have something very important to tell you.
What is it?
My father called me just now.
He said your grandfather
went to my house.
After that, my mother
had a change of heart.
Grandpa is amazing indeed.
Was it your doing?
I've spent a lot of efforts
in order to win your parents' hearts.
Why are you so nice?
However,
my mother hasn't
been convinced completely.
You have to perform well
for the next few days.
You must strike while the iron is hot.
Don't worry. I'll perform well.
Do you know what to do?
I do.
Put me down, Jin Shichuan!
Is this okay?
Her parents said yes!
Put me down!
Put me down first!
Her parents said yes!
- Sister-in-law!
I'm a little nervous.
Don't be nervous.
You can do it.
After you.
Look at how terrified you are.
Dad, Mom.
Our baby girl is back.
Jin, you're here too?
Everything is ready.
We were waiting for you guys.
You're here, huh?
Come inside.
Come.
Mr. Xu.
Look at this child.
He bought so many things for us.
What a waste of money.
Mr. Xu,
are you changing the light bulbs?
Yeah.
I think the house is pretty dark.
I'm changing the bulbs.
Let me do it.
Be careful.
Mom, I'll help you out.
Don't get shocked.
It'll be fine.
Here you go.
Be careful.
You did it in one go.
Look at you.
Jin,
change that bulb too later.
Okay. Jin, come.
Let's lift the sofa.
Okay.
I'll remove the carpet.
Lift this side.
This side?
I'll remove it.
You want to remove it?
Jin, you're really muscular.
I'm sure you're very fit.
Do you go to the gym often?
That's not it. We just have
plenty of physical training.
I'll lift this side.
Slowly.
Mom, you can find Jin Shichuan
when you need help.
He's amazing. He knows everything.
You can find him if you have
faulty electronic devices or circuits.
He's a firefighter. He knows everything.
I'm looking for a son-in-law,
not a technician.
We have to be practical in life, right?
You can rest at ease
when he's able to
take care of me, right?
Good job!
Dad!
Dad, what's wrong?
I sprained my waist.
Jin Shichuan,
carry my father to the hospital!
Hurry!
Are you sure he can carry me?
He can!
Alright then.
Carry me then.
Come.
Okay.
I'll head to the hospital then.
Slow down.
I can't walk now.
Slowly.
Be careful.
Jin, be careful.
Slow down.
Hug me tighter.
Am I heavy?
I'm used to carrying weights
while ascending stairs.
Is that so?
How's your waist?
My waist is fine.
Xu Chengyun,
stop pretending.
Do you think I'm a fool?
You broke the bulbs
and pretended to sprain your waist
so that he could
show his skills, right?
That's dirty of you.
Do you think he's a laborer?
Get down.
Stay here for dinner.
You didn't get to
try my cooking last time.
You can try it this time.
Mission accomplished!
Thank you, Mrs. Xu!
Let's go.
Are you sure your waist is fine?
Yeah.
Be careful.
I'm fine.
Kid, slow down.
Jin, eat up.
Come.
Have a try.
Listen,
you contributed a lot today.
Later,
your mother and I will head home
after dinner.
Your mother can't sleep well
if she's not sleeping on her own bed.
Yeah.
I'll head home later.
You should come back too.
Don't stay outside.
People will gossip about you
if news of this gets out.
You're not married to him yet.
You need to be more reserved
when you date Jin.
Why are you staring at your food?
You should thank your mother.
Your mother
has given you her approval.
Not entirely.
Alright.
It depends on Jin's performance.
I won't agree to it
if he lets my daughter
suffer.
Mr. Xu, Mrs. Xu,
I promise you guys
that I'll treat her well.
I won't let her suffer at all.
You two can supervise,
test, and inspect me at all times.
Okay.
Eat up.
Are you bringing your pajamas?
Nope.
What about this?
Fine then.
What's on your mind?
I am thinking about this house.
Look.
Your house was empty in the first place.
Once I leave,
it'll be more desolate.
Yeah.
I'll return to the station
while you'll move back home.
The house will become vacant again.
But I've already developed feelings
for this place.
Whenever I feel helpless,
this place acts as my shelter.
It provides me with a sense of security
and warmth.
But I think it is because
you are around.
A home should look like a home.
This is the rescue scene
of a chain car accident.
This was the first photo
I'd taken of you
when we had to cover firefighters
as our topic.
You took this photo
when you came to find me
as I was training them.
Do you remember it?
And this.
I took this photo in the training camp
when you were training Peace.
♪When the snood they have no clue♪
We've experienced
so many things together
without realizing it.
All of these
are proof of our love.
I wish to fill this house
with these photos.
This way,
when we see the photos,
we can remember
the moments that belonged to us.
This is how a home should look like.
♪Why the fishes, are in the sky?♪
♪I don't want to be just another guy♪
This isn't right.
What's wrong?
All of these are photos of you.
There's no photo of me.
Why don't I take a photo of you then?
Okay.
Take a photo of me and this wall.
This way,
I can declare
that you, who are in all these photos,
belong to me.
I'll take it now.
One. Two.
♪Flowers in the sky,
clouds and butterfly♪
♪That's when I day dream about you♪
♪I don't want to be another guy♪
♪Why don't you have another look
inside of me?♪
Wait.
Let me set the timer.
Ten seconds.
We have ten seconds.
♪That's when I day dream about you♪
(The News Department)
- Morning.
Morning.
A person in love does change, huh?
She looks better now that
she's in a good mood.
Morning, Zhou.
Zhou?
Ms. Xu, were you calling for me?
You looked distracted.
What's on your mind?
Ms. Xu,
today the internship-to-full-time-employee
name list
will be coming out.
I'm a little worried.
Don't worry.
You perform well.
I'm sure they'll let you stay.
Come.
I'm returning to work today.
I'm buying everyone here coffee.
Everyone has one.
Why are you guys still sitting? Come.
Come here.
Thank you, Ms. Xin.
Here, have some coffee.
Don't mention it.
Thank you, Ms. Xin.
Take it yourself.
Thank you, Ms. Jiang Xin.
Don't mention it.
Thank you, Ms. Xin.
Do you know how many interviews
she had done prior to coming back?
I heard that her interviews
were pretty well-received.
She's experienced after all.
Of course she's capable.
Xu Lai,
here's your coffee.
Thanks. But I don't
take coffee in the morning.
I'll have a gastric attack
if I take coffee.
Actually, I've been
doing some reflections
during my suspension.
I was too competitive in the past.
Let me apologize to you.
Let's get along in the future.
You don't need to apologize.
We're colleagues after all.
Ms. Xin, I will get along with you
as long as you don't
make things difficult for me.
Excuse me, I have something to do.
Zhou, here's your coffee.
I have an important announcement to make.
Our station has already
issued a notice.
Next month,
I will be transferred away
from my position
to assume a post
in the provincial TV station.
Okay. Thank you.
After my departure,
the position of Chief will be vacant.
After my observation,
I think
Xu Lai has always excelled in her work.
And, she has
an optimistic attitude as well.
That's why I've recommended
Xu Lai to be the next Chief.
Thank you, Chief.
I will work hard
so that I won't let you down.
You can do it.
Besides that,
the internship-to-full-time-employee
name list
will be out soon.
It will be announced in two days.
Any questions?
If not,
we'll end our morning meeting here.
Get back to work.
Chief,
I have a question.
Is Zhou included in
the internship-to-full-time-employee
name list?
I think
he has great potential.
He's hardworking too.
I want to keep him around.
About that,
that's under the HR department.
Don't worry about it.
Remember this.
Although I did recommend you
to be the next Chief,
it still depends on your performance
whether you get the post or not.
Try your best not to mess anything up
during such a crucial moment,
okay?
Okay.
What are you doing now?
Have you eaten?
No.
This sounds too childish.
I should be more mature.
Remember to take your meals on time.
I'll be worried
if your gastric issue acts up again.
Captain Jin?
You...
Did you hear that?
I would rather I didn't.
So now, you can draw comics too?
Don't look.
As if I want to look at it.
I'll take a bath.
♪The light in the flame♪
♪It's where time sinks in♪
♪It guides me in♪
♪I wish to tell you my woes♪
♪So my faith can be whole♪
♪I stand unwavering right next to you♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To show you the path♪
♪Overcoming the perils that come to pass♪
♪Searching for the traces you left behind♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To find a way into your heart♪
♪Fearlessly, I run toward you♪
♪Through the crowds♪
♪The shine in those eyes♪
♪It paused time♪
♪It guides me in♪
♪I wish I could tell you my woes♪
♪To have things I can hold onto♪
♪I stand persevered right next to you♪
♪I will be the light♪
♪To show you the path♪
♪Overcoming the perils that come to pass♪
♪Searching for the traces you left behind♪
♪You're the light in my life♪
♪That is shining so bright♪
♪Life goes on, my search continues♪
(Adapted from the novel "Shi Guang Ru Yue"
of Jinjiang Literature City by Xiao Lu)
♪I run toward you♪