We will now conclude our 38th Violin Mentor's meeting.
Thank you for coming!
You worked hard!
You'll eat with us, right?
Oh, I can't go today.
Why not?
I'm heading a chamber orchestra this year,
and today is our first dinner.
You must be busy with just your work at school, but a chamber too?
You're really amazing!
Come see us when we perform.
I'll get you tickets.
I commend your students for buying your tickets.
I'm sorry?
You see, for my chamber, we usually sell over 80% of the seats,
so I don't pressure my students to buy tickets for me.
So, since you've already started, work hard, okay?
Who knows, you may even have an audience some day.
Oh right, Professor. Remember the middle school student who got first in Seongjoo Ilbo?
She was your student, right?
Ah, yes. Ji Won?
At any rate, any student that gets to learn from you
should count themselves lucky!
Please share with us your professorial secrets too sometimes!
- What are you talking about?
- But you should, Unni.
Don't limit your teachings only to Jung Kyung because she's your student.
What?
Ji Won's supplemental teacher is Lee Jung Kyung, right?
You treated Jung Kyung like your own daughter,
you must have taught her your professorial techniques as well.
It looked so nice with them being so close together.
You did well!
Hah.
Miss Jung Kyung! I got first place!
Yes, I did it just like you taught me the other day.
How do you do, Professor?
Oh, I was late wasn't I? Did many people come?
Yes, almost everyone made it.
Oh right. You know the list of tickets for our performance?
I noticed that you also had purchased tickets of your own,
but you don't have to buy any.
I'm sorry?
You've been working hard as a secretary. Why would you need to buy ticket's on top of that?
It's fine if just the playing orchestra members buy them.
- Ah but, Professor?
- Hmm?
- Am I... not a member?
Of course not! Only good players are invited here.
I've been thinking of making you work as my secretary from the start.
Wrap it up and come in.
Oh you're all here?
Sorry, just one sec.
Yes, professor?
Come again?
You must think you can tackle Seoryeong University by yourself, do you?
Seeing you stab me in the back like that.
What do you mean, Professor?
Professor, that's not what happened. You see...
What's wrong?
Why? Who was that? Was that Professor Song Jung Hee?
What did she say?
I gave Ji Won some lessons,
but it looks like she found out.
Ji Won? The middle schooler?
What do I do? I think I need to go see the Professor.
H-hey!
♫   I'm reminded again of you who drifted away   ♫
♫   though I loved you   ♫
♫   The radiant memories of our past days  ♫
♫   come visit me again.   ♫
♫   In the end, I wasn't able to forget anything about you   ♫
♫   I must have loved you too much   ♫
♫   Because I miss you, I cry out your name   ♫
♫   Even if it's just a lingering attachment, I'll have no regrets   ♫
♫   Can you hear my heartfelt story?  ♫
♫   Without you, I'm nothing   ♫
Because I've seen you grow up as a child,
I must've only seen you as a child.
I always thought you'd depend on me
and I thought I would always need to look after you.
But it looks like you can do without me just fine.
How could you think of stealing my student from me?
That's not it, Professor. I had no such intentions!
I was just...
I was just... reminded of my childhood.
So I wanted to help her.
Because life was so hard for me, back then.
Thoughts of your childhood?
Ji Won is different from you.
Do you think Ji Won will fail like you did?
You're home?
- Where's Jung Kyung?
- Jung Kyung is...
She was practicing, but she suddenly left in a hurry.
Suddenly?
Let's go home first.
Go upstairs and have some rest.
I'll put away the instrument for you.
I thought of my mother.
I saw Ji Won,
but I thought of my mother.
No... I did it because I remembered
how I suffered because of my mother.
Even so, I shouldn't have done that.
It was all because I was too impulsive.
Just go upstairs and rest first.
I shouldn't have done that to you in New York either.
Joon Young, do you really...
have no feelings for me anymore?
Then, what am I to you now?
Do you pity me?
Why? Because I don't have a mother?
Or...because I've lost my talents and become an ordinary girl?
- Jung Kyung.
- You're the one who's pitiful.
You couldn't express your true feelings
and could only send a recording of your playing on my birthday every year.
You probably thought you were holding back because of your friend,
but was it really...really because of Hyeon Ho?
Okay.
I'll be honest.
All the things I received from your family...
Money, piano...
Because of all that, I never dared to think about having you.
I received a lot from your family,
so even when I didn't want to see you, I...
So...just let me go.
Please just let me go.
From now on,
I don't want to receive anything from you.
Your father called me just now.
Why did he... call you?
Did you... send him money?
- Did you do that?
- Yeah.
I did.
Joon Young, no matter what you say,
you need me.
I also need you.
What are you doing right now?
I'm sorry. I didn't know you were here.
Have you been helping Joon Young so that this would happen?
Then, why did you help him, Grandma?
What were you hoping for?
I wasn't hoping for anything.
I just wanted Joon Young to happily play the piano which he loves so much.
Then, you've failed.
Joon Young has never once been happy playing the piano.
Because he was burdened by the money we gave him,
he only played because he had to. For me, you,
and the foundation.
But I got too used to it...
To Joon Young's piano playing.
The thing that comforted me wasn't you or Father.
It was Joon Young, who played this piano.
I don't have any talents anymore,
and I even gave Hyeon Ho up.
I can't lose Joon Young too.
Joon Young, I can't reach you on the phone.
We got the money!
Your dad has it all solved, so don't worry.
I'm coming to Seoul.
Let's talk when I'm there.
Joon Young, you're back.
Mom, what are you doing?
Oh, nothing...
I was just waiting for you and there was nothing to do...
You saw my message, right?
I got a call from your father when I was on the bus,
so I just came anyway.
I wanted to see where you lived, too.
Where did Dad get the money?
What?
- That...
- From Jung Kyung.
Joon Young...
I... I really didn't know.
Joon Young, no...
Your dad probably...
He probably called her because he had no other way...
Why did we take Jung Kyung's money again?
Why?
I begged you guys.
Please... please stop making me look so pathetic.
I begged you.
But... once again, Jung Kyung...
No... Joon Young...
If Dad didn't keep doing that...
If he didn't take the money...
I might have...
At the very least, I may have
become a lot happier than I am now.
Mom, right now, I...
I'm not happy
playing the piano at all.
Jung Kyung Seon
♪ Congratulations on your admission  ♪
♪ Congratulations to our dear Song Ah  ♪
Congratulations!
- Song Ah.
- Yeah?
Are you happy?
I'm happy.
Song Ah.
Were you practicing?
I have to go to my lesson soon too, so I dropped by for a bit.
I see.
How was your gathering yesterday? A lot of seniors must have been there.
Yes.
Sorry I didn't contact you yesterday. My phone died.
That's okay.
No.
I don't think I'm okay.
I saw you and Jung Kyung yesterday.
You guys left in a taxi.
Where did you go?
I was Jung Kyung's accompanist yesterday, and then we had to go to Professor Song Jung Hee's house for something.
Why did you go there with her?
We had something to do.
And...
Did you... send him money?
Yeah.
I did.
Then, I went home and my mom came. That's all.
Sorry. I didn't think it was significant enough for me to tell you...
It keeps bothering me.
That fact that you're Jung Kyung's accompanist bothers me.
I told myself I'm worried about nothing, and I wanted to trust you and not think about it...
I thought everything would turn out fine...
but it's not fine.
I'm sorry.
And... you don't have to worry about it anymore.
I'm not going to be Jung Kyung's accompanist anymore.
I shouldn't have done it from the start,
but I guess I didn't think it through properly.
You're here.
Oh, how have you been?
Thanks for making the time to come here today.
I'm the one who should thank you for inviting me.
But where's the Chairwoman?
She said she's just arrived.
Let me know if you need anything.
- Hi!
- Unni, you're here.
Unni, was the gathering fun yesterday?
Thank you for helping out with our event.
I didn't do much. Team Leader Cha did everything. I just came to say a few words.
But... you heard from Jung Kyung already, right?
Yeah, I did. She gave Ji Won a lesson.
Yes.
Excuse me for saying this, but Jung Kyung has acted greatly inappropriately, against me.
I suppose you still don't know Jung Kyung very well.
She's a child that's used to doing what she wants.
All right then. I still have a lesson, so I'll head off now.
Good luck with the guest lecture and take care.
Yes. Thanks for leading the way.
Unni!
The guest lecture today is from the Kyunghoo Foundation, right?
Oh, right. It's today, isn't it?
Do you think it's worth going?
It just started not long ago...
But Unni, you were a intern with Kyunghoo before, weren't you?
I'm also kind of curious.
Let's go.
Sorry, I'm late.
Oh, right... I heard you said something to the teaching assistant about the piano in the practice room.
The pianos at the school are pretty lousy, aren't they?
If there's nowhere for you to practice, you can practice here if you want.
All right!
To summarize what I talked about,
the performance ability of a classical performer is essential.
As well as the ability to self-market and plan
is not merely needed, but mandatory.
I'll end my talk here today.
Thank you for listening.
All right, so far, we've heard great words
from Kyunghoo Foundation's Chairman Na Moon Sook
and Marketing Team Leader Cha Young In.
Are you going to continue being like this?
How many times have I told you this isn't correct?
Are you going to continue playing however you want to like this?
Is that wrong?
What did you say?
Am I not even allowed to play the piano however I want?
You said you wanted to get first place.
If you want to play how you want and win first place too,
you must first have such overwhelming talent
so no one can touch you like Seung Ji Min or Kim Gyu Hee!
But you're not them.
Don't you get what I'm saying?
Let's stop here today.
Rest for a day.
I'm a flute major. I'm also interested in performance planning.
But looking at the people around me who graduated from music school and worked in performance,
oddly, a lot of people quit really quickly.
Is there some particular reason for that?
For those who start playing music and transition to planning,
and I'm being careful to say this,
they weren't able to handle their own emotions,
and in many cases give up.
They wear dark clothes to not stand out, and they wait behind a darkened stage.
and for the sake of those colleagues who studied music with them,
they now quietly watch them receive the spotlight and play music.
I think that thought is what's hard for them.
To give up such a fervent dream,
is easier said than done.
Team Leader!
Oh, you're here!
Of course, I had to come! I really enjoyed the talk today!
Song Ah! Come over here.
Song Ah, you're here.
How have you been?
Song Ah!
- Our summer interns, right?
- Yes.
Oh right! I remembered last time you complimented how hard a worker Song Ah was
so while I was getting my chamber together I had her do my secretarial work.
Ah, I see...
She's such a hard and diligent worker!
Not just you, but Joon Young also is such a good judge of character!
You couldn't ask for a better wife for a performer.
- I'm sorry?
- Well, nowadays women all have their own job keeping them busy,
but honestly, for musicians like Joon Young who go on tour,
they need a wife who packs their bags and manages their schedule, after all.
That's not a bad thing.
That's how they can focus on their music only, without having to worry
about bothersome things like managing their money.
- Excuse me—
- Joon Young
isn't one to date someone over that kind of thing.
Ah, yes. Of course, Director Na.
I was just saying it because I find it so adorable that they are dating.
Yes, of course, you were.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Well then, be safe on your way.
- Yes.
- I'll see you some other time.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you for your work.
- Yes.
Joon Young!
Oh, Master Park Joon Young!
- You're here?
- Hello, Oppa.
Hello.
All this time... I've been hurting many people.
The closer they were, the more they have been hurt.
Joon Young. Chairman Lee, Jung Kyung's Dad.
Even keeping his own position is too much for him.
He is too soft.
I thought I needed someone to protect the foundation after my passing.
That's why when it came to who would be next to Jung Kyung, rather than picking who she wanted,
I preferred someone who would want to be the son-in-law for Kyunghoo Group,
someone who would want to be the board director of the foundation. That's what I thought.
I was only worried about myself,
I couldn't see into your heart.
I am sorry.
Please don't be.
I realized too late what you meant to Jung Kyung.
Joon Young, could you stay by Jung Kyung's side?
My apologies.
I have... no such feelings anymore.
I see.
I realized that too late as well.
I'm sorry.
People really... say whatever they please.
Not everybody is an adult just because they are older.
But still, I'm envious.
What? Of what?
People who say everything they want.
I envy them.
Even though they hurt other people by doing that?
Still, at least they can protect themselves.
So that other people can't hurt them however they please.
You don't have to walk me out, it's fine.
Still, I can accompany you to where your driver—
No, I'm really fine.
Brahms. I think I can listen to you playing Brahms now, no?
I really want to hear it one day. Can you grant me that favor?
Yes.
Thank you, Joon Young.
Be well. Take care.
Did your meeting with Director Na go well?
Yes.
What about you? Did it go well with Young In Noona?
I'll go see Jung Kyung.
To return the sheet music of the accompaniment to her.
Today will be the last time. Seeing Jung Kyung, that is.
It's really great.
The sound seems firmer and the reverberation is good.
You did something to the sound post, didn't you?
Yes. I'm glad you like it.
Woah, instruments are fascinating.
They're sensitive and expensive.
The front part of this one is cracked.
Yes, the bridge fell.
I have only ever heard of that happening, it's the first time I actually see it.
It happens sometimes.
It can also fall when the instrument receives a strong impact.
By the way... I heard you aren't joining Professor Lee Soo Kyung's chamber orchestra anymore.
Yes, it ended up that way.
How did you know? Rumors travel really fast.
This field is so small.
By sitting here, I hear all kind of stories I don't even want to hear.
Nothing interesting?
Nothing. People don't talk about other's success, you know.
They only talk about their failures.
What the? So you're saying all those stories of failures included my story?
Don't be like that. Tell me. Is there nothing about someone in a worse situation than me?
What's this? There really is?
No, just...
Jung Kyung.
What about her?
She...
She's been disowned by Professor Song Jung Hee.
I don't think I can be your accompanist. I'm sorry.
I'm about to fail being appointed anyway, so there's no need for you to be my accompanist?
Is that what this is?
That's not it.
Then why can't you do it?
I understand.
You're done, right?
About the money... I'll repay you.
And...
Let's... not see each other anymore.
Ever again.
If you don't have a place to practice, you can just come here.
I'll go now, so practice at ease.
Am I maybe stopping you from practicing?
I was going to go home.
Work hard.
Thank you.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
Let's enjoy the meal.
- Enjoy.
- Yes.
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
You were taken aback when I suddenly asked you to eat tteokbokki, weren't you?
No, I also like tteokbokki.
Really?
I like instant tteokbokki the most, actually.
I see.
I couldn't have any since coming back to Korea, actually.
Welcome.
Have you been well?
What's the occasion?
Instant tteokbokki.
Song Ah.
I'm really glad that a good person like you is by Joon Young's side.
I sincerely think so.
Well... somehow it turned out this way.
When I came to Korea after graduating, I had many dreams.
What were they?
To earn a living while playing the cello I like,
and start a family with the person I love.
But it turned out to be quite a difficult thing to achieve.
Until now, both for the cello and in love, I was getting back from it as much as the amount of effort I put in.
But now it feels too unfamiliar. Everything does.
Until now, there were only two times when I summoned the courage to do something.
- Song Ah, you're not finding a job, but majoring in something else?
- Yeah.
Fighting for me too?
You've gone mad, right.
I'm not mad.
You're applying to the College of Music instead of getting a job?
Song Ah. Do you have a talent for the violin?
For the violin...
I like you, Joon Young.
... and for love.
Since I love it so much...
Am I... not a member?
Of course not. I only gathered the talented ones here.
Then even though I get hurt
Song Ah. Our secretary.
and hurt over and over,
I thought I could continue to love.
Perhaps, that might have been
my...
own vanity.
Ah, Unni?
What is it?
I heard you sent Jung Kyung away.
But I saw she hasn't withdrawn her application to the Professor position, yet.
Do you think she's in the state of mind to think about that, now?
Right...
But...
I do kind of think it would be nice if Jung Kyung became a Professor... now.
What?
I'm thinking of backing her up. Nothing says I can't, after all.
What is it about?
I'm sure you didn't call me just to see me.
Uhm, perhaps...
Would it be possible to schedule a performance or an event?
Of course. Yes, of course.
I'll look into it.
- Thank you.
- No, well.
Then about the payment, will something around what was expected from the event at Kyunghoo Cards work?
Would maybe a little more be possible?
Yes?
Song Ah. What do you need?
Hello, Professor.
I came to tell you something.
Yes, go ahead. By the way,
it's better if I wear it on the side without the pocket, right?
How is it?
Here. Is it nice?
Ah right! Are you scheduling with Joon Young your lessons together?
Since you're dating him, you should adapt to his mood.
Musicians are always sensitive and fussy.
They aren't ordinary people, so you can't date them like you would anyone else.
Right?
Anyway, talk to him and bring him over here.
I'm thinking of asking him to be a collaborator in our chamber orchestra's new year performance.
Okay? Ah!
What is it? What did you want to say?
- Professor.
- Yes?
I will... quit my work for the chamber orchestra.
What?
Wait, I didn't hear that wrong, did I?
You will quit working for the chamber orchestra?
Yes.
Wait, it's not like I asked you to play the violin.
Your job as a secretary is only to do some stuff on the computer or over the phone. Was that too difficult,
that you're saying you won't do it?
Or is it because I talked about Joon Young?
No, it's not.
You're making a very wrong decision right now.
Think it over again, and let's talk later.
No, Professor.
I thought a lot about it.
I will quit my work for the chamber orchestra.
Looks like you don't want to attend school.
Did something happen today?
I don't know why I think of you during difficult days.
You should also call me during hard days too.
For me... I think I'll call you when I'm feeling good.
That's even better. Don't forget!
Okay.
Joon Young,
I want to see you today.
Do you have time?
I have something to do outside.
I'll wait for you at the cafe in front of the school this evening.
With this much, it would be a hundred million won and five hundred thousand won  (≈ $80,000 and $400) .
Why? Is it over your budget?
Song Ah, could we meet briefly?
Joon Young. It looks like my lecture will finish a bit late today.
It's alright, I'll wait.
Joon Young, I know you don't want to be in touch with me, but I thought I had to tell you this.
Listen to this. It sounds like you playing.
So why is it presented as Professor Yoo Tae Jin's?
♫   My feelings towards you  ♫
♫   Have always been the same, I've always stood behind you   ♫
♫  Like this   ♫
♫   I pray again today   ♫
Song Ah, something suddenly came up and I had to go home.
I'm sorry.
♫   Because you're my everything   ♫
♫   I confess now   ♫
♫   A melody for you   ♫
♫   A melody directed towards you   ♫
♫   My beautiful, unwavering feelings   ♫
No matter who asks, my answer is you   ♫
♫   I love you with my whole heart   ♫
♫   I'll give you my heart   ♫
Jung Kyung,
you're going to cause misunderstandings if you visit at this hour.
Even if you're friends.
I'd like it... if you don't come here anymore.
♫  I can't stop remembering all the moments of when we first met  ♫
♫  The memories come pouring out  ♫
♫  Like the stars in the night skies  ♫
♫  The quiet hours I now have  ♫
♫  Are spent staying up and longing for you  ♫
♫  The rain makes me feel particularly lonely  ♫
♫  Since you're no longer here, where we used to stay together   ♫
♫  I can't stop remembering all the moments of when we first met  ♫
If we say a teacher stole his pupil's performance, how sexy is that?
I wish they would just take down this piece as soon as possible.
Because I think Song Ah will feel concerned about it.
Do you know why you hid this incident from Song Ah?
It's because I like Song Ah. Not because I can't get over you.
Do you know what it means that he played it again?
No matter what others say, you just have to make a decision that will make you happy.
Because I wanted to see you and feel at ease.
I'm going through a hard time. I wanted to lean on you, Joon Young.
It's all my fault, so lean on me.
Lean on me.
I wouldn't be able to fully portray its depth  ♫