I apologize for barging in at this late hour.
I thought I should speak to the family in person,
despite knowing I wouldn't be welcome.
How are you not welcome? I'm glad you're here.
Please have a seat.
(Episode 37)
Is that the hotel chairman?
Stay out of it.
Don't stick your nose into another family's business...
and cause us trouble.
This is my family too, you know.
I was ready...
to tell her brothers-in-law about us,
but Kwang Sook wanted to do it her way,
so I held back.
Because of that, things happened out of order.
"Kwang Sook?"
She asked me...
to wait until things settled at the brewery...
and the brothers-in-law were on a stable path.
I'm the one who pushed it.
I hope there's no misunderstanding about that.
Of course not.
It was just unexpected for my brothers. That's all.
Really, don't worry about it.
Chun Soo!
Heung Soo. Calm down and let him finish.
Kwang Sook and I took long enough to get to know each other,
and I believe we were cautious enough as well.
I'm well aware that the brewery...
and all her brothers-in-law...
must settle down for Kwang Sook to be happy.
I won't rush anyone to satisfy my needs.
So please,
could you brothers-in-law watch how we do?
So basically,
you're saying you'll take our sister-in-law.
- Oh Heung Soo. - Heung Soo.
You should go, sir.
We'll talk about it among ourselves.
Yes.
We're flustered because we just found this out.
Please don't get the wrong idea.
Okay. Let's meet again.
Kwang Sook, you should see him off.
Go on.
I'm sorry I left you with extra homework.
Not at all.
Sorry for keeping you so late.
I'll call you when I get home.
They blurted stuff out in shock.
Don't take it to heart.
They'll all come around when we talk calmly again tomorrow.
Is the chairman gone?
I guess the others went to bed.
You should too.
Okay.
Why would a hotel chairman...
go for someone like your sister-in-law?
Does he have weird taste?
It's none of your business.
Butt out and go back to the motel.
What will happen to the brewery?
We must get our share before she gets remarried.
Stay out of my family's business.
You'll lose your share again, acting like you're sweet and nice.
I flew in at the perfect time.
It hasn't been that long since Jang Soo passed away,
yet you're already dating another man.
Jang Soo would be turning in his grave.
He'd be devastated.
After Jang Soo died,
as soon as the funeral was over,
we even tried to send Kwang Sook home.
Why are you complaining now?
It was easier to consider letting her go back then...
because we weren't too close.
Be honest for once.
Is it all good that Kwang Sook's dating...
a hotel chairman?
Do you think that's how I feel?
I know I should wish for her happiness,
but part of me is sad to let her go.
But we can't keep her with us forever.
I'm not saying it's forever.
It's just that...
I never imagined that Kwang Sook...
would get over Jang Soo so soon.
That's what hurts the most.
Kang Soo. Don't you have anything to say?
Well...
I didn't think Kwang Sook would fall in love again.
It's a surprise.
See?
Not everyone welcomes her marriage wholeheartedly.
To be honest, I'm not completely up for it.
I don't think I'll like this place without her.
I know. But we shouldn't be like this.
We should put her first.
I actually don't like the chairman either.
This was Jang Soo's home,
and it's not right for him to walk in whenever he wants.
Did you see the chairman off?
Yes.
This is why...
they say you shouldn't show too much favor to others.
You slaved away for them and restored the brewery.
Out of guilt, at the very least,
they should say,
"Kwang Sook. You met a great guy."
"Don't worry about us."
"Marry him."
That's what a decent person would say.
How dare they react like this?
Were you very hurt?
I didn't think...
they'd welcome the news.
But I didn't expect this reaction.
That's why...
you can never truly be family with in-laws.
You always talked about caring for them...
like they were your real brothers.
Goodness.
I want to sleep, Mom.
Okay.
Don't think about anything tonight.
Goodness...
Why is it so complicated?
Good morning.
Sit and have breakfast.
Why should I cook...
for people who are standing in my daughter's way?
You should know better.
The food I served you was all a waste.
Let's all eat.
I had too much to drink yesterday.
I apologize.
Don't blame the alcohol.
Now, I know exactly how you feel.
You're all the same.
Not one of you congratulated her to my satisfaction.
Where is Kwang Sook?
At the brewery!
Where else would she be?
I'll go and talk to her.
I have some materials to go over.
I need to go to work early.
I also...
Stop moving.
I'm giving you a final warning.
If you make my daughter cry, I won't let it slide.
You know what I mean, right?
Yes.
(Eagle Brewery)
What brings you here so early in the morning?
You didn't have breakfast, did you?
Let's go and get some food.
Now.
Gosh, what is he doing here so early in the morning?
I was going to talk to Kwang Sook.
Your eyes are all puffy.
I guess you had a good night's sleep.
You must've been upset yesterday.
I'm sorry.
I'm a businessman, you know.
When I face a crisis,
my fighting spirit kicks in.
I'm fine.
Please enjoy.
Here. Take your time and chew it well.
What?
Do you not want me to cool your food?
Come on. On a day like today, I should cool it down myself.
Gosh, it's hot.
- My gosh. - Oh, dear.
Why don't you...
leave the brewery?
What?
Right now,
all I can think about is...
getting you out of that house as soon as possible.
When you said they were like your brothers,
I believed it too easily.
It's not as easy as it sounds to date someone new...
while living with your in-laws.
This is...
my choice.
Just like how my relationship with you is my life,
my relationship with my brothers-in-law...
is also my life.
It's not like...
I can give one of them up.
How can you say that after seeing what happened yesterday?
Of course,
I was a little flustered too.
But that just makes me...
want to try harder to make things right.
Please wait and let me take care of it.
I understand what you mean.
Let's just eat.
(Gongjubuyang Shampoo)
It feels so good.
It's really smooth.
Come in.
Come out and have breakfast.
Okay.
What? Your hair looks more voluminous than usual today.
Did you use my shampoo?
Yes. It's really good.
You were already pretty, but you look even prettier now.
Thank you.
(Calls)
He hasn't called.
What is going on?
Hey.
Thank you for the food.
You're an early bird.
Professor doesn't have a class today,
so we're meeting later.
Is it a date?
Yes.
Good for you.
Did something happen to Professor's big brother?
I don't know.
He hasn't called.
I'm sure it's not a big deal.
Let's eat. Go ahead.
(CEO Dokgo Tak)
Have you heard anything about your birth parents?
Honey.
What could I possibly know?
Kang Soo was brought to the brewery...
long before I started working there.
There must be something.
Something doesn't feel right.
Come in.
I'm back, sir.
Did you take care of it secretly?
Yes. I sent the samples to a private genetic testing agency.
I didn't use the real names,
and the comparison target was recorded with anonymous codes.
When will the results come out?
I think they will be available tomorrow.
Good job.
Make sure to keep it to yourself.
Yes, sir.
I need to make things clear.
Of course, I do.
Hello?
Can we talk now?
Yes, go ahead.
Did you...
hear anything from Kang Soo?
What do you mean?
The thing is,
my husband asked me to have dinner together yesterday,
so I went to the restaurant,
and Kang Soo was there.
He called Kang Soo over without telling me.
What for?
He had no special reason.
I guess he felt bad about what he'd said to Kang Soo.
He wanted to apologize.
But it wouldn't be good for the two of them to meet.
I agree.
How is Se Ri doing?
Actually, I was going to give you a call.
Do you have time this afternoon?
- You're here. - Yes, hello.
Gureum.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
Stay healthy, okay?
Come here, Gureum.
Come here.
Say bye to them, Gureum.
I'll call you, Doctor Baek.
Okay.
Gureum.
Bye.
Take care.
(Vet)
Calm down.
What are you two doing?
In broad daylight,
how can you be touching her like that out on the street?
Ok Bun, you.
How can you cry in front of another man?
Can you stop interfering in what's clearly our business?
He knows you're innocent and has been using the puppy...
to make a move on you.
Now, you're crossing the line.
What do you mean I'm crossing the line?
I get it.
I saw right through you.
Whether he makes a move on me or not...
is none of your business.
What?
What am I to you?
What are we to each other?
Am I your girlfriend?
Hey, that's...
I knew it.
You're running the shop I invested in,
and I was a fan of yours back when you were a dancer.
That's all there is to it.
Correct me if I'm wrong!
You should collect yourself and head inside for now.
Okay, Doctor Baek.
Hey, wait.
I'm sorry about that.
I bet that offended you.
Use me...
all you want.
Sorry?
You're both obviously playing hard to get.
Doctor Baek.
You want to make the sandwich shop owner jealous...
so that he'd confess his feelings for you.
Aren't I right?
Well, not exactly, but...
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
I've always known...
that you had feelings...
for the sandwich shop owner.
You knew that, but you were still so nice to me?
Why?
Because you have...
a heart warmer than anyone else's...
and a lot of love to spare.
I'm happy to know that I can help.
I'll do my best to help you,
so hang in there until he confesses his feelings.
Doctor Baek.
But if it doesn't go as planned,
you have to give me a chance too, okay?
Welcome.
Hey, Chun Soo.
You look awful.
Is something up?
Yeoung Ju's mom...
is back from the US.
Right.
I see.
She doesn't want a divorce...
and has been insisting that we get back together.
Just know...
that I don't intend to do that one bit.
I mean it.
Right.
I'll try to talk some sense into her...
and convince her to go back to the US.
Mi Sun, don't worry so much.
Got it.
You shouldn't get antsy about this either.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Goodness.
I'm sorry I interrupted your busy day.
That's nonsense.
- Let's have a seat. - Sure.
My gosh.
I won't beat around the bush.
I'll cut right to the chase.
How about...
you take over the brewery as the CEO?
Have you ever thought about that?
Why would you say that out of the blue?
Kwang Sook...
seems to be taking on a huge responsibility...
all by herself.
I was wondering if you could take...
some of the weight off her shoulders.
I've been helping her with the bookkeeping...
and administration,
but brewing the liquor itself is a whole different story.
I'm trying to tread lightly,
but the brewery has been in the family...
for three generations.
If you took over as CEO,
it'd be like returning the brewery to its rightful owner.
Chairman Han.
With all due respect,
I don't think it's your place to involve yourself...
in how we run our business.
Goodness, no.
I wasn't telling you how to run your business.
I just thought it would be nice for Kwang Sook...
to lighten her responsibilities a bit.
I understand it hasn't been easy...
to watch Kwang Sook go through all this,
but maybe you could have a little patience.
Kwang Sook and us brothers will try to resolve this on our end.
That's how it's been so far.
I'm wishing you two the best,
but family matters should be handled...
within the family.
On that note, I'll pretend...
this conversation never happened.
(Eagle Brewery)
Honey.
Didn't I warn you not to come near our house?
It's still not too late to sell the brewery...
and take what we're entitled to.
Unbelievable.
By the looks of it yesterday,
your sister-in-law will soon marry that hotel chairman.
Once she marries into that family,
we'll lose everything...
and be left with nothing.
Stop sticking your nose in our family's business.
Do you have to put it that way?
Let me make myself clear.
Our second court-mandated date is coming up next week.
You'll have another thing coming if you don't show again. Got it?
(Eagle Brewery)
Stubborn as always.
Your mother is inside.
Talk to her.
- Professor... - She's worried sick about you,
so let her see you.
I tagged along excited, thinking we were going on a date.
We can go on one some other time.
I'll wait for you in the car.
Mom.
Se Ri.
Have a seat.
Do you hate me that much?
You won't even meet my gaze.
Professor Oh told me.
You got a job at a convenience store.
Right.
I thought you relied on me for everything.
I'm impressed.
I know you're disappointed in me and your dad.
I'm also aware that I can't talk my way out of this.
But back then,
your dad and I had nothing to our name.
Our future seemed dim,
which is why we did the unthinkable.
What we did was wrong.
So please forgive us, Se Ri.
Why ask me for forgiveness?
You should be apologizing to Professor Oh's family.
I'll go to them soon and ask for their forgiveness too.
I will. I promise you that, okay?
But Dad has no intention of doing so.
Give it some time, and he'll also come around.
He's being stubborn right now,
but he'll see that he was wrong.
I'll talk to him.
So please, come back home already.
I'm miserable...
without you in my life.
I'm as good as a living corpse.
You know better than anyone what you mean to me.
Please.
If you and Dad...
sincerely apologize to Professor Oh and his family...
and bury the hatchet with them,
I'll come home then.
Does that matter that much to you?
Yes.
Only then will I be able to see you and Dad...
the same way again.
All right.
Give me some time, though.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Thanks.
I feel better now that I've talked to my mom.
Good for you.
Your mother looked as though she was about to cry.
Maybe you should head back home.
Once they do as promised,
I'll go home.
What did they promise?
You'll find out soon.
Just a second.
Yes, Chairman Han.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Yes?
- Hello. - Right.
Welcome.
Let's have a seat.
I know I caught you off guard last night.
It was surprising, yes.
I spoke to you in person about the outside director position,
so I was more accepting.
But the third brother...
had only met you once,
which is why he took it personally.
I guess that's possible.
I'd like to ask you something.
Don't you think I'm a suitable match...
for your sister-in-law?
No one would doubt your social status,
but we're not sure if you'll care for her...
as much as we want you to.
Frankly, we don't know what kind of person you are,
so I can't give you a straight answer right now.
You'll give me an answer after getting to know me better?
That's right.
Kwang Sook is no longer just our sister-in-law.
She's like our big sister, our big brother,
and even our parent at times.
That's why I think you can't ever be...
too cautious.
This won't be easy, will it?
However, what the brothers think doesn't matter at this point.
We should respect...
Kwang Sook's wishes.
I don't know if I should be glad or worried.
Am I your girlfriend?
You're running the shop...
I invested in,
and I was a fan of yours back when you were a dancer.
That's all there is to it.
Correct me if I'm wrong!
I was going to propose to her after I had found my footing,
but it's time to step on the gas.
If I don't, some sleaze will take her from me.
I've thought about it,
and you are my girlfriend, Ok Bun.
This is our first day as a couple.
It's day one.
Welcome.
What brings you here?
I have something to say,
but I'll wait until you're done.
I'll wait over here.
- Wait. That... - Goodness.
Are those flowers?
Oh, right.
This is also for later.
Sure thing. I won't be long.
Wait, who's this?
("The lives of animals come before the family name.")
It's the vet.
The doctor who owns the vet...
is the youngest son of Sangjin Group's CEO?
("The lives of animals come before the family name.")
- All done. - What?
Do you like it?
Of course. Thanks, Ms. Ji.
Thank you.
Please come again.
What did you want to say?
It's nothing.
What do you mean it's nothing?
You had something to say just a second ago.
I did, up until a second ago,
but I won't say it.
I'll get going.
- But... - By the way,
these flowers...
Someone had thrown them away.
Do the same if you want.
I'll get going.
But...
Is this a joke or what?
Ok Bun could marry into a wealthy family.
I shouldn't get in the way of that.
The clunker should know when to clear the road.
Yes, hello.
I'm with LX Hotel and called a few days ago...
I was just about to call you myself.
I won't be delivering the sandwiches anymore.
What?
He refused to deliver the sandwiches?
That's what he told Mr. Kim.
All right. You may leave.
Yes, sir.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
These brothers aren't messing around, are they?
I know you're busy with your new store,
but I asked to see you to clear up a misunderstanding.
May I ask why you refused to supply...
our sandwich order?
A large order like that...
is a great boost to our sales.
But I rejected it because I sensed an ulterior motive.
"Ulterior motive?" What exactly do you mean by that?
I don't want to sell more at the expense of my sister-in-law.
I'll ask you point blank.
Do you dislike the idea of Kwang Sook remarrying?
Or is it me you disapprove of?
It's both.
It's both?
I don't like that Kwang Sook's seeing someone...
when Jang Soo hasn't been gone that long.
And I don't like...
how you used your wealth to approach us brothers.
I used my wealth to approach you?
Don't you think you jumped too far to reach that conclusion?
I don't know what you'd say about it,
but that's how I felt.
It feels like you're trying to buy our approval.
Your intention seems very impure.
"Impure?"
Yes. It feels very foul.
Welcome.
Do you broker sales of business properties too?
It's a brewery.
Yes.
It has a license to manufacture traditional alcoholic drinks.
The property includes manufacturing facilities,
storage, and office space.
You know Eagle Brewery, right?
The transaction's complete.
That's right.
The trademark?
I'll ask my husband about that.
Okay. Call me back soon.
Just a moment.
Here you go.
Goodness. I left these here?
I looked for them everywhere.
You must have a good eye.
What?
I was here just once before.
How did you remember me?
You left a strong impression.
Thanks anyway.
She's trying to put the brewery...
up for sale without telling anyone.
Hello, Eagle Brewery.
A real estate agent?
Why would you call...
No, we never put the brewery up for sale.
We didn't.
Okay.
Is Chun Soo out?
Did you...
put the brewery up for sale?
Yes.
You should sort things out...
before you remarry and leave the family.
You seem to have things very wrong.
I have no plans to "sort out" the brewery.
Then what?
You're going to marry a hotel chairman...
and keep the brewery too?
What are you talking about?
Whatever happens, I will...
keep the brewery up and running.
Don't you think you're being a bit too greedy?
You'll become a rich man's wife.
Will you turn your back on your struggling brothers-in-law...
to scrape together every cent and leave with it?
Who said I was leaving?
The brewery...
belonged to the Oh family for generations.
I still can't believe...
someone completely unrelated took ownership from the family.
Now, you want to take...
the family business and marry a rich man...
when you're no longer a member of the Oh clan?
I'm not the one who no longer belongs to the Oh clan.
It's you.
You shouldn't be so involved in another family's business.
I made it very clear.
Legally, I'm still Chun Soo's wife.
And I'm the mother of Yeoung Ju,
who holds the Oh family name.
That means nothing...
because the brewery...
is in my name.
Don't even think you have a claim to anything.
The brewery is not...
up for sale.
You want to turn your life around with another marriage.
You took the brewery from your husband.
Will you take...
the chairman's hotel next?
How dare you?
Watch what you say.
We'll see...
if you get your way.
If I see you near the brewery again,
I'll report you for trespassing!
Kwang Sook!
What happened?
Wake up.
You might die at this rate.
I'll take you to the hospital. This is not good.
I'm fine.
Do as I say!
Get up. Come on!
Hello.
I came to check on the store and buy a gift.
Something for your boyfriend?
No. My father has plans to play a round of golf,
and I want to get him something.
How about these?
The air moves through easily and cools the heat right down.
It's a nice, casual look.
I like it.
He might need a cap too.
How about this?
It'll go well with the shirt.
Pack them both for me.
Your father will be so pleased.
Kang Soo.
I'm off to the head office...
to discuss details of the golf outing.
- Sure. I'll see you later. - Bye.
I'm well aware that the brewery...
and all her brothers-in-law...
must settle down for Kwang Sook to be happy.
I won't rush anyone to satisfy my needs.
So please, could you brothers-in-law watch how we do?
I'm back.
Hi.
Where is everyone?
The manager went to the head office.
The others are at the country club to prepare for the VIP outing.
Did you check on a few stores?
Yes. I got a golfing outfit for my dad too.
Did you know about it too, Bom?
Know what?
That your father is dating my sister-in-law.
What?
The woman my dad is dating...
is your sister-in-law?
(Bongyoung Clinic)
You're in this state...
because of your brothers-in-law.
I'll make them pay for this!
Why is this their fault?
You still can't stand...
listening to me blame them?
Will you stop that, Mom?
You were married only for ten days.
So, you should never say that you can't do this...
to your late husband...
or that you feel bad for your brothers-in-law.
Don't even have such foolish thoughts.
But still,
I don't want to make my brothers-in-law upset.
Did you not hear what your mom just said?
Mom, why are you hitting me when I'm sick?
It's them who have no shame if they are upset.
No one can blame you.
So,
when there's someone who loves and cares about you,
go your way without looking back.
Even if you sacrifice yourself, no one will appreciate it.
(LX Hotel Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Hello, Chairman Han.
This is Kwang Sook's mom.
Kwang Sook is in the hospital now.
Mom!
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Hospital?
What's wrong?
She was...
stressed out because of her brothers-in-law,
so she collapsed.
It's not because of my brothers-in-law!
Which hospital is it?
I'm home.
Heung Soo, you're home.
Why is the house empty?
Aren't Ms. Gong and Kwang Sook home?
Kwang Sook is in the hospital.
Why?
It's nothing serious. She was feeling faint,
so Ms. Gong took her to a doctor for an IV drip.
Was she stressed out because of me?
So you know.
Which hospital is it?
I was going to leave after getting the IV.
Why did you come?
I came because I was worried.
Do you have any other problems?
I'm fine.
I just came because Mom kept nagging me.
Where's Mother?
Something came up at work, so she went there.
Please take good care of yourself.
Stop surprising me.
When I heard you were in the hospital,
I thought you were badly hurt and worried about you a lot.
Please don't get sick, at least for my sake.
Okay, I won't.
Kwang Sook.
My gosh.
Well...
Hi, Heung Soo.
You're here.
I came because I was worried about Kwang Sook,
but you got here before me, Mr. Han.
Well... I got a call a little while ago,
so I rushed over here.
When something happens to Kwang Sook,
she has someone to come running even before me and my brothers.
I'll get going, then.
What do I do?
It's not like he's a little kid.
Kwang Sook.
You've been dearly loved by your brothers-in-law.
I met Se Ri earlier today.
Beom Soo came with her.
Se Ri says she will come home...
if we apologize to the family...
of Eagle Brewery...
and bury the hatchet with them.
What nonsense is that?
What did I do wrong that I should apologize to them?
Denying what we did won't make it go away.
Let's take this opportunity...
to deal with our past and move on. Okay, honey?
Stop being ridiculous.
Honey...
My goodness.
Deal with the past and move on?
That's what I'm supposed to say.
What?
Professor.
I'll stay here with you until you're done.
I still have two hours left until I get off work.
I'll be reading this, so it's okay.
Where's Ha Ni?
I put her to bed.
If she wakes up, her uncles will take care of her.
Get back to work.
Then I'll read sitting next to you.
A book of poems?
It's Mi Sun's book.
Why are you staring at me?
Is something on my face?
Where?
Here?
And here.
What is it?
What?
Something.
Something?
A handsome thing.
Why are you teasing me?
Don't think about anything tonight. Just sleep well.
Drive home safely.
I'll leave after you go in.
Go ahead.
You should go first.
You're a patient today, so you should go first.
All right.
I'm going in, then.
Hello, sir.
You're home late.
Yes.
Did you just meet Kwang Sook?
Can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
Since we met...
before I met your brothers,
I'd like you to understand how I feel and help me.
Before that, may I ask you a few questions?
When did you start developing feelings for Kwang Sook?
I don't know.
At first,
there were misunderstandings,
so I didn't like her.
But as we worked together,
I gradually began to see good things about her.
So, I can't say exactly when it started,
but it's been quite a while.
Then, are you sure you can take care of her...
with a sense of responsibility?
How would I like someone without such feelings...
at my age?
What do you like about Kwang Sook so much?
Her brothers-in-law...
are no joke.
I need to bring my A game.
Goodness.
(Pot Number 12)
Hello?
Hey, I just got home.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling much better, so don't worry.
What were you up to?
Oh, that.
I was checking the fermentation of the makgeolli.
You just got back on your feet.
You shouldn't be back at work so soon.
You're not doing yourself any favors.
Head home and rest, right now.
It's all right. This is only routine for me.
I have to get back to work, so I'll hang up.
Is she haunted by a ghost who died a workaholic?
That's just wrong.
Unbelievable.
I looked into it,
and many traditional breweries in rural areas...
have shut down.
The expertise and craftsmanship...
of the masters who once worked there are being wasted.
Maybe you could hire some of them.
Sorry?
There's the yakju you're exporting,
and you'll need the extra hands...
once people start ordering more makgeolli.
Shouldn't you be prepared?
It kills me to see you doing all the work.
The technical aspects...
are being taken care of by the brewery manager and Kim.
We're good for now.
What I'm suggesting...
is that you should let the experts take over the brewery...
and take some time off.
Take time off?
Yes.
Don't you think it'd be better to rest...
while others manage the brewery?
Chairman Han, don't you think...
you're overstepping?
How am I overstepping when I'm only concerned...
about your health?
You should know...
that I won't ever...
stop working at the brewery.
Also,
I don't want anyone interfering or meddling in my work.
You have Chun Soo as the vice-CEO,
so why are you adamant about running the brewery yourself?
Are you trying to torture yourself?
Torture myself?
Don't you think that's a bit harsh?
I'm only asking because I don't understand...
why you're taking on all the responsibilities...
at the risk of your health.
Is this some kind of hero fantasy?
- What did you just say? - Also,
it's not normal...
to live under the same roof as your brothers-in-law.
Hold on. Are you calling me weird or something?
Like I mentioned before,
it's tough to date someone new when you're living...
with your in-laws.
Is this your way of saying I should move out of the house?
I have no intention of finding my own happiness...
at the expense of hurting my brothers-in-law.
The way I see it is...
My gosh.
Before you realized what was happening,
you let yourself be crushed under the weight...
of all these responsibilities.
That's also an illness, you know.
Are you now saying...
there's something wrong with me?
(For Eagle Brothers)
It's not like I'm one of his employees.
Who does he think he is, bossing me around?
Kwang Sook's a bit stubborn, isn't she?
That's an understatement. She's extremely stubborn.
Because I was worried about your health,
I suggested you take a break...
while letting others run things.
How was I wrong to say that?
I already made myself clear.
I won't stop working at the brewery!
Honey, why did you marry me?
Even though you were broke, you always talked a big game.
I felt like I could rely on you.