(Episode 11)
This feels wrong
no matter how I think about it.
We already settled this,
so what now?
It'd be a nuisance...
for me to stay at the brewery
when Jang Soo's not around.
How many times must I tell you
that you're not putting anyone out?
I'm scared to live in
that big house...
with just my mom.
A few days ago,
a stray cat jumped into the yard
in the middle of the night.
My mom and I got hysterical
thinking it was a burglar.
It's too scary for two women
to live alone,
so I'm asking you to keep us safe.
Are you going to turn
your back on us?
Is that the right attitude
for a defender of our nation?
- That's not what I meant.
- If not,
then just do
as your sister-in-law says.
Got it?
Saying it's scary is just an excuse.
She wants to stay close to him
to look after him.
Chun Soo, do something.
She's so stubborn about it
that I can't get a word in.
He could just stay with me.
Did her mother agree to this?
Kwang Sook said
she got her approval.
There's no way she'd agree to it.
I bet Kwang Sook
made this decision alone.
Does this mean our baby brother...
around Ms. Gong?
(Jang-Kwang Makgeolli)
This must be the makgeolli
from the news.
That's right.
It's Jang-Kwang Makgeolli
that's the talk of the town.
- Dr. Lee, allow me.
- Sure.
From what I saw on the news,
your daughter seems to have
a knack for business.
I don't want to sound like
I'm bragging about my daughter,
but CEO Ma is a supertaster.
- A supertaster?
That's right.
With just one sip
of any alcoholic beverage,
she can identify...
the ingredients
and the ratio of them.
Goodness.
She's a supertaster for sure.
It's an impressive feat...
to have makgeolli sold at LX Hotel.
Your daughter is truly remarkable.
Dr. Hwang, your high praise...
makes me a proud mother.
Now, everyone.
Let's all raise our glasses.
Here.
- Cheers.
You're here, Professor.
Goodness, Chairman Han.
It's been a while.
He was a student of mine.
Is that so?
Well, I'm CEO Ma's mother.
We met at the brewery
a few days ago.
Oh, right.
What a small world this is.
I had no idea you were one
of Dr. Hwang's students.
He's actually one of my favorites.
Goodness me. I see.
Anyway, Ms. Gong...
is like family and a close friend,
so do right by Eagle Brewery,
Chairman Han.
Right.
Does the food suit your palate?
The food is always exceptional,
but it tastes even better today
thanks to Jang-Kwang Makgeolli.
I'll make sure
you're served well tonight.
Enjoy your evening, then.
Goodness, what a small world.
I had no idea
Chairman Han of LX Hotel...
was one of your favorite students.
He'll do right by the brewery
since I put in a good word.
I appreciate everything.
My one and only daughter...
became a widow
ten days into her marriage,
and I was worried
she might lose her mind.
It's a good thing she was able
to pull herself together...
and focus on the business.
Don't you want her to remarry
given how young she still is?
Of course, I want that.
She should start fresh
with someone decent.
Then why don't I set up
a blind date for her?
My nephew is divorced,
and is doing well at Hanse Group.
Yes! A million times, yes!
My youngest brother-in-law
lost his wife three years ago,
and they didn't have any children.
Goodness me.
He used to be a pro golfer.
These days, he teaches clients...
and runs a golf business,
which is quite successful.
Your brother-in-law, Dr. Lee?
I would say yes
without even blinking!
A lot of my students
are now living alone.
Bingo.
Anyone you recommend...
would instantly have
the nation's stamp of approval.
Please settle on a date
as soon as you can.
If all goes well,
I'll return the favor
with a stylish suit.
- Let's raise our glasses.
- Sure.
- Cheers.
A premium strategy that emphasizes
craftsmanship has proven successful.
We do not compromise and stick to
the traditional way of brewing.
Makgeolli is an honest liquor.
Rice harvested from healthy land,
clear water, and our special nuruk.
We bring out the best flavors
with those three ingredients.
- Have you seen this?
- That's what defines our makgeolli.
- Sorry?
- Finding a new way...
- to bring back...
- Did you watch...
the TV interview
with Eagle Brewery's CEO?
Yes, I watched it.
What's your take on it?
I must say she had a way with words.
Why you... You punk!
I didn't ask for a review!
Even that tiny brewery
made the news,
so why aren't we doing any better?
Well...
I followed up on your order...
and suggested tweaking...
some of our existing recipes.
But?
None of them met the standards
we expected.
Unless we implement
a premium production line...
Premium or whatnot!
We must do what is needed.
How can Silla be seen
as a second-rate brewery?
Have the head of sales
and the technical director...
come up with a plan
to implement a premium line.
(CEO Dokgo Tak)
The money we set aside
to buy Eagle Brewery...
will all be poured into that.
Shoot.
Darn it!
He said I could bring Ha Ni.
His children are grown...
Don't be ridiculous!
Professor Oh is a single dad?
That never crossed my mind.
Why have you been staying
in your room all day?
Are you not feeling well?
Gosh, no.
I had something to think about.
Is something troubling you?
Mom.
What could make a woman walk out...
on her newborn baby?
What?
I've been trying to understand,
but I'm still at a loss.
Even if she didn't love
her husband anymore,
it still wouldn't be right to leave
her newborn baby.
And then, after all this time,
she wants her child back?
How shameless is that?
Be clearer with your words.
Who are you talking about?
What?
It's just someone I know.
Right.
I'm sure that woman
had her own reasons.
The mother wouldn't have left...
her newborn baby without a reason.
What?
What reason?
One can never be forgiven...
for abandoning their child.
No way.
(Eagle Brewery)
Kwang Sook.
I urge you to rethink this.
You haven't been around in a while,
so stay for dinner.
Kwang Sook, please.
I promised your big brother.
That I'd do for you all...
what your late mother would've done.
It's not just because
of that promise.
My mom and I live alone
in this huge house,
and it can get scary and daunting.
We're in desperate need
of Kang Soo's help.
Did you really talk this through
with your mother?
Yes.
My mom was much more pleased
about it than me.
Isn't this house too big
for just the two of us?
Don't you think it'd be nice...
to have a handsome and sweet son?
A son-in-law is the same as a son.
Okay, then.
Kwang Sook insists.
Stay here for a while,
fix up the house and brewery,
and sort out their complaints.
Okay. I'll do that.
Let's all go inside.
How about budae jjigae for dinner?
Budae jjigae is my specialty.
Let's get inside.
Come along.
Let's go.
He'll need to find...
a place of his own
when he finds work.
Let him stay here until then.
That will put Kwang Sook at ease.
Let's do that, then.
I'll drop by the brewery for a bit.
- Okay.
- I won't be long.
Hello?
Mom. Where are you?
I'm almost home.
Already?
What's the busy CEO doing out here
welcoming me home?
Did you have a good time
with your Golden Castle friends?
Yes. We had an elegant lunch
at LX Hotel...
and watched a movie too.
I was the center of attention today,
and I owe that to you.
Everyone praised you
and said they were impressed.
I owe a lot to you.
Thank you, Mom.
A daughter shouldn't have to thank
her mom.
- Mom.
- Kwang Sook.
You go first.
No. You go first.
No. You go first, Mom.
Do you want to tell me something?
I'll tell you after I hear you out.
Okay. Then I'll go first.
My brother-in-law Kang Soo.
He left the navy today.
And he'll live with us for a while.
So what if he left the navy?
Why would he live with us?
I want him to stay with us
for a while...
so I can plump him up...
- and look after him...
- You crazy thing.
Why would you do something
like that?
I can't believe you took over
your dead husband's brewery.
You'll take in a brother-in-law too?
Don't you have a spine?
Are you out of your mind?
That really hurt.
I'm warning you.
I won't accept that.
I won't allow it.
He's here already.
I lied and said
you'd given permission.
What? Are you a total nutcase?
Let it go for my sake. Please, Mom.
He's the youngest brother
that Jang Soo raised like a son.
I want to look after him
until he recovers his health...
and finds a job.
How did I give birth to a halfwit
like you?
Oh, my darling husband.
Take me with you.
I want to go to wherever you are...
Mom.
Let it go just this once.
Just this one time.
I promise to do
as you say from now on.
Will you really do as I say?
Then go on a blind date.
A blind date?
My Golden Castle friends...
will set you up
with people they know.
Go on the dates and don't complain.
Are you crazy? That's ridiculous.
Then I have no choice
but to kick out your brother-in-law.
No.
This isn't fair.
Kang Soo's inside, right?
Okay, fine. I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I'll go on the blind date.
Here you go.
Hello.
Welcome, Kang Soo.
Make yourself at home, okay?
Thank you, Ms. Gong.
You wanted a son your whole life.
Now you have one.
Yes.
I'm so blessed in my old age.
I'm grateful...
that you think so.
He'll stay only until he gets well
and finds a job.
Let's catch up...
over our dinner feast.
This looks amazing.
I'll serve Ms. Gong first.
Excuse me.
- I'll serve.
- At this crucial moment...
(Ms. Ji)
(Angel Piano)
- I'll serve the others.
- This is for you, Kwang Sook.
Transferring to voicemail...
He won't take my calls now?
One day,
you'll bow to me with gratitude.
(Angel Piano)
Shoot.
You...
I got you today.
Taxi!
That car, sir.
Follow that car.
Don't lose it.
Think again.
Catching them at it
won't do you any good.
What?
Aren't you after
your cheating husband?
My cheating what?
I'm about to catch
a fraud red-handed.
What?
Hey.
Turn right.
Don't lose track of that car.
Okay. I won't.
She said she lived in Gangnam.
Why is she heading up so high?
Hello?
You closed already?
I came to get a trim.
Come early tomorrow morning.
What's up?
Why did you close this early?
Are you unwell?
No. Something important came up.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
What? Where did she go?
It's really strange.
She was here
just a little while ago.
Where on earth did she go?
No one's home?
Dad.
Where are you?
I have some work left to do,
so I'm still at school.
Where's the domestic helper?
She told us this morning
that she'd go to her hometown...
for her younger sibling's
60th birthday.
Oh, right.
It's dangerous at night,
so don't come home too late.
All right. Okay. Bye.
What is this smell?
They say ox knee soup...
is good for broken bones.
You're way too naive
and kindhearted.
Don't make Kang Soo uncomfortable.
Just make sure to keep your promise.
- What promise?
- The blind date.
Okay. I will.
Oh, right.
I went to the hotel earlier today...
and ran into Chairman Han.
What a small world.
Chairman Han
used to be Dr. Hwang's student.
I see.
Dr. Hwang asked Chairman Han...
to take good care of you.
Why would he do that?
Chairman Han is obsessed
with integrity.
He hates it when he's asked
for a special favor.
Obsessed with integrity?
When I gave him
some makgeolli as a gift,
he almost called off
the supply contract.
He must've been annoyed
because he wasn't satisfied...
with the lame gift.
Seriously,
he's so particular and picky.
- What?
- What a jerk.
Gosh, it's hot. Darn it!
Hey.
When I gave him
some makgeolli as a gift,
he almost called off
the supply contract.
He must've been annoyed
because he wasn't satisfied...
Honey, why is there still no news?
About what?
About the makgeolli
that you brought as a sample.
Why is there no news
of it being released?
It's the best makgeolli
you've ever made.
Is there any problem?
- Come on!
- My goodness.
I told you
not to meddle in my business.
You startled me.
I'm not meddling.
I'm just asking because I'm curious.
It'll be released when it's time.
Can't you just wait patiently?
What's wrong
that's making you feel so down?
Se Ri, where are you going?
I'm going to school.
You have no class today.
I'm working as Professor Oh's TA
starting today.
"TA?"
She means a teaching assistant.
I'm running late, so I'll go first.
I'll see you later.
She should just learn
to be a good wife...
until Gyeol finishes
his military service.
Why would she work
as a teaching assistant?
Our Se Ri...
will be taking over LX Hotel.
For Se Ri,
learning to be a good wife...
means studying something useful
for hotel management.
Apparently,
he's a very promising professor...
who studied in the US.
If she works as his assistant,
it will be helpful...
when she takes over the hotel.
So, you don't have to worry
about Se Ri.
You should just focus on your work.
Okay?
Come on!
Why are you nagging me so much
when I have to go to work?
Wait. I'm coming with you.
Okay.
It's nice.
Hello, Professor Oh.
Hey.
It's my first day,
so I took extra care of things.
I see.
This is made with my favorite beans.
I hope you will like it.
I can make my own coffee,
so you don't have to do this.
Okay.
It does smell good.
By the way,
this doesn't feel like my office.
Why not? Do you not like it?
I appreciate the gesture,
but I don't want you
to do this again.
This is a professor's office...
where graduate students read books
and study together.
I don't think
we'd need flowers here.
You bought them for me anyway,
so I'll gratefully accept them
this time.
But don't do that again.
Okay.
This is for the flowers and coffee.
Please don't do this.
I didn't spend much on this.
Still, I can't let a student
spend her own money.
Just take it.
Your office is also my workplace.
I just wanted to work
in a comfortable and nice place.
I can't take your money.
I will stop buying flowers.
If you still feel indebted,
please buy me a meal.
At the school cafeteria.
Sure.
Hold on.
Hello?
It's me, Beom Soo.
What now?
Professor, I'm heading
to the department office.
I believe we were done talking.
Ha Ni...
Let me see her just once.
Please.
Enough with this nonsense.
That must be Ha Ni's mom.
What if this upsets
Professor Oh again?
(Professor's Office, Oh Beom Soo)
What's the occasion?
It's not like you to call first.
- I'm at the airport.
- The airport?
Are you going somewhere?
I mean I'm
at Incheon International Airport.
What?
Incheon International Airport?
- Honey.
- Hey.
I was going to fly out there
in two days.
I figured it'd be better for me
to make the trip.
There are things to sort out anyway.
Let's order first.
What do you mean?
Are you saying you're out of a job?
In a nutshell, yes.
You've got to be kidding me.
How could you keep
something this huge from me?
I wasn't keeping it from you.
It never seemed like the right time.
I was going to tell you
when I got to the US.
How have you been paying
for our living expenses...
and Yeong Ju's tuition?
Was it from your severance pay?
I sold the apartment.
What?
I don't care if it was in your name.
How could you sell it
without telling me?
Calm down and lower your voice.
How can I calm down?
I'm sorry
I didn't discuss it with you,
but I didn't tell you
because I didn't want...
to worry you or Yeoung Ju.
I didn't sell the apartment
to make my own life better.
What can we do
now that we're in this situation?
This is worse than pathetic.
It's appalling.
Do you have to talk that way?
What else?
Should I applaud you instead?
Darn.
What about
your brother's inheritance?
- What do you mean?
- Didn't the brothers...
sell the brewery
and split the money?
We didn't split anything.
Our sister-in-law is running it.
Why is that woman
taking over the brewery?
That woman? Watch your words.
You gave the brewery to a woman
he was married to for just ten days?
All the brothers agreed to it.
Well, I didn't.
Heung Soo, Beom Soo, Kang Soo,
and I made the decision.
How did you reach that conclusion
when I never agreed to it?
Aren't I a member of this family?
If that's how you felt,
you should've come to the funeral
when we were sorting things out.
What good could come out
of bringing that up now?
Being the pushover you are...
is why you're always duped.
What?
I'll be staying at Seok Jin's.
At your brother's?
If I stay with you,
all we'll do is argue.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Come in.
Someone is here to see you, sir.
Someone? Who?
She's the mother of CEO Ma
at Eagle Brewery.
Why is CEO Ma's mother
here to see you?
Beats me.
There's no reason for me to see her.
Should I talk to her instead?
Ms. Gong...
is like family and a close friend,
so do right by Eagle Brewery,
Chairman Han.
Have her come in.
Go ahead.
Thank you.
I greeted you...
with Dr. Hwang
at the restaurant the other day.
I'm CEO Ma's mother.
Right. I remember.
I apologize for taking up your time
when you're busy.
I'll give you what I came here for
and be on my way.
I heard from my daughter...
that you helped her immensely...
in getting her makgeolli
supplied to this hotel.
Gosh, no. The decision was made...
after a blind test was conducted
by the employees.
My daughter and I...
see you as our lifelong savior.
A lifelong savior? That's absurd.
My goodness.
You're also quite humble.
CEO Ma may be on the older side,
but she has no grasp
on the real world.
Even I'm frustrated
by my own daughter at times.
Many of our guests have been
ordering Jang-Kwang Makgeolli...
ever since your interview aired.
Those who tasted it
at the restaurant...
come by to purchase it too.
I had no idea our makgeolli...
would be served at a hotel.
I'm overwhelmed.
Anyway,
I hope we get along.
I should be saying that to you.
Hello, Mr. Park.
Hello.
You must be here with your mother.
- Sorry?
- Your mother is...
in the chairman's office.
Mother...
as in my mom?
Yes. She came by just now
to meet with the chairman.
Why would my mom be here?
Are you kidding me?
Excuse me. Sorry about this.
Darn it!
What's this?
It's a black and white porcelain jar
from the Joseon Dynasty.
Back when my husband was alive,
he cherished it dearly...
as if it would fly away
if blown on...
or shatter if touched.
But why did you...
It's for you, Chairman Han.
For me?
(Eagle Brewery)
Seriously.
The call cannot be connected.
- Transferring to voicemail.
- You're killing me, Mom.
Why isn't she picking up?
(Eagle Brewery)
Shoot!
Darn.
Darn it.
You're going out of your way
to help my daughter.
Honestly, I could offer you
not just this...
but also Joseon white porcelain
or Goryeo celadon.
Please accept this
as a token of my appreciation.
Goodness.
You can't do this.
I can't accept this.
I'm coming to you
as someone's mother.
I mean nothing else.
- Here.
- But...
Let me say this again.
There's no reason for me
to accept this.
Of course, there's a reason.
Ever since the news coverage,
orders have been piling in,
and our online business
has taken off.
I owe it all to you, Chairman Han.
I had nothing to do with it.
It's because...
your daughter's makgeolli
is of high quality.
You're being too modest.
The brewery was close
to shutting its doors for good,
but you breathed life back into it.
You changed CEO Ma's life.
You have every right to accept this.
I understand your intention.
However, accepting personal gifts
from a partner or supplier...
goes against my business principles.
My conscience won't allow it either.
You're only embarrassing me
by saying that.
I was wondering
how to express my gratitude...
and wanted...
to give you something
that means the most to me.
I guess a porcelain jar like this...
must seem like nothing
to someone as wealthy as you.
Gosh, no. That's not what I meant.
But it's the most valuable thing
I own,
so please accept it.
I come to you as someone's mother.
Come in.
Goodness.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I had something to give
to Chairman Han.
What could you possibly give him?
What...
What is this doing here?
Thanks to Chairman Han,
the brewery is doing well,
and my daughter was on the news.
I wanted to express my gratitude.
You're killing me.
I'm sorry, sir.
Well, there's no need to apologize.
- Get up.
- What? Why?
Goodness.
Oh, no. Why would you take that?
It's for the chairman.
Stop it, will you?
My gosh.
Oh, no!
- My gosh!
- Goodness.
What now?
But this jar means everything to me.
It's a black and white porcelain jar
from the Joseon Dynasty!
Oh, no. I can't believe I lost this.
No, leave that there.
I'll have my secretary
clean the floor.
I apologize for the commotion, sir.
Please leave with your mother.
What?
Oh, right. Of course.
Mom, let's go.
Anyway,
my apologies, Chairman Han.
Right.
I'm sorry you lost
something precious to you.
I know.
The jar may have shattered,
but please know how grateful I am.
Sure thing.
Forgive us for the intrusion.
I'll see you again
if the situation allows it.
Sure.
Let go.
Just a second.
"Made in China?"
- Made in China?
What...
You said it was
from the Joseon Dynasty.
What? Well...
That's what your father said.
Could it have been brought
to Joseon...
from China by boat?
You're killing me, Mom.
How can I look at him
now that you've humiliated me?
Your father said...
it was from the Joseon Dynasty.
Mom!
Goodness me. My heart.
What would he think of me now?
I already got on his bad side...
for putting makgeolli in his trunk.
That's why I came by.
To help you get...
on his good side.
My gosh.
You're impossible, Mom.
- Wait for me.
- Take the bus!
Wait for me.
Hold on.
She disappeared
around here somewhere.
Did your mom
allow you to get a perm?
Yes.
That's great. Congratulations.
Hey, kid.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I thought you were someone I know.
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
Wait.
Do you perhaps know
a girl named Eun Seo?
She seems to live around here.
I don't.
Is that so?
Got it. Thanks anyway.
Is this not the right neighborhood?
It's currently a yoga studio,
but it's big enough
to fit four pianos.
A bus stop is right outside it,
which makes it
incredibly accessible.
The location seems better
compared to your current academy.
Sure. It seems that way.
It's nice to see a married couple
speaking to each other with respect.
You're like a pair of lovebirds.
We're not married, ma'am.
You're not?
I thought that was the case
because you two look good together.
Who knows if that will be the case?
What on earth?
Why are they together again?
Did I offend you earlier?
With that remark about us
possibly getting married someday.
Why would I be offended...
when it was only a joke?
I wasn't joking.
It wasn't a joke.
I...
I'd like us to formally date,
Ms. Kim.
You feel the same way about me,
don't you?
Thank you.
My gosh!
What is it?
Over there.
Goodness!
What...
What were you doing out here?
I believe I pleaded with you.
Why won't you take me seriously?
Ms. Kim's not the person
you think she is.
She's hiding a massive secret.
What secret?
Well...
I'm not ready to tell you yet.
If you give me a little time,
I'll reveal whatever the secret is.
My gosh.
It looks like you watched
too many K-dramas.
What?
Stay out of my business...
and focus on your salon business.
Hey.
If you two want to talk a bit more,
shall I leave?
No. We're done.
Let's go.
But...
Why that sly little...
Darn her.
Hey. What are you doing out here?
I was cleaning the floor.
Your arm's not healed yet.
Don't waste your energy.
I can do it in no time.
Thank you, Mr. Go.
For staying with my sister-in-law.
Jang Soo will thank you
from where he is too.
I thought you were childish
and naive,
but you're pretty thoughtful.
And you're a hard worker too.
I like you even more.
Treat your sister-in-law well.
I will.
I should.
The CEO and her mother
got into another huge fight.
There's never a quiet day.
Why did you go to the chairman
without talking to me first?
How am I to face him now?
I didn't know this would happen!
You're in the wrong!
Don't yell at me!
I apologized to you
all the way back.
What more do you want?
Should I go on my knees?
What's the matter?
Is something wrong, Kwang Sook?
Kids do nothing for you
once they're grown up.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I meant well, and I messed up.
I can't stand it anymore.
Let's see how you manage without me.
Darn it.
Did something bad happen?
My mom did something terrible.
Something terrible?
Hang on.
If they didn't break it by mistake,
I'd have believed it were
a Joseon white porcelain jar.
My gosh...
They're really something.
Se Ri.
Hi.
What are you thinking about?
What you see
isn't always what you get.
What do you mean?
They look perfect on the outside...
as if they lack nothing at all,
but if you look inside,
they're full of hurt.
There's an insane story
they can't tell anyone.
- Who do you mean?
- What?
Sorry.
It's just someone I know.
I got a breakfast set. Let's eat.
Thank you.
(Egg Toast)
It's nice and sweet.
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
Is your TA job doable?
So-so, I guess?
Is the professor nice to you?
He doesn't say much,
and he's a bit on the cold side.
But I understand why.
I think I'd be the same
if I were him.
Does he have
some special circumstances?
What?
No.
I just have a feeling he does.
I see.
I gave birth to Ha Ni.
I have a right to see her
when I want to.
Isn't it too cruel
to keep her from me?
The call cannot be connected.
Transferring to...
Where on earth is she
that she won't pick up?
Welcome.
I went to a few realtors.
The brewery's the only thing
that hasn't changed around here.
There's a low-rise complex,
and a high-end townhouse
might be built.
The price of land soared.
- How much?
- Two dollars.
Thanks.
It'll keep going up.
How could he lose it all
to his sister-in-law?
Here's your card.
Exactly.
I'll take my share and go.
Yeoung Ju's dad?
He's no help at all. He's too soft.
The woman was married
for just ten days,
and she took over the brewery...
that had been in his family
for generations.
Does that make any sense?
"I'm so very sorry..."
"for what..."
"happened today,"
"Chairman Han."
(LX Hotel Chairman Han Dong Seok)
(Pot Number 3)
My mother went to see you
with the simple intention...
of showing her gratitude.
(Eagle Brewery)
My father got the jar
from an acquaintance...
who owed him money
instead of a payment.
The person who gave him the jar...
said it was from the Joseon era,
and that it was an antique
with great monetary value.
My family...
cherished it
as if it were a treasure.
So please,
do not have any misgivings.
I'm sorry
someone as upright as you...
had to witness such a disaster.
In the future,
nothing like this will happen again.
Yours sincerely,
Eagle Brewery's Ma Kwang Sook.
(LX Hotel Chairman Han Dong Seok)
(Sent)
(Eagle Brewery Ma Kwang Sook)
(My mother went to see you
with the simple intention...)
(of showing her gratitude.
My father got the jar...)
(Yours sincerely, Ma Kwang Sook)
Okay.
(Okay.)
"Okay?"
What?
It took me hours
to write the message,
but he just said,
"Okay?"
Is that it?
She could've just said sorry.
Why did she have to say
so many things?
There is no one I can trust.
This is really baffling.
And what's wrong with this wine?
What are you doing here?
About Ms. Gong.
She didn't even have dinner.
She's been stuck
in her room all day.
She will be fine tomorrow morning,
so you don't have to worry.
From what I heard,
she just tried to help you
with your business.
Please don't be upset.
You're worried about my mom?
You're so sweet, Kang Soo.
Okay.
Now that you say that,
I'll be cool
and make up with my mom.
Happy now?
Thank you, Kwang Sook.
I should thank you.
I feel so reassured and happy
because I have you.
(Dancing Prince)
We're not married, ma'am.
You're not?
I thought that was the case
because you two look good together.
Who knows if that will be the case?
Hello?
I'm calling you as I was wondering
if you got off work yet.
Yes. I just parked
in front of my house.
Are you coming
to the class tomorrow?
Of course. Why do you ask?
Nothing. I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay. Bye.
What is going on?
Isn't this the neighborhood
she lives in?
I'm sure she has something to do
with the kid and the old lady.
Did you drink?
A little.
What's the matter?
Pack your stuff and come back.
I told you. I like it here.
We're married.
Why should we live apart?
Come back with your stuff right now.
Are you saying I should live in
that tiny room with you?
There won't be any space left
with my suitcase open.
I'll get you a hotel room.
We can stay there, right?
Let's go.
Hotel room, my foot.
I like it here.
So don't worry about me.
Honey.
Don't call me like that.
I want to stop being your wife.
What?
I came back to end things with you.
End things?
What does that mean?
I want a divorce.
Let's get divorced.
We should.
(For Eagle Brothers)
I gritted my teeth
through the hard times,
thinking of you and Yeoung Ju.
But all I get in return
is a divorce?
Kwang Sook, you might get
a new sister-in-law soon.
I'm planning to propose tomorrow.
Am I finally getting
a younger sister-in-law?
Where is the woman?
Are you talking about Kwang Sook?
You want a piece of me?
I do want a piece of you!
The brewery is mine!
I will never let you
take it away from me!