Do you...
have...
feelings for me?
It's stupid, isn't it?
I must've briefly lost my mind.
Sorry. Pretend you didn't hear me.
You're right.
I'm right?
Yes, you're right.
I have feelings for you.
Yes, of course.
As your hotel's supplier,
you consider Eagle Brewery as...
This goes beyond that.
I have romantic feelings for you.
Why would you make
such a terrifying joke?
It's not a joke. I mean it.
My gosh. Goodness me. That's insane.
Where do you think you're going?
My head just started ringing.
I think
I should wrap things up for now.
CEO Ma. Hold on.
(Eagle Brewery)
What on earth did I just hear?
This is ridiculous.
I shouldn't have asked.
I shouldn't have asked!
Ever since it was exposed...
that an executive at Silla Brewery
orchestrated the attack,
the market and public opinion
have been scathing.
How about you apologize publicly...
and show your remorse...
to Eagle Brewery
in an official capacity?
What are you saying?
Why should I apologize
for something my subordinate did?
What's the point in distinguishing
whether one man...
or a whole company is responsible?
If your subordinate was corrupt,
you're partially responsible
as the CEO who hired them.
I heard he fled abroad.
Your company
doesn't have to suffer...
the criticism until he's caught.
You also have a duty
to explain away...
the misunderstanding
you caused Eagle Brewery.
May I ask why...
you're so involved in this issue?
What ties do you have...
with Eagle Brewery
that you're doing this?
I don't get it, to be honest.
Eagle Brewery is my supplier
and business partner,
and I selected their product
and decided to buy it.
Their reputation is mine also.
Is that all it is?
What answer were you expecting
or hoping for?
Well,
you're not the Chairman Han
I used to know.
I asked out of bewilderment.
Don't you think...
we should avoid doing something
our children would be ashamed of?
Think about it carefully.
Thank you for listening to
an uncomfortable suggestion.
I'll see myself out.
I should avoid doing something
my child would be ashamed of?
How dare you lecture me?
(Eagle Brewery Unrefined Makgeolli)
Yes, you're right.
I have feelings for you.
I just asked
because I couldn't believe it.
Ma Kwang Sook.
Why on earth
did you ask such a thing?
How am I to face him now?
What are you doing out here?
I was resting a bit
to recover from a headache.
Where are you going?
I took a long enough break.
I should get back to protesting.
(Silla Brewery Dokgo Tak,
Apologize for the fake video)
You don't have to protest.
What?
I told you...
I'd make Dokgo Tak apologize.
Chairman Dokgo...
will call a press conference
to apologize soon.
Will he really?
I only say what I mean
and what is true.
Thank you, Chairman Han.
I won't forget what you did for me.
Oh, dear.
You know,
I always keep my word.
I'll get back to work, then.
I solved a huge problem for you.
"Thank you."
"I'll never forget it."
They're just empty words.
What?
Can't you at least buy me
bean sprout soup and rice?
Bean sprout soup and rice?
I left home before breakfast
to stop by here before work.
Oh, my gosh.
Chairman Han!
My goodness.
Come in.
How are things right now?
I asked security.
The woman who was protesting...
packed up and left.
Goodness.
It's as if that woman
and Chairman Han are in cahoots.
Hello, it's me.
Hello, ma'am.
You can go.
What are you doing here
out of the blue?
I did some thinking after you left.
Don't make things worse.
Apologize to Eagle Brewery
and end it.
My gosh.
Why do you...
and Chairman Han both
want me to apologize?
Why is no one on my side?
What do you mean?
Chairman Han told you to apologize?
He was here just now.
He lectured me...
and told me
to apologize to the public.
I couldn't stand it.
I'd have headbutted him
if only our kids weren't engaged.
How did he know what happened?
His hotel
serves Eagle Brewery's makgeolli.
Do as Chairman Han says,
whatever the cost.
- What?
- Don't you want to marry Se Ri off?
Se Ri's a smart and pretty girl.
He should be grateful...
that he could ever get her
as a daughter-in-law.
Why do we have to bow
and grovel all the time?
You caused this disaster
because you got too greedy.
How many times must I tell you?
I had nothing to do with this!
Director Seo went and did it
behind my back!
What is it?
What?
Since you lie so much,
I expect you to be better at it.
Then and now,
you're still so transparent
when you try to lie.
What?
Stupid people like you...
should never lie and obey the law.
How dare you talk like that to me?
If Se Ri's marriage falls through
because of you,
I'll divorce you, and that's final!
What the heck?
Oh, my gosh.
If only...
they'd handed over
the brewery to us,
none of this would've happened.
It's all on Ma Kwang Sook,
that darn viper.
Enjoy your meal.
Let's eat quick and leave.
Why won't you eat?
Cool it for me.
What?
You cooled it for me last time.
That's hot.
I see you require a lot of care.
I spoiled him rotten.
Did you think about it?
About what?
About what I said earlier.
Stop joking about and eat your food.
Why do you act
as if I crack jokes all the time?
I wasn't kidding. I was serious.
You must know so many cool
and amazing women.
Why would you like me?
Do you lack...
that much self-esteem?
I do know...
I look good enough
that I shouldn't be intimidated.
You're not that beautiful.
I'm so cheerful and energetic...
that people say
I have the spirit of a strong woman,
and they often praise me
for being upbeat...
As I said last time,
you're not dislikable,
but you are a nuisance.
I empathize with others...
quickly and easily,
and I help people feel at ease
most of the time.
You might find it attractive too.
You are...
the woman who swears better
than anyone...
I've ever met.
Then why do you like me?
Because it's you.
What?
I don't like you
for any special reason.
I just like you because it's you.
Because you're Ma Kwang Sook.
That's why.
What...
What does this response mean?
I have something urgent to do,
so I think I should get going first.
Please finish your meal.
I'm not done talking.
No. I don't think I should hear it.
I'm leaving.
My goodness.
What was that?
I finally made up my mind
to tell her about my feelings.
Kwang Sook.
Where did you go so early
in the morning?
Well...
I went to Silla Brewery
for a one-man protest.
Why did you go alone
without consulting me?
I'm the one who should be
doing the one-man protest.
I'll do it starting tomorrow.
We don't have to go anymore.
Why not?
Well... Chairman Dokgo Tak says...
he will make a public apology soon.
Really?
Yes. He says
he's going to do it soon.
I'll make Dokgo Tak
apologize to you.
So stop doing this.
- Are you feeling hot?
- What?
It's not even hot,
but you keep fanning yourself.
Well...
You're right.
Did I get heatstroke
during the one-man protest?
Hello, Mr. Go.
Did something happen to Mi Sun?
Why?
I stopped by the convenience store
on my way here,
but I haven't seen her
since yesterday.
Actually, I was worried,
so I left a voicemail,
but I haven't heard back.
Is she sick?
The phone is turned off.
Transferring to voicemail.
Your call may be charged
after the tone.
Her phone has been turned off
since yesterday.
What is going on?
Hello?
Hey, it's me.
What do you want?
You threw a tantrum
as if you'd never see me again.
Come on. That day,
I got upset
and complained a little...
because the choreography
I poured my heart into was rejected.
Let me tell you something
for old time's sake,
so don't take it personally...
and think about it carefully,
Heung Soo.
Okay. Sure.
The world has changed.
Times have changed a lot
since the days...
when you and I performed on stage.
So what's the point
you're trying to make?
Don't be so obsessed with it...
and make a realistic choice.
So the rest of your life...
won't be so pathetic.
Stop it.
That's enough.
I will never ask you
to consider my choreography again.
I'm hanging up.
What does he know
about choreography to criticize me?
Mr. Rooftop House. Are you in there?
Yes.
Hello.
Hey. Well...
When will you be able to move out?
Move?
I can move out right away
if you want.
Right away?
Yes. The furniture here isn't mine.
I just need to pack my clothes.
I will move out in exactly one hour.
But you'll need to find
a place to stay.
Don't worry about me.
I've already found a place.
Can you give me
the deposit right away?
You can't do this.
We promised
not to tie each other down.
I'm not tying you down.
As if you're not.
You tied my arms and legs.
Heung Soo.
Are you going on a trip?
It's not like that.
I just moved out
of the rooftop house.
What?
Here.
What is this?
The money
I borrowed from you before...
and the monthly rent
you paid the landlady in advance.
Heung Soo.
Thank you for everything.
Are you...
trying to run away
before I hold you back?
It's not like that.
Forget it. I should get going.
(K-beauty pioneer G Hair Salon)
Have a nice life without me,
Oh Heung Soo!
I have no lingering affection
for you anymore!
- Hey, Ji Ok Bun!
- What?
Don't even call my name, you coward!
You...
Why are you being so reckless?
When you're being so reckless
like a moron,
why do I have to stay reasonable?
- "Moron?"
- Yes, you moron!
Oh Heung Soo!
Don't you dare pass by my store.
I'll kill you if you do!
Darn it.
She doesn't even know
how I'm feeling.
What's wrong with her?
Hello.
I'm Lee Yong Dae, the new TA.
You must be Dokgo Se Ri.
Yes. I got the call
from the department office.
I'll transfer the work to you.
Hey, you guys are here.
Hello, Professor.
Did you two introduce each other?
Yes. I'll learn a lot
from the former TA...
and make sure
everything runs smoothly for you.
Things have been well
thanks to your thoughtful work.
Thank you for everything.
Managing the accounting work
according to the regulations,
sending data to the researchers,
and preparing for meetings.
These will be your main tasks,
so make sure to take over the jobs.
I'll do a good job
without making any mistakes...
so you won't have to worry about it.
Okay.
I've organized the main tasks
in each file.
If you read it, you'll be able
to understand it easily.
You've organized them in detail.
Well,
I should get going.
Se Ri.
Dokgo Se Ri.
Se Ri, wait.
I'm sorry I hurt your feelings.
Is having feelings for you
really such a terrible thing?
Bad enough to get me kicked out...
of my TA position?
Don't cry.
All of this is for your sake.
For my sake?
My heart's in pieces,
and the pain is unbearable.
How could this be for my sake?
This is cruel, Professor.
Gyeol.
Hey. You made it.
Have you been crying?
Why did you cry?
Did something happen?
I was just forced out
of my TA position.
What?
My mom met with the professor.
Don't resent her too much.
It's understandable that your mother
would react that way.
I know.
All mothers are protective
of their children,
but your mother, in particular,
devoted her life to you.
From how I wear my hair
and the way I dress,
to the colleges I applied to
and the friends I spent time with,
I did exactly
what my mom told me to do.
Even you know
I'm Mommy's little girl.
But for the first time ever,
I finally feel like
I'm in control of my own life.
I think I get what you mean.
That man you like.
Is he the professor
I saw you with...
when I visited campus on the day
I was discharged...
from the Navy?
Yes.
I didn't get a good look at him,
but he seemed like a gentleman.
It'll take me a while
to support the two of you,
but I'll at least respect
your feelings.
I'm too ashamed
to say anything to you.
I'm really sorry.
I've thought about it,
and this isn't something
anyone should feel ashamed of...
or apologize for.
It was out of your control.
The heart wants what it wants.
I haven't told my dad or Bom yet.
I'd like to tell Bom in person.
I feel like I should.
Sure thing.
(CEO Dokgo Tak)
If Se Ri's marriage falls through
because of you,
I'll divorce you, and that's final!
Unbelievable.
I can't afford to go through
a divorce at this age.
Darn it.
Hello?
Right. It's me.
So,
have you thought about it?
I'll do as you suggested.
As the CEO,
I should take responsibility...
for any wrongdoing committed
by my subordinates.
That's how it should be.
You made the right decision.
I'll make a public apology
tomorrow afternoon.
I'll get my people on it.
I appreciate your courage.
This will pull both Silla Brewery...
and Eagle Brewery
out of their holes.
Sure thing. We'll get together soon.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
(LX Hotel Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Hello?
What took you so long to answer?
Were you busy?
What's this about?
I called for two reasons.
Two reasons?
First,
how could you ditch me like that
at the bean sprout soup place?
You didn't even pick up the bill.
Goodness.
I was so frazzled
that I forgot to pay the bill.
You owe me a meal,
and I'm going to hold you to that.
Is that the reason you called?
That was the first thing
I needed to tell you.
Now, here's the second.
Could I hear that some other time?
How come?
I have to admit, hearing that
you have something to say...
makes me nervous.
Tomorrow afternoon,
Silla Brewery will make
a public apology.
Really?
I was just on the phone
with Chairman Dokgo Tak.
Will he really apologize?
I never expected him
to apologize so easily.
I told you I'd get him to apologize.
I'm not the kind of person
who makes promises I can't keep.
- I...
- Wait.
I can't listen to any more of this.
That's enough. Stop.
Stop?
I've got a feeling
this might take a weird turn.
I'd rather end it here.
So you're only going to listen to
what you want to hear?
Yes. I'm done listening after this.
Then, I'll hang up first.
How can she just pick and choose
what she wants to hear...
and ignore the rest?
That's just wrong.
I guess...
being a bulldozer is part
of her charm.
(The 8th Golden Castle
Dance Team Recital)
The women at Golden Castle
will brag to no end.
I know it's last minute,
but should I call Dr. Hwang
to say I can't make it?
Darn.
So, what will happen to us, Mr. Go?
What do you mean?
Will the brewery shut down?
Even though the video
was revealed to be fake,
we're still not getting any orders.
Nothing's changed.
It does seem tough
to bounce back this time around.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Hey.
Are you going somewhere, Mrs. Gong?
Where else would I be going...
besides my part-time job?
Mr. Go.
Me?
Are you free this Saturday?
This Saturday?
Kwang Sook.
You've been fanning yourself
since this morning.
Are you not feeling well?
Maybe I've been too stressed
over the loan.
My heart feels like it's on fire,
and my face is burning up.
Kwang Sook, I...
I hate to bring this up
since it's a sensitive subject,
but you did what you could.
Even if we shut down the brewery,
no one would hold it against you.
- So...
- I'd consider it...
if things were dire,
but let's not talk about that
just yet.
- What...
- It's Heung Soo.
- Chun Soo.
- Hey.
Heung Soo, come on in.
What brings you by unannounced?
I have something for both of you.
Take your seats.
Let's sit.
What's this?
See for yourself.
(10,000 dollars)
Hey.
Where on earth
did you get this money?
Well, I know it's not much,
but use it to pay off
some of the bank loan.
But we're well aware
of your financial situation.
Where did this large sum of money
come from?
I won the lottery.
What?
Where did you get this money?
An idol group selected
my choreography,
and this is the payment I received.
No way.
That's amazing.
Congratulations, Heung Soo.
And here I thought
you were partying all the time.
I'm proud of you, brother.
Wait. Hold on.
You worked so hard
to earn this money.
You shouldn't give it all to us.
Come on. If I could,
I'd gladly contribute...
not just 20,000 dollars,
but 200,000 or even 2 million.
It's not much,
but I want to do this for you.
Please, accept it.
Thank you.
If that's how you feel,
then I'll gladly accept it.
Aren't you proud of me?
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
You see,
I can't reach the store owner.
Have you heard from her?
I talked to her this morning.
She's in the hospital.
The hospital?
She's having surgery today.
Surgery?
Sir, I'm sorry to ask,
but could you speed up a little?
Sure.
Thank you.
In my case,
my mom passed away
before I started elementary school,
and my dad died last year
from cancer.
In this vast land of Korea,
I'm all by myself.
Goodness. Sorry about that.
(Surgery Center,
Intensive Care Unit)
(Operating Room)
Excuse me, but may I...
Mi Sun.
Are you Ms. Mun Mi Sun's guardian?
- Yes.
- Her hernia...
has been repaired.
The surgery was a success
with no complications.
I see.
It'll be an hour or two
before she wakes up.
Right. Thank you.
We're moving her
to the recovery room now.
Sure.
I wanted Se Ri to marry Gyeol...
so she'd become
Chairman Han's daughter-in-law,
and for Kang Soo to marry Bom...
so he could become the son-in-law.
If that works out,
I'll have nothing to worry about.
My daughter, you're home.
They say you're better off
not having children at all.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Are you really not going
to answer me?
You got what you wanted.
Are you happy now?
What do you mean
I got what I wanted?
I lost my position
as Professor Oh's TA.
This only happened
because you went to see him.
How come?
Did your professor say something
about me?
Mom, please.
He's not the type of person
to badmouth others.
I get that you're upset,
but you'll truly thank me one day...
for shutting this down.
I can guarantee that.
I want to be alone, so please leave.
Get back to me...
after you have a daughter
just like you.
Then, you'll understand
why I did this.
But Ha Ni's enough for me.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Come in.
Mr. Kim Sa Man is here.
Right. Invite him in.
Gosh, it's been so long.
How long has it been?
The last time we met
was before COVID hit.
It's been over five years.
Exactly.
I was worried when I heard
you had been hospitalized.
It's great to see you back
on your feet.
Don't even get me started.
Back then,
I honestly didn't think I'd make it.
- Let's sit.
- Sure.
How's your business doing?
With Korean food
becoming more popular,
I'm buried in work lately.
I already had stores out West,
but now I've expanded...
to New York, Washington D.C.,
Atlanta, and even Texas.
I recently opened my 100th store.
I like the sound of that.
I've been busy
expanding the supply chain...
and only just found time to visit.
By the way, your mother-in-law
is one of our regular customers.
She's been filling me in
on how you're doing.
She's famous among the locals
for her fashion sense.
Her English is fluent,
and she could argue for days.
She's a force to be reckoned with.
I'd expect no less from her.
By the way, is liquor...
among the products you sell?
Yes, we offer soju
and green plum wine. Why?
We've been serving
traditional liquor at the hotel...
to our international guests.
It's been receiving rave reviews.
I was wondering
if you'd like to offer it too.
A liquor you guarantee?
I'd strongly consider that.
It can compete
with any wine out there.
Is it that good?
Could I meet with the company CEO?
I'll be free tomorrow evening.
Say no more.
(Eagle Brewery Payment Log)
(LX Hotel Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Hello?
Could you come
to the hotel right now?
Why?
There's something to discuss.
What is this about?
Can't we talk over the phone?
I'd like to discuss
a business-related matter.
I'll meet you in my office
in an hour.
A business-related matter?
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
Come in.
I'm Eagle Brewery CEO Ma Kwang Sook.
I'm here to see
Chairman Han Dong Seok to discuss...
a business matter.
What on earth are you doing?
If you don't mind, I'll sit down.
Shall we start the meeting,
Chairman Han?
I get it.
You want me to talk business
and nothing else?
What did you want to see me about?
I have this childhood friend,
and he emigrated young
and settled down.
He owns a chain
of Korean supermarkets in the US.
Oh, does he?
I met him a short while ago.
I suggested he sell
your Jang-Kwang Makgeolli.
What?
If things work out,
you could export
Jang-Kwang Makgeolli to the US.
Export to the US?
I think the yakju you sold...
at the festival we hosted...
would do better than your makgeolli.
You bet.
Our product might be sold in the US?
It doesn't feel real.
Thank you, Chairman Han.
However,
there's something...
you should be
much more grateful for.
I plucked up the courage
and told you I had feelings for you.
Why would you crack
such a scary joke so suddenly?
How many times must I say
I'm serious?
Do you think I'm the type
who would joke like that?
You should learn to accept it
when someone tells the honest truth.
Why do you keep twisting it?
I'll put it simply for you...
by means of an example.
You're like a soccer player
who plays for a premier league team.
I play for some random village
on a third-division team.
We couldn't be a good match.
Do you like soccer?
I'm glad we have that in common.
I'm saying that you and I play
in different leagues.
Why would you say
you're on a third-division team?
I think you're a premier-league...
I mean,
you could play
in the Champions League.
You're at it again.
I'll pretend
I didn't hear that and leave.
How can you pretend
when you heard everything?
I'm well aware...
things don't always go
as you want them to.
I also know
the hardest thing to do...
is to win someone's heart.
I won't rush you.
Let's take the time
to get to know each other.
Don't shut me out from the start.
Think about it carefully.
I should get going. Goodbye.
Oh, dear.
Will you be more careful?
I'm fine. Goodbye.
I'm off.
Goodness.
I'm back.
What is it? Do you feel hot?
I don't know. I feel flushed.
Give me that.
Are you menopausal already?
You're not old enough for that.
That's why you should remarry...
as soon as you can.
Give in to the guy...
when someone's willing to have you.
The hotel chairman likes you.
Trust me.
I have feelings for you.
This is between us,
but why would someone like him
go for someone like you?
That's my point exactly.
Something's bound to go wrong
if I forget my place and get greedy.
What's wrong with you?
You're the CEO of a brewery.
You're young, pretty,
and well-educated.
What do you lack?
Why are you smiling?
They say...
blood is thicker than water
and family sticks together,
but don't try to set me up
with someone out of my league.
You're a human being
with a conscience, okay?
Why does she keep talking like that?
Now I feel flushed.
(Hypy Land)
You're so successful.
You went from dancing for Winners...
to a rich businessman.
I'm not rich.
Can I stay as long as I want?
Yes. Stay until you want to leave.
Okay.
I get to save money
thanks to a rich friend.
Can I have two baked eggs?
We're out of baked eggs.
- Would you like anything else?
- No, thanks.
Why do you deal with customers
and not your staff?
Someone quit this morning
because of family issues.
I wish I had ten clones.
Can I have a cup ramyeon?
- Sure.
- Just a moment.
I'll get it.
(Haega Noodles)
That's three dollars.
Scan your locker key.
The payment was successful.
If it tastes good,
it's zero calories. Okay?
- Enjoy your snack.
- Thanks.
Have you worked at a sauna before?
You bet I have.
There's no part-time job
I haven't done.
Then can you man the snack bar
until I hire someone?
Okay. I can do that.
- Here.
- What?
I need to take this.
Go ahead.
Kang Soo.
Chun Soo just told me...
you gave them a huge sum.
You can't call that a huge sum.
I'm almost ashamed.
They said you got paid
for selling your choreography.
Yes.
That's true. That's what I said.
I'm impressed.
Don't flatter me.
I'm an artist.
This is nothing.
It's just a basic skill of mine.
(Taking the world by storm,
Oh Heung Soo, a backup dancer?)
You got duped by Ms. Kim...
and almost ruined your life,
and I saved you from her.
I protected you...
when the thugs almost killed you.
And you moved out of your place
just to run away from me?
Fine. Good riddance.
I'll find a man who loves me...
and date him and get married!
Oh Heung Soo!
Good luck
with the rest of your life!
Just a moment, Ha Ni.
What's the matter?
I'm calling you to say thank you.
I heard Se Ri quit
her teaching assistant job.
Thank you for making
such a difficult decision.
It's the right thing to do
as a professor for Se Ri.
You have no reason to thank me.
Se Ri is having a hard time,
but she will get over it soon.
I'm sorry for the trouble
we've caused you.
If you have nothing else to say,
I'll hang up.
And don't call me ever again.
It makes me uncomfortable.
Ha Ni, you must be hungry.
Do you want to eat?
All right. Let's go.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
What?
Chun Soo.
Are you awake?
Yes.
What are you doing here?
How did you know I was here?
How could you surprise me like this?
I should've known
that you were having surgery.
It's nothing serious.
It was just a minor hernia surgery.
Still, you should've told me.
Do you know how shocked I was...
when I heard
you were having surgery?
The surgery schedule was set
at the last minute,
and I thought...
you'd be worried and bothered
if I told you.
Why would you say that?
It's really upsetting.
If I had surgery,
would you be bothered?
Chun Soo.
I told you
that if you had a hard time,
I'd come running
to you right away...
and give you special treatment.
Why?
Is the pain bad?
Do you want me to call the nurse?
No. It's not that.
I'm just grateful...
that you said that.
What are you so grateful for?
It's something I have to do.
Actually,
I was a little scared.
"What if I don't wake up
after the surgery?"
"What if something goes wrong?"
"I have no family to look after me,
and I'm all alone."
Why are you alone?
What about me?
I'm right here next to you.
Why are you alone?
Thank you for saying that.
Doesn't your incision hurt?
Are you all right?
Yes. It's bearable.
By the way, Chun Soo,
the thing is,
when they gave me the anesthetic
before surgery,
your face came to mind.
I wondered if I'd ever...
wake up and see your face again.
Darn it.
I wanted to finish the surgery
without anyone knowing.
I dreamed of a perfect crime.
But I failed.
What?
(Lynx Golf Wear VIP Styling Class)
Hello, Lieutenant Oh.
It's been a while.
Congratulations on your new job.
Bom told me
she'd be working with you.
She sounded so happy.
Are you here to meet Bom?
Yes.
She's in there.
Go in.
Has the model for the makeover
arrived yet?
No. I've been calling her,
but she's not answering.
It's almost time.
What if she doesn't show up?
Bom.
Hey, you're early.
Yes. I was waiting at the cafe,
but I was bored.
You must be Bom's friend.
Can I ask you a favor?
Hello.
I'm Han Bom, who will be hosting...
this styling class event.
Now, let's start the styling class.
Our 2025 SS collection captures...
the beauty and elegance of a journey
on the golf course.
With their unique patterns
and functional materials,
these pieces are perfect not only
for performance golf wear,
but also for everyday
and resort wear.
The one on the left...
is a performance style suitable
for a couple's round of golf,
so it's neat and comfortable.
The right one...
is perfect for everyday wear.
Among those who are
attending the event today,
I'd like to pick one
and give her a makeover.
Could you come up to the stage
for a moment?
You look great in the outfit.
It's a bright outfit
that gives off the spring vibe.
She looks stylish already,
but how about this?
With a purse
that spices up your fashion,
you can complete
a much more sophisticated style.
It seems like Bom hosted the show...
a lot more smoothly
than we expected.
I think so. I was impressed.
Apparently, Silla Brewery will be
holding a press conference soon.
As soon as the press conference
is over,
we should hand out press releases...
stating that our hotel
will continue...
to collaborate closely
with Eagle Brewery...
to help advance the quality
and culture of traditional liquor.
I'm Chairman Dokgo Tak
of Silla Brewery.
First of all,
I would like to deeply apologize...
for the unfortunate incident
involving our company.
Although...
the incident occurred
due to the personal greed...
of a member of our company,
I feel ashamed...
that our Silla Brewery,
which has been loved by the public,
has failed to live up...
to people's expectations.
In addition,
I would like to express...
my deepest apologies
to Eagle Brewery...
that suffered greatly
due to this incident.
That jerk, who's like Kim Jong Un,
is trying to get away with this.
He looks like a sneaky trickster.
Just wait and see.
I'll lay bare the truth
and make him...
rub his hands together
and beg us for forgiveness.
You made him apologize
by doing the one-man protest.
You did a great job.
I'll get him to apologize to you,
so please stop this.
What man would like...
someone he cares about
being stared at?
Are you feeling hot?
Well... I suddenly got a hot flash
out of nowhere.
You should be on your way
to that meeting.
- Goodness.
- Right.
Look at the time.
This is the business proposal
for the convenience store.
I just changed the title.
You can use that as a reference
when speaking with the buyer.
Thanks, Mr. Vice-CEO.
Kim, have you sealed the bottles
of Jang-Kwang Yakju?
- Yes.
- Can you box them...
and have them gift-wrapped?
I'll head home
and quickly get changed.
- I'll see you in a bit.
- Sure.
No way.
Kwang Sook, my gosh.
Your look screams CEO.
Thanks.
Don't be nervous and stay relaxed.
- I'll do a good job.
- Sure. Let's go.
Hello, CEO Ma.
What...
What brings you here?
The chairman sent me
to escort you to the hotel.
What?
Actually, let me.
My goodness.
Welcome. I've been waiting for you.
Why were you waiting for me?
That just makes me uncomfortable.
You should step out of the car now.
Sure.
Of all the times I've seen you,
you look the most beautiful today.
Why would you say that to me?
It's a compliment.
Please don't compliment me
like that.
You're making me feel uncomfortable.
I can't say harsh things
when you look that good.
I'd prefer
you said harsh things instead.
(For Eagle Brothers)
Let me borrow your brewery manager
for a day.
I want to take him
to Golden Castle today.
I doubt Mr. Go would agree
to go there.
I don't think I can do this.
No way. Absolutely not.
It's about Heung Soo.
- He's been staying at a sauna.
- There you are.
- What?
- Are you the owner of this sauna?
Meet me outside the brewery.
I'm waiting for you.
If you're cooking ramyeon,
make an extra portion.
I'd like to have some.
That must be my mom.
Hold on.
Why should I hide
when I've done nothing wrong?