(Episode 22)
Volume Ten.
My gosh, I'm so sorry.
You didn't answer when I knocked,
so I thought you fell asleep.
I was...
I was only going to leave
with the next book when...
I'm sorry. I really am.
Sorry.
Are you kidding me?
I can't believe I messed up
and embarrassed myself like that.
Darn.
Yes?
My gosh.
Here you go.
Right.
Don't stay up too late reading that
and tuck in early.
Sure.
CEO Ma.
Good night.
Good night to you too.
Hey, Beom Soo.
Kwang Sook.
I only just got around
to checking my phone.
How are you doing?
The headache's gone,
and I'm no longer dizzy.
I'm feeling much better.
I'm glad to hear that.
I'll stop by the hospital
after class tomorrow.
You're already busy enough as it is.
Don't worry about me.
Hold on.
Is something wrong?
You don't sound
like your usual self.
You see,
I met Ha Ni's mom today.
She wanted to see Ha Ni
before she got married.
Ha Ni's mom is getting married?
Yes, this Saturday.
My gosh.
Beom Soo, are you doing okay?
Not really,
but it didn't rattle me as much.
Ha Ni's mom wanted
a flashy life in the spotlight,
but I wasn't someone
who could possibly give her that.
Going our separate ways
was for the best.
I see.
I laid out my problems on you...
when you should be resting.
Sorry about that.
Don't apologize.
I love how you opened up...
about what's been bothering you.
It feels like you finally see me
as someone you can rely on.
That makes me proud.
Don't be ridiculous.
You're the person I trust most
after Jang Soo.
Of course, I mean that.
Sure. Sleep tight as well.
Professor.
Here you go.
Having this at times like that...
always puts me in a better mood.
If you let it dissolve slowly
in your mouth,
you'll forget about your troubles
by the time you're almost done.
He's not my boyfriend.
I'm sorry.
I assumed he was.
He must've thought
I was really strange.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
I should stop reading
and go to sleep.
Oh, dear.
It was quite an interesting day.
By the way, I wonder
if Kwang Sook had breakfast.
I bet she did.
It's the VIP room,
so the food must be good too.
I'll go visit her at the hospital
after breakfast.
Good. You should do that.
I'm busy with work here,
so you should go to the hospital
and keep her company.
No. Don't bother.
You should let her rest quietly
for her sake.
Until she's discharged,
don't go near the hospital.
- Why not?
What?
Well... The thing is...
She must be tired
from all the tests.
Having her family members around
will make things worse.
You should never go there.
But she's alone at the hospital.
End of conversation.
Let's just eat.
(Park Sang Nam)
This is driving me nuts.
Well...
Sang Nam.
Why are you calling in the morning?
What time should I go
to get the purse back today?
Well... The thing is,
my friend borrowed it from me.
And she's out of town now.
It'll take me some time
to get it back.
Then...
give me the cash.
You want to get it back in cash?
I can't give you
that much money right away.
Sang Nam, I didn't know...
you were so unreasonable.
No, don't be like that.
If Kwang Sook finds out,
she'll get furious.
Okay. I get your point.
I'll call you back soon.
This is driving me crazy.
You like abalone rice porridge,
so our housekeeper made it for you.
Have some.
If she was going to make it,
she could've made a bigger portion.
You just brought one serving?
But you don't eat much.
What?
Well... That's true.
What's wrong?
I'll eat it later.
It's not as tasty when it's cold.
I have no appetite now.
You can leave it here.
I'll eat it later.
Do you want me to leave already?
I was going to take a walk
around the hospital...
and have some tea with you.
Don't treat me like a patient.
I'm leaving the hospital tomorrow.
Just leave it and go.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
Yes?
Good morning.
Did you sleep well, Chairman Han?
It wasn't so bad.
Did you have breakfast?
I just ate.
Already?
Why did you eat so early?
What?
I mean...
My housekeeper made
some abalone rice porridge,
so my daughter brought it.
I brought it for you.
Why don't you eat it?
I...
don't like abalone rice porridge.
I didn't want to throw it away,
but you already had breakfast.
I guess I'll have to throw it away.
Wait.
Give it to me.
You already ate.
I'll eat it.
Actually,
I love abalone rice porridge.
Will you?
My goodness.
It looks so good.
Oh, right.
No. I'm okay.
It's so good.
The abalone is really fresh.
It's perfectly seasoned
with salt and sesame oil,
so I don't need any soy sauce.
Oh, right.
I finished "The Celestial Drops"
last night.
You can take them
and finish reading them.
Is Volume 15 the end?
No. There are 44 volumes.
But I bought
only 15 of them for now.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Do I have rice on my face?
No.
It's nothing. Enjoy your food.
Wait.
You finished Volume 12, right?
Thank you.
Yes?
Ms. Ma Kwang Sook.
Please get ready for a test
after you finish your meal.
Okay.
And you should go to
the rehab center, Mr. Han.
You will start
the exercise therapy program there.
Okay. I will.
By the way,
do you two know each other?
We're friends.
I see.
I'll see you downstairs then.
Well... We're sharing comic books.
Doesn't that make us friends?
You're right.
I'm just honored to be your friend.
- This isn't right.
- I know.
- How is this happening?
- It's just wrong.
- This isn't the first time.
- It isn't.
- This is the second time.
- Who should we talk to?
- I can't believe this.
- This is unacceptable.
- Hey, you're here.
- Hi.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Today's class has been canceled.
- Why?
- Mr. Oh is absent again.
He skipped class twice
without any prior notice.
- This is too much.
- I know.
Tell me about it.
I know he's having a hard time
because of Ms. Kim.
But he should draw a line
between public and private matters.
By the way, did you guys watch...
- Mr. Oh's stream yesterday? No?
- No.
You wouldn't believe it.
He was completely out of his mind.
He was being so pathetic.
- Gosh, it was so upsetting.
- Oh, no.
Darn it.
I was busy,
so I barely made time to come.
But it was a waste of time.
- You can't waste your time.
- Surely not.
We should at least eat something
before going home.
Are you in there, Mr. Oh Heung Soo?
Mr. Oh Heung Soo?
Who are you?
You know Kim Seon Ah, right?
Seon Ah?
Of course, I know her.
Where is she now?
You punk.
How dare you?
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you address
our boss's wife like that?
Your what?
Why is Seon Ah your boss's wife?
Who are you?
We're here to kill you.
Stand up!
What are you on about?
Where's Seon Ah?
Don't you dare say her name.
Hey. Wake him right up.
Yes, sir.
Step aside.
You fool.
Hello?
A group of thugs are here...
beating someone up.
Get over here quick.
The guy's dying.
Where's Seon Ah now?
Our boss is still alive and well.
How dare someone like you
try to date her?
Don't just stand there. Crush him.
Yes, sir.
Stop!
Hey.
If you so much as touch my darling,
I'll kill you myself!
My gosh.
Who's she?
Ms. Ji.
I know who you are.
Kim Seon Ah's husband...
who's in Uijeongbu Prison
sent you, didn't he?
What?
Do you know our boss?
Just you wait.
Police cars are on the way
to pick you up.
- Darn you.
- Hey.
They're here.
You're all dead meat.
- Darn you.
- What?
Where do you think you're going?
We need you to be arrested.
Mr. Oh.
Are you all right?
Were you badly hurt?
What was all that about?
Let's go inside where we can talk.
You mean...
Seon Ah had a husband
and a daughter?
Yes. She did.
It must be a misunderstanding.
Seon Ah's not like that.
You're saying that
when you just got beaten up?
Let me see.
Be gentle.
Her husband's pretty hardcore.
He's an enforcer...
for a nationwide gang
called Oseong Gang.
He's doing time
in Uijeongbu Prison now.
How come...
you know all that?
I told you...
Ms. Kim was wearing a mask.
Something felt off,
so I hired a private investigator.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I didn't want you to get hurt.
You'd feel so betrayed
if you heard the truth.
It would be better
not to know at all.
I'd rather have you misunderstand
and curse me out...
than see you suffer
from a broken heart.
I boiled you some barley tea.
Drink some and see a doctor.
You look dreadfully ill.
I'll do that.
Ha Ni. Have fun with Granny.
Dad will get better soon.
Let's go so Dad can see a doctor.
Hello, Professor.
Hi. I'm down with a bad cold...
and can't come in.
Are you badly ill?
Yes. I can't teach at all.
Apologize to the students for me...
and say I'll schedule
an extra lecture.
Okay.
Don't worry
and focus on getting better.
Bye.
Oh, no.
He sounded really weak.
I knew it.
What is she thinking?
I should nip it in the bud...
before things go wrong.
I brought what you asked for.
Good job.
("The Celestial Drops")
Well,
I'm stuck in my room all day,
and I'm bored.
I get it.
Reading comics when you're bored...
is great fun.
This isn't...
just an ordinary comic series.
It's more like a guide
that teaches you the history...
of wine and gives you knowledge
that will last a lifetime.
I decided to use the time to study.
Of course.
What? Is there something on my face?
It's not that, sir.
You've been more cheerful
and energetic since you came here.
Oh, really?
Yes. You look more at ease
than ever before.
Well...
CEO Ma.
I'm coming in.
CEO...
CEO Ma.
Oh, dear. Is she away to get tested?
Chairman Han.
What were you doing out here?
Right.
I was on my way back from a test...
when I saw these beautiful flowers.
I was looking at them
while listening to some music.
I didn't know people still
listened to music on those things.
They're easy to use,
and you don't have to worry
about the battery.
Would you like to join me?
Goodness.
It's my brother-in-law.
Will you excuse me?
Hey, Chun Soo.
I called to brief you
on where we are today.
Deliveries were made
to the supermarkets and restaurants.
In the afternoon,
I'm going to
the convenience store head office...
to discuss what we talked about
last time.
Sure. I hope it goes well.
Go, Chun Soo.
My brother-in-law's been
covering my work.
If the company had any losses
because of your accident,
just send the invoice to the hotel
with the paperwork.
Everything's good
thanks to my brother-in-law.
By the way,
when will you be discharged?
Isn't it boring and stuffy
being in the hospital?
Not at all.
Why? Are you uncomfortable here?
I have work at the brewery,
and my mom and my brothers-in-law
are back home.
I'm eager to hurry back.
Still, having you around
made it less boring,
and I actually had fun.
The rest of "The Celestial Drops"
from Volume 16 to the final book...
is in your hospital room.
Really?
I asked Mr. Park...
to get them from a bookstore.
No way!
Let's head inside
and finish them off together.
Together?
What was that?
It was nothing.
Come on.
Chairman Han.
Hello, Ms. Jang.
What brings you here?
I heard you were in the hospital...
and rushed over
because I was worried.
I'll leave you
with your guest, then.
Right.
Who may she be?
She's one of our suppliers.
I just happened to run into her
at the hospital.
I see.
Let's head inside.
Sure.
I didn't come
just to see how you were.
I'm actually here...
to discuss a certain matter
with you.
I see. What is it about?
I wanted to speed things up
with our kids' wedding plans.
How does that sound?
If that's what they both want,
I have no reason to object.
How about the first week
of September?
Do we have enough time?
It's only a few months away.
With enough money,
we could even pull it off next week.
Sorry?
What I meant was
that there wouldn't be a problem.
I see.
Gyeol and Se Ri...
have been apart for too long.
They seem to want to be together.
We should let them love each other
with all their hearts.
One, two, three.
What do you think?
No way.
It could use a makeover.
Come on.
Welcome back to civilian life,
my friend.
Thanks, my friend.
How does it feel
to be a civilian again?
It's good, I guess.
That reminds me.
You should look around...
and greet the staff.
Can you introduce me to them?
- Why don't we get going?
- Sure.
(Traditional Rice Porridge)
Who's there?
Hello.
Right.
You were with Professor Oh
when he picked Ha Ni up.
That's right.
Hi, Ha Ni.
Did you have fun with Granny?
I think he's home.
He's fast asleep,
so he didn't hear the doorbell.
I see.
But I have dinner plans.
What do I do?
Let me take Ha Ni, then.
I'll watch her
until Professor Oh wakes up.
Would you do that?
I feel like
I'm always troubling you.
Not at all.
(Traditional Rice Porridge)
I'll take Ha Ni.
You can come to me.
There you go.
She just had her bottle.
Sure.
Ha Ni.
Say bye to Granny.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Take care.
Bye.
Goodness.
Ha Ni, while I clean up,
play with this toy. Okay?
Hi.
Aren't you sweet?
Se Ri's gone.
Peekaboo. Here I am.
I'm right here.
Glide.
And slide.
Hello.
I thought she was
officially starting next week.
Since it's her first time
working at a company,
she wanted to get familiar
with the place...
and meet you before her first day.
That's why we came together.
The chairman said I should treat you
just like the other employees,
so they'd feel more comfortable.
I'll drop the honorifics.
Of course.
I'd feel more at ease that way.
This is where the TF team
will be working.
One will work
in planning and marketing.
One in fabric design.
Two more interns...
including you will make up the team.
- Got it.
- Okay.
Shouldn't we visit her
in the hospital?
Working hard is
what makes our boss happy.
You don't need to worry
about visiting her.
How uncaring you are.
Her test results came back fine,
so she'll be discharged tomorrow.
You don't have to worry.
Hello?
I got the job?
Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
Did you get a job?
- Yes.
- Congratulations.
What's the name of the company?
Gwangseong Defense.
That's a defense company
that's doing really well these days.
It's been on the news a lot.
I didn't expect to get the job,
but I guess I was lucky.
It's not luck.
That's because you're competent.
You should take us out for a treat.
Of course.
Can we have beef?
Sure.
(Eagle Brewery Unrefined Makgeolli)
I'm not saying
I won't give you the money.
I just need a few more days,
but why are you forcing me?
I'm Macho Man Park Sang Nam.
I don't want to care about
trivial things like this anymore.
I will settle things
with you today...
and let go of what happened
in the past.
I understand what you mean,
but I don't have any cash
with me now.
So I'm asking you
to give me some time.
You have to return
the purse right away...
or give me 5,000 dollars in cash.
Or I'll report you
to the police for extortion...
under the pretense of marriage.
Extortion
under the pretense of marriage?
How could you say
such a harsh thing?
Let me be honest with you.
If I hadn't had the intention
of marrying Kwang Sook,
would I have given you
a designer bag worth 5,000 dollars?
This is ridiculous.
How can you be so cheap
just because of 5,000 dollars?
If you think I'm cheap,
just give me 5,000 dollars.
The money you want!
I'll give you.
Mr. Go.
I'll give you the money.
So get out of my sight immediately.
Your account number!
Tell me.
It's 482-439-021972.
Hansu Bank, Park Sang Nam.
Slow down.
- Four, eight, two.
- Four, three, nine.
- All right.
- Zero, two,
- Yes.
- one, nine, seven, two.
- Seven, two.
Hansu Bank, Park Sang Nam.
Sang Nam.
Done.
Check it.
It's in my car.
Go.
Get lost.
Yes, sir.
- I just met Chairman Han.
- Okay.
We agreed to hold a wedding
in September.
Did Chairman Han agree to do that?
He said he'd do that
if our children were okay with it.
My goodness.
The chairman of LX Hotel
is going to be my in-law.
Dokgo Tak! How successful you are!
And who made it happen?
It's all thanks to you.
I'm glad that you know that.
Thank you.
My gosh.
I, who suffered...
all kinds of humiliation
at Eagle Brewery,
am now marrying my daughter off
to the son of LX Hotel.
How unbelievable.
That petty old man
of Eagle Brewery would want...
to open the lid of his coffin
and come out.
He only treated you harshly...
because you played cheap tricks
and ruined the makgeolli.
He was actually
a kind and generous man.
You're fine
until Eagle Brewery comes up,
and then you always end up
saying something mean.
But then again,
you went through a lot too...
working at the brewery
and raising their youngest child...
instead of the boss's wife.
Come to think of it,
you weren't even married,
but they let you
take care of the newborn baby.
That's horrible.
They were being too harsh on you.
Professor.
What are you doing here, Se Ri?
Well... I need to get your signature
on the budget application form...
for the industry-academic
cooperation project.
I mean, how did you get in here?
Well...
I ran into the babysitter
at the front door,
so she let me in.
Then you should've
woken me up first.
I thought
you were fast asleep, so...
Still, you should've woken me up.
I'm sorry.
This is my private space.
And you and I are
working together at school.
That means...
you can't just come into my place
like this.
I don't want this to happen again.
Where's the document?
Okay. Please wait.
Here.
Did you...
Yes?
Did you clean this place?
Well... Yes.
I thought the vacuum would wake you,
so I just tidied up a bit.
What is the matter with you?
- Pardon?
- You just barged into my place...
and touched my stuff
without my permission.
Were you really this rude?
It's not like that. I just...
I want you to leave.
I'm sorry. I'll get going then.
I came
because I was worried about you.
What?
Actually, getting your signature
was just an excuse.
You seemed very sick,
so I was worried about you.
I appreciate your concern,
- but it's still...
- You know what?
I can't help but worry about you.
I'm worried
that you're having a hard time...
working and raising your child
at the same time.
And I'm worried
about how hard it will be for you...
to raise Ha Ni without her mom.
I'm also worried...
about how hard it will be for you...
when Ha Ni's mom gets married
this Saturday.
How do you know about that?
I heard.
Heard what?
When she came...
to your office the other day,
I spilled coffee on the floor,
so I was under the desk
wiping it up.
Why would you bring up something
I've never even told you about?
What does it have to do with you?
I don't know
why I'm being like this.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Ha Ni. You're up.
All right. It's okay.
It's all right.
Mr. Rooftop House.
Yes?
I forgot that I had received this.
Thank you.
Bye.
(Kim Seon Ah, Angel Piano, 273-2,
Hwageum-ro, Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul)
Seon Ah?
What is this?
Thank you.
I'm sorry about everything.
(I'm sorry about everything.)
"I'm sorry about everything?"
Come in.
You're done already?
You're not done yet?
My eyes hurt.
Why are you laughing?
You read comic books
like you're studying for an exam.
Well, I tend to concentrate...
when I'm doing something.
Hand me the books when you're done.
I don't play.
My mom brought them
to read fortunes with...
if she got bored
while looking after me.
I watched
my maternal grandmother play...
when I was a child.
You play Go-Stop too?
I know the basic rules. That's all.
Shall we play a game?
No, thanks.
Come on. My eyes are sore.
Let's stop reading comics
and play cards instead.
I'll play nice and coach you.
I'm not good at it.
I won't play too hard.
Let's play...
just three games.
Okay, then.
Deal. I'll set it out.
One Joker equals a Double Pi.
You'll know that official rule.
There's Ddadak and Jjok,
and the first Bbeok gets you one Pi.
Pibak and Gwangbak are in play too.
You get both and if I win,
my points quadruple.
You can shake just once per game,
but bombs are an exception.
Wait. In my neighborhood,
if you collect all three Jokers,
you get five points
just like Godori.
So, are you in?
CEO Ma.
Are you a card shark?
I'm not that good at it.
I played with my mom
when we were bored.
How much per point?
I don't gamble.
We must wager something
to keep us competitive.
Shall we smack our wrists?
Or flick our forehead?
A wrist smack.
Deal.
Hey.
(Joker!)
(Joker times 2)
Gosh.
Hey.
What's this?
What's going on?
I'll put them like this.
It's Godori.
(Bbeok)
Shoot. I lost them all.
You had that card too?
If I put this here,
it's Pibak for you,
and it's my third Go.
Smack my wrist already.
We must play again.
I won't let you off lightly.
I'm known for my painful smacks.
Shuffle the deck.
Okay.
Oh, dear.
Godori.
I feel bad that I keep winning.
There's no time to waste. Be quick.
Shuffle the deck.
Shoot.
Do you play online every day?
I do not.
Hi, Mom.
What are you doing?
I'm busy right now.
Why are you busy?
I'm busy. Talk to you later.
Darn it.
Hello?
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
I'm handling something urgent...
and can't talk now.
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
What?
Let's talk tomorrow.
Pibak.
Gwangbak.
Are you a card shark?
My gosh.
Welcome.
Hi.
Is something wrong?
Of course not.
Everything's fine.
You were crying.
Today...
I settled my divorce.
The lawsuit's over.
Good for you.
Considering what the fool did,
I'm wondering
if I gave in too easily.
But I was becoming too miserable.
I felt a bit dispirited...
and couldn't help but cry...
when you came in.
When will the part-timer come?
Let's go for a walk
when you get off work.
The cherry blossoms are pretty.
I used to wash, bleach, and iron...
my husband's shirts...
so he could go to work.
And I bought seasonal vegetables...
to cook for him daily.
I had plans to invest...
the money he brought home...
and gradually expand our home.
That's how I thought I'd live.
I dreamed of building
a red clay house...
in the countryside,
growing vegetables in the garden...
for us to eat,
and growing old there together.
Mi Sun.
Let's not give up too soon.
What?
We're still young.
Divorce doesn't mean
our lives are over.
You're right. Divorce isn't the end.
Let's cheer up.
Yes.
Congratulations...
on your new beginning.
- Gosh.
Goodness.
My word.
I came
because I was worried about you.
I'll be there with a bottle.
Just a second.
You know what?
I can't help but worry about you.
(Hankuk University Hospital)
Have you really not done this
since you last played...
with your grandmother as a kid?
I got lucky, that's all.
I highly doubt that.
All right, then.
Thank you for the game.
No, wait!
One more round.
Forget it.
I feel too bad to play anymore.
Says the man
who's been smacking me nonstop.
Just one more round.
Are you sure about this?
Go even if you don't win any points.
Ma Kwang Sook does not look back.
One round. That's it.
Instead of smacking each other
on the wrist,
the loser will grant
the winner a wish.
A wish?
What kind of wish?
I'm not sure. But whoever wins...
can think about that later on.
Deal. Now, shuffle and deal.
Go on.
All right.
Did my opponent wander off?
Wait.
That's not what I meant to play.
Let me take it back.
Stop.
No take-backs. Don't you know that?
I got confused
and played the wrong card.
Let it slide this once.
No way.
This is what you get.
Darn.
There.
(Bbeok)
It's a triple stack!
Game over.
No way.
Are you kidding me?
Put down your promise in writing.
In writing?
We agreed that the loser
would grant the winner's wish.
Have you been fooled all your life?
My word is my brand.
I wouldn't go back on my promise.
I don't trust what people say.
I only trust what's in writing.
You'll write it yourself
and hand it to me.
Here.
Have you been fooled all your life?
Fine.
I don't see a piece of paper.
Wait.
You can write it on your wristband.
It even has your name on it already.
Is this really necessary?
I prefer certainty.
What should I write?
Write
"Wish Fulfillment Agreement"...
and sign it.
Wish Fulfillment...
Agreement.
Ma Kwang Sook.
Happy now?
Okay.
Get that to me
once you're discharged tomorrow.
I'll get going.
He's so persistent.
I don't get it.
How could I have been so unlucky
with my draws?
Seriously. Like this. There you go.
Why was that so hard?
(Eagle Brewery)
You might still feel dizzy
after discharge,
so avoid strenuous activities
for the time being...
and get as much rest as you can.
Be sure to take the painkillers
I'll prescribe...
and don't forget to use a compress
on the injured area.
I'll keep that in mind.
Sure. Bye, then.
Kwang Sook.
Guys.
I could've taken a cab home.
You didn't have to come
when you were busy.
What are you saying?
Of course, we should pick you up.
I'll pack your things.
Thanks.
What's with all the books?
Come in.
Right.
Were you also leaving, CEO Ma?
Yes, my brothers-in-law
are here to pick me up.
It was a tough couple of days.
Here you go.
Goodness.
I almost forgot.
I'll get going, then.
Sure.
(Wish Fulfillment Agreement,
Ma Kwang Sook)
(Eagle Brewery)
Shall we, sir?
Yes, let's go.
Since my wife passed away,
those were the happiest two days
I've had.
It felt as though...
a once-shut window had opened
to let sunlight pour in.
It was an absolutely perfect,
happy vacation.
(Eagle Brewery)
Welcome home, CEO Ma.
You've had a rough couple of days.
Hardly.
I was able to rest up.
I see.
Mr. Go, I bet things were tough
for you without me here.
Chun Soo and Kang Soo
helped out a lot.
Hello. Have you been well?
What are you talking about?
Why is our brewery on the news?
It's bad!
- What is it?
- You need to watch the news.
- The news?
Yes.
What's going on?
(Eagle Brewery)
A tradition of 90 years.
A brewery kept in the family
for three generations...
that has been maintaining
its reputation...
and supplying
one of the country's top hotels.
It's renowned
for brewing its liquor...
exclusively with organic rice...
from the partnered farms...
and using nothing else
but nuruk and water.
However, we've received
a shocking tip...
about this brewery.
It looks like they use
the best ingredients,
but the rice they use
is actually stale.
Not just that,
it's riddled with insects too.
My gosh. That's not our brewery.
It is our brewery.
What does that mean?
Who would tell such a lie?
This can't be.
(For Eagle Brothers)
Yes, sir.
You're mistaken. That's not true.
I love my professor.
Shut your mouth!
Will you marry a divorced man
with a kid?
Can you spend the rest of your life
raising someone else's kid?
Why are you such a scaredy-cat?
Why are you here?
I came to stand guard.
To stand guard?
I just came back from submitting
a letter of complaint.
I stake the honor
and future of our brewery...
and promise to fight to the end
to reveal the truth.