(Eagle Brewery)
Hold on a second!
Who are you...
to paint someone innocent
as a briber?
Don't you think
you're too stuck-up about things?
My personality isn't the issue.
The issue lies with
your attitude and actions.
I'll warn you one last time.
Should anything like this
happen again,
I'll cancel the contract
with you as a supplier.
What?
I warned you loud and clear.
I'll cancel the contract.
(Eagle Brewery)
Look here.
- Step on it, will you?
- Yes, sir.
Roll down your window.
Hey, let's talk.
Hey.
Roll down your window.
But...
Hey, wait!
Seriously?
Shoot.
That man just now
is the chairman of LX Hotel?
That's what I said.
He seems to know you personally.
We crossed paths a few times,
and I got the contract with LX Hotel
because he introduced...
Jang-Kwang Makgeolli to his people.
I see.
How did he know
I was your mom though?
The second he saw me,
he said,
"I'm here to see your daughter."
We look alike,
so he probably guessed.
He's a charismatic man.
Maybe it's because
he's the chairman of a luxury hotel,
but there was a light
shining behind him.
Darn, that jerk.
- Who?
- Who else?
The chairman of LX Hotel, of course.
Why would you say he's a jerk?
He made me look like a swindler
handing out bribes.
That ticked me off!
I apologize, sir.
I'll make sure
this doesn't happen again.
Good job today.
Thank you.
Dad.
Good night.
Hello, Chairman Han.
Yes, hello.
Well,
I went to Jinhae...
to give Gyeol some side dishes...
and ran into Bom at the hospital.
You went all the way to Jinhae...
to give him side dishes?
If your wife were still alive,
she would've visited him
even in Jeju.
I should care for him now
in her place.
Right.
You should've told me...
that you were going
to see your brother.
Oh, that.
It was a spontaneous decision.
The brave marine...
who protected Bom
from her stalker...
was injured while training.
Of course, she should see
how her savior is doing.
She had a stalker?
Who?
Goodness.
Did you say
I shouldn't tell Chairman Han?
You should've told me...
if something like that happened.
Why am I hearing about this
so much later...
from someone else?
I'm sorry.
You're suffering from
insomnia as is,
and I didn't want you to lose sleep
over my matter as well.
It's still wrong.
How could I not know...
about the safety
of my only daughter?
Who was the jerk?
What kind of jerk would do
such a thing to my daughter?
He was a friend from college.
He's a bit mentally unstable
and prone to paranoia.
His family apologized
and promised to get him treated.
It's under trial now.
What if he shows up again?
The police issued
a restraining order,
so you don't have to worry.
Anyway, if anything like that
happens again,
you should tell me right away. Okay?
Yes, I will.
- Let's drink.
- Hey.
It's been a long time.
- Cheers.
- Hey.
- I'll be right back.
- Gosh, seriously.
- It's all right.
Who are you waiting for?
Well, Chun Soo.
He told me he'd come,
but is running late.
I should call him
to see where he is now.
Don't bother.
He'd be too upset
to come to a school reunion.
Why would he be?
Did you not hear that?
Chun Soo got fired.
Come on. That's no big deal.
It's nothing unusual...
- for people of our age.
- Sure.
It's not just that he got fired.
He lost all his money...
while running a business
with an acquaintance.
And now he's just broke
and living in a gosiwon.
Come on. That can't be true.
- See? I told you.
- Hey, even if he got fired...
and failed in his business,
he's still the Oh Chun Soo
with a brilliant mind.
How would he live in a gosiwon?
I also found it hard to believe.
But there's someone
who has seen it firsthand.
Then there should be
no money changing hands.
Why? Did Chun Soo try
to borrow money from you?
It's not like that.
He has never shown up
at the school reunion before.
Why would he suddenly want to come?
I bet he's coming to ask us a favor.
- Come on. That's crossing the line.
- I know.
We're meeting again
after a long time.
Let's just say good things.
All right. Let's drink.
- All right. Have a drink.
- Okay.
I guess you're upset...
because we're speaking ill
of your first love.
What?
- Stop drinking.
- What?
- Hi, guys.
- Hey. Come here.
- Hi, Chun Soo.
- It's been a long time.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Come here.
- It's been a while.
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
- Good to see you again.
- You too.
Hey, how are you?
Hey, long time no see.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
- Why are you so late?
- I'm sorry.
I was out of town,
so it took me some time.
I'm glad you made it.
All right.
The traffic was bad.
You must be hungry.
- Eat.
- Okay.
You two look good together.
Now that you two are
sitting together,
you make a cute couple.
- Aren't they a perfect match?
- My gosh.
Hey, you're drunk.
- You should stop drinking.
- Why?
When else would I get drunk
if not on a day like this?
I'm feeling great. Don't ruin it.
Let's just finish the food
and leave.
I just got here.
Are we leaving already?
I'm not feeling well.
Why? Are you sick?
- You startled me.
- It's not too late.
Mi Sun, you're
in the middle of a divorce.
- You're just talking nonsense.
- She's...
My gosh. You must be really drunk.
I'm fine. Why do you keep saying
I'm drunk?
Mi Sun's husband...
had an affair with his secretary,
so she's getting a divorce.
That's what you told me.
She's being ridiculous.
- She's the one who told me that.
- I didn't mean to tell her.
It just came up.
Mi Sun, I'm really sorry.
It's not too late. You two...
should be together.
Chun Soo, you live alone,
and your family is abroad.
Right? You told me that.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong?
- I'll call a cab.
Can you take her home?
Sure. I'll do that.
- Hey, let's go.
- Why?
- I don't want to go.
- Just come.
- She's so drunk.
- Let me be honest!
Your husband's affair would hurt you
if you were younger.
But at our age,
shouldn't you be grateful...
that he's walking away on his own?
If you're that jealous,
get divorced too.
What?
Don't be so hung up
on your cheating husband...
and just get a divorce like me.
My lawyer is good. Do you want me
to give you the number?
Hey, Mun Mi Sun.
Watch your tongue!
- Hey, you crazy brat!
- Hey. Stop it.
- Stop her!
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Stop it!
- Hey!
- Get off of her!
- Let go of it.
- Don't be like that.
- Hey! You!
- Stop it!
Hey, stop it.
Mi Sun, don't do that.
Stop it.
- Here.
- It's okay.
It's no big deal.
I don't need a relaxing pill.
Stop acting so cool
and just take it.
Let's share it.
You must be in shock now.
I'm fine.
Take this.
Go ahead.
It's not like we're schoolchildren.
I can't believe this.
It was
the elementary school reunion.
I guess we all went back in time.
I'm sorry I lied.
When I was
in the midst of a divorce lawsuit,
I pretended I was happily married.
You don't have to say that.
What she said is true.
That jerk had an affair
with his young secretary.
He even had a child
without me knowing.
I was the fool
for not noticing it for ten years.
How is it your fault?
The one who fooled you is at fault.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Can I tell you
something embarrassing too?
Actually,
there's something I didn't tell you.
I'm unemployed.
I got fired.
Why are you laughing?
The guys told me that
before you arrived.
What?
Gosh, there are no secrets
in this world.
Then we can call it even now.
Right?
Sure.
Call it even.
Oh, dear.
(Chairman Jang Je Hyeong
announces his marriage.)
Ha Ni, I'm coming.
Are you feeling better
in a fresh diaper?
I'll be right back
with your milk, okay?
All right. That's my girl.
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
To be honest,
I don't know if I can raise her.
I'm sick of the burden...
that has been laid on me!
Darn it.
I also have mine.
Don't poke your nose in my business.
What do you mean?
You say that like we're strangers.
That'd actually be better.
Darn it. Seriously...
Gosh.
Darn it.
You're old enough to know better.
The only thing you can cook
is the cup noodles?
I can cook instant noodles too.
As if there's any difference.
Can you even cook rice?
I've never tried cooking rice.
Don't I just put rice and water...
in the rice cooker and press "cook?"
My gosh. That darn woman.
Didn't she teach you anything?
I'm home.
Hi, Mom.
Good for you.
You left to take food
to someone else's son,
so your husband and daughter
are eating cup ramyeon.
How is he someone else's son?
He'll be my son-in-law soon.
Send Se Ri
to cooking class immediately.
What?
Why should I take cooking classes?
Will you serve cup ramyeon...
to your future father-in-law
and just say,
"Here's some hot water?"
Set the table!
He's so annoying.
Why should I learn how to cook?
That's why people mock him
for being lame.
Don't mind anything he says.
Why should you
take cooking classes...
when soon
you'll be managing LX Hotel?
Will you stop
talking about that hotel?
It's stressing me out.
Why is my princess
in a foul mood today?
Did something happen on campus?
Hey. Is the new professor
still tormenting you?
No. He's not like that.
He's nice.
You said
you got to supply LX Hotel...
because the chairman helped out.
And all you gave him to say thanks
was a crate of makgeolli?
Wasn't he here...
because he was offended
by the trivial gift?
Didn't you hear what he said?
He doesn't want gifts of any sort.
How could you be that naive
and take his words at face value?
He meant you shouldn't make do
with something small.
Stop talking nonsense, Mom.
Go to your room and sleep.
I have to make a delivery
at the crack of dawn.
Give and take
is the basic rule of business.
You'll never find someone
who doesn't like freebies.
You don't know anything.
How is a crate of makgeolli a bribe?
He's so weird.
Hi, Gyeol.
You're worried about Bom, right?
Sorry, Dad.
I can't do anything
about a past incident,
but from now on,
don't even dream of keeping secrets.
Discuss everything with me.
I kept it from you
so you wouldn't worry.
I shouldn't have.
One more thing.
What's your relationship with Se Ri?
What?
If there's nothing between you two,
her mother would have no reason
to bring you food.
Jinhae's not exactly close to Seoul.
I was going to tell you
after I got discharged.
Dad.
I want to marry Se Ri.
You don't object, do you?
I've known Se Ri
since she was little,
and our families are friends.
Why would I object?
Okay.
Let's discuss the details in person.
Bye.
Why do the kids...
have so many secrets?
What's wrong with the wine?
Did all that makgeolli...
change my taste buds or something?
The store at the crossroads wants...
five more boxes.
Shouldn't we hire someone
to handle the deliveries?
Why should we hire someone...
when the three of us
can take turns going out?
I want a subordinate
to boss about too.
Just you wait.
If sales go up a bit more,
I'll hire someone...
and promote you to section chief.
No, department head.
You look very pleased.
Hey.
Hello?
Hello. I'm Kim Sang Yi
with KBC Morning News.
"KBC Morning News?"
I got your number from LX Hotel.
I'd like to interview you, Ms. Ma.
You want to interview me?
I did as you told
and looked into Eagle Brewery...
in terms of their assets
and financial status.
And?
After the last CEO's sudden death,
they released a new product,
and it's a fact that they had
some financial troubles.
But I don't believe
there's anything to worry about.
As of right now,
there are no concerns?
That's right.
There is one thing, sir.
The rumor that Ms. Ma...
took a huge gamble
to take over the brewery...
against the wishes
of her brothers-in-law.
That was true.
There was disorder and strife
within the family, then.
I can't say for sure
if the strife was due to...
the brothers-in-law owning a stake,
but right now,
none of the former CEO's brothers...
have a say
in the brewery's operations.
- Good job.
- Yes, sir.
(Chairman Han Dong Seok)
What Mr. Dokgo said
doesn't seem to be entirely false.
He's been feeling discomfort
in the ears.
He had a severe case
of middle ear inflammation as a kid.
The doctor says
it could be an aftereffect of that.
If he had that problem,
he should've come to us.
He struggled with it on his own.
He should quit...
if diving could cause
loss of hearing.
I've been thinking.
Kang Soo will stay with me
when he moves back to Seoul.
Aren't you bringing your wife back
from the US?
She'll understand.
We all know what your wife's like.
Do you want to torture a sick kid?
Yes. Kang Soo can stay with me.
We shared a room as kids anyway.
Forget it.
You must be exhausted
from all the teaching and childcare.
You both can forget it.
I'm single.
Kang Soo can stay with me.
You?
Yes. He has a pretty face,
and he's fit too.
I should help him debut.
Will you be serious? That's stupid.
Why is that stupid?
I was in the entertainment industry.
I'll use all my experience...
to make Kang Soo a star.
I'll look after him.
What he wants is most important.
Let's hear what his plan is...
and meet again to discuss.
Okay.
He said he'd been thinking about it
for a while.
He must have some kind of idea.
Oh, dear.
Hello, Professor.
Hi. I heard from the TA.
I look forward to your help.
Did I pass, then?
Don't be silly.
I'll be in your debt.
What do you need my help with?
Looking up the material I need
will be your main job.
Searching for
and printing research papers,
and borrowing books
from the library.
Okay. I'm good at that.
I hope we get along.
Yes, sir.
Hello? Ms. Kim, it's me.
Welcome.
Here.
Gosh. You got me hallabong.
It's a bribe from me to you...
before my first lesson.
Come on in.
Here. Please try one.
Sure.
Sour flavors don't seem
to agree with you.
I'm afraid so.
I must look like a fool.
Actually, I find it cute.
I mean...
I know this is a boring question,
but why haven't you married
when you come from a good family...
and are a beauty yourself?
Well,
it's because I haven't met someone
who's my destiny.
What about you?
Why are you still single?
My biggest issue is
that I'm not financially stable yet.
That's ridiculous.
When you meet someone
who's your destiny,
financial problems
won't be an issue.
The one who's better off
can support the other.
Please have another.
I see you still have some left.
(Angel Piano)
Whoever it is sucks.
My gosh.
What...
Goodness.
- Not like that.
- No?
Play it with just this hand.
What are those two doing?
It's still too bright outside
to be glued to each other.
Shouldn't they move together?
- Gosh, no.
- No?
- Mr. Oh!
- What?
- I can't do it.
- Mr. Oh, come on.
Try it again.
Oh, well.
I told you before that I was taking
lessons from Ms. Kim.
This is my first lesson.
What brings you by unannounced?
I doubt you're here
for a lesson yourself.
I'm too busy to take piano lessons.
I came by to say this for sure...
before you moved
your academy elsewhere.
Let me see.
The soundproof rooms...
should be returned
to their original state.
Return the partition walls
to their original state too.
Ms. Ji,
didn't I talk to you about this?
You two are the same class members.
Please be considerate to each other.
You can't force her
to leave like this.
Stay out of it, Mr. Oh!
It's not because
Ms. Kim has nowhere to go.
She grew attached
to the kids in this neighborhood...
and doesn't want to part ways.
Mr. Oh.
I'm all right,
so please don't get worked up.
We should talk alone.
I'll say this again.
This is a business deal
between me and Ms. Kim,
so stay out of it.
Her landlord ego is
through the roof.
Darn.
I'm annoyed and stressed out as is,
but you're making me see red.
My gosh, that tone...
You sound the sweetest
in Mr. Oh's presence,
but you switched up your tone
now that we're alone.
That's why...
I warned you.
Study more before you come at me,
you callow cow.
Why you...
Who exactly are you?
How many masks do you have on?
What's it to you?
Whether I wear 10 or 100 masks
is none of your business.
I suggest you worry about
your own life instead.
- What?
- I say this loud and clear.
I won't leave this neighborhood.
Holding out won't do you any good.
We'll see...
who ends up losing more.
Why that...
Who on earth is she really?
I'll be the one...
to unmask that witch.
(Eagle Brewery)
I came up with the proposal,
but I thought
you should go over it...
before I handed it in
to their head office.
Goodness me.
Great job, Chun Soo.
Please go over the main points...
and share any good ideas you have.
I'll read it as quickly as possible.
By the way, I might be on the news.
The news?
A KBC reporter called
and asked for an interview...
about our makgeolli being supplied
to LX Hotel.
It'll be filmed
at the brewery tomorrow.
That's great.
I can't believe
Eagle Brewery will be on the news.
You're amazing.
It's all thanks to Jang Soo.
To celebrate Kang Soo's discharge
from the hospital...
and my appearance on the news,
let's all go to Jinhae...
and party.
What is it?
Is something up?
Once Kang Soo gets discharged,
we'll have to bring him to Seoul.
Why?
It seems
he'll have to leave the service.
But I heard
he was recovering just fine.
Did his case worsen?
As a kid, he had a severe case
of middle ear inflammation.
Constant deep-water training
in the Marines...
led to an ear disorder.
But Kang Soo never said anything.
Things are already hectic for you
with the brewery.
He probably didn't want
to worry you.
Is it serious?
The doctor said...
he could lose his hearing
if he continues diving deep.
So following this injury,
he won't extend his enlistment...
and will choose to be discharged.
That poor thing.
Welcome.
Hey, you're here.
I just dropped by
after visiting my sister-in-law.
Did you get to rest well last night?
The embarrassment kept me up.
What?
I was embarrassed
for making a fool of myself.
Didn't we agree
to call it even last night?
I slept like a baby
thinking that was our agreement.
- Coffee for a hangover cure?
- Sounds good.
Catch.
How's the lawsuit going?
I was told
not to save money on lawyers,
so I hired one
with a good reputation.
I'm getting what I paid for.
I might become rich
once I receive the alimony.
Right.
Time will solve it for you,
so don't stress yourself out.
That I should.
By the way,
would you like to take these?
What are they?
They just passed
the expiration date and...
(Waste)
I always take them home too.
Don't if it feels iffy.
Why would I think that?
I'd actually be grateful.
They just passed
the expiration date?
Yes.
These look delicious.
Don't skip meals
just because you live alone...
and make sure to eat well.
Those are enough.
I'm going to the US in a few days.
Is that so?
Your family will be so happy.
Right.
I think I'll have my daughter
go to a boarding school...
and come back with my wife.
Goodness.
You're finally done
being a husband who lives alone.
Congratulations.
- Thanks.
- Right.
Eat well until you leave,
- and have a safe trip.
- Thanks.
I'll probably see you
when you get back.
I guess.
Be well until I get back.
What's the occasion?
I didn't expect...
a scrooge like you
to take us out to a top-class hotel.
You were on my case
about only asking you for food,
so I'm treating you
to get on your good side.
Why? We can leave
if you're not satisfied.
Why wouldn't I be satisfied?
I love it, of course.
This hotel will soon be Se Ri's.
Mom, please.
Someone will hear you.
Please don't say things like that.
So what if people hear me?
You'll soon be the daughter-in-law
of the hotel's chairman.
I couldn't care less
about the hotel.
When will you grow up?
Teach her how to be a good wife,
will you?
Why should I do that...
when the hotel has a restaurant,
a laundry service,
and cleaners?
There's nothing that isn't here.
Se Ri.
You will live...
without getting a drop of water
on your hands.
It's enough for me
to have a hard time...
doing household chores.
Okay?
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
You came with all your family today.
Yes. We're dining out together
in a while.
I'm glad you're here.
Maybe it's because
it's been a while,
but you look even prettier.
Pardon?
Thank you.
You should visit my place sometime.
I hope to see you more often.
Yes, I will.
Chairman Piccoli has arrived.
Please excuse me.
I have an appointment.
He'd give us the cold shoulder.
What's gotten into him?
He came over to talk to us?
I guess
he heard something from Gyeol.
I bet that's what it is.
My goodness.
I'll take your recommendation
for a drink.
A Korean liquor, please.
Shall we start with a drink...
that our hotel has just launched...
with our makgeolli,
Jang-Kwang Makgeolli.
Jang-Kwang Makgeolli? A new drink?
I'm looking forward to it.
Get him Jang-Kwang Makgeolli.
- Please enjoy it.
- Thank you.
My gosh. Hey.
(Gyeol)
What are you doing?
Hurry and answer the phone.
Hi, Gyeol.
I'm having dinner
with Mom and Dad at LX Hotel.
What?
Hang on.
He wants to talk to you, Dad.
Me?
Hi. It's been a while.
Yes. I'm always healthy.
Actually, I just met your dad
and talked to him.
All right. After you finish
your military service next month,
we should work out
together sometime. Okay.
Take good care of your health.
All right.
Gyeol.
Yes. Enjoy your dinner.
Bye.
Chairman Han taught him well
at home.
He's polite and respectful
to his elders.
That's why I have my eye on him
as a potential son-in-law.
I chose him.
You do have an eye for men.
(Jang-Kwang Makgeolli)
Are you done?
I just lost my appetite.
Why?
I made myself clear
so that he could understand.
What on earth is he thinking?
What do you mean?
Just finish your food
so that we can leave.
- Do you want me to go first?
- No.
- Let's hurry and eat.
- Okay. We will hurry.
I'm home.
Thank you for your hard work,
CEO Ma.
What are you doing still up?
People from the broadcasting station
are coming tomorrow.
It's not like you're the one
being interviewed.
I'm the CEO's mom,
so I should look nice.
By the way, Mom,
isn't this house too big
for just the two of us?
We have many extra rooms
we don't use.
Do you want your old mom
to run a boarding house or what?
That's not what I'm saying.
When I'm at work,
you must be bored alone
at home all day.
It would be nice
if you had someone...
to keep you company.
Right?
I'm glad you brought it up.
You have to be successful...
and send me back to Golden Castle.
As I told you last time,
the news about our hotel's service
of traditional liquor...
will be
on the KBC morning news tomorrow.
I had an interview yesterday.
And today, CEO Ma Kwang Sook...
of Eagle Brewery
is having an interview.
We're on the news as a first mover?
That's a lot of pressure.
About the CEO of the brewery...
I hope she won't say anything stupid
out of the blue.
In particular, with balanced acidity
and rich bubbles,
we aim for a sophisticated
and refreshing aftertaste.
I think that's why...
LX Hotel chose our liquor.
Our CEO has such a way with words.
It's not just that
she's a good speaker.
She takes after me,
so she has a small face,
which makes her
look better on screen.
You are taking your first step...
with the first makgeolli
at a luxury hotel.
I wonder what your future plans are.
This isn't just about the taste
of the liquor.
We will continue to collaborate
with LX Hotel...
to make the best liquor...
and offer our customers
emotional satisfaction...
through good design and packaging.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you for your hard work.
- Thank you.
You didn't seem nervous at all.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
The interview will be
on tomorrow's morning news.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I was so nervous.
I'm not sure
if I did well as I practiced.
I think you're gifted
in broadcasting.
You did a lot better
than when you practiced.
I can't believe
my daughter will be on the news.
It's such an honor
to our family, CEO Ma.
Welcome.
Hey. Did your mom
allow you to get a perm?
Yes.
That's great. Congratulations.
I told her to go to a hair salon
in the neighborhood,
but she insisted on coming here.
I want to look just like you.
I love your hairstyle.
Okay. I'll make you
look the same as me.
Have a seat here.
Would you like some tea?
I'm fine. Where's the restroom?
Is your name Eun Seo?
Yes.
What grade are you in?
I'm in fifth grade.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I got dumped a few days ago.
So I'm getting a perm
to make myself feel better.
My gosh. Why did you get dumped...
when you were so pretty and lovely?
He says I'm not his type.
He likes a girl
who is smart and a model student.
Does your mom know
that you got dumped?
My mom isn't interested in me.
Come on. That can't be true.
I'm sure she's just busy with work.
I can't even call her Mom
when people are around.
What? What do you mean?
Anyway, my mom likes the piano
more than she likes me.
I see. Does your mom play the piano?
She's a piano instructor.
Is your mom a schoolteacher?
Close enough.
Eun Seo, stop talking to her.
You don't want to bother her
at work.
(Oh Beom Soo, Out of Office)
Isn't he here yet?
Hello.
(Professor's Office)
Beom Soo.
It's been a while.
Jong Tae told me
that you were teaching here.
What brings you here?
You didn't even call me.
If I had called you,
you wouldn't have wanted to see me.
Hey, it's Ha Ni.
She's adorable.
Is this his older brother?
Oh, no. What the heck?
Silly me.
I have a lecture.
You have three minutes.
Did you see the news?
It's the hottest topic right now.
I wanted to tell you
before it got out.
I just didn't have...
the courage.
I didn't cheat on you.
I wanted to tell you that myself.
You didn't have to bother.
Our families are friends.
I've known him since we were young.
We met in the US a few times
when I interpreted for him.
We met again over here
to discuss family matters,
and it led to this.
Believe me.
What changes if I believe you?
I don't want...
Ha Ni to be ashamed of me.
You did the shameful stuff already.
Why are you doing this now?
Has she grown a lot?
My darling baby.
Is she doing well?
- Where is she?
- Why do you want to know?
This isn't easy to say,
but the chairman knows my situation.
He said I can bring Ha Ni.
His children are grown...
Don't be ridiculous!
I was just asking
about your circumstances.
It's not easy
for a man to raise a baby alone.
There'll be a lot to do...
The moment
you packed your stuff and left,
I told you clearly...
that it would be over
if you walked out the door.
You chased money and happiness.
I won't criticize you for that,
but...
don't you dare mention Ha Ni again.
She's my daughter
and has nothing to do with you.
- Beom Soo.
- Don't say my name.
Why are you being so cold?
Na Young Eun.
Ha Ni's the one thing I have left.
How can I be nice to the person
who wants to take her from me?
I'll raise her just fine
without a mom.
Focus and care about yourself.
As you always did.
I'm not trying to take her from you.
You and Ha Ni
have always been a part of me.
It's almost time for my lecture.
I need you to leave.
I'll ask you one last thing.
Why did you come back?
You wanted to settle in the US.
You left without even turning back.
Why do you want to know that now?
Are you sure you didn't come back
to Korea for me?
So we could start over?
Quit the nonsense and get out.
If I ask for forgiveness,
can you take me back?
I'm barely able to think of you
without hating you.
Don't make me hate you again.
Now leave.
What did I just see?
The weak point of economics...
is that it hasn't focused much
on studying the human mind...
beyond numbers.
When facing a crisis,
the human mind...
does not act rationally.
It can be quite fickle.
Each time, the economy moved
in a direction different from...
what numbers-based studies suggested
and in a drastic manner,
causing another crisis.
Let's go back to the slides.
"If economics
fails to read the human mind,"
"policies could be
set up to be inefficient."
Who'd have imagined
that our professor...
kept that kind of secret?
Reducing taxes...
or handing out more subsidies...
won't be enough to do
what humans want.
I feel so sorry for him.
Here's another example.
(Angel Piano)
Hey. It's the kid from earlier.
My mom isn't interested in me.
Come on. That can't be true.
I can't even call her Mom
when people are around.
What? What do you mean?
I...
Anyway, my mom likes the piano
more than she likes me.
Wait.
That little girl is...
I got it.
Hang on.
I need to catch her red-handed.
(Start with the basics,
Beyer for Children)
Oh, my darling, Ms. Kim
(Dancing Prince)
Why is this woman calling again?
Hello?
Spare me some time.
I have something to tell you.
What's it about?
I'll tell you in person.
We meet for class tomorrow.
After Zumba class...
It'll be too late then.
Right now.
Right now?
Over here, Mr. Oh.
Why did you suddenly want to see me?
Try not to get the wrong idea.
I will...
reveal the truth pretty soon,
but I'm giving you a heads-up
so you don't get hurt.
Ms. Kim.
She's fishy.
You need to be careful.
If she asks you for a loan,
you must never lend her any money.
- And...
- Will you stop it?
Stop what?
Stop badmouthing Ms. Kim.
I can't stand it.
I'm not badmouthing her.
I'm sharing a fact.
Ms. Kim never says anything bad
about you.
Why are you...
so insistent on slandering her?
Ms. Kim...
isn't the person you think she is.
Why don't you see that?
When it comes to women,
there's more than what you see.
Some women don't put makeup
on just their faces.
They put makeup on their hearts too.
Ms. Kim's like that,
and you should see it.
I have...
feelings for her.
So don't badmouth...
the woman I like
in my presence anymore.
It's hard to put up with.
When I asked you last time,
you said you weren't flirting
or anything.
I didn't know how I felt back then.
But I do now.
Ms. Kim and I have a thing going on.
You can't!
I won't accept it.
What right do you have
to accept it or not?
Stay out of my personal life
from now on.
I'm not meddling
in your personal life.
I'm trying to save you
from being deceived...
by a fake and suspicious woman
like Ms. Kim.
I'm doing this out of concern.
I don't want to hear any more
of this.
I'll request this one last time.
Stay out of my relationship...
with Ms. Kim.
You can't leave like this.
Please hear me out.
Darn it. I need to move faster.
This is serious.
(Eagle Brewery)
Eating in this big house...
with just you by my side...
leaves me with no appetite.
For a pleasant dinner,
there should be more people
at the table.
Right?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You've been constantly saying...
how lonely you are,
and I find that suspicious.
I bet you're seeing someone!
What nonsense are you talking about?
Why would I be seeing someone?
As if you have to ask.
You should remarry
while you're still young.
Not that again. Stop it with that.
Don't you think it'd be nice...
to have a handsome and sweet son?
A son-in-law is the same as a son.
Forget I said anything.
(Chun Soo)
Hey, Chun Soo.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine except
that I can't use my left arm.
Don't worry.
I'll be heading to you
with Heung Soo and Beom Soo.
As if you need to say that.
That's the least we can do...
when our baby brother
is leaving the service.
Of course, we should comfort...
We should be there
to congratulate you.
Sure. I'll see you tomorrow.
(Eagle Brewery)
Come on, guys.
The news just came on.
- Already?
- The news?
Go on and hit record.
- Hurry.
Vertical farming...
that isn't affected by the elements
is garnering attention.
I'm busy with today's deliveries.
When will it be on?
Just give it a minute.
It'll be on as soon as
they're done with the headlines.
I can't believe
my daughter will be on the news.
What a great honor in the family.
Anyway, the chairman of LX Hotel
is our savior.
How could we ever repay him?
One should speak the truth
even with a crooked mouth.
It's our late boss
who paved the way.
He's the reason my daughter
is working her butt off as a widow.
I thought you said
this was an honor in the family.
Stop it, Mom.
According to the National Institute
of Fisheries Science,
what was discovered
along the eastern coast...
- We deliver this week's trend.
- Come in.
This is Weekly Trend.
- Did you sleep well?
- Good morning.
Did you manage to get some sleep
last night?
Somewhat. Did you sleep well?
Of course, I did.
Are you watching TV first thing
in the morning?
Is there something important
you're trying to catch?
Yes, here it is.
That is not the same
for the traditional liquor market.
The transformation of makgeolli.
Here is Reporter Kim Sang Yi.
A top-class hotel restaurant
in Seoul.
Makgeolli has been listed
on the menu.
It's the first time since the hotel
opened its doors in 1978.
With more and more guests
taking a liking to Korean culture,
they have been asking
for traditional liquor.
That is how we came
to serve makgeolli.
The makgeolli served
at this hotel...
retails for over ten dollars
per bottle.
A premium strategy that emphasizes
craftsmanship has proven successful.
We do not compromise and stick to
the traditional way of brewing.
Makgeolli is an honest liquor.
Rice harvested from healthy land,
clear water, and our special nuruk.
We bring out the best flavors
with those three ingredients.
That's what defines our makgeolli.
Finding a new way to bring back
our traditional liquor...
is also something to note.
I'm impressed.
I didn't know
makgeolli was served at our hotel.
I should try it.
It's not bad.
Actually, it's quite good.
The CEO of the brewery is a beauty.
She has a way with words too.
Shouldn't an aspiring artist
like yourself have better taste?
Sorry?
As if anyone would say
she's a beauty.
But she's beautiful.
Your mother is someone
you'd call a beauty.
She's nothing
compared to your mother.
Why is he getting worked up
over something trivial?
(Crafted with natural bedrock water
and traditional nuruk)
(Eagle Brewery Unrefined Makgeolli)
Where are you going?
My friends at Golden Castle
saw the news...
and are taking me out to lunch
to congratulate me.
My gosh.
They say everyone
has some sort of special talent,
and you made it on the news.
I'm proud of you.
You should pay for the coffee.
Compliments lead to
even nicer things.
Thanks, CEO Ma.
I'm sorry, Mom.
What are you saying that
out of the blue?
I'm sorry about everything.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Is something up?
Why won't you answer me?
Are you going to do something
behind my back?
Of course not.
Are you off to make a delivery?
Yes, and after that...
I'm heading outside the city.
Where?
To meet with a partner company.
Victory!
Victory.
Company executive officer
of the 21st Navy SEAL team,
Lieutenant Oh Kang Soo,
will be discharged from service...
as of March 21, 2025,
and join the reserve forces.
I hereby report.
Victory.
- At ease.
You served your country well.
We wish to keep serving with you,
but we only approved your discharge
considering your physical health.
With the diligence and leadership
you demonstrated in the Marines,
continue to bring honor to the UDT
even as a civilian.
I wish you well.
That is all.
I will keep that in mind.
Victory!
Victory.
(For the country and our people)
(The country, the spirit
of the people, and the sea)
(Nothing is impossible, UDT)
- Victory.
(Brave heart, unwavering mind)
Lieutenant Oh Kang Soo,
I hereby report
that I was released from service.
Victory!
- Victory.
I'm proud of you, baby brother.
- I'll take that.
- Sure.
Kang Soo.
You did great.
You're done with the hardship
and will now welcome happiness.
I have grand plans for you,
so don't worry about anything. Okay?
Have you eaten?
Yes, I ate with the members
of my unit.
Come to Seoul with us.
(Eagle Brewery)
What's this?
Am I the odd one out?
No.
We thought you'd be busy
with the brewery.
We agreed
that I'd be your big sister.
- Don't do this.
- Sorry.
We were going to come
straight to you.
Lieutenant Oh Kang Soo.
I hereby report that
I've been discharged from service.
Victory!
Victory.
Lieutenant Oh Kang Soo.
You are to get into
your sister-in-law's truck.
Get to it.
What?
Lieutenant Oh Kang Soo
will return...
to Eagle Brewery
with his sister-in-law.
Do you understand?
(Return to Eagle Brewery)
- What?
(For Eagle Brothers)
Did her mother agree to this?
There's no way she'd agree to it.
Let it go just this once.
I promise to do
as you say from now on.
What's the occasion?
Incheon International Airport?
Why is that woman
taking over the brewery?
You gave the brewery to a woman...
he was married to for just ten days?
My mom did something terrible.
Something terrible?
What is this?
It's for you.
For me?