[Love Class 2]
I'm sorry.
No, no, it's okay.
He's my friend, so it's my fault.
I'm sorry.
No.
I've learned a lot from this.
What?
I'll just
go home and rest.
I'll be splitting my shifts with the other part-timers for a while.
It's also comfortable for me to stay at home
Nobody was available this afternoon, so I asked my friends to come and help out.
I'm making you look like a good basketball player.
Let's go.
Did you see that?
What? I didn't see it.
Do it again. I didn't get it on camera.
Keep your camera on the ball.
Failed.
What was Hyeon doing?
He was drawing.
I filmed him because I thought his eyes were striking.
What was he drawing?
Me...
Good work on your assignments.
Is it bringing you and your partner closer?
Yes.
I hope it was a new experience to watch someone
being absorbed in something they enjoy.
Here's your next assignment.
Your next assignment is to meet with your partner's friends.
Meet and talk to the people who have shared
your partner's history.
Write about the things you saw, heard, and felt in an essay.
Oh...
Think of it as a journal.
Wow.
What?
Did you like my eyes?
I said "striking."
It's the same thing.
When should we do the assignment?
I'll gather my friends.
When are you free?
I'm not doing this assignment.
Why not?
Why?
No reason.
My friends want to see you.
I said I'm not doing it.
I don't have any friends suitable for this assignment.
I'm sorry.
Maybe not very close ones,
but you still have friends, right?
I really don't.
I saw a friend of yours the other day.
What?
Nothing.
Whom?
I don't know his name. It was brief.
Where?
On campus.
What did he say to you?
Well...
What does he look like?
Just normal.
Don't talk to strangers.
I'm not a child.
Got it?
Yes.
Let's eat together.
I'm hungry.
I'm really hungry.
I think we should go.
Rooftop, rooftop.
He's Kim An, the rooftop guy.
That's him.
Rooftop.
I lost my appetite.
Do you still not eat cucumbers?
They don't taste good.
Do you still remember that?
Wow.
You haven't forgotten a single thing about me.
Be honest.
Did you think about me a lot when you couldn't see me?
Shut up and eat.
I thought about you all the time at first,
and it slowly stopped.
But I thought of you once in a while.
When that happened...
When that happened,
it lasted long.
It lasted really long.
What's that face?
Are you touched?
You look touched.
Are you touched by my profound love?
Be quiet.
But I didn't feel sad
because I knew I would see you again one day.
Who are they?
The manager's friends.
Where is the manager?
He's taking a break.
- What's wrong?
- I got something in my eye.
Did you get something in your eye?
Let me see.
They must be best friends.
Yes.
I should go.
See you at home.
- Okay.
- Thanks for the drink.
Hello, Professor.
Yes, I set up your computer.
You should have everything you need.
Oh, the chair?
The screw at the bottom...
No, I'll come in early tomorrow and fix it.
Yes.
Okay, Professor, goodbye.
Are you even fixing his chairs now?
You're spoiling him.
Who caught a cockroach for him?
Oh, that was me.
But I have my limits. You don't.
- I do.
- I doubt it.
He calls you because you do everything for him.
Stop acting nice.
It will just make you get old.
I already feel old.
- Exactly.
- What?
Did you just say "exactly"?
You should learn the art of flattery.
Oh, my mouth told the truth again.
Hey, I think I'll get going.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, listen...
What we did yesterday—
"We"?
You screwed me over and ran.
- No, that's not what I mean.
- I bet you had a blast.
Don't you dare light that cigarette.
Don't you dare throw me in the gutter.
Look.
That's not what I'm doing.
I know we were a bit drunk, but it's not like we didn't agree...
- I know. I had fun, too.
- So did I.
But why did you run away?
You left me in that cold motel room.
It wasn't cold. The heating was on.
And it wasn't just a motel room, I booked the premium suite.
Is it okay then to wake up alone in a warm premium suite?
I called you, wondering if you went out for just a second,
but your phone was turned off.
Do you think that was okay?
No...
I mean...
I'm sorry.
I didn't know you would think that way.
What did you think I would think?
Are you really sorry?
Really?
Yes.
Then prove it to me...
with your body.
Hello?
Where are you?
Min Wu, I can't hear you. What did you say?
Never mind.
I'll be home later. Don't stay up waiting for me.
Okay, come home safely.
I did it without thinking.
You didn't even have the basics.
That's harsh.
I know because I tutored you.
You didn't know everything about me.
I believe I knew everything grade-wise.
You barely know me.
You'll be surprised.
I doubt it.
By the way, where are you going?
Wherever you're going.
Did you just follow me here?
Yes, why not?
Behind this tunnel is where I live.
Oh, really?
Did you bring me to your place?
You were following me, but I didn't have anywhere else to go.
I'll walk you home every day.
That's not why I brought you here.
I can do it.
The lights went out.
It happens sometimes.
Do you have work gloves?
Work gloves?
I'm going to fix them.
You'll get an electric shock.
Are you worried about me?
Hyeong.
Stop.
What?
Don't come closer.
♫ Would you please show me only good things? ♫
♫ Whenever, forever, breathe beneath me ♫
No.
♫ I want to go up with you to the highest point ♫
♫ Into a world just for you ♫
Let's go.
I came all this way, can I at least get a glass of water?
Just go.
Go inside first.
I'll leave once you get in.
I'll go inside once you leave.
No, you go in first.
Fine.
See you.
Come in.
You didn't change the lock combination.
Were you waiting for me?
What are you doing?
Come on.
Where's my welcome?
Get out.
I have nowhere to go.
You shouldn't be here, Hyeong.
Why not?
You know why.
Where else can we go if not to each other?
You know that.
You're still awake.
This is a rare sight, Oh Min Wu drinking?
Is everything okay?
Hey.
If you can drink this well, why don't you drink with us?
It's always me who gets drunk.
I just...
I'm worried I'll say things when I'm drunk.
Do you have big secrets?
Like the PIN for the bank account with your family's fortune?
You don't need to know.
Sure.
We know too much about each other.
I kind of want to clean everything up,
but it's too late, isn't it?
Hey.
For now, let's go to bed together and leave that for tomorrow.
Sure.
If friends sleep together and stuff,
I can do that, too.
Let's sleep together.
You go ahead.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey.
My hair is still wet.
Can I just dry my hair?
What's going on?
You're acting weird.
Are you okay?
You were acting strange like this last time too.
When?
When I got drunk.
Didn't you pull a prank on me that time?
Like how?
I don't know, it was just a silly prank.
You never do anything silly.
But you were acting weird that day.
I think I need some fresh air.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Where are you going? I'll come with you.
No, it's okay.
You're drunk.
No, I'm sober.
Go to sleep.
I told you to stay on the app.
Why did you have to pick the teaching assistant and take the hard way?
Why are you having a go at me? It was your choice.
Aigoo, all right, all right.
Stop whining and come up with a plan.
Although I'm not sure your plan will work.
I think you've already messed it up.
All right, I'm going to hang up.
It's an emergency.
Something important is about to happen.
I'll pay back the debt.
What debt?
I have some money saved up, so I'll bring it to you tomorrow.
What are you talking about?
Do you think I'm here for money?
Then why are you here?
Because I can't live without you.
And I know you can't live without me.
We finished talking about this on the rooftop two years ago.
It never ends when you're family.
You're my family,
and I'm your family.
Nothing is over for us, ever.
Where are you going?
I have other places to stay.
Are you going to Hyeon?
He knows everything.
Knows what?
You know.
Everything.
Hyeong?
Huh? You're still here.
Yes, I was waiting for you to turn off the lights.
What?
I could have stayed up all night.
Then I would have been here all night.
Stop being so reckless.
Did you come back out to scold me?
Where are you going?
Can I sleep over at your place?
[Love Class 2]
I should go.
It's late.
♫ That moment when you, whom I have been waiting for, ♫
♫ Appeared before me ♫
♫ When life gives only you light ♫
♫ Be the light by my side. The way you look ♫
♫ Raises me up again ♫
♫ It makes my heart feel full, makes my heart flutter ♫
♫ It's you ♫