JIALIN PUBLIC TRANSPORT
GROUP LTD., OFFICE 403
First, they went to the bus
company pretending to be reporters.
Then they went to Wang
Xingde's dormitory.
The last call made
from Xiao Heyun's phone
was to a locksmith.
What are they trying to do?
Are they trying to
destroy some evidence?
Wang Xingde's roommate
just happened to come back
so the locksmith
company didn't go there.
But the people they interacted
with have already been picked up.
They are on their way.
Maybe these two
aren't witnesses.
Perhaps…
it's possible that they coerced
Tao Yinghong and Wang Xingde.
They purposely came to us
to lead the investigation
in the wrong direction
and bury evidence against them.
Don't jump to conclusions.
Play this video for me.
Okay.
Just to let you know,
we need both of your phones
and all other electronic
devices for investigation.
Of course.
You can use your phones to
contact your family first
and let them know
that you've been cooperating
here at the police station.
Do you have two phones?
Yes.
- Is this yours too?
- Yes.
Are you sure you don't
want to call home?
It's okay. I've
already told them.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It's okay. We want to stay.
We want to see if we can help.
We won't feel at
ease if we go home.
Yes.
Your girlfriend is indeed
not in a good condition.
- Mr. Zhang, I'm here for the electronics.
- Here.
Mr. Zhang.
Do you have any new leads?
Yes, a few.
Do you know where
the bomb came from?
We're still verifying it.
It's related to that lady with
the plastic bag, isn't it?
Tell me. Why do you ask that?
Didn't you say she worked
at a chemical plant?
You heard everything?
I thought you weren't paying attention
since you weren't feeling well.
- I was the one who told her.
- I…
We analyzed it just now.
If this woman worked
in a chemical plant,
isn't it easy for her
to collect chemicals?
If she had enough knowledge,
could she have created
the bomb herself?
I have another question for you.
You said you smelled
chemicals in the bus
and that it came from
the pressure cooker.
Can you describe
the smell to me?
It's…
It's hard to say. It
was kind of pungent.
It was a sharp smell that you
don't commonly come across.
It stank a little.
It was…
I don't know what
chemical it was.
I don't know much
about that stuff.
- Anyway…
- It was a little…
- Did you smell it too?
- Yes.
I didn't pay much attention.
It did smell a bit.
But it's summer. It's normal
for the bus to smell a bit.
Ms. Du.
PHONE RECORD
Mr. Zhang, Wang Xingde
and Tao Yinghong
never had any direct contact
with Li Shiqing and Xiao Heyun.
There's nothing suspicious
on any of their call records.
They had no interactions either.
There's nothing
suspicious so far.
We're still digging for more.
You both smelled
such a unique smell.
Then the other passengers
must have smelled it too.
How did they react?
I don't think they had
much of a reaction.
There were so many people
on the bus. A bit of...
Mr. Zhang, I suddenly
thought of a question.
What did she do at
the chemical plant?
She was a quality inspector.
Quality inspector?
In that case,
she has the ability to
make her own bomb, right?
Then we were right.
She had the ability
and the means to do it.
Can't that prove she
made the bomb herself?
WHAT ABOUT XIAO
HEYUN'S OTHER PHONE?
MR. ZHANG: WHAT ABOUT
XIAO HEYUN'S OTHER PHONE?
It's still being recovered.
It really doesn't.
It only proves that she had
the means to commit the crime,
but none of this can
be used as evidence.
So are you not going
to investigate?
Mr. Zhang.
The fish has taken the bait.
You can reel it in.
Of course we'll look into it.
I have a question
for both of you.
Before you came here
after getting off the bus,
you two pretended to be reporters
and went to the bus company.
Can you tell me
why you went there?
CITIZENS ARE LIKE THE SEA,
TREASURE EVERY DROP OF WATER
AUTHORITY CARRIES
WEIGHT, DON'T ABUSE IT
JIALIN CRIME POLICE
Recall your memories.
Did these two go
to the bus company
to ask about Wang Xingde?
Yes, it's them.
They said they're students from
the university television station
who want to interview
Wang Xingde.
That's not what they told me.
He said he was Wang
Xingde's relative.
I knew something
was off about them.
Just after they came to
look for Wang Xingde,
we were notified that Wang
Xingde was in an accident.
In the blink of an
eye, they disappeared.
Did they get any
information from you?
They didn't have the chance.
When we started talking about Wang Xingde,
I got notified that he died and left.
I didn't get to tell them.
What about you?
The man said he came to
get the household register.
I realized they
searched the whole house
only after they left.
The woman kept
asking me questions
about Mr. Wang's family.
Other than that,
she didn't say anything else.
She was very emotional
after watching the news.
She kept saying she indirectly caused
the deaths of everyone on the bus.
What does it have
to do with her?
But she kept saying that, so I…
We happened to be nearby,
so I took her to the company,
thinking she might feel more at ease
if we figure things out.
At first, I didn't really believe
there would be a bomb on the bus.
But the more we dug,
the more serious it got.
This has gone beyond
our capabilities,
so we thought we'd
report it to the police.
I know we're being
very suspicious,
but we're definitely
not bad people.
If you don't believe us, you
can check our identities,
our school, or our workplaces.
We'll cooperate.
After a disaster happens,
many survivors feel a
strong sense of guilt.
They feel like disaster struck
because they didn't
do well enough.
They even question themselves,
"Why am I still alive?"
The more moral you are,
the stronger that feeling is.
We call this condition
"survivor syndrome."
Is there such a thing?
We gave all the information
we know to you right away.
Could you
also update us with all the
information you currently have?
That way…
I'm just quite
worried about her.
Ignore me and tell
her. It's fine.
I really just want an answer.
Mr. Zhang, come to
the surveillance room.
MAY 9TH, 2019, THURSDAY
Sit for a bit first.
Do you think he'll believe us?
I don't know.
She made the bomb in a garage.
The residence is on the second floor
and the first floor is the garage.
In addition to raw materials
used to make explosives,
we also detected traces of a
chemical explosion at the scene.
What about fingerprints?
Among the fingerprints
found at the scene,
they all belong only
to Tao Yinghong.
That matches up.
She made a bomb in the
garage that she rented.
Aside from the garage,
did you search her house?
Yes.
Our colleagues
from the cyber team
found transaction records of
chemicals on her computer.
They were all done online.
We're in the process
of verifying them.
I'll get Xiaoliu to
update you later.
Arrange for the relevant departments
to cooperate with the investigation.
Call the cyber team to follow
up on the transactions.
Verify the merchants.
I got it.
From the looks of it,
it's becoming less and less
likely that these two are guilty.
By the way,
what's the situation
at the bus company now?
Wang Xingde's roommate said
that after the two arrived,
one of them went
rummaging inside,
while the other one probed
for details outside.
The topic mainly revolved around
how Tao Yinghong and Wang
Xingde's relationship is
and how they get along.
So it seems like Shiqing
and Heyun's tracks
basically match up
with what they said.
They are indeed looking
for their motives.
Was there anything suspicious
at Wang Xingde's place?
It was turned over.
Logically speaking, these two should've
been there to destroy evidence.
Then why did they leave such
obvious traces of a rummage?
And according to what
the roommate said,
if these two didn't
approach him,
they wouldn't have
made any contact.
Why would they leave
another witness?
When can the flower-patterned
phone be recovered?
Soon. I'll ask the
tech team to hurry.
Mr. Zhang.
Right now, these two witnesses
have me a little puzzled.
We need to find out the
truth as soon as possible
no matter what it takes.
They are here with us now,
so everything is in our control.
I got it.
JIALIN POLICE STATION,
YANJIANG BRANCH
What is the meaning of this?
Don't worry.
It's just a routine inspection.
Thank you.
We can almost be certain
that the bomb
was made by Tao
Yinghong herself.
In that case,
over the four years that the
couple has been in Jialin,
one got familiar with the route
and the other created the bomb.
Was all of this just to
cause today's incident?
Your deduction makes sense.
I just want to know
what other details you remember
that you can provide to us?
That pressure cooker…
I remember she was
very alert at the time.
She kept her hands on
the pressure cooker,
so I'm wondering
if it could be the device
used to detonate the bomb?
But I think
since she's capable
of making a bomb,
could it be a time bomb?
Because she kept going
on and on about 1:45 p.m.
Could it have
a special meaning to them?
I'm just guessing.
Yezi.
Check the case files.
See if there are any past accidents
on the river-crossing bridge
that are related to
the time of 1:45 p.m.
I got it.
By the way,
about the flower-patterned phone
that you guys took away just now…
I got it from Wang
Xingde's dormitory.
Why didn't you tell me just now?
Well, I was a bit scared.
This is the police station.
I stole it after all.
I felt that the phone
was so out of place
in that environment.
I don't think it's his.
So I wanted to take it out and
see if there was any information.
We already knew that
the phone wasn't yours.
I'm glad you told us yourself.
Do they have kids?
What I mean is,
could the phone
belong to their child?
SPOUSE INFORMATION: TAO YINGHONG
CHILDREN INFORMATION: WANG MENGMENG,
BIRTH DATE: DECEMBER 21ST, 1993
HOUSEHOLD REGISTRY: CANCELED
Mr. Zhang.
They indeed have a daughter.
Wang Mengmeng.
She died five years ago.
We found out that they
do have a daughter.
Her name is Wang Mengmeng.
However,
she passed away five years ago.
Miss.
Are you studying at
Jialin Normal University?
Yes.
My daughter goes there too.
Your daughter goes there too?
Which graduation
class is she in?
What major?
She's working now.
Following this logic,
the death of his
daughter, Wang Mengmeng,
could be the key to
solving this case.
Mr. Zhang, come to
the conference room.
By the way, if you two
think of any details,
tell me right away.
Okay.
You must be hungry.
I'll have someone bring
you some food later.
Thank you.
He said his daughter
died five years ago.
But I remember
Wang Xingde told me that his
daughter also went to my school
and that she had graduated
and started working.
Why did he lie?
Right.
When we went to his dormitory,
his roommate told me
that they didn't
have a good marriage.
So do you think those two
were in on it together
or was Wang Xingde coerced?
Mr. Zhang.
- What is it?
- The phone can't be turned on.
The tech team said it will take
some time to pull out what's inside.
But we checked the SIM card.
It belongs to Wang Xingde
and Tao Yinghong's daughter,
Wang Mengmeng.
- Did you check the call history?
- I did.
Wang Mengmeng's last call
was 5 years ago on
May 13th, at 1:44 p.m.
The person she called
was Wang Xingde,
but he didn't answer.
1:44 p.m.?
Mr. Zhang, come.
Have a seat first.
Yezi.
Play it.
JIALIN RIVER-CROSSING
BRIDGE, JIALIN
Stop.
The time was exactly 1:45 p.m.
That's Wang Xingde and Tao Yinghong's
daughter, Wang Mengmeng, right?
On May 13th, 5 years ago,
there was a car accident on the
river-crossing bridge in Jialin.
She died on the spot.
The time of the incident just
so happens to be 1:45 p.m.
It's quite obvious
that the time and
place of the bombing
were the same as Wang Mengmeng's
accident five years ago.
Also, at the time
of the incident,
Wang Mengmeng was also
on the Route 45 bus.
There's one more thing.
The accident happened on
May 13th, 5 years ago.
It's only May 9th today.
Why did they move it up?
I visited the place where the
couple lived in Gangwu New Village.
Someone in their neighborhood told
me that starting this afternoon,
fireproof tests are being
done in all the garages,
so it's highly likely they were
forced to push it up to today
because they can no
longer hide the evidence.
What's coincidental is that
the reason for this
fire inspection
is because on April 4th,
there was a small fire
in Tao Yinghong's garage.
Notice of today's fire inspection
was given at the last minute.
This case…
Everything adds up too easily.
This entire case
has taken less than eight hours
since the incident happened.
Every step we've made
was in the right direction.
Every breakthrough we've
made has been smooth.
That's why it seems too easy.
If these two young people
hadn't come forward,
we would've taken
a few wrong turns.
With our usual
investigation routine.
Mr. Zhang.
What do you think
they are after?
- Mr. Zhang.
- What did you say?
I asked you what you
think they're after.
According to them,
they just want to know
Wang Xingde's real motive.
But no matter what,
with all the information
we have gathered so far,
we have a very clear direction
on how to solve this case.
While you two wait
for the case file,
contact the civilian police
who handled Wang
Mengmeng's case back then.
Get all the surveillance footage
inside and outside the bus.
- Yes.
- I got it.
Come on.
As for the two youngsters…
I'll handle them.
Okay.
I realized a problem.
We went to all this trouble
to find the driver's motive
so we can try to get him to
stop the bus and open the door.
But if the motive
is really related to
his daughter's death,
then there's nothing we can do.
His daughter's death
is already a fact.
We can't change it.
So we still have to
stop the explosion.
Actually, the best way
is to find out what the police would
do if they faced a situation like this.
But the problem is…
Will they tell us?
I'm sorry.
I arranged such a
late dinner for you.
I wasn't sure if you
could eat spicy food.
How is it?
Do you like rice
noodles with clams?
It's good.
Did you recall any details?
I just wanted to ask
if you're sure that the
phone is Wang Mengmeng's?
Also,
can you tell me how
Wang Mengmeng died?
We just want to know
if the couple's motive
has something to do with
their daughter's death.
It's like this.
The incident has
already happened.
Even if you know their motive,
what can you do?
Then what if…
What if it didn't happen?
I mean, what if…
What if the moment
I open my eyes,
I find myself back
on the bus again?
The bomb is already on the bus
and there are less
than 20 minutes
until the explosion
happens at 1:45 p.m.
There's such little time.
Knowing that there's a bomb
and who the culprit is,
what can the two of us
do to stop the explosion?
That's enough. Stop asking.
This had nothing to do with you.
From the time the woman
got on until we got off,
it was only five minutes.
We're not secret
agents. What can we do?
Then should we do
nothing and just wait?
Do we just wait to be blown up?
This incident has
already happened.
There's no way to
change it. You…
Stop thinking about it.
I had no idea you were
this kind of person.
Let me explain.
If that were to happen,
the police usually wouldn't
choose to stop the bus.
That's because it could
provoke the suspect
and end up detonating
the bomb earlier.
The police would usually choose
to have a police officer pretend
to be a passenger in advance
and get on the bus
at the next stop.
We would position our people
based on the suspect's location
and find the right moment
to control them.
Then we would defuse the bomb.
In that case,
there's only Yanjiang
East Road stop.
There are no more
stops after that.
Would you guys be able to
make it in five minutes?
Five minutes?
That's too tight.
So the safest way
is to get on the bus at
Yanjiang East Road stop.
Delaying the time that the
bus arrives at the stop
might be able to buy the police some time
to get arranged. That's all I'm saying.
Delay the time…
Mr. Zhang, we're having a meeting
in the task force conference room.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Mr. Zhang.
I still want to know
how Wang Mengmeng died.
She…
She died in a car accident.
Five years ago,
on a Route 45 bus,
on May 13th at 1:45 p.m.,
Wang Mengmeng got off the bus ahead
of time on the river-crossing bridge
and got into an accident.
Why did she get
off on the bridge?
If one day,
you get a text from a stranger,
saying that there's a bus that
will explode in 20 minutes
and they need your help,
would you trust him and
dispatch right away?
I would dispatch
with no hesitation.
Wouldn't you think
it could be a prank
or someone making
a false report?
We'll find him no matter what
and hold him
legally responsible.
But if it's true,
dispatching right away
could save a whole
bus of people, right?
I'm sure it's not just me.
All my colleagues would
make the same choice.
That's why we are
police officers.
I got it.
Mr. Zhang.
May I have your number?
The bus is moving.
Please hold on tight.
Next stop, Yanjiang East Road.
What happened to you?
Why are you bleeding?
Here.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Actually, after the
time stopped moving up,
I could feel that
my health has been
deteriorating.
If the time loop
isn't infinite for me…
It's okay.
We did so much
preparation this time.
We'll definitely succeed.
MR. ZHANG, THE ROUTE 45 BUS THAT
JUST LEFT GANGWU NEW VILLAGE…
These two are the
most likely suspects.
Pull out their files
and show them to me.
Okay.
UNKNOWN NUMBER
Hello. Who is it?
Mr. Zhang,
I sent you a picture.
Take a look at it.
Who are you?
Then get back to me.
MR. ZHANG, THERE IS A BOMB
ONBOARD THE ROUTE 45 BUS
THAT JUST LEFT
GANGWU NEW VILLAGE!
I got it.
I GOT IT
Pervert!
Ma'am, this man is a pervert.
He just touched me.
- Young man, how could you do that?
- I…
What's happening?
- I didn't do anything.
- Sir.
Let's pull over.
This pervert touched
me while I was asleep.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
You tried to cop a
feel in broad daylight!
- Why are you filming? Did I say you can?
- Stay away!
- Be careful. Don't fight!
- Stop!
- Did you hear?
- Why are you taking my phone?
- Did I say you can film me?
- Don't go up to him.
We're filming so
we have evidence.
Don't go up to him.
He's a pervert.
- If you get any closer…
- They're fighting back there.
- Sir.
- Stop it!
I'll pull over in front.
Hurry and get off.
Don't worry, we're here. He
can't do anything to you.
How shameless.
Get off now.
Is there anything else?
My bag is on my seat.
Don't move.
I'm not getting off.
Why should I get off?
I didn't do anything wrong.
You're the one who should get
off. Come with me to the police.
Fine. I'm not afraid.
Where's my flash drive?
- What...
- Did you take my flash drive?
I didn't. Don't accuse me.
Then where is my flash drive?
- Young man, what…
- It's the same color as the floor.
Let's hurry and
help him find it.
Get him off the bus too.
A flash drive?
There are files on it.
What is going on?
All right, stop looking.
She said you sexually
harassed her.
You said she stole
your flash drive.
I didn't harass her!
I didn't steal it either.
There's surely something
wrong with you two.
We can't help you two.
Let's call the police.
- No, don't close the door.
- Wait, open the door.
I haven't gotten off yet, sir.
- Sir.
- Sir, don't close the door!
Sir.
- Didn't I say I'm getting off?
- Sir, let them off.
Stop messing around. We
have stuff to do at home.
- My goodness.
- I'm busy too.
But those two can't get off.
Keep driving.
The police station is two stops
away. Go there and talk it out.
There's CCTV anyway.
I'm not afraid of you.
Okay.
I'm right anyway.
I'm not afraid.
You definitely took
my flash drive.
Youngsters are so
hard to understand.
YANJIANG EAST ROAD STOP
Mr. Zhang.
We've dispersed the people.
Our people have
surrounded the area.
Okay, I got it.
Once the bus arrives, take action
at both the front and rear doors.
You must be quick. Stay safe.
Copy that.
Go after it!
Why didn't you stop
at the bus stop, sir?
The bus kept going.
What's happening?
Sir, why didn't you stop?
There were people on
the platform, sir.
Why didn't you stop?
- Mr. Zhang, the bridge is sealed.
- Get in.
I got it. I'll follow
them from the rear.
Is the bomb still on the bus?
Listen to me.
Be careful.
If conditions permit,
keep in touch with me.
Okay, bye.
There are police cars
following us. What's happening?
You're right.
Stop the bus, sir.
The bus ahead, pull over!
Pull over!
Stay still!
- What's happening?
- Nobody moves.
The bus must get on the bridge.
Sit down!
Nobody moves!
This woman wants
to blow up the bus.
The bomb is in this plastic
bag. Everybody, stay back.
Blow up the bus?
Mr. Jiao, help!
- Help!
- Quick!
Let go.
Let go of me!
Attention.
The bus is speeding
up onto the bridge.
Roger that. The
bridge is set up.
- Let go of me!
- Sir, stop the bus!
- What are you thinking? Stop the bus!
The driver is her accomplice.
Sir, stop the bus!
The police already
know about your plan.
- There's still a chance if you stop now.
- We're almost on the bridge.
Turn yourselves in.
If you turn yourself in, they
might be lenient with you.
Mengmeng is waiting for us.
JIALIN RIVER-CROSSING
BRIDGE, 1,500 M
Mengmeng is waiting for us.
- She's waiting on the bridge.
- Yes.
What happened to Wang
Mengmeng was unfortunate.
But that's not a reason for you to
drag a bus of people to die with you.
They're all innocent.
That's nonsense!
How do you know Wang Mengmeng?
- Let go!
- I know Wang Mengmeng
was in an accident on the
bridge five years ago.
I know.
Stop the bus.
Nonsense!
- It has been five years.
- Stop the bus.
If you can't let it go, ask
the police to reinvestigate it.
You don't have to do this.
The driver has been reprimanded.
But Mengmeng asked
to get off herself.
- Bullshit!
- She...
If you wanted to investigate,
you would've already done so.
You wouldn't have
forgotten all about it.
What's the use of
saying this now?
Yinghong.
You were right.
You were right to insist.
Hang in there.
Mengmeng is waiting
for us in front.
Driver Wang Xingde,
pull over immediately.
this is your last warning.
Pull over immediately!
Stop the bus, sir!
Wang Xingde, stop
the bus right now!
Come to your senses now.
Tell us any requests you have.
We'll do our best
to fulfill them.
Stop the bus now.
Open the door, sir!
Sir, open the door!
Let go!
Wang Xingde, open
the door right now!
- Police!
- Get out!
- Open the door!
Open the door now!
Let go!
- Turn off the engine!
- Let…
Open the door!
Turn off the engine!
Subtitle translation
by: Chloe Chow