=Dusk Love=
=Episode 9=
(Should I forcefully make him sign?)
Sign it.
I'll sign it.
No, no.
(Maybe I should act more demurely.)
Jinyan, Jinyan,
please sign.
Okay.
(Forget it, I'm going all in.)
Hello?
Moran,
I've discovered your secret.
Meet me tomorrow.
(Jane's Group)
Why are you here?
I
was just nearby.
Didn't your watch break?
I bought you a new one.
Let me put it on for you.
Okay.
Thank you.
What do you know?
You and Huo Jinyan aren't a real couple.
What do you mean?
Real couples don't need a contract
to bind their relationship.
Tell me,
what's going on?
Yes,
I admit,
Huo Jinyan and I are faking it.
Break up with him.
Impossible.
Then do you want
this contract to surface
at the shareholders' meeting?
By then,
Yuni will no longer be yours.
Yuni is my parents' lifelong wish.
I won't let it go.
What about Huo Jinyan?
If my dad finds out you've been lying to him,
he won't let Huo Jinyan off.
Leave him alone.
It depends on you.
Fine,
alright.
I'll break up with Huo Jinyan.
Good.
(It's empty.)
(It was a bluff.)
What about Huo Jinyan?
If my dad finds out you've been lying to him,
he won't let Huo Jinyan off.
(Contract Love)
The new watch I gave you,
doesn't it fit?
I'm used to the old one.
About the renewal you mentioned...
There's no need.
Anything else?
The company found me
a new endorsement in Paris.
I'm leaving tonight.
That's good.
I have an important video conference tonight,
so I won't see you off.
Huo Jinyan?
Have you come back?
(He really left.)
(He won't come back.)
♪Your voice♪
♪Gently reappears in my ear♪
I left in a hurry
and forgot to give you the key.
♪Those once♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪I can be by your side♪
♪Until the day you remember me♪
Goodbye.
♪If you still remember me♪
(Mini Theater)
♪We don't have to be alone♪
♪Enduring lonely times♪
♪Your voice♪
♪Gently reappears in my ear♪
♪It seeps into my heart♪
♪Your memories♪
♪Silently and effortlessly, always revive♪
♪The forgotten times within me♪
♪Yet why do I♪
♪Think of you countless times♪
♪And those fragmented memories♪
♪Always repeatedly invade you and me♪
♪You in the night♪
♪And the tides on the shore♪
♪Seem to portray solitude♪
♪I no longer want to endure the tears
without you♪
♪Those once♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪I can be by your side♪
♪Until the day you remember me♪
♪If you still remember me♪
♪Then we have never truly lost each other♪
♪We don't have to be alone♪
♪Enduring lonely times♪
=Dusk Love=
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)