=Dusk Love=
=Episode 24=
Moran,
even though we're already married,
both our relationship and marriage
started with lies.
This time,
I want to end all the lies
and set aside all external factors.
I hope
we can be like children,
treating each other with innocence,
and like parents,
loving each other instinctively.
Are you okay?
I hurt my ankle.
Be
my boyfriend.
Moran,
am I late?
Just in time.
Let's go.
Moran,
you are the girl
who I will love
from beginning to end.
When you were walking towards me just now,
I was thinking
I might never love you
the same way as I do today.
But I thought the same yesterday.
I am well aware that
one day we will grow old,
be abandoned by this world,
and even
forget our own lives.
I'm telling you,
if anything happens to her today,
I won't let you off.
But the moment I take your hand,
I know
you
are the love of my life.
Jian Moran,
from now on,
I will love you
with my life.
♪Your voice♪
♪Gently reappears in my ear♪
Will you
marry me?
♪Your memories♪
Confessions should be made by men.
Jian Moran,
I love you.
let's get married.
Jian Moran,
will you
marry me?
I will.
♪If you still remember me♪
♪Then we have never truly lost each other♪
♪We don't have to be alone
enduring lonely times♪
(Dusk falls on paper,
dawn rises with our love.)
(In this world full of wonders,
wherever I look, I see you.)
(Every chance encounter comes from love.
The End)
♪Your voice♪
♪Gently reappears in my ear♪
♪It seeps into my heart♪
♪Your memories♪
♪Silently and effortlessly, always revive♪
♪The forgotten times within me♪
♪Yet why do I♪
♪Think of you countless times♪
♪And those fragmented memories♪
♪Always repeatedly invade you and me♪
♪You in the night♪
♪And the tides on the shore♪
♪Seem to portray solitude♪
♪I no longer want to endure the tears
without you♪
♪Those once♪
♪Lifelong promises♪
♪I can be by your side♪
♪Until the day you remember me♪
♪If you still remember me♪
♪Then we have never truly lost each other♪
♪We don't have to be alone♪
♪Enduring lonely times♪
=Dusk Love=
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)