That's the truck?
Yes.
It's going to make me look really uncool!
Excuse me, your backlight is out.
Which one?
The left one.
Something happen?
But I just replaced them.
Anyway... drive safely.
Thank you.
This is so not cool.
My heart is racing.
The Royal Council meeting is tomorrow?
Prince Hyosung petitioned for it,
and the Prime Minister approved.
If we don't get enough votes,
it'll be a waste of time.
All 8 members except
for the Speaker of the House
and the Chief Justice will attend.
Don't worry, Your Majesty.
The Royal Kin and the Lower House
members are with Grand Prince Hyojang.
Only Prince Hyosung, the Prime Minister,
and the Director of Palace
will welcome Prince Hoo.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What about the Deputy Prime Minister?
He has many ties with the Royal
Council and the lower house.
I don't know if the Deputy Prime
Minister will vote in favor.
I'll need at least 6 votes then.
That'll be hard.
Your Majesty.
The Royal Council approved
of Prince Hyoin's wedding.
That marriage was never revoked.
Why would they disapprove of His Highness
Emperor Hunchin's descendant?
It's Prince Hyojang!
As the head of the Upper House,
he has control over the ruling
party and the Royal Kin!
He thinks nothing of me, and this
concerns Prince Moonsung's future!
I can't even register a direct royal
descendant without their approval.
What would my father say if he saw this?
I feel like a caged bird.
Who is that stunning lady?
Welcome, Mother.
Like mother, like daughter.
You're more beautiful than
most actresses out there.
No wonder many men want
to be your palace attendant.
This ballet performance was put
together by Professor Huh's son.
Mother, how many times do I have to tell you?
I don't want to get married.
Let nature take its course!
You're a woman, too.
Why would you want to live by yourself?
It's been seven years
since you took the throne.
I don't know how I'll face
the late Emperor when I die.
Don't you know how I feel?
Of course I do, Mother.
But...
That's enough.
I'll tell them that you're coming.
Bye.
Mother!
I can't believe you're
keeping a secret from me!
Remember how we met at that
huge Court Lady Exam?
We were in the same group,
and ended up becoming roommates!
How can you do this to me?
I'm disappointed.
But, you're a blabbermouth.
I'm going to turn this into a pin cushion!
No!
You'll have insomnia until the day you die.
I'll talk! I'll talk!
You're crazy!
He just stepped outside.
No, he ran away!
If they find out, you'll never get promoted.
You'll forever be a trainee.
No way...
Didn't you hear what
happened to that one girl?
She set a chicken that was in
the Senate free out of pity...
and ended up being a trainee
until she was thirty!
He said he'll be back soon.
And, you believed him?
He ran away in the middle of the night!
We can't sit back. Tomorrow's your day off.
Find him and bring him back.
What?
Kang Hoo, where the heck were you?
There are so many palaces. I asked
Mr. Cho and he wouldn't tell me.
What about those guys?
Where were you?
You idiots!
I told you I was in the
palace with the Empress!
Were you in the hospital by chance?
Anyway, I'm going to have a duel with Bulbam.
A duel with Bulbam? No way!
Bulbam may be short,
but he's a tough fighter!
You won't stand a chance!
You know me, the legendary 17 against 1!
He's in a rage right now! He's
not Bulbam. He's "Bul-bomb!"
I'll go with you.
Hey, it's supposed to be a duel!
A man's got to keep his cool.
It's that girl.
Don't answer that!
Who is she?
Miss Forgetful.
I'm off.
Don't follow me.
Okay.
Aren't you going to follow me?
You told us not to.
Come with me.
- You!
- Yeah!
Yo, Bulbam.
How've you been?
Are you a nice guy now?
You got my bike back from the shop.
If you even laid a finger on it, you're dead.
Don't even think about
pulling something funny.
Aren't you cold?
Be quiet, man...
Take it easy, man.
I'm going to crush you!
No!
Bulbam! Calm down.
I still have payments left on that bike.
You have no idea how mad I am!
No!
- Let me ask you one thing.
- What?
Are you sure you fought 17 against 1?
Weren't you one of the 17?
Of course I was the 1!
Whatever!
I asked someone about this, you jerk!
What? Don't talk crap about my legend!
Tell me the truth!
You're right!
I was one of the 17!
I was sent to the ER because he
beat the crap out of me. Satisfied?
Really? I'm sorry then.
Hit me instead!
I'll take it.
Something smells fishy.
He's holding something.
Is that a knife?
Kang Hoo!
You're about to lose your teeth!
Wait, Bulbam!
You should know something before you hit me.
Why, you!
I'm actually a very important person.
Whatever!
I'm going to be the next Emperor!
- Whatever!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Let go!
Come over here!
What did you say?
Police are coming!
Wait up!
Bulbam! See you later!
Bulbam! Hop on!
A one, a two, a one-two-three-four!
♪ Feels so hot, feels so hot hot ♪
♪ The soju bottle I'm holding in my hand ♪
Woooo!
- Get up, man.
- Get up!
- I can't!
But, I can't sing.
A toast of love between the two bosses.
Lift up your glasses.
This is so embarrassing...
Applause!
Sit down.
Let's drink ourselves silly tonight!
Does this mean Bulbam's group
and Kang Hoo's group are together now?
Kang Hoo, let's take over the
other areas while we're at it!
Leave me out of it.
Why?
I have to go to the palace.
Gosh, I don't want to go.
This is more my style.
Here we go again!
You and that nonsense crap
about being the next Emperor!
I'm serious!
Want me to tell you again? I'm a prince,
and my grandfather is Emperor Hunchin!
I've been in the palace
for the last two days!
- Whatever!
- You're sick in the head!
I'm dead serious!
I can't sleep or wear whatever I want!
I can't even hold my
chopsticks the way I want!
This is driving me crazy...
- You're crazy!
- Shut up!
Stop it.
I'll just consider this as
your way of saying farewell.
You better manage my piers well.
And take care of Mr. Cho, too.
Aren't you going back to The Palace?
Not that Palace. The other palace!
Your Highness!
Yang Sooneui, you're in trouble.
Okay.
Hello?
Is Kang Hoo with you?
Kang Hoo?
Yes.
Where are you?
In the restaurant. Where else?
The restaurant?
What's that?
It's Tae Wang!
Tae Wang? Where's that?
In Incheon, Chinatown! The best Chinese
restaurant! You don't even know Tae Wang?
Hello?
Hey!
How did the Prince leave the palace?
What were the Royal Guards doing?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
It happened all too sudden.
We don't know what happened.
I'll report to you after we
inspect the security cameras.
I knew he'd be a mischievous boy,
but I didn't know he'd be this reckless.
There will be a meeting to determine
whether he'll be registered today!
- Grand Chamberlain!
- Yes?
No one must know what happened.
Keep that in mind, and find the Prince!
I'll do as you say, Your Majesty.
It seems like a new wind is blowing
ever since the Prince came here.
I hope it's a wind of fortune.
I'd like you and Saeryung
to get engaged soon.
What do you think?
The Deputy Prime Minister will be the
next Prime Minister unless I cross him.
I need him to make you the next Emperor.
Saeryung is a perfect candidate for a bride.
I know that I won't be able to find
a better bride than her.
But, Saeryung and I are still in school.
And, I need to know her thoughts first.
I'm sorry to disturb you, Your Highness.
Our intelligence in the palace's
Internal Affairs has told me
that Grand Prince Hyoin's
son has disappeared.
Disappeared?
I don't know the details, but it appears
he has escaped of his own will.
According to these snapshots
from the security cameras,
a palace attendant must've helped him.
What great news to hear for
the Royal Council meeting.
The meeting hosted by Her Majesty
will be a stumbling block for her.
He must've gone to his former residence.
Siyun, find him discreetly.
Yes, my lord.
Dad, why do you want me
to get engaged so soon?
Even if Grand Prince Hyoin's
son gets registered,
he still needs the Royal Kin
and Royal Council's approval.
No one's on the Empress' side.
And?
The Imperial Court is in
Prince Hyojang's hands.
I know who's going to win.
I beg to differ.
We have nothing to gain by acting in haste.
I want to wait and see who holds the ace.
[Prince Hours]
Tae... Tae Wa... Tae Wang...
Where is he?
Kang Hoo!
You're such a nuisance!
You royal loser! Worthless piece of crap!
I'm going to kill you with my
own two hands when I find you!
What?
He's not here.
Did something happen to His Highness?
Oh, I see.
Okay, got it.
I'll call you right away when he does.
Bye.
Did they...
- Did you see Kang Hoo?
- No.
Did you get the background
information on Cho Sangki?
I see.
No.
I don't think he's here.
I sent someone to Seoul.
Good.
Keep an eye on him just in case.
We've come a long way.
Hey! Kang Hoo!
Hey!
Hey, Kang Hoo!
Kang Hoo!
Hey, Hoo!
Ahhhhhh!
You mean you left because of this bike?
Yes.
That's so ridiculous!
You jerk!
I'm not dead.
Don't yell.
Fine.
Let's just get out of here.
Go by yourself.
I have some business to take care of.
What business?
None of your business.
What?
You dirty jerk!
How can you be so selfish?
If they find out that I helped you,
I'll be fired!
No one will know
as long as I keep my mouth shut.
What if they still find out?
They didn't!
You just got scared.
The palace must be in chaos by now.
This is your fault, so you need
to take responsibility for me!
What?
Are you asking me to marry you?
I can't do that. I'd rather die.
I must've gone mad.
I shouldn't have helped you.
I'm the crazy one.
Well, you did help me.
Thanks.
I'm going with you.
What?
I'll be dead if I don't take
you with me anyway.
Suit yourself.
Bye.
You're such a nuisance.
The palace must be in chaos right now.
This is the same as running away.
Geez!
Hey! Kang Hoo!
Stop yelling before I turn deaf!
You're so irresponsible, you jerk!
Don't call me a jerk!
Coward.
You're such a coward!
What?
If you really hate the palace,
then go and say so!
Don't run away like this,
and ruin my life, too!
You're not royalty! You're too
inconsiderate and selfish!
You're a dirty and irresponsible coward!
You're such an obnoxious jerk!
Do whatever you want!
You don't deserve the people's respect!
I don't even want royalty like you!
Yang Sooneui!
What?
Are you going to walk?
Hop on.
Okay.
I don't even want an attendant like you!
What?
[Prime Minister Han Euihyun]
Does anyone have anything to say about
registering and appointing the Prince?
I will now officially register
and appoint the Prince.
As an official member of the Royal Family,
he is entitled to the benefits
and rights given by the country.
Wait!
What is it?
I heard that Prince Yi Hoo has
left his quarters without permission
and is missing.
I'd like you, Mr. Prime Minister,
to say something about this.
Same here.
That's right.
I'd like to say something.
We can't confirm that here.
And, even if we could,
that has nothing to do with this.
What do you mean?
Of course it matters!
We're trying to determine if he's qualified
to be a member of the Imperial Court.
Why are we having a meeting if we don't care
whether he left the palace
without permission?
We should first find out
if this is true or not.
If this is true...
then we don't know what dumb
things he's up to right now?
Dumb things?
He's of direct royal lineage!
Watch what you say about Prince Youngsung!
I'm only saying that
if that's what's going on.
Prince Youngsung?
Don't call him by that name!
I have an idea.
Why don't we adjourn the meeting and
ask the Imperial Court what happened?
That seems to be a good idea.
Let's adjourn the meeting for now
and continue after we find out.
The meeting was adjourned?
How did it come to this?
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
It's Prince Hyojang!
His has his men everywhere in the palace!
Your ID Card says Kang Hoo.
But, my real name is Yi Hoo!
I'm the Prince!
I'm a palace attendant.
This is His Highness Prince Yi Hoo.
I don't know anything about that.
I was in there until yesterday!
Stop it!
I can arrest you for trespassing
and hand you over to the police!
Wait right here.
I'll get the Grand Chamberlain.
Hey!
Stay right here, okay?
Please try again.
What's going on?
- What are you doing here?
- Pardon?
[Prince Hours]
Nice.
Is that a real gun?
Why isn't she here yet?
Hello.
Your Highness, what are you doing here?
I'm just... waiting for someone.
Do you have a visitor?
Huh? Yes... So, what are you doing here?
I have to do something for an
event hosted by the Imperial Court.
It'll be nice if you could come.
Would you like to come
with me if you're not busy?
Wow, this bike is nice!
Yes, I just fixed it up!
Can you ride a motorcycle?
How cool!
Are you telling the truth?
Believe me, His Highness
is waiting at the gate!
Okay, I'll believe you.
But, you'll be punished if you're lying.
Where is he?
He was here a minute ago.
Since we don't know where the Prince is,
I'll postpone your punishment.
But, even if he comes back safely,
you still need to pay the
price for what you've done.
The Imperial Court's Justice Committee
will decide what to do with you.
Until then, your privileges as a
palace attendant will be revoked.
Hi, this is Yang Sooneui's cell phone.
Please leave a message.
Darn, maybe I should've stayed there.
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Now that you're here, I'll just head back.
No way!
I have something I want to show you.
You'll have to participate in a lot of
Imperial Court activities from now on.
Let's go!
You brought this upon yourself.
Don't blame anyone!
Follow me!
Maybe he's being threatened by them again.
I think he's in Seoul.
The Captain of the Royal
Guard is still looking for him.
Since everyone knows who the Prince is...
Prince Hyojang won't be able to harm him.
Don't worry too much.
I thought he was a branch out of firm roots.
I thought he'd have his father's qualities.
Your Majesty...
But, I guess my hopes were in vain.
Your Majesty, remember what we
said when you first took the throne?
You were afraid and thought you
weren't ready to be the Empress.
I remember....
And, you told me I have
nothing to be afraid of
as long as I'm willing to serve
my country and people.
Everything needs time.
The Prince needs to have the heart
to do so before he becomes qualified.
When will he have the heart
to be Crown Prince?
His Highness Prince Moonsung is here.
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Her Majesty is not in a good mood today.
She's not accepting visitors.
You should go back.
I think Attendant Yang will be fired.
Really?
Of course!
She helped the Prince run away.
She'll get fired even if he comes back.
You jerk!
It's okay.
Nothing will go wrong.
It's okay. Don't cry!
Use this.
It's okay, Your Highness.
Use it.
Or else you're embarrassing me.
Thank you.
Are you in a relationship with the Prince?
Huh?
No.
Don't worry...
Even the palace has clemency.
Hello?
Hold on, Mom.
Me?
I'm doing fine.
Really?
Do you trust me?
Mom...
I'm sorry.
No, nothing's wrong.
I just feel bad for not calling too often.
This is a reenactment of the enthronement.
There are many events hosted
by the Imperial Court.
All proceeds from this event will be donated
to UNICEF for impoverished children.
Your Highness!
Hold on.
Did you look into what I asked you?
Yes, I looked into it...
Good.
You two are so dead.
I was going to tell on you guys,
but decided to take it like a man.
What are you talking about?
Did we tell you to watch?
What?
He's right.
We never asked you to watch with us.
Fine then. Let's say that's true.
Then, why'd you leave me by
myself at the last minute?
I can't stand dirty rascals like you guys.
Tell me how many punches do you want?
Let's talk it out.
No. He's a big talker.
Alright, then let's duke it out!
Stop it!
This is Prince Yi Hoo.
Pay your respects.
Prince Yi Hoo?
You mean...
I'm late, Mother.
What happened?
You're never late.
I'll be more careful from now on.
Hey.
The Royal Council meeting has been adjourned.
You mean he's not registered yet?
Joon, you have nothing to
worry even if he's here.
Just follow your father's lead and
a throne will be waiting for you in the end.
You must be the Emperor,
for your mother's sake.
Let's go inside.
Anyway, it was very manly of you
to keep silent about what we did.
We apologize for putting you
in a bad situation that day.
Well, since you say that...
After all, real men are of few words.
A man's got to watch his mouth, right?
Watching men reconcile is pretty interesting.
Gentlemen, how was the women's dressing room?
As a student, it was a
good learning experience.
It was an opportunity to gaze upon
the blossoming female body...
And, well... the body is a piece of art...
I hope you'll be more understanding of
us gentlemen's need to appreciate art.
What an interesting way to put it.
Your Highness...
I need to talk to the people
who are preparing this event.
You should wait here
with these dirty gentlemen.
Joon!
When did you get here with him?
Who?
Ah.
His Highness was kind enough to
give me a ride here.
A ride?
Like delivering black-bean noodles?
I hope you don't get the wrong idea.
The wrong idea?
I just want to know who your rival is.
After all, he's a candidate.
I'm going to be the best woman.
And, of course, I need the
best man to be by my side.
And, as of now, that's you.
So don't worry.
Should I say thank you?
Why?
You now have two cards to choose from.
He needs to be up to par.
Hello, Your Highness.
[Prince Hours]
I wonder if Sooneui is okay.
What are you doing here, Your Highness?
What?
Did you get Her Majesty's
permission to leave the palace?
Of course.
Although you've grown up
with roughnecks from the streets,
you must maintain your dignity as royalty.
You can't enter and leave
the palace like that.
I don't think that's any of your business.
If a future successor to the
throne leaves without permission,
the palace will be in chaos.
Don't you have any discernment?
If the people find out...
how will they respect and trust royalty?
I'm stunned at how much
you lack common sense.
Those are fighting words!
Go back right now.
Let's pretend we didn't see
each other here today.
I came here of my own free will!
Free will!
Above free will, royalty must consider
responsibility and duty as priority no. 1.
Otherwise, he'll only be a
shell of someone who's royal.
Shell?
What did you just say?
Now that you've come to your
senses, go back to the palace.
Move it!
It's up to me to decide whether
I'll go back or not! Got that?
Captain, what are you doing?
Stop it, please.
There are many people watching.
I think the two of you,
Highnesses, must stop now.
You're right.
I was wrong.
The two Highnesses?
You mean... he's...
You should say hello, Your Highness.
This is Prince Moonsung Joon Lee,
King Eunchin's grandson
and Grand Prince Hyojang's son.
You two are second cousins.
Excuse me. Who are you?
Your Majesty...
[Prince Hours]
The reason why I personally came here
is to give you an opportunity.
An opportunity?
Leaving the palace...
An opportunity for you to return here.
There was a court lady who
helped me leave the palace...
I was wondering what happened to her.
That attendant will find it
difficult to stay in the palace.
Don't ever appear before me again! Got it?
Can we trust Grand Prince Hyojang?
There seems to be no
other way, Your Majesty.
If the Inspector Court Lady
sees me, I'm dead meat!
I'm sorry. Please help me just once!
She becomes more interesting
the more I see her.
This is not a simple matter
of exiting the palace,
but damaging the Empress and the
authority of the Imperial Court!
He had no idea of his identity and lived
as a commoner for 20 years.
It, indeed, was a scandalous matter...
But, no one can deny that the
Prince is a royal descendant.
You left the palace without
permission. Was there a reason?
After the incident, public opinion has been
negative. How do you feel about that?
I feel... happy about it.
The world is ready to welcome you, Your Highness.
Are you ready to face the new world?