Episode 19
Qian.
I'm here for you.
Give the nod
and I am right here for you.
Can I hold this hand?
Mistress!
Please go and see Guard Hua.
He is bleeding profusely.
Tell me, what happened to Hua Rongzhou?
Just go and see him, Mistress!
Lord, thank you for coming
to deliver the divorce letter to me.
I will pretend I didn't hear what you said
and I hope you'll never bring this up again.
Let's go.
Lord.
Well
I have been waiting for so long
but now I'm getting anxious like a kid.
Physician, how is Hua Rongzhou?
Mistress, he is fine
but his wound ruptured the second time
so it is hurting him a lot.
He has taken some medicine
and fallen asleep.
His wound ruptured the second time?
—Qianzhi.                        —Yes, Miss.
What's going on?
Mistress, don't you know?
Miss Hua, Guard Hua was injured
when he jumped off the cliff that day.
Maybe Master's attack yesterday
made the wound rupture again.
Jumped off the cliff?
That day, Guard Hua followed you
into the valley
and brought you back the next morning.
We saw a wound around his waist.
He probably got scratched
by a branch when he fell.
But he didn't say much to us.
He fell into the valley after me?
Mu Yao, you owe me one.
—Mistress!                            —Qian!
Qian!
Why didn't anyone tell me about his injury?
Mistress, you have been feeling down
and keeping to yourself in the past few days.
You wouldn't listen to anything we say.
After all, he's just a guard
and he doesn't listen to us.
How dare we talk about it at this moment?
Guard Hua insisted on guarding the compound
even though he was injured.
And he took a blow from Master yesterday.
Despite that, he didn't say a word.
I didn't know how badly he was hurt
until he passed out in front of me.
But, Mistress, you didn't care about him.
—Cuizhu!                       —Guard Hua...
Miss Hua.
The physician prescribed him some medicine.
We're supposed to collect it.
We shall do it now.
You said that I was prone to ignore you
and I refused to admit.
Now it seems
you've all been very kind to me
and I've been nothing
but selfish and self-absorbed.
I did that to you
and to my brother.
Fortunately, it isn't too late to know now.
What is he dreaming about?
He's gripping on so tightly.
You're awake. Does the wound still hurt?
Can you let go of it now?
You pulled me close
before I even had time to talk to you.
I am so sorry. Please punish me.
Why do I want to punish you?
You're seriously injured.
You'd better go back to bed and get some rest.
Get up and put on some clothes
and I will come and see you later.
I didn't sleep well last night
so I'll take a nap.
Wake me up if anything happens.
I was guarding the entrance
of the compound last night.
Miss, you were in Guard Hua's room.
He fell asleep and couldn't wake up
so I stayed for a while.
Don't worry, Miss.
Fortunately, I made it look like
you had gone to bed last night.
It should be able to cover this up.
Why should I worry?
Men and women should observe the proprieties
not to mention between the master and servant.
It's better for you to be more careful.
If this gets out
I'm afraid it will ruin your reputation.
I know gossip is a fearful thing
but Hua Rongzhou was seriously injured
because of me.
It's only right that I serve him tea and water
in his room.
If it were you, I would do the same.
Now you are no longer servants to me
so don't say such words in the future.
Perhaps it is not suitable
to talk about this right here right now
but I still want to ask
if you would like to be with me.
If you have a little affection for me
leave everything to me.
And I'll have you stand rightfully beside me.
Qian.
I'm here for you.
Give the nod
and I'm here for you.
Miss just fell asleep. What do you want?
If you're not in a hurry, talk to her later.
I'll kneel here as punishment.
She doesn't need to know.
Why are you kneeling here?
Your medicine is ready.
—What are you doing?     —Get out of my way.
—I want to talk to Mistress.            —No!
Miss is sleeping. You can't go in.
—Get out of my way.                 —Cuizhu!
—Mistress....!             —You can't go in.
—I need to talk to you, Mistress!       —No!
—Cuizhu!                          —Mistress!
—Qianzhi...                       —Mistress!
—Cuizhu!           —What's going on outside?
—I need to talk to you. —Cuizhu, I told you.
—You can't come in.           —Let go of me.
Miss is sleeping.
Mistress.
Guard Hua was seriously injured
and unconscious yesterday.
Please...
Please don't punish him
since he's such a loyal servant.
When did I punish him?
Guard Hua is kneeling outside now.
Qianzhi, help me comb my hair.
Cuizhu, go and bring Hua Rongzhou in.
Yes, Mistress.
Get up.
You are still injured.
Why are you not in bed resting?
Who punished you?
I have offended you
and should be punished.
You're honest to a fault.
As I said, it was nothing serious.
I wanted you
to rest for a while before asking questions.
I think it's better to do it now
and not let your imagination run wild.
Leave us. I have something to ask him.
Tell me.
You found me so quickly in the valley.
Did you jump off the cliff after me?
Yes, I did.
Was your abdomen injury caused by the fall?
No.
When I came ashore from the river
I saw a man in black.
I thought it was the man in black
who followed us
so I attacked him.
He injured me during the fight.
Wait.
If we continue this fight
the woman you are looking for
will be even harder to find.
Did you see his face?
His face was masked.
I probably made a mistake.
The man in black
didn't seem to want to fight me.
So, after we both got injured
he left in a hurry
and I didn't chase after him.
I'm afraid you didn't make a mistake.
You jumped off a cliff and were injured.
Why didn't you tell me about these incidents?
Because you never asked.
I had been depressed for the past few days
but you must tell me everything from now on.
Is that clear?
I'm always busy with my own affairs
and cannot take care of everything.
I know you usually don't talk much
but you have done so much for me
and you have to learn to speak up.
And I have never regarded you as a servant
so you can speak freely.
I won't think you're asking for credit
or showing off.
Understood.
One more thing.
Since you're injured, you need rest.
You shouldn't have fought against Zhong Yelan.
You need to learn how to protect yourself
before you can protect others.
Is that clear?
Miss, you have said this to me before
but I thought about it long and hard.
You treat me...
I mean, us very well.
I don't care about myself.
I just can't watch you get hurt.
All right.
You can go back and have a rest.
Take a break from guarding the compound
for a couple of days. You need a good rest.
If you need anything, just tell Qianzhi.
Yes, Miss.
By the way
I have poor eyesight.
Refrain from wearing black.
It's not noticeable if you get injured.
All right.
Zhong Residence
Make your decision. Choose neither
and they will both die!
That will help you avoid guilty
for making the choice to save only one.
Mu Yao, you owe me one.
—Mistress!                            —Qian!
Qian!
Are you okay?
Master.
Gather all the men in Zhong Residence.
Conduct a thorough search for Mistress.
Yes, Master!
Let's go!
I attended Hua Shen's funeral yesterday.
People should hear about
the divorce between Hua Qian and me today.
It's so sudden. What happened?
Is it sudden?
I thought you couldn't wait for it to happen.
I don't know what you're talking about.
By the way
Hua Qian told me to pass you a message.
What message?
She said you owed her...
two lives.
Yao.
You said that I trusted Hua Qian blindly
and she made used of this
and lied to me repeatedly.
Indeed. That was what she did.
But what about you?
Stop!
—Documents.                 —H-Here you are.
Go!
What's in your bag?
Clothes.
Go!
Check thoroughly!
—Go!                             —Thank you.
Wait.
Next.
Hey, stop. Routine check.
Stop!
—Have you seen him?                     —No.
Wait! Did you see anyone suspicious?
No.
Why are there so many soldiers on the street?
Master, the enforcement of the martial law
has become even stricter.
People getting out of the city
people who behave suspiciously on the street
and individual travellers in inns
are all being questioned one by one.
Although you change inn every few days
I'm afraid that you will inevitably
attract attention after a while.
Have you found a way to get out of the city?
The main exit is out of the question.
It is strictly guarded.
To the east of the city lies Donghuang Mountain.
The road there is rugged and steep.
Usually, no one will pass through there.
Security is weak there.
Sometimes there are even no guards at all.
We can give it a try.
Are we going to exit by force?
No, there are not many of us in the city now.
If you want to leave
the rest of our men
will create a distraction at the main exit.
When that happens
Leaving the city from the east secretly
shouldn't pose much of a challenge.
Master.
The longer you stay
the more difficult it is to leave.
What was I thinking?
In the end
I have got nothing.
But that was my parrot
and she should be mine.
I fell in love at first sight
but I just gave an excuse
and said I would test her out.
If I had known better
I might as well abduct her and leave.
Master.
Never mind.
Just do as you said.
Shen
brought me this tea when he was alive.
He knew that I liked tea
so he spent a lot of money
to buy these fragrant tea leaves.
I reprimanded him many times for this
but he turned a deaf ear to it.
I...
wanted to keep the tea to myself.
Why don't you try the tea?
How is Mother holding up?
She stopped crying and making a fussing.
Her mood is much more stable now.
If you can, go and see her more frequently.
You are her only child now
and she won't fight with you again
when she's thinking more clearly.
What's wrong?
I'm fine.
I think it's the sequelae of the arrow injury.
Soon
I'll send your brother's memorial tablet
to the ancestral hall in our hometown.
Only after that
will I resign from my position as head butler
lest the old stubborn folk of the clan
see that they no longer have someone to rely on
and try to stop me.
It's all up to you.
Qian.
Is there somewhere you want to go?
After we settle the matters here
we shall not rush to return to our hometown.
Let's go travelling
so that your mother can forget her troubles.
All these years in Huangcheng City
I realised I had never taken the family out.
I had neglected you all.
Father, can you lend me some men?
Did you get into some trouble?
My guard is injured
and now I want to investigate something.
Unfortunately
I don't have people whom I can deploy.
Tell me the problem.
I'll see if I can help.
It's nothing serious.
I can do it myself.
Qian.
You can deploy anyone in this house.
You don't need my permission.
Just let me know
if you run into a roadblock.
Thank you, Father.
Why are you being so polite to me?
Go on. Have a sip of the tea.
—Miss Hua.                        —Miss Hua.
I have picked a few men for you.
They are agile and clever.
There are too few men.
I will bring a few more later.
All right.
You don't need to bring them to me though.
Just do as I said
and have them get ready.
At the command of you.
Six of you will guard
the perimeter of Zhong Residence.
You have two main tasks.
One of them is to pay attention
to every move of Concubine Mu.
Follow her whenever she goes out.
But make sure she doesn't notice you.
Report to me whom she meets.
The other task is to look out for night visitors
at Zhong Residence.
If there is, find out his whereabouts
and report to me.
Noted, Miss Hua.
Don't panic if you're caught.
Just say that you are the guards
of Hua Residence
and that you're under my orders
to monitor Mu Yao's movements.
Don't bother about what they might say.
Noted.
—You may leave.              —Yes, Miss Hua!
Miss Hua.
They may be agile
but monitoring all movements
in Zhong Residence could pose a challenge.
After all, there are many capable people
in Zhong Residence as well.
I know that.
That's why I only need them
keep an eye on Mu Yao.
Get six more men
to take turns with the six of them just now.
Bear this in mind. Remain focused.
Now that Huangcheng is under martial law
there's no way he can escape.
Knowing his temperament
I'm sure he will bid Mu Yao farewell
before he leaves.
So you must pay close attention
to Mu Yao's movements.
Don't confront her
unless it is absolutely necessary.
I don't want to confront Mu Yao right now.
She won't believe a word I say.
Miss Hua, don't worry.
I'll be sure to remind them again.
Just do your best.
After all, they can run but they cannot hide.
Yes, Miss.
Time is running out.
I can't just sit and wait.
Send a message to Zhong's Garden later.
Tell them that I will go there tomorrow
to thank Her Highness.
Yes, Miss.
Yinxing.
You have always been
in charge of my jewellery.
Do you remember the white jade bracelet
that Her Highness gave me when I got married?
Yes, I remember.
Help me find it.
I'm going to Zhong's Garden tomorrow.
I should return it.
Got it, Miss.
Master.
I just came back from outside
and I noticed there were people
snooping around.
I secretly observed them for a while.
They seem to be monitoring
the movements in Zhong Residence.
Whose men are those?
They seem to be...
from the Hua family.
Get changed and run an errand for me.
Yes, Master.
Mistress is here, Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Sit down.
Yes, Your Highness.
I haven't seen you for a few days
and you have lost a lot of weight.
I didn't get out of the house these days.
I wouldn't have lost weight.
Your Highness, besides thanking you
I came to return this bracelet to you.
After all, I have not met your expectations.
It is yours since I have given it to you.
You don't have to return it to me.
The late emperor gave this to you.
I'm only an outsider.
I dare not accept it nor should I.
There is no outsider here.
Even though you and Yelan are not meant to be
you don't have to keep a distance from me.
Just take it as a gift from an elder.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Since you were married
I bore witness to your actions and conduct.
I know that you are sensible
and know what you should do.
Yelan is not fortunate enough
to stay married to you.
I'm not some foolish old lady
who only favours her own child
so you don't have to keep a distance from me.
If you want to come to Zhong's Garden
feel free to come and see me
so that I won't be so lonely.
Are your parents okay?
Those Ge family members
completely disregard the law.
The assassination was executed in public
and they did not show
the Zhong family any respect.
In a way, we brought upon your brother's death.
Lord has been overwhelmed with
the investigation in the past few days
and he seems to have lost a lot of weight too.
My brother was destined to suffer an ill fate.
He was unlucky to have me as his sister.
Speaking of which
I realised two days ago
that I forgot about passing down the order
to approve the divorce between you and Yelan.
When I remembered it
I heard that Lord had already given the order.
Your Highness, thank you for remembering.
I couldn't wait any longer
so I asked someone to send a message
to Zhong's Garden.
That reminded Lord of the matter
and then he passed down the order.
Lord is so occupied
with the assassination investigation
that he rarely comes to my compound
and I haven't seen him much.
I was worried about him
the day before yesterday
so I sent someone to bring him some food
but, in the end, no one was there.
He has a stable personality
so I wonder
why he slipped out of Zhong's Garden secretly
without informing me.
If you're talking about the day before yesterday
Lord had gone to look for me.
The Lord showed sympathy towards me
due to my brother's recent death.
And he also took into account my father's
long-term contribution to the Zhong family
so he personally delivered
the divorce letter to me.
Lord has overstepped the boundary
with regard to this matter.
Please don't take it to heart.
I will make sure he leaves you alone
in the future.
Your Highness
when the truth about the Zhong's Garden
assassination comes to light
my father will tender his resignation
and return to our hometown
and I will go with him.
I suppose I'll never return
to Huangcheng ever again.
Why?
My brother grew up in Huangcheng.
It is too painful for me
and my parents
to continue living here.
Right...
That's right.
Don't blame me.
The Zhong family has always
valued its reputation.
Xiwu and Yelan have been as close as brothers
since childhood.
But they may turn against each other
because of you.
And if word got out
I'm afraid I wouldn't be able to protect you.
Your Highness, thank you for the reminder.
Bonus footage
Mother, I want to fly the kite myself.
Wait a minute. I'll fly it higher for you.
I want to fly it myself.
You want to fly it yourself?
Wait a minute. I'll fly it higher.
I want to fly it myself.
Come and catch me then.
Mother, I want to fly it.
Mother, give it to me.
I want to do it myself.
I'll do it myself.
Here you are.
If you like the kite, then hold it tight.
Okay?
Go on and play with it.
If you like it, then hold it tight.
What is he dreaming about?
He's holding on so tightly.