Episode 25
Senior, how long has it been
since we had dinner together like this?
—I don't remember.            —That's right.
Since you came back from the South
you have become more and more taciturn.
When you're with me
we only talk about the incense workshop.
And you're the same even after you got married.
Senior, do you miss the days
when you managed the shops in the South?
I'm doing quite well now.
Senior, do you mind going back to the South?
Lord, what do you mean?
The Meng family monopolises
the shops in the South
and their ambitions are growing bigger.
I need someone to counterbalance them.
There are many excellent butlers in the city
to choose from.
You handed over the operating rights
of the shops in the South to Butler Meng.
No one is more suitable than you
to take it back.
I've been away from the South for many years
and now things are different.
I'm afraid that
I might not be a good leader if I go back.
Senior, please don't underestimate yourself.
Although it's been a while
since you returned to Huangcheng
you were the one who established
the business in the South.
Everyone remembers that.
You are my father's only apprentice.
I know that
when I first took over the position of Lord
all the butlers were watching me closely
and you handed over the operating rights
of the shops in the South
in order to reassure my mother and me.
But...
I need you now.
Tell me what you want me to do.
I'd like you to have the position of Head Butler
in charge of the shops in the South.
Since you worry about the Meng family
monopolising the business
aren't you afraid that I will do the same?
If you had the intention, you'd have done so
when I succeeded as Lord.
You were fully capable of that at the time.
Although you are kind since you were young
you have never been submissive.
I'm flattered to hear you praise me.
Will you help me then, Senior?
When do you want me to leave?
After this month's banquet
I'll make the announcement
in front of all the butlers.
Senior.
Miss, what brings you here?
I'm here to see my mother.
I thought that you would never come again
because you were mad
at the remarks Madam made.
I could have done better.
It must have been tough for you.
It's fine...
Go in.
Mother.
I'm here to see you.
I wasn't a filial daughter.
I caused you trouble.
But don't worry
even though Shen is gone
as long as I am still here
I will never let anyone hurt you.
Mother.
I miss you.
Qian.
It was my fault.
I reprimanded you.
—Mother.                —I broke your heart.
It was my fault.
Good girl.
Forgive me.
I heard you and your mother have reconciled.
Father, what are you talking about?
When did Mother and I fall out?
What?
No, you didn't.
It would be great
if I could get closer to my mother sooner.
It's not too late now.
Miss.
Miss, you've received a reply.
How time flies.
Qian.
What's wrong with you?
You seemed to want to say something
but you held back.
Tomorrow is the fifth of the month
the day of the banquet in Zhong's Garden.
I think my mother had better not attend it.
Zhong's Garden will be crowded
and my mother's health isn't doing well.
That's right.
Anyway, the banquet in Zhong's Garden
isn't really interesting.
In the past two weeks
I've been handing over my duties.
After the banquet
I should be able to relinquish
the position of Head Butler.
When that happens, we can live
in the small town South of the Yangtze River
that you mentioned. What do you think?
That's...
nice.
By the way
do you know Junior Lord Wu on a personal level?
Yes, I do.
The inferior agarwood incense
that even Mu Yunping couldn't tell apart
came from him.
He harboured a member of the Ge family
who was on the run.
That's impossible.
Why not?
But the previous...
In the previous life, Wu Shuomo did not
harbour a member of the Ge family.
He helped Mu Yao
and even became the mastermind
behind the downfall of the Hua family.
It's unlikely he would cooperate
with my father now.
What went wrong?
What's the matter?
He...
He belongs to the Wu family.
How would he get involved
in the Zhong family's matters?
Precisely because he's from the Wu family
it's safe to work with him.
She is gentle by nature?
She is timid and cowardly?
When did you start suffering from eye disease?
I know my daughter.
You two share a strong bond.
If you want to get emotional
I can understand.
Look at you.
You look all calm and composed.
I can't believe you're actually threatening me.
Are you really not afraid that
I might let the cat out of the bag
and tell everyone about how we collaborated?
Between you and me
you're the one who's more worried
about our collaboration coming to light.
In order to steal the incense formula
the Wu family went ahead to harbour
the wanted member of the Ge family
risking being condemned.
You then tried to secretly
concoct fake incense pills.
I wonder if Senior Lord Wu knows about this.
Or did you carry out this reckless act
of your own accord?
I merely just provided you
with an incense formula
so that you could frame your colleague.
We made a deal.
Why are you suddenly burning the bridge
and turning against me?
Of course, I know what you're thinking.
But the internal struggle of the Zhong family
has nothing to do with you.
You're not at a disadvantage.
And now, you're involved in their affairs.
Does it mean you're ready to give up
working with the Zhong family?
Like father, like daughter indeed.
You'd threaten to drag your enemies
down with you
and make sure your enemies
have it worse than you.
Therefore
I urge you to be careful with
your words and actions, Junior Lord Wu.
If word gets out
I would rather hurt myself
than let you live in peace.
This matter poses great risks.
I personally contacted him
and no third party knew about it
so I didn't mention it to you before.
There's no way the investigations
will point to him.
Qian.
Don't worry.
He knows what he can and can't say.
As long as I don't mention it
this matter will not be found out.
Indeed, it won't be found out.
Otherwise
I wouldn't have just found out now.
I didn't deliberately hide it from you.
Fine.
If there's something you want to know
ask away.
Father, can you tell me what exactly
did you do to the Mu family?
All right.
I...
got it now.
It's getting late
and we have to go to Zhong's Garden tomorrow.
Father, go to bed early.
Qian.
Yes?
All these years
I had neglected you and your brother
a great deal
while chasing after power and fortune.
You're a sensible girl.
Unfortunately...
I didn't teach your brother well.
Why did you say this?
Since you got married
the way you speak and act has changed
and you have become distant.
I noticed all that.
I asked you about it
but you refused to tell me what happened.
I couldn't help but wonder
what had happened to you.
Nothing of the sort. You think too much.
After your brother passed away
I finally understood.
I failed as your father.
I never considered things from your standpoint
so my daughter couldn't share her feelings
with me
when she met with trouble.
Now...
as long as you are safe
I'm relieved.
Father, don't say that.
You've done well enough.
It was my fault.
On the night I got married
I had a dream.
I dreamed that everyone in our family
died unexpectedly.
That dream was so real.
I wondered if this was a warning
from the heavens.
That's why I changed the way I behaved.
But it's all right now.
With me here
I will definitely protect you
and the entire family.
My good daughter.
Now, go to bed.
Oh, heavens.
You are so cruel.
You gave me a second chance in life
and also a big challenge.
Miss.
Go get Hua Rongzhou here.
Yes, Miss.
My father will tender his resignation soon
and after our discussion earlier on
we have decided to settle down
in the South of the Yangtze River.
So, help me run an errand tomorrow.
Find a good house there
for us to settle down.
Why do you want me to leave earlier?
It feels like you're sending me away.
It is good to make preparations earlier
so that it won't be a mad rush
when it's time to move.
Which is why I need you to go settle in first
and wait for us to get there.
Only you and Qianzhi
remain in my compound.
Qianzhi will stay in Huangcheng
so you're the only person
who can help me and whom I trust.
But I still feel
that you're trying to drive me away.
You'll be away for half a month at most.
Can this house and I escape from the city
in such a short time?
I think it's better to leave together
when the time comes.
I'm worried about leaving you alone.
There are so many people in the compound.
What's there to worry about?
I gave you a task and all I heard were excuses.
If you don't want to do it, just say so.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
I'll set off tomorrow.
Good. I'll wait for your news.
Remember to shortlist a few houses
for my father to choose from.
Avoid crowded areas
but also stay away from secluded spots.
We're going to live there
so choose carefully.
I won't fail you.
But I hope you will keep your word.
Don't lie to me.
Didn't you say that I was a bad liar?
So, why are you worried?
Then I will set out tomorrow.
That's strange.
There is no incense in my room
but why do I smell a familiar aroma?
Can you smell it?
Yes.
Can you really smell it?
The nice aroma is emanating from you, Miss.
But I'm not wearing any incense.
But you're always emanating this nice aroma.
What does it smell like?
I can't put my finger on it
but it's very special.
Since the first time I met you
it's always been this nice aroma.
Never mind. You're leaving tomorrow.
Go and get some rest now.
All right.
Going to the South of the Yangtze River
and choosing our new house...
I guess it will at least take him
half a month to go back and forth.
Miss, what are you talking about?
Nothing.
Do you smell something on me?
No.
You haven't been using any incense
so you won't be emanating an aroma.
My father will go with me today
so you don't have to go
to Zhong's Garden with me.
My mother has just recovered.
Take care of her on my behalf.
Are you ready to set off?
Miss, remember to look for me soon
or I will come back for you.
All right. Be safe.
Zhong's Garden
—Here.                  —A toast to you all.
Cheers.
Xiwu.
Thank you, Mother.
Sis Hua, what's so urgent that you had to ask
to see me here?
You look so cold and indifferent.
And you've been ignoring me lately.
What, did something happen?
Stop pretending we are close.
It's disgusting.
What's wrong with you today?
Have you forgotten that Lord is allergic
to lychee honey?
Is that so?
I only know that Lord has a sweet tooth
so I guess he must also like lychee honey.
Is that why you alienated yourself from me?
I really didn't know...
Don't you get tired of acting day in and day out?
Sis Hua, who told you
that Lord couldn't have honey?
He told me himself.
You thought you could get away
with such a clumsy trick.
Did you think
I wouldn't ask Zhong Xiwu directly?
Or did you think that no one else knew
what you whispered in my ear that day
so you could pass the buck?
You've really wronged me.
Keep this up and our conversation ends here.
What do you want to talk about?
About...
why you tried to kill me.
—You...                       —Since I asked
it shows that I've verified the fact
so drop your act.
You're a cautious person
you must have checked the surroundings
when you made your way here.
There is no one else here, except you and me.
This proves I'm not trying to trick you.
Why would you think so?
You told me yourself.
When I mentioned that
I was the assassin's target
at the Mid-Autumn Festival banquet
you didn't seem surprised at all.
So, you started to be suspicious of me
since then.
You've always treated me exceptionally well.
And I know I don't stand apart from the others
so I can't help but have doubts about you.
I merely asked a casual question
but I heard something I wasn't expecting.
Since you asked to see me alone
I'm guessing you don't have evidence.
I still haven't figured out
what made you want to kill me.
Blame yourself
for overestimating your capabilities.
Since you already married Zhong Yelan
using some underhand means
why did you come and seduce Lord?
You're promiscuous and greedy.
How disgusting. I just can't stand it.
Look at all the people in Zhong's Garden.
Nobody likes you.
When did I seduce Zhong Xiwu?
Do you think I'm stupid?
After you got married, you became
a frequent guest at Zhong's Garden.
Soon, Lord started to look at you differently.
Lord has always valued his brotherhood
with Zhong Yelan.
If you hadn't deliberately seduced him
how could he ever have designs on you?
As you said, Zhong Xiwu had designs on me
but in the end, I was the one you wanted to kill?
What, you would only bully the weak?
If you were innocent
I would surely leave you alone.
But you, an abandoned woman
are still longing for a man
you could never have.
How could I stand by and watch you
create havoc in Zhong's Garden?
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at your duplicity.
You are obviously afraid that
I might steal your position
yet you said that you did it
for the sake of Zhong Xiwu's family.
Her Highness is still alive.
You're just a temporary resident in the house.
Who are you to maintain
the stability inside Zhong's Garden?
You think you're the daughter of a butler
of the Zhong family so that gives you status.
But the truth is, you're an abandoned wife.
Who are you to criticise me?
So what if I'm a temporary resident?
At least I am unmarried.
And Her Highness has me in mind
to be the future matriarch of the Zhong family.
You're wary of me
because you know that
I can trample on you
if I want to.
The matriarch of the Zhong family?
Get this.
You will never be able to assume that position.
You should thank me
for letting you off.
I have no interest in becoming
the matriarch of the Zhong family.
Since you did this to me
I was tempted to turn your fear
into reality.
You bitch...
I told you some facts and it crushed you.
It seems that your pampered life
has made you useless.
Such a slow reaction.
Are you waiting for me to turn my face
so you could slap me?
Let go...
Go on screaming
if you want your face to be disfigured.
—I dare you!                          —Sure!
Do you think that I'm a kind soul?
Now, get this!
It's because I have no interest in becoming
the matriarch of the Zhong family
and not because I'm afraid of you.
I look down
on the position you cherish so much.
Are you crazy?
Aren't you afraid that I will ask Lord
to dismiss Butler Hua
and drive you out of Huangcheng?
I'm afraid you won't have a chance to do so.
You did this to me
even Lord won't be able to protect you!
Believe it or not, whatever I do today
Zhong Xiwu will suppress it
and not pursue the matter.
Don't think that you will be safe and sound
just because your bastard brother
shielded you from the sword attack.
You and your family will die a horrible death
sooner or later!
You...
Blood...
If it wasn't for Zhong Xiwu
I wouldn't let you off so easily.
A scar in exchange for my brother's life.
That's a bargain for you.
One more toast to you.
Come on, Butler Zhang.
Master, tell Lord...
Lord...
Eat this.
This mushroom is rare.
Try it.
If you don't like these dishes
I'll take you out to eat something else
on our way home.
I'm afraid we won't have the chance.
Father, no matter what I do later on
I'm doing it to protect the Hua family.
Qian.
What are you doing?
Lord, Your Highness.
I have something to report.
What's the matter?
I plead guilty.
What crime did you commit?
The case of Mu Yunping's embezzlement
a year ago.
He was framed by my family.
Qian...
The confession letter of the missing Broker Qian
the contract between her and my family
and the signatures of the people involved...
I have them all here with me.
Bring them to me.
What's going on?
Concubine Mu, do you know about it?
Lord.
I'm just a woman
and don't know much about business.
Thanks to your benevolence
my father has left the city.
That matter is water under the bridge.
Butler Hua.
What do you have to say
about framing Butler Mu Yunping?
I plead guilty.
Detain Hua Wen'ang
and we will investigate this matter later.
Hua Qian.
I know you are a sensible person.
I'm right indeed.
You have set an example for women
by placing righteousness before family
so I will not punish you.
—In Zhong's garden...                 —Xiwu.
Lord, I have something else to say.
My father and Butler Mu were both
the butlers of the Zhong family.
They had worked together for a long time.
They cherished their relationship.
My father knew nothing.
I was behind it all.
All this happened because of my jealousy.
I used to be in love with Master.
I was petty and unwilling to share him
with someone else.
I hated Mu Yao and wanted to harm her.
So, I came up with a vicious scheme
to eradicate her family.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Everything I said is true.
I secretly bribed the men who worked
at the incense workshop
to replace agarwood incense
with inferior ones.
And with the help of the broker
whom I introduced to Mu Yao
I sent the furniture with agarwood wood incense
into Mu Residence.
Both Master and Mu Yao knew about this.
As they're benevolent, they let the matter slide.
But I couldn't rest at ease
holding on to the evidence
of my mistakes.
I've been eaten up with guilt
so I came here to plead guilty today.
Since you pleaded guilty voluntarily
we will detain you
and question you another day.
Are you going to question the Hua family here?
My father has been upright all his life
but no thanks to his good-for-nothing children
he got dragged down.
Lord, Your Highness. Please consider
my voluntary confession today
and not implicate my father.
I'm ready to bear all the punishment alone.
Silly girl.
How can I let my daughter
bear the mistakes I made?
Lord.
Your Highness.
Since Mu Yunping
the former butler of the Zhong family
was transferred from the north to Huangcheng
I became wary of him.
I was worried that
he might threaten my position.
Besides, we couldn't see eye to eye
about how we managed the shops.
So, we fought a lot.
And his workshops became increasingly
competitive against mine.
As time went by, I bore grudges against him
and couldn't get over them.
When I found out
that my daughter and Mu Yuping's daughter
were on close terms
I started from there.
Later on, I got someone
to expose the agarwood pills fraud
and instigated the regular customers
who bought them
to take Mu Yunping to the magistrate court.
Father, you...
Lord, I have been a butler for decades
but in the end, I was blinded by greed.
I disregarded right and wrong
and only focused on eradicating my enemies.
I couldn't careless about righteousness.
Even as a child
she understands the basic principles of ethics.
Qian had warned me several times
but I went ahead with my scheme.
She's kind-hearted
so she took the initiative to confess.
She intends to take the fall for me
out of filial piety.
No! It's not like that!
All the other butlers
knew about the frequent disputes
between Mu Yunping and I.
Now that I've come clean
please do as you deem fit, Lord.
No! It's not like that!
My father has nothing to do with it.
I fell in love with Master
and disliked Mu Yao
so I framed her and her family.
I was behind it all!
Lord, she's just a girl.
How could she set up such a meticulous trap?
You couldn't do it.
Bonus Footage
This is the busiest street in this town.
Look at the pond
and the flowers.
Here we are.
Take a look.
There are many knickknacks here.
Sir, what do you think of this house?
It's too noisy. She prefers a quieter place.
All right. Let me take you to another house.
Sir, this way, please.
This is the quietest house in this town.
What do you think?
Not good.
She's fond of gardening.
I think this place is remote, cold and dry.
Plants and trees cannot survive.
Are there more?
Yes. Let's go to the next one.
This won't do either.
She loves fresh fruit.
It's better if the house has a backyard
where fruit trees can be planted.
Are there more?
I'll bring you to view more.
How about this house?
This tree is really good.
It provides shade so she can sit under it.
She enjoys sitting in a reclining chair
under the eaves to daydream.
I can tie a swing for her under the tree.
It'll be more comfortable than a reclining chair.
Sir.
What do you think of it?
That is it.
All right.