MkvDrama.Org
Episode 27
Let me go.
Let me go!
What does this have to do with you?
I owe her a favour.
I'm just here to repay the debt.
Get someone to deliver it to...
Wu Shuomo.
What are you waiting for? Do it.
—Don't waste my time.                 —Miss.
I must return.
There's no one by her side now.
I must return!
Return?
And what can you do?
—I'll be with her and...      —Die together?
I'm not afraid of death.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Now, I get why she wrote
to ask me for this favour.
Miss Qi, Lord is busy.
I'm afraid he doesn't have time to see you.
I know that.
Miss Qi, you'd better not bother Lord now.
Your Highness.
—Miss Qi.                          —Miss Qi.
Lord, I...
—I need to talk to you.            —Get out.
I don't have time for your nonsense.
I just went to see Hua Qian.
Zhong Xiwu, like I said
we suffer the same fate.
You're destined to not get what you want.
Lord has passed down an order.
Qi Ruxin, the daughter of the Qi family
is narrow-minded and vicious.
Out of jealousy, she hurt
the daughter of the Meng family.
Considering her father's contributions
she's merely being driven
out of Zhong's Garden.
And her relatives are
not allowed to take her in.
Lord.
Take it away. I have no appetite.
Her Highness sent someone to deliver this.
It's your birthday today.
You'd better eat some, Lord.
Birthday?
That's right. Did you forget, Lord?
A month ago, you said that you wanted
to keep the celebration small and simple.
Her Highness sent people here
several times today
and you said you were busy
so Her Highness had someone bring
some food for you just now.
Lord, where are you going?
I brought some snacks.
Care to eat them with me?
Are you still angry with me?
I'm a sinner.
It's wrong of me to be angry.
Qian, I know you're unhappy lately...
So, you do know that I'm unhappy here.
Do you see that you're forcing me
to do something that I don't want to do?
Qian, why won't you relent?
Zhong Xiwu, this is meaningless.
Either let me go or kill me.
And I'm never one of your options, am I?
Zhong's Garden is never short of women
be it now or the future.
It's too crowded for me.
But what if I only want you?
Can you give up
being Lord of the Zhong family for me?
You can't
because your future has been mapped out
to be Lord of the Zhong family since birth.
Indeed.
As long as I could remember, I have never
stopped learning how to be a good lord.
You are the only exception.
I was indeed sounding you out at first
but over time, I began to know the real you.
Rumours and hearsay cannot be trusted.
It's hard to meet another woman
who is as clear-headed and kind as you.
I couldn't control my emotions.
I followed my heart.
You know all that.
Why did you force me to choose?
Is that a joke, Lord?
Who is forcing who in this situation?
I told you to expose Butler Hua
because I wanted you to draw the line...
You're ignoring what I said
so I don't want to listen to you as well.
You really don't care about anything anymore?
Even the guard that you sent away?
What do you mean?
So, you'll listen to me now?
What did you mean by that?
Do you think I could do nothing about it
just because you sent him away
and got someone to protect him?
Are you threatening me?
Does he mean that much
to you?
If you harm him...
I will...
You said you were afraid of death
but you jumped off the cliff for my senior
took the rap for Butler Hua
and now, you even threaten to harm me
because of that guard.
Qian, you're not afraid of death.
You just don't love me.
You just...
don't love me.
Let go...
It's my birthday today.
"I've cooked soup for the man I love.
I look forward to him tasting it."
I have been looking forward
to your birthday noodles
but now it seems...
I'm not meant to have them.
Don't worry.
I never had the intention
to hurt the people you care about.
What happened to your hand?
Lord...
I'll go get a physician.
Don't.
Don't let anyone know about this.
But, Lord, your hand is injured.
Go get me some wine.
—Lord...                             —Do it!
—Madam Wu.                     —Steward Gao.
Her Highness sent me here
to collect the food box.
Lord is busy with work.
He doesn't want anyone to disturb him.
It's only a food box.
I'll get someone to return it to Her Highness
when Lord is done.
Never mind the food box
but Her Highness is worried about Lord's health.
She insisted that I came here
to check if he had eaten dinner.
Her Highness won't be happy
if I go back empty-handed.
How about this? Please wait here.
I'll go inside and take out the food box.
I'm fine if Lord gets mad at me.
Thank you, Steward Gao.
I owe you a favour.
Hearing that the food was sent by Her Highness
whetted his appetite.
He finished them all very quickly.
That's great.
I'll go back and report this to Her Highness.
Take care, Madam Wu.
Are you sure?
Yes, Your Highness.
I am sure.
I will not tolerate her anymore.
Greetings, Your Highness. I'm Yinxing.
—Take her away.                        —Yes.
Your Highness...
Spare the formalities.
You have no respect for me anyway.
Do you remember what you promised me?
Why are you still entangled with Lord?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
Can't you see it, Your Highness?
If I had wanted that
I wouldn't be imprisoned here.
Answer me.
Lord got injured last night. Did it happen here?
—Yes, it did.                 —How dare you!
It was unintentional. He forced my hand.
Fine.
Do you know what I'm here for?
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry for
not appreciating your kindness, Your Highness.
I only ask that you spare the lives of my family
and I will be eternally grateful.
You're a filial daughter.
I will spare Butler Hua's life.
I'm not a filial daughter.
Consider carefully what to say
and what not to say.
Father...
Father!
—I did it all alone.                —Father!
Don't worry.
I never had the intention
to harm the people you care about.
Miss, remember to look for me soon
or I will come back for you.
All right. Be safe.
I tried to change the course of my life
but the outcome didn't change.
But at least some of them survived.
Your Highness.
Get rid of her.
Make sure no one sees this.
Men.
Make sure no one sees you.
Get rid of this too.
Yes, Your Highness.
Master...
I've told you umpteen times.
Stay composed no matter what.
Master, Lord...
Speak clearly.
Is Lord... inside?
Lord had a drop too much yesterday.
He has a headache and is still sleeping.
Everything else has to wait.
But, Master, I saw...
I saw Her Highness going...
to that compound.
Lord!
—Lord!                              —Master.
Lord...
Lord!
—Hurry!                              —Water!
—Somebody!                       —Let me go!
This way.
—Here it comes.             —Douse the fire!
—This way!                        —Somebody!
—Let me go.                       —This way.
Miss!
Come out!
—Coming!                              —Miss!
Over here!
—Watch out!                      —Let me go!
—Hurry up!               —Make way.
—Qian!                                —Lord!
—Qian!                              —Lord...
The fire is out of control. You can't enter!
Lord!
—Miss!                                —Lord!
—Lord...                              —Qian.
—Qian!                                —Lord!
—Men!                      —Lord, I checked.
—Qian!                   —No more survivors!
Qian! Men...
Lord!
—Men!                                 —Lord!
There are no more survivors.
Qian!
—Let go of me!                        —Lord!
You can't go in there.
Qian!
There are no more survivors.
Qian...
She's still in there.
Somebody help!
Help her!
Please. Somebody, save her.
Where's Chen Yuan?
—Her Highness just left.          —This way.
Come on. Give it to me.
Miss...
Can someone please help me?
—This way.                       —Let me go.
—You can't go in there.          —Let me go!
Let me go.
Miss...
Let me stay with my lady.
Let me go.
Miss...
You terrible servants!
How could you let Lord come out
in a dishevelled state?
Quit slacking or you'll be executed.
Please forgive us, Your Highness.
Mother, why did you do that?
Can't I punish the servants
for their poor performance?
You know I'm not referring to this.
I thought you liked Hua Qian as much as I did.
Now it seems that I was wrong.
I'm the only one who wants her safe
in Zhong's Garden.
Leave us.
You like her, so what?
As Lord of the Zhong family
you're not free to do as you please.
You've been telling me this since I was little.
I'm sick and tired...
of hearing it.
Have I been too obedient?
Should I start getting into trouble like some
so that you won't be so strict with me?
Haven't you been creating havoc lately?
You kept the daughter of the Hua family here
for a long time. And I put up with it.
I also turned a blind eye to you
driving Qi Ruxin away
because I trusted that you could handle it well.
And what did you do?
You got hurt
and tried to hide the incident from me.
You should know that
I did all of this for your own good.
I did it for your own good.
I was afraid that you would not believe it
so I got Chen Yuan to bring the Li couple here
to testify against him.
I was worried that
Qi Rongzhou might get mad and hurt you
so I came to see you.
You thought Hua Rongzhou might hurt me.
Is that the real reason why you're here?
Why can't you see that
I'm doing this for your own good?
I hope one day
you can understand the true meaning...
of these words.
That is...
how she felt when she heard these words.
Xiwu.
Mother.
I only wanted to be with the woman I love.
Why can't you let me have what I want?
It's because you're Lord of the Zhong family.
You represent the entire family.
Stop trembling.
You're spilling the medicine.
Do you know how expensive it is?
Master.
I have not done such chores before.
Let me do it.
I'm just throwing away my money.
He won't eat or drink
so I have to spend so much money
buying expensive herbs
to nurse him back to health.
This man may look young
but he is tough.
He would make a good spy.
I think he can endure the torture
if he's caught.
It's a pity
that he doesn't work for me.
Master.
What did you say? She died?
Yes. The pigeon messengers sent the news.
Word hasn't gotten out yet.
Master.
It seems that the Hua family did not
to rat us and the Ge family out
so we don't have to do their bidding anymore.
You're stating the obvious!
They are not stupid.
Which is worse? Framing his peer
or conspiring with the enemy?
Surely he would confess
to the lesser of two evils.
She's a ruthless woman.
I don't believe she's dead.
Are you sure this is not a setup?
I'm sure it's not.
Her Highness saw to it herself.
It's of grave importance.
The spies had verified it before reporting.
What a pity.
If she wanted me to return the favour
by asking me to rescue her
I might not turn her down.
But she wasted such a precious chance
on this wolf guy.
She probably overanalysed the situation.
Let's pack up and leave.
Just leave him here.
Since she's dead
I no longer need to keep my promise.
So, we'll just... leave him here?
What, do you want to take care of him?
Huangcheng is full of odd characters.
I'd better stay far away from here
and not get involved anymore.
Hua Residence
What do you want?
I'm one of the guards of the Hua family.
Her Highness has passed down an order.
The Hua family is imprisoned.
No one can enter or leave without permission.
Where is Hua Qian?
Is she in there too?
Miss Hua took the rap for her father.
She set herself on fire ten days ago
in Zhong's Garden.
Set herself on fire?
Where's Hua Qian?
Who... are you?
The nerve of you to come here.
Chen Yuan.
Don't kill him.
Throw him out.
Where is she?
Where are you hiding her?
She died.
It's impossible.
Why is it impossible?
Even though I'm Lord of the Zhong family
I'm unable to protect everyone...
in Zhong's Garden.
You were unable to protect her.
Since you were unable to protect her
then why did you...
force her to stay here?
I really don't know what she saw in you.
How could you trap her in such a place?
I will give you a chance.
On the fifth day of every month
you're free to come here.
If you can defeat my guards
then we will talk about...
her.
Do you mean...
Why do you treasure such a tattered sachet?
Xin?
Am I dreaming?
Do you still think it is a dream?
Why are you here?
I caused the wound on Meng Yifei's face.
What do you want?
Freedom.
Think about it.
If Hua Qian is charged with assault
even if the Meng family doesn't pursue it
she will never be able to marry you.
I'm here to take the fall without being asked.
As far as I know
you used to hate Hua Qian.
Why would you do this for her?
Things are different now.
I know someone is waiting for me.
Zhong Xiwu is such a petty man.
I made some sarcastic remarks about him
so he ordered that my relatives
were not to take me in.
I've lost everything for your sake.
So...
are you able to provide for me?
Of course!
I'm picky about food.
I'll cook for you.
I'm picky about my living condition, too.
I'll save up and buy a house.
I have never done any household chores.
I will do everything.
If you're going to do everything
what will I do?
You can just...
be my wife.
Qian.
Bonus footage
Why does Lord always
carry medicine with him too?
I didn't notice.
I don't know when Lord started doing this.
You said "too". Why is that?
Miss Hua used to carry a pouch with her.
There was a small bottle of medicine inside it
which looked quite similar to Lord's.
Maybe our masters
are more thoughtful than us servants.
Steward Gao, what's wrong?
Don't mention this to Lord.
What?
About Miss Hua carrying
a medicine bottle with her.
Why?
It hurts too much.
It's easier for him to get over her
if he doesn't know that
the feelings were mutual.