Does anyone here ever even care about me?
You were off together all happy and content.
Did you even think about me?
Then you can both choke to death on your happiness!
Don’t worry.
Everything will turn out alright.
Do you like me?
Yes, I like you.
For the longest time.
Are you happy now?
Then stop liking me.
It’s impossible between us.
What do you think you’re doing speaking to my granddaughter that way?
What do you mean?
Grandpa, I think...
You are dating my granddaughter.
Then how could you say that to Inn?
I’m not dating Inn.
But...
If you two have problems, you should talk about them later.
Don’t you see that Inn is seriously injured?
You should leave.
You can’t leave yet.
What did you mean by what you just said?
I’m not dating Inn. We’re just friends.
There’s no way that I will date her.
What about what you told me last time?
What I said to you last time, I was talking about...
I think we should let Inn rest. She doesn’t look okay.
Inn, is it true, what Namcha just said?
Is it true?
Grandpa, I’m begging you.
Please stop talking about it for now.
Please go home.
I have something I need to tell you.
I don’t want any further misunderstandings.
I...
Get out!
Get out, all of you!
Otherwise, I’ll kill myself.
Get out!
I think we should leave.
I hope you understand what I said.
Pechaya "Min" Wattanamontree
Metawin "Win" Opas-iamkajorn
Kanyarat "Piploy" Ruangrung
Suphakorn "Pod" Sriphotong
Nirut Sirichanya/Apasiri Nitibhon/Phollawat Manuprasert
Ploi Horwang/Kanticha Chumma/Phatchatorn Thanawat
Directed by Ekkasit Trakulkasemsuk and Pantip Vibultham
Inn told me that she was dating Namcha.
How come things turn out like this?
I don’t know either.
Kids these days are like this.
Their relationship is always on-and-off.
If something upsets them, they usually make a big deal out of it.
They aren’t patient.
You don’t need to worry about it.
I think they will make up in a few days.
Inn is still hospitalized.
This is not okay.
How can she date someone unreliable?
How did his family raise him?
Why did he grow up and become like this?
I guess he doesn’t take his work seriously as well.
I think so.
It’s a relief that he was not my grandson.
Stay away from this kind of man.
He’s not diligent and also gets other people off the track.
Tell Inn to stop seeing him.
Why did you tell him that?
Tell him what?
About Namcha.
You shouldn’t say things that mislead my grandpa about him.
I think I didn’t say anything that is not true.
I saw you are working hard for the company
but he seems to be playing around.
I’m not even sure if he is still working.
To be honest, I think he’s not the right man for you.
Thank you for your advice.
But I think you should mind your own business.
Why are you smiling?
What is so funny about what I said?
I think Inn is right about you and Namcha.
What do you mean?
I just wanted to see
if you would be upset if I talked negatively about Namcha.
This is what I saw.
You know that people usually protect what they love.
But I’m not someone who gives up easily.
I’m going to prove to you how sincere I am to you.
Sincere?
Those who are sincere don’t talk behind other people’s backs like this.
I don’t know what kind of things you said to other people about me.
Twisting things from wrong to right or right to wrong.
I guess this is what people in your occupation are trained to do.
Don’t call the truth a gossip.
If what I said is untrue, it’s your job to prove it to others.
That’s unfair.
Someone says bad things about me
but I’m the one who has to prove that it’s untrue.
What about the person who bad-mouths me and damages my reputation?
What kind of responsibility does he take?
I wouldn’t feel anything if those words
came from a jealous or competitive child.
Instead, they came out of the mouth of
a man who has claimed to be an adult.
I think you can no longer call me a child.
I never thought that you would want to
defeat me so much that you took the low road.
That’s enough.
You should leave.
That’s too many problems already.
But I need to talk to you.
But I have nothing to say to you.
But I have.
You can’t force Irin to do what you want.
Do you want me to say it here?
Say it in front of other people.
Or should I say it when your grandfather is present?
Cha, I’m begging you.
Then come with me to talk.
You don’t need to go anyway. I’ll get you out of here.
You have gone through many stressful things today.
You don’t need to listen to him.
I need to talk to him.
What?
I was so worried about you.
Cha, let me go.
You must feel terrible.
It’s alright. I’m here for you.
No matter how hard you try to get rid of me or run away from me,
I’ll always be by your side.
So stop blaming yourself.
It wasn’t your fault.
Help me.
I’m in here. Anyone, please help me.
She always pretended to be sick.
She kept making excuses to avoid working on group homework.
If she keeps taking advantage of others like this,
she should change to homeschooling.
Are you alright?
Don’t cry.
Are you going to eat it all by yourself?
I thought you like to do things and go anywhere alone.
Next time, don’t go anywhere alone.
Then who should I go with?
No one wants to be my friend.
Then don’t go anywhere without me. Okay?
Good.
Try it.
You’re so stingy.
- Give me some more. - Stop taking my snack.
Why did you come home so early? I thought you had a tutorial class today.
I feel a bit unwell.
Are you alright?
I’m alright.
Did mom and dad know?
I don’t think we need to tell them. I’m feeling much better now.
Hello, Irin.
Do you remember Namcha? He lives next door to us.
Namcha?
You’ve grown up so abundant that I can’t recognize you.
I haven’t seen you for years.
I was studying overseas as an exchange student.
I remember that Tan told me about it.
But I always remember you.
Alright. Then I won’t bother you anymore.
Okay.
Does Irin have a boyfriend?
I don’t think so. I’ve never seen her like any guy.
Why did you ask?
Nothing.
How are you feeling?
I was shocked after Irin told me that you are admitted to the hospital.
Why did you two come together?
He wants to visit you. So I gave him a ride.
How did he know that I’m in the hospital?
Where did you two meet?
He went to see you at our house.
Your IV drip is almost empty. I’ll go tell the nurse.
I’ll let you two talk.
What happened? Why did you end up in the hospital?
My condition suddenly got worse.
Where were you yesterday? I tried to call you but I couldn’t reach you.
Are you feeling better?
I think I will be discharged tomorrow.
That’s good.
Why? What do you want to say?
I have a favor to ask you.
What is it?
It’s about Irin.
Why? Did Irin do something bad to you?
It’s not like that.
Then what is it?
I like Irin.
I want you to help me so I can date her.
Then why are you...
I have had a crush on her for a long time since I was young.
The more I get to know her, the cuter I think she is.
Can you help me?
Can you give this to Irin?
Why don’t you give it to her yourself?
Please help me and give this to her.
Irin, this is from Namcha.
Thanks.
Do I have to be dead to get your attention, Namcha?
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Inn?
I should have died.
When will you stop hurting yourself?
Your condition isn’t bad enough?
Why should I live? No one wants me to live.
I do.
I won’t let you go anywhere.
I’ve always been defeated all my life.
I don’t want to lose anymore.
Trust me.
I’ll help you win.
I have never lost in my entire life.
I can’t do this.
You know that Inn...
I can’t hurt her feelings.
What about my feelings?
Don’t you care about me?
I’m sorry.
Even though you run away from me like the last time,
it doesn’t mean Inn will get what she wants.
It’s true that Inn will feel hurt.
But it’s not my fault that I don’t love her.
It’s neither your fault.
Inn is an adult.
She needs to find her own way to be happy.
She shouldn’t expect other people to sacrifice themselves for her happiness.
You also have the right to be happy.
I will never let you run away again.
What happened?
Let’s go talk outside.
Suicide?
Yes.
Luckily, I found her in time. So nothing bad happened.
Don’t worry.
The nurse has dressed her wound.
I also told the hospital to send a psychologist to see her.
I feel bad for Inn.
How hopeless she must have felt
to decide to hurt herself to make people aware of her existence?
I feel sorry for her.
Did Inn say that to you?
Yes.
Her mental is very weak right now.
I’m worried that she might attempt to do it again.
We might not be lucky like this time.
It’s true that Inn will feel hurt.
But it’s not my fault that I don’t love her.
It’s neither your fault.
Inn is an adult.
She needs to find her own way to be happy.
She shouldn’t expect other people to sacrifice themselves for her happiness.
You also have the right to be happy.
Why do things have to turn out this way?
Why?
What should I do?
Let’s go!
Are you crazy?
You cannot ride motorcycles on this road.
Don’t think about running away.
I’ll call the police to arrest you.
There are many CCTV cameras around here.
Are you alright?
Why did you do that?
If you jumped like that, you would get hurt.
Are you alright?
I’m alright.
How would you be alright?
This is the real world, not fiction. You shouldn’t play the hero here.
I already got hurt. Do you need to scold me too?
Yes. How could you do that without thinking?
There are many other ways to help me.
It’s the media’s fault. They present the wrong way to help people.
Don’t do anything like this again. It’s very dangerous.
Do you hear me?
Why are you laughing?
If it was other girls, they would have thanked me for it.
But you...
What do you mean?
Are you criticizing me? Why are you so rude to me?
You are very cute.
Cute? I’m seven years older than you.
I think you should go see a doctor and take a look at your wound.
I’m alright. I’ll be fine because you are treating my wound.
You’re talking nonsense.
I mean it.
We are living next door
but we don’t have many chances to talk to each other.
Does it matter?
I want to get to know you better.
Cha, why didn’t you call and tell me that you would come to see me?
I...
What happened to your arm?
Does it hurt?
Irin.
Cha.
What a coincidence?
Can I join you?
Sure.
How is it?
Irin.
Irin, can I ride with you?
Cha, did you get the tickets?
Yes.
Why did you book seats in the front row?
Do you want to taste it?
(Irin)
I won’t let you run away from me again.
I’ll fix this problem myself.
She’s so stupid.
Why did she hurt herself for a guy like him?
I think Inn is pitiful.
She’s pathetic.
I have only one granddaughter and she is acting like this.
How would I trust her to run the company?
Only granddaughter?
What do you mean?
Nothing. I said it wrong.
What did he say?
I’m not sure if Namcha knows about it.
Good. That’s good.
Don’t let him know what Inn did.
But I think he should know what kind of impact his action caused.
Do you want my family to feel embarrassed?
Do you want other people to know what my granddaughter did?
Alright.
Are you going to visit Inn at the hospital today?
No. I would be upset if I went.
She has a psychiatrist taking care of her.
Yes.
Hello.
Irin, are you still at the hospital?
No, I’m at the office now.
Today, I have a meeting about a new project.
Did you get any sleep?
What’s going on?
I thought that you were still at the hospital.
So I thought I would go and pick you up.
I thought you didn’t get much sleep. I didn’t want you to drive.
If you are not busy today, can you go and take care of Inn for me?
I don’t want to leave her alone at the hospital.
Sure, I’ll take good care of her. Don’t worry.
Thank you.
Irin.
Yes.
Please take care of yourself.
I don’t want to see you feel too stressed.
Thank you.
I have to go to work now. I’m hanging up.
Alright.
Please take care of yourself.
I don’t want to see you feel too stressed.
How did you get in?
I opened the door and walked in.
Do you want me to call the police and have you arrested for trespassing?
Call the police? But this is not your house.
One more thing, I always come to this house.
No one seems to have a problem with it.
I think you are the problem here.
I’m pretty sure that
I have never caused problems to anyone like you did.
Really?
Then what did you say to Irin last night?
Suicide?
Yes.
Luckily, I found her in time. So nothing bad happened.
Don’t worry.
The nurse has dressed her wound.
I feel bad for Inn.
Her mental is very weak right now.
I’m worried that she might attempt to do it again.
We might not be lucky like this time.
You said all those things to stress her out
so she would end her relationship with me.
But today you said you are worried about her.
You also act like this when you are with her grandfather.
When you are with him, you pretend to be a gentleman.
But you talked negatively about me behind my back.
I guess you are acting like this with everyone.
You are acting like a chameleon that keeps changing its colors.
Your words keep changing when you are with different people.
I think you have too much prejudice against me.
Only children would act so petty like this.
Even if you tell anyone about it, no one will listen to you.
Really?
I’m not surprised that you would deny it.
But I believe that whether it’s a big or small deal,
people will use the same mindset to judge it.
I’ll wait for the day when the things that you did
will turn into big problems.
I don’t think that day would ever arrive.
I think you should be the one who needs to be careful.
What you did might turn into a big problem.
What are you doing here?
I’m asking you what you are doing here.
I came to see you.
Has no one taught you that you need to make an appointment
before going to see someone?
It’s rude to not do so.
I have the truth that I need to explain to you.
You should spend your time talking to me to do your work.
It’s almost time for your shift, isn’t it?
Is your father okay that his only son doesn’t show up at work?
You told me that I should respect and follow the tradition.
So I’m here to tell you what I think you should know.
I didn’t know what kind of person you are
I hate a loser like you.
Whatever.
Since you weren’t dating Inn, I don’t want to have anything to do with you.
You should stay in your place and away from my granddaughters.
If your family didn’t teach you about this, I would do it myself.
A fresh graduate should pay attention to their work to secure their job.
They shouldn’t pay attention to nonsense stuff like you.
Stop getting other people off their track.
But I think some adults are not much better than me.
He falls for other people’s words
and believes that I’m like what he’s heard.
Namcha!
I’ll take you to your workroom.
A kid like him might not understand what you said.
This is such a waste of time.
Grandpa, please wait and see.
I’ll prove to you that I’m different from what he has told you.
Hey, baby.
What are you looking at?
I’ll give you all the details and advice you need.
Sure.
PJ Professional Dog Training
will provide training both at home and at our facility.
(Your brother is meeting with a girl.)
Hello, Irin. What’s up?
Are you calling to scold me about my brother?
No, it’s not about that.
Did you talk to Cha about the woman?
Yes.
What did he say?
Um...do you want to talk to him? He’s here with me.
What?
Sis.
Take a look at this.
This is the project I want to do with our hospital.
How can you be sure that it will work?
I’ll do everything I can to make it work.
So people would stop calling me an incompetent kid.
Irin wants to launch the book and make it the talk of the town.
I’m sorry for being late.
I won’t risk my company with a kid like him.
If you hate me that much,
you should speed up your recovery and compete with me.
If you can beat me, I will give you whatever you want.
Don’t forget your promise that you will give me anything.
You can cry as much as you want.
I’m here for you.
When you are with me, you can do whatever you can.
But please don’t run away from me.