-So glad, it passed right?
-Yes, I'm so glad.
-Let's go have some chicken and beer.
-Yes. I would love that!
Suyeon.
Hey, Wooshik.
You are here early today.
Yes, I no longer need
to go five o'clock live.
-What are you looking at?
-Well...
Because I envy them.
Envy of what?
Those women,
they seem like my age. And they
already got a job and do what they like.
They are stepping forward.
I don't know how long do I need
to live by working as a part time.
It's not like I have something
I want to do nor am good at.
So I'm just feeling little stuffy.
I see.
Right.
Didn't you say,
you want to be a news anchor?
I do, but...
...being an anchor is not an easy job.
How am I going to become now?
Why? They have an academy for anchor.
You can enroll and prepare.
And how am I going to pay for it?
It's fine.
I will head inside first.
Three million won per three months?
Why is it so expensive?
Kibong, where are you going?
Of course, I'm going for the training...
Right... I got kicked out.
It became my habit.
I should get more sleep.
Gosh, seriously...
How am I going to get the money?
I should think after getting some sleep.
Why did you do it to me?
Tell me.
Why did you do it?
You humiliate me.
Don't joke with me.
Tell me the real reason.
Tell me.
What did you do it to me?
Say something!
Wow! Byunghun's acting
is really amazing, right?
How can you watch a movie at this moment?
Aren't you worried that
Kibong has been kicked out?
He was crying his eyes out in the
corner of the room few days ago.
Really?
I'm worried.
He hasn't been eating these days.
Well, I have no choice.
I should step out.
Guys, I will make sure Kibong
to gain his strength back.
-Just trust me.
-Trust what?
You always cause trouble,
whenever you say that!
-Just don't do anything, please!
-I'm telling you,
I have my own way. Just trust me!
Wait for me.
What kind of trouble are
you going to make this time?
Tell me.
Yes.
What happened to the event that I asked?
Today?
One million won?
Okay, got it. I will be there.
Okay, thanks!
What do you mean event?
-You said, you would never do event.
-I have my reason.
-See you!
-Tell me.
Tell me where are you going.
What kind of event are we having in here?
-Is it an opening ceremony?
-No.
-It's my boss's wife's birthday.
-Pardon?
You guys are having her
birthday party in the pub?
Wow.
I guess you guys are very open minded.
Let's hurry.
I told you,
you shouldn't have done it.
Don't be scared.
We just had a small problem.
-Let's go.
-Yes.
Sir, the singer has arrived!
Hello, you are here.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kim Yongpal.
Hello.
Wait,
Kim Yongpal?
I've heard it before.
Where did I hear it before?
Don't tell me...
Kim Yongpal of Yongpal gang?
You have watched the news, have you?
Don't trust it.
I'm just...
...a hard working business man.
Yes, boss.
I mean, sir.
Today is my wife's birthday,
whom I love more than myself.
Please sing well for us,
and make her happy.
My wife likes music very much.
Yes, yes. Don't worry.
Madam has arrived.
Really?
Honey!
You are here.
-Ta-da!
-Welcome, madam!
Oh, my. Are you all here for my birthday?
How sweet.
Have you cut your hair, Dongsu?
-It's so cute!
-Thank you, ma'am.
Shave his head.
Sorry... I'm sorry, sir!
I just cut it because it was too long.
I didn't know it will turn out this cute!
I will cut it again, sir!
Please save me. I'm so sorry, sir!
What is wrong with you again?
-I just said it was nice.
-Just?
The way he looked at you
was wicked since before.
Now,
don't mind him and let's party.
Gee, you are driving me crazy.
Right.
He is...
...a singer to sing for you.
-Say hello.
-Really?
-Nice to meet you.
-Hello.
Are you...
...Shiva Wooshik?
You are Shiva Wooshik of Taj Mahal, right?
What? Yes, yes.
-How do you know me?
-Oh my god, it's me!
I'm president of Taj Mahal, Kang Miyoung!
Nickname is Shiva lover!
Shiva Wooshik lover!
-Don't you remember me?
-Wait, Shiva lover...
Miyoung?
Yes, that's right! How long has it been?
Oh my god, yes! How long has it...
It's been a long time, madam!
Gee, don't call me that.
Anyway, it's so good to see you!
I can't believe it's real!
Hey, Kibong.
How long are you going to be like this?
You need to eat something! You are
really going to die due to starvation.
It' doesn't matter.
I can't even play baseball no more.
-I'd rather die.
-What?
Are you saying it for real, you jerk?
All I have been doing was playing
baseball, since I was young.
Baseball is all I have.
But I can no longer play it.
I can't play forever.
Do you even understand how I feel?
-Still... Kibong.
-Never mind.
Stop bothering me and leave.
-I said, leave.
-Kibong, don't be like that.
I bought some dessert. Have some.
I bought it from hand-made chocolate shop.
If you eat this,
it will make your worries gone
because it's too delicious.
What?
Do you really think this
chocolate will make me feel better?
I can't even swallow single grain of rice.
-It feels like I'm chewing sand.
-Okay, I got it.
If you just have one,
I will bother you no more.
You promise?
You will leave, if I just eat one.
Unbelievable. What do you think of me?
This is good.
It's so good!
How can it be this good?
I don't know if chocolate is
melting or my tongue is melting.
This is incredible. Truly amazing.
The taste is actually
melting all my worries away.
How is it? Isn't it good?
-You actually feel better, right?
-What?
It's just so-so.
Really?
That's weird.
-Everyone felt better after this.
-Told you, it won't work.
How can he feel better with only this?
Do you really think he's
some simple-minded idiot?
Sorry.
Shall I leave it here,
so that you can have it?
Gosh, don't! He obviously
doesn't have a mood for this.
Let's just leave him rest. Let's go.
Go. Get some rest, Kibong.
-Get some rest.
-Okay.
Darn it.
-Wow!
-This chocolate is really good.
-You are right.
It really makes me feel good.
Right?
But it doesn't work for Kibong.
I wonder how sad he is.
-Hey, Kibong. Do you need something?
-No...
-I just want to drink water.
-Here it is. Drink and get some rest.
What?
They already ate it all?
Cheap jerks.
I want it.
I want it too.
I really want to eat.
It's bit embarrassing to ask for one now.
What should I do?
-What the!
-Oh, dear.
I made a mistake.
It's okay. We can just wipe it.
Jungi, get some rag.
Sure.
Gee, it's all wet.
Wipe it with this first.
Kibong, we will take care of it.
Go and get some rest.
Where did he go?
That was good.
It was so natural.
Shall I try it now?
Gee, you startled me.
What are you doing in front of the door?
You scared me.
I was just...
Why didn't you knock?
Isn't it weird to knock
on the door for my room?
Gee...
Let's see. Where did I put it?
Where did it go?
-Hey, get a good rest.
-Sure.
Oh, geez. What is it?
Almost stepped on it.
What is it?
It's a chocolate. Why is it here?
Don't tell me,
-did you bring to eat it?
-Well...
No!
You are right.
-You said, you have no appetite.
-Of course.
-I will throw it. Give it to me.
-Will you?
Why do you want to throw it?
It will be a waste! I should eat it.
Gosh, it's so sweet.
Darn it.
You are still the same as before, Wooshik.
-You are still handsome.
-Gosh.
No, I'm not.
It was my dream to marry you.
What do you like about that jerk?
What do you like about that gentleman?
Of course, it's because of singing.
Wooshik is really good at it.
Singing, you say?
-I am good at singing too.
-Well,
you are good but you can't
beat Wooshik with it.
Is that so?
Shall we compete with our singing skill?
-Let's bet on our finger.
-Fi... Finger?
Don't be too scared.
-It was a joke.
-I see...
The winner gets to finger
flick on loser's forehead.
What do you say?
-I don't think that's a good idea...
-What are you doing? Get things ready.
-Yes, boss!
I will...
...start first.
-You know my wife's favorite song, right?
-Yes, sir.
"Fire by Blackpink"
Well, you need to practice more.
"Point 65"
What a shame.
You got 65 points.
Well now, it's Wooshik's turn!
I'm in trouble.
He is overly jealous.
My life will be in danger, if I win.
I need to lose no matter what.
What kind of song do I need to choose?
Yes, this is it.
"Hen pheasant hunt by Kim Serena"
Full score! Congratulations!
Chocolate box should be around here.
Gosh, I should have
checked the name of the store.
Stupid, stupid!
Oh god!
What are you doing over there?
Why are you looking into rubbish?
I need to look for something.
By the way,
where did you throw...
...the chocolate box you guys had?
Oh, that sweet stuff!
-Why are you looking for it?
-What?
I think it's a perfect
size for name cards.
Name cards.
-But you don't have any.
-I might in the future!
-You think I will live as jobless forever?
-I'm not saying that.
Hey, when you get a job,
I will buy you a name card wallet.
-Don't worry, you jerk.
-Hey!
What name card wallet?
It's all waste! Waste!
If we keep the box, we can save the trees,
reduce waste, solve global warming.
How wonderful is that?
So where is the box?
I put it outside for
garbage truck to pick up.
-Outside where?
-What do you mean?
They already picked up,
when I went outside.
What?
Why did you put it out so early?
-Do you even think?
-What?
How can you not think about Earth?
You jerk!
-You clean this up!
-Why should I... Hey!
Why is he scolding me over throwing a box?
Gosh, I'm going crazy!
Why did he throw it away?
I'm dying to have one.
How am I going to buy one when I
don't even know the name of the store?
Right.
Yuri bought that chocolate.
Yuri should know the name!
The caller is unavailable right now.
What? Why isn't she picking up?
Why isn't she picking up? Darn it!
He's really pissed off. I'm sure of it.
Should I just run away?
What about Suyeon's academy fee?
Gosh, this is insane!
Right, Wooshik.
Do you remember when we
went to camp with members?
Yes?
Yes. I remember.
We did Pirate Roulette
with 40 club members.
And you never caught
once and won the game.
-Did I?
-Yes, you did!
You are so handsome but lucky as well!
Really? You are lucky, aren't you?
I, myself is pretty lucky too.
I have been...
...stabbed about 40 times.
And I'm still alive.
I... I see.
You are...
...incredible.
Why don't we compete on our luck?
This time,
-loser gets 10 flicks.
-10 flicks?
-I don't know. I don't really...
-What are you guys doing?
-Set it up right now.
-Yes, boss!
I must lose this time.
I must lose no matter what.
If I win again, today will be my last day.
Then,
who should be the first?
Roulette game!
It's a game of probability.
The person who starts
first is advantageous.
If then...
Why don't you start first, sir?
We need to follow the order of seniority.
Sure.
I will start to stab.
Yes, that's right!
No one can lose in the beginning
unless he's an unlucky fool.
My life comes before money.
-I need to get out of here.
-Hey!
Singer boy.
Where are you going in a
hurry without saying a word?
Yes? Well, I just....
I think I didn't turn off the gas range.
But you still need to end things with me.
What do you mean end?
-You seriously don't know?
-Please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
Stop right there!
I need to give you the event cost!
I'm back.
Are they all sleeping?
Gee, I'm so tired.
I should get some sleep.
-Oh, gosh. You scared me!
-Yuri.
Where have you been?
I was doing my research of
market for Yuri's Kitchen.
What's wrong?
Why didn't you answer my call?
Do you know how many
times I have called you?
Sorry.
My battery was out.
Do you have something to say to me?
Well...
The chocolate you gave me,
-where did you buy it from?
-What?
-Why are you asking?
-I want to get some of the boxes.
-I don't have place to put my name cards.
-Name cards?
-You don't have name cards.
-I might have one in the future!
Why does everyone think I
will live as jobless forever?
-Am I that incompetent?
-No. It's not like that.
-When you get a job, I will buy you...
-I said, it's a waste! Waste!
It's a destruction of environment!
So what is the name of the store?
Tell me the name of the store right now!
Why are you getting angry at me?
Then,
can't you use other box?
I have a box around that size...
It's because I like the design
and the color of that box, okay?
Why do you talk so much?
Just tell me the name, name!
Okay, okay.
Okay, I heard you.
I will message you the name
and address of that store.
Okay.
By the way, are they still opened?
I want to know their operation hour.
-Do you want to go now?
-Yes.
Of course they are closed.
It's already late.
You should have come home early!
Send the text right now. Gosh!
Why is he getting mad at a small thing?
What's wrong with you?
If someone looks for me, tell them
I'm gone. No, I've immigrated. Okay?
Gosh, you scared me.
Brother,
-why are you doing down there?
-Yuri,
can you pass me a milk?
By the way,
has anyone come and look for me?
No one.
What is wrong with you seriously?
-Did something happen at the event?
-What?
No, it's nothing.
-Where is Suyeon?
-She has no appetite.
Suyeon looks down these days.
I wonder if she has worries.
Where did Kibong go
without having a breakfast?
Finally I can get to eat it. Finally!
Chocolate that is moisture on the outside
and full of sweetness in the inside.
This is the place!
What is this?
"Odiv Belgium Chocolate Store"
-Excuse me?
-Yes?
What are you lining up for?
I'm lining up to buy chocolates.
This is really famous for chocolates.
You can't buy,
-if you don't line up.
-What?
Excuse me.
What do you mean I can't buy?
They only sell limited quantity. Once
it's all sold out, they close the store.
What?
What the heck...
That means I might not be able to buy.
Gosh, no. I need to.
I really want to eat it.
Darn it.
They won't take revenge on me
just because of finger flicks.
I'm anxious to go events now.
How am I going to save up
for Suyeon's academy fee?
I don't know this number.
He...
-Hello?
-Wooshik, it's me. Miyoung.
-Miyoung, I mean...
-...madam!
-Don't call me that!
-What is the matter?
-You left without taking the event cost.
So I have called you to take it.
-Right, event cost...
-So...
-...do you want to come to my house?
-Pardon? Your house?
Can't you just bank in to me?
I have your guitar in my house too.
Right, I left my guitar too.
-Then, can you just send by delivery...
-Is it because of my husband?
My husband left for his work
so just come and get it. Okay?
Wait, wait, madam.
Gosh.
I don't want to go.
I'm scared.
Come in, come in.
-Why are you wearing a mask?
-Pardon?
I'm having some flu.
Where is my guitar?
There it is.
-Well, then. Goodbye.
-Wait.
You should take the money.
Wait for awhile.
There you go.
-It's one million won, right?
-Yes.
Thank you.
-I should go now.
-What?
You are leaving already?
-I have an urgent matter.
-What kind?
I need to get some money in a hurry.
-How much?
-Well...
Around two million won...
-Do you want me to give you that money?
-What?
Why should you...
-It's not right.
-Then,
what about lending it to you?
You can pay me back when you can.
Still, it's bit...
Why...
-...are you helping me?
-What do you mean why?
Don't you know I was the
president of your fan club?
I should help my favorite singer
out, if he's in trouble.
Gee, I'm not a singer.
I'm just a low class entertainer,
-who performs at birthdays.
-What are you saying?
In my heart, you are always a star.
I will be your fan until I die and
will be your fan forever. So cheer up!
-Thank you.
-You don't need to.
Where are my senses?
I will bring something to drink.
My fan until the day she dies.
Just hearing that makes me happy.
Yes, Cha Wooshik.
Let's cheer up for my fans.
Wooshik, I brought sikhye...
Oh, my...
What have I done?
Okay, I'm almost there. I can eat it
soon, if I wait few more minutes.
It will be so delicious.
Sorry to inform you that all chocolates
that we prepared have been sold out.
We will end our business today.
"As all ingredients are out,
we will end our business today."
"Close"
It's sticky, isn't it? It's my husband's.
Get changed and come out.
Okay.
Gee, look at myself.
I should get changed
fast, and get out of here.
Honey.
When did you come?
Just now. By the way,
-why are you so surprised?
-What?
No way. What do you mean surprised?
I thought you were
going to archery center.
How come you are here early?
Because of my migraine,
I couldn't get it right.
I shouldn't have let him leave like that.
I bet you are tired.
Why don't you get some rest?
Wait, hold on.
I should clean my bow at least.
Madam, I don't think the
clothes fit me...
Sir!
What are you doing here?
Those are my clothes.
Wait,
did you take a shower?
No, it's not like that...
I got sikhye all over me... Yes, yes...
-Yes, it's the truth.
-Shut up!
Are you expecting me to believe that?
-It's a misunderstanding.
-Yes, misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? What misunderstanding?
You both caught in action!
I can't just let it slide this time.
You come here.
-Come here.
-It's a misunderstanding.
Okay!
I will tell the truth. Actually,
that man just came to our house.
What?
Why are you saying that?
I'm right. I told you no
but you came to my house.
You asked for one cup of sikhye,
-and start to pour it on yourself!
-What?
No...
It's not like that.
You... You...
I bought it! I finally bought it!
Wait, wait.
I can't let guys see me, eating at home.
I got no choice.
I should finish it first and go home.
Mister!
-Could you please throw the ball to us?
-Sure.
"Hansung elementary"
Thank you.
Kibong's incredible pitch.
Thunderbolt Fire!
It's a strikeout!
Player Kook Kibong, no hit and no run,
he has won world series championship!
What are you doing, Kibong?
What?
I was wondering, where you have
gone since early this morning.
I see you have gone to
get the chocolate box.
Hey,
what's wrong?
They remind me of the old days.
I always played like them,
when I was their age.
I didn't even imagine,
I would be like this.
Yuri.
What should I do?
How should I live?
I hope someone can teach me.
Kibong,
I saw this in some movie.
Life is...
...same as this chocolate box.
This box contains sweet chocolates,
but it also contains bitter ones too.
So the baseball was...
...a bitter chocolate for your life.
It's too bitter to swallow.
That kind of chocolate.
But there' still...
...a lot of other chocolates in your box.
"Chocolate"
Your career for baseball might be over,
but your life...
...hasn't been over.
Don't you think so?
Perhaps, if you choose other chocolate,
there might be another way.
But what if other
chocolates are bitter too?
Even so,
you have no choice.
Then,
you just have to pick
up another chocolate.
-But what if it's bitter as well?
-Seriously.
Never mind.
I was giving you a serious advice.
I'm just joking.
So I still have...
...other chocolates to try, right?
-Hey, can I have one too?
-No!
I went through hoops to get this.
I will eat it all by myself!
Gosh, you are so cheap.
Wait a minute.
You said it wasn't good.
I guess it was, right?
It was good, right?
Gee, I guess I'm right.
Hey,
give me one. You cheap jerk.
No way. I'm going to eat it all by myself.
Hey!
-I told you about the store.
-No.
Come and get it, if you can.
You think I can't?
How can you? You can never...
Oh my, Wooshik.
-What are you doing here?
-Why did you do that to me?
Tell me. Why did you do that to me?
You have given me a humiliation.
What kind of crappy excuse is that?
No, not that kind of reason.
Tell me the real reason.
I have thought about it a lot.
And I still don't know.
Were you trying to kill me?
Were you really trying to kill me?
You said,
you will be my side until you die!
Tell me.
Say something!
Then what should I do?
I could have gotten a
divorce, if I haven't done it!
Is that why you framed me?
Are you here to argue about that?
-You petty minded jerk!
-What? Petty?
-You old lady...
-Old lady?
I won't let it slide
if you keep on doing it.
What are you going to do then?
Why are you whistling for?
Hey, you!
-Darn it. You traitor!
-Hey!
Next news, one of the biggest gang,
Yongpal gang has been arrested by police.
Leader of Yongpal gang, Kim and hundreds
of other gang members are arrested for...
...mob violence and robbery.
Gosh, that jerk is finally arrested.
You are right.
Wooshik, I know you've been through
a lot for running away from them.
I was so scared and stressed out, Jungi.
I know. I know how you feel.
Let's watch something else.
-Next news...
-Hello.
I just saw a familiar face.
And tear invoking sad stories.
Who is that?
We visit fascinating places.
The popular segment on "6PM My Hometown",
"Oh, my. How can this happen?" time!
Shall we say it again?
"Let's go!" One more time, "Let's go!"
-That's you, right?
-What are you talking about? That's not!
-Switch it to something else!
-Wait, wait!
-Wait, stay still!
-Hey!
-Stay still!
-Help! Let me go!
No!
I'm reporter version of
Yoo Jaesuk, Lee Jungi.
Yes, I'm here to meet a dog which pees
standing up at Jungeup, Jeonlabuk-do.
Gildong! There you are!
-Let's go, Gildong!
-Gildong!
Its name is Gildong!
It's his lucky dog!
-Gil...
-Don't.
-Gildong.
-Stop laughing!
Especially you, stop laughing!
You jerk!
-You were about to die a minute ago!
-Sorry, sorry.
What is that?
When did you become a reporter?
What should I do?
I'm about to be seized
lawfully due to my card debts.
Still, what's up with that outfit?
-It's all concept, okay? You jerk!
-Hey.
That show is hosted by Cho Sangwoo, right?
-How do you know?
-I'm a big fan of anchor Cho Sangwoo.
Can you...
-...get me his autograph?
-Autograph?
-Okay, why not.
-Yes!
How is your reporting work, Jungi?
Is it fun?
It's actually quite fun.
You can get to meet fun people,
and eat delicious foods.
I see.
That sounds fun.
-Do I look like a mantis?
-Totally.
What's up with you? Came all the way
here and now helping me with my make up.
What?
Well... No reason.
When will anchor Cho Sangwoo come?
Sangwoo?
Of course he has his private room
with professional make up teams...
Hold on.
-Are you here to see Sangwoo?
-No, I'm not.
-I'm obviously right.
-No!
I was wondering what was up with you.
-Jungi!
-Sangwoo, you are here.
Have some donuts.
-I got it from my fan.
-Thank you, sir.
Sangwoo, this is my friend.
And she's a big fan of yours.
-I see.
-Come on, say hello.
Hello, I'm Kim Jeongeun.
Hello, nice to meet you.
-I will see you around.
-Yes.
Take it easy.
-I will see you in a bit.
-Sure.
I was so nervous.
-My heart was about to come out!
-Gee.
Do you like him that much?
-Why don't you ask him out?
-No way, how could I...
Why can't you?
Do you want me to help?
You?
Who am I?
I'm the master of dating, Lee Jungi.
I can get you both married to each other.
-Really?
-Of course!
Exchange of that,
you need to help me with my makeup.
What do you say?
Deal?
Deal.
I think this is enough for
business plan for Yuri's Kitchen.
Start up fund is most important.
Where can I get it from?
-It's giving me a headache.
-I'm back.
Where did you go, Kibong?
I just...
...went out for a jog,
since I've been feeling heavy
from lying down all day long.
What happened? You didn't even
eat well and were feeling down.
You told me, there will be
other chocolates left for me.
So...
...I've decided to start again.
I don't know what to do yet.
-Do you want me to help you?
-Really?
That'd be great!
I don't think you are
a study type of person.
What about modeling?
You have a good body.
-I have bow legs.
-Really?
-What about personal trainer?
-My shoulder is injured.
-A chef like me?
-I can't even cook fried egg.
Then,
an astronaut?
An astronaut?
That sounds good!
But I don't like helmet
because it's too stuffy.
Gosh, what are you good at?
Why aren't you good at anything?
You are right.
I guess I'm nothing without baseball.
I don't know, why I'm like this.
No, no.
I was just joking around.
Let's look for it again.
Then...
...is there anything you were good
at before playing baseball?
Thing I was good at?
I was awarded for a poem when
I was in elementary school.
-What? Poem?
-Yes.
-You wrote poems before?
I wanted to be a poet
before I played baseball.
Really?
Poet sounds nice.
Why don't you write a poem?
A poem...
-Come on.
-Welcome!
-Hello.
-Why did you bring me to gym out of blue?
I've done my research about Sangwoo.
He always comes to this gym,
and works out every evening.
-So get yourself register first.
-Me?
-Why?
-What do you think?
Don't you know repeated
coincidences become a relationship?
Think about it.
After seeing you at a dressing room,
he runs into you again at the gym he goes.
What would he think?
"Oh my god, I can't believe this.
How interesting." Wouldn't he think that?
-I'm not sure.
-Not sure, my ass.
Anyway, if he keeps running in to you
like this, someday he will think...
..."Perhaps, this woman is the one.
No, my destiny."
And he will keep thinking about you.
Before you realize, you guys will be
dating, wearing couple rings, proposing,
married, have a child, and become parents.
-Do you really think so?
-Of course!
-But isn't this place really expensive?
-That's not the problem.
You said, you wanted to be his girlfriend.
-Never mind. Forget it.
-No, no!
I will do it.
How can a gym be this expensive?
I've lost all my expenses for this month.
I wonder,
where is Sangwoo at?
There he is!
Oh my, aren't you the
news anchor, Cho Sangwoo?
Yes.
-I am. And you are?
-I...
...am friend of Jungi that you
saw at broadcasting station.
I'm Kim Jeongeun.
-Hello.
-Oh, my.
How can we meet twice in a row by chance?
Unbelievable.
You work out at this gym?
I've never seen you before.
Well... It's...
With spring here,
I wanted to start working out.
So I registered today.
Today is your first day?
I'm quitting today.
-Pardon?
-Well, good luck with your work out.
No, I...
Gee, my money...
Die, you jerk. Die!
Stop it already!
-Do you think, I knew?
-Shut up!
What are you going to do with my money?
They don't do refund!
Hey.
-That's enough.
-See? She said, enough. Stop it!
-That won't make him back to his senses.
-Yes, what?
-Make it quick with this.
-What?
-Hey, Lee Jungi!
-Gosh.
I wonder, when they will grow up.
I know right?
What is this?
I guess this is Jungi's reporting script.
Wow, so this is how script looks like.
"Waikiki Guest House"
Hey,
let me know if you receive
any calls about event.
Okay, bye.
You still want to go
events after what happened?
-I just need some money.
-Why so sudden? What for?
Nothing.
Yuri, Yuri!
-Gee, what is this fuss all about?
-The thing is...
I've written a poem. Can you take a look?
Poem?
-What poem?
-Kibong wants...
...to try to be a poet.
-So you can write a poem, Kibong?
-Yes.
Do you want to hear it out?
But don't laugh at it. It's been a while.
Okay, sure.
Title is "Are you that happy?"
By Kook Kibong.
"Are you okay now?"
"We've been through a lot."
"Our..."
"...final is..."
"...just a farewell."
"But it was..."
"...too difficult for us."
Let me explain you about this part.
I've quit my baseball due to my injury.
So I expressed my feeling back
then as couple's break up.
It's pretty nice. Keep on going.
Okay.
"Sometimes I heard,"
"you were doing great."
"You are..."
"...doing great with a nice guy you met."
"I didn't ask,"
"but you told me anyway."
I am telling this to
all my baseball gears.
I left it at training center,
and I heard it's fine.
I expressed how coach told me he gave
them to my junior, when I didn't even ask.
I see. You must be heartbroken.
Actually when I was writing this part,
it keeps reminding of my gears
so my heart was broken...
Sorry.
Not again.
I will go and wash my face.
He is so big,
but so emotional.
-Don't you think?
-But Yuri,
doesn't it sound familiar?
-What?
-Me too.
Wait,
isn't this from song lyrics?
It sounds similar from "Are
you happy?" by Kim Jongshin.
Yes, it is!
Are you okay now?
We've been through a lot. Our...
...final is...
It's just same!
What? He thinks the song lyrics
is the poem that he wrote?
I think he does.
No wonder it sounds so fine.
Hey, just pretend you know nothing.
He is finally trying to do something new.
Let's not disappoint him.
-Got it?
-Okay.
Yes, Yuri.
Jeongeun! Where is she? Jeongeun!
-Big news, big news, big news!
-What do you mean?
I've done some research
about Sangwoo again.
I found that, he's active in a
club these days. And just in time,
today is regular meeting day.
-So what?
-What do you think?
You should sign up that club,
-and go make the coincidence.
-You and the coincidence.
Hey, hey.
About coincidences,
It has to occurred at least three times...
...for it to be a relationship.
It may seem like nothing
but it never fails on anyone.
What kind of club is it?
Your name is Jeongeun, right?
I never imagined for a woman
to join our alphorn club.
Were you interested in Swiss
traditional instrument, alphorn?
How fascinating.
Not many people know about it.
Gee, where is Sangwoo?
What happened?
Sorry, I'm late.
Oh, my. Sangwoo, we've met again!
Unbelievable!
I've been in this club for a while now.
-You two know each other?
-Well, yes.
-A little.
-I see.
Well, you can teach Jeongeun.
Well, why not.
That will be wonderful.
Yuri, Yuri! Wooshik.
I wrote another poem.
Would you like to hear it?
Poem?
-You wrote another one?
-Yes.
I keep getting inspired,
so I can't keep myself still.
Is that so?
-Then, read it out to me.
-Okay.
Before that,
let me explain about this poem.
I...
...am a beast which
got hurt by baseball.
so I am giving out a warning
message to not bother me anymore.
Here me out then.
Title is "Roar".
By Kook Kibong.
"Yo!"
"Okay."
"I'm warning you just in case."
"Listen carefully."
"It's dangerous now, so dangerous."
"Stop provoking me.
There's going to be a trouble."
"I don't even know myself. Hawl!"
"It's going to get..."
"...fierce from now on."
"I'm..."
"...growling, growling, growling."
"I'm growling, growling, growling."
"If you don't back away,"
"then I don't care if you get hurt."
-How was it?
-Wow, it was good.
-It got some tension.
-Right?
I think I'm really talented with it.
It doesn't even take me
30 minutes to write one.
I just got inspired!
I should write more!
-Hey, brother. Wasn't it good this time?
-How was that good?
That was EXO's "Growl".
He just switched "Growl" to "Roar".
No wonder, I felt like I wanted to dance.
-Are you going to let him be like that?
-What else can I do?
He works so hard.
It doesn't cost him money.
Just pretend, you don't know.
Gosh, it's tiring.
I told you, that's not how you do it.
-You are such a slow learner.
-I'm sorry.
What the heck am I doing here?
I'm getting scolded
for nothing by Sangwoo.
-Why is it so hard to blow?
-Let's...
...start again.
Jeongeun, put your strength on stomach,
and exhale as if you are letting
all air out inside your body.
Try now.
That's right. Okay. Let's go.
Harder than that.
You are almost there. More. More!
I'm so humiliated in front of Sangwoo.
How can I fart at the
moment like this? How?
What are you doing over here?
What's up with your face?
Is it because of what happened just now?
Don't bother about it.
I farted a lot,
when I started to learn.
And your fart sound was cute.
Please stop. I'm already embarrassed.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I just wanted to comfort you.
By the way Jeongeun,
don't you think we have some connection?
Pardon?
-I don't know, what you mean.
-I mean,
we met at the broadcasting station,
we met at the gym,
and alphorn club.
It's fascinating to meet you
three times coincidentally.
If you are free tomorrow,
do you want to go for a drive with me?
Yes?
Where did you buy this sausage from?
-It's good, right?
-Yes.
-Where is Kibong?
-Kibong is writing a poem again.
He fidgeted all night by writing,
so I couldn't get a wink of sleep.
And now he's searching
for literary contest.
What?
-Literary contest?
-Yes, that's right.
Yuri, why don't we tell him the truth?
I want to but I'm scared,
he will be disappointed.
It will be more disappointing
to know it later.
-Okay, I will talk to him.
-Yes, you need to.
Guys!
Ta-da! How do I look?
Amazing.
-Is today a dressing up as a woman day?
-What?
Do you want to die?
Where are you going dressed up like that?
I have a date with Sangwoo today.
Gee, are you that happy?
You know I helped you, right?
Yes, it's all thanks to you.
Why do you even brag?
-Why are you bringing that pipe?
-Hey!
This isn't a pipe! It's alphorn!
It's a traditional musical
instrument of Swiss.
This is an instrument?
No wonder,
it looks much longer than a pipe.
Where are you going to date?
We are going to Sangwoo's
mansion in Gapyeong.
Gapyeong? Mansion?
How can you go to a trip,
when you guys just met? No way!
It's not a trip. We are coming back today.
By the way,
who do you think you are to say no?
Me? I'm your best friend.
Of course, I want to let you go.
But you are like...
...a child at water's edge.
So I feel anxious.
Why don't you take care of yourself.
See you guys!
Oh, god.
Hey, I'm going for shooting.
What about my make up? Hey, Hey!
This is why,
I shouldn't be so generous.
Should I go instead of her, Jungi?
Today is my off-day and I want
to take a look at the set too.
Really?
That will be great for me.
Kibong, shall we talk for a moment...
I guess he's asleep.
Gosh, I guess he fell
asleep while writing a poem.
What did he write this time?
"Stylish as Gangnam"?
"A girl who is warm and
humanly during the day."
"A classy girl who knows how to enjoy
the freedom of a cup of coffee."
"A girl with that kind of twist."
"Oh, oh, oh I am as stylish as Gangnam."
This time is "Gangnam Style" by Psy.
I almost danced "Horse
dance", while reading this.
What? Another one?
"Momma Mia Rhapsody"?
This is plagiarism of "Bohemian Rhapsody".
How can he plagiarize Queen?
My gosh.
Momma, I'm sorry. Sorry, momma.
Rhapsody. Sorry, sorry, momma.
He even synched with the melody.
So he saw the video of him.
Definitely, saw it.
Alright!
What should I do with him?
So this is how they shoot.
Amazing!
How is it amazing?
Shall I practice first?
Hello! The place I will introduce
today is Kal noodle restaurant,
in Boryung, Chungnam...
Gosh,
what's up with my throat today?
Really?
-I will go and buy some water. Hold on.
-Water?
Thank you, Suyeon.
She's so nice.
Jungi.
Hello, producer.
Wow, who is she? I like her looks.
-Is she an actress?
-No, she's just my friend.
I see. Why did she come
instead of Jeongeun?
Actually,
Jeongeun and Sangwoo are
hitting off each other.
They have gone for a date.
Really? But...
...she better be careful of Sangwoo.
-Why?
-He has some bad rumors.
He brings women to mansion in Gapyeong,
saying that he will give them a tour.
And cut off his contacts
after having fun with them.
We are going to Sangwoo's
mansion in Gapyeong.
Pardon?
What do you mean having fun with them?
Darn it, why don't you answer me?
What is going on with you?
Gee, it's driving me insane.
-Gosh, Kim Jeongeun.
-Hey, Lee Jungi.
Where are you going?
Hey, where are you going?
I need to tell Kibong.
I'm afraid, he might be devastated.
I'm going crazy. Seriously.
Hey, Kibong.
What are you doing over there?
Yuri...
What is this song?
Song?
What song?
Kibong...
You heard this song?
Yes.
Yuri, this song...
...is really good.
-What is the name of this song?
-What?
"Are you happy?" by Yoon Jongshin.
"Are you happy?" I've never heard
of this song, but it's really good.
But...
...its lyrics is similar with my poem.
How amazing.
What?
Then, you...
...never heard of it before?
Yes.
I was too into baseball,
I didn't have any interest in songs.
What about...
"Growl" by EXO and
"Gangnam Style" by Psy?
Also,
what about "Bohemian Rhapsody" by Queen?
What are they?
I've never heard of them before. Why?
What?
No...
It's nothing.
I really enjoy this song.
I should go and download it.
What is going on?
Then, he really...
...wrote all the poems?
Jungi... What?
-Where did Jungi go?
-I don't know. He just left.
Pardon?
-What are you saying?
-I need to finish the shooting by today.
Where am I going to
get a reporter right now?
Excuse me,
didn't you say, you were friend of Jungi?
Yes.
Why do you ask?
Hello, viewers. I'm reporter, Han Suyeon.
The most popular segment of
"6PM My Hometown", "Oh, my."...
..."How can this happen?
Oh, my. Oh, my."...
...will start now.
-Let's go!
-Cut, okay! That was good!
-You are good at it.
-Yes, you are really good at it.
She's better than Jungi.
I sang all day long,
but I only earned 30,000 won.
How am I going to save up for
Suyeon's academy fee like this?
Hey,
Suyeon!
Hey, Wooshik.
Where have you been?
What?
I just have business to do.
-Why are you alone without Jungi?
-I don't know.
He just said he couldn't do it and left.
It was such a big mess.
Did he cause some trouble again?
I wonder.
I even reported instead of Jungi.
You did?
Producer asked me urgently
so I had no choice.
Writers said I was good at it,
and they will introduce
reporting job to me.
Really?
It was quite fun.
-I thought I could give it a try.
-Really? Hey...
Wait,
then you no longer have to
go to news anchor academy.
And I no longer have to go for events.
What do you mean?
-News anchor academy?
-Well...
It's nothing.
Anyway, I'm so glad.
-Good luck with it.
-Thank you.
We have a good thing to celebrate,
-shall we go get some hotteok?
-Hotteok?
Oh my god, yes! That sounds great.
Let's go, hurry!
-I want three, okay?
-Okay, got it.
Shall we have some wine,
while watching the stars?
You shouldn't drink and drive.
Then, we can sleep here
tonight and leave tomorrow.
Pardon?
Jeongeun, Jeonguen.
-Jeongeun.
-Let me go.
How are you going to go home?
I will go by myself so let me go.
Hey!
-Let go of her!
-Jungi.
Jeongeun,
are you okay?
-Did anything happen to you?
-No.
How can you follow to a place like this?
You fearless fool!
-How can you make me worry this much?
-Hey, Lee Jungi.
What the heck are you doing?
What about you? How petty.
What?
Jeongeun, let's go.
Gosh,
I was just having fun because I'm bored.
Who does she think she is? She's nothing.
I can't hold it anymore.
Jeongeun,
wait over here.
-Sangwoo.
-What now?
You need to get punched by me today.
Are you crazy?
If you really want to see what's
crazy, why don't you talk more?
You really want to quit your
job, aren't you?
With one word of me, I can get you fired!
Whatever.
I no longer want to do even you ask
me, you jerk.
Let's go, Jeongeun.
"Welcome to Waikiki 2"
It doesn't make sense. I'm into Jungi?
-I'm completely crazy!
-Did you do something wrong to me?
I need to write my resume.
Can you lend me your laptop?
Let's see. No address...
What do you mean no address?
I've never seen the owner of this place,
so I've written it as no address.
Is it wrong?
Basic attitude of reporter is
having a good pronunciation.
But they said, they can't work with a
girl without a basic attitude like me.
Do you know any reporter, Jungi?
-I know one senior reporter.
-Hello.
-Gosh, she spits so much.
-Ya, ya. No, no.
I can't even say she is spitting so
much, when she's teaching me for free.
Pu!