Bring it on.
Cut. Okay.
That was great stunts. Good work.
Thank you.
Alright, we're done with the stunts,
so bring in the main actress.
Okay.
Good work, good work.
Geez.
Is it too hard for them to say
that I did a good job?
How did I end up becoming so pathetic?
-Oh my god, that tastes so bad.
-Jungi, your phone.
It's been ringing for a while.
Thank you.
Hello?
What?
Darn it.
This song is dedicated to you ladies here.
It's called "Ddaeng Beol".
Sing along.
Please clap along.
"Housewives Singing Lesson
with Shiba Wooshik"
What? I'm busy.
I'm in the middle of a class.
What?
Darn.
"K B Kook"
Yes, there is only one pitch left
to win the championship.
No one has been able to hit
Kook Kibong's pitch for all nine innings.
Everything depends on this last pitch.
The count is three balls and
two strikes right now.
Kook Kibong needs to be careful
about throwing a breaking ball.
It's because Sato is probably
expecting for  a breaking ball.
Yes, this is a very nerve-wracking moment.
It's a full count for
Kook Kibong right now.
Ready...
-Strike. He strikes out the batter.
-Yes.
That was great. What a great win.
Thank you, Sato.
Everyone, Kook Kibong has
led the team to a victory.
Kook Kibong is truly a great player.
Hurry and get up.
Hey. Kook Kibong.
I did it. We won. We won.
As if it's not enough
that you passed out while running,
now you're even dreaming, you punk?
Get up already.
Don't you want to join the major league?
Are you going to rot
in the minor league forever?
Coach,
can I take this call?
You idiot, just take it.
Hello?
What is it?
I'm in the middle of training.
What? Darn.
That's it. That's how you should have run.
What is he doing?
Where are you going?
"Waikiki Guest House"
"Waikiki"
What do you think?
It's neat inside,
and the interior is great too.
-It's not bad, right?
-Yes.
On top of that, the location is strategic
so it gets a lot of business.
You can use everything in here.
-Isn't that great?
-Yes.
You should think about it.
This is going to drive me crazy.
Why aren't they here yet?
Everyone who lived here
has become successful.
We've had movie directors, reporters,
shopping mall CEO, and even a pastry chef.
They have all become successful.
-Ma'am.
Who is this?
-Who are they?
-They're the only strange ones.
I'm serious.
I'm going to give it a bit more thought,
and I'll call you back.
-Goodbye.
-Wait.
-You should have a closer look.
-If you would excuse me.
There's more to see.
-If you just...
-No, no.
Good grief. What are you guys doing?
Ma'am...
How could you put this up for sale
without even discussing it with us?
You should've paid your rent then.
Do you know how many
months you're overdue?
About that...
Could you give us a week?
We'll figure it out.
One week? Do you know how many months
you've been saying that?
I think it's been about
four months and two weeks...
Fine.
I'll give you one more week,
and this will be your last chance.
You better pay up all the overdue rent.
Would you just look at yourselves.
Are you guys a traffic light or something?
-Enjoy your day.
-Take care.
What is this tire doing
at this guesthouse?
Look who's talking.
Hey, Red Light.
-Red Light, stop.
-Don't touch me.
-Red Light.
-Hey.
I called you ages ago.
What took you so long?
I ran over as soon as I got the call.
Can't you tell by the fact
that I'm still in my wig and costume?
I even brought this all the way here.
This is driving me nuts.
How are we going to get
all that money in a week?
I know, right?
Jeongpal, do you have some money?
Do you think I'd be living
off of you, if I did?
I knew it.
But, what's up with your look today?
That's what I'm saying.
How did I end up from Newsroom's
Song Joonseok to shit like this?
I mean, look at me. I'm a talented actor.
Does it make sense for me
to just play as body doubles?
-Just body double?
Looks like you still haven't
come to your senses.
Shut up.
That's why you get dumped by girls.
Kim Jeongpal!
I told you not to talk about Chewbacca...
I mean...
I said don't talk about Seojin, didn't I?
And again...
...I wasn't dumped.
It was a mutual breakup.
Did I not tell you that?
Alright, whatever.
I'm just going to go shower.
A shower out of a sudden?
You're leaving after
bringing up a sore spot?
What's that? Why...
Why are you dancing?
You stuck your tongue out?
Don't shower, the water bill will be high!
Shut up!
In any case, this is all because of you.
So you take the responsibility.
Why?
-Why is it my responsibility?
-You're the CEO.
We're just investors.
You said it would be a good investment.
You said we'd be raking in money
if we renovated the house.
The global economic recession had change
consumer behaviour, so all guesthouses...
Shut up!
I'm the idiot here for
trusting you and investing.
You only call me the CEO
when something bad happens.
-Hey, hey.
-People have gathered at Han River Park,
-Look at that.
-to watch a meteor shower.
It looks like there's
a festival over here.
-So, what?
-In order to watch the meteor shower,
-What about it?
-that will happen tonight...
I'm just saying that
there are a lot of people there.
Family, friends and couples...
Who could it be?
Who's Meteor Shower?
Who is he that there's that much fuss?
A singer?
If not. Then, an actor?
-Are you kidding me?
-I know!
A soccer player?
Wow.
I'm the crazy one here...
...for trusting you guys and
agreeing to work together.
It's all my fault.
I'm the crazy one.
So who's Meteor Shower?
I feel like something good will happen.
Are we in a situation to be relaxing
and watching the meteor shower?
This is the biggest meteor shower
in history. We can't miss it.
You'll never know.
If we make a wish upon a shooting star,
money might rain down from the sky.
It's better to just give it up.
Why are you so negative all the time?
Then what?
We might be homeless in a week.
I should stay positive?
That's why you need to be positive.
Wooshik, listen to me carefully.
Hey, Beanpole. Look.
Look at each other.
Things can't be worse
than this, can they?
-So?
-So my point is...
....we've hit rock bottom in life.
Then, that means...
all that's left for us is to go up.
Do you get it?
Do you think things could
get worse from here?
This is the most positive situation
there could be. Don't you think so?
Do you think that makes
sense, you crazy jerk?
Yes.
Just die. It's a waste of oxygen
for you to breathe. Just die.
-Hey, hey. Stop.
-Die.
Seriously, you two.
Hey! It started.
There. Look over there.
So, that's a meteor shower.
-It's so cool.
-I know right?
Hey, hey. Look at it.
Hey look at that.
That one is huge, right?
You're right.
But don't you think...
...it looks like it's coming towards us?
I know right.
-Right, Wooshik?
-Whatever.
But, isn't that...
...getting a bit too close?
It's so thrilling.
At this rate, it might really fall...
"Guest House Waikiki"
Where is it?
Did a meteor really fall?
On our guest house?
It seems like it.
So that's a meteorite.
I guess so.
This is so cool. Awesome.
That's so fascinating, right? Isn't it?
It's a meteorite.
You said nothing could get worse.
You said all that was left for us
was to go up. That we had hit rock bottom.
I mean, it's true that we hit rock bottom,
but I didn't think we could
go through the bottom.
Shut up!
Look at that.
There's a hole on the ceiling.
If the landlady finds out about this,
we won't just kicked out,
we'll get sued.
Do you know that?
Hey.
It's not our fault.
-It's gravity's fault.
-Do you think she'll believe that?
Last time, when the windows broke
because of the hailstorm,
she blamed it all on us.
That was then and this is different.
How could a meteor fell down
on our guest house?
What do we do?
I can't believe a meteor has fallen on us.
Why isn't anything working out for us?
Hey... Wooshik.
-Are you okay?
What do we do?
-Wooshik.
-Hurry.
What a genius. A true genius.
You really have the appetite
to eat right now?
-Yeah, it's tasty.
-Tasty?
What if the landlady finds out about this?
You've been whining from a while ago.
Stop it.
I'll handle this. Me.
-What will you do?
-Just sit and watch, Sir.
You need to use your brains.
I think this hole got bigger
than last night.
See. Doesn't it look completely fine now?
This is perfect.
The TV's so huge from here.
Ta-da.
-What's this?
-Hey.
Every cent is precious.
We should at least try to sell
whatever we can.
Let's see. Where was it?
Here it is.
What's that?
You know Randy Johnson, right?
The major league's legendary
left-handed pitcher.
This is a glove signed by Randy Johnson.
-We could get money if we sell this.
-Really?
"I hope you have a happy life
-Randy Johnson"
This...
Randy Johnson wrote this?
So, Randy Johnson wrote in Korean,
with clear handwriting...
...and even knows the phrase
"Hope you live a happy life"?
-Well, he must've learned Korean.
-Does that make sense?
It's fake. Fake.
No, it's not.
I paid my senior 1 million won
to ask this favour from him.
Then what about...
What about this signed bat?
"Kook Kibong-San, Please be happy-desu
-Ichiro"
Fine, let's just say
Ichiro learned Korean.
But even then, would he write
"desu" in Korean?
Oh...
"Oh"?
Kibong.
Please use your brain.
Shut up!
You guys are so loud. I can't even eat.
Is it a sin that he's ignorant?
Come here, Kibong.
As long as you're healthy,
that's all that matters.
You're tall, and you're still growing.
I'm going crazy.
What's this?
Where did you get this microphone
with Cho Yongpil's autograph?
-I think this is Wooshik's.
-Really?
What are you doing? Get up.
-For what?
-We have to cover that hole.
-Get upstairs quick.
Wow, this hole is bigger than we expected.
Since we have to cover it with the sofa,
bring the sofa here
then push it that way.
-Understand?
-Yes, got it.
I fell in here.
Why did you push so hard?
You told me to push.
Why are you getting mad at me?
-Jeez, you're all brawn but no brain.
-What?.
My foot is all stuck now.
What are you doing? Hurry and help me out.
You're such a mess.
Mr. Cha?
-Are you home?
-Isn't that the landlady's voice?
Why is she here so early?
Hold on. She can't know about this.
-Hurry, pull me out. Hurry!
-Mr, Cha!
I'll go down first and stall her.
Kibong, you pull him out.
Got it.
Come on, Jungi.
Hello, Ma'am.
What brings you here?
I just thought that I lost my earring
here yesterday.
Have you seen it, by any chance?
Your earring?
No, I haven't.
Really?
Use some more strength.
I'm trying my best.
But, why isn't your foot budging?
What was that noise?
Wasn't there some noise just now?
A noise? No, I didn't hear anything.
Did I mishear it?
Anyway, where could it be?
You must be busy, Ma'am.
We'll look for the earring...
...and bring it to you later.
It's fine. I'll find it myself.
1, 2, 3...
You heard that too, right?
A sound? No.
I didn't hear anything.
No. I heard something for sure.
I think it came from above.
What are you doing right now?
So...
Well...
I love you.
What?
For a long time,
I've had feelings for you, Ma'am.
What nonsense is this?
It's a bit hard to tell you here.
Let's leave first.
-Let's leave and talk.
-Oh my.
Gosh.
-Come with me.
-Let me go.
Let me go.
Ouch, it hurts.
You're hurting me.
I'm sorry.
So...
...is that true?
Do you really...
-...love me?
-What?
How long has it been?
Well...
It's been about six months.
Six months?
Is that why you've been
putting up with my nagging?
-Yes.
-Oh, my.
I get it now.
I didn't even expect this.
Still, this is not right.
Our age gap is too large.
Plus, I have children and you know that.
A young man like you and me?
That wouldn't make sense.
Right?
I know...
...it doesn't make sense.
Exactly. This is just ridiculous.
This isn't right.
I guess I was being too greedy.
I apologize.
I'll be off then.
Try being greedy.
Sorry?
It's not like you can stop
your feelings for someone just like that.
So...
You should try become greedy, for once.
I like greedy men.
What?
-You're dating the landlady?
-Yes.
Today's the first day of our relationship.
We have to go on dates now.
Why would you lie about
something like that?
-What should I do now?
-No, no.
It's for the better.
She probably won't ask for rent
for a while.
Would she ask for rent from her boyfriend?
-Then, I'm supposed to keep dating her?
-Yeah.
That's a scam, you punk.
No, it's not.
-You can just date her for real.
-Huh?
I mean, she's not that bad.
She owns a lot of buildings,
money, wrinkles...
And she's old too.
Look at yourself.
She's completely out of your league.
Do you think that makes sense right now?
Then, should we just start
living on the streets?
This is driving me crazy.
Why did things turn out like this?
Think about it. It's an opportunity.
I'm here.
Hi. Did you come back
from your part-time job?
Yeah. I had three part-time jobs today.
I feel like I'm dying.
What's up with him?
He has his reasons.
What's this box?
What's with this yearbook?
That's our high school yearbook.
Really?
Should I take a look?
There's nothing to see.
"Kook Kibong"
"Cha Wooshik"
You all look so young.
"Lee Jungi"
Who's this girl?
-Why is she surrounded by so many boys?
-Which one?
It's Suyeon.
Her name is Han Suyeon.
Our first love.
-First love?
-Yeah.
What do you mean by "Our"?
So she was you three's first love?
That's right.
Not just us, but all the boys
in our entire school.
Really?
She's not even that pretty.
Kim Jeongeun!
Gosh, you startled me.
Why did you yell at me?
You're out of line.
"She's not even that pretty"?
Suyeon was...
...a goddess.
A goddess!
"Huam High School"
-Left, right, left, right.
Guys!
Huge news.
What is this fuss about?
There's going to be a transfer
student in our class today.
And guess what?
It's a girl!
Plus, she's supposed to be super pretty.
I thought it was something big.
We're not interested in things like that.
There she is.
We're not interested.
Move.
We fell in love with Suyeon
at first sight.
She had a nice face, body,
and even a bright personality.
She was just perfect.
Not only was her family rich,
but she was exuding elegance
from head to toe.
So, what happened?
Did you confess your feelings?
Of course we did.
Knock, knock.
Have a drink.
Alright. Thanks. I'll enjoy the drink.
If you drink it,
it means we're dating.
Too bad.
I already saw you take a sip.
So, today's our first day of dating...?
That day, Suyeon vomited
all her gastric juice and bile.
Every single drop of it.
What about you, Kibong?
What happened?
Han Suyeon!
With this ball,
if I can hit that can,
it means we're dating.
That was the first day Kibong's
pitch resulted in a home run.
And that was how our first love
came to an end.
How pathetic. So pathetic.
What about you, Wooshik?
You didn't confess your feelings?
That's none of your business.
Geez.
What was that?
What's with him all of a sudden?
I don't know. He does that
whenever we mention Suyeon.
That's right.
It's the stunt director.
Hello, sir. Yes.
One more person?
Yes, I know someone who can do it. Yes.
Alright. I'll see you soon.
-You don't have any training today, right?
-Yes. Why?
The stunt director just called,
and he said he needs an extra urgently.
Why don't you come with me?
-Don't hit me too hard!
-Okay. I got it.
Here? Do it properly.
Shooting is not a joke.
Okay, listen up!
Quiet down.
Listen to me carefully.
This scene is where the police discovered
the gangsters' hideout in the mountain.
It's a fight scene with
the police officers.
So, you just need to follow exactly
what we practiced. That's it.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Okay.
Now, then...
-You. What was your name?
-I'm Kook Kibong.
Kibong. That's right, Kibong.
Kibong, since you're the first person,
you'll be hit in the head
with the police officer's baton.
Then, you'll die instantly.
Just like that.
Understand? Don't close your eyes.
Never close them. Keep them wide open
and then die instantly.
I'm going to die with my eyes open?
Didn't I just tell you that
you'd die instantly?!
-In an instant!
-Okay.
And, for Junho...
I'm Jungi. Lee Jungi.
Jungi. That's right, Jungi.
Sorry, sorry. Jungi.
Jungi, you'll fight the police,
but you'll be holding the fire
extinguisher and die instantly like that.
-You just die instantly.
-Die instantly.
-Yes, that's right.
-Alright.
Okay. Everyone is clear right?
Die instantly.
You.
What was your name again?
Sorry?
Just play along with it.
I'm Kook Kibong.
Kibong. That's right. Kibong.
Kibong, so, what should we do with you?
Kibong, since you're the first person,
you'll be hit in the head by the
police officer's baton.
-And then...
-You...
...already told me.
Die instantly.
I did? Yes, I did.
Kibong, die instantly.
Don't close your eyes.
-And as for Junbong.
-It's Jungi. Jungi. Lee Jungi.
-Jungi. That's right, Jungi.
-I'm Jungi.
So for Jungi... you'll fight the police,
but you'll be holding
the fire extinguisher and...
You already told me.
I have to die instantly.
-Lee Jungi, die instantly.
-Right, die instantly. I already told you.
Okay, die instantly. Okay.
Everyone knows what they're doing, right?
Excuse me, Director.
-We're ready.
-This is the director.
-It's me.
-Director, we're ready.
He's gotten worse.
Jungi...
...isn't he a bit strange?
He's always like that.
He hurt his head while doing a stunt
so his memory only lasts three seconds.
I see.
Just be understanding.
So, Kibong, you'll die instantly.
I'll die instantly, too.
Lee Jungi, you punk.
You'll really die instantly today.
Come here!
Die instantly.
Okay...
Ready, action!
Don't follow me!
Ouch. That hurts.
Get off me.
Thank you.
Die!
That's right. Die instantly.
Ouch. Geez.
Don't come any closer.
Go away. Go.
No. No, no.
Don't come near me.
No.
Cut, cut, cut, cut.
Be quiet!
Director, it seems that there's
a problem with the fire extinguisher.
I'm the director.
Hey, cut! Cut!
Kibong!
My eyes!
Open your eyes.
-Open your eyes.
-Ouch! That hurts.
Ouch, it hurts. I can't open my eyes.
My eyes won't open.
Why would you aim the fire extinguisher
to your face like that instead of dying?
And how could you kill
a guy who's already dead?
I'm sorry.
Hey, hold on.
This is so frustrating. Here, hold this.
Hold on to this, and get some rest. Okay?
-Thank you.
-How frustrating.
By the way, who's this guy next to you?
I've never seen him before.
How many times have I told you
that he's my friend?
Really? He's your friend?
Why is he here, though?
Obviously he came here
to shoot some scenes.
No, never mind.
He's just here to hang out.
I see? Okay.
I'm glad you're here.
Enjoy your visit.
It's cool, right?
-Cool?
-What is the next scene?
--The next scene will be...
-Gosh.
Well, then...
What are you guys doing here?
Are you not filming?
You told us to take a rest
because our eyes hurt.
I did?
I did...
That's right. Okay.
I'm sorry. Just take a rest.
What's the next scene?
Geez. Seriously.
His condition is getting worse.
Ouch. My eyes.
My eyes. My eyes.
My eyes.
-They hurt so much.
-This is all your fault.
That's why...
... I told you to eat slowly.
Yes.
Why? Are you really that nervous
to be with me?
What?
Oh, yes.
You're cute.
Anyway,
I should've caught on sooner.
It must have been so difficult
keeping it to yourself.
I'm sorry, Mr. Cha.
No, I mean...
I'm sorry...
...Wooshik.
Wooshik?
This is driving me insane.
Cha Wooshik?
How much longer will you put up with this?
No matter how desperate you are
to pay the rent, this is just not right.
Fine.
I'll just be honest with her now.
Ma'am.
-Yes?
-I have something to tell you.
What is it?
The thing is...
Hold on.
Hello?
What?
It was a lie?
Don't you know that out of all things,
I can never tolerate with lies?
What else do you think
you're supposed to do?!
Throw him in prison right now!
How dare he lie to me?
You don't need to show mercy
to trash like him.
Even if I have to put all my fortune on
the line, I'm not letting him go.
I don't care if it takes
a 100 or 1,000 lawyers.
Make sure that he doesn't see sunlight
again for the rest of his life.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
It's another new tenant,
and he lied to me.
The thing I hate the most in the world...
is lies.
By the way...
...didn't you say
you have something to tell me?
About that...
I wish time stopped like this.
Oh my. Geez.
Would you just stop it.
I fell asleep.
Ouch. My eyes.
Wait.
Why is it so quiet?
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Excuse...
Ouch!
Hello?
Director?
Is nobody there?!
Gosh, you scared me.
What the hell.
Why are you shouting?
Sorry, sorry.
This feels weird.
I don't think anyone is here.
They left us here
after finishing the shoot?
Call the director quickly.
Okay, good idea.
Are you calling him?
The staff members said they'd keep
our phones, remember? You idiot.
That's right.
What do we do now?
How am I supposed to know? You idiot.
Gosh, how could they leave us
when we can't even see properly.
Hello?
-Hello.
-There are people here.
-Hello. Hello.
There are people here.
This is nice.
I don't even remember the last time
I walked with a man like this.
But...
...why have you been
breaking in cold sweat?
-Are you sick?
-What?
No...
...it's not that.
What is it, then?
You're unbelievable.
Gosh...
Is this good enough?
If you wanted to link arms with me,
you could've said so.
You fool.
I'm going insane.
She'll go berserk,
if she finds out the truth.
But, still, this isn't right.
It's not right.
I'd rather go to prison,
I can't ignore my conscience anymore.
Ma'am,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Well, the thing is...
-Mom!
-Well...
Son!
Wooshik,
say hi.
This is my son.
-Hello.
-Mom!
Oh my, son.
Wooshik,
say hello.
This is my second son.
He...
Hello.
Who is this?
It's someone I'm dating as of today.
My sons, you understand me, right?
Of course.
We're fine as long as you're happy.
But did he approach you...
...because of your money,
like the last one?
No...
He said he liked me since six months ago.
But, he finally mustered
the courage and told me now.
That's a relief, then
Hey, listen.
We won't let you go
if you make our mom cry.
Wooshik's not that type of person.
Didn't you say you had something
to tell me earlier?
What is it?
Well...
I just wanted to say that
I don't want to say goodbye yet.
Oh my.
My kids are watching,
and you've just blurted it out like that.
Jungi, wait for me.
Would you just hurry up?!
Where are we?
Are we even going the right way?
What the hell is this?
That's why we should've just stayed there.
They could've come back for us.
What? Come back for us?
I've known the stunt
director for eight years.
But, he still doesn't know my name.
Just give it up!
He won't come back looking for us.
Still, we can't even see,
how are we supposed to get home like this?
We'll just try to find the main road
and hitchhike.
Just follow me.
Fine.
-Hold on. Wait a minute.
-What?
My stomach hurts all of a sudden.
I told you to eat only a little.
But you ate three servings.
I was hungry, I couldn't help it!
Is there any toilet around?
How can you go to the bathroom
when we can't see anything?
Just do your business anywhere.
Fine.
But, do you have tissues?
Why would I have tissues
in the middle of a mountain?
-Just wipe it with your necktie.
-Fine.
-Why do you keep getting annoyed at me?
-How can I not be annoyed?
Go do it. I'll stay here.
-What's this?
-My stomach.
Kibong.
There are tissues here.
"Scent Of The Woods Camping Grounds"
How about we play a silent 007 game?
-That sounds good.
-Sure.
You'll get punished if you make a sound.
I'll start first.
Oh, my stomach. Ouch.
It's quiet here.
There must be no one here.
Geez, I thought I'd die.
That's right.
My tissues.
Who's there?!
Kibong.
Kibong. I had tissues with me.
What's wrong with him?
What was that?
What's that sound?
Who are you with?
-Jungi.
-Yeah?
I pooped.
"Waikiki Guest House"
We didn't get paid,
and our eyes got hurt.
All I got is utter humiliation.
What kind of life is this?
That's still better than my situation.
I have to go to a theme park with
the landlady and her sons tomorrow.
They said they want me
to buy them cotton candy.
I have sons now.
How come nothing works out for us?
When I tried my very best.
Why does life never turn out right?
We had pretty great lives back then.
Right?
Yeah, that's true.
When I think about the old times,
I thought that by now,
I'd be in Carnegie Hall
with an orchestral group,
and performing an amazing concert there.
I thought I'd be in Hollywood
and win Oscars.
I thought I'd be in the Major League,
and be playing along side with
Ryu Hyunjin and Choo Shinsoo.
But, you know...
...it's not over for us yet, right?
It's not...
...time to give up yet, right?
Of course not.
I'm never giving up.
That's right.
I can't give up
with the situation I'm in right now.
I have to strike out Choo Shinsoo
before I do.
Let's not do that with a fellow Korean.
You should cut Choo Shinsoo some slack.
Nonsense.
You think so?
Then...
I won't give up until Choo Shinsoo
gets a home-run from my pitch.
-Yes, that's better.
-You crazy punk.
That's it. Let's cheer up.
"Success is for those who don't give up."
An old saint once said that.
That's right.
Let's just try our best until the end.
It'll work out somehow.
But, Wooshik...
...who's Old Saint?
Oh my.
What?
You said the quote was from Old Saint.
Is there any Old Saint in our country?
I've never heard of that name before.
-Why you little...
-Hey, stop. Don't do it.
It'll only infuriate you even more.
Just don't.
Let's go to bed. I'm sleepy.
Yes, you're right.
Hold my hands.
Take me...
Wait...
Who is that Old Saint?
-He's a scientist? He's Chinese, isn't he?
-Shut up!
Take me, too. I can't...
I can't see, either.
Be gentle. Ouch, it hurts.
Hold on.
Oh yeah! I can see.
Wow, I can see now. I can see!
Me too.
Thank goodness.
Why do you guys live like this?
What's wrong with you guys?
By the way, where's Wooshik?
Wooshik?
He went...
...somewhere.
Mom, Mom.
Let's just ride the merry-go-round
one more time.
-One more time. One more time.
-Again?
Wooshik, you don't mind
if we ride one more time, right?
Whoa, uncle, you're the best.
Uncle, you're so cool.
-Ta-da...
-Oh, yes.
Let me get some first.
If you're going to be like this,
then work at a ramyun company.
One chopstick full.
Just take a little.
-You should just eat little.
-I didn't even take anything yet.
-I'm home.
-Hi. Come sit and eat some ramyun.
Did you have fun at the theme park?
That headband looks great on you.
Did you buy her sons cotton candy?
Did her sons say, "Thank you, Father".
"Dad! Daddy, Daddy."
Don't laugh at me!
What is this?
What is all this?
What kind of grown men
like the merry-go-round so much?
I rode that more than 30 times.
Just be patient until we get enough
money for the rent and repair costs.
-He's right.
-What?
That's almost 10 million won all together.
You're telling me to keep this up
until we save that much money?
Then, what?
You rather sleep on the streets
where it's cold and windy?
This is driving me crazy.
-Who is it now?!
-What's wrong?
Eat up. Eat up.
Hello?
What?
Really?
Okay.
I'll be there soon.
What is it? What happened?
It's a wedding planner I know.
She said a wedding singer canceled
and wants me to fill in.
You just got back
and now you're leaving again?
Have some ramyun first.
Do you think I have time
to eat ramyun right now?
I'm going to get money
as soon as I can,
and break free from
this horrifying situation!
You guys shouldn't be
idling around either!
Go out and make some money.
Do you understand?!
Ouch!
It's time for my part-time job.
Hey! Wait for me! Let's go together!
Sit here and eat. Wooshik, you should eat.
Hi.
You're here.
I'm sorry for calling you
at the last minute.
The wedding singer got into an accident.
It's okay. I'm grateful that you did.
I'm in need of money, you see.
Really? It all worked out then.
Let's meet the bride and groom first.
Follow me.
Alright.
-Thank you.
-You're so beautiful.
-Your dress is so pretty.
-That's right.
-Don't forget your bouquet.
-Thank you.
Han Suyeon?
Why are you being so shy?
Let's go meet her.
Hello, Miss Han.
What's wrong?
-Are you crazy?
-On second thought...
...let's leave first. Right now.
Please.
We're already here. How can we leave?
Oh my.
Miss Han, I'm sorry. Please excuse me.
Don't do this.
What's wrong with you?
Oh my god.
Put me down. Put me down. Put me down.
-What's with you?.
-I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
But you need to find someone else to sing.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
Why are you being like this?
Don't ask.
Just let me go.
But the ceremony will start in 30 minutes.
How can I find another singer?
Plus, you said you needed money.
Even if I need money...
...I can't do this.
I'm really sorry.
Alright. Fine.
I'll pay you double.
1 million won.
Money isn't the problem right now.
-1.5 million.
-Whatever. I can't do this.
2 million.
Fine. Whatever.
I can't take this any longer.
Geez.
Don't...
In return...
...I have a favor to ask.
Oh, yes.
I wanted a consultation for a loan.
Yes.
Employer?
I don't have one.
Collateral?
I don't have any.
A car?
I do have one.
Her name is Rebecca.
She's a 2001 or 2002 model...
Hello? Hello?
They hung up on me again.
Gosh, even people at the bank
look down on me too.
-Alright.
-What are you doing?
How can you eat ramyun...
How many packets did you cook?!
Eight.
We should eat a lot
to get the energy to work.
Fine.
Keep eating. Eat up.
So hot.
Can't money just fall from the sky?
A few days ago, a meteorite fell
on a greenhouse and it became a hot topic.
It fell here, too.
-It is dubbed as the "fallen lottery".
-Ah, "lottery".
-Yeah, right.
-In the past, a rare 500 grams meteorite,
was sold for 500 million won.
The outside is seriously blackened,
however since the inside
is denser than most rocks,
it is a defining factor to show
that it might be a meteorite.
500...
500 million won?!
It's true.
I'm serious. For real.
It fell on our guesthouse a few days ago.
Yes.
The coffee shop at Grand Hotel?
Yes, I know where it is.
I'll see you soon, Professor. Goodbye.
Jungi, what did he say?
He collects meteorites,
and said that he'll see our pretty
little thing before he buys it.
-Let's go.
-Hold on.
You're going to take Rebecca?
Yeah.
I don't want to get in that.
It smells weird inside.
She'll be hurt if she hears that.
Shut it. You smell even worse. Just go.
It really does smell pretty bad.
You smell worse.
Let's go.
What's this? What's wrong with this?
It's fine.
You said she smelled weird,
so Becca's upset now.
Just close the door so that we can go.
Sorry.
It's totally fine.
You can just close it really gently.
Like patting a baby.
I'm sorry, Becca.
Gently...
Is this AI, or what?
It's fine. We can close them
at the same time.
Both at the same time.
Alright. One, two, three.
Jungi.
We're so lucky.
I know.
By the way, how much are we selling this?
Earlier, the news said
it's 500 million won for 500 grams.
Then, this one...
-Maybe 1 billion won?
-1 billion...
No, no.
-2 billion?
2 billion?
No. Wait a second.
We'll sell this...
-...pay our rent, then...
-Yes, the rent.
I'm sorry to Rebecca,
but I'll buy a great car too.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Then, what else?
First thing first,
I want go to a fancy buffet
and eat all I want.
-That sounds delicious.
-Then...
I'll go to a fancy sushi restaurant
and eat a tonne of sushi.
Then, I'm going to a fancy
Korean barbecue restaurant,
-and eat...
-Hold on. Hold on for a second.
What are you doing?
This is my meteorite.
Why are you making plans?
What do you mean it's yours?
Why is it yours?
It fell on my guesthouse.
Isn't that what you guys said?
I'm the CEO and you are the investors.
So, I can just pay back your investments.
Isn't that how it goes?
If you say that, then the landlady
is the true owner. How is it yours?
The landlady does not know about this.
Then I can just tell her.
Me.
-Are you crazy?
-What do you want to do?
Do you want to split or not?
Or, I'm just going to give her a call.
Don't do it, or you'll die.
Don't do it.
So, hurry and answer me.
If not, I'm going to press call.
Okay, fine.
This is what you want, right?
Then go for it.
Go ahead. Do it. Do it. Do it.
Fine...
I'll really call her.
-You see it, right? I'm halfway there.
-Do it.
-The call is about to be connected.
If I let go, the call
is going to go through.
Do it.
-Don't do it. Stop.
-Hey.
So, let's split in half.
Let's split...
Hey, focus on the road!
Alright, now, the star of the day,
the bride, will enter.
Please give her a big round of applause.
The bride is entering.
She's beautiful as always.
Because of money, I'm singing
the congratulatory song,
at my first love's wedding.
Life sure is crappy.
-You animal. How can you bite my arm?
-Shut up.
You're unbelievable.
You're really bad at driving.
We're going to split
it exactly in half, okay?
Don't you dare play any tricks...
I'm going to call the landlady right away.
Got it?
Fine. I get it.
Gosh, you're so cheap.
Get off the car.
Hold up.
Why are you holding it?
Let's hold it together.
Are you being suspicious of me right now?
You think I'll run away with this?
I know you'd do more than that.
Just get out.
How can we both get out
if we both hold it?
Why not?
I'll just get out from that side as well.
-Okay, then.
-Yes. After you.
Hey, take it slow.
-Get out.
-I'm trying...
Lee Jungi.
Come over here you.
-I told you not to play tricks.
-Stop it.
-Let's hold it together.
-I won't run away.
-Let's hold it together!
Do we have to go this far?
People are watching at my meteorite.
You let go, then. I'll take it myself.
As if.
You're not even my friend,
you cheap jerk.
Then, if we're not friends,
don't talk informally,
Mr. Lee Jungi.
Geez, I'm sorry, Mr. Kook Kibong.
Too bad. The coffee shop is that way.
-No, it's not. It's that way.
-It's this way.
-You little...
-You don't believe me?
-Let it go.
Ouch.
My 2 billion won.
My meteorite.
No. No!
No!
My 2 billion won.
What if it's only worth 1 million now.
Are you okay?
Are you broken?
Hey, brat.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Han Suyeon.
There she is.
It's really is Suyeon.
Our first love is getting married.
This feels strange.
I know what you mean.
If only one of us really got
to confess our feelings,
we could be standing next to her now.
-Right?
-It could've been me.
Now, it's time for a congratulatory song.
Please give a big round of applause.
What is that?
What on earth is this?
What a peculiar congratulatory singer.
-You are all surprised, right?
-Is this the Masked Singer or what?
Actually, this person is a new singer
who will be debuting soon.
So, he said that he cannot
have his face shown.
We ask for your understanding.
Well, let's listen to the song.
Please applaud.
Initially, there is a song
that the couple requested,
but I do not know that song well,
so I prepared a different song.
What are you doing here?
Hi, Suyeon.
Did I surprise you?
Sorry.
What are you doing, though?
This?
I'm rearranging the song.
I'll be singing at the concert.
You're performing at a concert?
Can I go watch?
Yes, of course.
Of course you can.
I'll give you an invitation.
Really?
Thanks.
The next song has been requested
by Han Suyeon from class 2-3.
It's "I love you" by Lee Jaehoon.
I requested this song.
Wooshik, what do you think
about this song?
It's nice.
It's my favorite song.
Oh, really?
Should I practice this song and
sing it for you later?
Are you serious?
That's a promise, okay?
Promise me.
I sincerely congratulate you two
on your marriage.
And to the bride...
...please...
...be happy.
Goodbye, Suyeon.
Be happy, Suyeon.
Next... the couple will pay respect
to their parents...
-...who have raised them.
-Great job. We did it thanks to you.
Here's your money.
No, thanks.
I kept my promise, so that's enough
Promise?
What promise?
-What about the money?
-Give it to them as a wedding gift.
It's the masked singer.
We enjoyed your performance.
Kibong. Jungi.
What?
Who are you?
It's me.
Cha Wooshik, how are you here?
You...
You're the masked singer
that sang just now?
Well... About that...
Why are you guys here?
What's with that rock?
Well, the thing is...
This rock...
Whatever. It's a long story.
Let's go out and talk.
Yeah, yeah. Let's leave.
Hurry up.
-What the...
-What...
What's he doing?
Over there.
That...
There...
What is this?
What's going on?
This scene happens a lot in movies.
Isn't that Suyeon's ex-boyfriend?
Sir, the company went bankrupt.
Hurry and leave this place.
Get out of here, sir.
-Bankrupt?
-Jungi, what's bankrupt?
Geez.
Suyeon, you should go
somewhere safe for now.
My meteorite!
Why is that your meteorite?
It's my 2 billion won.
-You promised to split in half.
-My 2 billion.
-No.
"2 billion won"?
What are you talking about?
Let go. Let me go.
Gosh. My phone is completely broken.
My meteorite.
My 2 billion won.
Who the heck took my 2 billion won?
Who told you to come here with that thing?
You think we know this would happen?
Wooshik, you jerk.
It's good manners to watch your first love
for the last time as she gets married.
Then, what about you?
You even sang the congratulatory song
to your first love.
I did that to earn some money.
Whatever. I don't care.
Our money is gone now.
Let's...
For the last time...
...can we just watch the security footage?
Just once more.
Once more.
We've already checked it ten times.
What else is there to see? Let's just go.
One last time, please...
-Give it up.
-One more time...
You never know.
Hurry up.
Hold on.
Jung...
...wasn't the trunk open earlier?
I don't know.
It just opens and closes by itself.
I want to go back!
My 2 billion won!
The wedding hall was turned upside down.
They bragged so much
about how rich they were,
but they went bankrupt,
so the creditor came.
It was just a complete chaos.
Lee Jungi, I'm a fool for trusting you.
-Geez, shut up.
-We lost that 2 billion won...
It's not your meteorite, it's mine.
-Stop fighting, you two!
-This useless car.
-Shut up.
-Will you stop fighting?
You shut up, too.
We just lost 2 billion. Darn it.
-Geez. You call this a car?
-It's all wasted.
It's an automatic door now.
Darn it.
Are you okay?
What's wrong with this door?
Whatever. There's nothing
to steal, anyway.
-Just get rid of this crappy car!
-Go in.
Geez.
This is driving me crazy.
Wait. Hold on.
What's that noise?
I think it's coming from the car.
What kind of noise
would come from the car?
You must be going crazy. Crazy.
Shut up. Just go inside.
Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey!
Why does it keep making a noise?
That's odd.
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's...
Something's in there.
What do you mean?
Let me see.
You better not be joking
about that meteorite.
I'm traumatized by the meteorite today.
What could there be in here?
"Welcome to Waikiki Season 2"
We met our first love
for the first time in 10 years.
We should leave a good impression.
Is this the time to talk
about "first love?"
-Wooshik.
-That's your girlfriend?
-Should I just stay the night?
-What?
The landlady is not well, up here.
She is not well, up here.
-I need to pee really badly.
-Action.
Are you Bidam?
-You don't need...
-Director. Hold on.
There are bugs.
It's so dusty.
Kang Minho, come to your senses.
You're telling me to go there?
We're stuck.
What's inside all of this?
-What do you mean? It's all for you.
-These?
Honey.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing I can do.
Who is it?
Us? We're Suyeon's first loves.
What about it?