At one going
Who dares to功
To face yourке
Wave at the wind
선와의
Kid
You're still a little bit slow.
Now that I've made it to the big game,
you're running out of ideas.
Running out of ideas?
Father,
have you ever heard of the God's hand?
What?
The God's hand?
Then it's the Heaven's will.
The Heaven's hand.
I've lost.
When can you stop?
I didn't notice at all.
Are you that good now?
I've lived for so many years.
I'm not a fool.
Come on, practice more.
Go, go, go.
Young Master,
Miss Li Yanran wants to go to Li's house for you.
Li Yanran wants to see me?
Why?
What are you talking about?
Miss Li asked you to go.
Then hurry up and go.
Go, go, go.
What?
Hurry up and go.
Okay, okay.
Here.
God bless, God bless.
My Feiyang finally has a girlfriend.
Bless, bless, bless, bless.
Bless, bless, bless.
Okay, you'll know when you come.
You should be more enthusiastic.
This is...
You, you're here.
I've seen Uncle and Aunt.
Feiyang is here.
Sit down.
Come, come, come.
Come inside.
Hurry up.
Please, please.
Feiyang, come.
I'll fill it for you.
I wish you a good result in the future.
You'll be a great model.
You'll be a great model for me.
Come.
Okay.
I'm here to discuss with you
about what happened.
When did you and Yanran
get engaged?
G... Geng?
Yes.
Your father and I
have already engaged.
You're the only one in the Zhao family.
So you're the one who's in trouble.
I always think
it's good to see my wife.
But I'm always nervous
when I see this.
Uncle.
Why don't you discuss this with my father?
It's because
you have three children.
I'm also a little selfish.
I hope Yanran can be a great model.
You don't know how to talk, do you?
Of course not.
Father, I've made a promise.
I'll treat Feiyang to a meal today.
It's for your own good.
Feiyang, don't listen to my father.
I'm looking for you today
to have a simple meal.
It's not meaningful.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
Please.
Yanran,
I've found a place to rest.
Let's...
Bajie.
Zhao Feiyang,
why are you here?
I'm here to have a meal.
You're here to have a meal with your family?
Yes.
I was invited.
You were invited.
What?
What's the problem?
What's going on?
With Zhao Feiyang's
reputation in Tianxuan City,
he's invited to have a meal with his family.
And he looks like a good model.
Yanran, why are you still standing here?
Your sister is here.
Why don't you invite her to the meal?
I'm sorry, Bajie.
I was just born.
Since you're here,
let's have a meal together.
Let Chu Ge have a few dishes.
Yes.
I'll toast you.
Okay.
Old man,
are you drunk?
How can I be drunk?
Come on.
I'm drunk.
This wine...
I'm not drunk.
It's just a little bit.
It's not good.
Don't be so sad.
Eat more.
The fish in the net is still good.
It tastes the same as when I was a kid.
Why are you looking at me?
Have a meal.
Here.
All right.
Just a chicken leg.
Here you go.
Eat.
Are you hiding something from me?
What's so special about you?
Sister Bai Zhi,
didn't you say that there's a good place to practice?
Let's go together.
Are you changing the topic, Yan Ran?
No.
The dance meeting is in a hurry.
If you want to practice,
let's hurry up and grab some time.
I was going to call you first,
but I'll call you Sister Qiu Shui.
Call her?
I'm not going. I'm not going to talk to her.
Then...
Then don't call her.
Sister Qiu Shui doesn't like to be called.
Fine.
Then let's go.
Okay.
Here it is.
Someone dares to break into here?
What practice is this?
There's a border.
What's going on?
Zhao Feiyang and Yan Ran are together.
They're related.
Don't think too much.
It's exactly what you think.
I'm not going to call her.
What do I think?
Sister Qiu Shui.
We were outside and we were forced into the border.
So we came in together.
How did the three of you come in together?
Anyway, it's a coincidence.
That's really a coincidence.
You're really my sister Qiu Shui.
You let me go and bring the dog with me to this place.
Dog?
Chen Qiu Shui, you're going to marry me again?
Don't talk to me.
I can hear you talking and I feel disgusting.
You...
You bastard.
You resigned?
You can't think of it?
You'd better be in the Martial Arts Contest and not meet me.
I'm going to kill you.
I'll make you regret it.
I regret it now.
After the Martial Arts Contest,
before we go to the North, let's get married.
I'm not in a good mood with you.
What did you say?
I said, get married.
Who can be so cruel?
There are three ways to live a life.
How many times have I been cruel?
How sweet is the cold spring?
I'm happy.
I'm drunk. I'm drunk. I'm drunk. I'm drunk.
Who is the person who has a warm face?
How can I live with tears?
I'm not a good person.
How can I be nice to him?
Who can be so cruel?
I'm drunk. I'm drunk. I'm drunk.
Who is the person who has a warm face?
How can I live with tears?
Who can be so cruel?
I'm happy. I'm drunk. I'm drunk.
Who is the person who has a warm face?
How can I live with tears?
Who can be so cruel?