Come on in.
Wow, your place is cleaner than I expected.
Cleaner than you thought?
Well, yeah, I live alone.
If you don’t keep up with it, it turns into a mess fast.
I’m jealous. My place is always a disaster.
Go ahead, sit down.
I’ll whip up some snacks real quick.
Sure.
Is this like a member logbook?
What the heck is this?
Name: Kim Do-yoon. Occupation: Novelist.
Personality: Rarely shows emotion, doesn’t talk much, but sharp observer.
His eyes keep lingering in my head.
This feels like more than just being a fan.
- Do-yoon.
- Want to start with a beer?
Yeah, sure.
What were you doing?
Just reading a book.
What book?
A book about fitness.
Then should we make this official as our first running partner session?
Have you been writing well these days?
No, not really.
Why? Is something wrong?
Honestly, I just can’t come up with any ideas.
That’s partly why I started working out.
I thought maybe getting in shape would help spark something.
That’s actually a great idea.
Taking the first step takes a lot of courage, and it’s not easy.
But you’ve already made that leap, Do-yoon.
I’m sure new ideas will start flowing.
You think so?
Do-yoon?
Would it be okay if I shared a plot idea with you?
You have a story synopsis, Hyun-woo?
Yes.
If you’re okay with it.
As your fan, Do-yoon,
and as someone who loves novels,
I’ve had a few ideas.
Hmm...
The main character slowly changes after meeting someone.
At first, they found the person annoying,
but strangely, being near them made it easier to breathe.
So little by little, they open their heart.
But then...
The other person might not even realize it.
Is this really a story for a novel?
Yes, it is.
Please, tell me more.
Thanks to you, I had a really great time today.
Do-yoon.
It’s a leaf.
Oh, I’m sorry.
Do-yoon, why did you close your eyes?
Uh, well...
Did you think I was going to kiss you or something?
Huh?
Just kidding.
But you know what?
I can hear your heartbeat, Do-yoon.
I’m not the only one hearing it, right?
It’s so quiet here...
Your heartbeat changes depending on the situation.
But your heartbeat, Do-yoon,
thump thump thump...
It sounds like the rhythm of excitement.
So I want to respond too.
I'm feeling excited too.
On a street where cherry blossoms are falling,
they share a romantic kiss.
The two are different but strangely similar.
They both have walls in their hearts.
So breaking down those walls is simpler than you think.
How?
Just by being there with them.
Casually, slowly.
And then, before you know it...
they become someone who can't live without you.
In the end, does that person fall in love?
Yes, probably from the very beginning.
It's a story, of course.
I think I talked too much in front of the writer.
What I just told you—
please take it as reference only.
It’s a bit scattered with no clear beginning or end.
No, it was great.
It was a story good enough to make even a stopped heart beat again.
Really?
It sounded even better coming from you, the writer.
Next time, tell me your story, not just mine.
Alright.
But you can’t fall asleep if it’s boring.
No way.
I’ll be taking notes while I listen!
You’re funny too.
Oh, I’m serious though.
Let me grab a pen and some paper real quick.
I'll start writing now.
It’s okay.
Let’s toast first.