- Taxi!
- Be careful.
- Okay.
There's an easy way to check
if you're in love or not.
If you see that person together
with someone else
and you get jealous or not.
I can't… deny it any longer.
I've fallen…
in love.
I have no memory of how I got home.
I'm home.
What's wrong? Why were the lights off?
You came home quite late.
Ms. Maiko was really drunk,
so I had no choice but to take her home.
It's late for just having dropped her off!
Huh?
I went to drink alone afterward.
Is that true?
Yeah, it's true.
Wait, what's wrong?
Don't tell me you're jealous?
If that's true, I'd be really happy.
No…
I'm…
I won't cheat.
Because my heart belongs to you.
So, about my investigation report…
I don't care
about the investigation report.
No, what the heck am I thinking?
In short, Maiko Suzusaka was blackmailing
the R&D manager, Takashi Mizusaki,
who was receiving money from the company
he was leaking information to.
Yes.
Looks like they both got terminated.
They got what they deserved.
Shiba, you did well.
Thank you, sir.
Let's get right into the next case.
This client is managed
by our New York office,
a Japanese automotive parts manufacturer.
The prospects are grim though.
Of course I'll accept it.
If you succeed with this case,
your name will spread across New York.
However, there isn't much time.
We need you to show results within a week.
One week should be enough.
No, a week won't be nearly enough.
I won't cheat.
PARTNER
RYOMA SHIBA
Because my heart belongs to you.
No!
When I think about him,
I can't focus on work.
Are you okay? Can I come in?
Yes.
I heard you accepted
the automotive parts manufacturer case.
If you can win this,
it'll be a big leap forward for you.
And you'll be closer to becoming
the Guardian of the Law.
Both work and love are smooth sailing, eh?
Love?
Yeah.
What on earth are you talking about?
Isn't love…
the very best…
MEGAVITA E
…energy drink?
Ryo!
Hey, Ryo!
- Ryo.
- This can't go on…
I can't stay this way.
Ryo?
Love is not an energy drink.
It's an obstruction, it's evil!
To become the Guardian of the Law…
I must…
quit being in love.
Ryo, what time are you coming home today?
Hmm?
Acqua Pazza!
Nice, Themis! Good idea!
I won't be home due to a new case.
What?
Ryo said he wasn't coming home.
Is there anything I can help with?
NO
I bottled up my feelings for Haruto
and drowned myself in work.
CORPORATE LAW DEPARTMENT
REPRESENTATIVE PARTNER
I drowned in work.
Drowned in work.
And drowned.
Ryo.
Ryo!
Are you okay, Ryo?
Am I so in love
that I'm hallucinating now?
Your skin's really breaking out.
You've been pulling all-nighters.
It's his scent.
This isn't a hallucination!
W-Why did you come?!
What?
I brought you food and clothes.
Since eating only protein bars
will be harmful to your body.
You're the harmful one.
When I think about you,
my brain goes numb as if a poison
had spread through my body.
Ryo. Here, eat this.
Here we go.
Here. Say "ah."
Then love is a poison after all?
How is it?
The citric acid in those pickled plums
will help your tired body recover.
You like that kind
of logical stuff, don't you?
It's good.
I'm glad.
I'm sure I will never forget the taste
of the rice ball I ate that day.
Hang in there, Ryo.
After finishing Haruto's food,
the path to victory
suddenly came into view.
All right.
Is love the very best
energy drink after all?
So you're one step away from victory?
No.
Hmm?
To secure a comeback win for this case,
the current plan isn't enough.
That thoroughness of yours
is your strong point.
When I watch you, you remind me of him.
Him?
He started at the same time as me.
He was just undefeatable.
Everybody expected him
to become a world-famous lawyer.
What is that person doing now?
He fell for a terrible woman and
lost his status and reputation.
After losing everything he disappeared.
He was such a highly competent man,
but he was head over heels in love
and it got the best of him.
What a foolish man.
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Please excuse me for today.
What?
I'm the foolish one!
This is no time
to be head over heels in love!
Besides…
It's those real estate scammers.
If people find out that my partner
is a fraud, I'll lose everything.
Have I lost my sense of judgment
due to love?
I knew that love was
just an obstruction to me.
It's a poison.
But anyway, what is this?
It feels like…
my body's burning up as if a poison
were spreading throughout my body.
Ryo, are you okay? Ryo!
Ryo, don't get up yet!
Please, just rest in bed.
But I still have work left--
It's all done.
What?
Wait one second.
Here.
All of my unfinished work
is neatly organized.
How did you…
I read and studied all
of those books there.
All of them?
Yeah, all of them.
Laws are amazing.
The law exists to protect
the weak people in society.
It made me want to study more and more.
You know, I've been through many jobs,
but this is by far the most fun one.
That's why I want to study more and more,
become your greatest partner,
and help all kinds of people.
Anyhow, just rest for now.
Here.
Don't give me that nonsense.
What?
You want to help all kinds of people?
You're someone
who only thinks about yourself.
You're from the underground world.
You're a fraud.
Ryo…
Since when did you know?
Just leave my place at once.
Right.
I'll cause trouble if I'm here.
Thanks for everything up to now, Ryo.
Hey, Ryo.
To be honest,
I only thought of you
as a good person to tease.
What?!
How cute.
Don't tease me.
Maybe I should upload this.
But now…
I'm so stupid.
I'm a fraud.
I can't believe I seriously fell in love.
Haru!
Yo, how were you guys?
Hey, wassup?
Here, allowance.
What?
This much? You sure?
Yeah.
Since I'll be making good money soon.
Why's that, Haru?
I'm going back to where I came from.
What?
That's right.
I'm from the underground world,
I'm not worthy of Ryo,
who lives on the surface.
Goodbye, Ryo.
I hear you've got a good job?
This was the right decision.
Where are you now, Haruto?
Ryo!
That's not where you belong.
Ryo, you know you can't leave me.
Subtitle translation by:
Kanami Kitabayashi