What is this?
This is so cool.
- What is this thing?
- Look at this.
- It's amazing.
- When did they build this?
This is really...
(The older members appear
with admiration.)
The design looks amazing.
Gosh, what's that?
What is that sculpture?
- This is so cool.
- My goodness.
- What is all this?
- This place looks so cool.
This is Songhyeon Green Plaza,
located near Anguk Station.
- I know.
- Yes. Today,
to celebrate the Seoul Biennale
of Architecture and Urbanism,
which takes place every two years,
we've gathered in front...
of the Humanize Wall,
a landmark structure.
- I love it.
- It looks so cool.
- So, this is what it is.
- It looks amazing.
- This is a piece of work.
- There are sculptures here.
The Seoul Museum
of Architecture and Urbanism...
offers free access to exhibitions
that showcase architecture...
from Seoul and around the world,
including the works
currently on display here.
- Is it free?
- Yes, it's free of charge.
- It's K-architecture.
- Designers from around the world.
- It's amazing.
- Right.
Seoul is now a truly global city.
It is a global city, indeed.
So, can anyone visit
the exhibitions?
You can see the architecture
from around the world.
People of all ages and genders?
- That makes sense!
- In Seoul.
It'll be great
to go there with your family.
- This is really...
- Was it...
- last year?
- We played foot volleyball here.
- Exactly.
- This is the place.
Yes. With the idols, right?
- The idols were here.
- Yes.
- BABYMONSTER.
- You look cold, by the way.
Yes, I'm cold.
Hey, aren't they too short?
He's a so-called
"Young Forty" these days.
- The Young Forty.
- This is what the Young Forty does.
Why would you say that?
- The Young Forty.
- Hey, show us your phone.
- Show it off!
- I really didn't know.
- Go ahead and show us.
- I didn't know when I bought this.
The Young Forty.
- Not you!
- Give it to me. I'm fine with that.
I showed off my new phone...
during my radio show like this.
And suddenly,
people posted a lot of comments
saying, "Young Forty."
Young Forty? Why?
But on the other hand, we have...
always been told to do...
- whatever we wanted.
- I know.
- We were told to do that.
- That's what we've been told.
But those who pursue youth...
- And now..
- I know. This is really...
Who do you think you are
to judge me? Darn it!
Haha isn't Young Forty!
- Who do you think you are?
- Haha is still young!
Look.
He is the epitome of Young Forty.
(Ha Dong Hoon's life in his 40s,
where he was busy chasing youth)
- My gosh.
- I got this sponsored.
By the way, when we were
talking about Young Forty,
Seok Jin had no idea
what the meme really meant.
- I didn't know.
- "I'm Young Fifty."
- I had no idea.
- Young Fifty?
- He liked it.
- Right.
- He's not Young Fifty.
- Young Sixty.
Actually, he's not Young Fifty.
- Yes.
- Are you sure you're Young Fifty?
- Of course, you brat!
- Young Sixty.
- Haha's Young Forty...
and my Young Fifty
are totally different.
- You're Young Sixty.
- And...
- Sixty!
- Why do you keep saying fifty?
- What's wrong with you?
- Be honest about your age now.
- Here's the thing.
- I'll make it clear here.
- Okay.
The "Young" of my Young Fifty
doesn't mean youth.
It means eternity.
I'm in my fifties forever.
- How lame.
- It's so boring.
- I'm serious.
- Enough.
- How lame.
- I'll be in my fifties next year.
I almost threw up in the morning.
I feel nauseated.
I'll be in my 50s for 3 years.
- That's so lame.
- Don't be ridiculous.
This is like
Jee Seok Jin's campaign.
- My campaign?
- Jee Seok Sam!
- I'm Young Fifty!
- He keeps saying Young Fifty.
- Forever Fifty.
As you saw earlier,
we have a guest joining us today.
Please bring the guest in.
This is controversial.
- Is he good enough to come alone?
- I don't think...
- he's good enough to come alone.
- He's not enough.
- Is he really alone?
- You're being slow.
- Hurry and run.
- Run.
Run.
- Jonathan.
- You should run.
I can still see your feet.
- Hello.
- His shoes...
- Okay.
- Stand here.
Jonathan.
You came from far away.
- Okay.
- Your shoes are soaked.
Hey, Jonathan.
You didn't text us on Chuseok.
- Right.
- Did you?
How could you be so disrespectful?
- It's not like that.
- We are closer than that.
I thought you would be busy.
- Come on.
- Why would we be busy on Chuseok?
- The production crew doesn't work.
- No one's busy.
He was on our show last September,
so it's been a year.
- Really?
- Jonathan.
- We met again after a year.
- I see.
That doesn't sound right.
- It feels like we met often.
- Jonathan isn't a guest.
- Exactly. He's just...
- He's just stopping by.
- He's our family.
- Right.
I'm very grateful.
Why is it so silent?
- We're not saying anything.
- Hey.
- This is why...
- Why is it so silent?
This is why he isn't good enough
to be here alone.
This is why.
- And...
- Seriously...
- We aren't usually so quiet.
- You should keep talking.
Jonathan is quite busy,
- so it's hard to have him here.
- Right.
He's still not good enough
to be here as a single guest.
- That's right.
- These days...
Am I the only guest for today?
- We should ask how he's doing.
- Yes. You're alone.
- Are the other guests hiding?
- We don't need to ask.
- Behind the walls?
- What?
We have nothing to ask about him.
Should we ask him?
- Do you have any questions?
- How have you been?
I recently lost 2kg.
Our response...
- Hey, you can't be here alone.
- Why...
- Losing 2kg is not important.
- It should be at least 10kg.
- What else?
- He shouldn't be here alone.
It's okay.
What do I need to be here
as a single guest?
You should at least
have something...
- to tell us about.
- Something that makes us curious.
We need to run up to you in awe.
(He should bring a bunch of
intriguing stories to come alone.)
You guys have gathered here today
to participate in the Biennale.
You will first have a mission
to get a chance card...
- that will help you with your work.
- I see.
The mission consists
of two types of running.
- What's that?
- Are we doing it here?
- It's so muddy.
- Right here?
We asked your stylists to get you...
- cheap pants in advance.
- You did?
I see. Did you talk to them?
Are you wearing shorts
because it's muddy?
Well done, Young Forty.
- Young Forty.
- The shorts are expensive, though.
- Good.
- Young Forty.
It's finally Haha's time.
Right.
- Finally, Haha...
- For Young Forty.
It's Haha's time.
(Exclaiming)
(Complete)
It's for the Young Forty.
Young Forty.
(The meme of Young Forty
is coming to its end.)
- Okay.
- I'll explain the first game.
The first game is the 80m Rank Race.
- An 80m race?
- What's that?
You must get your running records...
in the order
chosen by the production crew.
You are supposed to achieve
your own records,
from 1st to 8th place,
- in the specified order.
- To match the given order?
It's not about winning the race.
Let's say I randomly pick
Ji Hyo's ranking,
and she is supposed to rank second.
- Then you should work together...
- We should match it.
to make Ji Hyo rank second.
- Really?
- Yes. The rest of the members.
- We should think about the ranking.
- It's the game of wit.
But all the members
must finish the lap...
- within 35 seconds.
- Within 35 seconds.
One person has to finish...
- Per person.
- the lap in 35 seconds.
And we need to match the ranking.
We should have the fast runners
run fast anyway.
Please decide on the first runner.
Then I will pick a number
for the runner's ranking.
- Okay.
- Who should go first?
- Jae Seok, the first runner...
- Shouldn't it be Ji Hyo?
- Let's go with Ji Hyo.
- She should be the reference point.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo, you go first.
I'll go first.
Song Ji Hyo.
- She picked the number.
- Ji Hyo should run...
(Ji Hyo's goal is to come in 5th.)
- to come in fifth.
- It's not bad.
- Fifth place.
- I can go slow.
- Then...
- She should finish in the 20s.
- It's the middle rank.
Then you should run fast.
Ji Hyo, you should finish the lap
in about 25...
- to 27 seconds.
- About 25 seconds.
No. It doesn't have to be so fast.
She shouldn't be too slow.
- Ready.
- What should she do?
- It's fifth place.
- You don't have to be so fast.
- That's what I think.
- Ready.
Don't run too fast.
- This is...
- Not so fast.
- Good.
- You shouldn't be too fast.
- Don't be so fast.
- She's the fifth place.
You have to finish it in 35 seconds.
- Right. It's 35 seconds.
- Isn't one of us supposed...
- to be counting the numbers?
- She should hurry anyway.
- Run!
- You should run.
- Hurry!
- I think you should hurry.
- How many seconds has it been?
- Keep it up!
What's her record?
- Has it been 20 seconds?
- It's fast.
- You're too fast.
- Ji Hyo shouldn't run too fast.
- She's fast.
- Come here.
- It's okay.
- All right.
- I think this is good enough.
- Okay.
- Is it 26?
- I bet it's 24 or 25.
- I should be the fifth.
- Ji Hyo's record...
- is 25.40 seconds.
- Okay.
- That's perfect.
- It's 25.40 seconds.
- Good.
- It's not bad.
- That's good.
- It is good.
- Well done.
- Next up is...
- Young Forty. No, Young Sixty.
- Young Sixty.
- Young Fifty.
- Young Sixty?
- Young Sixty goes next.
- Yes. Did you not know?
- Just don't pick number one.
He's in his sixties now.
- Is he 60?
- He looks young, doesn't he?
Running in jeans.
Just don't pick number one.
He looks young, doesn't he?
- Running in jeans.
- He should be in first place.
- First place?
- Seok Jin, Jonathan just said...
- Seok Jin, Jonathan just said this.
"Is he 60?"
- No.
- First place.
- I'm not.
- You need to come in first place?
- He's got first place.
- Are you?
- Just run fast.
- She picked number one.
This is better.
- Run as fast as you can.
- I'll just run fast.
- You are not so slow.
- You have to run fast.
(Start)
- Run fast.
- Go!
- Good. It's okay.
- Run faster.
- What if he trips and falls?
- Run as fast as you can.
(The Young Sixty is jogging
in the middle of the Biennale.)
- Run fast!
- Hurry!
- Just come quickly.
- Run fast.
- Seok Jin, run.
- Seok Jin.
- Hurry!
(With the support and encouragement
of the younger members,)
(he successfully finishes
the 80m lap on two legs.)
- That was fast.
- Sixty!
- That was good.
- What's his record?
- I bet it's 10.
- It's 15 seconds.
- Young Sixty!
- Young Fifty!
- Young Fifty.
- All right. Seok Jin's record...
- is 20.08 seconds.
- My gosh.
- It's 20 seconds.
- It's pretty good, right?
- That's good.
- It's not bad.
- But he ran at full speed.
- It's 20.08 seconds.
- At full speed...
- It's okay.
It's only 20 seconds?
But he ran at full speed.
- That doesn't make sense.
- That's because...
- he had to make a turn.
- Right.
- That's why.
- He had to slow down.
- He didn't run straight.
- And the ground...
- is muddy.
- All right then.
The first place record is
20 seconds.
- That's enough.
- There's enough time.
- Do you want me to go next?
- Yes.
- Okay. You go next.
- Me.
It's burdensome
to be the last runner.
- Right?
- It's Jong Kook.
It's better to run first.
- It's hard for me.
- The last runner is important.
- He should be in second place.
- Then...
Make it 21 seconds.
- No.
- It should be 21 seconds.
- It's 21 seconds.
My turn is good.
You have enough time
between the two.
What was your record?
- Between 20 and 25 seconds.
- Right.
Young Sixty, are you out of breath?
It should be about 21...
- or 22 seconds.
- Right.
- It's easy for you.
- All right.
- Ready.
- You can make it 21 seconds.
- Yes, 21 or 22 seconds.
- Go.
- Okay.
- Yes, 21 or 22 seconds.
- Go.
- Okay.
- Go!
- He's got it!
- He's fast.
- Go.
- Okay.
- One, two, three,
- four, five...
- He's got it!
- He looks like a bear.
- He runs like this.
We should be counting numbers.
- All right.
- Me.
Good.
- Wait.
- Slow down.
Slow down.
- Wait.
- Don't come yet.
Is it too soon?
- Come closer.
- He's too fast.
- Twenty, twenty-one.
- I think it's too soon.
- Come in. Twenty-three.
- Okay.
Twenty-three.
- Is it done? Did I do it right?
- No?
- Is it too soon?
He was fast.
All right.
Kim Jong Kook's record...
(If he is faster than 20.08 seconds,
the mission fails.)
- is 22.54 seconds.
- Yes!
- It is 22.54 seconds.
- You did it.
- What a relief.
- It's a relief.
- I got it right.
- Good. Did you count?
- Yes.
- Daniel.
- Daniel is next.
- I wish he were in first place.
- I'll pick a number.
- Okay.
- It's possible.
The records are good now.
It's easy for the lower ranks.
- It's third place.
- Three.
- Make it 24 seconds.
- It should be around 24 seconds.
Ready.
He's not a good runner, though.
One.
- He's just...
- You shouldn't run too fast.
He's not a good runner, though.
One.
(The human stopwatch
starts counting.)
- He...
- Look at his legs.
- Look at his feet.
- He's faster than I was.
Ji Hyo, was your record 25 seconds?
- My record was 25 seconds.
- Hang on.
- Darn it. This is...
- Hey.
- It's hard to stop here.
- You should hurry.
- Make a spurt.
- No. It's okay.
- You have to come.
- Come.
- You should wait here.
- Fifteen, sixteen...
- No, you fool!
- Hey.
- No.
- Keep running.
- No. Wait here.
- Wait.
- No.
- Don't come.
- Wait.
- You should come.
- Come.
- He's being slow.
- Done.
- It was too late.
- No. It's perfect.
- He waited too long here.
Daniel is in third place,
- and his record is 25.03 seconds.
- Darn it.
- See?
- It was too late.
- His record is 25.03 seconds.
- Darn it.
- It was too late.
- Seok Jin.
- He should get here first.
- I was counting.
- He should wait here.
- He was too late.
- Right.
- It was too late.
I was counting.
- So...
- You should come quickly.
Ji Hyo is in fifth place now.
- Yes.
- She's in fifth place.
Daniel is in third place.
The gap between them...
- is only 0.4 seconds.
- It's over then.
- It's over.
- No.
We have to get the 0.4 seconds.
Yes. Fourth place...
should be slower
than 25.03 seconds...
- and faster...
- He should've come sooner.
- than 25.40 seconds.
- You shouldn't have stopped.
- He should've waited here.
- But...
- Am I going next?
- We're doomed.
- I'll go.
- We're in trouble.
You have no idea.
- As you run...
- Of course not.
You should count as you run.
- Right.
- You should be in sixth place.
- In 6th place?
- Make it 27 seconds.
- Slower than her.
- Around 27 seconds.
- Around 26 or 27 seconds.
- All right.
- Around 27 seconds?
- You can go slow.
- You should go slow.
- Ready.
Around 27 seconds. Like a jog.
Okay.
As slow as Ji Hyo.
- No.
- I think you're too slow.
Go faster than that.
- You should go faster.
- It's 26 seconds, so it's okay.
Jae Seok, go fast
and slow down when you return.
Eleven, twelve,
- thirteen, fourteen,
- I should go quickly anyway.
- You should come.
- fifteen,
- sixteen, seventeen,
- No.
- eighteen, nineteen,
- twenty, twenty-one...
- Just come here.
- Wait, Jae Seok.
- How long has it been?
- Twenty-three,
- A little more.
- twenty-four,
- Twenty-four.
- twenty-five.
- Come.
(If he finishes faster than Ji Hyo,
the mission fails.)
- Come here.
- It should be around 27 seconds.
- He's in 6th place?
It should be around 26 seconds.
It's 26 seconds.
- It's 26.03 seconds.
- Yes!
- Good.
- Good job.
- We succeeded.
- It's perfect.
- Well done.
- Jonathan.
- Me?
- I'll go next.
- Jonathan. Okay, good.
- You can run wearing that.
- Okay.
Jonathan isn't good at running.
He says,
"Jonathan isn't good at running."
Isn't he a good runner?
My nickname was
Yongsan Usain Bolt. Seriously.
- Jonathan.
- I'm ready.
- It's seventh place.
- Our single guest.
Seventh place!
It should be
between 28 and 29 seconds.
- Ready.
- In 29 seconds.
(The goal is 29 seconds.)
- Around 29 seconds.
- Young Forty, are you cold?
(Jonathan sets off!)
- Four, five...
(The old stopwatch
is still working properly!)
Thirteen.
(Josain Bolt
with a unique running technique)
- Wait.
- Twenty-five.
Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven.
You should come.
- Okay. It's perfect.
- He was right on time, right?
- His record is 28.15 seconds.
- See?
- That's good enough.
- We did it.
- That's just good.
- It's not bad.
No one intended it,
but it was just good enough.
- We intended it.
- That's good enough.
- I'll go next.
- All right.
- Good.
- These days,
he's working out his legs.
- Go, Young Forty.
- Haha.
- Young Forty.
- Good.
- It's fourth place.
- Oh, no.
What's the record for fourth place?
- It's fourth place.
- Oh, no.
What's the record for fourth place?
- This is...
- Is it the 0.4 seconds?
- This is it.
- It should be 25 seconds.
It should be between 25.03
and 25.40 seconds.
- That's impossible.
- Just give it a try.
- Haha.
- Give it a go. You can do it.
Just give it a try. It's possible.
- We will count here.
- You can do it.
- Get here as soon as possible.
- I will...
run as fast as possible.
It should be 25.40 seconds?
- My gosh.
- Your shoes are perfect.
- Go.
- Ready.
- You can do this.
- Go, Young Forty!
Go!
Not yet.
Young Forty!
- One.
- Run.
- Run fast.
- Three.
- Hey!
- Turn around.
Hurry.
You can do this!
Gosh, it's cold.
- That's difficult.
- Young Forty!
Eleven.
Not yet.
You should get here first.
Wait here.
Come in now!
- Go!
- All right.
- I think it was fast.
- It was a little fast.
- A little fast.
- No.
He was one second faster.
- He was fast.
Haha's record is...
- It's 24 seconds, right?
- I think he was slow.
It's 25 seconds...
It's 25.60 seconds.
It was so close, but he failed.
- It's amazing that it was so close.
- So close.
- It was really close.
- We were almost there.
- Hey, you were...
- So close.
- That was amazing.
- Unbelievable.
- It was so close.
- I know.
We could've succeeded.
We should've counted when he ran.
What a shame.
- It was so close.
-The first mission...
- What a shame.
- failed.
We have the second mission.
The second mission is...
the Tail Running.
- What is it?
- Tail Running.
You wear a long tail
around your waist.
- Each person runs for 20 seconds.
- That's easy.
The goal is to keep...
your tail above the ground
for 20 seconds while running.
(That means
they should run around like a dog.)
- But...
- Hey.
- Young Sixty.
- What do you think you're doing?
This is upsetting.
I can't rest.
He ran 80m at full speed,
and it took over 20 seconds.
- This is Running Man.
- We will measure...
- We can't rest.
- how long the tail...
- remains on the ground.
- I see.
The eight members will take turns.
- That's better.
- The goal is to keep...
the combined time under 50 seconds.
- I see.
- That's not so bad.
What's the tail?
- The tail is too long.
- This is...
- It will drop well.
- Is it that long?
- This is...
- How are we supposed to run?
My gosh. This is too long.
This is too long.
- But...
- It's really long.
It's not a tail.
- I know.
- It's rolled up. Unbelievable.
You shouldn't step outside the line.
You should make a big turn.
Okay.
I'll go first.
- Haha.
- Put it on as late as possible.
Go, Young Forty!
- He is...
- The wind...
- Make good use of the wind.
- It will be better this way.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Young Forty!
(He starts running for 20 seconds.)
He's running well.
(The tail is floating.)
(Time of touching the ground)
He's running well.
Young Forty!
- There you go.
- You're running well.
(It touches the ground!)
Young Forty!
- There you go.
- You're running well.
- No! Run faster.
- Okay.
- Nice.
- Young Forty!
Young Forty!
- A little more!
- He's really good.
- Careful when you make a turn.
- Make good use of the wind.
He's really good.
Make good use of the wind.
Young Forty's
protruding belly is funny.
Haha's record...
- is four seconds.
- Really?
- We can make it.
Go, Young Forty!
Get up, Young Forty!
Do whatever you want!
Supreme has been popular
since we were young.
Stussy?
It became popular because we wore it
when we were young!
(His incomprehensible appeal)
Listen. I think...
you should slowly run...
- back and forth here.
- That's better.
In the direction of the wind.
- I see.
- You can run this way.
- Go back and forth?
- In the direction of the wind.
- Okay.
- Go back and forth.
Okay. Let's do that.
(Jae Seok starts running
against the wind!)
- Oh, no.
- It's floating.
- Get it.
- It's high up.
- It's floating.
You should run faster.
(As he makes a turn,
the tail touches the ground again.)
You should run faster.
Oh, no.
- It's this way.
- Turn around right away.
- From here.
- This isn't bad.
The wind is good here.
Go right away.
Turn around.
Right. The wind is good there.
- Go that way.
- No, it touches the ground.
- Oh, no.
- It's not windy at all.
Your record is six seconds.
- This is...
- Six seconds.
- It's good.
- It falls when you come back.
Next up is Young Sixty. Let's go.
Here I go.
- Ready.
- Yes.
Hey.
- Cheer for me.
- Okay.
- Go!
He tells us to cheer for him.
- It's not touching.
- It didn't touch the ground.
- You're doing well.
- There you go.
- Run.
- You're doing well.
- It didn't touch the ground.
(Shouting)
(He takes off his hat
with a scream.)
It's not touching.
He's trying really hard.
He's about to fall.
He might fall.
(He was running an 80m marathon...)
(in the mud earlier.)
(Now he's doing
a ridiculous sprint with a tail.)
- Go!
- Jee Seok Sam!
Jee Seok Sam!
- It's touching the ground.
- It's touching the ground now.
(Hyun Woo, don't watch the show
and study hard.)
The belt lowers.
No way. He's really trying his best.
(Dad's Challenge, the end)
The belt lowers.
Jae Seok, we have to hold the belt.
- Sounds good.
- Seok Jin,
you dragged the tail for 11 seconds.
I did quite well
despite the belt going down.
- We can do this.
- We should drag it up.
- Get ready.
- He's not good at sports.
That flimsy Daniel.
- That flimsy Daniel.
- He won't be able to do this.
- Being tall helps.
- He's doing great.
- That flimsy Daniel.
- He won't be able to do this.
- Being tall helps.
- He's doing great.
Keep running. Make a turn.
Make a turn!
- It's not dragging.
- It's thanks to his height.
- It's not touching.
- It's not touching at all.
- It's not dragging.
- Is it not touching?
- It's not.
- It's not dragging.
- It's still not dragging.
(Running with big strides,
beaming with joy)
It didn't touch at all.
(Daniel's long legs came in handy
once in a while.)
- Zero seconds.
- It's not touching at all.
- I think it's zero seconds.
- Nice, zero seconds.
- Zero seconds?
- It only dragged for a second.
(Total seconds: 22 out of 50)
Being tall helped.
Daniel, that was awesome!
I didn't know I'd be good at this.
- You were like...
- It didn't touch...
- because you were so tall.
- the neighborhood fool.
- How am I doing?
- Run faster.
- Faster?
- That's it. Run!
- Jong Kook's up.
- All right.
(Total seconds: 45 out of 50)
You're the last one to run.
How many seconds do we have left?
The total accrued time
is 45 seconds,
so you need less
than five seconds...
- to succeed.
- Okay.
- That's more than enough.
- Can I go?
- Get ready.
Take your time.
It'll be a disaster if he trips.
If he falls, it'll be a disaster.
Get ready.
(Taking off)
(Mr. Out-toed Gait is off
to a good start.)
- Looking good. It's not touching.
- We've got this.
- What's with that face?
- It's not touching.
- Why is he making that face?
- We'll win for sure.
- Is he sucking the air in?
- Seriously?
Put on a smile!
- He's changed a lot.
- Faster, Jong Kook.
He never ran like that
on "Let's Go! Dream Team."
- He...
- He's working harder...
- now that he's married.
- How is that not a comedy?
He's working harder
now that he's married.
(The tail did touch
the ground a bit.)
- Why was he running like that?
- All right.
(Did it drag less than 5 seconds?)
Kim Jong Kook...
- Two seconds.
- Three?
- Three seconds.
- Half a second.
- It touched for only three seconds.
- Okay!
- Good job.
You succeeded in the mission...
- and won one chance card.
- Jong Kook,
why were you running
with your mouth open?
- What a relief.
- That was hilarious.
Young Forty, we're still kicking.
Young Forty.
We're still kicking.
- Earlier...
- See him roll his hips.
Did you see him run
with his belly sticking out?
- I love it.
- Young Forty.
Today's race is
Photographers Who Capture Time.
You must take photos
to enter the photo biennale.
The photos will be taken
at three locations.
However, there's a set time frame
for every location,
so you can only take photos...
- Really?
- when you arrive exactly on time.
Here's the catch.
Starting now,
- you will hand over your phones.
- What?
We will also cover
any visible clocks,
including the one in the van.
- How can we tell, then?
- You must guess the time.
- Hold on. Seok Jin...
- We'll use a sundial.
- needs to check the stock market.
- Exactly.
- Seok Jin...
- It's an important day for me.
It's an important day for Seok Jin.
It's do or die for him today.
- It's do or die for him today.
- Not really.
- It's D-Day.
- It could be a disaster for him.
A penalty will await you
at any location...
where you miss the time.
You will only be able to move on
after receiving the penalty.
You'll each enter one of the photos
you took today,
and through a vote by the citizens,
- the winner will receive a prize.
- Really?
With the chance card
you won earlier,
you may either extend
the error range...
by plus or minus three minutes,
or check the time whenever you want.
- Whenever we want?
- Yes.
- That'll be a last resort.
- So that's the bonus we get.
Can't we check the time
even without our phones?
- With the sun.
- The sun isn't out today.
- You can't see the sun today.
- There's no sun.
- It's not out.
- On a deserted island...
- Use a sundial.
- If only the sun was out today.
- I'm good at reading a sundial.
- Exactly.
(What's the time?)
(The sun's direction
and the shade's angle)
(Calculating all of that...)
Hold on. That's west.
(Calculation completed,
It must be around 1 p.m.!)
(Isn't it around 1 p.m.?)
(Jae Seok is
an unlicensed sundial reader.)
(A charmer)
(Of all days,
the sun chose to hide.)
I can tell what time it is.
- How?
- What's the current time?
- Isn't it about 10:30 a.m.?
- You should tell us that much.
Shouldn't we know
what the current time is?
- What did you say?
- Isn't it 10:32 a.m.?
- So, 10:32 a.m.?
- No, it's 10:47 a.m.
- Yes, 10:47 a.m.
- It's 10:51 a.m.
- It's 10:47 a.m.
- He checked his watch.
- I checked my watch.
- Did you?
- He was surprised.
- Was I taking it too seriously?
Aren't you allowed to peek...
- at other people's watches?
- No.
- Someone walking down the street.
- Why not?
Can't we check their phones?
- Maybe someone with a phone...
- Can't we ask what time it is?
- "Hello, there!"
- You can't ask for the time.
- We can't?
- No.
- I'm hungry.
- Won't we be hungry at noon?
Are you saying we should trust
our internal clocks?
- Internal clocks, seriously?
- Unbelievable.
Now, please hand in your phones.
Don't forget to hand in
your watches as well.
- Come on.
- My stylist has my phone.
- I have yours.
- Hey.
- Mine... It's the new 17.
- Your watch, please.
- Here.
- I'll keep the chance card.
- Young Forty's phone.
- Remember the time.
Wasn't that my phone?
Oh, it was my wallet.
Sorry about that.
I can't believe
you tried to fool her like that.
I need to check
the stock market today.
(Small Investor Jee can relate.)
- The current time is...
- It's a big day today.
- Tell me about it.
- It's 10:50 a.m.
Jong Kook,
there's a way we can tell.
Office workers leave the building
to grab lunch.
Lunch breaks usually start at noon.
- When they all leave the office.
- Exactly.
The first location
you'll take photos at...
is Namsangol Hanok Village.
- We're giving you...
- Namsangol Hanok Village.
the first location.
We'll drive you in a van...
- and let you off at the entrance.
- Sure.
You must arrive at exactly 11:45 a.m.
- At 11:45 a.m.?
- Yes.
- That's in an hour.
- To succeed,
- you must enter the village...
- We have 50 minutes.
- at exactly 11:45 a.m.
- Right, 11:45 a.m.
Seok Jin's good
at counting the time,
- so start counting.
- He's right.
- Go on. You kept bragging.
- What?
- Don't participate in the games.
- It's 10:55 a.m.
- Start counting.
- Two, three...
(Current Time, 10:50:21 a.m.)
- Keep counting.
- We'll head out...
- after you change clothes,
- Sure.
so guess the time...
- while changing as well.
- Got it.
- Right now, it's 10:50 a.m.
- Is it 10:50 a.m.?
- It's like the military.
- We should change in here.
Shouldn't we do something
about the shoes?
- Should we go to the restroom?
- Yes, let's do that.
- Sure. Where is it?
- Let's go.
I'd know the time
if the sun were out.
Exactly, but it's hiding today.
The sun isn't out.
Let's look around us...
to see if there are any clocks.
- Okay!
- Let's get going.
- Let's see. Let's take a look.
- Let's go.
- Is it 11 a.m.?
- Hello.
I bet it's 11:18 a.m.
- No, it's 11:16 a.m.
- Is it 11:16 a.m.?
Let's say it's 11:17 a.m., then.
- I keep touching my pocket...
- It's 11:17 a.m.
to see if my phone is there.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm having cellphone withdrawal
right now.
- As a group, you'll...
- We're heading out now.
- Is that allowed?
- Can you guess what time it is?
- It's 11:20 a.m.
- It's 11:22 a.m.
(They get in the van at 11:17 a.m.)
- It's 11:19 a.m.
- It's...
- It's 11:19:20 a.m.
- It's 11:19 a.m.
- It's 11:20 a.m.
- It's 11:19:20 a.m.
- I bet you're surprised.
- It's 11:20 a.m.
- Then...
- Aren't you going to tell us?
No, we're not going to answer you.
- They're surprised.
- You must enter the village...
- at exactly 11:45 a.m.
- Can you drive for now?
Don't we just have to make it
before 11:45 a.m.?
- At exactly 11:45 a.m.
- The deadline is 11:45 a.m., right?
It can take 30 minutes...
since it's about 11:20 a.m. now.
There's no way to tell the time.
It's frustrating
not to be able to see outside.
- This is crazy.
- Why did you cover the windows?
Just in case you'd see a clock.
- Come on.
- Seriously?
- What do you take us for?
- We wouldn't do that.
- Keep checking the time.
- No?
- Myung Jae.
- This is broken.
I have to take my medicine
at 11:40 a.m., so let me know.
(He takes his medicine
at a very specific time.)
Let me know.
I have to take my medicine.
Myung Jae, Seok Jin
has a lot riding...
- on the stock market today.
- I need to check the market.
Don't tell him
if it's a sea of blue.
- Don't tell him.
- I have to abort if necessary.
(Of all days,
it's the big day today.)
- Are you a Samsung?
- Trash cans have to be installed.
- Who has a Samsung?
- Why did they remove trash cans?
- A Samsung phone.
- They were difficult to manage.
(Seok Sam's suddenly asking
for anyone with a Samsung phone.)
Hi, Bixby!
(Calling for a virtual assistant)
- Hi, Bixby!
- Siri!
- What's the time?
- Siri, what's the time?
Young Forty!
- Young Forty?
- Young Forty.
- He's a Young Forty.
- Here's my take on the iPhone.
I've been using their phones
since the original iPhone.
Me too.
- I've been using iPhones...
- It's not about having an iPhone.
- from the 1st one to the 17th.
- Having that model is the issue.
What about that model?
- It's the color.
- What about that color?
- The color is the issue.
- The color's the problem.
- How so? Says who?
- Who knows?
The younger generation.
Why should I listen to them?
- Exactly.
- This is my life I'm living.
It was the first phone
to be in orange,
so I bought it out of curiosity.
I bought it with my own money!
- Haha.
- Yes?
You should gather
the so-called Young Forties.
Young Forties,
gather at Yeouido Park.
Wear a Supreme sweatshirt.
You know the one.
- Wear a Supreme sweatshirt.
- Supreme.
- Bring the orange phone.
He's been gathering
a lot of people lately.
Meet me at Yeouido Park.
That's hilarious.
Young Forty, shut that mouth.
Young Forty closed his mouth...
at exactly 11:32 a.m. I'm sure of it.
- Go, Young Sixty.
- Said by a Young Sixty.
A Young Fifty spoke at 11:32:22 a.m.
- Forever!
- He's on point.
- We should get him to count.
- It's 11:32 a.m.
- Aren't I right? I know I am.
- I'm sure.
Young Sixty, shut it.
(The human timer isn't good
at counting minutes.)
- Junior Jee.
- Compared to then...
- What is it?
- Massage my hand.
- What? Why should I?
- Well...
- You're his junior.
- You're my junior.
- Because you're my junior.
- That's not a thing.
- He's your senior.
I debuted three years earlier
than him.
As he talks about his seniority,
it's 11:37:22 a.m. right now.
(It's probably 11:37:22 a.m.?)
Were you startled? I bet you were.
- It's 11:40 a.m.
- If only the sun were out...
- I'd be accurate.
- It's cloudy.
It's 11:38 a.m.
- No, it's 11:30 a.m...
- It's 11:30 a.m...
It's so frustrating
not to know the time.
- Spin that. The Sony thing.
- Does that turn?
- Oh, yes. That thing.
- This?
- No, Seok Jin.
- He means that.
Myung Jae.
I really need to take my medicine.
- Tell me when it's past 45.
- Is it 11:40 a.m. now?
- Myung Jae. Is it 11:40 a.m.?
- He'll pass out.
- The time...
- They're not ready for lunch.
It's not yet past 45.
The current time is forty...
I think we have
about ten minutes left.
- No, wait, you think so?
- Yes.
- I don't think so.
- I think we have...
(Jae Seok accurately guessed
the current time.)
- I don't think so.
- From there to here,
- it took 15 minutes.
- It's about 11:40 a.m. now.
- I think it's 11:40 a.m.
- We rode for about ten minutes.
It's just 11:30 a.m.
if we drove 15 minutes.
About ten minutes.
Ten minutes to go.
This is pretty hard.
We have five minutes left.
We're here.
- Three plus one...
- It's Namsangol Hanok Village.
We're here.
(They reached the parking lot.)
I think we're almost on time.
- Four, five minutes to go?
- We have about eight minutes.
- Four, five minutes to go.
- It's 11:40 a.m. right now.
- It's 40 past right now?
- Yes.
We have some time left.
Not a lot, but I think we have
about seven minutes left.
No, we have less than five minutes.
We have seven minutes to go, mister.
Less than five, I say.
- Yes, less than five.
- Less than five.
No. We have seven minutes left.
- Shall we get out?
- Let's use the chance.
- We must get out.
- Once we're outside...
- Do we get out?
- Yes. Let's all get out.
I'm dead curious.
Let's get... What's this?
Hang on. This is...
Move, mister.
I see.
We have about four minutes twenty...
Four minutes 60 seconds...
We have 4 minutes 32 seconds left.
We have less than five minutes.
A camera...
Let's get moving first.
We need to go.
- Yes. In front of...
- We must set up.
Is this the hanok village?
I could guess
if the sun were shining.
I think we're cutting it close.
The current time is 11:41 a.m.
- It's 41 minutes?
- No.
- No?
- It's passed that.
It's about 43...
- Really?
- It's 43 minutes past.
- You reached the first location.
- Yes.
If you open the main gate
that's behind you, you'll see...
- a white line on the ground.
- Okay.
We'll stop the timer the moment...
you all cross that line.
If that time is exactly 11:45 a.m.,
you succeed.
- All of us?
- Yes.
You must cross it together.
Talk among yourselves
when to open the gate.
How about we go for 11:42 a.m.?
- Seok Jin.
- Not 43?
I also think it's past 11:40 a.m.
- It's past 40. We're on 42, 43.
- Yes.
Not yet.
Time doesn't go that quickly.
I think it's about 11:39 a.m. now.
- It's not yet 40 minutes past?
- No.
It's impossible to get it
without using a chance.
It's not impossible.
I think we should use a chance.
- Using it now...
- We must use a chance now,
- then count down to the deadline.
- Yes.
- Isn't that better?
- Check the time and count out loud.
- Count out loud.
- Yes. You can get it about right.
I'm oddly accurate.
Usually, in my case,
when I'm at home
because I don't have work,
- I go to the gym around this time.
- Do you?
I go to the gym.
I reach the gym at around noon,
- on average.
- Okay.
- Eleven...
- Listen.
- Look over there.
- It's about 11:42 a.m.
People start to flock.
The office workers...
- are off to lunch.
- They're exiting the buildings.
- They just left.
- The early starters...
- get moving at around 11:30 a.m.
- Yes, at 11:30 a.m.
You see quite a few people now.
- Then...
- We're nearing our deadline.
- Shouldn't we ask?
- Right now...
- It's about 43 minutes past.
- Who here...
- wants to use the chance?
- Me.
- Who thinks we need it?
- We must use it.
- We don't need to.
- No?
- We can't use it now.
Right now... Listen, everyone.
- You think...
- We'll miss the deadline.
Look at the streets and sights.
We must still try.
Look at the streets.
Sorry, but even if we look,
how can we tell...
- There's nothing.
- We can't guess when it's 11:45 a.m.
- How can we do that?
- Don't mention your marriage.
- When did I mention it?
- My wedding...
- It's 11:44 a.m. now!
Let's go in.
One, two, three...
- I feel hungry at this time.
- It's 43 minutes.
At around 43 minutes.
We must go in now.
- No.
- I think...
Isn't that truck scheduled
to deliver something at 11:45 a.m.?
(Se Chan's guess:
The truck is coming in at 11:45 a.m.)
- That truck...
- Hang on.
- Wait.
- Fourteen. I'm still counting.
Fifteen.
We need to go inside now.
- We must guess...
- What time did we set off?
We left at 11:15 a.m.
- It was 11:15 a.m.?
- Yes.
- Over there.
- Then...
It usually takes 15 to 20 minutes...
- from there to here by bus.
- It does.
- Then it's... 11:40 a.m.?
- 11:40 a.m.
- Thirty-six, thirty-seven...
- We stood here talking for five.
- Then...
- We must go inside!
- We must go!
- We must go.
- Forty,
- Go inside.
- forty-one,
- This is...
- forty-two,
- We must go.
- forty-three, forty-four.
- We must go. One,
- two!
- One, two!
(They have just 1 minute left!)
- Three!
- Open!
- Hang on.
- Forty-seven.
We haven't crossed it yet.
(Yet to cross the line)
(They just have to wait 50 seconds!)
Not yet. We must all cross it.
- Forty-nine.
- Wait.
- We must go now!
- No.
- Wait. Two,
- We must all cross together.
- three,
- We must go.
- four,
- Go, now!
- Wait.
- five,
- They all look anxious.
He looks anxious.
- They look tense.
- Okay.
(Can they cross the line
at exactly 11:45 a.m.?)
- Nine, ten.
- Let's go!
- Now!
(They crossed the line.)
- Let's go!
- We did it.
- Now.
- Stop the timer.
- Stop.
- Stop it.
(If it's 11:45:31 a.m., they succeed!)
- We're almost on time.
- They look surprised.
- They're surprised.
- Right now...
- No way.
We stopped the timer
when you crossed...
- the white line.
- Yes.
Wasn't that amazing?
If it's not noon...
You can come
and check the time yourself.
- Can we?
- Yes.
(Check the time
they crossed the line)
- It says over there.
- The current time's on the left,
and the timer you stopped
is on the right.
Does this even make sense?
(Is it 11:45 a.m.?)
- Oh, shoot.
- It was 11:44 a.m.?
(44 minutes...)
It was so close.
- It was 31 seconds?
- 11:44 a.m.
(They failed by just 29 seconds!)
I said we should wait...
- No way.
- We were almost on time.
(They entered the gate
at 44 minutes.)
(Wait)
(Nine...)
(Ten, now!)
- Let's go.
- Now!
(At Seok Sam's yell,
they crossed too early.)
I said we should wait...
Let's not complain.
- You crossed the line at 11:44:31 a.m.,
- We were almost on time.
- so you failed the mission.
- I said we should wait!
We could've used a chance.
That's why I mentioned the chance!
I said we should wait!
Jae Seok.
You're the one who gave the signal.
- It was so close.
- Hey, still...
You acted like a general.
"Let's go!" That was you.
- Hey! We did pretty well.
- "Let's go!" That was you.
I said we should wait.
We did well. This is amazing too.
- My gut feeling...
- This is impossible.
- Wasn't I right in the car?
- You were.
- I was, right?
- You were right.
And the time you said
after you got here...
- I counted. Was I almost right too?
- Yes.
It's such a shame.
It's such a pity.
- We just had to wait 30 seconds.
- It is a shame.
Haha, we're awesome. What we did...
All you idols. Come at us.
- Can you do this?
- Take us on!
- What is he saying?
- Take them on for what?
What got into him?
You can't live without your phones.
- Come at us.
- We can.
- We used pagers.
- Name tag elimination, anyone?
Why do you want the idols
to challenge you?
- What for?
- We almost had it.
(Young Forty and Young Sixty
are taunting others for no reason.)
- We can beat them.
- Why the idols?
We accept team challenges.
- Just a little...
- Trust my hunch!
Yes. I trusted you.
- Right, Kook Jong?
- I trusted you.
But how can someone tell
when it's 11:45 a.m.?
- You were almost right.
Why didn't we use the chance?
Young Forty. Keep quiet.
It's Fifty. Why didn't you speak up
when I said Young Forty?
(Born in early 1986, aged 39.
Born in 1986, aged 38)
Young Forties. Come here.
- Haha.
- Why didn't you complain?
You do whatever you want.
- You keep the title.
- They're 40, not Young Forty.
Young Forty's the term
for people like you...
Who make a huge fuss
about trying to be in their forties.
They dress up
and wear sunglasses like that.
You're Young Forty. Not us.
- This is Young Forty.
- He makes a fuss.
My pant leg went down.
See? Things like that.
- See? Things like that.
- Take pity on him, guys.
- Take pity on him.
- Why?
You can't bear the weight.
- I'll treat you better.
- Why am I pitiful?
Why am I pitiful?
Comfort him.
- Be nice to him.
- You too.
- Be nice to the poor guy.
- Stay away.
Don't you dare console me.
He acts out.
This village brings together
traditional Joseon houses...
and the ridges of Mount Nam.
- I didn't know this place existed.
- Oh, this place is nice.
You cannot take photos here,
and you'll all get the penalty.
- What is the penalty?
- As for the penalty,
- We're getting the penalty here?
- we'll move as we look around.
- Is that so? Since it's fall...
- Then, we'll tell you about it.
Gosh, we have to get the penalty.
Hey, but it was such a close call.
- I really have my own...
- Hey, the...
routine right around...
- A routine?
- this time.
Then, it must be noon about now.
It was about 50-something earlier,
right? No, that's not it.
- It was 11:45 a.m.
- Earlier, it was 40...
We have to check.
So, here is the first penalty.
You must cut up
each of your team uniforms...
in order and collect the pieces...
so that they weigh a total of 1kg.
- What is that?
- What?
A total of 1kg.
- What is that?
- What?
- Come on.
- One kilogram?
- How will the team uniform...
- I mean...
- Cut what up?
- Cut this?
- Why would we cut this up?
- How will we get 1kg of this?
- How can we get 1kg of this?
- I mean...
Once the uniforms are cut up,
you can keep wearing them...
- throughout the day.
- What did you say?
We have to keep wearing them?
- Look here.
- Please save us.
- Hey, at least the important bits.
- You can't do this to us.
- Hey, let us cover our nipples.
- We have to cover our nipples.
- This is...
We have undershirts on,
- so we can cut up to about here.
- Then, that's fine.
You can cut off everything
except for this bit.
- Yes, you can do that.
- Cut it all off except the collar.
- That wouldn't look decent.
- Just leave this part.
(Already looking forward to seeing
their masterpieces)
So, decide on an order,
and each person will add
their pieces to get 1kg total.
If the first few people cut off
a small piece,
- the next people can cut off a lot.
- Right, they have to cut off a lot.
- Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
- Hey, this...
How many grams is this?
- Each shirt is...
- Probably about 500g?
- We measured it,
- About 500...
- and it was about 300g.
- Does it only weigh 300g?
Se Chan,
you should just take it all off.
- No, you should...
- Why cut it up? Just take it off.
Aren't you wearing an undershirt?
- I'm naked underneath.
- Oh, dear.
- I just need to...
- Why didn't you wear anything?
Gosh, this is hard.
We should play
rock-paper-scissors for this.
- Right.
- Okay, rock-paper-scissors.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's play.
- Rock-paper...
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jae Seok and Seok Jin lose.)
(The two older guys
will have to go later.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Se Chan wins 1st place
in this group.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Jonathan loses.)
- Okay, you're in last place.
- Rock...
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay!
- Rock-paper...
(Jong Kook wins 1st place
in this group.)
First place, come on up.
- Who was in first place?
- I was.
- Okay, we're deciding this now.
- I was in second place.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- I won first place!
- Okay.
(Se Chan comes in 1st place.)
- He'll get to keep his shirt.
- Please cut off a lot.
- Come on. Just cut some off.
- What?
- I mean...
- Se Chan.
- You won. Don't cut off a lot.
- You're in first place, but...
- That way, it's more fun.
- I know.
- Go ahead and cut it off.
- Right.
- Come here. I'll cut it for you.
- But even if you do,
- Oh, you will? Jae Seok.
- it won't be enough.
To get 1kg,
we have to cut off a lot.
In that case,
it wouldn't make sense...
for you to cut off too much.
What will you do?
Should I cut it here?
- But he'll have to show his belly.
- It's fine.
- No, it'd be a bit embarrassing.
You have to keep wearing it
like that.
- He was in first place.
- Hey.
First of all,
just cover the important parts.
- Right.
- I'm fine, but for the viewers.
- Then, I'll cut it about here.
- Okay.
But mister, I was in first place.
Mister, I wasn't in last place.
How far up are you going to go?
Then, what? Should I make this
a short-sleeve shirt?
- Let's do that.
- Yes, cut off his sleeves.
- Let's go with short sleeves.
- Let's go with short sleeves first.
- I should give something up...
- Give him short sleeves.
- even if I'm in first place.
- That's right.
Well, that's because...
- If not, we won't have enough.
- we can't make this work.
- It won't be enough without him.
- Hey, hold this for me.
- Gosh, you're cutting a lot.
- Oh, this is...
- Mister, is this...
- That's a lot.
- It'll be enough for short sleeves.
- Short sleeves...
This will show my armpits.
- No, it won't.
- Let's see it. Lift your arms.
All right.
- You have short sleeves.
- That's all right.
- Hey.
- It looks nice.
- It's about that much.
- You had to give up your sleeves.
Yes, that much is... Hey, this is...
- That much is...
- Hey, that's good.
- Hey, you still gave up a lot...
- This isn't...
- even as the winner.
- too bad.
- First of all...
- This is only about 50g.
Let's give him a crop top.
I'll just cut off this much.
- But this doesn't weigh much.
- Each person...
has to give up over 100g.
- Go higher.
- But if we give him a crop top...
- when he's in 1st place...
- He's in 1st place, but...
- It'd mean to do that to him.
- Just do it.
But he was in first place.
He's still in first place.
- Where are you cutting?
- Jae Seok.
- Oh, but...
- He's in first place.
- This is...
- Wait.
(Working swiftly)
- No, but...
- Can't I do this?
(A totally different design
from what they agreed on before)
- I mean, mister.
- Well...
- From the moment you poked it in,
- Well, the length...
- it was way too high up.
- No,
I just measured it wrong.
Oh, the length...
(He started cutting pretty boldly
to call it a mistake.)
Apologize before you move on.
Let's just leave it
after I apologize.
(Peekaboo)
- I think you cut too much.
- Apologize.
Hey, but just a little bit here...
Jae Seok, that's trendy these days.
- Just cut it all the way around.
- Hang on. Let's go around.
- What...
- I can't...
I just can't stand that sight.
What do I do?
- I'll pull my pants up, Seok Jin.
- Yes, pull them up.
Or I could pull my underpants up.
- Make it unbalanced.
- I did make it unbalanced.
Unbalanced?
Hey, do you still want to
look stylish in that state?
(He easily pulls off
the client's request.)
(The masterpiece is complete.)
- Hey, that's looks good.
- That's not bad.
- It looks stylish.
- Nice.
- Oh, my.
- Hey, let's see it.
- Hey, that's kind of pretty.
- Se Chan.
- That's nice.
- It looks good.
- By the way...
(The designer is very pleased too!)
Hey, that's nice.
- It looks so fashionable.
- No, really.
- Se Chan.
- Do I look like a celebrity?
- You totally do.
- You look like a celebrity.
- Do I look okay?
- Hey, you know,
you look like you came from Milan.
You're quite talented.
It's really not that bad.
You're good.
The current weight is 158g.
My belly feels nice and cool.
Next, who was in second place?
- Me.
- Kook Jong.
- You can cut off a lot from mine,
- Yes?
but for the people to have some fun
later down the line,
- shouldn't we go easy with me?
- Sure.
- Just cut off a little.
- Cut the sleeves off.
- Hey, you should go sleeveless.
- Yes, sleeveless.
- You should go sleeveless.
- That's right.
- Jong Kook needs to go sleeveless.
- Show his shoulders.
I'll go sleeveless.
You can make it look like
a soccer jersey.
- You know?
- Sure, I can do that.
Hey, you can go even deeper.
Like this, all the way down.
- All right.
- Yes.
- Cut it longer.
- Because to get 1kg...
- Please hold this.
- I'll hold it.
- Oh, yes. You can do that.
- Because to get 1kg...
- I'll hold it.
- That's right.
But... Wait.
Why are the people
who are behind me in order...
Hang on a minute.
Why are the people
who are behind me in order...
Hang on a minute.
Attention.
(The older guys were trying to
get all 1kg from those before them.)
Attention.
- Look, Jong Kook.
- You should ask! Hang on.
We can torment them too.
- Mister.
- You should ask us nicely, mister!
- We're in 1st and 2nd place.
- Yes.
- Well...
- Yes, I know.
- Please help us.
- You should ask us.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Please help us.
- My goodness.
- I mean, you're treating us...
- Cut this much.
- He was in first place...
- Go in this deep.
- Gosh, I can't go too deep.
- No.
- He...
- I can't cut too much off.
He usually wears stuff like this.
It's fine
since he's wearing an undershirt.
- Oh, nice.
- That much is...
- Nice.
- See? That's good.
- This is nice.
- That's good, isn't it?
- This looks good.
- It's not bad.
That looks cool.
The total is 272g.
You should stop now.
- Let's stop.
- Yes, stop now.
- I'm cold.
- Third place?
Why did you...
- give in so easily?
- Third place.
I don't know. This man suddenly...
- They should've asked you 1st.
- Were you 2nd place in that group?
- Next, who was in third place?
- It's cold.
- Third place?
- Third place.
- All right. Third place.
- Why are you...
always trying to do things
when it's my turn?
What? Why? Come here.
- Hey, 200 between the 2 of you...
- You have to do it.
It's perfect if we can get 240g
between the 2 of you.
As long as we each give up
this much...
- Yes, that's right.
- Since there are four pairs,
- we can get enough.
- We can't do that.
- Why not?
- We should give up less in front,
- and you should give up more later.
- I know.
But then, you shouldn't have
given up your shirts.
- Why did you cut off so much?
- My gosh.
You should've refused.
- Just do it for now.
- My goodness.
- Cut off both my sleeves too.
- Okay.
No, cut off both sleeves.
But just a bit from your belly...
You have an undershirt.
Right, you have an undershirt.
- Watch your hands.
- Well, so...
No, but what are you doing?
- Watch your hands.
- The two of you...
Hey, you two from Antenna.
- What are you... Hang on.
- No, right here...
Hold still.
- I'm in third place.
- Just wait a second.
- Hang on.
- Hold still.
Hey, this undershirt is mine.
- All right.
- Leave the collar alone.
- I won't touch your undershirt.
- How are you...
- going to cut it?
- We'll leave some. What's wrong?
You're driving me crazy. Seriously.
- Will you get rid of all of that?
- No.
Don't worry.
You have to leave
his name tag behind.
Of course, I will.
- It's fine. Leave the name tag. No.
- Yes, leave that.
- You have to do that.
- The name tag will be fine.
- Just hold still.
- Right.
- What will he do?
- Okay.
All right.
- This is fun.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, okay.
- No, but...
What is that? It's just a rag!
What is that? It's literally a rag!
- Haha, it's fine.
- We got a lot from him.
- What is this?
- You took so much.
- You look like...
- Seriously.
- You look like you were stranded...
- Come on!
Were you stranded
on an island somewhere?
- It's all right. For real.
- Were you stranded somewhere?
- The order means nothing this way.
- Are you about to eat?
- This looks like a bib.
- Next.
Right. You have 523g now.
- Okay.
- Who's next?
- I'm next.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- We have 520g.
- What, 500g?
But if it's going to be like this,
- those in last place won't...
- We pretty much got everything.
- even have to cut anything off.
- No, but...
He's not wearing an undershirt.
- You're not wearing one?
- I'm not wearing an undershirt.
- No, it's my bare skin.
- Let's cut off this part for him.
- Let's cut this part off here.
- All right.
- Let's just do that first.
- You should just get a crop top.
- Let's cut it like this.
- Let's just give you a crop top.
- Is this how it's supposed to be?
- What is this?
- Is this supposed to be fun?
- That's cool.
- It's cool.
- What is this?
- Hey, can't you make that stick?
- Hey, that's...
Who's next?
First place is actually worse.
Okay, nice.
- I'm next.
- Okay.
- Jae Seok. Okay, come here.
- I'm relieved.
- Don't go overboard.
- Jae Seok, first...
- I'll do it.
- Okay.
- I'll turn him into Superman.
Do what you want to do.
- No, but Haha.
- Hey, pull it so it's taught. Yes?
- Be sensible with it.
- Okay.
- Give it some thought, okay?
- Pull it.
Be sensible with it.
- That's what I'm doing.
- I mean...
- It has to be fun.
- Come on.
Come on.
- Over here too.
- Watch out.
- Hey, don't cut the mic too.
- You have to let me wear a mic.
- Of course, he needs his mic.
- You can still wear it.
- Keep the mic.
- I'm scared.
- Hey, the mic...
- You're going to show everything.
What are you doing?
It's so...
- Superman!
- Hey!
Pull it.
- Okay, let's go with a short cape.
- Oh, no!
- There. Go ahead.
- You look cool.
Okay. Turn around.
Superman!
(A shabby transformation)
Go ahead and do this pose.
Gosh, seriously. I'm so mad.
That's good.
- Seriously. I'm so mad.
- That's all set.
- That's 884g.
- I mean, what...
- We just need 120g more.
- Who's next?
Go easy on her.
Ji Hyo should get
three-quarter-length sleeves.
That's good. That's enough.
- That's cool.
- It looks cool.
- But the next...
- So, right now, you have 922g.
We only have 80g left.
- Let's finish it here.
- Right.
- I don't think I'll have to go.
- That's cool.
- Jonathan, are you wearing a shirt?
- Are you wearing an undershirt?
- I'm not wearing an undershirt.
- You don't have one on?
- Let's go.
- Hey, this is nice.
- Should we give him a crop top?
- Let's do...
- Or what about this?
- something like this.
How about we cut it like this?
Hang on. How about this?
Do you remember
what Rain used to wear?
- He should have...
- Just stringing his arms through.
- Do that.
- Jong Kook, but...
You can't do that
since I'm really hairy.
Or we should give him
a sleeveless shirt.
- Let's see. I'll take a look.
- I want it to be something new.
Jong Kook. No, we can't.
- You can't do this.
- Why not?
- Then... Jong Kook.
- Rain?
- Hey, I know what we can do.
- Look at him being shy.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
- Just cut it.
- Se Chan. No, really.
- Just do it.
Oh, or you could do...
- I'm an expert. Watch out.
- He's done this a lot.
- Right now, Seok Sam is...
- Hey.
Look at him being shy.
- Gosh, Se Chan.
- Hey, that's nice.
- Like this.
- That's kind of cool.
- Let me see.
- Oh, that's nice.
- But my chest hair...
- Hey, just...
- My hair is showing.
- It's fashion. Pull it.
My hair is showing!
- Protect him.
- Please protect me.
- He's so shy.
- Oh, nice. Try it.
- Oh, nice.
- Let's stop now.
Hey, you're doing so well.
- Do the back too.
- There you go.
- That looks good.
- Cut off everything in the back.
- Let's show his back.
- Is this better?
- Sure, go with the back instead.
- Go ahead.
- It's best to remove it all.
Like this.
Se Chan must be fond of Jonathan.
He's being protective.
- Nice.
- You look good.
Jonathan,
he protected your integrity.
- There.
- Let's get rid of the sleeves.
- The sleeves.
- Stop it.
- You fools!
- Please, not the sides.
- Cut only that.
- Got it.
A bear must've attacked you.
- That looks good.
- There. We'll leave it at that.
- This looks nice.
- You look good.
- Nice.
- That looks nice.
- You look great, Jonathan.
- This is stylish.
Then there's me.
You're exactly at 999g.
- Nice.
- We only need 2g.
This much would be enough.
I want to see him
only wearing arm warmers.
We'll give you arm warmers.
He should take the most off.
You'll then take this off.
- What?
- Don't cut more and take it off.
No more cutting is needed.
- Take it off?
- Yes, just take it off.
- Just wear the arm warmers.
- We only need 2g.
(They leave him with arm warmers
when they only need 1g.)
You managed to cut off
1,252g of clothing.
Because it's over 1 kg,
your penalty is complete.
- What on earth is this?
- Come on.
This isn't even funny.
- It's funny.
- It's not funny.
Exactly. It's not funny at all.
That's the beauty of it.
- At least make it funny.
- That makes it funny.
The fact that you're not funny
is funny.
- What on earth is this?
- That's how it is.
You look cool.
- You'll now move...
- We should.
to the next location.
- Wait, the time.
- We can't afford these penalties.
- I told you we should use...
- We can't afford it.
- the chance card.
- We should.
We should use the chance card
in the next round.
The second location
will now be revealed.
- The second location...
- Go on.
can be guessed based on the photo.
- Without a GPS,
- What?
you'll have to drive there yourself.
- To the location in the photo?
- Yes.
Jong Kook, aren't you good
at doing this?
- As long as I know where it is.
- Right.
Is there no deadline for this?
- There is. So...
- There's a deadline?
The tasks aren't easy today.
Once you arrive
at the next location,
we'll give you a new camera.
It's a digital camera
that automatically...
- timestamps photos.
- Really?
To succeed, you must take a photo...
with the timestamp
that reads 1:10 p.m.
It'll be a little over noon
right now.
- I think it's 12:10 to 12:20 p.m.
- It won't be easy unless we focus.
The current time is 12:10 p.m.
- I was right.
- Nice.
(Se Chan guessed correctly.)
- Se Chan, that was awesome.
- Right, 12:10 p.m.
You were right on the nose.
You can ask people on the street...
where the location in the photo is,
but you can't have them
look it up online...
or use an AI program to find it.
If you want, we can give you
a paper map.
- Please give us that.
- We need one.
Before GPS,
we found every place on a map.
- Before GPS.
- Here's the photo of the location.
- Sure.
- We'll instantly know.
- I'd be able to tell.
- The SBS building before...
- What is that?
- I can't tell what this is.
- What's this? Daerimjang?
- I haven't a clue.
(Daerimjang)
(Where an old inn still stands)
Is it an inn?
For photos like this,
we should look at what's behind it.
A mountain.
(Find this photo spot
somewhere in Seoul)
Since it's called Daerimjang,
is it in Daerim-dong?
- Daerim-dong's far from here.
- Hold on.
I don't think it's in Daerim-dong.
- Is that an inn?
- Wouldn't it be in Euljiro...
or Jongno?
- It ends with "jang."
- Is that an inn?
Somewhere near Hoehyeon Station.
(Around Euljiro or Jongno
where old inns would be)
We should look at what's behind it.
- A mountain.
- There's a mountain.
It's on a clean brick road.
This could be in Insa-dong.
Could it be Seongsu-dong?
Or maybe Pyeongchang-dong.
Brick roads like this...
- aren't common.
- Where else?
This reminds me of Daehakro.
- It could be Daehakro.
- Daehakro.
- Near Hansung University.
- You know what?
We should ask people about this.
For some reason,
Daerimjang sounds familiar.
Let's head out for now.
(They agree to ask the people
on the street for now.)
Daerimjang's an inn.
Daerimjang.
I've heard that name a lot before.
We should consider
the thought process...
- behind these missions.
- Right.
This location
must be somewhere nearby.
- Exactly. It's not far away.
- Euljiro, Daehakro...
What's our deadline?
- Jongno. 1:10 p.m.
- It's 1:10 p.m.
- It must be kind of far.
- That's an hour.
It must be at least
an hour from here.
- Jong Kook.
- Yes?
- Think about it.
- Okay, maybe not an hour.
- Maybe 40 minutes.
- It's less than 30 minutes away.
- Really?
- Yes.
But they gave us about an hour
to get there.
It's Jongno, Euljiro, or Daekhakro.
It's must be about 12:20 p.m.
- Right.
- We'll have time for coffee.
- Something like that.
- Let's grab a cup of coffee.
- Can I call shotgun?
- Go ahead.
Daerimjang sounds
awfully familiar to me.
Maybe it's somewhere
we have no clue about.
I think I've heard Daerimjang
many times before.
Right? The name sounds so familiar.
They covered everything.
- Tell me about it.
- Anything that tells time.
(The GPS)
Don't you think
that sticker would come off?
I don't think
a mountain's behind it.
It just looks like a tree.
I don't think that'll help
identify the location.
I think I've seen that in Daehakro.
It's why I said we should
use the chance card...
in the first round.
Sitting on that wouldn't earn you...
- any extra treasure.
- Young Forty.
- We ended up failing miserably.
- We...
We can use it this round instead.
- It's like this.
- Look at us right now.
- If we had...
- It's not like your guess...
was perfect.
- Young Forty, come on.
- Don't be angry.
Young Forty, hey.
Look at how we're doing.
- Young Forty, that's enough.
- As if you know better.
You should be young at heart,
not just dress young.
- Shut it!
- Sure, okay.
There's a limit to how much
we can take, Young Forty.
- Let's first go to Jongno.
- Sounds good.
We'll stop by that area
and ask the older generation...
if they recognize it.
Let's get off at Jongno...
and ask the elders
if they know the place.
- Do you think they'll know?
- Yes.
That inn seemed old.
You can get to Daehakro from here.
- It's close by.
- Right.
- This is Euljiro in Jongno.
- I see.
This bulgogi restaurant
has been around...
- for a long time.
- I know that place, Jae Seok.
- It has a long history.
- Is the food good?
Yes, they serve good food.
- And over here...
- Yes?
Ojang-dong Hamheung Naengmyeon
is on the right.
- Is the food good?
- Of course.
That's Myungbo Movie Theater
on the right.
- Of course.
- I know what it used to be.
- Shin Young Kyun Art and Culture...
- That's right.
I remember waiting in line
to watch "Over the Top."
This used to be
the Piccadilly Theater.
- This building right here.
- That's right.
I'm not familiar
with this neighborhood.
- We're now in Jongno.
- Right.
Seoul Cinema used to be on the left.
Exactly.
Jae Seok, ask people
about the location in the photo.
- We should get out.
- Why don't we lower our windows?
I'll make a left first.
Seok Jin should get out...
so that we can ask his peers.
- Give him the photo.
- Here you go.
- Ask your peers.
- Give it to Seok Jin.
- This?
- Get close to them.
- I know.
- This is Songhae Street,
named after Song Hae.
- First...
- I see.
We're near Nakwon Musical
Instrument Arcade.
Let's ask the people around here.
Hello, sir.
- I see.
- Perhaps...
- He already walked past us.
- Hello.
We should ask the older generation.
If only we could
look this up online.
- Tell me about it.
- Hello, sir.
Do you know where Daerimjang is?
- I don't.
- You don't?
- He doesn't know.
- Daerimjang.
What do we do?
- Goodness.
- Hello!
Ma'am, do you know
where Daerimjang is?
- Daerimjang?
- Yes.
- Do you know that place?
- Jongno 3-ga...
- What?
- Is it on Jongno 3-ga?
(Jongno 3-ga...)
(She asks him back.)
Jongno 3-ga?
We don't know.
- You're asking me where it is?
- Yes.
There are detached houses...
- in the neighborhood.
- It can't be...
- Jongno 3-ga.
- It's not Jongno 3-ga.
Where do you think this is?
Jongno 3-ga...
It's not Jongno 3-ga,
but I should take a photo first.
Sure, take the photo.
So, it's not on Jongno 3-ga.
- Hold on.
- Take the photo.
It's not coming out right.
- Hold on. Where is this inn?
- She's clueless.
Since there are detached houses,
it might be up there.
- Up there?
Are there detached houses?
This must be
in a trending neighborhood.
I agree,
- so we should ask youngsters.
- Youngsters might know.
- Let me take a look.
- Sure.
(An old gentleman followed them,
as if he knew something.)
- Do you know where Daerimjang is?
- This...
(This...)
I don't know where Daerimjang is.
- You don't? Thank you anyway.
- Thank you.
- Do you know this place?
- Do you know where Daerimjang is?
(It'll be a huge miss
if it's not in Jongno.)
- Daerimjang?
- Daerimjang's over there.
- Where?
(Someone who knows
where Daerimjang is?)
- In Ikseon-dong.
- Ikseon-dong?
- Yes.
- Is it there?
- Over there, near Sulla-gil.
- Sulla-gil?
- Solla-gil?
- No, Sulla-gil.
Sulla-gil.
- Sulla-gil.
- Sulla-gil in Ikseon-dong.
- That's right.
- Then...
Is it on Sulla-gil in Ikseon-dong?
Go diagonally from here.
- This way?
- In Ikseon-dong...
- Sulla-gil.
- Straight ahead?
- Sulla-gil in Ikseon-dong.
- Sulla-gil.
(Current Location,
Jongno 3-ga Station)
(Seosulla-gil)
(Seosulla-gil is a 6-minute drive
from their current location.)
- Let's head over there.
- Let's go.
Let's get back in the van.
She told us it's on Sulla-gil
in Ikseon-dong.
I don't know if she's right though.
- I think she is.
- Right?
- Sulla-gil in Ikseon-dong.
- Ikseon-dong.
We can go that way.
- Do you know your way there?
- Yes.
What's our deadline?
Our deadline is 1:10 p.m.
- We have some time left.
- Don't we have some time left?
- Yes.
- Sulla-gil in Ikseon-dong.
Sulla-gil.
- Hold on. The back isn't blocked.
- This way.
- You're right.
- We can look outside.
Seok Sam, over there.
- Can you see anything?
- I'll find a clock no matter what.
- Here we go.
- I know I can find one.
No wonder the name sounded familiar.
I had a feeling Daerimjang
would be in Jongno.
Of course.
We're currently near
Nakwon Musical Instrument Arcade.
- About 200m ahead...
- We're now in Insa-dong.
Look for Sulla-gil, Seok Jin.
- Sulla-gil?
- Check the street names.
- I haven't heard of it before.
- You can ask me, Seok Jin.
Sure.
I went there two weeks ago.
- Really?
- Yes.
Where is it?
It's in Ikseon-dong.
What the...
(As if they don't know that.)
I wonder what time it is.
Look at the scenery on the streets.
- What?
- As if that tells the time.
- It does.
- We can't see anything back here.
Lunch break is almost over.
See that cafe over there?
That means it's around
12:45 p.m. to 12:50 p.m.
(A crowded cafe,
Estimated time: 12:45 p.m. to 12:50 p.m.)
As you know, I usually work out
around this time of day.
Right around this time,
coffee shops are usually packed,
especially after 12:30 p.m.
He's not wrong.
What time do you think it is?
Right now?
I think it's a little over 12:40 p.m.
What a joke.
- Don't make...
- Hey, that's called Gyeongwoongwan.
You keep calling me Young Forty,
and I keep becoming absorbed
into that character.
Do you feel braver or something?
- I don't know. I just...
- Well...
I think it's somewhere around
here and Anguk-dong.
- Look. The street already feels...
- Here?
- like it.
- Hey, where is Ikseon-dong?
- Where? Duksung Women's University.
- This is... Oh, wait.
- Over there. In there.
- This is the Jongno campus.
- Hey, it's the same brick road.
- Really?
- The road?
(The brick road looks similar
to the one in the photo.)
Hey, look at the map!
I'm getting motion sickness
from looking at this so much.
Make a right turn
at Anguk Station here.
- Make a right turn.
- Turn right.
We're in the right turn lane anyway.
Or should we park the car
and walk around?
Wouldn't that be better?
- I think that might be better.
- I think it would be too.
Is it a walkable distance?
Oh, this is nice.
- Hey, but this is...
- Wouldn't the police officer know?
- Let's stop the car here.
- Let's get out.
- This paid parking lot here? Okay.
- Yes.
- Let's park it here.
- Will they charge us for parking...
by the minute?
I think we should know the time.
- Oh, right.
- It logs the time when we park.
- It does.
- Right, we can't help it.
- Right. You're seriously a genius.
- That's true.
- Yes, we can't help it.
- We need to get the parking stub.
- We can't help it.
- If you exit the car,
- we will park it for you.
- Pardon?
- You're so uptight!
- That's so strict!
- So uptight!
- So strict!
Hey, I think that person would
definitely know if we ask.
- "It's in the back alley here."
- He looks like he would know.
He looks like he'd say that.
(He looks as though he'd know
the area like the back of his hand.)
- He looks like he'd say that.
- Let's ask this gentleman.
Are we all getting out?
- Get out.
- Okay.
- Sir, where is Sulla-gil near here?
- Pardon?
- Ikseon-dong.
- That way.
- Oh, do we have to go this way?
- Go that way.
- Sir, where is Daerimjang?
- Yes?
- Daerimjang? Oh, it's that way.
- Yes.
- Oh, over there?
- Right there? Gosh, thank you!
(Go straight and turn right.)
- Thank you, sir. Is it right there?
- Go straight that way?
- Did we find it?
- For real?
- Is it here?
- All right. Let's go.
- Where is it?
- Is it really here?
- That's right.
- Jae Seok, the time.
- Let's go.
- It's this way.
(Running past)
Look at him acting up again.
Seriously, that guy.
(A rodent tries to take the lead.)
Mister!
Stop acting up!
Excuse me.
Where is Daerimjang around here?
- Over there. Yes.
- Right there?
Hurry up!
- Gosh, we found our way so well.
- Not there! It's on the other side!
- The other side! Where is he going?
- Oh, is it on the other side?
- Hey!
- We have to go this way.
- Not that way! It's the other side!
- This way!
- It's across from here!
- Is it across from here?
- It's across and to the right.
- They said it was this way.
- What?
- Hurry up.
But... I mean...
- She said to go this way.
- Are you sure it's this way?
- I think we should go in here.
- A 2 or 3-story building.
- Seok Jin, I bet it's around here.
- Yes?
- I bet it's around here.
- Hey, this...
- Should we head into this alley?
- Should I try going in?
- Go in.
- Gosh, it's cold.
- Your back is cold, isn't it?
Yes, it's cold!
(They head into an alley
that looks similar to the photo.)
- This is the right vibe.
- It is a brick road. Look.
- Oh, this looks like it.
- It was this kind of road, right?
- Hang on.
- What?
The thing we thought was a mountain
is this tree. This kind of tree.
- You're right. Then...
- It's this way.
- Then, it must be that building.
- This is the place I meant.
The stone wall.
Oh, I think it's that one.
(They walk away from the tree.)
- That one.
- My goodness.
- Hey, Ssaebssaeb.
- Yes, Jae Seok.
- That one.
- It's here!
(A red brick building
that seems to be Daerimjang)
- It's here!
- Is it there?
- Yes. It's this one.
- Did you find it?
(Running past)
What's up with you, Haha?
(He tries to
cut in front of them again.)
Why is Haha doing that? Seriously.
It's here!
The dry cleaner's.
- Hang on.
- Over there!
It's this one.
(Will it really be Daerimjang?)
- Daerimjang.
- It's Daerimjang.
Daerimjang!
- Is that it?
- Is it there?
- It's Daerimjang.
- Is this it?
- Daerimjang.
- It is this building.
- It's Daerimjang.
(They arrive 11 minutes before
the set time.)
The background looks similar.
- This is it!
- It's right here.
It looks similar.
- They must've found it.
- I think they have.
- Is this it?
- It's right here.
No, don't come yet.
Gosh,
I guess this is where Daerimjang is.
Oh, this is nice.
It's so pretty
if you go to the back here.
(Just like how it looked
when it was built in 1975)
- It's fascinating.
- Gosh, that's awesome.
I know, right?
From now on,
at the time that you want,
you can take a single photo.
If the time that
the photo is taken...
- is 1:10 p.m.,
- Then,
- At 1:10 p.m. We still have...
- we should...
- some time. I think...
- use the chance card in a bit.
- Let's find out what time it is.
- That's right.
- Hey, it's not 1 p.m. yet.
- Then...
- Not yet.
- I think we have about ten minutes.
Jae Seok, in about five minutes,
- We should ask.
- let's use the chance card.
- Let's use it in five minutes.
- Okay.
It was amazing
how we found this place.
- Yes, that's right.
- Gosh, it's insane.
You know,
my experience really came in handy.
- How often did I come to Jongno?
- Right, back in the day.
- You know? My gosh.
- Goodness, you went around...
- all over the place.
- I came to Jongno...
as if I lived here.
- My goodness.
- This is where I hung out.
- Oh, you hung out here?
- Gosh, that's crazy.
- Really, if it hadn't been for me,
- Even if we use the chance card,
- I said to make a right turn.
- it should be 1 or 2 minutes prior.
- That's right.
- This neighborhood has...
- a sentimental vibe.
- Right.
By the way, I've also...
- walked around Jongno so much,
- Yes.
but this is my first time
coming into this back alley.
It's really nice here.
This back alley is a popular spot.
(Making eye contact)
- Hey, don't raise your hand.
- Oh, sorry.
- Is it a popular spot?
- My nipple keeps...
This alley in the back
is really popular.
- The Young Forty crowd must come...
- Back there.
- Hey, don't raise your hand!
- Back there,
- there's a comic book store.
- Don't raise your hand. Seriously.
Oh, man. Is anyone cold?
Do you want to huddle around?
- I know, right? It's cold. Come on.
- Come here. I'm so cold.
You're so weak.
- The Young Forties have gathered.
- Hey, I mean...
- I'm barefoot right now.
- I'm so cold.
- Gosh, why is your belly so warm?
- I'm so cold, though.
Hey, man.
Se Chan, are you wearing Armani?
- My gosh.
- Are you trying to show it off?
Hey, Armani underpants.
It's because I'm cold.
I can't stand how cold it is.
(Laughing)
That's crazy.
- Oh, it's warm like this.
- It's warm, right?
- Just covering your belly button...
- He only wears Armani undies.
- By the way, come to think of it,
- Yes?
wouldn't it be better to use
the chance card...
for plus or minus three minutes
instead of asking for the time?
- No.
- No, we should ask for the time.
That's not bad either.
- They told us the time at first.
- We kind of know.
But if we use
the three-minute chance,
- we must count for three minutes.
- Yes, if you think about it,
it's three minutes before or after.
But we should find out
the exact time...
- And use it five minutes later.
- That's right.
"What time is it?" Then,
we can start counting from then on.
For example, it can be three minutes
before or after.
- That's right.
- Yes, plus or minus three minutes.
- I think that's better.
- We could get up to six minutes.
(One person is deep in silence.)
(Fidgeting)
(Mumbling)
Should we use the chance card now?
- No! Wait. Right now, wait...
- No.
- I feel like...
- Let's use it in one more minute.
(It's still too early
to use the chance card.)
There's about six...
- Two minutes.
- Five or six minutes?
- Really? About 3 minutes later?
- There's about 5 or 6 minutes left.
- What do you think?
- Pardon?
Let's ask the time, then.
Asking the time...
So, you think asking the time...
- and counting is better?
- Hey, mister.
Don't you eat, mister?
We were ruined because of you
in the last mission.
Haven't you been eating lately?
Why?
Just know that we have 5 minutes
left now.
About 6 or 5 minutes.
- You mean 5 or 6 minutes.
- Yes, 5 or 6 minutes.
- Hey, you sounded like a foreigner.
- No.
- Hey, you sounded like a foreigner!
- It's about four minutes.
- Because of the 6 or 5 minutes?
- Yes, 6 or 5 minutes.
- There's 6 or 5 minutes left.
- You sounded like a foreigner.
Hey, Jonathan, are you sure?
- Five minutes.
- Do we have five minutes left now?
- Then, in about 5 minutes.
- We have 5 minutes left.
- let's use the plus or minus three.
- Yes, right.
- But we don't even know...
- Yes?
if the time we choose is within
the plus or minus three timeframe.
Wouldn't it be better
to find out the time?
- Then, if we have about 3 minutes,
- No, the 3-minute card.
- Yes?
- then we have to count 180 seconds.
- We can count.
- No.
- No, instead of doing that...
- We have three minutes left, right?
- What Jae Seok is saying is that...
- we can count a bit more.
- But then...
(In the meantime,
Jonathan Watch is so precise.)
(Laughing awkwardly)
All right. We'll take the picture
in about 1 or 2 minutes.
(Mediating)
Three minutes. No, two minutes.
- Who do you think you are?
- We have two minutes left.
(Sighing)
- I...
- You're nothing but a Young Forty.
"Nothing but?"
- "Nothing but?" Young Forties.
- Who are you?
All of you, stand behind me.
Hey, if he keeps treating us...
Why are you avoiding me?
(There isn't much time left.)
If you have an orange iPhone,
you're in front. The iPhone 17.
- Nice.
- As we speak, two minutes left.
- All right.
- Let's go!
- Do it. Use the chance card.
- We have plenty of time.
- We'll use the chance card.
- Which chance card will you use?
- Plus or minus 3 minutes.
- Let's use the three-minute card.
- If we use that,
- we have to take the photo now.
- Let's do that.
Not that one. Let's just...
- ask for the time.
- Let's ask for the time.
- No.
- That's better.
- Asking for the time is better.
- Come on.
- That one is better.
- Then, play rock-paper-scissors.
- Fine, play rock-paper-scissors.
- Asking for the time is better.
(Rock-paper-scissors
when we don't have time?)
- Ssaebssaeb, you do it.
- Plus or minus three minutes...
- I choose plus or minus three.
- Me too.
- Hey, hurry up!
- Plus or minus three minutes...
- Rock-paper-scissors. Okay.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay, we won.
- Darn it.
- Since Se Chan won...
- Plus or minus three minutes, then.
- We chose to ask for the time.
- Yes, the time.
- But we have to play too.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- But he was your representative.
- Why is he the representative?
- He's not the representative.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
(Time is almost up!)
He's not the representative.
We only have one minute left
as we speak!
- Okay, let's go.
- Do it.
- Hurry up and use whatever!
- The time!
- Hurry up! Just ask the time!
- Come on!
Play rock-paper-scissors again!
- The current time?
- The time.
(They use the chance card to check
the time as they won.)
- No.
- Okay, the current time...
is 1 p.m...
It's 1:09 p.m. and 13 seconds.
- Now! Count!
- One.
It's 1:09 p.m. and 13 seconds.
(They'll succeed as long as they
count the remaining seconds well.)
- Fifteen. Sixteen.
- See?
- Seventeen.
- Asking for the time was right.
- Eighteen. Nineteen. Twenty.
- I told you!
We can take our time
and take it during the tenth minute.
- We have a whole minute to take it.
- Four. Five.
- We can take our time.
- We have to succeed in this.
- Seven.
- He's the clock man.
- Don't confuse him.
Twenty-nine. Thirty.
- That's too fast.
- One.
Eight. Nine. Fifty seconds.
Eight. Nine. It's ten past.
- Let's take a little time. One.
- Take some time.
- Take it!
- No.
- Here. Fifteen.
- All right.
- I took a photo.
- He took a photo.
- Did you take a photo?
- Now,
- we'll check the time.
- I think we'll be okay.
- We did well.
- That was sufficient.
- It's okay. The time was...
- We took it at the right time.
- Now,
the exact time
at which you took the photo was...
Was it 1 p.m.?
- It was 1 o'clock and...
- Ten minutes.
Ten minutes and 25 seconds.
We did it.
(They took the photo exactly
at 10 past 1!)
- We did it.
- We did it pretty easily.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- Don't act out.
- Jae Seok, using...
Using the three-minute chance card
would've worked.
- It wouldn't have worked.
- No.
- It would've worked.
- Three minutes...
It would've been perfect, you fool.
- Why?
- It's plus or minus three minutes.
- This is more dramatic.
- That's right.
- We counted the seconds.
- This is...
- more fun.
- It was so much fun.
- I really don't like you guys.
- Seriously.
Then leave.
Why would I leave?
(Their combined age is 99,
but they fight childishly.)
- Hey, leave.
- Where would I go?
- Go home.
Who wants to come with me?
He told Haha to leave.
- Leave. Go home.
- Let's eat.
This is the route
that was taken by Sunragun,
the public safety officials
of the Joseon dynasty...
- called Seosulla-gil.
- This is Seosulla-gil.
This place became popular
when trendy shops entered...
- along the stone wall.
- I was here.
This place is pretty.
It looks nice.
This place has changed so much.
Yes. Now,
you can finally take photos.
Please take a few photos
you'll submit...
in a free-spirited manner.
You'll compete
with those photos at the end.
- We need to capture the street?
- Yes.
(Citizens will have a vote
using the photos they've taken.)
Our photos will be evaluated.
Only first place comes with a prize.
If you want, you can use a model.
None of them will make
a useful model.
- Me.
- Everyone is useless.
Should this place be the background?
A photo that resembles
an oil painting.
I'll take an incredible photo.
I'm sorry, but would you be
my model?
- No.
- No?
- Are you expensive?
- Yes. I'm sorry.
- Okay.
- And today is my day off.
- Is it your day off?
- Yes.
I'm sorry,
but how much will you pay me?
I'm a model in Korea.
I'll feed you three meals a day.
Three meals a day.
- That sounds like a swear word.
- The cost of living is high.
- Are you kidding me?
- Hold on.
- This...
- These flowers are pretty.
He loves flowers.
It's natural to love flowers
as you age.
(Photographer Kook is captivated
by flowers, the cheap models.)
Good.
(Focused)
(He puts his heart into the task
and takes a photo.)
Look at this.
So many spots are pretty...
and atmospheric.
It's pretty.
Why can't I press it?
(Photographer Underboob
is at work as well.)
Why can't I press it?
It's so cold.
My belly is cold.
(Dongducheon's bicycle thief
captures his memories.)
Why is this place so pretty?
What's up with this place?
What are you capturing?
It's my aesthetic.
Why are you criticizing
my aesthetic?
(This time, he gets down
to the floor.)
It's pretty.
(This time, he tries
the shocking low-angle shot.)
- What are you doing?
- Jae Seok.
- Aren't you Jae Seok?
- No.
- No?
Don't you think people will like
Jae Seok's photo the most?
Exactly.
That's why I want to take
a photo of him.
But he keeps saying no.
(He fails to recruit
the popular model again.)
Sir, let me take a photo of you.
- No.
- No?
- Let me take a photo of you.
- Today is my day off.
- Is that why you're saying no?
- Yes.
- Let me take a photo of your back.
- No.
All right then.
(After failing to recruit a model,)
(he photographs Jonathan,
a celebrity.)
This is a celebrity who is moved...
by the tile-roofed hanok of Korea.
(A foreigner in Korea)
Oh, my goodness.
(Culture shock)
I love it.
(I love it.)
Laugh loudly.
Life is so much fun.
(Seok Jin recruited an older man
in the neighborhood.)
Laugh out loud.
(Giving a direction)
(Laughing)
Laugh out loud.
(Photographer Jee
keeps telling the model to laugh.)
Don't look at me. Look over there.
(Photographer Jee
keeps telling the model to laugh.)
Thank you. I'll do my best.
Would you please stand here?
Again?
(Without connecting with the model,
Seok Jin directs him to laugh.)
Please laugh as you look at the sky.
(Meanwhile, Haha)
This is cool.
This umbrella is in the shot.
(Young Forty Ha is absorbed
in the sentimentality of the past.)
What's the concept of your work?
It's the tile-roofed house
on a rainy day.
The tile-roofed house
and umbrella...
in the rain...
and loneliness.
It's nice.
Solitude.
(Solitude)
Regret.
(Regret)
Longing.
(Longing)
(And foolishness)
- Let's wrap up...
- I'm done.
and move.
Pick the best photo
and show it to us.
How cute.
A foreigner
who has just come to Korea.
How cute.
- This is mine.
- I'll go with this one.
I created a masterpiece.
I took a sentimental photo.
It'll be really tasty.
- What's this?
- It'll be tasty.
It looks like they're cooking.
I picked a truly shocking photo.
It shows you what happiness is.
The title is "Happiness."
(Whose work will be the winner?)
This is nice.
This restaurant...
is where you can taste
the authentic Texan barbecue.
Texan barbecue.
- Texas.
- My cousin lives in Texas.
- Why are you bringing that up?
- Seriously.
(No one wanted him to share
too much information.)
(The famous Texan barbecue appears!)
- Gosh, it looks so tasty.
- I'm sorry.
I'll judge the taste.
I've had the real Texan barbecue.
(Traditional barbecue that has been
smoked for a long time)
You had it too.
- That's right.
- You and I had the Texan barbecue.
(How will the Texas barbecue taste
where Jong Kook's cousin lives?)
- It looks tasty.
- You've succeeded in...
the time mission
at the second location,
so you won't have
any penalties here.
(They can eat comfortably
without any penalties!)
This is the best.
- If...
- Eat.
We succeeded in the mission.
If I hadn't told you to turn right
at Sulla-gil,
it would've been a disaster.
Hey, we were on the right-turn lane.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Seriously,
had you listened to Young Fifty...
Hey, get lost. Go home.
- "Go home."
- Eat barbecue and go home.
Why would I go home?
Seok Jin and Jonathan did well
in the beginning.
"Eat barbecue and go home."
Hey.
Eat and go home.
No!
No one is home.
- This is...
- Let's try it.
Do you have a small plate?
Gosh, this is...
I'm reminded of my trip to Texas.
- Is it tasty?
- This is...
Seriously.
- If...
- Eat.
We succeeded in the mission.
If I hadn't told you to turn right
at Sulla-gil...
(How is the burger he put together?)
Gosh, it's tasty.
You can eat it like this.
It's great.
The meat is so tender.
- It's so tasty.
- Yes.
(It gets approved
by the man from LA.)
What's this?
Hey, this is no joke.
- It's butter rice.
- It's garlic rice.
This is it.
Their ribs are tasty.
(It's the American taste
he hasn't had in Dongducheon.)
- They're baby back ribs, right?
- Yes.
- Seok Jin.
- This is it.
Seok Jin, the ribs are no joke.
They're so tasty.
(While the older members
focus on the meat)
It's so tasty.
(The Congolese man
is obsessed with garlic rice.)
This is how you eat it.
- Look at the meat. It's so big.
- It's tasty.
It's the best.
Do it now. There's no one.
It looks like a bib.
- A bib.
- I can't believe him.
(Jong Kook is especially excited.)
(This Korean American man
is absorbed in the taste of home.)
Yesterday... Today,
I came back from the US.
I feel like I'm still there.
Jong Kook, stop it already.
(Jong Kook's American dream)
I won't need to go
and see my cousin.
I'm full.
It was a great meal.
- The bread was great too.
- We ate so much. We enjoyed it.
Now, the last location remains.
- You know, he ate too much.
- His belly...
His belly is protruding too much.
- I'm sorry.
- It's so cute.
- Oh, my.
- We ate so much.
Your belly looks pretty.
- It looks cute, right?
- Some bellies are ugly.
- Some protruding bellies are cute.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- Some bellies are ugly,
but yours looks okay.
- It looks cute, right?
- It looks cute.
Your belly looks cute.
For the last chance card,
you'll have a mission.
- Okay.
- The mission is...
Fill in the Blank.
- Okay. It's my favorite game.
- Okay.
- You don't know what it is.
- I played it yesterday.
I played it like crazy
during Chuseok.
Young Forty, you're acting out
so much today.
I'm not acting out.
Can't I voice my thoughts?
Go home.
- Leave.
- Do you wear such clothes...
- at home?
- Yes, I do.
- You wear such clothes.
- Why do you ask?
It looks like you're home.
You wear such clothes at home.
I look like this at home.
It looks like
you're in the living room.
You'll get a three-syllable word.
To the beat, the production crew...
will say the first
and last syllables.
Then you'll say the whole word
that comes to mind.
- Okay.
- What does that mean?
- I love that game.
- For example, I might go...
Yu.
- Seok.
- Yu Jae Seok.
- That's how you do it.
- I see.
I'm good at it.
Bi.
- Cle.
- Bicycle.
- There you go.
- Young.
Ty.
- Haha.
- Young Forty.
That's right.
You'll take turns.
If everyone succeeds in it at once,
- you'll get a chance card.
- Let's go.
- Focus.
- It's simple.
- If we fail...
- Tomato. Bicycle.
- We need a chance card.
- It'll be unbecoming.
- You'll have six attempts.
- We'll give it a go.
- Good.
- Everyone needs to succeed in it.
Let's go in this order.
- You'll go first.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- He isn't very good at it.
- Let's go.
- Seok Jin, I'll give it a go.
Okay.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
- One, two, three, four.
- Three, four.
Man. Ray.
Scallop.
- Incorrect.
- It's "Manta ray."
Scallop.
- Incorrect.
- It's "Manta ray."
- Doesn't he know the rules?
- Manta ray.
- Mister.
- What's wrong with you?
- Let's start from that side.
- Mister.
- I thought it was "Scallop."
- For goodness' sake.
- You fill in the middle syllable.
- Seriously.
- For goodness' sake.
I'm sorry.
- Let's start from that side.
- It's quite nerve-racking.
- That means...
- you failed once.
- Let's start from that side.
- No.
- Let it slide.
- It was Jae Seok.
- Let's say it was a practice round.
- Jonathan will go first.
- Okay.
(Since he misunderstood the rules,
it'll be a practice round.)
I'll sit here.
- I can think of all the words.
- Seok Sam...
Jonathan will go first.
- One, two, three, four.
- Three, four.
Draw. Pad.
- Bellflower root.
- Incorrect.
- What?
- That was an easy one.
- Bellflower root.
- Incorrect.
- What?
- That was an easy one.
- Drawing pad.
- It was an easy one.
(Oh, no)
- He's a foreigner.
- Drawing pad.
- Do you even speak Korean?
- Can you speak Korean?
I didn't understand Korean.
- I couldn't speak Korean.
- Go easy on him.
- "Drawing pad" was easy.
- We'll change the order.
- Okay.
Let's start over with the order.
Okay. Let's go in the order.
- Jong Kook.
- Okay.
- I mean...
- He's a foreigner in Korea, okay?
- He's a foreigner.
- Drawing pad.
"Drawing pad" is a bit much
for a foreigner.
- Drawing pad.
- Let's go.
- Jong Kook.
- Help us succeed in it.
- Give us the easy ones.
- Jong Kook will go first.
- Let's do this. Okay.
- Let's go.
- Set, go.
One, two, three, four.
- Cheap. Te.
- Cheap.
- Cheapskate.
- There you go. It's easy.
(Jong Kook gets a pass.)
- It's easy.
- All right.
Brack. Fern.
Broken.
- Incorrect.
- Bracken fern.
- Broken.
Seok Jin, it was hard.
- Bracken fern. What was "Broken?"
- Get down on the floor.
- What was "Broken?"
- Give me a kick.
- It was obviously "Bracken fern."
- It was easy.
- He should've gotten it right.
- Mister, come here.
- Here?
- Jonathan, take that seat.
- Scoot over.
Listen. Don't try to do well.
- Don't try to do well.
- Just pretend to talk.
- Okay.
- Imagine watching TV.
- Don't focus so much.
- That's the problem.
- If you try to do well...
- That's right.
- Let's go.
Haha will go first. Set, go.
I got this.
- Three, four.
- An easy one.
- It's easy.
- Ham. Ger.
- Hammerger.
- What?
- What? Isn't it "Hamburger?"
- What was that?
- Fire extinguisher.
Hammerger.
What?
(Ham, ger)
- Hamburger.
- Incorrect.
Hammerger.
- What's wrong with him?
- Get lost.
What's wrong with Young Forty?
Come here, Young Forty.
(Haha's pathetic failure
makes Jong Kook laugh.)
- Hey, Diving Beetle, come here.
- Young Forty.
- Young Forty, come here.
- I mean...
- What was that?
- What are those glasses?
I said "Hamburger."
- Come on.
- Seriously!
I said "Hamburger."
Hey!
(He's nearly crying.)
I couldn't believe it.
He had no confidence whatsoever.
- Go over there.
- He had no confidence whatsoever.
I can't believe him!
There's nothing he does well.
(Fourth attempt)
(Only half the attempts remain.)
Ji Hyo will go first.
Let's begin. One, two, three, four.
Po. To.
- Potato.
- There you go.
- Ji Hyo is good.
- It was easy.
(It's Jae Seok's turn.)
Run. Shoes.
("Running shoes" is an easy choice!)
- Runna shoes.
- Incorrect.
Running shoes!
Runna shoes.
(In disbelief)
- Running shoes!
- Get up.
- No excuses.
- Runna shoes.
- Listen.
Jae Seok, it was too much.
- I mean...
- Not "Running shoes."
What's wrong with you?
(They don't understand
his poor performance.)
- I couldn't think of it.
- You said "Runna shoes..."
- instead of "Running shoes."
- Runna shoes.
He shouldn't criticize other people.
(He becomes quiet.)
- For goodness' sake.
- You couldn't get past two people.
- Seriously.
- Let's do this.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- We'll do this for real.
Please go slowly and give us
some time.
- Seriously.
- Then we'll answer.
- Please give us some time.
- Okay.
Again.
Let's show them what we can do.
Let's do this.
- Ajou University.
- Business major.
Ajou University's business major,
let's go.
- During a conversation...
- It'll come smoothly.
- One, two, three, four.
Mi. Ri.
- Miari.
- It was an easy one.
(After Seok Jin,
it's Jong Kook's turn!)
- Wash.
Sin.
- Washer...
- Wash basin!
Incorrect.
(Even the fifth attempt fails.)
- Washer.
- Wash basin.
It's "Wash basin."
(They only have one chance!)
Couldn't you think of "Wash basin?"
- Are you criticizing me?
- You should've thought of it.
He got it confused with "Washer."
Mister, sit here.
- Okay.
- It's funny since we're bad at it.
We're so bad at it.
Did you prepare many words?
Can you keep going?
Even if you give us
the same ones, we'll fail.
- We've never gone far.
- Give us...
- the easiest ones at first.
- Yes.
- When...
- It's hard.
- Then...
- Make it three strikes.
Count it as a success
if six members succeed in it.
Five out of eight members
need to succeed in it.
- Good.
- Let's do this.
- Even if you mess up, keep going.
- Okay.
Even if you mess up, keep going.
- Don't scold other people.
- This is the very last chance.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Se Chan will go first.
- He won't succeed in it.
- Okay.
- One, two, three, four.
Cut. Fish.
Cuttlefish.
(Correct)
(Se Chan gets a pass.
Jong Kook is next!)
Three, four.
- Au. Ra.
- Au.
- Aurora.
- There you go.
(The 1st 2 consecutive passes!
Ji Hyo is next!)
Hou. Cat.
It's an easy one.
Hochu cat.
- Incorrect.
- Go.
(She fails,)
(but they keep going!)
- Go.
(Se Chan, Jong Kook: Pass
Ji Hyo: Fail)
- A.
- A?
- Shell.
- A.
("Acorn shell" is easy!)
(Jae Seok has never gotten a pass!
Will he get a pass this time?)
Aga shell.
- Incorrect.
- Acorn shell!
Aga shell.
- Acorn!
(Among the 4 remaining members,
3 need to succeed in it.)
- Just keep going.
- What's your problem?
(They keep going. It's Haha's turn!)
- For goodness' sake.
- One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four.
- Honey.
- Honey?
Ger.
- Honey roger.
- There you go.
(Even Haha messes up!)
What is it? Go ahead.
- What is it?
- "Honey roger?"
- What is it then?
- Honey badger.
- "Honey badger" was a hard one.
- It was a hard one.
- All three need to succeed in it.
- All of us need to succeed in it.
- This is the beginning.
- One, two, three, four.
- Let's go.
Jeo. Ri.
- Jeogori.
- There you go.
(Daniel gets a pass.
Jonathan is next!)
One, two, three, four.
Mi. Phone.
- Microphone.
- There you go.
- That foreigner is good.
(Even Jonathan gets a pass!)
(They'll succeed in the mission
if Seok Jin gets a pass!)
Hob. Lin.
(Hob, Lin)
(It's so easy! It's "Hobgoblin!")
- Hobsalin.
- Hobgoblin!
Incorrect.
- Hobsalin.
- Hobgoblin!
(They fail the mission.)
- What even is "Hobsalin?"
- Come on!
You did it on purpose, right?
- No. I'm serious.
- You did it on purpose, right?
- No.
- "Hobsalin" could be a word.
- Both of you...
- What's wrong with you?
- Seok Jin, "Hobsalin" is...
- I couldn't remember the word.
- That happens.
- Jae Seok.
- What even is "Hobsalin?"
- Don't lie.
- You did it on purpose, right?
- I couldn't remember the word.
- Don't lie.
- Seriously.
- I didn't do it on purpose.
We'll do it without a chance card.
It isn't your decision to do it
without a chance card.
- You failed.
- You're so brazen.
- We'll do it without a chance card.
- Mister.
- You're so brazen.
- We'll do it without a chance card.
It's nothing.
How did we fail so miserably?
- Seriously.
- We'll do it without a chance card.
You failed the final attempt,
so you won't get a chance card.
Please give us the same questions.
- I'm just annoyed.
- Stop. Do it at home.
Why would I do it at home?
- With whom would I do it?
- Go home.
- Who will give me the questions?
No, I won't go home.
The third location is...
- Naksan Park.
- At the park,
- Where is it?
we installed a clock tower.
You'll succeed in the mission...
if you remove the cloth
exactly at 3:05 p.m.
The current time is 2:38 p.m.
Already?
- Naksan Park must be nearby.
- We have 30 minutes left.
- How far is it? Is it nearby?
- Ten minutes?
- Ten minutes.
- You'll take the car.
We'll drop you off nearby this time.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
It'll be a miracle
if we guess correctly.
In that case...
- Hold on. We need to count.
- Ten or fifteen minutes.
- Ten or fifteen minutes. So...
- We need to guess.
- the estimated time of arrival...
- Yes.
- Five minutes to three.
Once we arrive there,
we should do it in ten minutes.
It'll take ten minutes to get there.
Since it's raining,
it might take a bit longer.
It'll be a miracle
if we guess correctly.
Seok Jin, we might need to run
since there's a traffic jam.
- There's a lot of traffic.
- But...
- The time...
- We don't have much time.
Did you hear the time
when we left earlier?
It was 30-something or 40 minutes.
It was around 35 or 38 minutes.
I'm focusing on guessing...
Me too.
I'm doing it more.
We have to get there by 3:05 p.m.
- Right now...
- Just stay still.
- Then it's...
- About 10 to 12 minutes left.
Then it's past 50 minutes now.
- It's not past that.
- Then what time do you think it is?
What do you think the time is?
Pouty Mouth.
Tell us, Young Forty.
What time do you think it is?
Sixty can say it first,
and I'll say it.
Hey, it's Fifty.
(He snaps.)
- Hey.
- That's funny.
Should I say it now?
- Fifty.
- You'd get shocked.
It's 57 minutes 42 seconds.
- No.
- It's not that late.
- That's not right. Fifty...
- That's nowhere close.
- Right now...
- It's around 55 to 53.
It's 2:49 p.m.
- No.
- It's more than that.
It's exactly 2:53 p.m.
I think it's around 2:50 p.m.
- It's only been that much?
- Yes.
Our opinions are so different.
That's how it is.
Do our opinions have to be the same?
They can be different.
- Seok Jin.
- What's wrong with you?
Why are you swearing?
Why are you doing that?
(He's touched by all the scolding
from every direction.)
It sounded like I was mad, right?
I wasn't mad.
Don't intimidate him.
(Laughing)
I can see how
you might've misunderstood.
I was shocked.
You're at the back.
- You're the furthest from me.
- Is that so?
I was talking loudly.
- Is that what it was?
- "Why are you doing that?"
(He keeps talking in awkwardness.)
You could've misunderstood that.
I'll admit that.
You could misunderstand it,
but it was never my intention.
It's so funny how Seok Jin says
he doesn't get mad.
- He says he doesn't get mad.
- But...
why do you scold him all at once?
Because it doesn't make sense.
It's in the script.
Everyone says,
"Why are you doing that?"
- "Don't get mad."
- You should say it too.
- This is 100 percent script.
- You should also say it.
- Why are you doing that?
You should also say it
when the time comes.
This is so funny.
(Today's line that captured
the audience's heart)
"You should also say it
when the time comes."
- You should also say it.
- Seriously...
(One man is silent
amid the script talk.)
What is your guess, Jonathan?
Are you secretly counting the time?
- Yes. I'm...
- Jae Seok is...
- really into it.
- I would be counting it accurately.
He's doing it sharply.
Jae Seok is good at focusing.
What time is it now?
It would be around 58 minutes.
I think it's around 53
or 54 minutes.
(He's accurate.)
I think it's 45 minutes now.
- No.
- Around 43 minutes...
We were accurate earlier
because we had the chance card.
- We need it.
- This is hard.
It would be a miracle
if we get this right.
It would be hard to guess it right.
- I think it's going to be hard.
- Seriously hard.
It's making me a bit nervous.
It has to be 3:05 p.m.
- When we get there...
- It might be...
It's 2:55 p.m. now,
and we have to be there at 3:05 p.m.
We just have to guess it right
in between.
How are we going to time those
ten minutes without a chance card?
- This is hard.
- Now...
- We're here.
- Right now...
- It's 50 minutes.
- It's 57 minutes.
- No. It's 50...
- It's 50 minutes now.
- It's 57 minutes.
- It's 59 minutes.
- It's 59 minutes?
- It's 58 minutes.
- It's 58 minutes 22 seconds.
- What's wrong?
(The bus shook.)
- It's 58 minutes.
- It's 58 minutes 22 seconds.
- What's wrong?
- Can't we go up?
- Should we walk up?
- I guess it got stuck.
- It got stuck.
In the gutter.
- It's slippery.
- We'd have to get out.
We'll get out then.
If you give the bus a little push...
- Let's push it.
- Seok Jin.
You don't all have to leave.
- Let's get out.
- It's that bad?
- Get away.
- Don't do it.
We'll get out and go.
- You have to be careful.
- The right...
One...
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- It's moving.
- Did you get out?
- It's because of the metal.
Move forward a bit more.
Move forward.
I think it's done.
We just need to pass
over the metal part.
- It's done.
- You can move forward.
- Should we push more?
(They managed to save the bus.)
It would be nearly 3 p.m. now.
- Yes.
- What?
- Can it move?
- I think it's around 3 p.m.
- Keep going forward.
- Hey.
- It's cold.
- I think it's around 3 p.m.
It's so cold.
We don't have much time.
(It's exactly 3 p.m.)
- Let's go.
- It's 3 p.m.
- It's 3:01 p.m.
- Hey, hurry up.
- Get out. Let's all go.
I think it's around 3:01 p.m.
- What?
- I think it's a little past 3 p.m.
- How did you know that?
- Really?
- Is it your feeling?
- It's my feeling.
I've been counting in my head.
Hold on. Let's count from now on.
Do we have four minutes left now?
Around 4 or 3 minutes.
- Let's count three minutes now.
- One, two,
three, four, five,
- six, seven,
- Because earlier,
- it was around 3 p.m.
- eight,
nine, ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen...
You're a bit fast, Seok Jin.
- Slow down.
- Go on.
- I was counting.
- thirty-eight, thirty-nine,
Young Forty,
forty-one, forty-two,
- forty-three,
- It's nearing your age.
forty-four,
- forty...
- Shall we say "happy birthday?"
- forty-six,
- when he says sixty.
- forty-five,
Why are you saying forty-five
after forty-six?
- forty-nine,
- What's wrong with him?
- fifty,
- Okay.
- fifty-one, fifty-two,
- Two minutes passed.
- fifty...
- He counts backward.
fifty-four, fifty-five,
- fifty-six, seven,
- Seven.
- eight, nine...
- Eight, nine...
- Happy birthday!
It's finally 60.
- Happy birthday to you
Happy 60 years.
(Jae Seok isn't even participating
in teasing Seok Sam.)
(He's still counting the time.)
Has it been about ten seconds?
- Nine, ten,
- Yes. It's been ten seconds.
eleven,
- You're on 20 seconds.
- twelve, thirteen...
If only the sun were out,
I could tell the exact time.
I've been getting a grasp
on how long ten minutes are.
It's not a smooth road.
This is a hard mission.
It's very hard.
Where is it? How...
(They have to arrive
before the deadline.)
- Eight.
- We're here. We have to run.
It's been two minutes!
- We have to run.
- It's been two minutes!
Let's run as soon as we get out.
We have to hurry
as soon as we get out.
When should we arrive there by?
- By 3:05 p.m.
- Let's go.
(They arrive at the parking lot.)
- Hurry.
- Unbuckle your seatbelt.
- Let's go!
- Seok Jin.
We have to take it
as soon as we get there.
- Nineteen,
- Where is it?
twenty,
- twenty-one,
- twenty-two,
- Where is it?
- twenty-three,
- It's cold!
- Let's go.
- twenty-four...
- Hurry up and go.
- Go.
- Where is it?
- Twenty-six,
twenty-seven, twenty-eight,
twenty-nine, thirty,
thirty-one...
- We have no time.
- It's here.
- Thirty-three,
- Here.
- thirty-four...
(Will they be able to pass
at exactly 3:05 p.m.?)
Thirty-seven, thirty-eight,
- Hold on. Is it really the time?
- thirty-nine...
It's this one.
- Here.
- I don't think it's time yet.
- This one.
- Do we open this?
What was the time earlier?
When you think it's exactly 3:05 p.m.,
you can remove the black cloth.
- If it's 3:05 p.m., you'd succeed.
- No.
- I think we could do it now.
- Now!
- Should I do it now?
- Hold on.
- No.
- Ten seconds.
- Earlier,
- Ten,
- nine,
- you said it in the car...
- eight, seven,
- It's been three minutes.
- six, five...
- Six, five...
- Can't we wait a little longer?
- It's been three minutes.
Remove it. One,
- two, three!
- No.
(Would it be 3:05 p.m.?)
- Two, three!
- No.
- It's past the time.
(It's past 3:05 p.m.)
- So...
(Has it been 2 minutes
since they arrived?)
- We...
- It's past the time.
- We arrived after the time.
- What time is it now?
We should have removed it
right away.
The time would have passed
even if we had done that.
- Still.
- According to the digital watch,
it's 3:05:35 p.m...
- right now.
- Did we get it?
(The clock tower's time
doesn't match the real time.)
- Really?
- Did we get it?
- This is right.
- How did you know?
Is it correct?
(Current time: 3:05 p.m.)
- Really?
- I...
(They removed the cloth
at exactly 3:05 p.m.)
(30 minutes
before the members arrived)
(The clock broke...)
(in the pouring rain and wind.)
Jae Seok guessed this right.
I kept in mind
how long ten minutes were.
He kept saying it was 3 p.m.
as soon as we got out. "How?"
I had the same in mind.
I have goosebumps. Jinx.
It's also very similar
to what I thought.
It's exactly as I counted.
It's almost...
We three are really crazy.
- We three are crazy.
- We three did it.
(The human clocks
did it by their feeling.)
The idols...
- We three did it.
- He's saying, "We three did it."
"We three did it."
It's crazy.
- But...
- You're the best, Jae Seok.
We were lucky. If that bus...
- Right.
- had just come, we'd have lost.
Pushing that bus was also luck.
That's right.
We were lucky that the bus stopped.
- If we hadn't done that,
- Jae Seok is the best.
- we'd have removed it at 3:04 p.m.
- Right. At 3:04 p.m.
We've arrived at a park
where the walls of the Hanyang Fortress...
blend beautifully with the forest.
Recently, it appeared...
- That's right. It was there.
- on "KPop Demon Hunters,"
- It's right here.
- and has become popular...
- with foreigners as well.
- Really?
Actually, we prepared a penalty...
in case you would fail again.
But you're exempt from the penalty.
(All the members
are exempt from the penalty.)
(Sticking out)
We succeeded.
- I'm so relieved.
- We did a good job.
- It could've been dangerous.
- Well done.
- It could've been bad.
- Right.
I will now tell you the results...
of the citizens' vote...
- on the photos you took.
- Yes.
The winner,
with the most votes, is...
- Yes.
- I bet it's Se Chan.
(Who is the winner
to get the prize?)
The winner is...
Is it Jonathan?
Jong Kook with "A Flower Alley."
(1st place: Kim Jong Kook
with 17 votes)
Jong Kook with "A Flower Alley."
(He even named his work himself.)
- Why?
- I knew it.
- Seriously?
- Why?
What about the flowers?
- What?
- How many votes did it get?
The thing is, the title
and the photo matched well.
The second place
is "A Healing Smile."
(2nd place: Jae Seok with 12 votes)
- What was that?
- "A Healing Smile."
- Really?
- I see.
I'm the one in the photo?
- I took it.
- He had a model.
- It came in second place.
- It was him?
- "A Healing Smile" was a good one.
- The third place...
is "We're AI."
(3rd place: Jonathan with 11 votes)
"We're AI."
Seok Jin thought
he would win first place.
Seok Jin...
got only two votes.
(Jee Seok Jin came in last
with just 2 votes.)
Who's the last?
- I was really...
- Mine is a sensitive work.
To Kim Jong Kook,
who won first place today,
we will give the prize.
- It's a box of seasonal pears.
- Nice.
(A box of ripe pears that resemble
Ssaebssaeb's belly)
- Pears sound nice.
- I love pears.
Contrary to our expectations,
- you succeeded twice today.
- That's unbelievable.
- So you only received one penalty.
- Yes!
- Okay.
- Today,
you may go home now.
(All of them get to go home.)
We are amazing.
Good work, Jonathan.
- Thank you.
We did a great job today.
Right. It was amazing.
(The 3 keywords that heated up
Running Man for the past week)
(The protagonist
of the first keyword)
(Keyword 1: Ji Ye Eun's comeback)
(Crying suddenly)
(Why are you crying again?)
(I'm getting emotional
to come back after 3 weeks.)
- Tell us what you want to eat.
- Yangjangpi.
(A healthier body
and a stronger appetite)
(Narrow it down to 3
when I talk to you nicely.)
(Keyword 2: Young Forty Haha)
(He's dressed like
the Korean Association president.)
(They keep making fun
of Young Forty Ha.)
(Find the perfect style for Haha,
who is completely lost.)
(The Young Forty meme
is about to die.)
(He is the newly appointed director.)
(The original Peter Pan
watches for a chance.)
(Keyword 3: In his 50s for 3 years)
(If you get the massage,
you'll look 10 years younger.)
(Crushing his face
to maintain his youth)
(The long and arduous road
to rejuvenation)
(Haha is standing among the staff.)
(Fine clothes make the man.)
(It's sad. Don't do that.)
(To avoid the penalty,
complete the keyword task!)
(Running Man's Weekly Keyword)