It's sunny today.
The weather is cold.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Happy New Year.
Okay!
Congratulations, Jae Seok!
- Congratulations, Jae Seok!
- Congratulations.
- It's the 20th Grand Award.
- I knew it.
- Congratulations.
- I'm sorry I wasn't there that day.
- You made it.
(The 19th Grand Award
on SBS in 2022)
I've got 19 awards,
so I'll try until the end...
to get one more.
Yu Jae Seok.
- Yu Jae Seok.
(Yu Grand Award has run
without a break for 20 years.)
(After giving relentless effort
without hesitation in 2024...)
The 2024 SBS Entertainment Awards.
The Grand Award goes to...
Yu Jae Seok. Congratulations.
(He made history by winning
his 20th Grand Award...)
(at the SBS Entertainment Awards
this year.)
I made it.
(I made it.)
- It's the 20th Grand Award.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Our Jae Seok did it.
- It's really cool.
Have you won the Grand Award
every year for 20 years?
I didn't win it every year.
- It's 20 in total.
- Almost every year.
- In total.
- It's 20 in total.
- I've won 20 awards for 20 years.
- You won 20 Grand Awards.
- That's great.
- It'll be hard to break the record.
- Right. No one can break it.
- No one can do it.
I don't know how it feels
to win 20 Grand Awards.
Now that you've won 20,
you should announce that
you won't receive any more awards.
- Me?
- You should do that.
To the three broadcasting companies.
"I'm happy with 20 awards."
I don't want to win
any more Grand Awards.
- Well...
- He'll get it if he's given one.
- Yes.
- Sure.
And the number 21 is quite catchy.
Twenty-one.
- Number 22 sounds good too.
- It's 22.
- Make it 22 then.
Anyway, I'm also grateful
that we've been doing...
Running Man for 15 years.
- Right.
- Already?
- It's the oldest variety show ever.
- Right.
Running Man received an award.
- Congratulations.
(It is more meaningful
as it is chosen by the viewers.)
The Most Popular Show Award
chosen by viewers.
(Most Popular Show Award,
Running Man)
(And an award winner
chosen by viewers' votes)
(Scene Stealer Award, Song Ji Hyo)
(The Most Viewed
Short Clip Award...)
(with overwhelming popularity
around the world, Kim Jong Kook)
The Rising Star Award.
(And the two youngest members
won the Rising Star Award!)
Appearing on Running Man
was like a dream to me.
(Hoon gave his sincere speech calmly
though he was a little nervous.)
I won the award.
I love you, Mom.
(After Hoon's acceptance speech...)
I'm so grateful to be here today.
(She started giving a speech
with a goat-like voice.)
(Crying)
- Ye Eun.
- You should soothe Ye Eun.
I really wanted to join Running Man.
She really wanted
to join Running Man.
I'd like to thank Running Man...
- for having me on Running Man.
- Thank you.
I will work harder to become...
the rising star Ji Ye Eun
who makes people laugh.
- What an impressive pronunciation.
- Thank you.
(The cute speech of the youngest
shook the whole country.)
Ye Eun cried.
- She was so cute.
- Ye Eun.
Don't people stop doing that
when they turn four?
(Crying)
- Why did you cry?
- Actually, I prepared a speech.
- An acceptance speech.
- You did?
- What was it?
- What were you going to say?
I prepared something cool
for my acceptance speech.
But my mind went blank
when I got on the stage.
You should do it here.
Show us what you prepared.
- What is it?
- I forgot again.
- You forgot?
- Yes.
Did it have some famous saying?
I wanted to show
a different side of me.
But when I got up,
I was really nervous.
- Of course.
- You must've been nervous.
- Ye Eun was wearing a dress.
- Yes.
She couldn't breathe at all.
She was like...
The moment she let her guard down,
- her belly stuck out.
- No.
- "Hey, what is this?"
"It's nothing!"
In her dress?
She was about to die.
- She couldn't breathe.
- Really?
It was too tight.
People said my face was puffy
and I gained weight.
But I skipped meals.
I even skipped meals
on the previous day too. But...
It was so tight that
the fat got pushed up to the face.
- She was like this.
- Because of poor blood circulation,
it was pushed up to the face.
That's when I realized it.
When my waist was cinched up,
- it went all the way up to my face.
- I see.
- We had a cake there,
- She didn't eat.
but she didn't eat it.
Only Kang Hoon ate it.
- I couldn't. I was feeling dizzy.
- That's not good.
- Right.
- When I saw you and Kang Hoon...
at the awards ceremony,
you two looked good together.
- It looked nice.
- Right. They looked good together.
- Right? I'm serious.
- It wasn't bad.
- They made a cute couple.
- She seemed quite conscious.
(Laughing)
- She was conscious of it.
- You looked great together...
- when you were all dressed up.
- Right.
They make a cute couple.
- They looked cute.
- Be nice to him.
But, in reality,
- Se Chan is just perfect.
- Right.
Be realistic.
She's old enough to realize that.
- Se Chan is...
- Okay.
- We don't know how Se Chan feels.
- We don't.
Se Chan isn't interested in Ye Eun.
- No.
- It's an X.
It's an X.
- We are having two guests today.
- Really?
Please bring in the guests.
- Do we have guests?
- Guests?
- Who are they?
- Really?
- Jong Hyuk.
- What?
- Number 95.
- Jong Hyuk.
- The one who resembles Se Chan.
- Right.
- They look alike.
- Si Eun.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Hello. Congratulations.
- Hello.
Trickster Kwon Min Woo.
(Se Chan's doppelganger
who showed off his terrible dance moves)
- Short chin.
- I have a short chin.
Me too.
- Does your mouth touch a mask?
- Which one?
It's between us. It does.
(Jong Hyun because the new Bucktooth
sharing stories about his mouth.)
(He's playing Kang Gi Ho,
an assistant director in "Trigger.")
(He's being praised
for his good chemistry...)
(with Kim Hye Soo and Jung Sung Il.)
(The rising star on screen,
Joo Jong Hyuk)
(Kim Si Eun, the famous
number 95 of the "Squid Game")
(She became the talk of the town
for her resemblance to Ye Eun.)
(It will be fun if Kim Si Eun
appears on Running Man.)
(What? It wasn't Ji Ye Eun?)
(I thought it was Ji Ye Eun,
but it turned out to be Kim Si Eun.)
- Hello. Congratulations.
- Hello.
Hello.
- You two really look alike.
- She looks like me.
- She looks like Ye Eun.
- Hello.
- It's been a while.
- Number 95.
(Jong Hyuk looks comfortable
since it's his second time here.)
- It's been a while.
- He's really...
- Jong Hyuk, how have you been?
- Hey.
Hey.
(Welcome,
the handsome version of me.)
- Hi.
- Stand here.
Welcome.
- Hello.
She's Kim Si Eun.
Do they look alike?
People asked...
- if I was on "Squid Game."
- It looked like you.
- Hello.
- My goodness.
- They look alike.
- Yes. These two.
- We look alike.
Stand in the middle.
- You look really similar.
- Come here.
- Come here, Jong Hyuk.
- Okay.
- Stand here.
- Stand next to me.
- Stand together.
- Si Eun.
- They look alike.
- She was on "Squid Game 2."
- Right.
- She was number 95.
People said she looked like Ye Eun.
- Right.
- They do look alike.
- They look similar.
- That's true.
- This part looks similar.
- When she appeared on the show...
- People thought it was me.
- That's true.
- They do look alike.
- They really do.
- They look similar.
- It's my first time meeting her.
- But I feel a sense of closeness.
- I know.
- I understand.
- Still,
you can't be like
Se Chan and Jong Hyuk.
(The jaw doppelgangers are
on another level.)
We can't beat them.
They look the same.
- It's surprising.
- You should stand there.
- How can they resemble so much?
- They look the same.
I feel bad for Jong Hyuk.
Wherever he goes to promote his work,
people talk about me.
- I'm sorry.
- Even when I'm on a radio show,
they always talk about you.
Jong Hyuk is back after a long time.
- You're doing a new drama, right?
- Yes.
- It's on the air now.
- Really?
- What is it?
- It's called "Trigger."
- I see. "Trigger."
- "Trigger."
- It features Kim Hye Soo.
- I know that.
- Yes.
- The story is quite satisfying.
It's about
an investigative news show.
An investigative news show.
- Yes.
- It's fun and satisfying.
- So you are working with Hye Soo.
- Right.
- Oh, dear.
- How was she?
She's really...
There are
only good stories about her.
- She's really nice.
- My gosh.
- She's like a magnanimous boss.
- Right.
Hye Soo once came...
to Running Man with her niece.
- Right.
- She did.
- Just to watch?
- She was so sweet.
She came all the way here
because of her niece.
- She came.
- She came to the shoot?
Was she on Running Man before?
- Not even once.
- No.
Please join our show.
(He invites her all of a sudden.)
- Why?
- What?
- Why...
- Instead of coming for her niece...
- Why would you say that?
- Don't put pressure on her.
- We'd like to have you here.
- Don't be like that.
We all had
a plastic sheet of her photo.
- Exactly. We all had it.
- Right.
- The Taekwondo girl.
Other than "Trigger,"
Jong Hyuk, is there any news...
that you want to tell us?
I'm shooting a new drama now.
(Joo Jong Hyuk and Park Min Young
are cast for "Confidence Man KR.")
- Jong Hyuk.
- It's crazy.
- I'm successful now.
- You're successful.
By the way...
- You are successful.
- I am.
I'm happy
that things are going well for him.
He has good energy.
- Right.
- Yes.
After I did the challenge...
After I danced here,
I stopped saying
that I was a good dancer.
- Right.
- It's a good thing.
- My dance looked strange.
- That's good.
Many people became successful
after joining our show.
By the way,
this is your first time here, right?
This is my first time
on a variety show.
- Really?
- I'm serious.
- I see.
- I heard that...
you and Ye Eun had
something in common.
- Really?
- What is it?
- You like to eat.
- I do.
Me too.
You like to eat?
(They both like to eat.)
- That's it?
- What?
All people are like that.
You think so?
- Then I'm like Ji Ye Eun.
- Me too.
- Who doesn't like to eat?
- There's more.
- You both like Girls' Generation.
- Girls' Generation?
- Yes.
"Into the New World"
is my favorite song.
(Ddochi proved her love
as a fan with her whole body.)
Try dancing to "Gee" then.
- Show us your dance.
- I can do this.
Gee, gee, gee
(What?)
- I will do it again.
- I knew it.
- You don't have to do it again.
- I don't?
- That was good.
- Ye Eun feels sorry.
- That was enough.
- I wasn't ready.
- What was this?
- It was just...
I've always dreamed
of appearing on Running Man.
- Really?
- Actually...
- it was a dream of mine.
- When did you start watching it?
- Since elementary school.
- Of course.
This being a dream of hers is
another thing they have in common.
- Yes, Ye Eun too.
- You're also a Running Man Kid.
- How old are you?
- I was born in 1999.
- My gosh.
Why? Is that too much of an age gap?
- Hey.
- No, of course not.
- You're five years apart.
- We're...
- We're peers.
- You're like her big sister.
- How are you peers?
- We were both born in the 90s.
- Ye Eun isn't a Running Man Kid.
- She's not.
- She's a Running Man Teen.
- Yes, a teen.
- No, a Running Man Kid.
- She's slightly older.
Today, we're joined
by Joo Jong Hyuk and Kim Si Eun...
who are like family
in terms of their looks.
- It's Family in Joy and Sorrow.
- In joy and sorrow?
First, I'll announce the families.
- The families?
- The three lookalikes.
Yu Jae Seok, Yang Se Chan,
and Joo Jong Hyuk are one team.
- Because of our mouths?
- Because they stick out.
- You look alike.
- The bucktoothed trio.
- You're our big brother.
- You three do look alike.
- I know.
Those who look like
they've been wronged.
- Haha.
- Me?
(Only he doesn't know
what he looks like.)
Why me?
- That's out of the blue.
- You have that quality.
- You do seem wronged.
- Exactly.
- You seem wronged.
- It's so unfair!
- His face...
- Haha, Ji Ye Eun,
and Kim Si Eun are a team.
- Okay.
- Lastly, we have those...
- who are like a real family.
- Jong Kook and us.
Jee Seok Jin, Kim Jong Kook,
- I'm sorry, but...
- and Song Ji Hyo...
- are a team.
- we're the leftovers.
- That's right.
- The leftovers.
- The leftovers. Got it.
- You're the real family.
- Got it.
- Sure.
- Hey. I forgot to mention this.
- Yes?
We went to Jong Kook's place
on the first day of the holidays.
- Right.
- For the first time in a while.
There's something odd...
- about his place.
- How so?
He's now living among trash.
("Unanswered Questions"
A man living among trash?)
- He's the trash man.
- Yes, that's true.
- That's not it.
- SOS. Jong Kook...
He needs our help.
- How can this be?
- His house should be filmed.
- We...
- We should visit.
There's this much trash
piled up on his balcony.
The pile comes up to here.
That's where he places
his recyclables.
Plastic to be exact.
Plastic is collected on his balcony.
- Vinegar gochujang in his fridge.
- Seriously.
And the room next
to the master bedroom?
It's like Dongmyo Market.
- No way.
- The clothes.
- Yes, I have a lot.
- Dongmyo?
- You'd be surprised.
- You'd be shocked.
- Right.
- He has piles of freebies...
- lying around at home.
- No way.
(The shocking sight
will be revealed next week.)
Hand them out
if you have no use for them.
I'll hand out what I can,
but know that my house
is in its current state...
because I'm getting ready
for a move.
My house isn't always that messy.
Where would you move...
when you haven't even been
house-hunting?
- You haven't found a place.
- I'll be moving.
I'm looking into it.
The show should air this.
You'll be shocked.
- Really?
- Don't you dare clean up.
- Right.
- My gosh.
People should see this house.
He wouldn't know
even if you stole anything.
Each family...
- will receive a debit card.
- That's right.
The family...
with the most money left
on the debit card...
will win the race
and receive a prize.
The family
with the least amount of money...
- will receive a penalty.
- We need to accumulate money.
We need to accumulate money.
To accumulate money,
you must withdraw money
from an opponent's bank account.
Each round,
you will point to a family...
and withdraw as much as you want.
You were notified...
of the starting balance
this morning.
- The scratchcard.
- Hello.
- Hi.
These are scratchcards.
The amount you win
will be your seed money.
Please only choose one.
(The amount they win
will be the team's seed money.)
- Here.
- Bring it when we film the opening.
You can't steal what others have.
Hey.
That should be
a warning for Se Chan.
As for me...
Why should it be me?
I'm not that kind of person.
I see that nothing's detectable.
How meticulous of you.
I give you that.
I'll go with this one.
You can't steal from others today.
I'm not Haha, you know.
(They all chose one scratchcard.)
- Got it.
- The one that speaks out to me.
- I choose this one.
- I shouldn't scratch it yet?
- The amount that you win...
- I have mine.
- from your scratchcards combined...
- Here's mine.
- will be the team's seed money.
- All three?
- It shouldn't be public knowledge.
- No.
- Can we tell our teammates?
- Okay.
- Of course.
- Your family should know.
- Yes, we should know.
- The family should know.
- Will...
- Make sure to keep it a secret.
Will we not be switching teammates
for this race?
- No.
- The way I see it...
- Okay, I'll do my best.
- Seriously.
- Don't betray us.
- Please don't.
- Is it random?
- See how much you won...
and tell only the staff the amount.
We should scratch that part
with a coin.
We should do it right now.
- Let's scratch ours.
- We can do it here.
- With our backs against the wall.
- Give me that.
- I hope...
- What do you mean?
I hope we win a lot.
- Mine's not bad.
- Hold on.
- Really?
- It's not bad. Here.
(Seok Jin wins 70 dollars.)
- Mine's not bad either.
- I won more.
(Ji Hyo wins 30 dollars.)
- Meanwhile, I...
- I see a five.
I didn't win a lot.
Why do I never get lucky
with these things?
- Let me see yours.
- A seven.
- My goodness.
- Nice, right?
- We're not off to a bad start.
- Here.
- Let's do it here.
- Come here.
Get behind me.
Let's scratch it here.
- Wait. They'll see it!
- What's wrong?
They could see what you won.
Look at the others.
What if they had their backs turned?
The camera should film
from behind us.
- How much is it?
- How much do you think I won?
- I...
- Hush!
Please lower your voice.
- No, you can't.
- We should see.
(Gasping)
- I wasn't done.
- Oh, right.
(Haha won a whopping 150 dollars.)
No way.
(He scratches
Si Eun's scratchcard for her.)
No way. I asked
what the highest prize was.
Together...
(Haha's family: Haha 150 dollars,)
(Si Eun 50 dollars,
Ye Eun 20 dollars)
(Thanks to the unusually lucky Haha,
they start with 220 dollars!)
- Amazing, right?
- No way.
Hold on.
- Shouldn't we trick the others?
- Maybe...
Maybe...
Let me see.
(What's the balance
for the Bucktooth Family?)
Okay, good.
- Not bad?
- How much?
Nice. That's not bad.
How much?
- How much?
- It's not bad.
(They seem to have won
an adequate amount.)
We're good.
I think we have
the second highest amount.
- At the very least.
- Yes, at the very least.
(The three brothers
seem to have won adequate amounts.)
- Okay.
(How much seed money
does Jae Seok's family have?)
Okay, nice.
- We have more than enough.
- Everyone won decent money.
I'm one to be lucky.
We got lucky too.
(Order of withdrawal)
I'm amazed by Si Eun.
- Exactly. She's not shy at all.
- Si Eun, have this.
- I should be doing that.
- No, have this one.
- No.
- What?
- What...
- Why not?
Shouldn't I be getting this for you?
- Not at all.
- Thank you.
- See how Ye Eun is seated?
- Si Eun,
aren't you starstruck?
Ye Eun, I'm older,
but I got you some water.
Thanks.
- That's how the MZ generation is.
- You appreciate it?
Thanks, Mr. Haha.
Mr. Haha?
- Thanks, Mr. Haha.
- Wailing.
Allow me to explain the first game.
- Sure.
- The first game...
- is Triggered Domino.
- What's that?
One from each team
will enter a room...
and set up dominoes
for three minutes per team.
After all three members are done,
the dominoes will be triggered.
You will be ranked according
to the number of dominoes...
- you were able to trigger.
- I'm good at that.
- Really?
- The team that triggered...
the least amount of dominoes...
will try to withdraw money first.
The winning team
will be given an additional benefit,
- so it's important to trigger...
- We need to win this.
- the most amount.
- Let's go.
First, Jong Hyuk, Jong Kook,
and Haha...
will enter the room.
- Jong Hyuk, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Do well.
- Don't be nervous.
- Am I to set the dominoes?
- Yes.
Those going in next...
will be Jae Seok, Seok Jin,
and Si Eun.
- The last ones to go in are...
- I'll try my best.
- are Se Chan, Ji Hyo, and Ye Eun.
- Okay.
- I never did this growing up.
- This is a first for me.
- This...
- Right.
- What's this?
- This looks difficult.
What now? Why are there balloons?
Please take your places.
What is all this? Already?
Where you stand
is just as important.
Our places? I'll go here.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- I'll go here.
- Play rock-paper-scissors.
- Sure.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
- I won.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
- I'll take this seat.
I'll sit here.
(They grab the seat
that seems the best.)
I don't know what's happening,
but I choose this one.
We need to set them
according to color.
Yes, the dominoes
are under the desk.
(The dominoes must be set
with colors that match the line.)
Hold on. Why...
What on earth is this?
- What's this?
- Why has this been inflated?
- Why?
- They're going to make us jump.
Don't you know I get scared easily?
- Don't you?
- Get ready.
(Who will set the most dominoes
in this suspicious room?)
- Goodness.
- Do a good job.
- No way.
- My gosh.
- Is that the setting?
- What on earth?
- They're small.
- I can see it all.
- Are they placing the dominoes?
- Like that?
- Really?
- That's Haha.
He's good at it.
(Focusing with his mouth open)
Hold on. This...
(Kaboom)
(The sound of a lightning strike
came out of nowhere.)
- They can't scare us like this.
- Oh, no.
- What was that?
- I'd knock it over.
Who's that in the middle?
- He's doomed.
- That's Haha.
- Why is that?
- Haha's bad at this.
It was to shock them...
- and knock down the pieces.
- That's Haha.
I can't stand things like that.
We need to place dominoes
that are matching colors.
Yes, match the color to the tape.
(Screaming)
That... My gosh.
I almost knocked mine over.
(Just then)
(The vase dropped.)
(The two scaredy-cats
were startled.)
(Meanwhile, one of them is unfazed
despite the commotion.)
(He's even having fun with it.)
- I hate those things.
- I can't stand things like that.
I hate it.
We've already won.
Ji Hyo, we won.
- Jong Kook's calm.
- We won this round.
(A cardboard box explodes.)
(Screaming!)
What on earth was that?
(They were knocked down.)
I knocked all of mine down.
But I didn't knock any over.
Jong Hyuk's were all knocked down.
- Was Jong Hyuk's knocked down?
- Jong Hyuk.
- Nice job.
- They were all knocked down.
Isn't Jong Kook doing all right?
(His mouth
has now been opened wider.)
But...
They were knocked over by the wind.
How can one...
(Screaming on his own)
(A serious scream)
- They fell down.
- No!
They all fell down.
This is really...
No, if these fall...
There's a breeze.
(Blocking the breeze)
I have a fear of balloons!
(The big balloon nearby
is still quiet.)
(It looks like it'll burst soon.)
Hang on. The chair...
- Darn it!
- Can I move my chair?
My muscles stiffened.
- That scaredy-cat.
- Hey.
I swear. My muscles hurt.
For real, Hyung In!
Hyo Im! I'm in pain!
Honestly. I'm not lying.
Keep going, Jong Hyuk!
Looking good!
Blue.
(Jong Hyuk and Jong Kook
are advancing smoothly.)
- This is driving me crazy.
- As long as Jong Kook does well.
- It's all on him.
- He's good at this stuff.
- Haha.
- Gosh.
- He's good at this.
- I have to use my left hand.
- He's pretty good.
- He's doing great.
Oh, my muscles.
Darn you!
(The balloons burst,
and Haha's dominoes collapsed.)
Hey! My sore muscles!
- Saliva...
- I lost...
(Trembling)
- It's too...
- We'll switch players now.
(Round 1 is over.)
- You can leave.
- This is so annoying.
- You got quite a lot standing.
- I did, didn't I?
I got...
- I can't turn my head!
- That's a lot.
(Current 1st place: Jong Hyuk)
- Good.
- Weren't you surprised?
If you have lots of testosterone,
you don't get startled.
- Are they done?
- Hang on.
- Haha spilled his.
- No way.
- Si Eun, you need to...
- I'll do my best.
Get them all standing up
with your precise touch.
I'm not precise.
- You are precise?
- I'm not.
- I'm nervous already.
- No, you're precise.
- It's a mess.
- Let's go.
What's a mess?
- What is?
- We can see from here.
- Okay.
- Oh, you saw us?
- Haha!
- Darn it.
- Don't be afraid.
- Seok Jin!
- It's fine.
- I'm nervous.
- Don't be afraid.
There are ghosts.
- For real?
- Yes.
Oh, no. I'm not good at...
I want to do well.
Darn it. It's scary.
- Where's my seat?
- Where do I go?
- Is this it?
- Jae Seok is on the left.
Si Eun is in the middle.
- The ones here...
- He did so well.
That's a lot.
Get ready.
- No, wait.
- Wait.
- You have to extend the line.
- Oh, really?
- Okay, got it.
- Slowly.
Get ready.
- How long do we have?
- Three minutes.
What did you mean by "go slow?"
(Falling down)
Hang on.
- That was close.
- Oh, dear.
- I'm really bad at this.
- My hands are shaking.
- Hang on.
- Oh, no. This is insane.
- She should take off the scrunchie.
- Why is she wearing that?
- She should take it off.
- That needs to go.
Oh, she's not my team. Keep it on.
- Hang on.
- Si Eun is honestly...
- My gosh.
- Oh, no.
- She keeps hitting them.
- They keep falling.
- Keep going.
- That has to come off.
- I'm really bad at this.
- My hands are shaking.
- Hang on.
- Oh, no. This is insane.
(Falling on his own)
I'm terrible at stuff like this.
(The cardboard boxes explode.)
(A piece of cardboard)
This thing...
- This flew into my stack!
- Wait!
(Knee jerk)
(Collapsed dominoes)
What is this?
- Is that ours?
- Jae Seok!
- What happened?
- They all...
- He spilled them all.
- Yes.
Take off the scrunchie.
He must be out of his mind.
I really...
I got them lined up so nicely.
Why is Seok Jin
so close to the table?
That's why they all fell down.
This is nonsense!
What on earth is this game?
- That hit my dominoes.
- Jong Hyuk chose that seat.
This thing fell on me.
A breeze keeps
making the dominoes fall.
- The center seat's the best.
- Darn it.
- This is bad.
- The cardboard fell on it.
What fell? What blew up? Shoot.
- I think something will appear.
- Oh, no.
(Screaming)
Don't do that.
It'll take forever
to put these back up.
What is this game?
- Please, come on.
- I don't believe this.
They all fell down.
Not just yours. Mine too.
All the ones
that Jong Kook put up...
(A sudden fire show)
I really can't...
What are you doing?
What is this, really?
Will you stop it?
Why are you doing this?
There's no way we won't jump...
(A vase falls!)
- Hey, he toppled them again.
- Darn it!
- Darn it! This is infuriating!
- This is driving me crazy.
Darn it!
(Seok Jin and Jae Seok's dominoes
fall in turn.)
Jae Seok!
I think we'll win.
I think she can just stop and wait.
Darn it! Hey, you!
This is driving me crazy.
(Just then)
- Wait.
- This...
(She nudged it
with her scrunchie again!)
Wait. Oh, no.
- I...
- Shoot!
- Si Eun!
- Scrunchie Si Eun!
Si Eun, take off the scrunchie!
Take off the scrunchie!
Get rid of it!
You set it up so it's impossible.
How are we to do this?
People watching TV
will wonder what's wrong with us.
Try it yourselves. It's no joke.
My gosh.
I'm sorry, Ye Eun.
I'm sorry, guys.
Si Eun!
Si Eun's done for.
She stopped.
She'd done so well.
- This is impossible.
- This is...
This just won't work.
(Stacking with his mouth open)
We still have Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is somewhat...
- You need someone calm.
- Ji Hyo...
Ji Hyo is calm.
(He's already thinking of
leaving it to Ji Hyo.)
- This right now...
- This game...
Darn it!
(Toppling over)
How is anyone to play this?
- Just stop already!
- How are we meant to play?
- Hang on.
- My gosh.
I'm so angry.
- Ye Eun.
- I didn't hit it this time.
- I'm sorry, Ye Eun.
- Darn it.
I'm not making any progress.
(A switch blew up!)
Darn it!
- My gosh.
- Seok Jin got a lot standing.
- Right?
- That's a lot.
- Older people like such games.
- Yes.
Like finding matching hwatu cards.
He's doing better than I thought.
Let me off just this once.
You have one minute left.
- Forget the one minute...
- Shoot.
One minute...
- I haven't stacked any new blocks.
- This is too...
- My gosh.
- Keep still.
(Seok Sam survived yet again.)
What on earth is he...
- What...
- Is this a horror game or what?
Oh, Seok Jin...
- They fell again.
- What's wrong with him?
Right? He did that to be funny.
- You can't do it all at once.
- Si Eun.
Seok Jin, honestly...
(The eldest is gaping
while attempting damage control.)
(Round 2 is over.)
- The next...
- This is impossible.
What the...
(Jae Seok did well
for a scaredy-cat.)
This game was impossible.
You have the most standing up.
My gosh.
Just five. I'm really sorry, guys.
- My gosh.
- I'm sorry, Ye Eun.
I feel so bad. What should I do?
- Si Eun.
- I'm sorry. But...
- Si Eun. This...
- I tried.
- What were you doing?
- Si Eun. This was in the way.
- Hey, your scrunchie...
- Is that product placement?
- Were you even thinking?
- No.
You should've taken off
your bag too!
(Fiery criticism)
It's my first time.
Even so,
there are things you can do!
It's my first time
on a variety show.
That's true.
- Seok Jin. Don't try to be funny.
- It's really no joke.
- I wasn't trying to be funny.
- Honestly.
I'm not kidding. See for yourselves.
- I already had my turn.
- Ji Hyo.
My round
was way more potent than yours.
- Take off your bag.
- Okay.
- Good luck.
Good luck, Ye Eun.
- I'll just protect what's standing.
- Ye Eun, in the middle.
If you keep one down in the middle,
- they might not all fall down.
- Okay.
- Ji Hyo!
- Aebong.
- You're our hope.
- Good luck, Aebong!
Good luck!
No way.
- I honestly can't do this.
- Can't I forfeit?
I'm scared.
(Low-frequency waves)
The team with the most dominoes
with the longest trail...
when they're toppled wins.
- This...
- We'll start the clock.
This is crazy.
- I'm scared. I can't do it.
- Wait.
- Did you press it? I'm scared.
- Honestly.
I'm scared.
Will you please
raise the level slowly? Please.
Once I get messed up...
If it goes up at once...
- I'm scared.
- I'm scared of this!
- It hurts.
(Thunder roars)
(Scared out of their wits)
That scared me!
My gosh. That was loud.
- My goodness!
- Why was it so loud? I'm scared.
I'm scared.
Me too.
- I'm scared.
- I'm really scared.
My ear hurts.
(Screaming)
My ear hurts!
My muscles turned stiff.
(Collapse)
(Se Chan in first place
suddenly becomes last.)
My muscles hurt!
I'm scared.
My gosh.
- Come on.
- I'm scared.
I have a feeling
the balloons will pop.
Ji Hyo is tenacious,
so she's good at this.
- Yes. She's...
- She's tough.
- Ye Eun, you...
- Theirs all fell over.
Who is it?
(Ji Hyo's dominoes fell too!)
I'm scared.
My gosh.
(Ye Eun goes up to
first place by chance.)
- I'm so scared.
- Seriously.
Darn it.
(Double Chin is totally focused.)
Please, Se Chan.
- Don't be nervous.
- My gosh.
(Screaming)
(The low frequency device
has been turned on.)
- My fingers won't move.
- Oh, gosh!
- My fingers...
- Oh, gosh.
(Giggling)
- Gosh, this is crazy.
- Oh, gosh.
- Look at this, Ji Hyo.
- Her hands are...
- Ye Eun.
- How do I do this?
- How can her hands go like that?
- This is...
- Ye Eun, what are you doing?
This is insane!
(The other players are becoming
healthier as well.)
This is so...
(Yelling)
Oh, goodness. What do I do?
- There's no way...
- I'm going to stay still now.
- I'm scared.
(About to cry)
I'm scared.
Gosh, please.
Hey, please don't do this...
(A fresh cream gun salute)
- Ye Bong. My goodness.
- I can't believe...
- You're totally in last place.
- I had to...
You're doing well, Se Chan!
Let's go!
- Se Chan is doing so well.
- What?
- He's doing really well.
- Ssaebssaeb.
- Yes.
- Ssaebssaeb is good at this stuff.
(Sticking the dominoes in place
with the fresh cream)
I can put cream on here.
(He races ahead on his own
with his innovative and dirty play.)
(Right then...)
No!
(All of Se Chan's dominoes
fall over.)
Okay!
Nice shot.
(Shocked)
My gosh!
No!
Because of you, my dominoes...
(Ye Eun's dominoes fell over
as well.)
I was just sitting still.
You knocked mine over
because you bumped my table.
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and do it over.
But this is...
- The dominoes are so fast.
- This is just too much.
Gosh, seriously. Se Chan!
Ye Bong, seriously!
But this is...
The dominoes are so fast.
- This is just too much.
- You have 30 seconds left.
Gosh, seriously. Se Chan!
Gosh, that scared me!
Darn it. What was that?
Gosh, I almost swore out loud.
I'm sorry.
(The final 10 seconds!)
My shoulder muscles are stiff.
- Still, Ji Hyo is doing the best.
- Yes, Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo is good, indeed.
Ye Eun, you should cheat
or something. Kick the other table.
My shoulder muscles are stiff.
(Time is up.)
All right. Now...
(Blowing a whistle)
The mission is over now.
- Let's have everyone come here.
- It's over.
- Look at her!
- We have zero!
Ji Hyo did a lot.
She's great.
- We won!
- I mean...
- Why did you team us up like this?
- We won.
- It's over.
- Are we in last place?
- Ye Eun.
- Hey, I said to take your bag off.
- Se Chan bumped my table.
- Ye Eun.
- That's why they fell over.
- You should've hit his table too.
- Then, shouldn't we say...
- Yes, good job.
- Ji Hyo had the longest dominoes.
So, this family is in 1st place,
you guys are in 2nd,
- and you're in last place.
- Okay!
- Second place isn't too bad.
- Ye Bong.
- Sorry, Ye Eun. It was a strategy.
- You should be sorry.
Your hair.
What about my hair?
- There's a lot of cream.
- You have cream in your hair.
Sure.
But from what I could see,
Ye Eun made a lot of mistakes.
- Ye Eun, you're a troublemaker.
- I know, right?
You don't even know anything.
No, you're just a knucklehead.
(No, you're just a knucklehead)
- Add "super" to it.
- Gosh, seriously?
Super knucklehead.
Super knuckle!
Not salute. Super knuckle!
(They start teasing the youngest
without fail.)
If you were a soldier,
you'd be in the Knucklehead Corps.
- Ye Eun,
- Super knuckle!
you have a new nickname
called Toadface.
Who said that?
- Haha called you Toadface.
- No.
Toadface, Super knuckle.
- Flatfish.
No.
That means you look like that too.
- Flatfish was really my nickname...
- Then you look like it too.
- in elementary school.
- Her nickname in elementary school!
- Flatfish was really my nickname...
- Then you look like it too.
- in elementary school.
- Her nickname in elementary school!
- Si Eun.
- For real?
- For real.
- Seriously?
- You were Flatfish in school?
- Really?
- Hey, haven't you made that face?
- Try it. What is it?
- Going like this.
- What is it?
I made many friends laugh
with that face.
- What is it?
- This face.
- Just going like this.
- Hey, Ye Eun.
Hey, Si Eun. How can your nickname
in elementary school...
- be Flatfish?
- But...
Ye Eun is Flatfish
even without making that face.
- I seriously can't put up with you.
- You can't put up with him?
Now is the time when you can
increase your bank balance...
with someone else's bank balance.
Choose the card of a family
of your choice,
and you can make a single
wire transfer for an amount you want.
Ye Eun's card.
The amount you transfer will
build up in your family's account.
If you try to transfer
an amount larger than the balance,
you will obviously not get
any money.
We'll only reveal which family
you tried to transfer money from.
- Oh, really?
- We won't tell you...
if the transfer went through
or how much you transferred.
There is a benefit...
- for the family in first place.
- What is it?
Regardless of whether you succeed
in transferring money or not,
you will get one more chance.
Gosh, that's so nice.
That's awesome.
- We should try a big amount first.
- A huge amount at first.
- Yes, let's go for a lot.
- Oh, that's nice.
According to the results
of the mission from earlier,
the 3rd place family will go 1st.
So, once that team's balance
goes up,
- Will we transfer from that amount?
- are we taking away from that?
- Yes.
- Oh, really?
- That's why first place is good.
- You're right.
- That's a huge advantage.
- Right, we could get more.
You just have to be in first place.
First place is the best for sure.
- If they don't do it...
- Second place doesn't matter.
Gosh, this is...
Do you guys have a lot of money?
- Yes.
- We have a lot.
- Earlier, we...
- They have a lot.
- Ye Eun caught us.
- Then we could...
- I caught a glimpse.
- Oh, really?
- They have a lot.
- They do?
(In the waiting room
before the mission began)
How much money did you draw?
I think it was 120 dollars?
(Laughing)
Am I not supposed to tell you?
This is awesome.
She asked me how much money I got,
and I just told her...
- that I drew 120 dollars.
- What?
I told her that I drew 120 dollars.
The shoot is over.
Today's shoot is ruined.
I'll still lose, though.
We have a lot.
- Earlier, we... Ye Eun caught us.
- They have a lot.
- I caught a glimpse.
- Oh, really?
- They have a lot.
- First off,
Haha's family in last place...
- can go first.
- It's us.
- Who should we choose?
- You know.
- Let's go for now.
- Let's decide there.
Super knuckle.
- Se Chan and Jae Seok. For sure.
- Se Chan and Jae Seok?
- Because of personal reasons?
- I can't forgive them.
- They called you Flatfish.
- I'm so mad.
- I really can't forgive them.
- Super knuckle.
I'm going to get revenge today.
Flatfish is mad, and that anchovy...
The anchovy and bucktooth...
- I mean, the Bucktooth Family.
- Yes, Bucktooth.
- You know, the Bucktooth Family.
- Yes, the Bucktooth Family.
- How much?
- We'll take 80 dollars.
- Yes, 80.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, 80 is correct.
- Yes, totally.
That team said
they drew 120 dollars.
Okay, let's go for it.
- Eighty.
(They trust Jong Hyuk's spoiler
and try to transfer 80 dollars.)
Hey, how much did you draw?
- I had 20 dollars.
- Wasn't it 20 dollars?
Can you move out of the way?
(Can you move out of the way?)
- You had 50 dollars, right?
- Yes.
Come on.
(She forces her way back in.)
Right now, Haha's team...
- chose Jae Seok's team.
- Oh, is that so?
- I knew they would do that.
- Yes.
Their money? Then theirs...
(Jae Seok's family)
(They try to transfer 80 dollars.)
Please!
(Will they succeed in transferring
80 dollars?)
Please.
- Are we using this money on food?
- Oh, are we?
(They check the result.)
- The transaction has been denied.
- What?
(They fail to transfer 80 dollars.)
- Can they really have so little?
- What?
That's more than their balance?
- No way. That can't be.
- Hang on.
The balance is too low.
Darn it, Flatfish.
- No way!
- Seriously?
No way.
That means they lied to me.
No, but Jong Hyuk told me...
- That was a lie!
- It was a lie?
- Why would you fall for that?
- My gosh. Seriously?
- I didn't know he'd lie right away.
- My goodness.
Why would you actually believe that?
I didn't think he'd lie
when he's here for the first time.
Gosh, Flatfish. You're so...
- Did Flatfish make another mistake?
- I didn't think you'd be like that.
I didn't think you'd be like that.
(Are you laughing?)
I didn't take you
for that kind of guy.
Super knuckle!
All right. We'll be back.
- Thank you.
- The second place team will go.
It was actually a lie.
Joo Jong Hyuk is an actor.
- They must've thought we had 120.
- I think they did.
- I'm sure they failed.
- They failed.
- He said he drew 120 dollars?
- Yes.
- Hey, you must not know...
- How could he have 120?
because you're a newbie
on Running Man.
- No, but I'm...
- The highest amount right now...
- I'm a manager...
- If he had 120...
- or assistant manager level. Yes.
- You?
- You're still on probation.
- You're not even an intern now.
- That's right.
- I'm not an assistant manager?
- No.
- You haven't even been here a year.
- You're a part-timer right now.
I went past the part-timer phase
after three months.
Senior Managing Directors,
isn't this too much?
- What's wrong, Director Ha?
- Is Haha a director now?
Hey, Assistant Manager Jee.
What do you think?
- What did you say?
- Isn't this infuriating?
Hey, Assistant Manager Jee.
What do you think?
- What did you say?
- Isn't this infuriating?
Am I an assistant manager?
(Assistant Manager Jee,
16 years on Running Man)
- I mean...
- Am I an assistant manager?
- Gosh, I'm so angry.
- Why are you angry?
- We have to take Haha's money.
- Yes.
But if Jong Kook's team
takes money from us twice,
our balance would become known.
Then, should we go with Ye Eun's?
- Ye Eun's team has a lot of money.
- Wait. This is a dilemma.
If we bring some over
from this team,
- the next team will take it all.
- They will. They will know.
- That's why 1st place is best.
- That's right.
They have two chances.
- Then...
- Should we just take ten dollars?
No, 30. Or 20 dollars.
- Let's try 30 dollars.
- Or 20 dollars.
- From Ye Eun's team?
- Let's take 30 from Ye Eun's.
- Okay.
- We should still check.
- Because... Yes.
- If we fail... That's right.
- If we fail, the balance is lower.
- Okay.
We'll transfer 30 dollars
from Ye Eun's account.
Thirty dollars.
(They try to transfer 30 dollars
from Haha's account.)
The transaction has been completed.
(They succeed
in transferring money.)
(They're excited
after taking 30 dollars.)
- How should we react?
- Hang on.
- Jae Seok, should we just...
- Act like we failed.
Then should we look dejected?
- Let's do some weird reactions.
- What are weird reactions?
- Just pretend like we failed.
- Darn it.
(They're putting on an act
after taking only 30 dollars.)
- What happened?
- Hey, Jae Seok is smiling.
(Their lips are twitching.)
- They withdrew money.
- Hey, Jae Seok...
Hey, Jae Seok's lips are twitching.
He's smiling.
- They succeeded.
Hey, Jong Hyuk smiled too.
- I think they succeeded.
- I know it.
It won't be easy.
I bet they withdrew money.
Team Jae Seok targeted Team Haha.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- They didn't target us?
- Now it's time...
for the team in first place.
We got this. Let's go.
Jong Kook, go after this team.
They have enough money.
- I second that.
- Absolutely.
- Remember I'm family, Seok Jin.
- We were the safe choice.
- Chungju Ji.
- Chungju Jee.
- Cross!
Remember I'm family, Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's family gets 2 attempts.
Which account will they go after?)
We should target
Team Jae Seok, right?
- Yes.
- They should be our target.
- We'll aim for 150 dollars first.
- Yes, 100 dollars.
- We'll withdraw 150 dollars.
- How about 170 dollars?
- We...
- Or maybe 180 dollars.
- Go for 170 or 180.
- No way.
We get two attempts.
- Let's go for a simple 150.
- That's already a lot.
Is 150 dollars a lot?
I got five dollars, remember?
That was way too low.
I bet the highest amount
was 100 dollars.
Let's go for 150, then.
- Jae Seok's family, 150 dollars?
- Yes, Jae Seok's.
We'll give it a shot.
Let's see.
- The transaction has been denied.
- It was maxed out.
- I said 150 dollars was too much.
- They don't even have 150?
- It's too much.
- Let's only aim for 100.
- You two got a decent amount.
- Is that so?
- Was it to throw us off?
- How about 80 dollars?
What do you say to 80 dollars?
- We need to succeed this time.
- I only got us five dollars.
- Let's try for 80.
- Let's try 80 dollars.
You never know.
Those three might've all
been unlucky with the scratchcards.
Still, they must've at least
taken 50 dollars.
They couldn't have started off
with only 30 dollars.
- Let's try for 80.
- But...
- Sure, 80.
- Let's try 80 dollars.
Yes, without a doubt.
(Haha's family tried taking
80 dollars from Jae Seok's family.)
(There wasn't enough money,
and they failed.)
(However, Jae Seok's family stole
30 dollars from Haha's family.)
(Will Jae Seok's family
now have more than 80 dollars?)
Let's listen to Ji Hyo.
(They try taking 80 dollars
from Jae Seok's family.)
- I think they'll have 80 dollars.
- Of course they do.
(Will they be able
to transfer 80 dollars?)
The transaction has been denied.
(Transaction was denied.)
- Don't they even have 80 dollars?
- Not even 80 dollars?
No way.
How can they not
even have 80 dollars?
We were lucky with our scratchcards.
There won't be any joy
from trying to take our money twice.
- They targeted you twice.
- Really?
Okay.
(Jae Seok's family happily revealed
their scratchcards.)
Okay.
- Not bad?
- Hold on.
Okay, not bad.
(Ten dollars)
(Jae Seok got 10 dollars.)
Mine isn't so bad.
(Five dollars)
Not bad.
(What about Jong Hyuk
who said he won 120 dollars?)
(Ten dollars)
(All he got was ten dollars.)
We have 25 dollars.
I think we have
the second highest amount.
(They thought they did all right
after only winning 25 dollars.)
Like that, the first round
of transfer has been completed.
Now that it's over,
I'll let each family know
their current balance.
How much do we have?
The last team to transfer money...
That's right. I'm sure of it.
Let's check.
We survived.
We're at a minus.
(Team Jae Seok: 55 dollars)
The balance can never go below zero.
- This isn't it.
- Oh, no.
It's not? Are you sure?
- But...
- I'll go and ask.
- Is this a minus sign?
- No.
- You startled us.
- That startled us.
- It's not possible.
- We thought we were in debt.
- Exactly.
- Why would you write it like that?
That's a weird way to write it.
(Seok Jin's family earned nothing
even after winning the game.)
Okay, fine.
(Haha's family lost 30 dollars,)
(but their balance
is still dominating.)
Okay. Gosh, this isn't easy.
- Okay.
- Right.
You must be hungry right around now.
Today's lunch
will blast away your stress.
It's the chicken feet combo.
- Nice!
- I love it!
Since Haha is promoting
a different brand of the same dish,
- he'll be given something else.
- Why?
- Which brand?
- Will we not get to eat as well?
- No, we'll get to eat.
- Got it.
(What a relief.)
- That looks delicious.
- That looks amazing!
(The chicken feet combo
Haha can't eat is delivered.)
It looks incredible.
Gosh, this is crazy. Unbelievable!
- I can't believe this.
- No way.
- I'm gushing over this.
- Have your fill.
- No way.
- Can you believe this?
- That looks good.
- I'll enjoy this.
- Is this the chicken neck?
- Yes, the neck.
- No way.
- My gosh.
We're given it separately.
(The big brother who works out
has his proteins first.)
Boneless chicken feet.
Ji Hyo must want soju with that.
- This calls for drinks.
- I'll have that.
(The younger sister who loves food
inhales the chicken feet in sauce.)
- It's incredible.
- It's so good.
The chicken feet in sauce
is to die for.
- It's really good.
- No way.
This is unbelievable.
- My gosh.
- The smokiness...
is out of this world.
My gosh.
It's so good.
- Seriously.
- I like how it's easy to debone.
- No way.
- It's not that spicy.
(Yummy)
(The flatfish sisters
are in the zone.)
That looks incredible.
These days, such meals...
- They serve incredible meals.
- Tell me about it.
Is this a boneless option?
(Frowning)
- Isn't it good?
- It is.
No way.
- I've been craving this.
- Right?
This is really good.
(The flavors add dimension
to the face.)
This is incredible.
- You know...
- It's so good.
- That's the best.
- It's spicy.
- They love to eat.
- I know.
- Look at them eat.
- We have chicken neck.
(With eyebrows pinched together,
they cram the food in their mouths.)
(And here's someone
who has been forgotten.)
(Is the food any good?)
What's he up to
with that packed lunch?
I can't believe him.
- It's so good.
- Ye Eun...
went crazy over food again.
Chicken feet are best
eaten as wraps.
I love this.
No way.
What's going on?
It's so good. Try this.
- No way.
- It's good.
Have it as a wrap. A wrap.
- What?
- As a wrap.
(She's suddenly filming
her own TV commercial.)
Is it good?
What are you doing? What was that?
I had a wrap, that's all.
- How is it?
- It's good.
- Did you have it as a wrap?
- Yes.
It's incredible.
- It's so good.
- Try this.
- It's sushi.
- Hey.
- Come here.
- It's so good.
Bring me your plate.
- It looks so good.
- Go ahead.
(It's handed to Si Eun,
the new food fighter.)
- Isn't it good?
- That's what I'm talking about!
Make a rice ball first and then...
You know the drill.
- That looks good.
- This is incredible.
(She made another one
and gifted it to herself.)
- Is it good?
- While you eat,
- I'll explain the next game.
- Sure.
The next game is called
Find the Doppelgangers.
At the store or marketplace,
you'll find an object...
that resembles a family member
on an opposing team.
The family who finds the object...
- that resembles someone the most...
- An object?
will be given a benefit.
Jae Seok's family
will look for objects...
that resemble someone
in Haha's family.
- We should go to a fish market.
- We only have to buy a flatfish.
- A flatfish and halibut.
- Yes, a halibut.
Haha's family
will look for objects...
that resemble someone
in Seok Jin's family.
And Seok Jin's family
will look for objects...
that resemble someone
in Jae Seok's family.
A webfoot octopus.
That family also...
An aged seokbakji
will do for that family.
Or maybe an aged pumpkin.
An aged pumpkin.
- It'll be easy for us.
- Go to the market and...
Find anything
with protruding mouths.
Once you're done with your meal,
you'll head to the store
and marketplace.
The task is too easy for us.
- It's too easy for us.
- I know.
Even Si Eun
called herself a flatfish.
By saying it too much,
it won't be much of a shock.
- Right.
- They'll get used to it.
- Rather than saying it...
- Flatfish.
It'd be fun to bring the flatfish
if we hadn't said it that much.
- We said it too much.
- It wouldn't be as fun anymore.
It would've been better
to target Seok Jin's family.
- We'd teach them a lesson.
- I have so many ideas...
- for Seok Jin.
- Exactly.
I could've gotten his lookalike
somewhere nearby.
- Right.
- Right?
- The last leaf maybe.
- Exactly.
- The last leaf?
- The last leaf.
- That's Seok Jin.
- He could be anything.
Do you know
the withered grass in winter?
- The withered grass in winter.
- Right.
- Melted snow.
- Yes, melted snow.
It can be anything.
- A sign that has fallen.
- A plain stone.
- We can pick up leaves too.
- Right.
- Seok Jin...
- I have so many ideas for him.
Dissing him
is a default mode for you.
(Haha's family arrives
at the supermarket.)
We need to win and then think.
- We must win.
- Of course.
It's about time we won.
- Please.
- Please. I want to win a game.
Same here.
- Let's win this round.
- Please.
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Mr. Haha!
- They're adorable.
They called you Mr. Haha.
Hi, guys.
They're adorable.
- Haha.
- How adorable.
- When I was in elementary school,
- Yes?
I saw you guys filming Running Man.
- Really?
- I saw you guys filming.
- It was a window just like this.
- And?
Jong Kook and...
- you were also there.
- Really?
- You were resting.
- I see.
- I went up to you...
- Goodness.
- and did this.
- And?
- You waved back so cheerfully.
- Really?
That's why it became my dream.
- Nice.
- It became my dream.
- I wanted to be on the show.
- I love that comment just now.
Si Eun!
And now I'm here on the show
I dreamed to be on.
- My dream came true.
- Did you see that?
She's sulking.
Ye Eun!
(Teasing her until the very end)
Did you see that?
That's the kind of thing
one should say.
I feel the same way.
- I feel the same way.
- You should make something up...
- to praise me.
- No, for real.
I saw you filming Running Man
in Sinchon.
- In Sinchon?
- Yes.
Right. I remember that giant.
The little giant.
(They enter the supermarket
where they can find everything.)
I already found Seok Jin's item.
Jong Kook.
The snow crab looks
kind of like Jong Kook.
- Oh, you're right.
- Hang on.
(Will they be able to find
the right items?)
Oh, don't you think it'd be funny
to choose this for Jong Kook?
I thought of you when I saw this.
You don't have any sunglasses
that fit you.
Will you try this on once?
I think this will fit you.
- Will you try it on?
- No, but Jong Kook... This is...
Try it on here and come on out.
- You too.
- Oh, me?
Where is yours? You two are twins.
Is this right? Darn it.
Let me see. That fits now, right?
Hey! See? These are sunglasses.
She is...
Gosh, you should buy this one.
In 1, 2, 3.
Look. She can't wear any sunglasses
because of her nose.
But this fits.
Si Eun, you can't find ones
that fit either, right?
Try this on.
For real.
- Gosh, seriously?
- This fits so well on all of us.
Let me see, Si Eun.
Am I pretty?
Does it look okay?
- Si Eun, that's yours.
- Hey, you guys should each...
- That was made for you.
- Should we wear these as we go in?
- What do you say? I'll buy them.
- Ye Eun.
- No.
- No!
- No. We have to save money.
- It's only 1.5 dollars.
- Oh, it's 12 dollars.
- Save money.
- I'll buy them for you.
- No!
- They were perfect.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- Gosh, seriously.
We don't wear things like that.
(By the way,
when will they do the mission?)
- Right. Is there something good?
- Shall we go?
Is there something
that will make everyone laugh?
Traditional markets have
their own vibe.
Markets are fun.
Oh, my. Hello.
(Jae Seok's family's
lookalike assignment)
You know, Jae Seok, for Ye Eun...
Hey, this is Seok Jin.
- For sure... Dried radish greens.
- Dried radish greens.
- I want to take a bit of that.
- Just a bit...
Excuse me, ma'am.
We just need one strand of this.
Is this for sale?
You can just take a strand.
- Oh, is that okay?
- Yes.
- Thank you, ma'am. One is enough.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Goodness, Seok Jin.
You must be tired.
- Don't drop him.
- Oh, this is so...
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Be careful with this.
- We should be very careful.
- It's too dry. It's crumbling.
- Yes.
Goodness,
there are bunches of Seok Jin here.
- Oh, Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin...
It's a colony of Seok Jins.
- Shouldn't we bow to him?
- Seok Jin...
Goodness, Seok Jin.
- Why are we bowing?
(The polite younger brothers bow to
their big brother as they meet him.)
- Goodness, Seok Jin.
- Brother.
We're here, brother.
Goodness, brother.
(Laughing)
It's a colony of Seok Jins.
Seok Jin is all over the place.
Hey, this is...
If you spot something
that looks similar,
- say something.
- Okay.
(They leave Seok Sam behind for now
and start their real mission.)
(Exclaiming)
These aren't all that...
Gosh, these look tasty.
- Hey, we should get chapsal donuts.
- Chapsal donuts?
Should we buy
a few black rice donuts?
- Gosh, ma'am...
- You're so handsome!
- Oh, my.
- Gosh, thank you.
Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Have a good day.
- Hello.
- Take that off.
Gosh, how should we eat these?
(This looks good, doesn't it?)
It's good.
Oh, it's delicious.
- So, Ji Ye Eun...
- It's tasty.
How about bean sprouts for Ye Eun?
Jae Seok.
- How about bean sprouts for Ye Eun?
- Bean sprouts.
The seaweed stems look good too.
(Has no strength and is tall)
There are radishes too.
- Ye Eun does look like a radish.
- Yes, that's right.
- Anything long looks like her.
- If it's long, it's Ji Ye Eun.
- Chinese yam.
- Chinese yam?
- It hurts.
(It's grubby and tall.)
- But Ye Eun...
- It hurts!
One that's long.
(They can't find the right one
among many giants.)
Isn't this Ji Ye Eun?
- Jae Seok, that one.
- This is Ji Ye Eun!
- Isn't this Ye Eun? It is, right?
- It is Ye Eun.
- Should we draw a face on here?
- Yes.
- We could do that.
- This is Ji Ye Eun.
How much is this?
Should we buy a slightly smaller one
for Si Eun?
- A spoon?
- How about this one, Jae Seok?
- This one.
- This one is for Si Eun.
- Yes, these two.
- We'll buy two for now.
- How much is it?
We bought them too easily.
- We should look around more.
- Right.
(Jae Seok's family's
lookalike assignment)
- Baby octopus.
- Baby octopus?
- Who is it?
- Haha.
(They spot Haha
in the stall next door.)
- Baby octopus. This is so cute.
- It's Haha.
- This is so cute.
- Let's buy a baby octopus for Haha.
- All right. Let's go.
- Let's take a look.
There will be many items
that look like those guys.
Our assignment isn't that hard.
It's easy.
They look unique, to begin with.
- They look like mugwort rice cakes.
- They do.
- They're ugly too.
- Mugwort rice cakes? Good idea.
- Oh, fish.
- There's fish?
- Fish?
- You're right.
- Hello.
- Hey, over here.
- Guys, eureka!
- My goodness.
- Hey, this one.
- We found all of them here.
- Hello.
- They have squid too.
- Squid.
- So...
Oh, the mouth...
Ones with protruding mouths.
There has to be one that makes us
burst into laughter, right?
(They search for the ugliest one
among them.)
One that'll be a big laugh.
(Right then)
Jae Seok!
- This one?
- Yes, right.
- This is a monkfish.
- Is it a monkfish?
This is Jae Seok.
- This is the mouth, right?
- But monkfish is...
That's right.
This one looks like Yu Jae Seok.
- Right?
- For real, right?
- Over here! It's Jae Seok!
- It looks like him.
- Could you hold this up once, sir?
- It does look like him.
- What's this?
- This is Jae Seok.
- The face.
- The mouth.
- Gosh, it looks like him.
- Gosh, this is Jae Seok.
- Is this Jae Seok?
- My gosh.
- All sorts of fish...
- You're right.
- look like Jae Seok.
- Yes, right.
- Let's buy one of these too.
- Buy it.
It smells like herbal medicine.
Here it is. Seok Jin.
Seok Jin.
(Dad's underpants)
I don't know why,
but this pair looks like Seok Jin.
- Doesn't it look like Seok Jin?
- I detest it so much.
- You detest it, right?
- I do.
It's Seok Jin.
- Hang on.
- What about this one? Boxers.
But this pair kind of looks
like a gentleman.
Look at this.
Jee Seok Jin.
But seriously, look.
- But...
- Seok Jin.
(Boxer briefs)
(Reminded by a pair of underpants)
It looks just like Seok Jin.
It's so dejected, right?
(How our dads look from the back)
This is it.
- Oh, and...
- What is it?
- Haha.
- What are you looking at?
Do you keep seeing Seok Jin?
This is the best.
(As they think of our dads...)
- This one is...
- Seok Jin!
- How about this one?
- Hey, should we go there?
- Oh, that sounds good!
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Nice.
Hey, we get along really well.
- We get along really well.
- We get along.
- We're just shopping. We get along.
- We get along really well.
- We picked them out quickly.
- I know.
Hey, now that I think of it,
both your names end in Eun.
- The Eun Sisters.
You look the same, but you have
a high nose bridge. Yours is low.
Hey,
why are you saying it like that?
Hey, no.
I just said it like it is. Agreed?
If that's the case...
Hey, you. Follow me outside.
If that's the case,
I guess my nose is a bit...
- You know,
- Follow me outside.
I said she looked like
a baby bulldog. And she said...
(A bulldog?)
But you really look like it.
(On their way back from shopping)
But if I had my face
and a high nose bridge,
- it wouldn't look...
- Bulldogs are cute.
Hey, why? Bulldogs are cute.
I think
bulldogs are the cutest dogs.
I'm a Pomeranian.
- What? You?
- I'm a Pomeranian.
Look at this.
You look exactly like it.
- Look at this.
- They do look alike.
They look the same!
- They're the same, right?
- So cute.
- Jong Seo, look.
- I don't look like it!
They look the same, right?
I told you.
No, I'm a Pomeranian!
I'm a Pomeranian!
You really look alike.
You think so too, right?
That means you look like this too.
- No, I'm a Bichon Fris.
- You are...
- Hey, you are...
- I'm a Bichon Fris.
- You look like a Bichon Fris.
- Look at this.
- You look alike.
- I do too.
You don't have this nose.
- No, but...
- I said I was a Pomeranian!
A Pomeranian!
(While the Flatfish Eun Sisters are
having a dogged fight...)
This is so funny.
A Pomeranian!
For real, look it up once.
Okay!
- Hey, Ji Ye Eun.
- Yes?
- Hey.
- Sorry, but the market...
- was full of you.
- Ye Eun.
- There were so many of you.
- You seem so familiar.
Hey, we went to the supermarket,
and there were so many lookalikes.
There were
so many Yu Jae Seok lookalikes.
We greeted you several times.
- Jae Seok, why are you everywhere?
- Right.
- Jae Seok.
- We said hi...
to Jae Seok and Se Chan
several times.
On our way here,
we bowed to Seok Jin for the new year.
- We bowed to you.
- For real.
(He gets knocked out
in the initial mind games.)
- Sorry.
- Don't lie. Darn it.
- There was a colony of Seok Jins.
- It's true.
For real.
(Who brought
the most shocking lookalike?)
You each bought items that
resembled the other team members.
You will now present your items
and the reason for buying them.
- Haha's family will go first.
- Okay.
- Shall we take a look?
- Start.
- You looked for Seok Jin's family?
- That's right.
Oh, us?
Si Eun said she was confident.
- So, first of all,
- Ye Eun, you can show it.
we have Ji Hyo's item.
You found one for Ji Hyo?
- Ji Hyo must've been hard to find.
- Yes.
As soon as Ye Eun and Si Eun
saw this,
they said,
- "This is insane. Ji Hyo!" Me too.
- You found one for Ji Hyo?
- I thought so too.
- Ji Hyo.
We chose this
because Ji Hyo looks so milky.
- She's cute too.
- What is that? Isn't it milk?
- Is it milk?
- It's milk.
You're so snowy white and clear.
- And soft. Really.
- You're being nice...
So...
- It's a carton of soju!
- A carton of soju.
(A carton of soju)
(Like milk... No, like soju,)
(she's awfully clear.)
- Hey, that's Ji Hyo!
- A carton of soju.
- Hey.
- Oh, that's what you're going for.
- This kind of vibe.
- It's this kind of vibe.
I was going to pick a rock
off the street...
- for Ji Hyo.
- A pretty big rock.
- Come on. This is weak.
- Okay.
- Next, it's Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook.
- We had so many for Jong Kook.
- Is it me?
- Yes, there were so many.
- Is it kkakdugi?
- Just a protein shake.
- Protein.
This caught our eyes
when we turned the corner.
- Jong Kook is very firm.
- That's right.
- He's very firm.
- Firm.
- He also carries the spirit...
- Yes.
and strength of Korea.
- Seriously.
- What is it?
- "It's Kim Jong Kook!"
- A soy sauce dish.
(A soy sauce dish)
As soon as we saw it...
(It's well-known that his heart is
as solid as a soy sauce dish.)
Are you calling him small-minded?
(He punished Kwang Soo right away.)
It would've been nice
had you come from the start.
(When he's sullen,)
(he doesn't forgive easily.)
I guess...
there's an intangible resemblance.
His heart is
as big as a soy sauce dish.
- It isn't big.
- That's right.
So that's the vibe. How nice.
- He has a lot of anger.
- All right. He has a point.
- Well done.
- All right.
To be honest...
- You know, it was weak.
- Let's see the main event.
As for Seok Jin...
Seok Jin has so many lookalikes.
- The entire Korea is Seok Jin.
- There are so many lookalikes.
- So far, it was sentimental.
- That's right.
- The resemblance was sentimental.
- Come on.
- It wasn't physical.
- It should be physical.
The things we showed so far
were one-dimensional...
and abstract.
- We chose 1 each.
- Are there 3?
- They're special.
- They come together.
- They're a set.
- There are too many.
- Hey.
You seem very excited.
- Chungju Ji, you seem very excited.
- Ye Eun is happy.
- They're a set.
- She's happy.
- They're abstract, okay?
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
Seok Jin.
Look how weak it is.
Do you see how limp it is?
Seok Jin, he called it weak.
- Seok Jin.
- Doesn't it resemble Seok Jin?
- You know...
- Seok Jin.
Let's bring them together.
Seok Jin.
- Seok Jin.
- All of them are sentimental.
- Seriously.
- It flaps around.
- The resemblance isn't physical.
- Hey.
- Weak.
- Let's show the weakest item.
Let's begin.
- Grandpa.
- She thought of her grandpa...
- No.
and cried.
She saw this and cried
while saying, "Grandpa."
- Grandpa.
- Give him a hug.
- I hope Seok Jin wears them.
- For goodness' sake.
- They're limp.
- Please wear them.
I wear Calvin Klein.
Please put it on.
Calvin Klein.
- I wear Calvin Klein and Armani.
- The cap is cute.
- Isn't the cap cute?
- It's cute.
- Please put it on.
- For goodness' sake. All right.
(It suits him well!)
(He's like the father
who moved to the countryside.)
- It's perfect.
- It's nice.
Hey, why does it suit him well?
- Si Eun seems to be excited.
- Give him the items.
- We just met.
- Si Eun likes grandpas.
- My goodness. Okay.
- Their presentation is over.
- Up next is Seok Jin's family.
- Seok Jin's family.
- It's us.
- We can't wait.
- We...
- I'm really excited.
- The items that resemble us?
- So many items resembled Jae Seok.
As for us,
we chose the items
that bore physical resemblance.
- This one...
- Are you sure?
This one fell over.
For goodness' sake.
- A black plastic bag?
- This one fell over.
Hold on.
Why are all of our items
in a black plastic bag?
Haha, why are all of our items
- Hey.
- It's annoying.
- You know...
- Now, I can smell the sea.
- He put on gloves.
- Firstly...
He put on gloves.
How annoying.
Get me a pair of gloves.
- I have it.
- Do you have them?
Is it a new pair of gloves?
- Come on.
- We can't use bare hands.
- Firstly,
- Firstly...
this is a preview.
- You need to heat things up.
- Okay.
- This is Jong Hyuk.
- Jong Hyuk.
- It was hard to find Jong Hyuk.
- It was hard.
- It was so hard to find Jong Hyuk.
- We did find something.
- Is it a frog?
- Hey.
In the end, we found something
that looked exactly like Jong Hyuk.
The skin tone...
- and overall vibe...
- The skin tone is the same.
- What is it?
- It was hard.
(What's the item?)
It was hard.
This is Jong Hyuk.
It has eyes.
- Look. It has eyes.
- It's a bit...
This is Jong Hyuk.
It has eyes.
- Isn't it a dried persimmon?
- Look. It has eyes.
- It's a chapsal donut.
- We had it earlier.
- What is it?
- It's a dried persimmon.
- We had it earlier.
- Look.
- The resemblance is unclear.
No, it isn't.
Our items were better.
- Look.
- That's...
Show us an item
with a strong resemblance.
Hold on.
- They put it in a shopping bag.
- Now...
- It's raw.
- We'll start with Se Chan.
- Okay.
(The first main dish, Se Chan)
Hey. What's that?
- Is it a monkfish?
- Are you excited?
We knew it was Se Chan
the moment we saw it.
- I talked to it.
- Okay.
(Which fish looks like Se Chan
in particular?)
It's Yang Se Chan.
- Se Chan.
(My goodness)
(It has big fish eyes
and a protruding mouth.)
- What?
- I see the resemblance.
- I talked to it.
- Look.
I knew it was Se Chan
as soon as I saw it.
- It's opening its mouth.
- It resembles Se Chan.
- Yang Se Chan.
- My goodness.
- Its face resembles his so much.
- It looks scary.
- Now comes Jae Seok.
- Yes.
So many items resembled Jae Seok.
- So many items resembled Jae Seok.
- What is it?
- So we picked a special kind.
- Okay.
After much consideration,
we agreed to go with this item.
- We said hello to it.
- We did that.
- It's Jae Seok.
- You know,
- even the seller said hello to it.
- Yes.
When we asked for a fish
that resembled Jae Seok,
- he recommended it.
- That's right.
(Even the seller confuses it
with Jae Seok at times!)
It's an atka mackerel.
Take a look.
It's perfect.
- It's perfect.
- It looks exactly like Jae Seok.
It looks exactly like Jae Seok.
- It's totally Jae Seok.
- Seriously.
My goodness.
- Both of them are fishes.
- It resembles you.
- Why...
- They look the same.
- I mean...
Look. They look the same.
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you laughing?
- Why is its mouth twisted?
- What's wrong with its mouth?
- Seriously.
- The front and side profiles...
- Its mouth is twisted.
- Its mouth...
It looks exactly like Jae Seok.
- Why are they in a plastic bag?
- I mean...
Why are our items in a plastic bag?
- It's like...
- You know,
the resemblance used to be greater.
But it melted a bit.
It's so gross.
- The last one is Jae Seok's family.
- We put a lot of effort into it.
- We have many items.
- Yes.
- We...
- We'll show some extras.
- Okay.
- We'll start with that team.
- Start with the extras.
- All right.
- Seok Jin.
- Me?
Did you get one for me?
It's this, a jujube.
- Why is it me?
- A jujube.
- It's a wrinkly, dried jujube.
- Next.
- And here's the last leaf.
- The last leaf.
(The last leaf!)
- It's sentimental. Okay.
- They took...
the sentimental route.
- As for this...
- This friend...
This friend has been left behind
for many years.
Had it been left there
a bit longer...
It's dried radish green.
(He saved dried radish green.)
- Dried radish green.
- This is driving me crazy.
- Seok Jin,
ours is better.
(Seok Jin, ours is better.)
- Seok Jin.
- There were...
many other items.
- Now,
- Shall we begin in earnest?
- let's begin in earnest.
- Okay.
- Start with Haha.
- As for Haha...
- Haha.
- I can't wait.
(They start with Haha.)
- As for Haha...
- What is it?
- Let's see it.
- I see that it's small.
It's something small.
A baby octopus.
- A baby octopus.
It looks like him, right?
For goodness' sake.
(The one that brings shame
to the fish market)
Is it a baby octopus?
- Is it a baby octopus?
- A baby octopus.
- Haha!
- That's incredible.
My goodness, there's Haha.
Don't grab my head!
It's annoying. I hate it...
- when people touch my head.
- It's a baby octopus.
- A baby octopus.
- It's Haha.
- Yes.
(They're off to a good start
with a baby octopus.)
It looks exactly like Haha.
- A baby octopus is so cute.
- I know. It's cute.
- How nice.
- As for Si Eun and Ye Eun...
- We'll reveal them together.
- We made them together.
- They're similar.
- Si Eun and Ye Eun.
- Si Eun has a high nose bridge.
- So...
the big one is Ye Eun
and the small one is Si Eun.
(Si Eun, Ye Eun)
(Two spoons with different heights)
- You see the resemblance, right?
- Hey.
- Jae Seok, hold them up.
- They look the same.
- I see the resemblance.
- Seriously.
- They made them with so much care.
We added details to their hair.
- Did you make them?
- Is it dried laver?
- It's a plastic bag.
- A plastic bag.
- Yes.
- You made them.
- It's Ye Eun.
The very last one is...
- the highlight.
- It's the highlight.
- Is there another one?
- The highlight?
- Yes.
We found Ye Eun by chance.
(Is there a hidden item
that resembles Ye Eun?)
- As for this one,
- It's so big.
I personally think
it'll go down in history.
- Really? It's big.
- I bet you never imagined it.
- I can't even imagine it.
- Shall I cover it?
Is it a stand? What is it?
I bet you never imagined it.
- I can't even imagine it.
- I can't wait.
Ye Eun!
(Ye Eun!)
- Ye Eun!
- It's Ye Eun.
- Can't you see the resemblance?
- There's a mouth.
- Seriously.
- Ye Eun!
- It looks the same.
I was so startled.
- At the supermarket...
- We bought it.
- Jae Seok.
- It has Jae Seok's face.
- It has your face.
- Isn't it Jae Seok?
- It's Jae Seok.
- It's Ye Eun.
- Call Ye Eun.
- Jae Seok.
- Ye Eun.
- It's...
- Good.
- Seriously.
- It's Ye Eun.
Ye Eun.
This is...
It resembles her.
- Yes.
- It's Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun, take it home.
How does it look like that?
- The presentations are over.
- Yes.
Cameraman Kang Chan Hee...
will rank the teams in the order...
- of the items' resemblance.
- Okay.
- It has to be us.
- No.
- Please announce the third place.
It has to be us.
We put a lot of effort
into the game.
- The last place?
- I bet we didn't place last.
- Our items were witty.
- The third place is...
- Okay.
The third place?
Haha's family.
- Why?
- Only that one item made sense.
- No way.
- Us?
- We did well.
- It's hard to find such an item.
- That's right.
Good.
- We're the best.
- Good.
It was hard to pick the winner.
(The 1st and 2nd places
were neck-and-neck.)
Shall I announce the first place?
- The 1st place.
Okay.
I could totally see the resemblance.
- Okay.
- You could see it.
- I could totally see it.
- Okay.
I'll pick Jae Seok's family.
(Bucktooth Family placed 1st.)
- Yes.
- All right.
- Okay. You did well.
- It can't be helped.
- We admit defeat.
- This one looks like her.
- You can't beat it.
- This too.
This one looks exactly like her too.
You can't beat it.
- The 1st, 2nd, and 3rd places.
- You can't beat it.
Just like the last time,
- the withdrawals will take place.
- We can do well.
Haha's family will go 1st
since they placed 3rd.
- Okay.
Here's what I think.
(Haha's family
is currently in 1st place.)
We need to think hard.
- Okay.
- What is there to think about?
(Will they be able
to stay in 1st place?)
Listen.
- Let's say we withdraw a lot.
- Okay.
- Right?
- Yes.
Seok Jin's family has some money.
- We know that.
- Yes.
(Seok Jin's family had 2 chances
during the 1st withdrawal.)
(They predict that Seok Jin's family
has become rich.)
Let's take 100 dollars
from Seok Jin's family.
Okay.
- Then Jae Seok will pick us.
- Yes.
If we take a lot of money
from the rich team,
- we'll lose more.
- That's right.
If we chose Jae Seok's family...
- and withdraw 20 to 30 dollars...
- Okay.
We can take second place
if we get rid of our greed.
Then it'll be our strategy
to avoid placing last.
Since we're playing a game anyway,
we should aim to win.
(Number 95 wants to win
unlike how it was in "Squid Game.")
- It's okay. We can't...
- It's okay.
We won't win.
I don't think that we'll win.
But Si Eun has a point.
It'll be impossible to win.
I think you're right, to be honest.
- No.
- It'll be impossible to win.
I'm here to win.
- Do it next time.
- Visit the show again.
- You met the wrong team.
You met the wrong team.
- In that case...
- Gosh.
(They won't place 1st today.)
- We should pick Jae Seok's family.
- Okay.
- Let's avoid placing last.
We'll pick Jae Seok's family.
(They attempt to withdraw money
from Jae Seok's family.)
- Thirty dollars?
- Forty dollars.
- They won't have that much.
- We'll go with 30 dollars.
- Thirty dollars.
- They'll have that much, right?
(They attempt to withdraw 30 dollars
Jae Seok's family took.)
Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- All right!
(They make a big fuss
to keep the result hidden.)
Go!
It's necessary to make noise.
The device makes a sound
when the paper comes out.
(Working hard)
Please!
The transaction has been completed.
(The transaction is a success.)
(Oh, yes!)
(They succeeded in taking back
the stolen money!)
(They school their faces.)
I can't believe it.
(They begin acting
to avoid being the target.)
Are they that poor?
(Baiting)
"Are they that poor?"
- No. We need to see.
- Well...
- Let's see Ye Eun's face.
- Haha's family...
targeted Jae Seok's family.
- They took money.
- Okay.
The second place,
Seok Jin's family will go.
- Let's see Ye Eun's face.
- Okay. Seok Jin.
Ye Eun, are you in a good mood
or a bad mood?
I'm in a bad mood.
Let me see if you look sad.
(Smiling)
You're in a good mood.
- No, I'm not.
- You're trying to hide it.
- I'm in a bad mood.
- Seriously.
That's funny.
Whether or not it was a success...
- Haha's family. Fifty dollars?
- Haha's family.
(They used their 2 chances
on Jae Seok's family earlier.)
(They failed both times.)
(Seok Jin's family found out that
Jae Seok's family had no money.)
- Let's do it even if we fail.
- Seventy dollars.
- Okay.
- No. One hundred dollars.
- We can't do that.
- Don't do that.
- What's wrong with you?
- We can't do that.
- How about 70 dollars?
- Take it easy.
- Okay?
- Okay. It's simple.
No. That won't change anything.
What's up with you?
- One hundred dollars.
- Suddenly...
- One hundred dollars? Really?
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Haha's family. One hundred.
- Haha's family.
(If they steal 100 dollars,
they'll take 1st place.)
- Are you confident?
- It'll get denied.
- It's your decision.
- Really? Will it get denied?
All right then.
- Seventy.
- Seventy?
Okay. Let's play it safe.
Seok Jin's family...
chose to target Haha's family.
(Haha's family:
220 dollars in total)
(Haha's family will lose
a 3rd of the money.)
They couldn't have picked
a big amount.
I bet Haha's family succeeded in it.
- Okay.
- They succeeded in it.
We need to check out
Jae Seok's family's results as well.
That's right.
This makes me think.
(The transaction is a success.)
(Satisfied)
- All right.
- Good.
- We should've gone with 100.
Let's pick one team at a time.
(Jae Seok's family has 2 chances.)
- One team at a time.
- Yes.
We have two chances, right?
Let's bring 40 dollars
from Haha's family.
How about 30 dollars?
Shall we go with 30 dollars?
- Thirty dollars?
- Okay.
- Seok Jin's family too.
- For now...
Thirty dollars
from Seok Jin's family?
- Shall we bring more at once?
- Shall we do it?
They might have 100 dollars.
- Seok Jin's family...
- Okay.
didn't take our money
to keep their amount a secret.
I see.
They have a lot of money.
Let's be daring.
In that case...
- Shall we go with 90 dollars?
- Did you say 90 dollars?
- Okay.
- Seok Jin's family.
Ninety dollars.
(Bucktooth Family
finally stopped being small-minded!)
(Seok Jin's family:
90 dollars taken)
(The transaction is a success.)
- I guess our total was too small.
- I guess it was the smallest.
- I guess it was too small.
- I guess we started off too small.
- Haha's family had a good reaction.
- Yes.
Shall we get more money from them?
Haha's family.
One more time.
(How much will they withdraw
from Haha's family?)
One hundred dollars.
(Haha's family:
150 dollars in total)
If this works,
that means both teams had
a lot of money.
(Haha's family: 100 dollars taken)
(The second transaction is
a success.)
(They finally learned
that only they were poor!)
(Jae Seok's family:
215 dollars in total)
I told you not to do that.
(The first place and last place
are switched.)
You're grinning so widely.
- I'm annoyed.
- I mean...
(Haha's family plummeted
to the bottom from the 1st place.)
We should pick them next time.
- They...
- They're the richest.
- They must be happy.
Their facial expressions
show happiness.
- No. It was denied.
- Just you wait.
You'll get the current total.
(They check the current total
after the 2nd withdrawal.)
- Let's check it.
- Let's see it.
What's our total?
(Their total has multiplied by 10.)
They had a lot of money.
Let's see.
(Seok Jin's family's total
hasn't changed much.)
(Seok Jin's family:
85 dollars in total)
No way.
What? I can't see it.
For goodness' sake.
(Haha's family became poor.)
(Which family will laugh
in the end?)
They took a lot of money.
Is there another game?
Please prepare the last mission.
I'll explain the last mission.
The last mission is
the No Communication Quiz.
You'll listen to a question
and write down your answer.
All three answers must be identical
for it to be a success.
- Is that so?
- It's impossible.
- I see. Okay.
- I see.
The family with the highest number
of successes will get the benefit.
If it's a tie,
the family with the higher number
of two identical answers...
will win.
Jae Seok's family will go first.
All answers must be identical.
So we need to answer correctly.
Among Yu Jae Seok, Yang Se Chan,
and Joo Jong Hyuk,
write down the name of the person
whose mouth protrudes the most.
- It's hard.
- My goodness.
(Among Yu Jae Seok, Yang Se Chan,
and Joo Jong Hyuk,)
(write down the name of the person
whose mouth protrudes the most.)
(He writes his answer
without hesitation.)
The answers must be identical.
- Hold on.
- It isn't easy.
- Make sure they don't cheat.
- Okay.
So we get such questions.
- Let's judge objectively.
- We can't predict the result.
It's hard.
- So we get such questions.
- It's hard.
- Seriously, it's...
- What's your answer?
- Jae Seok.
- Really?
- How about you?
- Se Chan.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Even among the onlookers,
the opinions are divided.)
(Will it be the protruded mouth
with no chin...)
(or the protruded mouth
that's twisted?)
I'm sure they'll write down the name
of the ugliest person.
- The ugliest person.
- Just look at the vibe.
- No discussions.
(They need three identical answers.)
- Don't send signals.
- All right.
- He...
- Did you write down your answer?
- Yes.
- You had braces, right?
- They must be identical.
- I had braces.
- Still...
- You had braces.
One, two, three.
I think they'll be identical.
- I think they'll be identical.
- They're identical, right?
- Let's see. No?
- No?
(Aren't the answers identical?)
(Yang Se Chan)
Me.
- No. For goodness' sake.
- It's Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok.
- You're too modest.
- I mean...
- You're modest.
(Jong Hyuk wrote Jae Seok's name.)
(He throws it to the ground
so that Jae Seok doesn't see it.)
- You're too modest.
- Jae Seok.
- I mean...
- You're modest.
- Look at my mouth.
- Hey!
You're more handsome than Jae Seok.
I mean...
- Jae Seok?
- Why...
- I'm sorry.
- Do you know why he chose you?
He didn't want to pick me
because he resembled me.
You should've just written down
my name.
You should've written down
Jae Seok's name.
Gosh, it's me.
- You're my pick too.
- Right?
Same here.
We were close.
The answers must be identical
this time as well.
- Okay.
- Such questions are hard.
This is hard.
Your options are Yu Jae Seok,
Yang Se Chan, and Joo Jong Hyuk.
Consider
their physical appearances...
and write the 1st, 2nd,
and 3rd ranks in order.
Write the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd ranks
in order.
But this...
- Jae Seok.
- This...
In order?
This is difficult.
Hold on. This is difficult.
- One person has to let go.
- Let go.
- Give up what you have to.
- Hey.
The 2nd and 3rd are difficult.
- The 2nd and 3rd are so difficult.
- This will last forever.
You're admitting it.
(It's the battle of pride
between the fish.)
- The 2nd and 3rd...
- It's so difficult.
Jong Hyuk,
don't write it so confidently.
- People here have high self-esteem.
- Okay.
The members of Running Man
all think they look the best.
Se Chan doesn't look bad.
(Is it the young protruding mouth
or the handsome man made by society?)
Se Chan looks good
when he dresses up.
- Are you all done?
- Yes.
One, two, three.
Joo Jong Hyuk, Yang Se Chan.
(Jae Seok ranked last
by both of them.)
(Will Jae Seok rank himself
last too?)
(1. Joo Jong Hyuk, 2. Yu Jae Seok,
3. Yang Se Chan)
- Goodness.
- Why?
What are you doing?
(The baby octopuses
claim they're better.)
- Goodness.
- Why?
(He puts it down so Jae Seok
doesn't see it.)
- Why is it you?
- Give up what you can.
What is that?
- You're important.
- Who was it?
- Who did you write?
- I...
Goodness.
(You look the ugliest.)
(It was confirmed.)
- What are you doing?
- I told you to give up.
You should have thought about it.
- Why would you do that?
- He came because they look similar.
He wouldn't want to be third.
- I didn't think about that.
- You should have thought about it.
I should have thought about it.
This is it.
- As soon as I saw him.
- Your answers never matched,
- so you get zero points.
- Okay!
Okay!
Next is Team Haha.
We two had many matching answers.
- Yes. Many of ours matched.
- Yes.
We got them all.
- Let's go.
Let's just think simply.
As simple as possible.
(The first question for Team Haha)
Rank Haha, Ji Ye Eun,
and Kim Si Eun...
(Rank Haha, Ji Ye Eun,
and Kim Si Eun...)
- in the order of height.
- Their height.
(Rank Haha, Ji Ye Eun,
and Kim Si Eun in the order of height.)
Wait.
(Rank Haha, Ji Ye Eun,
and Kim Si Eun in the order of height.)
This is a battle of pride, Haha.
It's a battle of pride.
But this...
Isn't it too easy?
- It's easy.
- Why are you hesitating? It's easy.
- Hey!
- Wait. You...
- Seriously.
Did you group us like this
to give us this question?
- This is too easy.
- They grouped us like this...
- for this question.
- Right.
It may hurt your pride,
but the question is easy.
It's easy.
You have to get it correct.
This one is easy.
You're trying to hurt my pride.
She's shorter than me.
The question is easy.
(The bold Ddochi
writes her name first.)
Si Eun doesn't even need
to think about it.
- The tallest person.
- That's easy.
This was brilliant.
- Si Eun...
- You basically gave us free points.
Let's first get it correct.
One, two, three.
- I was serious.
- Seriously.
"Ji Ye Eun, Haha, Kim Si Eun."
(Ji Ye Eun, Haha, Kim Si Eun)
What?
- One, two, three.
- I was serious.
(She put down her pride
and wrote Ye Eun's name first.)
- I was serious.
- Seriously.
(1. Ji Ye Eun, 2. Kim Si Eun,
3. Haha)
(Si Eun's answer)
(Si Eun seriously thought
Haha was shorter than her.)
- I'm sorry.
- Si Eun.
Really.
Are you kidding? How tall are you?
You're shorter than me.
I'm taller than 170cm.
This is unbelievable. Seriously.
I asked her. She said she was 166cm.
- Si Eun.
- Haha.
- You shorty.
- I'm really sorry.
"You shorty."
Si Eun.
- This is so funny.
- I thought the question was easy.
But you wrote Ye Eun as the tallest.
I did that to win.
- I did that to win.
- Do you know what Haha did?
Are you 174cm tall?
- I'm 171cm.
- No. You're 173cm.
- You're 173cm, okay?
Tell people you're 173cm.
You really thought that way.
- Si Eun was serious.
- This is funny.
We failed to get this?
- We have to get it now.
- We have to win.
- Let's go simple. Seriously.
- We really have to win.
- It's so funny.
- I won't use my brain.
- I'll go by the facts.
Here is the second question.
Please write the common point
of the three words.
This is easy.
- They're just giving it to you.
- It's easy?
King Sejong, Yi Sun Sin,
and Shin Saimdang.
Okay. Three, two...
This is easy.
One.
Raise your answers.
(Great people in history)
(Their answers don't match.)
(Jong Hyuk bursts into laughter
after seeing something.)
What are we going to do?
He wrote "Korea."
They all wrote different answers.
Raise your answers.
- She wrote "The best."
- What are we going to do?
They all wrote different answers.
(Great people in history,
Korea, the best!)
Great people in the history
of Korea are the best!
- Korea.
- This...
Korea.
- Hey. Korea!
- Great people in history.
The best!
Si Eun is the best.
- "The best?"
- Korea.
Since answers did not match
for the last question,
you are in last place.
- What's wrong with us?
- It's so funny.
When these three are together,
you're the best.
Ye Eun.
Ye Eun is the most outstanding.
They might not be able
to get anything matching.
- Yes.
- That's possible.
- We're going to stay.
- That's amazing.
Let's drop our pride
and get it correct.
- Okay.
- Drop your pride.
Definitely.
You all need to write...
- the same answer.
- Okay.
Write Ji Seok Jin's age.
(Write Seok Jin's age.)
(The question caught them
off guard.)
Okay.
You know it, right?
- Your name is on the list...
- Right.
- of people who turned 60 this year.
- Your name was there.
No. That's not true.
I'm 58 years old.
We should go with the global age.
Your birthday is in February.
- What are you talking about?
- It hasn't passed yet.
Okay.
(It's a custom question for Seok Jin
who likes the global age.)
- You know it, right?
- Three, two, one.
Raise your answers.
(Seok Jin wrote 58,
the age he's been talking about.)
(Jong Kook also wrote 58.)
- Let's see.
- Fifty-eight.
- Sixty.
- What's wrong with you?
(She wrote 60
without subtracting anything.)
- Hey.
- You should have gotten it right.
I talked about it on the show.
You should have gotten it.
- Sixty...
- There's an age I'm claiming to be.
What's that?
- How did you get that?
- What's that?
- The year...
- Does my age change?
But you're 60.
Okay.
- This was an easy question.
- It was an easy one.
- Good.
- This is funny.
This time, you'll see a part
of the lyrics of a song...
and write the lyrics
that will follow that part.
- Okay. I'm in trouble.
- That's hard.
- We...
- We should meet halfway.
- Let's meet halfway.
- Don't write something too old.
Half way.
One, two, three.
- Five, four...
- Hold on.
(Songs that have "Dear"
in the lyrics)
("If Like Me" by Kim Jang Hoon)
("Adult Ceremony" by Park Ji Yoon)
("Cherry Blossom Ending"
by Busker Busker)
There are so many.
There are many songs with "Dear."
They're in a similar age group.
- Hold on.
- Seok Jin.
But first, this...
This might be a song
that only I know.
No, Seok Jin.
You shouldn't go that far.
But this is the only song
I can think of.
One, two, three.
- Raise them.
- Dear
("With You" by The Blue)
(Dear, look at my eyes)
- Look.
- Dear
Dear!
Don't change
(They're confused by the song
they're hearing for the first time.)
(Don't you know this song?)
("You" by Lee Jung Hee)
Look at me
(Seok Sam has gone
way back in time.)
- Seok Sam's songs...
- Yes.
are really from the 80s.
- When was it released?
- I've never heard it before.
(It was released in 1980.)
- Seok Jin. That's too old.
- Love is sad
- I've never heard it before.
- Me too.
The results of the quiz puts
Team Jae Seok in first place.
- Stay.
- We won.
Team Haha is in second place.
- Okay!
Seok Jin's family
will make the transfer first.
- It's the final transfer.
- This one was weak.
For the last transfer,
the team that is targeted...
will not be revealed.
We can't lose here.
We can't.
(Jae Seok's family had two chances
in the previous transfer.)
(Jae Seok's family:
25 dollars in total)
(Seok Jin's family:
90 dollars taken)
(Haha's family: 100 dollars taken)
(They succeeded both times
and took the lead.)
(Haha's family:
220 dollars in total)
(Haha's family: 50 dollars in total)
(They became last
after both families' attack.)
Since we don't have money,
we can go bold.
- Should we go bold?
- Bold.
They took ours.
- That's clear.
- Right.
- They have it.
- They do.
We should go higher than that then.
If they want to win,
they'll bet on an amount higher
than what they lost.
That's right.
(Will Jae Seok's family be able
to maintain their position?)
How much did we bet at first
when we lost?
- At first...
- How much did we bet?
We bet 80 dollars, and we lost it.
- We bet 80 and it didn't work.
- Then we can bet on...
- a smaller amount.
- No.
- They took this much of ours.
- Seok Jin.
- This...
- They took this much.
- No. It's this, not that.
- No.
We used to have 175 dollars.
- We had 175 dollars earlier.
- We had 175 dollars...
- Was it 175 dollars?
- It was 175 dollars.
- Did they take this?
- They took this.
- Right.
So, 9 plus 3.
They'd definitely have at least 12.
- That's right. They'd have that.
- Right?
- They'd have at least that amount.
- Twelve.
- At least.
- Even if they don't have much.
- The least amount.
- That's the safe amount.
- The minimum.
- How is it?
- Don't put too much.
- Let's go.
Let's do that.
Let's make it 120 dollars.
Who would you take money from?
- Jae Seok.
- Jae Seok's family.
(They make it safe and take
120 dollars from Jae Seok's family.)
(Seok Jin's family:
85 dollars in total)
(Jae Seok's family:
120 dollars taken)
(Transfer success)
It worked, right?
- Yes.
- All right then.
- Okay. It's done.
- Done.
(Seok Jin's family:
205 dollars in total)
We might take first place.
- We might win.
- Yes.
- We don't know it yet.
- We did really well.
- It's good.
- Yes.
(Haha's family: 50 dollars in total)
- How about 150?
- Are you ready?
- Did you say 150?
- What?
- That's too little.
- Okay.
(Haha's family: 50 dollars in total)
Let's make it 230.
- That's too big.
- Why?
- It's too big. What if we fail?
- But they took a lot from us.
But they took a lot from us.
- Make it bigger?
- Bigger?
What about 240?
(The final amount is decided
with the two tiger moths.)
- I'm so nervous.
- It has to work.
We don't know how it will turn out.
(How much money did they take
from whose account?)
(Haha's family is done
transferring the money.)
We have two chances.
Si Eun can't keep a straight face.
(Si Eun can't keep a straight face.)
(Did Haha's family succeed
in transferring the money?)
We got busted.
Should we take all the money
from Haha's family?
- We should do that.
- Let's do that.
Haha's family?
I think we should take Haha's money.
I think they just took
a lot of money from us.
I think they took... Earlier,
- did we take 90 dollars from them?
- It was 100 dollars.
- We got 100 dollars?
- From Haha's family...
We took 100 dollars
from Haha's family.
I think they took...
- more than that.
- I think so.
- What about 150?
- Let's go with 140.
Is it 140?
(If Haha's family took as much money
as they got on the 2nd attempt...)
Jae Seok, it's okay to fail once.
- Right. It's okay.
- It doesn't matter.
- Haha's family.
- How much?
We will take 140 dollars.
Please. It has to work.
(Trying to take 140 dollars
from Haha's family)
Why am I feeling so nervous?
If it fails,
things will get complicated.
It will be complicated.
(Does Haha's family have
more than 140 dollars?)
Please.
The transaction has been denied.
(Transfer failed)
Please.
(Haha's family has
less than 140 dollars?)
(Now they have
only one chance left.)
It failed.
(If they fail again,
they might end up in last place.)
The Family in Joy and Sorrow Race
is over now.
The family with the most money
will get the prize.
- Okay.
- Prize?
The family with the least money
will get the penalty.
The family with the most money is...
- The difference is overwhelming.
- Overwhelming?
(The family
with a huge amount of money?)
The amount is 245 dollars.
(The 1st place: 245 dollars)
- It's Jae Seok's family.
- Yes!
- Is it 245 dollars?
- How is it possible?
- That's a lot.
- It's 245 dollars in total.
- Why is it so big?
- No one took our money?
We just failed to take 140 dollars
from Haha's family.
I think Jong Kook's family
took their money.
- How much should it be?
- What about 150?
Okay.
(They found out where the money went
and took 150 dollars from Seok Jin.)
(Jae Seok's family:
95 dollars in total)
(Seok Jin's family:
150 dollars taken)
(From last place to first!
A success story of a poor family.)
Do they get the prize?
Here's the prize.
You can use the 245 dollars
in your account...
- to buy a prize you want.
- Really?
(They can use 245 dollars
to buy a prize.)
- This is amazing.
- Look at this.
- It's great.
- It's Royal Salute.
- How much is it?
- Gosh, this is...
- It's genuine.
- It's great.
- How much is this?
(They have more than 200 dollars,
so they can buy the whisky.)
- It's here.
- Is it Royal Salute?
- This is...
- You like to drink, right?
- What? I like it, but...
- It's Royal Salute.
- You should take it.
- Take it.
- Come on.
- Just take it.
All right then.
You will buy one whisky then.
How much do you think we have?
All right. Now I will announce
the team to get the penalty.
- I get the penalty again?
- It might be them.
No... I know. That's what I mean.
Because Jae Seok's family
took their money.
It was so close.
- The difference is five dollars.
- What?
- Only five dollars?
- Really?
(The difference between 2nd and 3rd
is only 5 dollars.)
- Only five dollars?
- Really?
I guess
you can transfer five dollars.
- The difference is five dollars.
- Really?
- My gosh.
- Unbelievable.
The team to get the penalty is...
They have 50 dollars.
- It's Haha's family.
- Yes!
- It's only 5 dollars.
- They don't transfer 5 dollars.
- Right.
- We won with five dollars.
- Five dollars saved you.
- Seok Jin's family is the second...
- with 55 dollars.
- Yes!
We should've taken 100 dollars.
We won if we took 100 dollars.
- Make it 250?
- No, 200.
- No, 220. Or 200?
- Should we go with 200?
- Who?
- Jae Seok's.
(They tried to take 200 dollars
from Jae Seok's after Seok Jin's.)
It has to work.
The transaction has been denied.
- What?
- This is crazy.
- Make it 140.
- Yes. Please.
Please. It has to work.
- We had 220 dollars at first.
- They had 220 dollars at first.
- They had 220 dollars?
- Gosh, that's a lot.
- They were rich.
- We were rich.
- And...
Jae Seok's family had
only 25 dollars.
- From 25 dollars to 245 dollars.
- You had 25 dollars?
Today's penalty is...
the fresh cream bomb.
Only two of you
will get fresh cream.
One of you will pass.
I choose number one.
I want to be number one.
- No. You can take number one.
- Okay.
- I'm unlucky.
- You are?
- I lose every time.
- Really?
- I pick number three.
- I don't know.
- My gosh.
- Please.
Ye Eun has
never avoided the penalty.
- That's true.
- The penalty.
(Ye Eun, the penalty collector)
- Avoid it today.
- This is driving me crazy.
All right. It will go off
on the count of three.
Gosh, hang on.
Hang on. Do it right away.
- Just do it.
- My heart.
One, two, three.
Three.
(Haha and Si Eun got the penalty.)
(Unlucky Ye Eun
avoided the penalty today!)
- Finally!
- Good.
(Screaming)
- This is your first time.
- You were the only one?
- This is my first time.
- Just one?
- Only one survives.
- One.
Two with the cream?
(The unluckiness moved to Si Eun.)
Ji Ye Eun!
She's really scary.
(This is how the one that came
to win first place ended up.)
Where are her eyes?
- She's really...
- I should've chosen number one.
Hey. There's only one survivor,
and it's Ye Eun?
(We'd like to thank
Joo Jong Hyuk and Kim Si Eun.)
- How did you know, Ye Eun?
- Si Eun is funny.
(The production crew headed to
Jong Kook's house after a tip-off.)
(A flood of testimonies
from the colleagues)
- He has this much...
- Plastic bags.
plastic bags on the balcony.
The house should be
on "Incredible Moment."
- That's not a lie.
- It's true.
(What about Jong Kook's house
worries people around him?)
- This is interesting.
- He cleaned up... No.
- It's the same.
- He didn't clean up.
(What on earth happened
to Jong Kook's house?)
I cleaned up the whole thing.
- How could you live like this?
- Look at that.
(Items piled up so high
shock everyone.)
- This is crazy.
- "Crazy?"
The pancake has become a fossil.
(He finally decides
to clean up the mess.)
(Cleaning with a man obsessed
with his stuff is not easy.)
I'm keeping this!
- Please.
- You still have a lot over there.
- Please get rid of it.
- No.
Jong Kook,
why did you not throw this away?
This is Dongmyo.
(Luxury items found
in the mini Dongmyo?)
I have Dior shoes. Do you want them?
(The members get excited
to see the treasures pouring out.)
(Who will get the treasure
at the chaotic Jong Kook House?)
(SOS Heavy Cleaning Zone)