(The two major gangs
of the killer world)
The Locust Gang, famous killers
specializing in battles of wits,
(Locust Gang,
specializing in battles of wits)
and their long-time rival,
the Physical Tiger Gang,
specializing in physical battles.
(Physical Tiger Gang,
specializing in physical battles)
A fierce battle for territory
that has lasted for 15 years.
Today, all the killers
are gathering...
to see an end to the battle.
Let's go and attack them.
We're going to crush them.
The Tiger Gang
versus the Locust Gang.
- You know...
- Nice to meet you.
Okay!
It's been a long time
since we've gathered.
- The killers...
- This is really...
- Hang on. Hey.
- This is like "Guns and Talks."
- While we were apart,
- I...
- you've become a petty thief.
- He's not a killer.
- You look like a petty offender.
- Hey.
- I'm Leon.
- Obviously, you will...
- get caught soon.
- Come on.
- Bang!
- For whatever reason,
- he will get caught soon.
- I know.
I was told my nipples were showing
through the shirt,
- so I keep hunching...
- The nipple show.
my shoulders like this.
- Boss.
- It's okay.
- Round shoulders.
- Boss, why are you...
- You're the boss.
- You would need this.
- You should attach this.
- Why...
- Isn't that too big?
- Hey.
- Will this work?
- What do we do then?
- Why...
- What?
Why have you changed, Boss?
- It's not like that.
- Seriously...
- My gosh.
- I put this on to try my best.
- I know.
- By the way,
- Seok Jin's outfit is just...
- I...
- What's that?
- Are you a sea urchin?
I'm a self-defensive killer.
- Sea urchin.
- Self-defense.
- No one can attack me.
- Sea urchin.
- This is crazy.
- Are you Jee Sea Urchin?
- I can fire this.
- How?
- Bang. Okay?
- So this will go off?
- I can shoot you with this.
- Shoot me?
- "I can shoot you."
- I can shoot you.
- Is it like a poisoned needle?
- I can... Yes.
- It's a poisoned needle.
- Sea urchin.
Ye Eun, today, you're...
- Jong Kook.
- You look good in that outfit.
Don't say that she looks pretty.
- Why not?
- Why?
She casts a spell on herself.
- When you say she lost weight,
- Really?
she thinks she's pretty.
- I'm pretty.
- I see.
- Don't say that she's pretty.
- I'm pretty.
- What's with you?
Anyway, you look good
in that kind of outfit.
Do I look like a celebrity?
(Do I look like a celebrity?)
- Do I look like a celebrity?
- No.
Why do you try to look
like a celebrity in front of us?
A killer should look like a killer,
- not like a celebrity.
- He's right.
- I'm cute.
- Goodness me.
(Acting cute)
Don't try to act cute
or flirt with us.
What's with that face?
- Don't do that.
- You...
- It's about self-satisfaction.
- Right.
(The youngest of the Tiger Gang acts cute,
which no one asked for.)
(The Locust Gang is gathering
at another place.)
- Hey.
- Hello.
- We're the Locust Gang.
- Are you the Locust Gang?
- Yes, I am.
- Okay.
Aren't you a bully
in your neighborhood?
Actually, I wanted to look
like Lee Jung Jae...
"Deliver Us from Evil."
But this is more like "Failan."
(A good-for-nothing bully
from "Failan")
- Aren't you a mugger?
- That's how I look.
- A bully in a neighborhood.
- Yes.
What's with your outfits? You...
- Did you take a boat?
- No.
I'm Black Mamba.
- What?
- She's the captain of a boat.
- You look like Leon.
- I'm Leon.
That's what I intended.
(What he intended is Leon,
but he has the height of Matilda.)
The short Leon.
Hey, I'm wearing these.
- Look.
- You're wearing boats as shoes.
- I sprained my ankles many times.
- It's at ankle height.
- Why isn't our boss coming?
- Hey.
- Oh, dear.
- Mr. Tae Jin Ah.
- My gosh.
- Are you a magician?
- He might have a pigeon.
- Why are you...
- A pigeon.
- Are you a magician?
- Hey.
- Pigeon?
Your boss is here.
What are you doing
when your boss is here?
- You're here.
- You should greet me.
- All right.
You're the captain of the ferry boat
in Tongyeong.
- She's the captain.
- Right.
- Are you Leon?
- Yes. Nice to meet you.
- I'm Leon.
- Why...
Pigeon!
(In reality, he's Mr. Pigeon.)
Okay. Today...
The muscular ones of the gang.
- Yes.
- We will crush them.
Those punks.
- I'll show you how I crush them.
- Good.
- And we have a new member.
- Do we have a new member?
- A new member?
Who is it?
- There he is.
- Hey.
- Hey, you...
Yoo Seung Ho!
- Nice to meet you.
- There you go.
- You fraud.
- He is...
- He knows the basics.
- Hello.
(A good-looking physique)
(And flustering skills)
Not me.
Seung Ho, it was going out.
Give him 20 dollars.
Take 20 dollars each
and give us 10 dollars.
- Good, right?
- That works.
- But we have only 20 dollars.
- We should split the money.
(It was a lie.)
(He learned fraudulent skills
right away on his first appearance.)
(He came again with V,
showing off his good looks.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Best out of three.
(Sly)
- He's somewhat annoying.
- He's strange.
He somehow gets on my nerves.
I hope I will come again.
(Despite his outstanding
performance, he lost both times.)
I'll come back next time and win
if I have a chance.
- All right.
- Good job today.
- He knows the basics.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
It's been a while, Seung Ho.
You betrayed me.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too!
(He speaks informally,
immersed in his role as a killer.)
It's been a while!
Come here, Seung Ho.
Seriously, Seung Ho...
How have you been?
- I've been well.
- What?
- "I've been well?"
- Hey.
- I've been well.
- He's...
- Didn't he get trained?
- Has he lost his mind?
Did he miss out on the training?
- Does he have his own theme?
- He's not disciplined?
I talked to him briefly
earlier today.
After doing a TV show
with Lee Bong Won...
- Hey, Seung Ho.
- He speaks...
casually to everyone now.
He's doing a TV show
with Paeng Hyun Sook and Lee Bong Won.
- It's no joke.
- So...
- It must not be easy.
- After working with those two,
- he must think we're easy.
- Exactly.
- So he speaks casually to us.
- Of course.
It's not like that.
That's it.
- But he...
- What...
Why does he keep
speaking casually to me?
- He's the boss.
- Why does he keep being like that?
- He's our boss.
- He's the boss.
How dare you!
You know what it is like
in a movie about killers.
Everything we're wearing
is a weapon.
What? What did you do?
Why did you kick it?
- I'm the boss, okay?
- I see. Then...
- You should be polite to me.
- Yes, sir.
All right. You can speak
casually to them, though.
- Why not?
- He can't do that.
You can speak casually to me.
It's okay.
- All right.
- Anyway,
we have Seung Ho in our gang now.
We should crush the Tiger Gang
with Jong Kook.
Apparently,
it's Jong Kook's birthday,
so they're having a birthday party.
- That's right.
- It's his birthday on Friday.
- Let's go then.
- Let's go and attack them.
- Let's go.
- Anyway, we're the Tiger Gang.
- Yes.
We have a new member
of the Tiger Gang.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Ho Jun.
- Hey, stand in the middle.
- Come here.
- You punk.
- You brat.
Hang on. Are you wearing perfume?
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
- You're dolled up.
- He...
- He looks better than before.
- I think so.
We're meeting
for the first time, right?
- It's not your first time.
- Is it the first time?
- Seok Jin.
- All right.
- Ho Jun, you were here before.
- Ho Jun.
Were you on this show before?
- Yes.
- When?
Hey, you don't remember?
- Neither of you remembers.
- I don't remember.
- Were you here back then?
- Hey.
- Hey, he was always here.
- Since Episode One.
- He's our original member.
- I've always been here.
- Seok Jin.
- Hey.
- You didn't see him?
- This is my first time.
- This is his 3rd time on our show.
- It's his 3rd time?
- He was here a lot.
- He was?
(It was 11 years ago.)
(Seok Sam from 11 years ago)
(They even had a 1-on-1 fight.)
My wife is a big fan of him.
- It's his 3rd time?
- He was here a lot.
- He was?
- Yes.
- Seok Jin,
- What?
don't try to get away with it.
Why can't you remember him?
- I don't remember you. I'm sorry.
- Actually,
- he was here many times.
- Right.
- He was?
- Yes.
- By the way, Boss,
- What is it?
we have a new member now.
We should see his dance.
- I want to see him act cute.
- Good.
- You should do that.
- Like a talent show?
A talent show?
(Intimidated)
- He just...
- Hey.
- Are you intimidated?
- A little.
- Isn't he older than me?
- Hang on.
- He just touched your shoulder.
- Right.
All right.
- Seok Jin.
- What?
It was Boss Jong Kook's birthday
a few days ago.
- Right.
- I don't celebrate it.
- Don't do that.
- It was his birthday.
- Get him his birthday meal.
- Don't do that.
- Stop it!
- Well...
How many times do I
have to tell you? Don't do that.
- Let's do what he hates.
- Is it your birthday?
- It was his birthday.
- Ho Jun.
Did you not know
it was his birthday?
- I really hate it.
- He hates it.
(A pink table with his birthday meal
is being set.)
This is amazing.
(Food Fighter is excited.)
This is great.
- This is it.
- Look at her.
- She's losing her mind.
- Hey, she's...
This is amazing.
They're setting things up
in the back.
(Happy Kook's Day)
- Ho Jun, what are you waiting for?
- He's handsome.
- Put this on his head.
- Right.
- You don't have to do that.
- Put it on him.
- You should wear it.
- All right. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Put it on. That's it.
You look pretty.
- This is nice.
- What took you so long?
- Hurry and come over here.
- Seriously...
Is he a magician or what?
Where's your pigeon?
- He let go of the pigeon earlier.
- Mr. Magician.
He let it go.
- He let go of it earlier.
- You punks.
It's a musical.
(He provokes Jong Kook
as soon as he gets here.)
Did you see that?
That's our boss's dance.
Is this "Charlie
and the Chocolate Factory" or what?
- Guys.
- Chocolate factory?
- I can tell you're really weak.
- Why?
The discipline of gangs
has been lax these days.
What do you mean?
(Boss Ttuk attacks
the Tiger Gang right away.)
- What?
- A boss of a gang...
is having a birthday party
like this?
- Don't you have work to do?
- The birthday party is like...
I'm sorry,
but this is part
of an advertisement.
Is that so?
Happy birthday.
- Congratulations
(A congratulatory performance begins
right away at the good news.)
Are you a musical team?
They're actors.
- Happy birthday to you
Okay!
(Ending fairy)
- All right.
- I like the strawberry flavor.
- All right. It's done.
- Hey.
- What?
- He's Jun Ho.
- Hey.
- Ho Jun.
- You just saw him?
- I didn't know.
It's been a long time, Ho Jun.
- Right.
- Ho Jun is really...
- Hasn't it been ten years?
- Because...
he was here
when we just started our show.
- All right, everyone.
- What?
Have something soft
that has a good texture.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Let's eat.
- I like the strawberry flavor.
Ice cream!
- Amazing. This is nice.
- Is it strawberry?
- Eat a lot.
- By the way...
Boss!
- Okay.
- Did you add this? Was it here?
Can you give me one?
- Here.
- All right.
It has jelly in it
- It's very chewy.
- It has?
It has gummy bears in it.
- It's so good.
- It's jelly.
- It's delicious.
- Yes. It's refreshing.
This is nice.
This is...
The jelly is so good.
(Jong Kook, who doesn't know much
about this, takes a bite.)
- It's good.
- Kids will love it.
- It has jelly in it.
- Strawberry and banana.
It tastes so refreshing
with strawberry and banana.
Right? It's strawberry and banana.
- It's so good.
- It's tasty.
- Is this ice cream too?
- Yes.
- Aren't they grapes?
- They're grapes.
- Really?
- It's ice cream.
Green grapes. It's Shine Muscat.
What?
- It's really good.
- It's so delicious.
It tastes so refreshing
with strawberry and banana.
- You're really handsome.
- Strawberry and banana.
Thank you.
He's my wife's favorite actor.
He's a great actor.
- You and I...
- The toppings...
- are polar opposites.
- are no joke these days.
You have a sharp nose...
- while mine is blunt.
- Is this ice cream?
You have deep-set eyes,
which I don't have.
- That's how different we are.
- What?
(Seok Sam only realizes
what everyone else already knew.)
Seung Ho, do you like ice cream?
I do. A while back...
- Oh, that.
- Yes, of course.
- Of course. He advertised it.
- When you were a kid.
- Yes, when I was about 20.
- You were a kid.
- That's right!
- I think I was in my mid-20s.
In your mid-20s?
The brand ambassador is here.
- Talk about nice timing.
- You're right.
My flavor was cherry blossom.
- Cherry blossom?
- I see.
I was the human cherry blossom.
- No way.
- Seung Ho.
- Yes? But now...
- You've become more shameless.
(The human cherry
is quite shameless.)
Hold on. You are
not the brand ambassador anymore.
- I'm not.
- Right.
- You've become more shameless.
- Maybe you shouldn't mention it.
- How old are you now?
- Wait a second.
Seung Ho, check out that geezer.
Wasn't his comment a bit harsh?
Why? How so?
What did you say to him...
when he talked about
his flavor being cherry blossom?
He's no longer the brand ambassador.
- So he shouldn't mention it.
- But still...
I'm sorry,
but aren't you his junior?
- Yes, I'm his junior.
- Right.
And you're my boss!
Still, there's a line
you shouldn't cross.
- Do you know what's funny?
- Unbelievable.
- We can't stand insubordination.
- Watch your words.
Do you know what's funny?
Against the Locust Gang,
it should've been Seok Jin Gang.
But Seok Jin serves
Jong Kook instead.
Haha, don't point it out.
- Get over here.
- Why would you say that?
- Haha, come on.
- Get over here.
I prefer not to be disturbed.
- You jerk.
- Don't point it out.
- Seok Jin is fine with it.
- The staff...
- Seok Jin, wait. Let me talk.
- Sure.
Why do you think
he wasn't chosen to lead the gang,
even though he's the oldest?
He isn't a man of such caliber!
I apologize!
You jerk!
(Seok Sam fights back against
the Locust Gang's strong attack.)
- How dare you?
- Hey!
- That's our boss.
- Get over here.
- How dare you?
- Hey!
(An explosive situation)
- You punk.
- Are you all right?
(Bang)
- How dare you?
- Why you...
- Hold on a second.
- Are you okay?
- Someone shot at me.
- He's our boss.
- How many is he going up against?
- He's one of us.
Who's this lady?
He's one of us,
but I'm embarrassed by him.
- That's our boss!
- How dare you?
- Who's this lady?
- Show some respect...
- to the lady.
- Come on.
- Show respect for our boss.
- Is this a circus?
- What do you think you're doing?
Shouldn't we talk about
why they're on the show today?
All right. It's been a while
since we had Seung Ho...
- and Ho Jun on the show.
- Sure.
They're in the play,
"Killing Caesar."
(Ho Jun and Seung Ho are back,)
(starring in the play,
"Killing Caesar.")
A lot of actors
have been starring...
- in plays lately.
- Yes, a lot of them.
- Tell us about the play.
- What is it about?
It's based on "Julius Caesar,"
the play written
by William Shakespeare.
It was reinterpreted...
for modern times...
to deliver a more relatable message.
In the original play,
Caesar's death scene...
- only lasts about ten minutes.
- I see.
But we extended that scene
to a full 100 minutes.
- I see.
- I get what you mean.
- Will it only be like this?
- Then...
(Constantly groaning)
(But he won't die.)
No, it's not like that.
- Die!
- How many more minutes to go?
You have 48 minutes left.
It won't be easy
to extend the scene.
(Yang hasn't grasped the concept
of adaptation yet.)
How ignorant of you.
- You still have 48 minutes left.
- I apologize.
I apologize.
- Of course.
- This is nice.
- I can't believe it.
- This is delicious.
For today's race,
we're joined by Yoo Seung Ho
and Son Ho Jun from "Killing Caesar."
It's Territorial Expansion
of Killers.
Long-time rivals,
the Locust Gang and Tiger Gang,
- have come together...
- Okay.
to settle their turf war.
We'll go head to head.
The winning gang of this turf war
will receive a prize.
The losing gang
will receive a penalty.
- Got it.
- After battling for each turf,
the winning gang will enjoy...
- all the luxuries it has to offer.
- I see.
The losing team
will receive a penalty.
We'll now begin the mission
to see...
- who will claim the first turf.
- Right away?
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- I like that lack of downtime.
- Okay.
We'll crush you!
Bring it on.
It's like "Guns and Talks."
The first battle...
is a take on the game
Why Are You at My House.
- It's Why Are You on My Turf.
- Why Are You on My Turf.
Unlike the original game,
you will play Cham, Cham, Cham
instead of rock-paper-scissors.
If the team playing offense
wins the Cham, Cham, Cham game,
the killer will be stolen.
If you lose, the opposing team
will get to play offense.
The team with the most people
at the end of the round will win.
Meanwhile, regardless of who wins,
the killers forced
onto the opposing team...
will become errand boys.
Really?
Can we give them any order?
- Yes.
- Our team...
- We can order them around.
- I know.
I'll teach them a lesson.
Those taken captive will serve
as both hostages and errand boys.
- They'll have to serve us.
- Nice.
It's best to be
with your original gang...
- when it wins.
- Exactly.
I'm going to plead with my gang.
Please don't let them take me.
It'll be a long day for me.
- Who wants to relieve some stress?
- If you come here,
you'll be done for.
- I'll be in tatters.
- You'll be done for.
Won't we be able to get them back?
- Not until the next game.
- Of course.
It's fine.
You can spend some time there.
- Get a taste of it.
- I'll be in tatters.
Don't be chicken!
- We should be on the offense first.
- Sure thing.
- We'll go first.
- Play defense first.
- What should we do?
- Okay.
- We need to hold hands.
- In the middle.
After the first chant...
Why did you come over?
Why?
- Shouldn't you stand in the center?
- Right.
(Awkward)
(Laughing)
Ye Eun is being funny
about holding Ho Jun's hand.
- Why?
- Seriously?
- What's with you?
- How annoying can she be?
- What...
- What's the matter with you?
He's giving you his hand,
so take it.
- But...
- Take it.
- What are you doing?
- What's the matter with her?
What are you doing?
I'm chaste, you see.
- What?
- What do you mean you're chaste?
- As if holding hands is a big deal!
- What is this?
It's not like Ho Jun
is making a move on you.
- But I'm conservative.
- Unbelievable.
But you took Jong Kook's hand.
- Why...
- I don't want to hold her hand.
(I don't want
to hold her hand either.)
(Hunchback's game of push and pull
backfired.)
- You hurt his feelings.
- But...
What was that?
- Seriously?
- Just take his hand.
Se Chan, you come here instead.
- Are you kidding me?
- Someone has to go at the end.
- There.
- What was that?
- What's the matter with you?
- Unbelievable.
- You embarrassed Ho Jun.
- Tell me about it.
I've thought about it,
and Ho Jun and Seung Ho...
came on the show
to promote their serious play.
Is this the right game for them?
It's their fault
for choosing to be on this show.
- It's all right.
- Good.
- Let's chant with seriousness.
- It's fine.
We can just act
like serious killers.
- Let's chant with seriousness.
- Yes, the chant.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
Who will play
the Cham, Cham, Cham game?
- We're on the offense.
- Who's on the offense?
- We'll go first.
- Offense.
- Go ahead.
- What?
- Really?
- Why?
Why did you say
you understood just now?
Am I not even allowed
to make a decision like this?
- But...
- Aren't I allowed?
That's not what I meant.
- Given my age...
- You should consult the team.
- He's 60.
- Why make a decision unilaterally?
- Come on.
- Unbelievable.
- Why make a decision unilaterally?
- I can't believe you.
- I...
- Stop it.
I may not have the authority,
but let me at least decide this.
- He's acting strange today.
- Don't you agree, Ho Jun?
- Let's be honest.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Do they go first?
Chant it with deep voices.
- Sure.
- Here we go.
And go.
- Why did you come over?
- We came to catch a killer.
- What killer did you come for?
(Who is Locust Gang's first target?)
We came to catch Killer Seok Sam...
(Targeting Jee Seok Sam)
- Killer Seok Sam.
- Why would you do it?
- Seung Ho, go ahead.
- Right.
- Don't be chicken.
- Cham, cham, cham.
- Seok Sam, don't be chicken.
- It's Cham, Cham, Cham.
- Don't be chicken.
- How old are you?
You can do this, Seok Sam.
- I'm 33.
You're 33?
- Stand strong.
- That's right.
Were you born in 1993?
Why do you look younger?
(Attacking him with a compliment)
- Seung Ho, don't be intimidated.
- Boss.
- Darn.
- Don't worry, and just do it.
- Don't worry.
- Smack him on the head.
- Wait for it.
- Why should I?
I've already decided
where I'm going to turn my head.
- I've made up my mind.
- Have you already decided?
- Don't move before he does.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Move after he does.
(Who will win the first match?)
Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay!
- Nice.
(Yoo Seung Ho wins.)
- Okay!
- He had his mind made up.
- Get over here.
- Nicely done.
- Seok Sam, get over here.
- Nice.
(He was brought down
by a game of Cham, Cham, Cham.)
- Seriously?
- Seok Sam!
The timing was on point.
- Seok Sam, please.
- The timing was on point.
- Join us, rookie.
- Come here.
- Seok Sam, come here.
- Can they get me back?
- It's fine.
- Go ahead.
- It's all right. Just head over.
- We'll get you back.
- Will he join you right away?
- Yes, he'll go over to them.
- Can't we get him back?
- Right away?
- We can get him back though.
Should it be this easy
to move from gang to gang?
- Get over here.
- Seok Sam, come on.
(They welcome the oldest rookie.)
- Get over here, rookie.
- Come on over.
- Nice!
- This way.
(Scuttling)
(Accept your rookie.)
- This is irritating.
- Come here.
- All right.
- Boss!
- Please.
- Hang tight.
- We'll get you back right away.
- Can't we get him back?
- Of course, we can.
- Please.
- This hurts.
- Someone else...
- His jacket.
- His jacket is a problem.
- Hold on.
- You.
- We'll get him back right away.
Take that jacket off.
- I don't want to.
- We could be pricked.
- Go on.
- It could hurt them.
- Why do I need to take it off?
- Then...
Swap jackets with someone else.
Wear it inside out.
- Go on. Wear it inside out.
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- He's a lunatic!
- Put it on inside out.
- Come here.
- Get over here.
(Haha found a trash bag somewhere.)
- Seok Sam, it's your choice.
- Seok Sam.
Wear it inside out...
- or throw it away.
- Daniel is right.
How is this allowed?
Here you go.
Stop picking on Seok Sam!
You jerks!
- You have another thing coming.
- Hey.
Put your arm through here.
(It's hard to see your family
being humiliated.)
Yes, let him stick out his arm.
Seok Sam, hang in there!
- Please...
- We'll get you back.
- You look cool, though.
- Ho Jun.
Why should I be fashionable
when I'm their hostage?
- You look cool.
- This is a matter of pride.
- Nice.
- Bag Man loves it.
- I love plastic bags.
- Bag Man.
- You're good.
- Let's go.
- Take me back.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's take them all.
(The next match begins.)
(The Tiger Gang is on the offense
this time.)
- What killer did you come for?
- Let it be me.
- We came to catch Killer Haha!
Hey!
- You should ask for me!
- Wait, Seok Sam!
- We'll get you back!
- Darn it!
- You should claim me.
- Let's go.
- Wait, Seok Sam!
- Ask for me!
Wait, Seok Sam!
- Okay.
- Let's play.
- Go for it.
- Okay. Do it.
- We need to succeed.
- Do it for us.
- Don't end up over there.
- Hey.
- Go.
- You can do it.
Good luck.
(Ho Jun attacks!)
Cham, cham, cham.
- Okay.
- Yes!
- Well done.
- Good job.
- Good for you.
- You did really well.
(Feeling let down)
- Ho Jun...
- You should've put in more energy.
- There's no room.
- It's okay.
- Come on.
- Hey.
- It's okay.
- What are you doing?
- Get back here.
- Who next? Ye Eun?
- It's okay.
Definitely Ye Eun.
How many times do we play this?
- Come on.
- Okay.
- Why did you come over?
- We came to catch Killer Ye Eun.
- Hang in there.
- I will.
- You can do it.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Daniel's up this time.
- I'm up? Okay.
- You play this time.
(Daniel attempts to attack Ye Eun.)
- All right.
- This is childish but fun.
- That's it. Go for it.
- This is better for you.
If you join our gang,
you can eat all you want.
Ye Eun, if you join us,
you get five meals a day.
- Most definitely.
- I won't eat.
Ye Eun lost weight for you, Daniel.
- Yes.
- For me?
Because of your
"do you weigh more" comment.
You played a big part.
You scumbag!
- She's back.
- Nice!
- Summon that energy!
- Bring that up!
- It's okay.
- Bring her to our side.
First of all,
if that's true, I'm sorry.
- Okay. Here I go.
- Okay. I'll fight back.
(The giants,
long-time archenemies have met.)
Ye Eun, hang in there.
Watch carefully.
Daniel, bring her over.
Cham, cham, cham!
- Yes!
- Get the ice cream.
- Cham!
(The giant that lost
becomes a hostage.)
- Get over here.
- Yes!
- She looked and then turned.
- Well done.
Going on the offense first
is an advantage.
- It helps to attack first.
- That's a good thing.
- Yes.
- It's an advantage.
Why did you decide on your own?
You have a point.
- Right?
- You're right.
- You're actually right.
- Why did you hand it over?
My head won't fit.
It'll fit.
- It will fit just fine.
- The arms go here.
- Hey, now, you lot... Wait.
- Here.
- Your design skills improved.
- Is that so?
You got better at this.
- Your mic.
- It looks much cleaner.
You're good at making this now.
- This will be much warmer.
- It's fashionable.
- Ye Eun's is pretty.
- This looks much nicer.
- They gave you shoulders.
- They did.
- It looks nice.
- That's nice.
- It's nice.
- It looks like a dress.
- It's much better.
- It's actually pretty.
It's better than before.
Wear that from now on.
It actually looks nice.
- It looks like a dress.
- Ye Eun.
Okay, let's go!
- It's us now.
- Okay, come at us.
Let's play. It's our turn to attack.
Who do you want?
Take us back.
- Take us back.
- There's no time.
- Ho Jun.
- You come to us.
- Let's go.
(Nodding)
- One, two, three.
- Why did you come over?
- We came to catch a killer.
(Getting dragged)
(Who will they choose this time?)
- What killer did you come for?
- We came to catch Killer Haha!
- Why does it have to be me?
- What about us?
- Why won't you save them?
- You won't save these two?
- This is really annoying.
- What about us?
You need someone like me.
Let's go!
You can play.
- I lack confidence.
- That's okay.
- It's okay. Go for it.
- I sacrificed for the gang.
- What about us?
- Go.
- Don't be intimidated.
- You can do it.
Why won't you save Seok Jin?
Good luck!
(He's up against Leon Ha again.)
- Let's do this.
- It must be done in one go.
- Okay.
- Be very sensitive.
(Ho Jun versus Haha, Round Two)
(What will the result be this time?)
Cham, cham, cham.
(Ho Jun lost 2 times in a row.)
- What was that?
- Well done.
- Great.
- Nice one.
- He's the problem.
- Yes.
- You're so shabby!
- Hey, Ho Jun!
- You're...
- Why are you so bad at it?
- Why are you so poor at this?
- Caesar!
- Why are you so weak?
- Why are you so poor at this?
Caesar!
(The simple game turned him pale.)
This is bad.
- Why is he so bad?
- I don't know.
It's okay, Ho Jun.
You can only play twice more.
- We can win once.
- You're so bad at this.
We should play both rounds.
It's our turn this time.
- It's not.
- But...
We must play once more,
and maybe you get the last round.
- Yes.
- That's right.
The audio team says you're rustling,
so don't move much.
What?
- Because of the plastic?
- Was this my idea?
- The movements...
- Audio director.
Was this my idea?
Stand still, old man!
The rustling gets into his mic.
They can't use his audio.
- Don't move.
- Try not to move much.
- Please don't.
- My gosh.
- Put this...
- This is a variety show.
- The plastic...
- How can I stay still on TV?
Don't move.
- That should do it.
- Okay.
It's really hot. I'm not joking.
I'm losing my mind now.
- We'll go first.
- We go first?
- Hey.
- Let's take one round.
Locust Gang, we'll attack once more.
- Okay.
- We'll go once more.
Play one last time. It's okay.
- I really can't.
- No, do it.
- You can do it.
- Ho Jun, you can do it!
You must break through.
You must get a win!
- Okay.
- It's the spirit.
- One, two, three, four.
- Why did you come over?
- We came to catch Killer Haha.
You're so obsessive.
- Come on.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- What about him?
- Why are they so fixated on you?
- The ace...
- What is this about?
- Taunt them. It's okay, Ho Jun.
- Okay.
- Taunt them a bit.
- It's him again?
- Not again?
- Oh, my gosh.
- Will you stop it?
- Make them nervous.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
- Okay? Be a bit...
Goodness.
- Be a bit...
- Stick to your pace.
- Good luck.
- Good luck!
(An enemy he had to let go twice)
Cham, cham, cham!
(Can he beat them this time
after they served him two defeats?)
- Yes!
- You did it!
(Ho Jun won!)
- Well done.
- It happened.
Well done. This is it!
You got the first win. Good.
- I'd decided which way to turn.
- This is it!
- You fell for it.
- Well done. This is it!
- My gosh.
- Come here.
Come here.
- Set things up.
- Come here.
- You need a mustache first.
- Why?
- Yes, a mustache.
- Come here!
- What for?
Stand still,
or I'll kick you in the shin.
- Why are you suddenly...
- Keep still.
Why do you draw only on my face?
Stay still.
He doodles only on my face!
You need this.
(He shows respect out of fear.)
Make that into a crop top.
- A crop top? Okay.
- Yes.
- Don't go too far.
- We're not harassing him!
Why are you so against our gang?
This is a welcoming ceremony!
- Excuse me?
- I'm making a pretty top.
How much flesh will you show?
(How will
the Tiger Gang's design come out?)
The mic has to go in from down here.
Hey, it's looking good.
- Keep still!
Stop this right now.
- We're all about showing skin!
- I have three kids.
I'm a dad of three.
- Keep still!
(The cruel gang doesn't care
for the poor dad's pleas.)
- Don't do this!
- What?
(He's paying
for his past misdemeanors.)
- Don't do it.
- Don't do what?
- Jong Kook, come on!
- Goodness.
You're enjoying this.
- A dad of three...
- We're done.
- Stay still.
- Shouldn't we draw something?
No, don't.
Why would you draw on my belly?
This is bullying.
- What will you draw down there?
- I mean...
- Come here.
- They're drawing on his stomach?
The sun, like KCM's sun.
- What...
- KCM's sun.
- What is this?
- Draw KCM's sun.
What is this?
- There.
- Gosh.
Just wait until you join our gang!
- You!
- Hey!
- Is this a yoga symbol?
- It's a sun.
- Hey.
- Oh, dear.
You humiliated our member.
No. We're showing you
how fierce we are.
- I love it. This is great.
- Haha, here.
- Oh, no.
- Hey.
We'll let you cover your stomach.
Okay. That looks great.
- Let's play.
- I look disgraceful.
- No, you don't.
- You look nice.
- It's cute.
- Let's play.
- How do you look so cute?
- What is this?
- You look adorable.
- They'll come like this.
- One, two...
- One, two, three, four.
- Why did you come over?
- We came to catch Killer Se Chan.
- Okay, fine.
- Hey.
- Make it back.
- If you join us...
- You can strip me if you want!
- Okay.
I'll avenge Haha.
Let's go, Seung Ho!
- Good luck!
- Let's go.
(The Locust Gang's ace Seung Ho
steps up to get revenge.)
- Let's go, Seung Ho.
- Don't worry.
(Will this attack
also be successful?)
Cham, cham, cham!
(Yoo Seung Ho won.)
(Seung Ho did it again!)
- Yes!
- Hang in there, Haha.
- Come here!
- Hang in there.
- Come here.
- Well done. You did great.
- Well done.
- He's in trouble now.
This is so funny.
- You're in trouble.
- Be gentle.
- You're dead meat.
- What do we do now?
This is bad. We're down to three.
Wait. This guy...
I'm like this, to start with.
Boss. This is my starting point.
- What do you want done?
- Kill him.
What do you want? Tell me.
- Make him topless.
- Topless?
- Okay.
- This is bad.
Why do you need that, Boss?
These are his pants.
(These are his pants.)
Come here.
(The locusts are worse
than the tigers.)
(If you expose my family's belly,
we will expose your bottom.)
- His pants... Nice.
- We won.
These are pants.
- Nice.
- Hey, come here.
You punk. How dare you treat
my gang member...
You want me to take my pants off
and wear this?
- This is bad.
- Seriously?
- Take his pants off!
- After taking these off? For real?
- Are they really taking them off?
- My goodness.
After that...
- What? His underpants are red.
- You belittled our gang.
- Hey, just pull those down.
- And a belt.
- Wear a belt.
- There you go.
- His belt.
- What is this?
Oh, no.
Go, you punk.
Get a taste of our gang's power.
This is the absolute worst
among everything I've worn.
It feels so bad.
(Dongducheon Leon barely got to
cover his private parts.)
Hey, that looks pretty.
(Totally satisfied)
Hey, please... Make me look cute.
This just looks unlikable.
- You keep making me unlikable.
- You punk.
- Hey, hang in there for a bit.
- All done.
- Hey, hang in there.
- Just rip it off.
Do I have to dress like this
all day long?
- No, just until...
- Not all day.
- we get to the next location.
- The next location? Darn it.
I have to dress like this
until the next location?
- Of course you should.
- I'll pull this back up there.
- No!
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Please.
- No, you can't!
- You look cute, you punk.
- No!
- All right. Let's go for now.
I have to walk around like this.
Then, you...
- I'm going to rip that off.
- No.
- Okay, fine.
- Darn it.
Here are the results of the mission.
The Locust Gang won.
- Okay!
- You've won the turf.
The benefit of owning this turf...
- will be revealed after we move.
- Okay, let's go!
(The first turf goes to
the Locust Gang.)
- Hit the slate. Daniel, the slate.
- I'll give you this one.
- The slate?
- Hit the slate.
Haha, you have to do it today.
- You have to hit the slate.
- Why should I?
You have to slap your own belly.
- Slap your own belly.
- Slap your belly to hit the slate.
- Why would I do that?
- Slap your belly after 1, 2, 3.
- Yes, do it.
- Lift your belly fat like this.
- That's right.
- Please focus on his belly.
- I'll hit the slate.
I'll hit the slate.
One, two, three.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
I'm going to rip your underwear off.
Seung Ho, come to the back.
- Me?
- Yes, come here.
- Come here.
- Seung Ho, come here.
- Seok Sam, move your arm.
- Watch out.
Hey. I mean...
If you're a staff member
of a gang... You know?
Isn't it not right
to talk down to someone?
I'm not talking down to you.
I'm just talking to you.
Why would you talk like that?
- Then, as the boss of the gang...
- What, talking down to you?
- Look at Haha and say that again.
- Do you think this is a joke, then?
- Everyone, we're kind of cold here.
- Look at Haha.
We'll turn off the air conditioning
over here.
- Come on. You can't turn it off.
- By the way,
who are those two thieves?
(Bursting into laughter)
- You guys must be petty thieves.
- These two.
- These two are petty thieves.
- These guys.
Don't lump me and him together.
- I'll rip his underpants off today.
- This guy...
We're about to go to war.
We'll rip everything off.
Seriously. I'm not lying.
Gosh, I know so many kids
who watch Running Man. This is bad.
By the way, Seung Ho
and Ho Jun's faces both look...
They're both shining.
- I know, right?
- They're just different.
Ho Jun, how old are you?
I was born in 1984.
- What?
- You're not that young.
- You were born in 1984?
- He's a year older than Daniel.
- Yes, he is.
Is that right?
- Is Ho Jun older than you?
- Yes.
- Oh, my.
- Hey, Daniel,
why did you live like that?
- Hey, he is...
- I mean...
He's pretty far gone.
- He is.
- I mean, he doesn't really have...
- a baby face, does he?
- No.
I praised Daniel earlier.
- Why?
- "You're so funny..."
"ever since you gained weight."
"For the sake of a variety show,
you are..."
- Gosh, he's getting a potbelly too.
- But...
- Daniel is developing...
- Seriously.
a proper physique for variety shows.
- He's developing it now.
- I mean...
- But do you know what's funny?
- So...
- What?
- Actually,
- all three of us are actors, but...
- Yes.
I feel like there's a difference,
- so I've lost my confidence.
- You can't think that way.
- Hey, what are you talking about?
- Here, you shine the brightest.
- You shine the most.
You.
I'll pass on
my KCM belly button today.
(I'll pass on
my KCM belly button today.)
- For real.
- You'll become a star.
- A star in the variety show world.
- You have to do it.
- By the way, Seung Ho.
- Yes?
Don't you have any older siblings?
- I have an older sister.
- Oh, you do.
I have a sister who's a year older.
- A year older?
- A sister who's a year older?
How is your relationship
with your sister?
You're not saying anything.
- Got it.
- You must feel awkward.
- It's the same for everyone.
- True siblings.
- She's just... Yes.
- How much older is she?
- A year.
- One year.
- They must be true siblings.
- You must be true siblings.
Wait. Excuse me.
Do I have three legs?
My gosh.
- Gosh, what is this now?
- You're right.
- Where are your manners?
- What are you doing?
- What are you doing to our boss?
- I mean...
- Why are there so many rules here?
- I know, right?
But he's our boss.
- You're being too rude.
- What's too rude?
It's not his seat.
You're supposed to be able to...
Don't cover this up.
(Laughing)
- Fine!
- It's too unlikable.
It's only funny
if you can see glimpses of it.
It's not funny
if you keep seeing it.
- Come on.
- No, don't cover it.
(Doggedly managing his bare belly)
- What?
- He's so annoying.
- Hey, he keeps covering his belly.
- Hey, man.
- Don't cover it up!
- It's not that.
- My belly looks so unlikable.
- Just let it show.
- It's only funny if it's round...
- But you know...
- like Jae Jun's.
- So...
- His belly is kind of awkward.
- Right.
It should be protruding like this.
It's not protruding a lot.
If it's sticking out a whole lot,
we just laugh and move on.
But how should I put it?
Is it like the Uncanny Valley?
(His diagnosis: Uncanny Valley)
I know that too.
- I keep losing confidence.
- So, his belly...
- You know how middle-aged women...
- Yes?
keep their purses here?
I get it now.
(I get why middle-aged women put
their purses here.)
- It's Hongdae? Are we in Hongdae?
- Is this Hongdae?
- Hongdae.
- Why did we come to Hongdae?
I see an R sticker there.
- Gosh, what is this?
- This place looks nice.
- Gosh, the weather is so nice.
- The weather is insane.
- Oh, it must not be time yet.
- This must be a cafe.
This place is beautiful.
This used to be a house,
but they changed it up.
- It's so pretty.
- Gosh, the weather is so nice.
It would be nice
to sit outside here.
- You know what I mean?
- This is so nice.
Should we go inside?
You have to knock
three times with the knocker.
- That's how you can enter.
- Is that so? Got it.
- There must be a quiz.
- Three times.
Is that so?
(Knocking 3 times)
Gosh, what is this?
- What is this?
- Why? What?
- Gosh, what is this?
- What?
- They're idols!
- What...
- What's going on?
- You're back, Miss and Master.
- What?
(You're back, Miss and Master.)
- You're back, Miss and Master.
- What?
(The first turf: A butler cafe)
- What is it?
- This is...
- What?
- They're idols!
- But...
- What?
- Please follow us, your butlers,
- to go to your seats.
- What is this?
Oh, it's a butler cafe.
- Is that so?
- Isn't this a butler cafe?
Whoever comes,
they call you Miss or...
What was that again?
- They look more like stars than us.
- I know.
I thought they were celebrities.
They really look more like stars...
- than us.
- Really?
Oh, hello.
- You're handsome.
- Hello.
- Gosh, what's this?
My outfit is so not proper...
- Hang on a minute.
- Yes?
Isn't there a dress code here?
These are our pet dog and pet cat.
Should we wait outside?
Come here. Come on in.
- Please take your seats.
- Gosh, this is so fascinating.
Ye Eun, you keep...
sitting next to Ho Jun.
Oh, you're right.
Nice to meet you,
Misses and Masters.
I'm Butler Kuro.
- So cute.
- It is a butler cafe.
- Hello.
- So, this is a butler cafe?
- I saw this place on social media.
- A butler cafe.
- I didn't see it.
- There are lots of places like it.
Do you normally work here?
I always reside in this mansion.
(Staying true to his character)
- Please open the menu before you.
- Shall we?
(Rules for Using the Mansion)
- First, to call the butler,
- There are rules.
you may never say, "Excuse me,"
or "Hey, there."
You may ring the butler bell
in front of you...
and ask for what you need in person.
You rang, Miss?
Next, personal contact
with the butlers is prohibited.
Of course,
all of our Misses and Masters...
are overflowing with dignity
and class as members of nobility.
So,
I'm sure that would never happen,
but please refrain
from talking down to...
or using informal speech to us.
There is one person...
- who will have to watch himself.
- He might talk down to you.
- Don't talk down to them.
- No informal speech.
He's the first generation of
the Ugly Korean.
- All right.
- Seriously.
- The Ugly Korean.
- For real.
- By the way, I...
- I'm serious.
He really is the first generation
of the Ugly Korean.
But informal speech is...
- my way of showing affection.
- No.
- You can't do that.
- Don't do it.
- I'll refuse with much gratitude.
- Yes.
- With gratitude.
This place is a hot spot of Mapo,
- the first butler cafe in Korea.
- Can we have assigned butlers?
Earlier, during the mission,
the Locust Gang's killers...
successfully won over this turf.
You will become
the masters and mistress...
and enjoy this place
as much as you want.
The gang that lost...
can only sit outside...
- and have coffee.
- That sounds amazing!
I like that.
- He seems so happy.
- Why are you happy?
- The weather is so nice.
- The weather is...
- nice outside.
- However, regardless of who won,
the killers who have been taken
to the other team...
will become butlers themselves...
and provide services to the members.
(The Tiger Gang won the final chance
at offense during the mission.)
- We came to catch Killer Se Chan.
- Me? Will you save me?
- Hey, you jerk!
- But why?
- We need an active guy.
- Hey, but...
Cham, cham, cham!
- Okay.
- Nice.
(They successfully saved
Killer Se Chan...)
(who was taken hostage
as he's performing well.)
The butlers are Seok Jin,
- Ye Eun, and Haha.
- Looking like this?
- The three of you are butlers.
- Me too?
- But our team won.
- You lost.
- You couldn't go back to your team.
- Hang on, Director.
Does the butler not get to eat?
- They can, right?
- No, they can't.
- They can't?
- No.
- No, the butler...
- But the winning team...
may choose one extra person
from the losing team...
to become an additional butler.
- Yes, so now,
- Anyone?
among Jong Kook, Ho Jun,
and Se Chan,
you may choose one person
to become a butler.
- A butler?
- Yes.
- Hey, but you know,
- Him.
- Ho Jun suits this place visually.
- He looks awful.
Come on.
(Come on.)
(Making his case
with beads of sweat rolling down)
He's sweating.
- Go outside. I'll think about it.
- Are you ready?
- You must look that good to be...
- I'll think about it.
Those of you who are butlers...
- Oh, there's a training part too.
- must receive training.
They have to receive training too?
(Ringing)
- Oh, Poro.
- Poro.
- Pororo?
- Pororo.
- You rang, Master?
What...
(Butler Poro,
has a belly button tattoo)
Poro, as in Pororo.
I look so unlikable.
Do you deliver things
with your nose?
Yes. You rang?
You rang, Master?
Well, we've received training.
With one eye covered,
it's kind of...
Watch out.
- Kusa?
- Kusa.
(Ho Jun is chosen as a butler.)
- You rang, Miss?
- Don't laugh. Be cultured.
My goodness.
- Koro.
- Around his neck...
Do they change into the outfits too?
(Surviving thanks to Ho Jun, Se Chan
and Jong Kook have coffee outside.)
They wear the outfits too?
Let's order for now.
- Yes.
- I'll have...
the Afternoon Tea Set
with peppermint tea.
I'll also have
the Afternoon Tea Set...
- with English Breakfast tea.
- Yes.
I'll have the strawberry latte.
I'll have the afternoon tea set.
Can I also have a strawberry latte,
with less sugar?
- Sure.
- Beauty...
(Just then)
Beauty...
was only added to the dictionary
after the birth...
of the young ladies
and gentlemen here.
- Nice.
- That was sweet.
Are they going around
saying nice things to us?
He sounds well-educated, doesn't he?
After serving them,
you must always praise
the young ladies and gentlemen.
"Beauty..."
"was only added to the dictionary
after the birth..."
"of the young ladies
and gentlemen here."
- Beauty...
(He memorized it.)
- I took my training seriously.
- Anchovy...
- Well...
- Please don't...
stick your hand out like that.
Master,
your face has bloated immensely,
and now you're even more beautiful
than the steamed bun I'm eating.
(Clapping)
- What was that?
- You've gained a lot of weight.
- You look stunning.
- What was that?
- What?
- I only say kind words.
How was that kind?
Meanwhile,
- Master,
- Yes?
you're like an anchovy.
You look like
you have strong bones...
like an anchovy.
What is this?
We received our training
for the day.
- We received our training.
- We can't say bad things.
- Miss...
- We can't say negative things.
- Miss,
- Yes?
you seem to be quite the charmer.
Is this a bell?
(Is this a bell?)
(Ringing the sun-bellybutton clock)
(Whimpering)
How rude of you!
(Leaving his post)
You shouldn't touch them.
- Of course. Sorry about that.
- No physical contact.
- I'm sorry I touched you.
- Hands off, please.
Okay.
(Jong Kook calls over Haha
after he sprinted out of the room.)
Butler Poro.
(These masters seem more difficult.)
Can you lift up your top a bit more?
- All right.
- Lift up your top a bit more.
- Hello, Masters.
Okay.
- Did you need something?
- We'll go with this.
- We'll have decaffeinated...
- Decaffeinated...
- iced Americano.
- Two of that.
- Yes, two.
Can we order something to eat?
Something to eat?
I'm afraid that won't be possible
since you're seated outside.
Goodness, foreigners.
- What...
- Don't cover your belly.
- Don't cover it up.
- Cover your face instead.
Sir.
You have a muffin top.
- Even with the belt...
- How rude of you!
(Slap)
- I'm quitting.
- Hold on.
- Where are you going?
- Come on.
Get back here!
How can they be this rude?
They're so rude.
(The butler, immersed
in his character, sheds tears.)
I can't continue to do this.
Why are you filming my belly?
Butler Poro ran away.
Shouldn't someone grab him?
- Haha ran away.
- Someone should chase after him.
(They're about to chase after Haha.)
- I can't be humiliated like this.
- He's back.
(Running around the Hongdae area
with his stomach exposed.)
(He was told
he'd be a formidable killer.)
(But Candy was tricked
into taking a different job.)
It's Butler Kusa.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Hey, Butler Kusa.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Can you stay and explain
the coffee we're drinking?
- Really?
- Yes.
- Since it's hot outside,
- Yes?
the coffee has been cooled down
with an adequate amount of ice,
and the right amount of water
has been added to the espresso.
Nicely put. Good job.
- Okay.
- We're in the same gang.
May I get a sip?
- He's a member of our gang.
- You're right.
Butler Kusa wants some,
- so he'll get a sip.
- Sure.
Why don't we play
the Cham, Cham, Cham game...
and let the winner take a sip?
- Between the two of them?
- The Cham, Cham, Cham game?
- Sure.
- With this?
- How about the crane camera?
- Which one?
Cham, cham, cham. Like this.
- Go ahead, then.
- Sure.
- I'll go first.
- The winner gets a sip.
- Right.
(The Cham, Cham, Cham rivals
go head to head.)
Cham, cham, cham.
- Nice!
- Okay.
(Haha succeeds.)
(How will Ho Jun do
when he's bad at this game?)
- All right.
- Ho Jun, you're up.
Cham, cham, cham.
- I won.
- Goodness.
- Why is he so bad at this?
- He's terrible at this game.
Why are you so bad at this game?
Beats me.
Thank you.
Enough!
You only get one sip, you punk.
(Slap)
Seriously.
You were begging for it.
(Butler Poro was begging
to be slapped on the belly.)
Mr. Kuro.
Butler Kuro,
they've been teasing me.
(He brings over his mentor.)
- Butler Kuro.
- I tried to serve them gracefully,
but they keep making fun
of my belly.
- Well...
- I want to quit.
Everything the masters say is true.
- What we say is true?
- That's right.
- Our word is his command.
- Lift it up.
- Lift up your top, Butler Poro.
- More.
- We were only commenting...
about how the outfit should be.
We weren't trying...
- to make him show more skin.
- Exactly.
Why do you keep hiding your belly?
Don't suck in your belly either.
- Leave it as is.
- What now?
Butler Kusa.
- Here.
- How long will it take?
- They're here.
- Here's your order.
- Butler Kororok.
- Yes?
- Thank you.
- This looks delicious.
Here's the strawberry latte
you ordered.
- But...
- This is less sweet.
- The English breakfast.
- Right. Thank you.
- It's good.
- It looks delicious.
Turn these so that
they don't block our faces.
I'm sorry but...
Don't touch them yourselves!
- What do you think you're doing?
- What?
What...
- I'm sorry.
- Butler Koro.
Why can't you speak properly?
I'm sorry.
I'm out of my comfort zone.
Were you scolding us?
- It's not that. I apologize.
- Right.
- Allow me.
- Sure.
- Can I have some wet wipes?
- Wet wipes?
Wet wipes, please.
Can I get a wet wipe?
- Just a second.
- I felt like I was at a diner.
Should a butler talk like that?
- But...
- This is frustrating.
- Can they yell like that?
- Wet wipes, please!
Here are the wet wipes.
- Could you...
- What would you like to have?
First of all...
Gosh, that looks tasty.
(The masters now enjoy the food.)
It's good.
Goodness.
(Even elegantly having
a crme brle)
This is good.
- It's so good.
- The strawberry latte is delicious.
(Stomping his feet)
- Jae Seok, this.
- Is it that good?
- Hurry.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
(The sweet dessert
brings out his cuteness.)
(Gulping)
- It's so good.
- The strawberry latte is delicious.
(Every time the masters
eat something)
- This should be cut.
- I see.
- That looks delicious.
- Unbelievable.
- And now...
- Yes?
- You can leave us.
Hold on.
(The butlers will now leave
since they've done their jobs.)
- That's not it.
- We're supposed to stay.
Don't stick around
and dismiss yourselves.
(Master Seung Ho uses that opportunity
to grant a favor.)
(Munching)
- I could peel the wrapper off.
- It's too dry.
(Laughing)
(Glancing)
(He is granted another favor.)
- Should I feed you?
- Seung Ho.
- Butler Kusa.
- It's all right.
The cake was too dry.
- Seriously.
- I'm sorry.
You must personally know
Master Seung Ho,
but that doesn't give you
the right to eat the food.
Shouldn't we be allowed to eat...
what the masters give us?
- What?
- Your word is our command.
Thank you.
I see.
- Have the butlers seen this?
- Excuse me?
- See what?
- You'll be performing live.
- A live show.
- We didn't catch that.
(A live show is listed on the menu.)
Perform live for us later on.
- We should see the show.
- Are you hoping to see it?
- We'll order the half show.
- The live show.
Is a live show on the menu?
(From flawless group dancing...)
(to being charming enough
to entertain the ladies)
Do I call them the butlers?
All butlers,
- let's prepare for our show.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
- You shouldn't...
- It's in English.
- dance the moves with force.
- It goes like this.
- Keep it light?
This is the concept of this dance.
- Can you show me?
- It goes like this.
- Here.
- The signature move is this.
Should we start off with this?
- Right.
- Left foot, then right. And left.
- Too bad?
- Like this.
- "Touch My Body?"
- That's English.
- Please do your best.
- Sure.
(Gently)
Butler Kusa, aren't you
sweating too much?
Your sideburns are soaked.
"Touch My Body" is a good option.
I feel bad for Ho Jun.
- I feel terrible.
- Please do your best.
- Sure.
- Butler Kusa,
- you'll have our attention.
- Sure.
Please give it your best.
Got it.
(What's the performance
that has Ho Jun trembling?)
What about Can's song?
- Whose song? "Barefooted Youth?"
- "Barefooted Youth."
Masters, Miss.
- Okay.
- Go for it.
Thank you!
(Sounding like a show host)
- That's how you do it.
- Thank you...
for being at our cafe today.
We're joined by a new butler.
Ho Jun, Son Ho Jun.
I don't know if he knows this song,
but he'll do his best.
- Go around in a circle.
- Let's party.
(The camera follows them
involuntarily.)
Okay!
Bring the beat.
(The cameras can't help
but film the star-studded lineup.)
- Let's go.
- Move.
Ho Jun, let's go!
(No connections and no vision)
No...
- No connections
- Let's go!
(He chokes right off the bat.)
How many times were you going
to kick off the song?
That was due to a lack of practice.
How many times were you going
to kick off the song?
What more do you want from us?
Is this a team gathering
for the butlers?
- What?
- What on earth is this?
(They were having fun,
regardless of the audience.)
We wanted to watch a performance.
Who was that performance for?
- Who was that for?
- Hold on.
I'll sing a better song.
- We'll sing something better.
- Something better.
- We should make a request.
- Of course.
- Butler Kusa.
- Yes?
Is there a song
you can confidently sing?
Oh, "Unpredictable Life..."
- Oh, "Unpredictable Life?"
- Oh, the song?
- The song by Lee Moon Sae?
- Yes.
Is that the song that goes
like "Bravo?"
- No, it's not.
- That's weird.
- By Lee Moon Sae.
- Okay, Lee Moon Sae.
- Let's go.
- It's so eye-catching.
Yes, thank you to everyone...
- who has come today.
- What is this?
(The cheap MC barges in again.)
Seriously, what is that?
- What are you doing?
- What is this, a dinner show?
- What is this?
- This time...
Our club is always open to you.
- Swa.
- This time,
we have a newbie butler.
It is...
Son Kusa!
When will I Know all about love?
About love
When will I know
all about the world?
About the world
(Why am I here
and why am I doing this?)
(Life really is so unpredictable.)
(Singing his heart out)
- Can't I?
Can't you delay it
(Holding back his laughter)
Is this a 70th birthday party
or something?
- Seung Ho seems so uncomfortable.
- It's like...
I'm at a team dinner.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Turn off the music!
It is too
Is this a team dinner?
- Gosh, we're sorry.
- I mean...
- Is this a team dinner?
- Well, then... Something else.
Why are you playing the tambourine?
- I wanted to make you happy.
- Then,
- if you give us one more chance...
- Try the performance once more.
- Give us one last chance.
- All right.
- Do what we asked you for.
- Okay.
- Do something exciting.
- I know.
Can't you make things
a little more exciting?
- Can't you do it?
- We're here to have fun.
- All right.
- Sorry. We have a special talent.
What is it?
This is seriously your last chance.
So, our Butler Ye Eun...
I mean, Butler Kororok...
"Be My Baby."
- "Be My Baby?" Yes, I know this.
- "Be My Baby."
- All right. "Be My Baby."
- Hey, you have to pull this off.
- I have to pull it off.
- If not, we'll get fired.
For real, I'll dance in front.
- I mean, this is their last chance.
- Seriously.
Please give us one last chance,
Master.
Also, stop talking.
Please stop talking
during the performance.
That's such an outdated thing to do.
- In that case, I will...
- Outdated thing to do.
Ye Eun, focus on the dance.
Hello, everyone!
Yes, thanks...
Thank you so much
for coming to our cafe!
- So,
- Gosh, I'm sweating.
the highlight of this show.
The performance by our butlers.
Please welcome them
with a round of applause!
(Good luck?)
As I keep watching, waiting
I hope you approach me
(Getting the lyrics wrong)
- Nice!
- You're doing well!
- Dreaming, I hope you feel the same
- Yes!
- This is the song I know, right?
- Yes, it is rather...
(A performance where the lyrics
and pitch are all unclear.)
(Why is this the pride
of Seok Sam Nightclub?)
(Her insane spirit)
- Here she goes.
- Say that
- You've got this!
- I love you
Two, three, four!
Please be my baby
(Please be my baby)
(Sprinkling cute acts
with every breath)
I feel like I might go crazy
- Because I want you so badly
- My goodness.
To the left. Go.
- Nice.
- Go.
(The MC, choreography, and spirit
were all perfect.)
- Nice.
- Thank you so much.
- Great.
- We did our best. Yes.
Did you vomit at the end?
I think I heard wretching.
Nice.
- I think you vomited at the end.
- Awesome!
- That was nice.
- It was.
- That was great.
- It really was.
- Gosh, that was awesome.
- It was great.
- This one was nice.
- Good job.
If not for this,
we wouldn't have paid.
- Right.
- Who are they kidding?
- Goodness. Thank you.
- That's right.
Give us lots of love. Thank you!
Thank you.
- We'll pay our bill now.
- Thank you.
- We'll pay the bill now.
- Pardon? Pay your bill?
- Oh, we should get the bill.
- The bill?
- How much...
- You were so good.
- Should we ask for 2,700 dollars?
- Yes.
Let's give it to them for
1,750 dollars since they're family.
- Okay, 1,750 dollars.
- Yes, 1,750 dollars.
- It's 1,750 dollars.
- Go and tell them.
- Shall we go outside now?
Tell them.
- Gosh, that was hilarious.
- Oh, that was a nice snack.
- You have to pay.
- So, which master will be paying?
Pardon?
Your total bill is 1,750 dollars.
- What did you say?
- What did he say?
- Your total is 1,750 dollars...
- Be confident.
Your total bill is 1,750 dollars.
Bring me the bill.
While I'm being nice...
(While I'm being nice...)
- You should pay...
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
- I mean...
- What was that?
- What are you doing?
- Why are you sweating so much?
- I mean...
What are you doing?
- Okay!
- Gosh, I'm thirsty.
Drink water if you're thirsty.
I'm thirsty.
Ye Eun,
can you grab me one on your way?
- Thanks. A bottle of water.
- What?
- Thanks, Ye Eun.
- Sure. Who wants some water?
Ye Eun, you're so annoying
ever since you lost weight.
- Because I've gotten prettier?
- What?
(Suddenly being mean)
- "Because I've gotten prettier?"
- No.
By the way,
you're very pretty in person.
- Is that so?
- You're very pretty in person.
- Really?
- Hey, don't say that.
- Don't say that stuff.
- It'll spoil her.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Ye Eun might not...
- be able to sleep.
- I used to really like Seung Ho.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Why?
- She's flirting again,
- Jae Seok.
- Flirting with who?
- With Seung Ho.
- No, but he said I was pretty.
- Because he said she was pretty.
- He said she was pretty in person.
He said she looks better in person,
and she said she used to like him.
- Really? But...
- Yes.
- You just look better than on TV.
- Right.
- I'm sure Seung Ho wouldn't lie,
- Yes.
but as soon as the shoot is over,
he'll get in his van
and leave right away.
- That's right.
- I'm sure he will.
I'm on board if it's Seung Ho.
- Ye Eun.
- What?
- Hey, what is this place?
- Gosh, what is this?
The second turf
you must take over is...
the pink-hued instant tteokbokki
restaurant that killers love.
- It's tteokbokki.
- Instant tteokbokki.
(The second turf:
An instant tteokbokki restaurant)
How nice.
The gang that wins the turf war...
- can eat as much as they'd like.
- Okay!
But the losing gang
must go back to the car,
and they can only enter
the restaurant...
when the winning team
calls them for an errand.
- That's the most annoying.
- Today's mission is hard.
The mission with lunch on the line
is Ball Security Area.
You must steal the ball
from one another.
When stealing the ball,
you can only use your feet.
- Feet only.
- Nice.
Can there be no physical contact?
- That doesn't matter.
- Okay, contact doesn't matter.
Oh, okay.
(This is
the Tiger Gang's specialty.)
(Round 1: Se Chan and Ho Jun
versus Daniel and Seung Ho)
All right.
Good job. That's it.
- Go.
- Daniel.
- This is...
- It's okay.
- Okay!
- Okay, we won.
We'll be able to eat.
(Next, Round 2: Jong Kook and Se Chan
versus Jae Seok and Daniel)
- Jong Kook.
- No.
- Hey, Jong Kook! This one!
- Hey, stop him.
Jong Kook, three of them. Yes, nice.
Take that.
- Stop it.
- Okay.
- Okay!
- What was that?
- What just happened?
- Yes!
The Tiger Gang won.
Hey, how can he...
Then, the Locust Gang can go...
- to the car now.
- Wait there.
Okay, go and wait. Hey!
- My goodness.
- My gosh.
- But it sounds so delicious.
- Gosh, I'm tired.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, I wanted to win...
- the lunch mission.
- I know, right?
- Oh, right.
- If we press this...
- Okay.
- Oh, will they come?
- I'll leave it with you, Seok Jin.
Hey, if you have anything you want,
feel free to call those guys.
- What should we ask them for?
- In that case...
- Let's see if this works or not.
- Yes, check it.
Yu Jae Seok.
He went to the restroom.
- Have him hurry up.
- Hey, wait.
What's with her tone of voice?
Have her come in here.
Oh, do you have to hold it?
Hey, Song Ji Hyo.
Get in here for a second.
Ji Hyo just went to the restroom.
Gosh, they can't do this.
- Say that I went to the restroom.
- Okay.
If they ask where you are,
we'll say you're in the restroom.
(The butlers have
no intention of being obedient.)
We should make Seok Jin angry.
Hey, Seung Ho. Tell me.
Tell me which ones went
to the restroom.
Seung Ho just went to the restroom.
- Was that Ji Hyo?
- It was.
- Tell Ji Hyo...
- Ask if they all went as a group.
- They went together.
- Did he go with Ji Hyo?
- How does that make sense?
- It was Ji Hyo?
Then, Song Ji Hyo,
get in here right now.
Get in here!
(Suddenly being stern)
Seok Jin, this is Seung Ho.
Everyone went to the restroom.
- Seok Jin, you should go out there.
- He learned something bad.
(He learned something bad.)
- You should go. Go to the bus.
- Yes, you should go.
(The oldest killer in the industry
can't take it and gets up.)
- Go and sort them all out.
- Gosh, I'm so mad.
- Seok Jin, yell at them.
- I am...
Gosh, I'm so mad.
I'm so angry.
(He sets off to tighten
their lax discipline.)
Hey!
Take turns to go to the restroom,
all right?
- Okay.
- Got it?
- All right.
- Don't go all at the same time.
- Okay.
The concept is that you guys
have to come to us.
- Got it.
- Okay.
- I shouldn't come to you, okay?
- All right.
- We understand.
- Before I get mad!
- All right.
- Okay, take turns...
- as you go to the restroom.
- Okay.
I'm watching you.
Gosh, these punks.
They're making me mad.
- I showed them who's boss.
- Good.
- Did you teach them a lesson?
- Were they all there?
- They were.
- Seok Jin, try calling them again.
I told them to take turns
when going to the restroom.
Oh, good job.
Then call someone now.
Call whoever is last to go.
Yu Jae Seok,
come in here for a second.
Seok Jin,
I'm in the restroom right now.
He said he was in the restroom.
(His lesson didn't make
any difference.)
Hey! Yoo Seung Ho.
You should get in here.
Please, I'm asking you a favor.
Seok Jin, I'll be right there
after I pee. One second.
They can't do this!
- Seok Jin, just... One person...
- Jong Kook, you should call them.
Say that we'll feed one of them.
Have someone come.
- Let's try that.
- Whoever comes can eat.
We'll feed
whoever gets in here first.
We'll feed you something good,
so get in here quickly!
- They'll come if we do this.
- Will they come?
And when they come,
we'll have them work.
We'll feed
whoever gets in here first.
We'll feed you something good,
so get in here quickly!
(Suddenly getting up)
(Their gang falls apart right away.)
- No, Haha.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay, rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Darn it.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- My goodness. Seriously?
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
- Hang on.
- Why is it that...
- This is a trap.
- It's a trap. They won't feed you.
- Let's see.
- Here he comes. It's Haha.
- Seok Jin, I used the restroom.
- Okay.
Why did you guys use the restroom
as a group?
- Thank you, Seok Jin.
- Put that down, Haha.
- To eat...
- Thank you for your hard work.
- Show your stomach.
- Yes.
Show your stomach.
- That's over.
- Come on.
- Show your stomach...
- Do it.
- and bring that.
- Come on.
- Will you really give me food?
- Yes, of course.
- Of course.
- Go and bring the food.
- Let me get ready first.
Okay. Show your stomach.
I called Seung Ho, but you came.
Did you erase it?
The food will be tasty.
- His belly is cute.
- Haha, your belly is so cute.
(He begins to serve food
with his belly hanging out.)
- There you go.
- His belly is cute.
(The customers
are highly satisfied.)
- This is fun.
- His belly is cute.
It's cute.
- It's cute.
- Let's give it to Haha.
- Haha should eat...
- since he works hard.
- That's right.
- He's good.
- Come here. They must be watching.
Well done.
(He puts on a show
in order to eat tteokbokki.)
Well done.
- Haha.
- Here.
Well done.
(He gets a flat dumpling.)
(Are you jealous?)
Gosh, he's so vulgar.
Seriously.
I can't believe him.
(Gulping)
- We'll give you more.
(Seung Ho is jealous
of the vulgar traitor.)
Come here, Haha.
We need to tempt them.
- It's cute.
- It looks delicious.
- French fries. It looks tasty.
- It looks tasty.
- Let's eat.
- It looks so tasty.
- It's no joke.
- It looks tasty.
- Take a seat.
- Gosh, it looks so tasty.
- It looks tasty.
(The chewy flour cake
has absorbed the soup.)
(Se Chan eats the noodles first.)
This place has tasty food.
(Food Fighter wraps the noodles
with fishcake and takes a bite.)
- It's really tasty.
- I know.
(Food Fighter wraps the noodles
with fishcake and takes a bite.)
- It's perfect now.
- Ramyeon is really tasty.
(Butler Son had to eat bread
with caution earlier.)
- Haha.
- That's right. Enjoy the food.
Daniel can show his stomach.
It's cute.
(He eats without reservation.)
(My goodness)
(The Locust Gang is suffering
due to hunger.)
- It must be tasty.
- I'm hungry.
- Seriously.
- I want to eat tteokbokki.
- I really want to eat it.
- I haven't had it for so long.
We aren't how we used to be.
By any chance...
(Why did he suddenly pick up
the walkie-talkie?)
- Do you need one more person?
- Yoo Seung Ho.
- For goodness' sake.
- Seung Ho.
(Smiling)
- Come on.
- Whoever comes first...
will switch places with Haha.
This applies
to whoever comes first. Go.
Who will it be?
- We're set.
- Don't give him more food.
(Big Nose makes
a generous proposal.)
What? Are you going to go?
Is that why you're giving it to me?
Seung Ho is coming.
- Should I go now?
- Yes, you should go now.
- Hey.
- Seung Ho.
- I want to drink some water.
- What?
- Water.
(Seung Ho becomes the new server.)
- Haha, go.
- Go.
Coca-Cola.
(He stuffs his face
until the very end.)
- Coca-Cola.
- Haha, go.
(Meanwhile, Seung Ho
delivers Coca-Cola.)
- The server is quite nice.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
- This is so nice.
(What's so nice?)
- Haha.
- It's so tasty.
- Haha, what's wrong with you?
- What?
Hey, they let you eat anything
if you show your belly.
(Hey, they let you eat anything
if you show your belly.)
Really?
Don't let your pride get in the way.
It's so tasty.
Why did you come back?
They told me to go.
If you dance
with your belly showing,
they'll ask you to come in. I swear.
Daniel.
(Haha tempts him to sell his soul
for tteokbokki.)
Seung Ho is ready
to show his belly too.
What is Seung Ho doing?
He keeps serving instead of eating.
- Seung Ho, you should open it.
- That's right.
- You should open it.
Thank you.
Why...
Can't he eat with us?
Hey, Ji Ye Eun.
- Focus, okay?
- Ye Eun.
"Can't he eat with us?"
Don't speak nonsense.
- There are rules.
- This isn't the right time.
- Hey.
- Don't speak nonsense.
- Do you think we're at that cafe?
- Right now...
This is a different place.
I want to eat with him.
Hey.
Take one.
- You should eat one. Right?
- Dip it in the soup.
Take one.
- One.
- One?
One. That's right.
No. Take one. Don't do that.
Don't do that.
- That's... Hey!
- One.
- Oh, my.
- That's...
(He runs off with the cup!)
Look at that. He's a spy.
- That's cute.
- He...
(That's cute.)
Hey.
How is that cute?
- What's wrong with you?
- How is that cute?
What's wrong with you?
- He's incredible.
- My goodness.
- Eat it.
- What?
- My goodness.
- What's this?
- Seung Ho.
- Seung Ho doesn't disappoint.
He's different from you.
- He's really different from me.
- He's different from Haha.
- You're...
- You're seriously hopeless.
He's something else.
- I can do the same.
- It'll be really tasty...
with tteokbokki soup.
It should be dipped
in tteokbokki soup.
(The taste makes them
crave tteokbokki.)
It's tasty.
(My goodness)
It's so tasty.
- Gosh, it's so tasty.
- It's tasty.
- What was that?
- Seung Ho, what was that?
What was that?
He's an enemy.
Did Seung Ho come back? What's this?
- Did you come back?
- What's this?
- I...
- I mean...
- What's wrong with you?
- Hey.
- I'll get you some water.
- You should've left...
- after that.
- How could you face us...
after pulling that stunt?
- I'll pour you water.
- He kneeled.
- My goodness.
- After hearing...
- that she's prettier in person...
- Hey, Yoo Seung Ho.
- What is the butler doing here?
- What?
(Haha entered the place to see
if there was something to eat.)
Why did you come back?
We didn't call you.
(Whistling)
You should show your stomach.
- You need to show your stomach.
- Look at this guy.
(Meanwhile,
Daniel becomes thoughtful.)
Gosh, why would I bet my life
on tteokbokki?
- That's right.
- Gosh.
I can eat tteokbokki when I go home.
Seriously.
(What?)
Gosh.
(Daniel shows his belly
as soon as he gets out of the car.)
Hey.
(Here comes a belly dancer.)
(The 2nd dance is twerking.)
- Hey.
- Daniel.
- Yes?
- Your belly isn't cute.
You should stick it out a bit.
He just showed it.
- He plucked up his courage.
- Show it.
Haha.
Show him how one's belly should be.
- Show him how cute it should be.
- His belly...
(Ta-da!)
(Prince Pot Belly gives
a nice demonstration.)
- Seriously.
- You don't have a belly.
I can't do it.
I'm hungry.
(Even as the others show skin,
Seung Ho remains composed.)
It's so tasty.
(Even as the others show skin,
Seung Ho remains composed.)
If you show your belly...
(Staring)
(He's filling his stomach
with water.)
(Glancing over)
Why isn't Jae Seok coming?
(Eat this.)
Ji Ye Eun, you're ridiculous.
You're feeding him.
- What a mess.
- You're ridiculous.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
He's a guest.
He's in the opposing gang.
- Come here.
- What?
(She invites him to the seat
next to hers.)
Sit here.
Are you inviting him to your house?
(Are you inviting him
to your house?)
My goodness.
(He goes as he's called.)
- The food is tasty.
- Seriously.
It's really tasty.
- Would you get me chopsticks?
- Of course.
Would you get me chopsticks
and a plate?
Will you share food with him?
It's so nice.
(Eat comfortably.)
Jong Kook.
- Ye Eun gave a plate...
- Ye Eun, what are you doing?
to Seung Ho.
- Hey.
- Did you give it to Seung Ho?
What are you doing?
- Eat.
- The two of them...
- If you eat this,
- Ye Eun...
you have to go out with me.
(If you eat this,
you have to go out with me.)
- If you eat this,
- Ye Eun...
you have to go out with me.
(It turns out that the meal came
with a hefty price.)
Seung Ho, run out.
(Halting)
Hey, date her briefly and break up.
(A clean piece of advice
from a total thinker)
Hey, date her briefly and break up.
- Seriously.
- Break up after the shoot.
Hey, date her briefly and break up.
(He eats it.)
This is our first day as a couple.
That's right.
(They're Romeo and Juliet
of the killer scene.)
- Jae Seok...
- All right.
(Daniel begins eating.)
It's so tasty.
- It's tasty, right?
- Yes.
- They seem very amicable.
- Really?
- Is Seung Ho sitting down?
- Seung Ho...
Yes, Seung Ho is sitting down
as well.
Jae Seok won't come until the end.
Is Jae Seok a director?
What's up with Jae Seok?
What's up with him?
(Seok Jin is frustrated
that he can't make Jae Seok come.)
(Is Ji Hyo surrendering?)
- That's right.
- Ji Hyo.
Welcome.
It isn't like that.
Jae Seok is waiting for you.
He's waiting for you.
He has so much to say to you.
Leave him be.
- Really?
- He really has something to say.
- Seok Jin.
- Really?
Seok Jin, I'm curious.
Would you please go just once?
I'm so curious.
Seok Jin, please go just once.
(Others want it, he's curious,
and he likes feeling important.)
For goodness' sake.
Hold on a second.
It's annoying, but I can't hold back
since I'm so curious.
(Due to the three reasons,
Seok Jin goes to the car.)
He's coming.
Hey.
- The rule... Why aren't you coming?
- Why are you doing this?
The rule...
To make you do something.
What do you want me to do?
An errand.
- I'm the boss of a gang.
- What about it?
I won't move easily
like my underlings.
What do I need to do then?
- In that case...
- What do you want?
Give me a plate of tteokbokki
and fritters.
I'm too annoyed
to bring them readily.
(What will be the result
of this negotiation?)
Hey, open the door.
Hurry up and open the door.
(He delivers tteokbokki.)
Here he comes.
It's time to go.
(The prankster escapes.)
(He visits the empty car.)
I can't believe him.
- There's a lot.
- I lost.
- What?
- How about Seok Jin?
Seok Jin went to see you.
How annoying.
(Seok Jin got fooled today as well.)
- How annoying.
- Seok Jin.
- Didn't you see him?
- You brought it.
Forget it.
- Seok Jin went out for a walk.
- My goodness.
- They missed each other.
- Oh, no.
- No.
- You brought it.
- I didn't bring it.
- Boss Kook.
- Go ahead and eat.
- Okay.
Don't sit down. You can't sit down.
- You can't sit down.
- Ji Hyo.
- What?
- This is my boyfriend's seat.
- Your boyfriend?
- This is driving me crazy.
This is my boyfriend's seat.
- Sit down.
- My boyfriend, sit down.
- Hey.
- You guys use a polite tone.
- You...
- Thank you, my girlfriend.
How could you abandon your family
just because you got a boyfriend?
How are you a member
of the Chungju Ji Clan?
Dad, that's how it is.
I can't believe you.
Are you going to eat like this?
Are you eating?
Are you eating
without my permission?
I'm sorry,
but aren't you an underling?
I can't believe these punks.
Hey, did you give him permission?
Sit down.
(Jong Kook orders him to sit down.)
You haven't done anything right.
- Don't ruin the atmosphere.
- It isn't like that.
Before we move to the next location,
- the two gangs should choose...
- Okay.
between inside and outside.
- What's that?
- The choices must be different.
(They must choose
between inside and outside.)
- Outside is better.
- As for us...
We should choose outside as well.
Then we'll need to compete for it.
Is that so?
(Laughing)
What's wrong with Ye Eun today?
Isn't she particularly strange today?
Seriously.
- She keeps twisting her body.
- She's particularly strange today.
- It's worse than usual. Hey.
- You know,
- Ho Jun...
- What does that make Ho Jun?
(Ddochi doesn't care
about Ho Jun at all.)
- Ho Jun looks so pitiful.
- For goodness' sake.
- What does that make Ho Jun?
- He's spacing out.
- Hey.
- Ho Jun looks unhealthy today.
- Seung Ho.
- Ho Jun is angry.
(She's excited by herself.)
What should we do?
Should we talk it out?
- Rock-paper-scissors?
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Ho Jun and Seung Ho should play
rock-paper-scissors.
- Ho Jun and Seung Ho.
- Yes.
- Ye Eun.
- The winner gets to choose.
You should root for him.
- Go ahead.
- I can't do it.
Isn't she on our team?
- Isn't she on our team?
- She's on our team.
Ji Ye Eun, you should root
for Ho Jun.
- I told her to root for Ho Jun.
- Why would you root for Seung Ho?
(For goodness' sake!)
Why is she rooting for her boyfriend
instead of her teammate?
What is it?
I don't want to play
rock-paper-scissors.
- Shall we just choose inside?
- No.
All right.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seung Ho wins.)
Nothing is working out
for Ho Jun today.
- Ho Jun just can't win.
- Let's choose inside.
- Shall we do that?
- Yes.
- Okay.
We'll choose inside.
- We'll choose inside.
- Really?
The Locust Gang will take
the inside.
The Tiger Gang will take
the outside.
I'll explain the meaning
once we reach the new location.
- Okay.
- What's that?
Will we be in different areas?
We'll be outside for real.
- Okay.
- Are we on this side?
- They must've made it.
- We're outside.
They made this structure.
- My goodness.
- There's something.
- They must've made it.
- Jong Kook, there's something.
- That's right.
This place is nice.
- Sit down, Ho Jun.
- We're outside.
- We can feel it.
- Being outside is nice.
- I like being outside.
- The weather is so good.
- They must've made it.
- Seok Jin.
- It isn't a real building.
- It's so nice.
It's nice.
I like it today.
- I like being outside.
- It's nice.
(Meanwhile,
the Locust Gang chose inside.)
What's up with the atmosphere?
- Why is it...
- Why is it suddenly so scary?
- Why do you look so serious?
- What's this?
What's going on?
- Why is it so solemn?
- We suddenly became quiet.
- It's the killers' hideout.
What?
We can't call ourselves killers now.
We lost our charisma.
It feels more like a butler cafe.
It ended after I showed my stomach.
I'm the only one who maintained
the vibe of a killer.
It ended the moment you showed
your stomach.
The last turf war
that'll determine...
the final winner is...
the Killing X.
In the set amount of time,
find the other gang's flag
that's hidden in their turf...
- in order to win.
- It's a war of flags.
A flag.
If neither gang fails
to retrieve the flag,
the gang that has
more surviving members will win.
The Tiger Gang chose outside.
They can hide the flag outside,
including the headquarters.
(Tiger Gang's turf: Front yard
of the outdoor headquarters)
The Locust Gang chose inside.
They can hide the flag
anywhere inside the building.
(They can hide it anywhere indoors.)
Can we hide it anywhere?
The race will consist
of three rounds.
In each round,
one target who can be eliminated...
will be chosen
by the spinning wheel.
After checking the target,
choose the method of elimination...
and use the chosen method
to eliminate the target.
- We need to choose the method.
- Yes.
If you succeed in eliminating
the target in a round,
you'll get a hint on the location
of the other gang's flag.
(A hint on the location of the flag)
In any case, we need to eliminate
the target in each round.
If we do it, we'll receive a hint.
- If we get eliminated,
- If we get eliminated...
- they'll receive a hint.
- And...
On the spinning wheel
that decides on the target,
there are two names per member.
You acquired a turf previously,
so you'll receive a chance
to change two names.
Please make both of them Seok Jin.
- Yes.
- Then we'll have a better chance.
You spun the wheel
with the changed names...
- and got your target.
- Who is it?
The Locust Gang's first target is...
(The Locust Gang's first target)
Who is it? I'm so curious.
Who is it?
It's Jee Seok Jin.
(Seok Jin's name was
on 4 out of 10 blocks.)
- I feel bad.
- All right.
- How do we eliminate him?
- You can eliminate him...
by using...
- one of these two methods.
- Is that so?
If we win, it's final.
(What's the elimination method
Locust Gang chose?)
- Does the target know?
- What is it?
(Elimination Method)
Piggyback Ride.
If someone gets on the target's back
for 15 seconds,
he or she's eliminated.
We need to get on Seok Jin's back.
Here Comes the Ball.
If you give a ball to the target...
and he or she kicks it or heads it,
he or she's eliminated.
James Bond.
If you hit the target's name tag
with a water gun,
he or she's eliminated.
Once you choose
an elimination method...
for Seok Jin from the three of them,
you won't be able to use it
for the following rounds.
The thing is, we should begin
by taking a win.
- That's right.
- We should win no matter what.
You're Yu-mes Bond,
- so pick the water gun.
- Shall we pick the water gun?
I also think
that we should take control...
- with a win.
- Seung Ho, you're here to win.
That's right.
I lost in my past two visits.
- I lost both times on the show.
- Again,
- I lost.
- Seung Ho.
- I really want to win.
- He hasn't won before.
Jae Seok, then we should pick
the water gun.
Then we can do it secretly.
We can only use them once?
(There are only 2 water guns.
You can only use them once.)
- Two water guns?
- All right.
- Seung Ho.
- You need to do well.
Seung Ho, you need to hide it well.
(The snipers are
Jae Seok and Seung Ho.)
They might choose the same method.
- Of course.
- Yes.
My goodness.
The Tiger Gang's first target is...
Who is it?
Song Ji Hyo.
Ji Hyo isn't an easy target.
"Elimination methods."
- "Are You Annoyed?"
- "If you get hit..."
- You need to get hit.
"by the target,
he or she's eliminated."
It's easy. Ji Hyo hits people often.
"If all members sign
the target's name tag,"
"he or she's eliminated."
- What's Recharge the Sugar Level?
- "If you feed a certain snack..."
"to the target,
he or she's eliminated."
- I should watch out.
- Seriously.
- This is perfect for Ji Hyo.
- Yes.
- It's the best.
I think we should use it first.
- Make an annoying comment.
- She hits you often.
- She hits me often.
- I'll annoy her.
- My goodness.
- Okay.
- "She hits me often."
- Do they get the same one?
- Yes.
- Tiger Gang. It's ours.
- But...
- Ours...
- Is it the same size?
Where are we supposed to hide it?
Where will we hide it?
Isn't the flag too big?
Jong Kook, can you lift the set
for a second?
- That's a good idea.
- Once you lift the set,
- we can put the flag underneath.
- On the top...
It'll be hard.
They'll find it if it's on the top.
They'll go up and look.
They'll see it from the top.
The location should make them go,
"This is too much."
- They'll do the same.
- Exactly.
If we break the set...
It'll be nice to put it
between the columns.
- I have an idea.
- What is it?
Chan Hee.
- Get up.
- Stick it in the back?
Yes. We can stick it in the back.
- I'm for the idea.
- From the pants to the top.
- Kang Chan Hee.
- Let's stick it in.
- Let's push it in there.
But it's too long.
Wouldn't it come out?
- No. If it's inside the pants...
- He's standing up.
- I see.
- When he walks,
his one leg can look like this.
Hey.
(Laughing)
We can put it there...
or use the light like this one.
- We can put it inside.
- The inside.
- Haven't we done that once?
- We can put it inside.
Haven't we done that once?
I feel like I've done it once.
A chalk.
(In Episode 566, they had
a mission of hiding a giant chalk.)
(Haha hid it inside the light
and took 1st place.)
- We can put it inside.
- Jae Seok, they'll find it.
- I think they'll think of it.
- Do you know why?
I used that method once.
When we had to hide a long chalk,
I hid it inside the light.
- It's dangerous.
- But they won't check each one.
Jae Seok.
Wouldn't you look inside this light?
I'd look inside.
(Let's see.)
Jae Seok.
- We can take this out.
- Let's see.
We just need to borrow
a hexagon ratchet...
from the props team.
- We can get it out?
- If we unscrew this and do it,
they won't be able to get it out
even if they find it.
- This...
- I think this is a good place.
- We might struggle too.
- This...
I think we could find a hex key.
He's determined.
- I want to win.
- If we do that, they won't get it.
- They'd never get it.
- If this is there,
they won't be able to get it.
- Right.
- They'd never find it.
- Let's keep this as an option.
They won't be able to get it
even if they find it...
- Yes.
- without the tool.
There's the Jimmy Jib.
Let's put it in the support.
- The support...
- The support.
- Good.
- There are several of them.
- We can put it in like this.
- That's good.
Inside here.
- Inside here?
Hey.
- We can put it inside.
- Right.
- This is the best.
- We'll put it in here.
- Look.
- That's amazing.
- That's amazing. Look.
- It's the best.
- They would never guess.
- If we put it here like this...
- The color.
- Put it the other way around.
The other way around...
- At the end...
- It will come out.
- Let's stick tape here...
- Let's tape it.
- We can stick it here.
- Where? Will that work?
Here.
It's perfect.
Is it done?
I'll look at it from afar.
- This is crazy.
- It's crazy.
- Hey.
- You wouldn't know.
- You really can't see it.
- They wouldn't know.
- We won!
We won.
It's perfect.
They wouldn't be able to find it.
- It's perfect.
- How will they find it?
The flag...
- Let's go.
- It started.
It's an emergency!
I hope we can find it.
- This would be hard.
- I think we won.
- It's an emergency!
We can go indoors, right?
It's an emergency!
- We need to go indoors.
- What are you doing?
What is it?
(The air is tense.)
What?
- Se Chan. Come here.
- What?
- Don't shake hands. He's weird.
- Come here.
- We have to find it.
- Let's go.
Go and search.
- Where did they put the flag?
- There's nowhere to hide it here.
(They search
the outdoor headquarters first.)
There's nowhere to hide it here.
Hold me.
(They search thoroughly
by even climbing up a ladder.)
Shouldn't we be moving this?
But there's...
- What?
- nowhere to hide anything here.
- There's nowhere to hide.
- There isn't.
Wasn't it the entire area
of the first floor? The fence...
We can search everywhere
within the fence.
They might have dug the ground.
Somewhere here.
Is this... Hold on.
Can you make such notices too?
- You can't do that.
- You can't, right?
- We can't do that.
- They wouldn't have done that.
(He's suspicious of everything.)
Would it be in a container?
(Staring)
Hold on. Excuse me.
You don't have it, right?
Okay.
An insect!
(While the newbie
barks up the wrong tree...)
It wouldn't be up here, right?
They won't have put it
where we can see it.
But they could have also
hidden it somewhere obvious.
- That's right.
- Right.
- Check under the chairs.
- You think?
Darn it. It's not here.
(Flipping)
We have to flip over everything.
- What?
- Things that are this big.
(The experienced members
are searching thoroughly.)
The camera's stand...
is hollow.
It's empty.
(The stand of the light
was caught by Jong Kook's radar.)
(The Tiger Gang is searching
the light stands with the boss.)
There won't be many places
to hide it here.
- Here...
- Did they put it in these stands?
They would have thought of it.
Haha definitely would have.
Seok Jin.
They would have opened up something.
(That moment)
- They surely opened up something.
- Right.
(Seok Jin heads toward the light
that Jae Seok chose.)
Where did they hide it?
(Would the flag be in there?)
There has to be something
that opens up.
I think...
it's here.
Is there somewhere
to hide something here?
(He checks the next light.)
It doesn't go in there.
It's not here.
(The flag isn't in the lights.)
I know. There are no places.
(It's already been 5 minutes
since the race started.)
This won't work. It's not there.
- Where is it?
- It's not there.
- Tell me.
(He finds Seok Jin alone.)
(He can get the location hint
if he eliminates Seok Jin.)
- Tell me.
- Check somewhere else.
- Tell me where it is.
- What?
But why does Seok Sam
keep coming out?
- Why?
- Isn't it...
Why do you keep...
Is there something here?
I was trying to go there
through this way.
- Why do you keep...
- I was trying to go this way.
(Seok Sam shows his back.)
(It's a perfect chance
to eliminate the target!)
Is there something here?
Why does Seok Sam keep coming out?
(He turns away
after seeing Se Chan.)
- Why does Seok Sam keep coming out?
- That was close.
That was close!
I missed my chance!
(Coward Yoo is disappointed
for losing his chance to shoot him.)
(He keeps touching it now.)
They wouldn't have put it here.
It makes sounds.
You never know.
Se Chan.
(They're right next
to the Jimmy Jib!)
(Glancing)
(Jae Seok
roams around the Jimmy Jib.)
(Se Chan also notices Jae Seok.)
Why are you scratching?
(He's searching
the production crew.)
Jae Seok.
(He gets closer to the Jimmy Jib.)
(There's not much time left!)
(Even Haha goes near the Jimmy Jib!)
Is there something here?
- I think we need to start.
- Why does Seok Sam...
(They need to eliminate the target
before they find the flag.)
(Ji Hyo will be eliminated
if she hits someone.)
(The target is approaching him.)
They became suspicious of me
because I went outside.
- But why are you outside?
- Seok Sam...
- What?
- Hurry up!
(Se Chan starts a fight
to be hit by Ji Hyo.)
- What is it?
- Wait.
(Ji Hyo doesn't hit them
even if they keep annoying her.)
- What is it?
- Wait.
Is it me?
(That moment)
(Seok Sam, the target,
was caught by the Locust Gang.)
(Seok Jin will be eliminated
if his name tag gets shot by a water gun.)
(He took out the water gun!)
- Is it me?
- Hold on.
- Okay!
- We did it!
(Jee Seok Jin was eliminated.)
- Okay!
- We did it!
(Yu-mes Bond eliminated him
in a flash.)
What is it?
We did it.
(He eliminated the target.)
- Seok Jin.
- We got attacked.
Why?
Jae Seok.
- Why?
- Good.
- Right.
- That was good acting.
- Good.
How did you do it?
Am I eliminated? I'm seriously out?
(Round 1 ends.)
- Goodness.
- You have to win!
Goodness.
What a shame.
Ji Hyo doesn't hit you
in these situations.
- She could have hit us.
- She doesn't.
You failed to eliminate the target,
so a hint will be given
to the other team.
- Look at that.
- They get a hint.
We have to use this...
- Let's get them.
- to win this time.
We should end it.
Column.
(Location hint: Column)
- Column? What column?
- It's something outside.
There are columns on the wall too.
There are columns outside too.
The second target has been decided.
The second target is Kim Jong Kook.
(The Locust Gang's second target
is Jong Kook.)
- Kim Jong Kook.
- Goodness.
(There are
two elimination methods left.)
The only thing we can do
with Jong Kook...
- Is getting on his back.
- is getting on his back.
- He wouldn't kick the ball.
Or would he get mad and kick
the ball since he likes balls?
We could tease him,
saying he's bad at soccer.
"Kick it."
- He would get angry.
- Do you want to try that?
- Let's get on his back.
- Yes.
That will be our target.
We'll go with getting on his back.
Let's not split up in this round.
Let's move together.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Let's stay together.
- Okay.
- It could be me.
- Stay within a meter of each other.
Always.
The next target has been decided.
The target is Choi Daniel.
- That won't be easy.
Should we hold him and sign on him?
- Signing would be better.
- As soon as it begins.
- Signing.
- That's not bad.
Signing as soon as it begins.
Honestly, it's not a bad idea.
- Right.
- Let's hold him and sign on him.
- I'll hold Daniel.
- Okay.
Let's all get him and sign.
We don't need
to use our real signatures, right?
- Is yours a long one?
- Are you going to write his name?
- "Thank you, I love you."
- Don't do that.
- No.
- Just scribble anything.
But Jong Kook.
I saw Jae Seok...
touching the backs of the cameramen.
- I guess he hid it on them.
- Right.
(Jae Seok was searching
the production crew's bodies.)
- Right.
- Really?
- If they put it here...
- On their legs.
- and stand like this...
- That's right.
- We should search them.
- Right.
Jae Seok was touching them.
Chan Hee. Chan Hee's leg.
- That's right.
- Was Chan Hee inside?
- The cameramen are there.
- They're there.
The experienced cameramen are there.
- Let's quickly check that first...
- Yes.
And when it's not there...
Right.
Do we search the legs first?
Do we hide it?
- Let's go first.
- Okay.
- One meter.
Wait.
- Let's go!
- Okay.
- Let's find it.
- Let's go!
- Where do you think you're coming?
- You startled me.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
- You'll start with the mission?
- What's going on?
- They're behind us.
- They came from behind.
- Go out.
(Jong Kook and Ye Eun
entered from the back door.)
(Cameraman Kang Chan Hee)
(He checks him first.)
(Would the flag really be with him?)
(Cameraman Kang Chan Hee)
(He doesn't have it!)
It's not here.
Where is it?
- The cameraman up there.
- I'll check.
(He checks the next cameraman.)
Do you not have it?
- He doesn't have it?
- You don't have it?
We should sign, then.
Let's go.
It's not here.
I checked him.
(The Tiger Gang is searching
all the cameramen in the building.)
- Let's just...
- Sign.
- Sign?
- Let's sign.
They're coming.
- Jong Kook is coming.
- They're coming.
He wants to catch us and end it.
- Should I get on his back?
- He wants to catch us.
Run.
(As the tiger shows up,
they all run away.)
Se Chan, I found them.
(Checking the cameraman)
Why are you running?
Why are you behaving like this?
What do we do, Se Chan?
Jong Kook, now?
- Jong Kook, now?
- Yes.
- Hey!
- Daniel!
- What?
- What? Hang on.
- What? It must be me.
He's holding something.
(Jong Kook caught Daniel.)
(Ye Eun runs toward him with a pen.)
What? It must be me.
- He's holding something.
- Hang on.
- Ye Eun is coloring it.
- Wait.
- Ye Eun is...
- It's done.
- It's a marker.
- Come here.
- Wait.
(Attacking from behind)
Is it done?
- Next.
- I did it.
- Hey.
- Hurry, Ye Eun.
Is it done? Next.
(Se Chan did it too.)
Hurry, Ye Eun.
- Hey, I did it.
- Hurry, Ye Eun.
- Go, Ye Eun.
- Help me.
(Ye Eun is confronting
her boyfriend.)
- Jong Kook.
- Go.
Jong Kook.
Hurry, Ye Eun!
- Hey, I did it.
- Hurry, Ye Eun.
Help me. Block my back.
- I did it.
- Give it to me, Ye Eun.
I'll give it to you.
- Ye Eun.
- Hurry.
Again. One more.
- I got him.
- I...
- I'm hanging.
- What's going on?
- Get him off.
I'm hanging on his back.
- I stole it from Ye Eun.
- I'm hanging.
- I took this away from Ye Eun.
- Good.
I took this away from Ye Eun.
(Her boyfriend suddenly
hugs her from behind.)
(Happy)
Don't give it to her.
Ye Eun didn't do it.
(He lies back down
to protect his name tag.)
My knee!
- His knee.
- My knee. My privates.
Let me do it once.
(Struggling)
Get him away.
- My privates.
- No.
Get him.
Pen!
It hurts.
- My gosh.
- I did it.
Come here, Ye Eun.
- What?
- Come here, Ye Eun.
(In the midst of chaos,
Jong Kook managed to sign on him.)
(Now Ye Eun needs to sign!)
- What?
- Hurry, Ye Eun.
(Ye Eun's pen
penetrates into the crowd.)
- What?
- Come here, Ye Eun.
- Kim Jong Kook is out.
Kim Jong Kook, you're out.
- Jong Kook is out?
- Kim Jong Kook is out.
(Jong Kook is out,
instead of Daniel?)
(While everyone was busy
trying to sign on Daniel...)
(If someone gets on Jong Kook's back
for 15 seconds, he's eliminated.)
(Haha got on Jong Kook's back.)
(15-second countdown)
(He's sticking to him
like a cicada.)
(Jong Kook was busy fighting Daniel,
so he didn't notice it.)
My knee. My privates.
Go!
- Hurry.
- I did it.
(Thanks to Haha's tenacity,
Jong Kook is out.)
- We did it.
- My gosh.
Am I out?
(He can't believe it.)
- I'm okay.
- Are you okay?
- What happened? I'm okay.
- Are you all right?
- Are you okay?
- Are you not hurt?
- I'm fine.
- He's okay.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- What happened?
- Is this a signature?
- It is.
I did it here.
(Daniel survived
because Ye Eun failed to sign.)
- You should do it on the name tag.
- Ye Eun failed.
Okay.
- We can do this.
- Okay. Let's do this.
We are winning.
It's okay. Let's do this.
There's no way.
Jong Kook is eliminated.
We're in trouble.
We should've done it
after ripping off the name tag.
We could've done that.
- We could've ripped it off.
- Right.
(It's new to see these two
in prison.)
We should've done that.
We have no choice.
How are we going to find it now?
There's nothing we can do.
We're at a huge disadvantage.
- No, that's not true.
- Why not?
This is a real fight now. Listen.
They will try to find the flag now,
instead of getting the name tags.
All we need to do
is find the flag first.
But I can't find it.
Where would it be?
Where did they hide it?
Where on earth is it?
- It's nowhere to be seen.
- No.
(They couldn't find
Locust Gang's flag anywhere.)
Is Jong Kook eliminated?
Ji Hyo, they will check this
for sure, right?
They'll definitely check this place.
- Is it a bad idea to hide it here?
- Where?
At the end over there.
- At the end over there?
- Yes.
(The place Daniel found is...)
At the end of here.
I think it'll be okay.
(The end of the hallway
behind the bars)
Look.
It's open.
Hang on. They are outside,
- so they don't know the structure.
- They don't.
- That there's an empty space.
- They don't know.
(Locust Gang hid their flag well
using Long Legs.)
Can we hide it in the restroom?
(Se Chan and Ho Jun passed by
this place while searching.)
There's no place to hide it here.
- That there's an empty space.
- They don't know.
There is no other place where
we can hide something that big.
The last target has been decided.
The last target is...
Yoo Seung Ho.
No.
We should find the flag
while running away.
We can't complete the mission.
How would we let him eat the snack?
I know. It's impossible.
But Seung Ho is not good
at saying no.
- I should feed him then.
- How will you do that? Show me.
(Here?)
- He wouldn't take it.
- Eat this.
Hey!
Eat this.
(Her strategy to use her good looks
doesn't work.)
Don't you have your tongue?
Eat this for me.
Would you eat it if you were him?
You wouldn't, right?
Can you eat this for me?
I might eat.
(Almost crying)
The red gummy bear
is Ye Eun's favorite.
What about you?
You sound like Zhu Bajie.
- I, Ji Fox, am coming.
- Ji Fox?
- Good luck.
- Let's see how good you are.
- I'm Ji Fox.
I'll see how Ji Fox does.
The last target has been decided.
The last target...
is Son Ho Jun.
(The Locust Gang's last target
is Ho Jun.)
And the last mission
to eliminate the target...
- is to let him kick the ball.
- The ball.
Can we just throw the ball...
- at his feet?
- No.
- He should kick it himself.
- He should kick or head it.
You got another location hint.
There's no place to hide it.
- It's strange.
- It wasn't there.
Is it different
from the columns I'm thinking of?
- Is it different?
- Did they take it apart...
- to put it inside?
- The front yard?
There's a column in the front yard.
The place here is the front yard.
Outside...
Column? I bet they hid it
in the column.
It's outside. The hint is "column"
and "front yard."
Go and find it.
(Which gang will
find the flag first?)
- Make sure to run away.
- Okay.
(Round 3 begins.)
- Front yard and column.
- Make sure to run away.
Okay.
- Oh, dear.
- My goodness.
Hang on. The front yard...
This is the front yard.
- Check the front yard.
- Is this a column?
There's one. There's another.
There's another one.
(They focus on looking for the flag
instead of eliminating the target.)
- And a column.
- And this...
Did they drop it in here?
This is blocked.
It's blocked.
(Using the hint,
they are getting closer to the flag.)
It's blocked.
- Yard?
- What?
We didn't go in there.
We didn't.
(The Tiger Gang heads to the hallway
where the flag is hidden.)
Can we check the room here?
I guess we can.
(The flag is
at the end of the hallway.)
I guess we can go in.
There are cameras.
You're right.
But there's no place to hide it.
(If they find the flag first,
they can turn things around.)
- Is it on the rooftop?
- It's not here.
- Does the room have this?
- Did they drop it?
What?
If it's a column,
it must be supporting something.
It's supporting something.
- They can't put it in here.
- Yard.
Is it that my brain isn't working?
Seung Ho.
What?
- Seung Ho.
- Run away, Seung Ho.
We have only three members.
- Seung Ho.
- Seung Ho, don't answer her.
Don't answer. Ignore her.
Seung Ho.
(Seung Ho senses something strange
and runs away.)
Seung Ho, run away.
Go away.
- Seung Ho.
- Go away.
Please don't come here.
- Don't come to me.
Seung Ho.
Run.
- What are you doing?
- Seung Ho.
The red gummy bear is my favorite.
(She sticks to her strategy.)
- What?
- Do you like the green one?
(He receives the jelly from her.)
I like everything.
(He puts it in his pocket.)
Why...
- Seung Ho.
- What?
The red one is my favorite.
I like the blue one.
I don't have a blue one.
Too bad.
Eat the red one instead.
Thank you.
(He puts it in his pocket again.)
Seung Ho.
- Ye Eun.
- Seung Ho.
- What are you doing, Ye Eun?
- What?
Eat this.
- I'll eat one.
- Okay.
- And you eat one.
- Thank you.
Why aren't you eating it?
- I, Ji Fox, am coming.
- What?
I gave it to you,
but why aren't you eating it?
I don't usually eat
during the shoot.
It's probably in here.
(Se Chan is
right in front of the flag.)
It's "column" and "front yard,"
so it must be here.
(The Locust Gang is also
right in front of the flag.)
(He's checking the wrong place.)
I don't think they hid it here.
Gosh, I was surprised.
No, Seung Ho. What are you doing?
- Hey, she's an evil spirit.
- Don't eat it.
It's here.
I gave it to you.
- Don't eat it.
- It's too precious to eat.
Throw it away.
Throw it at her face.
- Should we check the Jimmy Jib?
- I gave it to you.
(Column, front yard)
(The Jimmy Jib?)
Column, front yard?
Hang on. Is it in here?
(They start checking the Jimmy Jib
where the flag is hidden.)
Can I check this?
We have to flip over everything.
Things that are this big.
I'm sorry.
I think it's here.
(I think it's here.)
Can I check it in the front?
If I find it, I'll be a hero.
But there's no place to hide it.
Sir, please bring it down.
- Right here.
- Please.
Right there.
Hey.
Did you find it?
(They found it!)
(The Locust Gang successfully finds
their flag.)
Is it over?
(What a shame.)
Who found it?
My gosh.
(What a shame.)
(Locust Gang, Tiger Gang)
The Locust Gang is the final winner
in the turf war.
- Okay!
- It's over.
- My gosh.
- But this was really...
The winning gang can save...
- one killer from the losing gang.
- Okay.
(The winning gang's benefit)
(They can save one killer
from the losing gang.)
Who will you save?
- Let's think about what to do.
- Okay.
- So...
- Seung Ho.
(Acting cute
as if it's as easy as breathing)
Stop it! Seriously, I can't...
- I can't stand it anymore.
- Stop it.
- My goodness.
- Hey, Seung Ho.
- Seung Ho, you should choose.
- Don't do it.
- Not my girlfriend.
- It's not like that.
- Seung Ho sure is impressive too.
- Then, in that case...
I thought
he'd definitely choose Ye Eun.
- But he excluded her right away.
- The penalty?
- No, it's not like that.
- Ye Eun can hold a grudge.
- No, it's not that.
- You won't be able to break up now.
- She'll curse you now.
- No, it's not that.
- A curse.
- He says you can't break up.
- You can't break up now.
- My goodness.
It was
Jong Kook's birthday today too.
- Oh, it was his birthday.
- It could be his birthday present.
- Gosh, you don't have to.
- Oh, you're right.
It's his birthday today.
- Who doesn't have a birthday here?
- Jong Kook doesn't care about that.
- Oh, my birthday?
- Everyone has a birthday.
- It's his birthday today.
- The birthday boy.
- In 1, 2, 3.
- Jong Kook!
(Saving Jong Kook
as his birthday present)
- Then, Jong Kook,
- Happy birthday!
- you're exempt from the penalty.
- Gosh, thank you.
- Happy birthday.
- Don't you have any pride?
- For real.
- But this is nice.
- It's nice.
- He has changed so much.
- Here is the winning prize first.
It's an abalone set to guarantee
the killers' nutrition.
(The winning team's prize is
abalones to invigorate the killers.)
This is my third time
on Running Man.
- Was it the 3rd time already?
- And I won for the 1st time.
I feel great.
- Gosh, great job.
- Nice!
- They're still alive.
- Except for Jong Kook,
the four of you
will get the penalty.
- Save at least 1 or 2 of us.
- This penalty is...
along the same line
as the killer concept.
Among the two water guns,
- one has ink and the other water.
- Oh, nice.
- Ink?
- My goodness.
- Only two will survive.
- Water and ink?
- In that case...
- Two will survive.
We'll be so happy if it's like this.
- Ho Jun, where are you?
- Here.
Pick one for me.
- Then, this one...
- No, Ho Jun was...
- Okay, then.
- really bad at picking things.
- Seok Jin.
- I always get...
Wait! I'm going to go with
the one Ho Jun didn't choose.
He seems unlucky today.
- Okay.
- Let's go with this.
- Face each other.
- Ho Jun, I didn't choose...
- Okay. Ready.
- Shoot directly in the face.
- Then, he got the one Ho Jun chose.
- Ready.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Yang Se Chan
gets blasted with ink.)
- My goodness.
- Ho Jun's choice...
- That's enough.
- This guy is super unlucky.
- My goodness.
- My gosh.
(Unlucky Ho Jun works hard
until the very end.)
- Gosh, that's so fascinating.
- This guy...
Among all the unlucky people...
Hey, but why did you get ink on you?
Why did he get ink on him?
- Why did you get ink on you?
- What's up with me?
They crossed paths.
Seok Jin, as the ink...
- and water crossed paths,
- Show me.
it must've splashed on you too.
Did I get splashed
as they crossed paths?
Why did I get ink on me?
- My gosh.
- This guy is amazing.
- Seriously.
- Hey, Ho Jun.
Then, the two of you can choose
the water guns...
- and shoot right away.
- This seems serious.
- Gosh, this is really serious.
- Is that what happened?
Will you choose that one?
- Hold it up.
- Yes, hold it up.
- You can just do it once.
- This is no joke.
- Look at them.
- Oh, really?
- Get closer.
- No.
- Come closer.
- It's okay. You can shoot me.
(Which of the two killers
has worse luck?)
- A bit closer.
- In 1, 2, 3.
(Ho Jun gets shot with water.)
(Ji Ye Eun gets blasted
with ink again.)
(But...)
(I'm sure she's shooting
with her eyes closed.)
Hey, this one is darker.
- Hey, how can that happen?
- It's so weird.
- This happens every time.
- For real.
- Don't smile.
- It's so weird.
(Moving quickly)
(The boyfriend takes care
of his girlfriend right away.)
Ji Ye Eun.
- Just wipe her eyes.
- No!
- Don't smile.
- It's so weird.
- This happens every time.
- "Don't smile."
It's so weird.
(Meanwhile, she's happy.)
- Call his name right now. Please.
- Call his name.
- Call Seung Ho.
- Seung Ho!
Hey, your teeth! Look at her teeth!
- Hey! Don't smile.
- Don't smile, Ye Eun.
Don't smile.
- Oh, no.
- That's hilarious.
- Okay!
- Oh, boyfriend and girlfriend.
- I know.
- Right?
- That's what happens in the end.
- In the end.
- After all that...
- Good job.
- Gosh, Ho Jun.
- Okay!
- Great job!
- Ho Jun, that was so awesome.
- Good job, Seung Ho.