- The weather is nice. - Okay!
- All right. - It's really nice.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- How are you? - Okay! Hello.
Hello.
- How nice. - All right.
- Hello, everyone. - Yes.
Good.
Jong Kook, you used to show up in gray tracksuits. What's with you?
- I should dress up. - Actually,
they came to say hello earlier. It's been a long time.
- Really? - Who?
- So Mi and Chungha. - I see.
- I.O.I. - Right.
I.O.I.
- This is insane. - I.O.I?
They got back together again after ten years.
- There they are. - They're back.
- Okay. - Hey.
It's been a really long time.
- Okay. - Chungha and So Mi are here.
Goodness.
They're back as grown-ups.
We didn't forget it at all.
- Hello. - Gosh.
- Hey. - "Gotta Go" hasn't changed at all.
- Hello. - They're grown-ups now.
- Thank you. - This is shocking.
Actually, I got a text from Se Jeong.
What did she say?
They reunited after a long time,
but she can't make it today because of her schedule.
This year marks the tenth anniversary of I.O.I's debut.
That's amazing.
How did you reunite after ten years?
Well... I made the calls.
- You did? - You suggested it?
- Chungha, you suggested it? - Really?
"It's our tenth anniversary. Aren't we going to do something?"
- Really? - And we got together right away.
- Actually, it's been a long time. - Right.
And they all were doing their own things.
That's true.
- They belong to different agencies. - Yes.
Even if they wanted to reunite,
- it must not have been easy. - That's true.
Did things work out right away?
- Right away. - Really?
- On that very day. - No one hesitated?
- You all agreed right away? - Yes.
It worked out right away?
I guess it was what they all wanted.
Hey, we should get together again after ten years.
- Ten years from today. - Seok Jin.
- Will you be there after ten years? - I'll call.
We can't be sure if you'll still be there.
- I'll be there. - Seok Jin!
- Seok Jin! - I'll be fine.
- Seok Jin! - I'll be there.
- Don't worry. I'll call. - Seok Jin.
Just stay healthy.
What are you doing? Why are you looking up?
- We want you to come down. - Ten years...
from today, I'll make the calls.
You have to agree right away.
For your 70th birthday party.
So, they got back together after ten years...
and danced to "Pick Me."
- Right. - How was it?
- Did it go well after a long time? - How was it?
- Did you remember the move? - It wasn't as bad as I thought.
Maybe because "Pick Me" was the first song we learned,
- our muscles remembered the moves. - Muscle memory?
- Your body remembers it? - Can you show us?
- Right away? - Show us "Pick Me."
- Please perform "Pick Me" for us. - Yes! We want to see.
Show us.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Pick me, pick me, pick me up - This is it.
Do you dance like this?
Pick me up
I remember this.
- Back then, it was really... - That was nice.
It was crazy.
- It really was. - I loved it.
It was ten years ago.
- I remember the dance. - We used to dance along.
It was 10 years ago, when Chungha was 20.
You know this, right?
- I know. - Very, very, very
Again and again
- Again and again - Again and again
This is amazing.
- They're so good. - They're lovely.
- Again and again - By the way,
we used to dance along to this a lot back in the day.
- We did the dance a lot. - It's so cute.
Isn't I.O.I's new song coming out?
- It is. - Did you not record one yet?
- Is it a secret? - It's not released yet?
- It's not released yet. - I see.
Isn't it that you came here too soon?
- You don't have a song yet, do you? - A little.
- No. - No, it's ready.
You just came here right after you reunited, right?
- We do have a new song. - We do.
They have a schedule planned for the new song.
We have a song that we recorded ten years ago,
which is supposed to be pre-released.
- Really? - Yes.
- It's meaningful. - Yes. The song is...
It will be released...
- the day after this episode. - Yes. It's coming out.
Please check it out tomorrow.
- That's great. - I look forward to it.
We're having a race with Chungha and Jeon So Mi,
who resemble a bright, sunny spring day.
It's called Flower Path for Different Colors.
What is it?
Just like the name of the race, your fate today...
will be determined by colors.
That's why we're dressed like this.
That's why we asked you...
to wear bright, cheerful clothes to welcome spring today.
I'm wearing bright colors.
What color are you wearing?
- Me? I'm wearing orange. - Orange?
If you look to the right,
there are color boards prepared...
- where random colors appear. - Okay.
If a color from your outfit...
appears on these boards,
- you will be disadvantaged. - I'm wearing many colors.
- I have so many colors. - I...
It's a disadvantage.
I'm wearing so many colors.
My colors should appear on the boards?
It works to your disadvantage if your colors appear.
- It's a disadvantage. - It's not good.
- Should I zip this up? - What is it?
- You should take this off. - I should take this off.
We are going to spin all three,
and you must avoid having your colors on the boards...
- to gain an advantage in missions. - Okay.
- Jong Kook has one color. - But...
if all three boards have the same colors,
we consider it a jackpot.
- Jackpot? - No one will have a disadvantage.
- That's better. - That's how it works.
So, the top three members...
with the highest mission funds win,
and the one with the lowest mission funds...
receives a penalty.
We will pick two more members by lot,
so three members will get a penalty today.
First, we will give everyone...
- ten dollars each in seed money. - Okay.
If the colors on your outfit don't appear on the color boards,
you can earn...
- additional mission funds. - We should avoid it.
- Okay. - I have so many colors.
- Ye Eun has a lot of colors. - Red, blue,
orange, white, and green.
I'm wearing so many colors.
- I have all colors. - Red, blue, white...
Why do I have so many?
Look at Haha.
- Gosh, I'm wearing too many colors. - I have blue.
I have red and yellow.
The bag isn't included, right?
Why do I have so many colors?
Ye Eun has so many.
Where do I have blue?
Blue?
Look at So Mi.
I...
Red and white should be included.
We usually wear at least three colors.
Pink? It includes the shoes?
Where do I have blue?
- Is this blue? - Ye Eun has so many colors.
- Ye Eun has red, blue, - Right.
orange, white, and green.
- I see. - This one...
My hat isn't included, is it?
- It should be included. - I'm not wearing it.
I didn't wear it.
But he's holding it.
What about it?
- Please spin... - Is it random?
- the first color board. - I'm nervous.
- White is... - Seok Jin should have white.
Jong Kook is the only one who's not wearing white.
- This should be random. - Let's go.
- Blue. - Yes, blue. No.
I want yellow!
- It should be yellow. - Yellow.
- Yellow. - Please.
Yellow!
- Yellow! - Yellow!
Red. What?
- Okay. - Pink.
- Gosh, it's me. - Seok Jin, it's you.
She's wearing pink.
- Seok Jin and me. - Pink.
Jee Seok Jin and Song Ji Hyo are out.
I don't have pink.
Jee Seok Sam.
I avoided it.
Jee Seok Sam and Song Ji Hyo.
How did that come out?
Of all colors.
Please spin the second board.
The second.
- Spin the board! - Spin the second board.
Spin it.
Green!
- Yellow. - It should be red.
- Red. - Yellow.
- Red. - Black!
- What? - It's black!
- Black! - My goodness.
Darn, I have black.
Black!
- Black. - Kim Jong Kook and Haha are out.
- Black! - Black!
Isn't this navy?
- Come on. - I thought it was black,
- but this is actually navy. - This isn't totally black.
- It's black. - It's black.
Isn't this navy?
- But why is everyone... - It's black.
- Is this black? - Just accept it.
- Just go with black. - Okay.
All right. Spin the last board.
- Yellow. - It can't be blue, can it?
- Yellow. - Yellow.
- No! - Yellow.
- It should be red. - Yellow.
- Please. - It should be red.
- Yellow. Please. - Yellow.
It's yellow.
- It's green. - Green.
- Green! - He's...
- It's yellow. - It's green.
Green!
I don't have any of them.
But I don't have green.
Jee Ye Eun is out.
I'm wearing navy.
- But this is... - It's green.
- This isn't green. - It's settled.
- But this is wrong. - Green.
This is not fair.
Seriously, this is not fair.
Green!
I don't have any of them.
- I don't have any of them. - What?
I have only two colors, and they both appeared.
What...
I have only two colors.
- You're unlucky. - Unbelievable.
- This is crazy. - Just accept it.
Okay.
All right. So, the survivors are...
Jae Seok, Se Chan, Chungha and So Mi.
It feels so good.
- Nice. - They'll pick their mission funds.
Bring in the table.
- Yes. - Nice.
The 4 survivors will pick 1 envelope each.
- Pick one? - Seriously...
- Each envelope has... - I don't know...
- a different amount. - That's so nice.
- Pick one? - That's so nice.
- The four survivors? - Ten!
I will pick number eight.
- Ten! - I will pick number eight.
They all have different amounts.
- I pick this. - Did you pick one?
- You got a good one. - I'm 25 years old.
- What? - I'm 25.
- Number two. - Done.
- Chungha is done. - Yes.
- Mine is very thin. - Can I open it?
All the envelopes are thin.
Can we check the amount?
I hope it's a dud for Antenna.
I got 30 dollars.
- I hope it's a dud for Antenna. - I hope they fail.
This is quite soft.
Is this bad? What?
I think this is pretty good.
- This is good. - Let's trade.
- I hope it's a dud for Antenna. - I hope they fail.
Get a dud.
I should've picked something else.
It's a dud.
Darn it. It's too small.
There's nothing.
- Nothing? - Yes.
What is this?
I'll give you all the same seed money...
- of 10 dollars each. - It's 10 dollars.
Since when did we have much money?
- We weren't born rich. - You are right.
- We start with nothing. - Exactly.
This is nice.
- I got some money, anyway. - I don't have anything.
There are balloons and a mat.
Do we have to pop the balloons?
I'm scared.
Here's the first mission for the mission funds.
It's Empty Head Balloon Rollercoaster.
- What is it? - Empty Head Balloon?
Empty Head Balloon?
The three of us shouldn't team up.
It will be a team match.
- Really? - Teams have been divided...
based on the gender ratio.
- That's good. - Yes.
Yu Jae Seok,
Yang Se Chan,
- Ji Ye Eun, - You'll lose!
and Chungha.
- We are the smart team. - Chungha is smart.
- We're the smart team. - She speaks good English.
Chungha speaks good English.
Seok Jin, Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, and So Mi.
- Okay. - Okay.
- All right. - Sit. Make yourself comfortable.
So Mi, you have a competitive spirit.
- Of course. - So Mi's pretty athletic.
Two members from each team...
will put on colorful rubber gloves...
and dance to the music when it comes on.
When the music stops,
you'll be quizzed on a proverb or a Chinese idiom.
- Oh, dear. - I see.
However, not everyone is allowed to answer.
- Yes? - Only the person...
who finds a slip of paper inside a balloon that says "answer..."
- I see. - Okay, got it!
- Only that person can answer. - Exactly.
- So... - Got it.
- You have to look for it. - A correct answer earns two points,
but you can also earn one point for dancing.
- Okay, got it. - Goodness.
The winning team...
Do you remember those 30 envelopes...
- Sure. - with money inside?
The winning team will get seven of them.
The losing team will get three.
- Sounds good. - Okay.
- Shouldn't Chungha play? - She should.
- And... - Chungha and So Mi.
- Jae Seok, you... - Make Ye Eun look bad.
Chungha and Ssaebssaeb.
- Let's see how she fares. - Why don't you... No!
- Why not? Just show them. - I don't want to.
You're Vata's girlfriend. He's a brilliant dancer, right?
- Ssaebssaeb, go ahead. - I'm Ji Ye Eun, darn it.
- Show us! - Nice!
- Se Chan, go on. - Me?
- So Mi should compete. - Let's start with So Mi.
- So Mi should go. - Of course, So Mi should compete.
I don't know how good she'll be with Chinese idioms.
- Yeokjisaji? - Yes, like that.
- Didn't you say you were studying? - Sangbusangjo.
That's the one.
- Haha, come on. - Should it be Haha?
- Ssaebssaeb. - Haha, come on.
- Haha? - Yes, it should be Haha.
If you don't know the answer,
- just dance. - Should I just dance?
Let's earn points through dancing.
Each team gets a different color of rubber gloves.
Do we have to pop the balloons with our hands?
You can only pop the balloons with your hands.
Okay!
- Got it. - Here we go. Get ready.
Music, play.
Hey!
- Oh, no. - You're amazing.
You're amazing.
They're different, aren't they?
They sure are different.
- They sure are different. - They're both amazing dancers.
Amazing!
- Amazing! - That's perfect.
Pop the balloons.
Pop them.
You should check the question first!
It's an easy one.
Something in dog food?
You know the answer, right? Come on.
You should check the question first!
Guys, read the question.
It's an easy one. Check the question!
- This is an easy one. - Hurry up!
- You know what it is, right? - A whole mess of dog food?
- What? - A whole mess of dog food?
She says it's a whole mess of dog food.
- Dog food... - Hold on.
Answer it.
- Why can't you pop it? - I have the ticket.
- Acorns. - What?
- Pop the balloon. - Acorns.
- What? - Answer the question if you can.
Acorns in dog food.
- Acorns in dog food. - Two.
One.
- Dog food... - Isn't it "Acorns in dog food?"
- Three... - Acorns in dog food.
- That is correct. - Okay!
- What was the question? - You...
- Wait, you're not on my team. - Are you kidding me?
- Thanks so much. - What's with Haha?
- Thanks so much. - What's wrong with you?
- Are you kidding me? - What's wrong with you?
- Why did you tell her that? - He's all over the place.
- You... - I'm your teammate!
He's been all over the place for a while now.
- Are you a spy? - I'm sorry.
- What... - I was shocked...
- when you told her the answer. - Why did you tell her?
I honestly thought she was on our team.
- I thought... - What's wrong with you?
- I thought she was on our team. - I thought he had the ticket.
- Why... - Why did you tell her?
- What's wrong with you? - I mean...
What kind of fool are you?
What does "acorns in dog food" mean?
- Don't you know that proverb? - Didn't you know?
- I've never heard it before. - What?
I've never heard it before either.
- You've never heard it before? - Acorns in dog food?
How have you not heard it before?
- You've never heard it before? - When do you say it?
- I've never heard it before. - It's like this.
- It's used when you're left out. - Exactly.
- Acorns in dog food? - Yes.
- Shouldn't it be pickled radish? - Really?
- I understand that, but... - I mean...
Without you, none of them would've gotten it.
He's not easy to work with.
Isn't he a terrible teammate? You should tell him.
Even last time...
Why did you tell her?
That was fun.
Chungha earns the point for dancing.
- Chungha? - She gets three points.
So Mi and Chungha both did great, but at the last second...
- She did this. - She swept the floor.
Sweeping the floor earned you the point.
Ssaebssaeb and Ye Eun are up.
Sure.
Let's go!
This is harder than it looks. The balloons don't pop easily.
We'll go with So Mi and Jong Kook.
So Mi, you need to kill it with the dancing.
- Here we go. Get ready. - Music, play.
I've seen this dance move a lot.
- Is this how you do it? - Like this.
- Like this. - Is this it?
- How do I do it? - It's like this.
- It's this. - Do it like this.
- Is this it? - It's this.
- I love this. - Am I doing it right?
- The beat is really fast. - Okay.
- Look at Ye Eun. - Ye Eun, wait.
- Ye Eun? - Ye Eun?
- Ye Eun, are you an old man? - Ye Eun, what...
Is this how you do it?
Isn't Ye Eun...
- I can't. - Hurry up.
Take off the gloves...
- if you need to. - This isn't it.
- Get searching. - It's not here.
Get searching.
- Look for the ticket. - Let me answer.
- Yes? - Let me answer.
- Sure. - Here.
- What's wrong? - The question...
It's not that.
- The question's been covered. - Incorrect!
- The question's been covered. - I didn't get to see it.
- The question's been covered. - I didn't get to see it!
- Se Chan. - I didn't get to see it!
- Let me answer. - Yes?
Meeinbakmyeong.
- That is correct. - Okay.
- Yes! - Seriously?
- Se Chan! - Okay.
He just held up the answer ticket.
- Let me answer. - You had to answer the question.
I didn't read the question.
Is that so?
I bet you didn't know the answer.
- Of course, I knew. - Did you?
- Is that so? - So Mi gets a point for dancing.
Nice.
- What a bummer. - Se Chan, good job.
- Chungha, we're up. - Sure.
The point for dancing is ours for sure.
- So Mi, would you like to go again? - Me?
- You should. - Okay.
You've got this.
Is So Mi coming back out?
Yes, I'm going to get it right this time.
- Is So Mi coming back out? - Of course.
- That's admirable. - Chungha's up for us.
- So Mi's coming back out. - We have Chungha in our corner.
- I'll read the question. - Music,
- play. - Got it?
It's "Gotta Go."
- Midnight - Midnight
- What? - So Mi, nice!
Chungha, go.
What's with So Mi?
Good job!
Chungha, go.
What's with So Mi?
Good job!
The battle is on.
They're both amazing.
- They're both... - How can someone dance like that?
- They're both amazing. - This is incredible.
They're amazing.
This is amazing.
So Mi, go for it.
Move to the front, ahead of Chungha.
- A kind of love - There you go.
Let's check the question.
- Seok Jin, behind you. - Pop the balloons.
Let's do this.
This is an easy one.
- Palbang. - Palbang.
- Yes? - Let me answer.
- What's the question? - Let me answer.
- She didn't see it. - Let me answer.
The answer is palbangmeein.
- That is correct. - I didn't read the question.
Was it palbangmeein?
Nicely done.
Chungha gets the point for dancing.
Nice. Did you see Chungha dance?
- It was amazing. - I was amazed.
- That was so cool. - Her dance moves...
Did you show us the question?
It's shown right after the whistle is blown.
Right? So Mi, you didn't see it either.
- You were preoccupied. - You have to be fast.
Of course, I know that one. I've heard the idiom before.
You knew that one, right? Of course.
She's a top dancer for a reason.
Her dancing is on another level.
- Feeling threatened by So Mi, - Yes?
she stuck her hips out even more.
- Exactly. - You're right.
She stuck them out like a drawer sliding open.
Push!
- Like a drawer sliding open. - It was a battle.
I'm pretty sure she'll be aching after that.
She stuck them out like a drawer sliding open.
Doesn't it hurt?
Your hips might be hurting.
- The women's division. - The women's division.
Let's go with the women's division.
- The women's division. - So Mi, you're up again.
- Again? - You're a guest today, remember?
The women's division?
It's fun to watch them since they're talented dancers.
Move to the front.
- As soon as... - So Mi, read the question.
- That's right. - Okay.
Music, play.
- It's "New Thing." - It's new
Look at his girlfriend dance.
Ye Eun, move to the front.
Go for it.
Nice!
- Now... - Read it.
- Ye Eun, go for it. - Read it.
- What's the answer? - I have no idea.
- A bad workman? - What is that?
It's a hard one. They're clueless.
- It's tough. - They don't know it.
I got the answer note.
It must be something about wood.
- The hands... - Poor workmanship...
Let me answer.
Yes?
Pinocchio.
- What? - What are you doing?
- Pinocchio. - Incorrect.
A bad workman is Pinocchio.
- It makes sense. - That's a thought.
- You could think that. - I'm from America.
Oh, yes. You're from America.
- What is it? - America.
Let me answer. A bad workman...
- What's the answer? - cuts his own hand?
- Cuts. - Incorrect.
This is too hard.
- Give us a hint. - The first syllable.
Then we can get it.
- Are there no hints? - It's so hard.
Okay. I'll give you a hint.
A bad workman blames something.
- Oh, that! - Oh, that!
Let me answer!
- Tools. - He blames his tools.
A bad workman blames others.
- No! - Not that!
A bad workman...
- blames his machine. - No!
- When thugs prepare to fight. - Yes!
"Hey! Be sure to take this!"
- So Mi. Let me answer. - She got it!
She got it!
A thug in an action film always takes something.
A bad workman blames his tools.
- Correct. - Yes!
- Oh, no. - Tools.
- Tools. - Tools.
- Well done. - How did you know...
that's what thugs take?
I know about tools.
You from America?
Yes.
- It was "tools." - Yes.
- Ssaebssaeb. - Ye Eun gets the dance points.
- You're up. Well done. - Good job, Ye Eun.
It's an all-male competition this time?
- Yes. You're up, Haha. - Man to man.
- Man to man? - Okay.
- New thing! - Everything is new!
Do your best this time, will you?
- This is the last question. - Good luck.
It's the fire dance.
- This dance... - Fire!
Burn it all up.
Fire. You're pretty good!
What is it?
This one's easy! I need that note!
- Let me answer! - Answer.
Go to a well for rice water!
Correct!
- What? How come... - I knew this one.
- Nice one. - It was easy.
- It was so easy. - It was easy.
You got it right away.
Dance points to Haha.
Okay. Great.
A dud. They're all duds.
They were all duds.
- I thought it was a grave. - What a shame.
I thought it was about getting wet.
Go to a well and dig a grave.
Rice water.
Here's the result of the first mission.
- We lost. - The team of five...
- won. - Yes!
They're no match for us!
We'll let you pick your mission fund.
- Yes! - Okay!
I still don't have any money.
The winning team can take seven envelopes.
- The losing team can take three. - We...
- Give us four. - Okay.
Let's take one each, then play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors. - Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
Play! Okay.
- Rock-paper... - No, it's you two.
- Is it? - Take one each.
- Six and sixteen. - Okay.
Come closer. I scored.
Okay!
In number three...
The weather...
- Fight to die, and you live. - Not bad.
You got ten dollars, right?
No. I made a lot.
- He got 10. - Or just 1.
- I got a huge amount. - It's one dollar.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock... - One gets no money?
- Yes. - It can't be helped.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Gosh.
You're really firm. Mr. Grasshopper.
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, dear. You two are left.
Number 28.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay. - Oh, gosh.
Number 28 for me.
- You beat her. - Gosh.
How come you three won, leaving the guest all alone?
You're so inconsiderate.
It can't be helped.
- You could say, - Or...
"Chungha, pick first."
- Well... - "Ladies first."
- We played for it. - You're so cruel.
Not bad. I did pretty well.
Not bad.
Oh, dear. What a weak choice.
I won't get anywhere at this rate.
You're so inconsiderate.
- It can't be helped. - You could say, "Chungha..."
Ten dollars. That's it. What a pity.
I'll tell you how much the person with the largest amount has...
- as well as the smallest amount. - Okay.
We need to know to figure things out.
The largest amount is 120 dollars.
- What, for real? - That's insane.
- It's 120 dollars. - That's insane.
No way. Someone got the 100-dollar envelope.
- They got 120 dollars? - Over 100 dollars?
- They got over 100 dollars? - How?
- That's a lot. - The smallest amount.
- That's... - Twenty is the smallest amount.
- Twenty dollars? - That's the smallest so far.
Who didn't get to pick...
- We all got ten to start with. - And ten dollars just now.
It's Seok Jin.
I can treat you all to a meal at a family restaurant.
You're blushing.
- Boo. - I can treat you all...
- We'll starve. - Yes.
You're stuttering too.
Let's head to the next location.
- Okay. - I envy the one with 120 dollars.
It's pointless unless you have 100 dollars.
That's how much you need. A hundred dollars.
Someone got the 100-dollar envelope?
That's the one we must get.
- Okay. - Relax, everyone.
Great!
Why did you go "gosh?"
I suddenly thought of Chungha's dancing.
Chungha and So Mi...
I thought of those moves.
- Earlier... - They're true dancers.
- It's beyond belief. - Their moves...
- It borders on wizardry. - The dancing...
It's fun to watch.
Her face is here, and her hips are there.
How do you do that?
It looked like a drawer sliding open.
- Her face was here, - So Mi...
- and her hips there. - stretched her body...
and the way Chungha moved her hips...
It was like a drawer.
That magic box trick where a body splits in two.
- Right. - That's what it looked like.
- It's really impressive. - I'm jealous.
- It's amazing. - We could never do that.
- Okay, everyone. - Yes?
- Are we doing something? - We're headed to a restaurant.
- Yes! - Great.
- Goodness. - We must do well now to eat well?
- Mr. Free Meals. - So...
we'll play another mission to decide the menu and your pay.
It's called Answer Calmly.
- Answer Calmly. - What's that?
Everyone in the team must answer one by one.
If everyone gives an answer that suits the condition,
you get one point.
If you repeat something someone already said,
if the answer doesn't work,
- or if you take over five seconds, - Okay.
- you fail. - We can't fail.
- Answer Calmly. - One team has just four people.
Someone in the team of four must answer twice.
- All right. - If you win,
you can pick seven envelopes like before.
- Okay. - Lose, and you get just three.
The winning team also gets to pick...
one dish they want to eat.
- Who goes first? - Chungha.
Chungha will start.
- Then you must answer twice. - Okay.
Who or what do I look like?
- Five... - A hamster.
- A puppy. - Koo Kyo Hwan.
- Incorrect! - Why?
- Why? - You look like him?
- Why not? - Darn you!
- Are you serious? - Are you kidding me?
- What's wrong? - You could name your brother.
- What... - Hey, Dex.
- Why not Koo Kyo Hwan? - Why not Yu Jae Seok?
- Why... - What's wrong with you?
- If he said Yang Se Chan... - Why say Koo Kyo Hwan?
- One mistake and... - A monkfish.
- I thought Koo Kyo Hwan... - Come on!
- He ruined it. - Switch turns.
- Are you ready? - Yes, let's go.
- It's not that easy. - Here's the phrase.
What is my flaw?
- Five, four... - There are so many.
I'm old.
- That's... Fine. - Five...
- I'm old. - That's not right.
- I'm too nice. - Three...
- Incorrect. - Incorrect.
- Incorrect. - Why?
- He is nice! - No way.
- That's nonsense. - Why say that?
You could say anything else.
Why is that...
- Pretending to be young is a flaw. - Darn.
That is my flaw.
You're short.
My mom always said my flaw was that I was too nice.
- No. - Don't be silly.
- That's what your mom thought. - Let's do this!
- Yes. - Let's go!
- Here's your phrase. - Let's go.
Describe yourself...
- with five syllables. - That's hard.
- Five... - I can speak English well.
- Really? - I am so very cute.
My mouth is protruding.
I am so very likable.
- That's not true. - What?
- Not "so very." - "Likable?"
- No. - He's likable.
- He is. - He is.
- Not "so very." - He's likable.
- Four, three, - My eyes are...
- two... - very long.
- Long eyes. - Correct.
Okay!
- Hang on. - Long eyes?
- Your eyes are long? - They're long sideways.
- How can eyes... - They're long.
Why not say your eyes are pretty?
- They are long. - They're long.
She has long eyes.
- They are... - They actually are long.
- They're long. - They're long.
I've never seen long eyes. I've seen them almost stuck.
- I was told they were long. - They reach sideways.
You get one point.
Say something in English to your foreign fans.
Thank you.
- Five... - Hi, love you.
- Five... - Be healthy.
- What? - He's right.
- "Be healthy." Good health. - Oh, "be healthy."
- Five... - I love you, everyone.
- She said that. - That came up.
- She said that! Come on! - Incorrect.
- He doesn't listen. - Why don't you listen?
What were you going to say?
I was thinking of something else because...
My mind went blank...
- when he said "be healthy." - "Healthy?"
"Why is he speaking Chinese?"
That's what I thought.
- We're supposed to use English. - We won.
That's when I forgot she said "I love you."
"Be healthy?"
- "Healthy." - "Healthy."
- I was wishing them good health. - "Healthy."
Nickname for a lover.
Kyung Eun, My love.
Very funny.
That's funny. Incorrect!
Babe.
- Babe. - Shouldn't it be in five syllables?
Those are the same words.
- Incorrect! - Incorrect!
She said that so Vata wouldn't misunderstand.
- You call him "babe?" - She calls him "babe."
Why didn't you say things like "ciabatta?"
- Ciabatta. - You handled it well.
- Ciabatta! - Ciabatta.
- Nice. - Ciabatta.
My role model in five syllables.
- Jee Seok Jin. Five syllables? - Five syllables.
Go!
Five,
- four... - Awesome Jee Seok Jin.
- That was close. - Five...
In with many dreams.
- "In" for person! - "In" for person!
- In with many dreams. - "In." Okay, for now.
One, two...
Protruding Jae Seok.
One...
Elderly Jong Kook.
Romantic Ye Eun.
- Come on. - Come on.
- It's correct. - It makes no sense.
- He said it well. - It makes no sense.
- She's my role model. - We're talking about role models.
- I think she's... - Am I your role model?
- He said it well. - What's wrong with you?
- She's my role model. - She's his role model.
- He said she's romantic. - He wants to be a romantic.
- Love... - If he has a valid reason...
- It makes no sense. - Since when were you a romantic?
My wife and I have been starting a really passionate phase lately.
- He wants to start it. - A timeless kind of love.
We're not just thinking about it. We've already started.
- I see. - He's lying.
- That's nonsense. - Like Ye Eun...
Like the way she felt when she first fell in love.
He fell in love, and he's been married...
- for 20 years... - Your 1st love...
What if he never loved her?
Would he take a one-week-old relationship...
- Tell them you never loved her. - And...
- you want to start fresh. - You'll start to love her now.
- If he agrees, count it as correct. - Okay.
Then we'll approve.
You got married without being in love,
lived without love all this time,
Now they'll start being in love.
and now you'll start love. If you admit that, we'll approve.
- Now, Ye Eun... - You...
You should have just mentioned...
- Lim Ha Ryong or Joo Byung Jin! - That's right.
- Why didn't you? - You could've mentioned...
That was a stretch.
What were you doing...
- during our five turns? - Exactly.
You should have been thinking.
- Honestly... - You saw me.
- Gosh. - Do you think I wanted to say...
"Awesome Jee Seok Jin?"
- "Dance King..." - I called an absurd person...
- "awesome." - "Dance King..."
- This also isn't right... - Let's play fair.
It's over.
As a result of the second mission,
the team of four won.
- Okay! - Yes!
Okay!
- Nice. - It can happen.
- It can happen. - The winning team...
- Yes. - You can pick seven envelopes.
No, it's...
- Then... - Chungha...
- Two? - should pick two.
- Let's all pick one first. - Okay.
Pick one.
I really didn't listen to what others said.
- This one. - At the...
- Number 19. - I got number 12.
I also told you that the winning team...
- wins one of the lunch menu items. - Yes.
- There are colors here. - Yes.
We'll give you the dish corresponding to one color.
- You should pick red. - Jae Seok.
- Red seems like kimchi. - Jae Seok.
Why don't we pick green?
- What if we get vegetables? - Right. It would be vegetables.
Then let's go with red.
What if they give us kimchi?
Yellow must be eggs.
- I want orange. - No.
What if they give us pickled radish?
- Right. Orange. - Orange.
- Orange. - What's orange?
- Orange. - There's orange food?
- What's orange food? - You've picked orange.
When we get there,
- All right. - you'll get the dish.
For orange foods, there are things like rose.
- Rose or malatang. - That's possible.
I want to eat.
- I'm hungry. - Right.
The restaurant.
- This place... - It's an udon place.
- Udon, nice! - It's Yeongbingak!
- Yeongbingak. - Hold on.
- A Chinese restaurant? - It's a Chinese restaurant.
What's orange here? Jjamppong?
- Jjamppong? - Why are you so excited?
- It's food. She's Food Fighter. - Ye Eun!
- Jjamppong would be great. - Jjamppong?
- Orange... - It must be jjamppong!
It's Chinese food!
Jjamppong. We'll get jjamppong!
Jjamppong sounds great!
- All right! - It must be so delicious.
What's orange here? Jjamppong?
The smell...
- What's orange? - What is it?
- What's orange? It's... - What is it?
What's orange? It's carrots?
What is it?
- Green was better. - Hello.
- Yellow. - We're getting a carrot.
- Yellow was nice. - Yellow.
We should have picked yellow.
- It was a carrot. - How disappointing.
We should have picked red.
Yellow was nice.
- It's a carrot. - We should've chosen that.
- What's the green one? - Jae Seok.
- Black was jjajangmyeon. - Carrot.
Black was jjajangmyeon.
- You should have picked black. - Goodness.
We should have just picked red to get kimchi.
- Can I eat those jellies? - That looks good.
I want to eat them.
Black, green!
- Goodness. Green was nice. - It's nice.
That's pink.
- What is it? - That's pink.
- Pink salt? - Pink salt.
The orange food the team of four picked...
after winning the second mission...
was raw carrot.
Seriously.
I guess they're horses. Are they horses?
Horses.
It's the Year of the Red Horse.
We should have thought more simply.
- Eat it. - Their faces...
- go well with carrots. - That's right.
You can see similar faces when you go to the zoo.
Everyone,
you'll also have a chance to choose a lunch menu item.
There are ten dishes here.
Please write down the color of the dish you want to eat...
on the panels we give out.
We're going to bet on it, right?
The people whose color...
doesn't show up on the color board...
- They won't get to eat. - They won't get to eat.
No, if it doesn't show up, you can eat.
You can eat if the color doesn't show up.
If it shows up, you can't eat.
If the same color appears in all three,
there will be no penalty for anyone.
Okay.
- The purple one is also tasty. - What's the purple one?
- Acai berry. - Acai bowl.
- That's not good for now. - I won't eat that.
We're on a diet.
- Isn't that right? - On a diet?
- What are you talking about? - What diet are you on?
- You're Food Fighter, not dieting. - We have to control our diet.
Food Fighter.
- Purple! - I want brown as well.
- Green is fine too. - Purple isn't bad.
- Purple and green. - I'll pick purple.
- We should have jjajangmyeon. - That's right.
Whether we get it or not, we should go with jjajangmyeon.
Let's go!
- Please! - All right.
Don't show up.
Please don't show up.
We'll spin the first color board.
- Let me just get one dish. - Don't show up.
Please let me have jjajangmyeon.
Don't show up.
That's right.
- Please. - Green, don't show up.
Let it be red.
- Green or red should show up. - Red.
Black!
- This is random, right? - Black.
- It showed up! - It's black!
Yes!
- Nice. - Amazing.
Okay! Nice!
- Jjajangmyeon is out. - But...
what if black shows up on all three of them?
Then no one will be at a disadvantage.
Everyone gets to eat.
That won't be easy.
Okay.
- Spin the second one. - It won't be easy.
Let it be yellow.
- Yellow. - Yellow.
- Please! - There's brown as well.
- Yellow shouldn't show up. - Purple.
- Black. - Brown.
- Look at that! - Brown.
Look at that! You never know!
It's black.
- Is it black? - You never know!
- Let's go! - Black!
- Right. - Will we all get to eat?
- Will we all get to eat? - Okay.
- The third one. - Black!
- Spin it. - It shouldn't be black.
- Black! - Let it not be yellow.
Black!
The lottery. Let's go!
No.
- Let's all be happy. - Let it not be yellow.
- Black! - Please.
Let it not be green.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
- Purple! - Okay!
Aren't we all eating?
No one chose purple. Who chose purple?
- No one. - Everyone gets to eat in our team.
This is interesting.
Everyone gets to eat in our team.
- This is interesting. - Goodness.
- This... - Did you manipulate it?
- How is this possible? - Okay!
- They all won't get to eat. - This is ridiculous.
- Yes! - Yes!
The five of you...
will get the dishes of the colors you wrote.
Okay!
Yes!
Manipulation makes no sense.
How would they manipulate that?
- Bravo! - We get to eat.
You'll get the dishes of the colors you wrote.
- We got pork cutlet. - How nice.
Pork cutlet!
Okay! Curry.
It's pasta, right?
- Pasta. - It looks great.
- Let's share. - It looks great.
- Let's share. - Is this...
- It's gnocchi. - Is it gnocchi?
Thank you for the food.
Okay!
Pork cutlet!
- I wanted an Italian dish. - Is it good?
It's good.
This is nice.
Try some.
I wanted an Italian dish.
Let's share.
It's really good for your health.
The pork cutlet tastes good.
I wanted an Italian dish like this.
It's amazing.
What's that? Is that pasta?
- It's gnocchi. - I'm hungry.
- The gnocchi looks good. - Oh, of course.
The gnocchi looks really good.
It's coated in basil pesto.
- What a bummer. - They're lucky.
How is it that only our team is left out of eating?
We're the only ones not eating.
Tell me about it.
This is just impossible.
We're the unluckiest people.
- So Mi, is it good? - You have no idea.
- No way. - The carrots are really good too.
- These are delicious. - Exactly. They're so good.
Lucky you.
These are really good for you.
Those who didn't get to eat...
Can we pay for our food?
- Can we eat if we pay? - Pay up if you want to eat.
For 50 dollars,
you'll get the dish of your choice.
- That's too expensive. - Are you kidding me?
- I don't have 50 dollars. - That's too expensive.
- I thought it'd be 10 dollars. - Who has 50 dollars?
- If it were 10 dollars... - For 5 dollars...
- Yes? - Get a random dish?
We'll spin the color board again.
I'd choose the five-dollar option.
Let's do it.
I'll pay five dollars.
- Five dollars? - Which one?
- I chose jjajangmyeon. - It should cost a dollar.
- I'll pay five dollars too. - Here.
Can I see the person pressing the button?
- I have my suspicions, you see. - You know...
- Let me see him. - No, don't.
- He's trustworthy. - We brought in an outsider.
I know. He's trustworthy.
- I'll take my chances. - Should I join in?
- I'll go first. - Se Chan, pay five dollars.
I'll pay five dollars too...
- Of course you should. - and join him.
Jjajangmyeon for five dollars is a good deal.
I should eat the jjajangmyeon.
The jjajangmyeon.
- Do us right. - There was a time...
when jjajangmyeon was only five dollars.
There you go.
- Aren't you joining in? - No.
- I'll see how it goes. - You're right.
The black one.
Why aren't you joining in?
This is a guaranteed win.
Let's go.
I'll go first since I paid up.
Se Chan will go first.
- I hope it fails. - I hope it fails.
Let him fail on the first round.
Just this once, please. I swear I'll enjoy the jjajangmyeon.
I don't think it'll show up.
Let it land on black so that it crushes his dream.
- I don't think it'll show up. - I have a good feeling about this.
- You're looking good. - It'll land on black.
Stop!
That's it.
- Okay, bring on the next one. - Next.
I have a good feeling about this.
It won't land on black because it started on black.
- This one started on black... - Stop!
and ended on black.
- She's right. - It went past black.
Stop. Okay!
Stop.
Okay!
Ssaebssaeb will get to eat at this rate.
Come on!
I have a good feeling about this.
I hope this one lands on black.
- It's the last one. - It'll be funny if this one fails.
It shouldn't show up for me, but for Jae Seok.
I have a good feeling about this.
This should land on black.
I think you'll be able to eat.
- I think so too. - Right?
- I have a good feeling about this. - Life is about timing.
Wait, this is getting dangerous!
My gosh!
Let me get a look at his face.
Mister!
Don't you play games with me!
- It's my turn now. - He played me.
- As if. - It's my turn now.
- That was close. - All right.
I think Jae Seok will succeed.
- Right? - Make him fail right off the bat.
- Play him in the first round. - Go, me!
- Go, Jae Seok! - Make him fail right away.
- Go, Jae Seok. - Go, me.
Those two already landed on black before.
- I know. - Unbelievable.
- Black... - I have a good feeling about this.
- Please. Let's do this! - Right off the bat.
- Make him fail on the first round. - That'll be really funny.
Don't let it get around to red.
- It went past black. - He's in the clear.
- Yes. - It went past black.
- Blue. - You're in the clear.
- I don't want to see red. - Mister, do your thing!
Tweak it a bit at the end.
Go, me. This is random, right?
- Yes. - I really believe this is random.
There aren't any tricks involved.
Seeing red is a bad sign.
- Seeing red is a bad sign. - Here we go.
- It's black! - Yes!
Go see the mister's face.
- Mister! - This isn't random, is it?
Don't mess with us like this.
- Let's party! - It must land on black a lot.
- This is delicious. - It's okay.
- You'll pass if you try again. - I agree.
This is how you lose all your money.
- "It's for real this time." - Se Chan, go for it.
- This is how you lose it all. - How can you not try again...
when you've already spent the money?
- This is how you lose it all. - It's only ten dollars.
Think you're retrying for ten dollars.
Think about how much you've already spent.
I'm sure it'll work this time.
This is how you lose it all.
- Can you spin all three at once? - Are you sure?
- This time... - Let's see that this time.
Go for it. I'm sure it'll work.
- Go, Se Chan. - I'll stand over here.
- The vibe over there is bad. - Sounds good.
- Spin all three at once. - At once.
This is making me nervous.
My color is black.
- Spin them all at once. - It'll work this time.
Don't try anything funny with the button.
Just press it.
- Press the button. - Here we go.
Doesn't this look like...
This looks awfully familiar.
- It's like we're in Las Vegas. - Hey.
- One, two... - Look.
- Are you kidding me? - Look over there.
Mister! Seriously?
- Try it one last time. - For the very last time.
- Try one last time. - Stop it.
- Ssaebssaeb. - Hey.
- Again? - Go ahead. It'll work this time.
- Just stop. - Mister.
- Ssaebssaeb, that's enough. - Are you kidding me?
- This time... - Why are you doing this?
- It won't land on black this time. - It won't.
- It'll work this time. I'm sure. - You'll get it this time.
- What if he fails again? - That'll be bad.
- That one got off to a late start. - It's okay.
- I have a good feeling about this. - I don't think it'll work.
Mister!
- There! Oh, no. - Mister!
Where on earth is he? Mister!
Where is he? Who is it?
What's with that guy?
Don't I get anything?
I made him gamble.
Don't I deserve about five dollars?
- Darn, forget it. - Oh, dear.
- Why not just eat for 50 dollars? - Exactly.
I'll try one last time, and that'll be it.
How is this even possible?
What do you have against me?
What could this be?
- What's this? - What's going on?
There's a lot going on over there.
No way.
- I wonder what this is. - What is this?
- Check this out. - These are darkrooms.
- What are these? - You're right. They're darkrooms.
What's going on?
- Is it something random? - What's this?
What kind of game are we playing?
Please go into the booth with your name on it.
- What? - Just like that?
- Just like that? - Right away?
- I love things like this. - But...
- I love being secretive. - Is this a sign?
- What? - Will I be getting a mission?
- What's this? - What's this?
What's this?
There are clothes inside.
What's going on?
Do we have to change clothes?
- What? - What's this?
I'm loving the hipster vibe.
This is pretty.
Hold on. Why are they priced differently?
What's going on?
Fifty dollars, twenty dollars, and free.
With the money you've earned,
- you may buy one of the T-shirts. - Right.
For this round's color board,
the color of the T-shirt you bought...
will be used.
There will be fewer colors, the more expensive the T-shirt is.
I see.
But this is really expensive.
I mean...
This one has four colors.
What can I do when I don't have a lot of money?
This one has a lot of colors.
There's a huge difference.
Do I have to take a gamble?
I don't have a lot of money.
I only chose envelopes with ten dollars in them.
I only chose envelopes with the same amount of money.
Seriously, Mister?
I'm broke.
I lost 20 dollars trying to eat jjajangmyeon.
I'm broke, you see.
Besides, I ate too many carrots, and I don't want to wear orange.
I'm broke.
I see.
- This only has red and yellow. - Right.
Which one should I buy?
- Number 19! - Number 19.
- I'll take number 12. - I'll take...
I hope you get the smallest amount.
- I could give him some. - Darn it.
Did you choose one with lots of money?
I'm pretty sure orange is in my color palette.
I think this will look good on me too.
Which color suits me better?
This one or this one?
Is this better?
I knew it. My color type is vivid spring.
I'm kind of rich.
I'll spend 20 dollars.
Here.
I don't need a receipt.
I don't need a cash receipt.
Okay. Do I put it on?
- I'm still on the fence. - I only have 30 dollars.
Seriously?
I spent 20 dollars in the previous round.
I'm broke.
Exactly, and you have to be wise about spending money.
- You ended up... - Tell me about it.
spending ten dollars trying to eat jjajangmyeon.
- I know. - Right?
I'm broke too.
I knew a lot of people would choose the blue one.
- Hey. - Hi!
I guess you had 20 dollars to spend.
Is Ji Hyo broke?
I love it.
- What on earth? - No way.
What?
Haha must have a lot of money.
- He won the last round, remember? - He's rich.
When did you go behind our backs...
and save up all that money?
I bet he got 100 dollars in the first round.
He must be rich if he bought this for 50 dollars.
- Still... - Didn't you spend your money?
I see you all chose not to spend money.
The red one was too expensive.
- It's not that. We're just broke. - It's not that. We're just broke.
You chose not to spend money.
You're showing off your big fat wallet.
- Do you have the most money? - Why are you showing off?
You have over 100 dollars to spend.
I didn't say anything.
- What did I say? - Of course, he...
How did you end up with 50 dollars to spend?
- What? - What?
- Are you broke? - Chungha, are you broke?
You must be broke.
Where's my bag?
- So Mi, you have cash. - So Mi.
So Mi has cash.
Rather than keep the money...
- Young and rich. - So Mi.
You went all out.
- I should stand here. - It's just me?
You're the only one in red.
Okay, let's go!
Gosh.
- I just have to avoid two! - You look cool.
- It would be fun if red came up. - What?
I just need to avoid these two.
We planned for you to wear that...
and take part in an outdoor mission,
but it's raining, so before we do that,
we'll have a short tea break.
- It's tea time. - Out of the blue?
It's what you like, Seok Jin.
- Tea time. - Desserts.
- Gosh. - Gosh, all this...
Nice one. Okay, thank you.
I like coffee and salted butter rolls.
- "Salt bread." - Yes...
- "Salt bread." - Why not say...
- Cheesecake! - Oh, gosh.
- Cheesecake. - Financier.
Cheesecake.
- Cheesecake. - I want cheesecake.
I guess we can all...
You don't get to eat for free.
- You don't get to eat for free. - What?
- What? - Is this the 50-dollar end?
- Really? - We spin that thing?
No more spinning.
- Don't spin that. - Don't do that.
- I have no money. - It can't be.
- What do we do? - It's not for free.
The cheesecake looks amazing.
According to the Running Man pricing system,
a beverage costs ten dollars.
- What? - That's too expensive.
- We can't eat, then. - Why are you like this?
- Coffees cost 1.5 dollars now. - Yes.
- We can't eat. - Ten dollars per baked good.
Don't do that!
- We can't eat, then. - We must starve.
Let's boycott tea time. None of us will eat.
- Put it down. - I won't eat.
- I won't eat. - I won't eat.
- I won't eat. - No one here can eat.
- I have no money. - I have no money.
They spent zero dollars on clothes.
We'd be willing if you priced them at five dollars each.
However,
if you pay five dollars, we'll let you pick one color...
- and test your luck with the board. - For real?
- It's too expensive. - Rather than eat for ten,
you get two shots at testing your luck.
I really have no cash.
I'll play.
Seok Sam. Come on.
- For real? - I'll play for an iced Americano.
What color will you pick?
It's black!
- Congrats. - Jjajangmyeon.
You must pay five dollars up front.
Here. I'd like the change, please.
I really want to eat, though.
Select a color.
Pink and brown didn't come up much.
Pink and brown. Brown is rare.
- Then I'll pick... - Seok Jin. Trust my gut.
- Green... - Go pink.
- Pink was rare. - I say pink, too.
- Pink. - Pink didn't come up much.
I'll go blue. The color I'm wearing.
Blue? I think blue will come up.
Blue came up often.
- Okay. - Let's go!
Here goes.
You want a shot?
- What color was it? - Blue!
I think it'll come up.
We want blue to come up.
- No. - No.
We want it to come up.
- Okay, good. - Pink.
Pink would've been a disaster.
That's pink? It's not purple?
That's pink.
Is that spinning?
Blue.
Seok Sam might get to eat.
I think it'll be blue.
- It's rarely the second one. - Blue just went by.
- It's white. - My gosh.
- I get to eat. - You'll get your way.
- I'm almost there. - I have a good feeling about this.
Go!
- It would be funny if it were blue. - Let's go.
- It would be fun it if were blue. - Let's go.
- We want that. - Blue!
Blue.
- It's over. - He skipped blue.
- He gets a drink. - Congratulations.
I'm so annoyed.
- He got a drink for five dollars. - He got it.
That must be so good.
- It's so good. - I want to play even less...
- because he scored. - Let's not eat.
- Let's not eat. - Me, too.
If he gets a coffee and I don't...
- It's so good. - I'm so annoyed.
I'll play.
- So Mi. - So Mi. Okay.
I can't stand this anymore.
What do you want?
- I want... - Cake?
- Cheesecake. - Cheesecake. Okay.
Let's do this.
- Go for it. - You gave in.
- Five dollars. - You all have cash to spare.
Let's do this.
Good luck.
- Which one? Brown? - What color?
- Brown. - We haven't had brown.
- Brown is a good choice. - It has been too long.
- Too long. - Let's go.
- Brown. - It's been too long.
Green? Brown?
- Brown. - Brown.
- Brown. - We haven't had that color.
- True. - Right?
If we choose brown and...
Okay. Here goes.
It's brown, right?
Brown looks risky.
- No, brown's fine. It went by. - It went by.
- It went by. - It went by.
It's the first time we got brown.
- The first one... - Try again.
Play again.
Play again. Bet on brown again.
- Try brown again. - It's so annoying.
It's not about money now. It's about pride.
Not again.
- Here I go. - She's a moth to a flame, too.
- Gosh. - This is your chance.
This time...
What do you want?
- Cheesecake. - Cheesecake?
What color?
Brown again, of course.
- Brown? - Brown.
Brown...
- Brown. - Get back on the wagon.
- Brown. - Brown again?
Hop back on the wagon.
So Mi, you're on!
Okay, brown.
Brown.
- Brown. - Brown.
Orange. We haven't had that, either.
On the top... That's brown.
- It looks risky. - We avoided it so far.
Oh, good.
It went by.
- Good for you. - Very good.
- It went by. - Very good.
Cheesecake...
It looks like...
You got it again.
You got it. You're safe.
You did it.
- Just one more... - Hey.
You're dancing?
- Cheesecake... - Just one more.
She's acting up. It might be brown.
She teased us, didn't she?
- Acting up... - The teasing...
- So Mi, look. - If you act up...
- For real? - You're in danger.
Oh, no! You got it!
Why did you dance?
- Play once more. - No more.
- I'm out of cash. - Buy the cake.
No. I told you so.
It's pointless.
I spent all my money on the clothes.
It's too expensive.
- Should I play? - Play.
Doesn't it look so good? The smell is driving me insane.
I want the strawberry thing so much.
- It's so risky. - The visuals...
- How about... - Should I when I wasted 20 already?
Who will chip in with two dollars?
An Americano lasts just two gulps.
Please...
I really want to eat.
- An Americano. - Se Chan.
- You said we'd boycott. - You'll play?
Ssaebssaeb, you gambled everything and now you're wearing blue.
We got one win and two losses. It's time for a win now.
- It's time? - Five dollars.
- You're gambling too much. - A coffee.
- A coffee. - What color?
- So Mi got brown twice. - Yes.
- I'll go brown. - Gosh...
- Go! - It could come up.
- I'm aboard the wagon. - Brown...
- It's on brown. - Brown.
Brown... I have a bad feeling about it.
- Brown... - We didn't have orange.
If we get brown again,
just know I'll keep betting.
- I think it'll be brown. - Brown...
- Brown... - No.
- Brown just went by. - Gosh.
- Red. - Good for you.
Okay. Let's go.
This time...
Brown...
- This time... - My gut says...
Great.
Let's go!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- It feels weird, doesn't it? - Will he score?
Let's go.
It's brown.
- It's brown. - It's brown.
Oh, no!
Does this make sense?
- Oh, no! - What...
Mister! Is it just me?
Let's see the buttons. What buttons do you use?
Isn't it weird how it's always the last board?
It is. Don't you think it's weird?
- Is it just me? - By now...
Am I the only one who thinks it's rigged?
The board is the entertainer.
- The machine... Is it just me? - Okay!
- For real? - Come on.
Seriously...
It's not random.
Let's do this. I'll do this instead.
- Orange or yellow. - No, I will...
I'll pick a color so they don't know and leave.
- I won't tell. - You won't tell?
- Only then will the machine... - You won't tell?
Then I can accept it.
- Without telling... - You know what I mean?
Because the house...
- I can't trust the house. - Right.
I'll catch them at their own game.
- Here. - The color...
- Okay. - What will you do?
Okay. Are you seeing this?
- You need to come forward. - It's psychological warfare.
- That's it. - It's psychological warfare.
- So they don't know? - So they don't know?
Considering the probability, if I choose this...
No, the one above.
- This? - Yes.
- I pick this color. - That hasn't come up yet.
This hasn't...
Spin all three at the same time. This is my color!
- Okay. - Let's see.
- Let's see. - If this comes up...
There's no mention of what he chose.
I'm suddenly seeing orange.
This is crazy.
If it comes up this time, then honestly...
It can't be. There is no way...
What?
- Move! - We got orange for real!
- My goodness. - We got orange for real!
- It makes no sense. - I mean...
- We got orange. - He just can't win.
I'm so annoyed. Jae Seok, what's this?
- Seriously. - Hey.
- You shouldn't do it. - When did AI advance so much?
How could AI read my mind?
- I can't believe it. - You shouldn't do it.
- I won't. - Hey, try it one more time.
- No, I won't. - It's so aggravating.
I lost so much money.
This is unbelievable.
- Did we really get orange? - Really?
- This is unbelievable. - Se Chan.
I lost all of my money.
I have no money. Seriously.
This is...
- how you lose money in gambling. - It was so fascinating.
- I can't believe it. - I just can't catch a break.
It stopped raining. Let's head outside.
- Let's go. - Let's do that.
What's this?
- What's this? - Oh, my.
What is this for?
This is Running Man. Isn't that right, So Mi?
How scary.
- What's this? - Oh, my.
This is so scary.
- It's no joke. It's so slippery. - My goodness.
- Isn't this too much? - Are you serious?
I'm reminded of the time I was on "Let's Go! Dream Team."
So Mi, were you on "Let's Go! Dream Team?"
Yes, I was on the show back in elementary school.
But I was just an elementary student.
- An elementary student? - Yes.
Please do your best.
- It's the fifth level. - All right.
Ms. Jeon So Mi is really good.
She looks cool.
- You're something else. - Right?
- You're so unique. - You really are.
- You've done all sorts of things. - Seriously.
All right. Now comes the last mission of the day,
- Okay. - Very Very Very Slippery Warning.
What is it?
Very, very, very
Two people from each team will enter...
and go up the soapy water slope in the pinball-machine shape...
by grabbing the poles.
- Go up the slope? - My goodness.
Some poles are hard...
while others are limp.
- Really? - The limp poles will ruin us.
And while you go up the slope,
you can attack members of the other team...
and make them fall.
Okay. That's good.
Gosh, I'll have to activate the combat mode.
In each round, we'll measure the time it took...
the last member of the team to arrive at the top.
- Gosh, it's a team competition. - The last member.
The time it took the last member of the team to arrive.
That means all members need to go up the slope.
We'll have 3 rounds of a 2-on-2 match.
Okay.
Will the teams remain the same?
- Yes, they will. - The teams will remain the same.
- Okay. - The teams will remain the same.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Yes.
- Nice! - Yes! Let's go!
- So Mi, can you do it? - I can do it.
I have a bad memory regarding soapy water.
- No! - Why?
- She has been traumatized. - I've been traumatized.
- She got criticized back then. - Back then...
Why?
I got criticized for being terrible at the game.
The 1st round will be between groups of 2 men.
- Two men? - Let's go.
Then Seok Jin and Haha should enter.
- No. - Do it just this once.
- Come on. Just this once. - Jong Kook, do it just this once.
- That's right. - I'm on this team too.
- We need to win. - We need to win.
We need to do our best.
- Jong Kook, you should try it. - Okay.
- Test the waters. - Shall I do that?
- I see. - Then come up with a strategy.
I'll enter with you.
I'm on this team.
But you don't look very pitiful.
- You're too happy these days. - Seriously.
- Too happy. - You're too happy these days.
- You don't look very pitiful. - I'm on this team.
- You're too happy. - She is a shrimp.
- Your body is shaped like a shrimp. - How pitiful.
- Why is your back so hunched? - She is a shrimp.
Scrunch up your face more.
She is a shrimp.
I got criticized after playing a game involving soapy water.
You were sick back then.
Jong Kook, please sit out this once.
- We'll test the waters. - Since it's slippery,
- strength might not matter. - Exactly.
The powerful Kim Jong Kook.
- The two of them are too strong. - Not bad.
- Shall we begin? - Are you serious?
These two will go.
I think they're pretty strong.
- All right. - Shall we begin?
- Gosh, it's cold. - Gosh.
Yesterday's weather would've been perfect for this game.
- It's cool and nice. Okay. - It's cold.
There are socks.
Socks are over here.
- There they are. - There are socks.
There they are.
Socks are over here.
- There they are. - There are socks.
It hurts.
What's this?
For goodness' sake. It hurts to step on the ground.
Why? Seriously.
My feet hurt! What's going on?
- Hey! - What's going on?
- What? - It's a penalty.
Hey!
Does it hurt?
Where does it hurt?
- My goodness. - It hurts so much.
It hurts too much to step here.
- It's no joke. - Here.
- It's an acupressure mat. - All right.
Is this the starting line?
Yes, this is the starting line.
- Okay. - Here.
- Let's check it out. - The powerful Kim Jong Kook.
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
- Hey. - Here we go.
All right. The teammates are wearing the same-colored helmets.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's see how it is.
Jong Kook is standing next to me.
- He'll shoulder you. - Let's go slowly.
- Slowly. - Of course.
- Let's go slowly to the pool. - Okay.
- Let's not make it hectic. - We'll get hurt.
- Let's get through the pool first. - Okay.
Let's go slowly.
Get ready.
Set.
- Slowly. - All right.
- Come on. - All right.
- All right. - All right.
It's that one.
Oh, my.
Let's do this.
- All right. - All right.
- It must be really slippery. - All right.
- Seok Jin, go where Se Chan is. - Let's do this.
Grab him and push yourself up.
- I can't go up at all. - Grab one.
All right.
- Go up. - What's this?
Let's do this.
- All right. - Jong Kook is really good.
- Why is he going up so easily? - Kick him.
All right.
I can't go up at all.
- All right. - It's slippery.
- Go up. - What's this?
Mister.
- All right. - It's slippery.
How is he so good at it?
Gosh, what's this?
I can't go up at all.
- All right. - It's slippery.
- Go up. - What's this?
Mister.
- You need to hurry up. - Hurry up.
- It's slippery. - All right.
All right.
- Mister. - Mister.
- Mister. - Hold on.
Mister!
Nice!
- All right. - All right.
- Mister. - Why can't you go up?
- It's slippery. - Mister!
Stop it!
Mister!
- What are you doing? - Mister!
- What are you doing, mister? - Jong Kook, you're too much.
- You're too much. - You're being too rough.
Mister.
- Hey, why can't you come up? - Seok Jin!
Come on up!
Seok Jin, I can't do it.
- Mister! - Hey!
- Come this way. - Seok Jin, come on.
Hurry up.
Why can't they go up?
I know that feeling.
Jae Seok, I can't do it.
- Hold on. Hey. - It's slippery.
Come this way.
Grab me. Come this way.
Here.
Ssaebssaeb, come this way.
Grab my leg.
Se Chan.
I know that feeling.
- Go. - I know that it's hard.
It's slippery.
Hurry up.
You're doing well.
There you go. Quickly.
- Grab me. - There you go.
- Quickly. - Hurry up and get him!
For goodness' sake!
Grab his leg!
- There you go! - That's it!
Seok Jin, grab one.
- Go! - Go up there with him.
- Grab his leg! - There you go!
- That's it! Pull him. - Go up there with him.
Pull him. There you go.
- Hurry up and climb up. - Hey.
Go up there.
- Gosh, Ssaebssaeb! - Hurry up and climb up.
- I can't do it. - Come on.
I know that feeling.
Seok Jin, get your legs up there.
Grab my leg.
- Get your legs up there. - Go up.
There you go.
- Go up. - Go up together.
- Ssaebssaeb. - Se Chan, hurry up.
- Let's go. - Go up.
- Come on. - They're going.
Hurry up.
Go up quickly.
- Grab the poles. - Go up quickly.
Here. Hurry up and grab it.
- Grab it! - Hold on.
- Grab the pole! - Go up.
- Hurry up. - Go.
- Come on. - You need to hurry up.
Hurry up.
I'm at the top. Come on.
- No! - Jong Kook!
Get him!
Jong Kook, get someone!
Come on.
- I did it! - For goodness' sake.
- I did it! - Yes!
Yes!
Gosh, I can't believe Seok Jin.
For goodness' sake.
No.
- Okay. - Gosh.
- For goodness' sake. - It's hard to climb up the slope.
Jae Seok, it won't be easy for them.
- Gosh, this is... - It's hard.
- It's hard. - My hands were slippery.
Stop giving excuses.
My hands were very slippery.
It wasn't that bad.
Okay. The next group will consist of 1 man and 1 woman.
- One man and one woman. - One man and one woman?
I'll go with Ji Hyo.
Jong Kook, go again.
- Okay. - Team up with So Mi and win.
Let's do this, So Mi.
- Okay. - Let's go.
- Chungha, let's go. - Okay.
- Okay! - Let's go.
So Mi is going this time.
So Mi is strong.
I lift weights.
Three. Four.
Come on.
You make me ambitious.
How nice. She is no joke.
I lift weights.
I only do cardio.
- Let's go! Let's do this. - Let's go.
- Okay. - Chungha, let's go.
- Good luck. - Let's go.
- All right. - Let's go.
Let's win this time.
- Let's win a round, Jong Kook. - Okay.
- All right. - This is the second round.
- Okay! - Let's go.
Get ready. Set.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Chungha, go.
- Let's go. Go up. - Jae Seok.
They switched it to a hard pole.
- Go up. - Nice!
- That's it. Let's go. - Here I go.
- Okay. - My goodness.
- They got this. - Easy.
So Mi is fast.
- Chungha, go up. - My goodness.
There you go. You're doing well.
- Okay. - Go up.
- Look at that speed. - Easy.
- Chungha is good. - She is good.
Chungha!
It's slippery.
We got this.
- Jae Seok. - Okay.
- They got this. - Chungha!
Very easy.
Easy.
- Push everyone down. - No.
- I'm here. - No!
They got this.
- Chungha! - Push!
No!
- No! - Chungha!
- Chungha! - We did it. Good job.
We did it. Good job.
Push everyone down. Okay.
We did it. It's okay.
Hey.
What's up with Jae Seok?
- Chungha. - Chungha needs to go up now.
Grab her.
Are you okay?
- Are you okay? - You survived.
So Mi is good.
So Mi sure is different.
It's time for the last round.
- Ye Eun, come on out. - This is the decisive round.
I can't go up there, Ji Hyo.
- Ye Eun, come on out. - We're bound to win, Haha.
It's Ye Eun. It'll be impossible to lose.
- They'll win. - It's Ye Eun.
We're in trouble.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Ye Eun, come on out. - What am I going to do?
Is Ye Eun going next?
Just go.
It'll be impossible to lose.
- We can do it! - We can do it!
- Yes! - We can do it!
We can do it!
We got this.
Ssaebssaeb, you need to do well.
- Okay. - Ssaebssaeb looks cool today.
- All right. - It's okay.
- You should be inside. - Go.
- He got this. - Haha, no.
We... What's this?
This is the last round.
It'll be a dogfight.
I don't have much faith in Haha.
- Haha is in bad condition. - Get ready. Set.
Let's go.
- They're at it already. - Go.
It's okay.
Se Chan.
- That's it. Step on her. - Step on Ye Eun and go up.
No way.
That's good.
She is good.
I can't believe her.
Gosh, Ji Hyo is incredible.
- Come here. - Step on her.
- I... - Why are you stuck in the pit?
Come on.
Ssaebssaeb.
Go up the slope and take care of Ji Hyo.
- Ye Eun. - That's right. It doesn't matter.
- Haha, hurry up. - Ye Eun, go up the slope.
Go to the right. The pole is hard there.
It's okay.
Ye Eun, go up the slope.
Se Chan.
Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun, what are you doing? - Ye Eun.
Can't she come out?
Ye Eun, go up the slope.
- Se Chan. - What is Ye Eun doing?
- Can't she come out? - Se Chan.
- Ye Eun. - I can't get up.
- Is Ye Eun for real? - Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun! What is she doing? - What is Ye Eun doing?
- What are you doing? - What are you doing?
- Is she for real? - What are you doing?
- Is she joking around? - Hey.
Are you serious or joking around?
What are you doing?
- What is she doing? - Get up.
It's my first time seeing someone...
- struggle to escape the pit. - Seriously.
Ye Eun, what are you doing?
- Go up there. - Help me up.
Drag Haha down.
- I... - Ye Eun, drag Haha down.
- Ye Eun, why... - Grab Haha and go up, Ye Eun.
There you go. Grab Haha and go up.
- There you go. - Come slowly.
Grab Haha and go up to the side.
- I can't go up. - Go up there, Ye Eun.
- I can't do it. - Grab Haha's clothes and go up.
Are there no stairs?
Who is she talking to?
Hey, who are you talking to?
Had there been stairs, we wouldn't have taken that route.
- Step on the bottom and... - Why are there no stairs?
See? The dogfight has begun.
The dogfight has begun. Seriously.
Seriously.
What is Ye Eun doing?
- Ye Eun. - Grab him and go up the slope.
- I mean... - You need to hurry.
- Se Chan. - Grab his leg.
- Grab Haha's leg. - She lacks the strength.
- I really can't go up. - Grab it, Ye Eun.
Grab Haha's leg.
- She can't go up. - I don't have the strength.
- Ye Eun. - She lacks the strength.
- Go up quickly. - He is going up quickly.
- Go up. - Come on.
That's it. They'll win.
Haha!
- No! - Come on.
What are you doing?
- Why... - Ssaebssaeb.
Hey, just step on the limp poles and go up there!
Ye Eun, step on it and grab the pole in front of you.
Step on the limp poles, you punk!
Go to the left, you punk!
That's it. Go that way.
Come on.
There you go.
- Ye Eun, go up. - Ye Eun.
The opposite side.
Hey.
Let's go!
If Ji Hyo pushes her gently, she'll slide down.
Ye Eun, go up.
Ji Hyo, I'm so exhausted.
Ye Eun nearly reached the top.
If Ji Hyo pushes her gently, she'll slide down.
Ji Hyo, please let me off this once.
Let me go up there this once.
- Let me go up there this once. - Hey.
- Ye Eun. - Just once.
There you go.
Ye Eun, go up.
Haha, go up quickly.
Hey!
Hey, don't do that!
Se Chan! That's my underwear, you punk!
Are you kidding me?
Don't do that.
- Hey. - Se Chan, take it off!
Unbelievable.
Hey!
Hey, you little...
This is my underwear, you little...
- Come on. - Come on down.
Have you no manners?
Hey.
- There are no manners on this show. - Hey.
- Back in the day... - My underwear got pulled off once.
Back in the day, Jong Kook lost his underwear.
My underwear got pulled off once.
For goodness' sake!
For goodness' sake! Hey!
- Hey. - Ssaebssaeb.
- He is good. - Hey.
- Go up there. - He is good.
- Ye Eun. - Okay.
- He did it. - He did it.
- Okay. He did it. - He did it.
- We won! - He did it.
He tried to take off my underwear.
- Just this once. - Underwear.
Ssaebssaeb has strong legs.
- We did it. - I can't predict the result.
- This is... - I can't predict the result.
- You never know. - We won.
We did well.
- He startled me. - The underwear fiasco was funny.
Where are Se Chan's pants?
Somewhere over there.
- I'll pull down my T-shirt. - Pants.
I became humiliated in front of everyone.
It was okay since you were lying on your side.
On your side.
He is a lunatic.
I can't believe him. I wasn't underwater.
I thought I had become Adam.
- It wasn't that bad. - Seriously.
- It wasn't that bad. - It wasn't that bad.
- Only your thighs were showing. - That's right.
Here is the result of the last mission.
I bet we lost.
- We lost. - We lost indeed.
- That's so funny. - The combined time...
- determined the result. - The combined time.
For the four-member team,
- Please. - the total for the three rounds...
is 8 minutes and 33 seconds.
- It's 8 minutes and 33 seconds. - Seok Jin should've taken longer.
- I know. - For the five-member team...
- My guess is 7 minutes. - Is it 8 minutes?
It's 7 minutes and 23 seconds.
- Thank goodness. - Well done.
- We were at a disadvantage. - Thank goodness.
A big disadvantage.
- I know. - A big disadvantage.
It's all thanks to Ye Eun.
Thus,
the winning team of the last mission...
can add a color...
for the other team.
- How many? - We can add colors.
Just two people in total.
Pick one person at a time to add one color.
Is it even possible to add a color?
The losing team can add 1 color for 1 person.
- I see. - One?
Then you'll spin the color board one last time.
Does Se Chan have a lot of money?
- No, he doesn't. - Se Chan is number one.
- No, I used up all of my money. - He doesn't have money.
I used up all of my money.
- I can't do anything. - He is broke.
- I'm totally broke. - Judging from last time,
- Se Chan is the type to save up. - That's right.
He didn't buy clothes...
- to hold on to the fortune... - No way.
- he had amassed. - That's your style.
- I'm certain of it. - That must be his strategy.
- He is like that. - Ye Eun and Se Chan.
Se Chan has a lot of money.
I don't have money.
I really don't have money.
- Then Se Chan and... - Pick Jae Seok.
I like that.
Protruded Brothers.
- Give it to me. - Give it to me.
- How about red? - Sure.
- Go ahead. - Red and yellow.
- Where is my bag? - To whom?
- Se Chan will get yellow... - Yellow.
and Jae Seok will get red.
- Let's share our pain. - Exactly. That's it.
- As for us... - Haha?
- Haha will get blue. - Blue. That's right.
- Me? - Yes.
- Do it. - Okay.
- We already did it. - Do it.
Just you wait.
- "Do it." - You...
You'll have to wear three layers of underwear.
All the way up to here.
Get it? You should be prepared.
Go on. I'll...
I don't know what I'll do now. If he's going so far...
- Okay. - I'll...
I only pulled down people's pants in places like the mud...
so they could cover themselves.
Those who received more, please attach it to your shirt.
- Yellow, red... - Blue!
Se Chan, seriously...
Yes!
Let's do this!
- Let's do this. - Okay.
We'll spin the final color board.
The color of your shirt shouldn't show up...
for the last mission fund.
Okay!
The odds are really...
If orange and yellow don't show up, I'll win.
Orange, yellow, red.
Green, yellow, white, orange.
- Okay. - Please spin the first color board.
Let's go.
Okay.
- Please! - It shouldn't show up.
- Please. - It shouldn't show up.
There are so many.
There are so many colors.
- It's hard to avoid them. - No!
- No! - Okay!
- What's that? - Orange.
- Orange. - Is it brown or orange?
- Orange. - Okay! Orange is okay.
- Orange. - Okay!
Nice! Good.
Blue is back.
Nice!
- Good. - Orange!
- Let's do it one more time! - One more time.
- Yellow! - Yellow.
Orange, red.
Brown!
- Okay! - Orange!
Orange!
- Orange! We're going to survive! - Nice!
- It's orange. - Good!
- Orange! - Orange! We're going to survive!
What is this?
If all of them are orange, Team Orange will survive too.
- Orange! - Orange!
Orange.
- Yellow. - You don't have it, right?
- Yes. - Yellow or red!
Since he has red, we need yellow.
Yellow!
- Yellow. - You don't have it, right?
- Yellow or red! - It should just...
- Yellow! - Red.
Red.
- Let's have pink! - Okay.
- Pink, white, or brown. - Now, yellow or red.
We bought the 20 dollar shirt. What's happening?
Spin the last one.
What's happening?
There is no way.
This cost nothing.
- Yellow! - Pink!
- Please! Pink! - Yellow!
Red.
Yellow!
- Does this make sense? - We survived!
Does this make sense? Does this...
- Is this even possible? - No.
We survived!
- We survived! - We survived!
Red... You even had red.
I survived when I even had red.
- I made it through. - They...
- You... - This costs nothing.
- You... - Does this make sense?
You're in this together, aren't you?
- Are you having fun? - Does this make sense?
The four people who survived, please pick one each.
This doesn't make sense.
- It didn't show up. - This is amazing. Super amazing.
- Will we all get one? - This one's not good.
Tell me the numbers.
This is not good. Can I pick another one?
You can't.
- You can't. You picked it. - You can't!
- You can't. - You already picked it.
- You can't. - You can't take it back.
- He picked it. - Seok Jin is feeling them.
- He's touching them. - It's over once you've picked it.
- Tell me the numbers. - Eighteen.
- One. - Jae Seok, one.
Seven.
Just one?
- Seriously. - That's nice.
- Ten! - I...
Seven.
Seriously, this...
Are you kidding me?
This must be a prank.
How could you put one dollar?
I also have one dollar.
It only has one dollar.
Great.
- I suddenly feel happy. - Right.
There are envelopes with one dollar?
How come he's counting the money?
- Thirty dollars. - That's quite a lot.
Seven.
- The money... - I'm satisfied.
- Are you satisfied? - Yes.
The person in last place gets the penalty for sure.
- Top how many? - The top three...
will get a prize.
For the remaining five,
we'll do a random name draw.
- We'll spin the names... - That's going to be fun.
I can't trust the boards.
and select two extra people to get the penalty.
- Let's do this. - Okay.
I'll announce the top three...
- who won. - Right away?
What?
Right away?
Do we each check how much we have?
Hold on.
- What is it? - Someone stole my money.
- No way. - Come on.
- Stop it. - Stop it.
That's enough now.
How much was stolen?
Her legs went weak.
Hold on!
- Hold on! - Are you broke?
- Who is it? - Who is it?
You did that to me all my life, and now my daughter too?
He's mad.
- Jee and Ji... - Are you broke?
Jee and Ji...
- Seriously... - Are you broke?
You should have kept it well.
I think this is payback for Vata.
What are you talking about?
It wasn't me.
- It wasn't me. - You should...
It wasn't me. You know that, right?
You stole Vata's heart. Just let it go.
Come on!
The person wouldn't have opened your bag.
- Who was it? - You should take care of it.
Who did it?
You should have taken better care of your bag.
Was it you?
What is this girl?
Goodness.
No.
What is this girl?
- I'm really simple. - You're simple.
Do we play it barefoot?
- Barefoot? - This is...
Maybe it was something else, not his.
- We'll split. - Ten dollars each.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Who will take it back? - I'll take it back.
I'll draw their attention.
- Goodness. - What is this girl?
When did you steal it?
It wasn't me. It was that guy in blue.
- Why did you do it? - Ssaebssaeb...
I swear I didn't touch your bag.
- That's right. - That's true.
The money was outside.
What do you mean?
It was on the table.
Why did you leave it there?
This is Running Man.
If we don't say at the opening that there's no stealing today,
you have to be careful on your own.
It can't be helped.
Don't you know how it is in Running Man?
- You guys... - No!
Seriously.
- Who... - You'd feel comfortable here.
- Well done. - This is Running Man.
- That's right. - Today's...
It's the Running Man I knew.
lowest mission fund holder.
It's Ji Ye Eun.
With 11 dollars, Ji Ye Eun.
Seriously!
- Ma'am! - Ma'am!
Farewell!
They split the money. How much was it?
I had 41 dollars.
If you have 11 dollars, they took 30 dollars.
- Ma'am! - Ma'am!
- They took 10 dollars each. - They took 10 dollars each.
- They took ten dollars each. - I really hate you.
Ye Eun will get the penalty for sure.
We'll pick two more members to receive the penalty.
I'll announce the person in third place first.
- Third place. - It'll be the end...
if we're not in the top three.
There was only a one-dollar difference between third...
Really?
- What a shame. - and fourth place.
One of the 3rd and 4th place is Song Ji Hyo,
and the other is Yang Se Chan.
- What? - It's starting again.
- With my money... - He was rich.
He cheated.
Third place...
He's so annoying.
- is Song Ji Hyo. - Right.
What a relief!
Congratulations, Ji Hyo.
- Congratulations. - I won't get the penalty.
Se Chan is in fourth place. You're a penalty candidate.
If I hadn't played this game all day...
Yang Se Chan. I wish Yang Se Chan gets it.
I'll announce the first place.
I picked many envelopes, but I don't have much.
- I don't have money. - You're in first place, right?
It would be So Mi.
- First place... - It's Jeon So Mi.
- has 175 dollars. - What?
- Why so much? - It's not me.
- First place is... - Why so much?
Chungha.
You had a lot of money!
- I guess I did. - You picked a lot.
- She... - You had a lot.
This is amazing.
That's it!
It's one bill.
It's 20 dollars.
Twenty dollars is the smallest amount.
- Twenty dollars? - That's the smallest so far.
Who didn't get to pick...
Chungha should pick two.
And the rest of us will play rock-paper-scissors.
- It's 1 dollar. - I also got 1 dollar.
There's an envelope with one dollar?
How much did you pick?
Me? I got 100 dollars.
- Now? - Yes.
Just now?
- Finally. - Seriously?
I've only picked a dollar so far.
- She picked 100 dollars at the end. - She got 100 dollars.
- Really? - That's amazing.
And second place is So Mi.
That's amazing.
- It suddenly went up. - It's amazing.
- Unbelievable. - I.O.I.
- All of a sudden. - My goodness.
So, the penalty candidates...
- I picked terrible ones. - are Se Chan, Seok Jin,
Jong Kook, Haha, and Jae Seok.
This is so disappointing.
I'm upset.
I played dirty today.
Gosh, Se Chan.
I hope he gets the penalty.
It has to be Yang Se Chan.
- I'm sure it will be him. - Yang Se Chan!
- Ye Eun. - If we spin it...
and get our names, that means it's our fate.
All right.
We will pick two members...
- to get the penalty with Ye Eun. - I want Yang Se Chan.
- Spin the board. - It's random, right?
It's random, right?
It's random.
- It's random. - It's random.
- Random! - It's not fun!
Yang Se Chan!
- It has to be Se Chan and Haha. - I lost many times.
- Yang Se Chan! - Yes!
This is ridiculous.
Yang Se Chan!
You guys input...
How does this make sense?
Can you believe this?
- It doesn't make sense. - The input... AI...
- Yang Se Chan! - How is this possible?
It doesn't make sense.
This is interesting.
Am I the only one who finds it strange?
Isn't it suspicious?
- It won't make sense if I'm picked. - The whole time...
- It's Haha. It has to be Haha. - Don't be like that.
- Haha. - Use all your skills.
- Make it Haha. - Make it Haha.
- That's impossible. - Please! Make it Haha.
- Haha. - Haha.
Haha, come on out.
This is it.
I don't care.
As long as I don't come in last place, it's fine.
If there is justice, it has to be Haha.
- Please. - Haha.
- Haha. - Haha.
- Use the tricks... - No!
- Haha! - Yes!
Darn it!
What are you doing?
It goes according to the plan.
Get lost!
You can do this.
- It doesn't make sense. - By the way...
I knew it.
- This is... - How is this possible?
- This isn't random at all. - How does this make sense?
I was completely fooled.
They say this was made using coding.
Haha's mother is here.
Mother!
"Get lucky this year."
Haha's mother is here.
- This doesn't make sense. - My gosh.
What's all this?
Bring in today's prize and penalty.
What's the prize?
The prize is a fruit rice cake set,
- which is popular these days. - Oh, dear.
A fruit rice cake set.
The penalty is...
- It's a rainbow. - the rainbow sponge.
- This is not bad. - Oh, dear.
But the three of us...
I'm happy. I'm feeling good anyway.
- Still, justice prevails, right? - Anyway...
Justice does prevail.
- My goodness. - How is this possible?
- It was a trap. - This is neat.
- Coding, my foot. - Good.
- Move from side to side. - Press well...
- as if you're taking a fingerprint. - From left to right.
- From left... One at a time. - Start.
Help them move their faces one by one.
- Se Chan goes first. - One by one?
- That's it. - My goodness.
- It looks good. - Hey.
- My goodness. - You look nice.
- You look like a soccer fan. - Hey, you look like a hooligan.
You look like a soccer fan.
From left to right.
You look like a soccer fan!
- You look like a soccer fan. - It looks nice.
- From left to right. - It's pretty.
It looks good.
- Hey! - You're soccer fans.
Soccer fans.
It looks cool.
- Thank you, everyone. - Thank you.
It's number three.
I picked number three.
Number three.
It actually makes sense.
Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- This is crazy. - Let's steal it.
- We should steal it. - This is it.
I knew it.
- Here we go. - Okay.
- Strike. - What was that?
- I was feeling anxious. - Why?
I was worried the guests might be changed...
because of the news about Ye Eun's boyfriend.
- Hey, Bald Eagle! - Good work!
I'm at 100 percent power right now.
- I was really surprised. - Won Been is...
It's out.
- What is this? - I stole it.
- Whose is this? - I stole it.
- What? - The hat...
- It stinks. - No!
His hairstyle is exactly the same.
How could that be, you fool?
What are you doing?
Move over.
- Hurry. - One, two...
The important thing is whether it's gold or not.