- It was 2020. - I think something incredible is...
about to happen today.
The Card Shark Association was founded by gamblers...
from all over the country.
I told you not to come!
Under the name, they robbed the pushovers of their caramels.
It's so sweet.
They even tried to make it big using the world-class card sharks.
I'm going all in.
An unexpected sweep by a rookie card shark.
The very existence of the Card Shark Association...
has become uncertain.
- Catch him! - Hurry.
Catch him!
To make a last stand,
the chairperson calls the card sharks back together...
after two years.
I'm the chairperson. Hello.
Before coming in here, Seok Jin told me...
I looked like a pathetic loser.
He's being ridiculous.
I won't let him off easy today.
I have to collect caramels first. Or I'll lose them right away.
- Hello, Jong Kook. - Okay.
I'm the chairperson of the association today.
- That's great. - I'll appreciate your cooperation.
I believe you've become the chairperson for a reason.
- That's right. - Sure.
I know. All right.
- Today, before people are coming... - Yes.
There they are. Hello.
Hello.
Hey.
- Hello, Chairperson Yang. - All right.
It's been a while.
- Oh, dear. - Thank you.
- Is this your first time here? - Yes.
By the way, why do you greet us like this?
- It's so... - Like this.
He looks like he stinks.
- I stink? - He stinks.
He really stinks.
I'm the chairperson.
- Okay? - He stinks?
- How dare you? I'm the chairperson. - He looks drunk?
- He looks drunk? - Hey, have you been doing well?
- Hey, you're Park Wan Kyu. - Park Wan Kyu.
- Hello, Park Wan Kyu. - Even after a thousand years
- He's... - I won't be able forget you
- Because I loved you - Because I loved you
- I'm Ryoo Seung Bum. - I like you.
- He does look like Park Wan Kyu. - What?
He's Park Wan Kyu.
- Park Wan Kyu. - I'm Ryoo Seung Bum.
You feeble things.
- Okay! - You guys are here together.
- Okay. - You guys are here together.
Who is he?
Hello. You're here.
- Hey. - Okay.
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Who is this silly-looking brat?
- This is... - I saw you at the salon today.
Yes.
- I guess you go to the same salon. - Yes.
- You do? - Yes.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Hello. - Hey.
- Yu San Seul. - A trot singer?
Isn't he a trot singer?
- Hello. - I'm sorry,
but aren't you a zookeeper?
- You are... - A zookeeper?
- Do you have animals? - Yes.
- A zookeeper. - I work at Everland.
- You work at Everland. - Nice to meet you.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
- You guys... - Why are you the chairperson?
- I know. - That's how it ended two years ago.
You're drunk.
I had a drink. Please understand.
- He's drunk. - Right.
I just had one drink.
- You can't be drunk at work. - You stink.
- How could you drink before coming? - You had just one drink.
- Wait. Are you a shopper or what? - No.
- I'm a pearl. - You're...
- My name is Ji In Ju. - What?
- Ji In Ju. - A white pearl.
Hey, why do you look so nice?
- I look pretty. - You should try harder.
- What's this? - Come on!
- Hey! What are you doing? - He's wearing a wig.
- It's a wig. - Look at him.
- He's a fake. - He's a fake.
- Excuse me, mister. - What are you talking about?
- He's a fake. - It's a wig.
- He's a fake. - No.
- You're a fake. - This is my hair.
My real hair.
By the way, why aren't you wearing a costume?
- I'm wearing a costume. - What are you?
- What are you dressed up as? - This is what I can do.
I get it! You're Trainer Yang Chi Seung.
- That's right. - Hey.
- That's it. - Trainer Yang Chi Seung.
- Trainer Yang Chi Seung. - Trainer Yang wears that.
He does?
I was going to wear a leopard-print outfit,
but I thought you guys would wear the same thing.
- That's so obvious. - So I'm dressed like this.
Today, we're doing the card shark thing again...
- after two years. - I've been waiting for this.
Because of Tae Hyung,
- Right. - we went broke.
- You went bust. - V.
Before the race begins today,
we will give you a gift.
- What is it? Are we betting it? - Is it a prize?
- A gift? - Is it someone's birthday?
- Who is it for? - What?
- Is it for the chairperson? - What is this?
- Is it a holiday gift? - Hang on.
- What? - Is this Seok Jin's merchandise?
Look at her hair.
Her hairstyle looks the same.
It's Su Wan.
She's a star.
- Let's take a photo together. - Their backs look the same.
- We look the same. - Do they sell this hairstyle?
- Su Wan's hairstyle. - The gift is...
- for Seok Jin. - What?
- I see. - From last week?
- Me? - It's for his 60th birthday.
- The thing from last week? - The thing from last week?
- Please give him a big hand. - Thank you, everyone.
If you tell us what you want,
we will buy it and give it to you next week.
Can we all have a team dinner with the prize money?
- This is... - Open it.
- Open it. - Can I open it?
- There were many comments... - This is...
wishing Grandpa a happy birthday.
You darn brat!
- How could you... - People can say that.
I have the face of a 40-year-old.
- There were comments like that. - Stay quiet.
You're officially a grandpa now.
- They celebrate Grandpa's birthday. - It's a secret.
It's a secret between the entire nation and us.
I'll become a grandpa once my son has a child.
You fool!
- But you're... - Unbelievable.
- Why are you so upset? - Right.
Just open the gift.
- Just open it. - Okay.
Actually, I wanted to have a team dinner with the money.
- But you... - I got a gift instead.
That's what the production crew thought,
but you called them and asked for a gift later.
You told them what you wanted.
- He did? - What he wanted?
They told him to say what he wanted for his birthday,
and he said he wanted shoes.
- Seriously? - I even told them my size.
That's a little...
They said they'd give me a gift during the opening.
- My goodness. It's Dior! - My gosh.
I don't like things like this.
You said you liked Dior.
He likes Dior.
- Let me see. - What's this? Dior?
- It's shoes. - I don't like things like this.
- It's pretty. - This is really...
- He chose this, right? - No.
- It's not like that. - He'd fall if he wore these.
You should get him LeMouton instead.
It doesn't have air-cushioned soles, so he will hurt his knees.
- They'd look great on you. - I'll wear them.
- They're pretty. - They really are.
They're pretty. They're not too fancy, so I like them.
He says they are not too fancy. It says Dior.
- No. - But this is...
- Don't get me wrong. - I thought we'd have a team dinner.
- It wasn't your choice, was it? - They forced me to choose one,
so I couldn't refuse it.
Then are you going to pay for our team dinner later?
- Sure. I will. - Good.
- I'll buy you dinner. - All right.
- Tell me what you want to eat. - Okay.
That's the day.
Thank you.
- It's your 60th birthday, - All right.
- so we got you a gift. - Okay. I'll put it here.
- Today... - I'll try them on.
Are we allowed to steal them during the shoot?
- It's possible. - Can we do that?
- You can. - It's possible.
- Totally possible. - I see.
He steals things even when there's no camera.
I was really surprised.
This is Card Shark Association: 2026 Return of the Gamblers.
- All right. - We will start the race now.
- I like the filming set. - You will start...
with 20 caramels each.
- We get 20 caramels? - Yes.
The person with the most caramels will win today.
- I wish I could win at least once. - The winner will receive a prize...
and select two members to receive the penalty.
- Two members! - Oh, dear.
- We should win the winner's favor. - You'll see.
Just wait and see. You have to be nice to me.
- I'll remember everything. - I don't want to get the penalty.
- Me neither. - Right.
And Yang Se Chan, who was the chairperson last time,
will start the race as the chairperson again.
- Okay. - We don't select a new chairperson?
- I'll collect a few caramels first. - Isn't Tae Hyung coming?
Please support me.
- Okay. I will. - Please support me.
The authority of the chairperson remains the same as last time.
They can arrange the mission orders and team members.
That's great.
- The chairperson. - And they can reset the game...
- only once. - I see.
- Reset the game? - But the chairperson changed...
every once in a while, right?
- We should pay ten caramels. - If you don't like the chairperson,
- you can impeach them again. - Oh, dear.
If you fill the proposal box with 20 caramels,
- We need 20 caramels? - We need 20 caramels?
the chairperson is impeached immediately.
You get random draw balls...
equal to the number of caramels you pay,
and you become the chairperson if your ball is picked.
We will give you 20 caramels each now.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- For now, we should... - I should collect two each.
All right.
- All right. - All right.
For the association fund, I'll collect two caramels each.
- Two. All right. - Okay.
Hey, don't be ridiculous.
- We should do as he says. - I'll take extra care...
- of those who set an example. - My goodness.
- Thank you. - Why would we have to pay it?
For those who pay quickly, it's one caramel.
- Okay. See? - All right.
- You should hurry. - For you, it's one caramel.
- You know what? - Two caramels.
You need to adapt quickly.
- Why does he live like that? - Please give me two.
- You have to adapt. - Why...
- Seok Jin, give me three. - What?
I won't pay.
- What? - I'm not going to pay.
Do you want me to punch him in the side?
- What do you want? - What?
- Why are you taking my caramels? - Give me three.
I'm the chairperson. Give me three.
Why do I have to give you 3 when he gave you only 1?
- I was quick. - He gave me quickly.
- You should hurry. - Here. Whatever.
I'll give you one.
He's giving it to you anyway.
- You should give him two more. - Give me.
But you gave him only one.
- I'll do the same. - I gave him two,
- but he gave 1 back. - He gave me 2.
- I'll give you if you get this. - Get what?
- Here. - All right.
You missed it.
- You fool. - Just give it to me.
- Give me 1 more. - Forget it. I gave you 2.
Give him one more.
- If you don't pay tax on time... - Exactly.
- You'll have to give me anyway. - Why are you stalling?
Why did you do that?
So, this is what you're doing? Okay.
You should be the chairperson...
- if you don't like it. - Right.
If I win, you two will get the penalty.
- All right. - No problem.
If you win? Okay.
- I don't think you'll win. - My goodness.
Okay. You'll see.
- You don't think I'll win? - I don't think so.
If I win, you'll get the penalty.
- The odds have increased. - Okay. Let's do that.
- I'll pick you two. - Good.
Let's do this.
- Se Chan, today... - Okay. Good.
So, the association is back after two years.
This time, we'll give you a chance...
- to make a quick buck. - I'd love that.
- Good. - There's a lottery.
- Lottery? - Lottery.
- It's called Card Shark Lottery. - Card Shark Lottery?
If you win the lottery,
- you'll receive 40 caramels. - My goodness.
It's four times the prize money.
The odds of winning are 50 percent.
- That's great. - It's high, isn't it?
And a ticket costs ten caramels.
- That's expensive. - You can buy one ticket per person.
- We should win. - I have to buy it anyway.
- We have to do it. - Of course.
I will collect the money first.
- The odds of winning are high. - The odds aren't so bad.
- I should take the risk, right? - Of course.
- Ten caramels. - Ten caramels?
- This is quite a lot. - We should do it.
Ten caramels. Ye Eun paid ten caramels.
Okay. I got ten caramels from Ye Eun.
Ten caramels from Haha.
Here are 5. I'll give you another 5.
Seok Jin is spending a lot.
- What? - Hey. Come on!
- Hey! - Seriously...
Don't try to be sneaky.
- Such tricks are what we do. - Good.
You will pick a lottery ticket first.
So it's 50-50, right?
- Pick one here. - Now?
- Yes. Pick one. - Gosh, this is...
- By the way, this is... - How many are there?
The chances are 50-50.
- This is really... Please. - What do I do?
Please, Jae Seok!
- Jong Kook. - Let's go!
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook. - I have to win.
- Where's a coin? - It's here.
- Okay. - Yes!
- Did you win? - Yes.
Really?
I'm so jealous.
- I have a bad feeling. - Ye Eun won.
- Really? - Ye Eun won.
Ye Eun, give me a coin.
You won 40 caramels?
I won 40 caramels!
Did you win?
Okay!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Forty caramels. - Thank you.
- Forty caramels. Okay! - Forty caramels.
Kim Jong Kook won 40 caramels.
I knew it.
What? I think I won.
Okay!
I'm sorry, but...
This isn't going to work.
What's the bomb for?
It's a dud.
It has a bomb on it.
No, Se Chan!
- Darn it. - Forty caramels!
- Ye Eun, the Chungju Ji family... - Why would I give you?
Why do you look like an ant today?
- An ant? - Jae Seok.
- All right. - What is he talking about?
Let's go to the first mission then.
- Yes! - Let's go!
Let's go.
What is this? I'm curious.
What is this for?
- What is this? - My gosh.
- There are a lot of numbers. - It must be fun.
What is this?
Here's the first mission.
It's called Pop Pop Caramel Bomb.
We have a board that has numbers from 1 to 49 on the floor.
As you move around the board,
you will either earn...
or lose caramels.
- We also lose caramels? - Yes.
Each player has their turn.
- Okay. - You will take turns...
moving as many spots as your leg length allows...
- We can move. - on the board.
You can move one spot at a time.
Once you step on one spot, it becomes your territory.
And you can put your sticker on your territory.
Then, anyone who steps on it must pay ten caramels as a toll.
- I get the caramels? - You get the caramels.
- If it's your territory. - I see.
Each number has a cue card...
- at the bottom. - Yes.
The cue cards say things like...
plus 30 caramels,
- minus 20 caramels, - Oh, dear.
Golden Key,
- That's the best one. - and a bomb.
- That's the worst. - Yes.
We have random cue cards like them.
That won't be easy.
You will place the bombs.
If you tell us which spot...
- you want to plant... - The number?
the bomb on,
we will place the bomb on the spot.
If you step on the land with a bomb,
- the bomb explodes. - Right away?
The player who steps on it loses 50 caramels.
That's too harsh.
- He's right. - That's too much.
We will have to starve.
- That's too many. - But the person...
who placed the bomb there gets the 50 caramels.
That's amazing.
- Fifty caramels are too many. - This is really fun.
- We can't avoid it. - And if two people...
- place the bomb on the same land, - It's double?
It's double?
that's a jackpot.
If you step on the land, you get 50 caramels.
- We get 50 caramels? - Okay.
The two people who planted the bombs...
- Minus 50 caramels? - must each give 25 caramels.
To the person who stepped on it.
- I have only seven. - This is really fun.
- That's too many. - What am I supposed to do?
- This is too much. - Are you eating it?
- He has guts. - Are you eating it?
There he goes again.
- What? - He will end up...
- losing the caramels anyway. - Right.
He will lose them anyway, so he's eating one now?
If you're scared, back off.
Eating a caramel is...
- I want to eat it. - actually quite a gutsy act.
- Right. - Simply put,
it looks cool.
- He will lose them anyway. - Should I eat one?
- No. - So he's eating one now?
Of course.
Grandpa, you can't do that.
Stay quiet, you brat.
No. You can't do that.
Are you talking about this?
Gosh, Seok Jin.
You don't look cool.
Why not? You fool.
He could collapse if he suddenly ate something sweet like that.
He's in his 60s now.
His blood pressure would rise.
We will now start the mission.
Tell us the number to secretly plant the bomb on.
- The bomb... Please. - The bomb is too much.
There are too many bombs.
I can see where I should plant the bomb.
We can assume that we will step on the bomb at least once.
- We will step on it. - I know, right?
It will happen for sure.
I might go broke here.
This isn't easy.
You don't actually plant a real bomb.
- It's a landmine. - Okay.
Jae Seok goes first.
- We will proceed in this order. - Okay.
- Where? Like this? - We should move one spot?
- Jae Seok. - All right.
I'm so nervous.
- Okay. - Jae Seok will start now.
You will check the cue card to see what's on your land...
before you start.
It's all about luck.
Seok Sam loves games like this.
I love them so much!
You're so curious to see what's on your land.
Let's go!
- I love it. - Here I go.
- This is all about luck. - What?
This is the beginning.
- Sit down. - Sit?
- Open it. What is it? A dud! - Please.
- Minus 20. - Plus 30!
- Oh, no. - What?
- What? - Jae Seok.
Give me some.
- Okay. - I sent you there.
- This is my land now. - What?
He got 30 caramels?
That's too many.
He's so lucky.
Now you can move one spot.
- Where are you going? - You can jump.
Can I jump?
You can.
Number 38.
- That's ambiguous. - Number 38 could be dangerous.
- You think it's a lucky number. - Number 38?
- Go to number 38. - No!
- I think he will slip. - I don't think it has a bomb.
It's considered a lucky number. You don't think we picked it?
- Of course, we chose number 38. - Number 36.
- Three, six, nine! - Thirty-six!
- Number 36 must have a bomb. - Number 36.
- Open the card. - He got it!
Please.
- Please. - It's a bomb!
- He got it. - It's a bomb.
- It's a bomb. - He got a bomb.
- Please. - It's a bomb.
- Please. - It's a bomb!
Minus 30!
- He got a bomb. - Minus 30!
- Minus 30! - So, this is just meaningless.
- Three, six, nine! - What did I just do?
- Three, six, nine! - It's your territory now.
- Put the sticker on it. - Wait, Hyeong Seon.
Why are you clapping?
- Why... - Our director is the best.
I can't believe this.
- Ye Eun is next. - Me?
Open the card on the starting point first.
This is so disappointing.
- One, two, three. - Minus fifty.
- Plus five. - Oh, no.
You don't seem happy.
- It's still a positive number. - It's a positive number.
I should put my sticker on here, right?
It's still a positive number.
This is so disappointing.
- Everyone. - You can move one spot.
- Ye Eun. - Yes?
- If you step on my land, - I think she stepped on it.
- you have to pay ten caramels. - I know.
- I'll go to number 32. - Okay. Where is it?
Should I choose number 39?
- Why? - That's not nice.
What?
- What did I do? - Don't do such a mean thing.
What did I do?
I will...
Number 38!
- Number 38! - Number 38!
I'll go to number 38.
- Seriously? - Yes.
- Take a look. - Open it.
Minus 50. It's plus.
- It's a positive number. - It's very small, though.
It's meaningless.
- Why is it so small? - It's too small.
- It's too small. - Next up is Ji Hyo.
- It's too small. - Right.
- I'll open this first. - Okay.
- Unbelievable. - Show us.
- Plus 10. - Plus 10.
- That's okay, but not great. - She didn't get lucky.
- Ji Hyo, go for 18. - Jump.
- Eighteen? - Ji Hyo, make your way to us.
But 18...
- What? - Did you swear on camera?
- Don't swear. - Why are you swearing?
- I think... - Why are you swearing?
someone planted a bomb on 18.
- Then, go for another one. - Number 12.
- Ji Hyo, be careful. - How much did you drink yesterday?
Two bottles of soju!
- Wait. - You stepped in another square.
- There. - I saw you.
- Number 12. - Let's see it.
- Yes! Plus 30. - She's so good at this.
- Okay, got it. - Meanwhile, I...
- She's so good at this. - Plus 30.
Okay, got it.
- Meanwhile, I... - This is killing me.
I started off with 30.
- I still have six. - Is it my turn?
Okay, let's do this.
There!
- What did you get? - Minus 20.
- Nice. I dodged a bullet. - Seriously?
- Are you kidding me? - That's delicious.
Seok Jin might receive the penalty today.
Aren't you starting below zero?
- Darn. - How are you already below zero?
- Are you kidding me? - No way.
- I should be grateful. - I wish you the worst of luck.
There's a saying. Death... What?
- Go with lucky number 33. - No.
- Take risks if you want to live? - Yes.
Take risks if you want to live. Playing it safe leads nowhere.
- Number 40. - Number 44.
- Okay. - Nice. Thanks in advance.
- You stepped on another square. - I bet that's rigged.
- All right. - The number 44 feels ominous.
Take risks if you want to live. Playing it safe leads nowhere.
- What did you get? - It's not much.
- Minus? No, plus 5. - Plus 5.
This brings me to minus 15.
- Haha's next. - Okay!
- Mnet is my home. - It's not much.
I started my career on the streets.
Channel 27.
See what yours is first.
- Oh, right. - See what you've got first.
- Unbelievable. - Are you kidding me?
- What's with him? - Mister!
- Why are you running wild? - Yes!
- What did you get? - A Golden Key.
Why are you running wild?
- Yes! - What did you get?
- A Golden Key. - What's that about?
- Lucky you. - A Golden Key.
- Don't forget me. - What is it?
Double Caramel Chance.
"You can double the amount..."
"you gain on your turn."
- No way. - Seriously?
- Does it apply to negative numbers? - What if it's a minus?
- It's twice the negative number. - That's how it works, right?
It's twice the negative number.
It will even double the negative number.
Haha, choose one behind you.
No way. I should stay close to where I am.
I choose number 20...
- Watch it. - Number 27.
- Okay. - Please.
Double Caramel Chance.
In 1, 2, 3.
Double Caramel Chance. In 1, 2, 3.
Ta-da!
It's Seok Jin's bomb.
- What is it? - It's a bomb!
Ta-da!
It's Seok Jin's bomb.
- What is it? - It's a bomb!
Yes, it's my bomb!
- Minus 100. - Minus!
- So, 100? - Haha...
I planted my bomb there.
The Double Chance card applies to Seok Jin,
so he'll win 100 caramels.
- Do I get 100? - Yes.
- Yes! - Nice.
Why is he getting 100 instead of 50?
- Still... - Because of the Golden Key.
That doubles the amount.
The Golden Key applies to Haha,
not that old man over there.
- It applied to this step. - He should only get 50.
- What? - You imbeciles.
- Imbeciles? - Use your brain.
I just got rich.
Haha's at negative 100.
There are bombs around us.
I'm sure they're around us.
- We should be careful. - They're around us.
They put the Golden Keys around the bombs.
- I think so too. - Really?
- That's how it's been set. - Of course, they'd do that.
We used to put things like this in corners,
but now...
I can't believe it was right next to the bomb.
That's odd.
You just had to find the Golden Key as well, right?
- I know. - Tell me about it.
- What? - You're eating this up, aren't you?
You see, at first...
I can't believe him.
- Go ahead. - This is hilarious.
- I wonder. - Go, Muscular Pig.
- Go ahead. - All right!
- This isn't bad. - That's not bad.
- That's a decent start. - Not bad.
- Hold on. - I'll go for number 47.
Plus 30!
- Yang Ssaebssaeb! - I had that one in mind.
- Mr. Yang, congratulations. - Congratulations!
- Thank you. - Congratulations, sir.
- Congratulations! - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Mr. Yang.
- Aren't you going to celebrate? - Congratulations, sir.
- What's with you? - Congratulations.
- Nice. - I expected no less.
- Nice! - Good for you.
- Nice. - That's now Se Chan's space.
- We should be careful. - Number 40?
There are still six bombs left.
- We should be careful. - Of course.
There are still a lot of bombs left.
- I... - Why is he loving this?
He looks like he got dunked in a sewer.
Dunked in a sewer.
He got dunked in a sewer.
- Totally. - In a sewer.
- Jae Seok, you're up. - Me?
- It's already back to us. - Which one should I choose?
- I hope you go belly up. - Go with number 30.
Jae Seok, here's a suggestion.
You need to take control of 30 to 32.
- That'll block the others' path. - Of course.
It'd be meaningless to choose other numbers.
- Take control of this area to... - Number 31!
- Okay. - Number 31?
Here I am. Number 31. Please!
- Number 31? - Here I am. Number 31.
- Please! - I hope you go belly up.
- I bet it's a bomb. - It's a positive number.
- Plus! - Not bad.
- How many did he get? - Plus.
- Nice. - I'm so annoyed.
This is bad. Once Jae Seok controls this area, it's over.
I should quickly move to number 25.
- You won't be able to move out. - I choose number 32.
- I should make my way over there. - You won't be able to move out.
- You're right. - I choose number 32.
- Which one? - This right here.
That's mine. Don't you go there.
Ye Eun, you should head to number 30.
- Go over there. - But... Why?
- What about us? - I'm moving here.
I wanted to go there.
- Let it be a bomb. - Plus.
Why am I only getting tiny amounts?
Tiny amounts? That's not bad though.
- You're getting way too little. - That's not bad.
It's kind of pathetic.
Ji Hyo's next.
- Ji Hyo, go for number 18. - Go for it.
Number 18?
Numbers 18, 19, and 11. Make that your area.
Number 18 is totally up your alley.
- Number 18 and 26 seem good. - Careful.
- Number 18 and 26? - Number 26 seems good.
Or move toward the center.
- This way, right? - Of course.
Move this way, Ji Hyo.
You won't have a path if you ignore the center squares.
- Exactly. - There's no way to go.
- I should move to the center. - We need the center squares.
Do you people not use your brains?
Do it already.
- Go ahead. - Number 26.
- Number 26? - Okay.
Number 26.
I bet that's a dud.
- Hold on. - Five, four,
- three, two... - Three, two...
- Let it be a bomb. - Let's see it.
Ji Hyo, let's see it.
What did you get earlier?
- Plus 30. - Plus 30.
- It's a bomb. - Nice.
- It's Jong Kook's. - It's a bomb!
Ji Hyo, what did I tell you?
- Goodness. - I never would've guessed.
Ji Hyo, come on.
- Why would you choose that one? - Jong Kook, I can't believe you!
- What did I do? - How were they next to each other?
I didn't tell you to go there.
- How can both 26 and 27 have bombs? - Gosh, 26 and 27 have bombs.
I can't believe you!
How were they next to each other?
- I bet they're all in the middle. - I didn't tell you to go there.
There's a good chance the bombs are next to each other.
- Seok Jin, go ahead. - This is scary.
What can I do but fight against the world?
- Exactly. - But you're playing...
like a scaredy cat.
- What do you mean? - You're being a scaredy cat.
- How so? - You'll be stuck in that space.
I'm going to number 39.
Show everyone you can make the jump.
I'm going to try to stop you.
- Number 39? Then... - Try to trip him.
I can pull you my way.
- Try to trip him. - There's no pulling.
- Like this. - You'll then be on my square.
If I pull you toward me, you'll then be on my square.
- How's that allowed? - Of course, it's allowed.
- You're right. - That's allowed.
- That's how we usually play. - Number 39 must not be a bomb.
- I can drag Ye Eun over here. - What?
- She's on my square! - Hold on.
- Come on. - Wait. This isn't right.
- You can't... - There!
- What? - You stepped on her square.
What?
- You stepped on her square. - Look.
- He stepped on mine. - You stepped on Ye Eun's square.
- You were in my square. - You stepped on hers.
- Ye Eun's square. - You stepped on hers.
Can't you cut me some slack?
- No way. - No way.
The toll is ten caramels.
- Well, it's fine. - Say that it's fine.
- Are you good? - Give her ten of yours.
- Give her ten of yours. - Are you good?
Here we go. There!
- It's a Golden Key. - I got Goldie. There!
- It's a Golden Key. - I got Goldie!
- Lucky you. - It's a Golden Key.
Okay, let's do this.
- And this is my square. - Move Opponent Card.
You may move any player to a square of your choice.
Really?
- That's huge. - Shouldn't it be someone...
with the most caramels?
- Who has the most? - That's Seok Sam.
- Move someone in the lead. - Exactly.
I might have to go to a loan shark.
Okay, I'll go easy on you.
Haha, you're my partner, Speed.
- Goodness. - There's a story we share.
I didn't think Seok Jin would consider that.
- So... - I might cry.
- It's me and you. - I'm going to send...
- either Grasshopper or Muscle. - Right.
- Go ahead. - I will.
- You never know. - Grasshopper?
Seok Jin's bomb was already activated.
His was activated.
It's Seok Jin's bomb.
- What is it? - It's a bomb!
It's one of these two.
I could move myself and get more caramels.
- Of course. - Exactly.
Or I could send someone to a possible bomb.
- That's right. - Think long term.
You're playing against everyone else,
so why let them...
- What do you mean? - win 50 caramels?
- You're right. - I know.
What should I do then?
- Pull someone to your square. - Yes, that's better.
Move someone to your own square.
One of you might earn 50 caramels if I send someone...
- to a random square. - Exactly. Of course.
I might give them 30 more.
Of course. That's how it is.
- That was pretty smart. - You should think it through.
- So now... - You, go over there.
- Number 44. - That's so smart of him.
That's so smart of him.
- Unbelievable. - You,
- go to number 44. - Nicely done!
- Go to number 44. - Nicely done.
- Pay up. - Is it now my square?
- Of course not. - You just pay a toll.
- You will just pay the toll. - Okay, got it.
- Now... - Moving on.
I keep ending up with no caramels.
- Haha, you're up. - That's odd.
- Then I'll go to number 25. - Go to number 18.
Number 25.
- Where is he? - Aren't you going to go there?
- That's it. Nice. - I bet that's a bomb.
I bet that's a bomb.
- It's not. - Let it be a bomb.
- That's it. Nice. - I bet that's a bomb.
- Let it be a bomb. See? - It's a bomb!
- I was going to go there. - See?
I was going to go there.
- What... - How is this possible?
Both of his spots had a bomb.
My gosh.
This is just great. My goodness.
- He's totally useless. - Totally.
You fell into a sewer and went into another sewer.
We've been calling him poop-related things this year.
- He's a turd. - Just like that?
- You're contaminated. - You're in a sewer.
How did we pick them without even overlapping?
Exactly. Seriously.
From 25 to 27.
Gosh. This is insane.
Didn't I tell you not to go there?
Why did you when I told you not to?
Why should I do as you say?
- Just wait for me to come first. - You sewer fool.
This is just great.
I'm taking out the bombs for everyone.
- We got three so far. - We revealed a few of them.
- Right? - How many so far? One, two, three.
- Did we find three bombs? - We found three.
Are there three left, then?
- This game... - Haha's bomb is still hidden.
There are three left.
Am I next? Gosh, it's getting nerve-racking.
- It's the center area. - Definitely the center.
I told you go aim for the center, so why did you go there?
- He's in his 40s... - These spots here...
- are taken and I can't go there. - Right.
I have no choice but to go where there's a way out.
- I must go to 19. - That's 19.
If I go this way, I'll become stranded.
- Yes. - You must get out.
I must get out.
- Head toward number eight. - You must get out.
- Why? - What?
- What's what? - What why?
- What? - What?
Nice one, Ji Hyo.
- Your left foot. - Good luck, Trainer Yang Chi Seung.
You know me, right? My knee will hit you first.
- My gosh. - Expect a knee kick.
- How? - This is how I'll jump.
- He's serious. - Like this.
- I don't care what happens. - What the... Why...
- Watch out. - You can just hop by.
She's scared.
I'm scared.
- Ji Hyo... - I'm scared.
I can do what I want when you pass my territory.
There's no ambulance here. I don't care what you get.
An orbital wall fracture.
- You're so scary. - Darn you.
Have you had an orbital wall fracture?
Not an orbital wall fracture.
Okay, good. I'm on 19.
- He moved. - Okay, good. I'm on 19.
My gosh.
- Number 19. - It's something big.
I think I got something big.
- Oh, dear. It ripped in half. - What is it?
Minus ten... Darn it.
- That's not bad. - That's okay.
- Minus ten is fine. - It's better than a bomb.
It's okay.
- Is it me next? - This isn't too bad.
- Will you go to 30? - We must find an exit.
This time... There's nowhere to go.
- Can you move a bit? - It's hard.
Forty-five is my only option.
- That's right here. - Yes.
I'll go to 45.
- Forty-five? - There's nowhere else to go.
- Wait a bit, and he'll weaken. - I know.
You're exercising. Gosh, you're energetic.
- A bit more. Come on. - He's getting weak.
What... That's it. Keep going.
Why you...
Darn it. I'm exhausted.
You're making the old man exercise.
- One, two. One, two. - How nice of you, Se Chan.
Don't do anything to exhaust poor grandpa.
He's still full of energy.
I'll move now. Let me...
You dropped by.
You dropped by!
- Welcome! - That happens!
- You trespassed there too. - Watch out.
- On either side. - Okay.
You lost on both sides.
The board is slippery!
- He touched both sides and mine. - The board is slippery!
He touched two other numbers.
- Seok Jin. - My word.
He must pay the toll only where his feet touched.
They touched my land.
This block counts, but not that one.
Over there. That's both sides.
- My feet touched him. - Really? Your head landed here.
- We don't count the head. - That's fine?
It's how I fell.
We can land on our heads, then.
- A Golden Key. - Shoot.
- A Golden Key. - Shoot. I should've taken it.
It's an Install One Bomb Card.
If and when you land on a bomb,
you can install one more bomb...
to turn that number into a jackpot.
Turn that number into a Jackpot.
- That's crazy. - Who do I give the number to?
If you land on a bomb, it turns into a jackpot.
That's insane. Gosh.
- It's a good card. - Got it.
- Jae Seok. - It's me, right?
- I'm envious. - Where will you go?
You need to go to 29 or 30.
- I think so. - There might be a bomb.
Jae Seok. You need to land on 30...
to block everyone in this area.
They can't move. Number 30.
- Even if there's a bomb. - Right.
Number 30. Even if there's a bomb.
- This is the right choice. - It's a bomb.
- It's a bomb. - I must see the big picture.
Plus 20!
- You gained more? - This is so annoying.
- How annoying. - How annoying.
- Why are they all gaining? - This is so...
If you gain in small amounts now, it never ends well.
Jae Seok...
I like your moves.
The Shanghai twist?
What dance is that?
He's using up all his luck on this game.
- Yes. - I gained a decent amount,
- but lost them all. - Small earnings.
- Put your name on it. - Get your sticker.
My earnings are too small.
Small earner.
- Hey. - Ye Eun.
Ye Eun's the greatest ever small earner here.
- To 41? - Yes, seriously.
Ye Eun earned really small today.
So small. She gained five here.
- Go that way. - Go over there.
- You must go outward. - There's nothing here.
- There's no land here. - Go to 43.
- There are many options there. - Number 17?
- Number 17 isn't bad, Ye Eun. - Number 17...
- Number 17 sounds good. - It's not bad.
I'll go to 17.
You'll fall trying to jump that far.
I have long legs.
- Gosh. - What do you get?
- How impressive. - It's a bomb.
It's a bomb!
My gosh.
- See? - Who put it there?
Who put it there? It was Jae Seok.
- This is madness. - Jae Seok, you...
I got lucky.
- I got lucky. - This is infuriating.
Seriously.
- I got lucky. - He's getting on my nerves.
- Lucky me. - I can't stand how his legs move.
- I got lucky. - The movements irk me.
I'm shocked how suit pants can look like thermal underwear.
- Seriously. - I got lucky.
Is this even right?
- You just lost 50. - I know.
- What a mess. - Okay.
I should go to 40 next.
- Ji Hyo. - Number 24?
Number 24?
Can you jump that far?
- Number 24? - Yes.
Okay.
- Number 24? - Can you jump that far?
- Go! - Ji Hyo's off.
- Going where? - To 24.
- Going where? - Don't go to number 24!
- To 24. - Don't go to number 24!
- Why not? - I'll go there.
That's why you should go.
Wait. I'll give you two caramels.
Don't go to 24. Let me.
- Why not? - I'll give you two.
Get moving already.
It's weird how desperate he is.
- It's weird. - I have nowhere to go.
- I see. - Pay me, then.
- I will pay you. - Go on.
Here. Two caramels.
Here. Two caramels. My gosh.
- Darn you! - Oh, dear.
- My gosh. Darn you! - Oh, dear.
- Sorry. - Number 24.
Number 24.
- This kind of trickery... - Number 24.
- Shoot! - My gosh.
Yang Se Chan, Haha!
- Yang Se Chan, Haha! - I wanted to go there.
I told you not to go there.
That's a jackpot.
Two bombs become a jackpot.
- Haha and Se Chan... - That's right!
- That's a hundred. - have to give Ji Hyo...
twenty-five caramels each.
- We give her caramels? - Why?
She must give me some.
- Why... - No, you give her some.
- We give her caramels? - Why?
- She must give me some. - No.
You give her some.
- The one who lands there gains. - It's good for her, not you.
- Two bombs... - Didn't you hear the instructions?
If there are two bombs on the same number...
If your bombs overlap and there are two on one number...
It's a double?
It's a jackpot.
The two people who put the bombs there...
must give 25 caramels each to the person who lands there.
Let's put them...
Yours and mine...
Wouldn't it be better in the center?
- Then 24. - Who took my bag?
- Yes, that'd be 24. - I'll go 23.
- She doesn't pay us double? - No!
You dragged me into this...
- without knowing the rules? - You plotted this?
Haha and I planned it together.
- You fools. - You're idiots.
Haha keeps going into debt.
You had it coming. You poop-faced fool.
"Poop-faced fool?"
So Ji Hyo hit the jackpot.
Why did you two do something so dangerous?
We found all but Ji Hyo's bomb.
- They all blew up. - Ji Hyo's is left.
Oh, no...
I might get stuck here.
- It's my turn? - Se Chan.
I have nothing. I'm dirt poor.
- I'm done for today. - This is purgatory for me.
- I can only go that way. - Yes.
Number 40. Or go to 33...
- Can you manage? You can't. - Number 33.
- You can jump pretty high. - Have a go.
I'm scared because I slipped last time.
- Take off your socks. - I might slip.
Take off your socks.
- I did it. - That was close.
It's the bomb.
- It's the bomb. - Please.
Please!
- It's the bomb. Oh, it really is. - Hey, the bomb.
It's a double.
- Jackpot. - Jackpot.
Will he get to use it again?
- Jackpot. - It's jackpot.
- Then, Ji Hyo has to give up 25. - Right.
The staff will give you 25 as well.
- We're getting paid! - Our paychecks.
Gosh, Ji Hyo has to give him this?
Congratulations.
Gosh, congratulations!
- Chairperson, congratulations! - Chairperson, congratulations!
- I was looking out for you. - A good thing has happened.
I'll give you guys allowances later.
- Yes! Se Chan! - Yes, allowances.
- Forget it, not you. - Our chairperson...
- must do well for us to keep going. - This is good.
Chairperson, will you please look out for us too?
- Don't worry. I'll give you some. - Then, 16!
Now, it's great. Only the good spots are left.
We could just go wherever we want.
I choose 13!
- Hey, you stepped on it. - You stepped on it!
- You stepped on Ji Hyo's. I saw it. - You stepped on mine.
You stepped on Ji Hyo's land.
You could never go there.
- You stepped on it. - See?
- You stepped on it! - He got in, didn't he?
- He stepped on it! - On his arm!
- Why did you step on my arm? - Hey...
Go to mine...
- What? It's a plus. - It's a plus.
Darn it.
At least you got one.
Shoot, why did I get this now?
Get a minus.
Please, let's get a big one.
Gosh, today is really...
Really...
More poop for you!
- You sure aren't constipated. - Look!
- Such perfect poops. - Are we done?
- Here are the number of caramels. - Okay.
Se Chan, you have 77.
That's quite a lot.
- Yes. - Indeed, Yang Se Chan!
- Indeed, he's our chairperson! - Thank you!
- Chairperson! - I won't take any fees.
Okay!
- Yu Jae Seok. - I bet he has a lot.
- You have 75. - Okay.
- That's quite a lot. - It's not bad.
- He got a lot safely. - I did.
Jee Seok Jin, you have 45.
Gosh, that's still good.
I lost a bunch in the middle.
Kim Jong Kook, you have 21.
- Well, that's not bad. - You have 17.
- Still, that's not too bad. - You have eight.
Haha, you have minus 130.
Just go home, why don't you?
He's done for.
With that, the first mission is over.
- We'll now have lunch. - Yes.
We must be paying with caramels.
Today's lunch is...
- Lunch is? - It's Chinese food.
- We have to pay with caramels? - Is it jjajangmyeon or jjamppong?
- You will choose between the two. - Yes, and?
So, the dish that fewer people chose...
- Only those will get 20 caramels. - This is hard.
- Only the fewer people? - Yes.
Gosh, this is hard.
This is really hard.
- But I really don't have very many. - They have too many.
- Oh, the fewer... - You will go 1 by 1.
But this will be a close game.
- It really will be. - The fewer...
Hello.
Between jjajangmyeon and jjamppong, which will you eat?
I will have jjamppong.
Even if I lose, I should enjoy my meal.
If I lose, I'll feel sad,
but I should eat good food and feel better.
That's good, right?
Are there a lot in here?
I can't tell you.
Quite a lot? How many are there now?
I told you. I can't say.
I usually don't do stuff like this.
- Are we shaking hands? - Yes.
- Okay, hear me out. - Okay.
If I can't even eat what I want...
and also pay caramels, it would be the worst.
Then, I have to eat what I want even if I must pay caramels.
Jjamppong.
I'll choose jjamppong.
Oh, okay.
Kim Jong Kook and Song Ji Hyo? Jjamppong is their default.
It just is. The others go back and forth.
Then, what should I do? I'll go with jjajang.
Jjajang.
There won't be very many.
Hello, there. I must be busy as the chairperson.
Jjajang or jjamppong?
I became allies with Haha.
He mentioned jjamppong.
- I swear. - You're so annoying!
- I'll choose jjamppong. - Oh, jjamppong?
- You'll choose jjamppong? Okay. - Earlier, you...
- Jjajang. - Jjajang?
I choose jjajang for today.
- Please go upstairs. - Okay.
You're totally ruined.
What should I do now?
Oh, I'll go to the waiting room...
Sung Ho, get me a bald wig.
I should try changing my character.
I should go back to the second chairperson.
So, Haha's winning move was right on point.
Hello, there.
You changed your hairstyle.
Yes, I was so mad...
that I pulled out some of my hair.
Between jjajangmyeon and jjamppong, which will you eat?
I ate jjajangmyeon yesterday.
- So, jjamppong? - Anyway, I have...
nothing to lose.
Is it jja or jjam?
- What's up with that guy? - What's wrong with him?
- Did someone shave your head? - What's wrong with your hair?
Gosh, I was under so much stress.
- Did you lose hair? - I lost some hair up front.
- Hey, there. Mister. - He's so strange.
- Yes? - You can't do that during the day.
- What? - You stand out too much.
You should keep your long hair. You can't do this out of nowhere.
It wasn't out of nowhere.
- You just found it uncomfortable. - Still,
- you were like Park Wan Kyu. - Right, you were getting hot.
I mean, I just lost some hair because of the stress.
- Do you think that makes sense? - How does that make any sense?
- Did you think that would be funny? - You have to be logical.
- Why? - Well,
go and change it back. What do you think you're doing?
Nobody is laughing.
I'll go and get hair transplants later after lunch.
Go and grow your hair out after lunch.
You're so unlikable.
Seriously, so unlikable.
- All right. Yes! - I'll announce the results.
- Let's go! - Please.
- Please. - Bring out their orders right away.
- All right. Please. - What is it?
- It was a really close game. - It was, right?
- It was 4 to 3, right? - Was it close?
- I knew it. - That's good.
That's good enough.
Wait, four? I didn't get it.
It's jjamppong.
Oh, I think it's jjajang.
- If it was 3 to 3, I wanted to... - There are 4 jjajangs.
- There are four jjajangs. - It's jjajang!
- No. What? Hang on. - What's this?
- There are 4 jjajangs. - Are there 4 jjajangs?
Okay!
For real?
- There are 4 jjajangs. - Okay!
Okay!
- For real? - But...
- Really? You went the other way? - Did you go the other way?
Gosh, but Se Chan is so annoying.
There was a week where we didn't talk to each other.
I was so mad.
I just need to ruin the chairperson.
I just need to ruin him.
- There are four jjajangs. - It's jjajang!
- Okay! - Okay!
Hang on. With the chairperson's authority,
- I can... What is it? - You can do that.
- Can he change this? Our food? - He can do that.
- He can change it! - Sure, he can.
With the chairperson's authority, I'll overturn the results.
Okay!
- Good one! - Of course, you can do that!
- Good job. - Then...
- Chairperson Yang! - Good job.
- Then... - Really?
Shouldn't we vote again?
- He's resetting the game. - We'll let you choose again.
- Right? We get to choose again. - Come on.
- Cover your food. - We'll give you cue cards.
- That's it. Choose again. - Choose again.
- Gosh, the jjamppong... - Okay!
This guy told me he'd choose jjamppong, but...
- Gosh, that guy is seriously... - Let's go.
- Nice going, man. - It's kind of...
- What are you guys doing? - Oh, are we writing it down?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
- All right. - Did you change it?
- Gosh, the chairperson... - Is it jja or jjam?
- Seriously... - Hurry up and write.
You...
- I'm sick and tired of you. - You're seriously...
- On two. - One by one.
- One by one? Okay. - One by one.
- Shall I start? - He'll choose jjamppong.
- Jjamppong. - Those two. It's their default.
- That side. - Me?
- Me? - Go.
I chose jjajang.
My gosh. I chose jjajang.
Jjajang.
- Ji Hyo. - Me?
- Jjamppong. - You had that before too.
- Oh, it's the same. - Please hold it up.
- Jae Seok. - What did you write, Jae Seok?
- Is it jjajang or jjamppong? - He must've said jjamppong.
- He had jjamppong before. - Is it jjajang?
- Jjamppong! Yes, I did it! - Is it jjamppong?
- How many said jjamppong so far? - So far, three.
- Three? With just one more... - Three.
Jjajang?
Jjajangmyeon. No!
It's 3 versus 2.
- All right. - At the same time.
- At the same time? - Yes.
- On 1... - On 1, 2, 3.
- Jjamppong. - Jjajang.
- Three for jjajang! - Jjajang!
Three for jjajang!
Fewer people chose jjajang.
It's because of Haha!
- Gosh, what a relief. - I mean,
why is it that today...
He keeps leaving poop bombs all over the place!
- You're totally today's villain. - Yes!
- Are you today's villain? - Totally the villain.
- I just need to get him. - Totally.
He's dropping poop bombs all over the place.
The four of you who are the majority...
- will pay 20 caramels each. - Okay.
You must give it to the three who are the minority.
- What about him? He has none. - He needs a loan.
- What about him? - You can take out a loan.
- The interest is 50 percent. - Oh, nice!
- This is nice. I'm so happy! - We won.
Haha went the other way.
Gosh, did you know Haha would do that?
Man, that looks good.
My gosh. Haha did this to us.
- Go away. Eat over at the end. - This is good.
It's delicious.
- Gosh, I swear... - Come on!
- I can't stand you today. - For real.
I can't stand him.
Go away. Eat over at the end.
You're just ugly.
My gosh. This is good.
He even changed his hairstyle by himself.
- I know. - He does whatever he wants.
Villains these days are charming,
but he's not even charming.
- I have 19. - I'll give you 1.
This is so good.
- I think I might blow it. - I know, right?
Seriously, why do you do that? My gosh.
Gosh, you have to stand your ground.
Hey, members.
My target was Yang Se Chan, not you guys.
- Okay? - Whatever.
Don't be mad anymore.
Hey.
- As the chairperson... - Yes?
I want you...
to enjoy your meals, so I'll give out some caramels.
- Really? - Thank you.
- Because I had a lot earlier... - This is great.
Even if there's a new chairperson, I hope you remember this.
- You're a nice person. - Yes.
Oh, after finishing his meal,
the chairperson seems to be a lame duck now.
- Oh, nice. - Right?
- He'll do that and... - Yes, a lame duck.
I think he's kind of scared now.
This is all because you guys did well...
- It's for everyone's sake. - Yes.
That's because politics matter, don't they?
I see you didn't get any.
Sewer Face didn't get any.
How can I give him any,
- when he keeps playing tricks? - Of course.
- I don't want to give him any. - Sewer Face asked for it.
I just got news from our dealer.
- Right. - Yes?
The suggestion box is full,
so the chairperson will face impeachment.
Guys, remember I just passed out some caramels.
All right. The former chairperson...
- Will he be drawing a name? - He'll draw a name.
I hope it's me.
I didn't expect this at all.
I'll pay five.
- I'll pay seven. - Seven?
Here.
- I'll pay seven. - Sure.
Seven from Haha.
I'll pay two.
This is a lot.
- We need 20, right? - Yes.
I'll pay four.
The former chairperson...
- Will he be drawing a name? - He'll draw a name.
- Nice. - I hope it's me.
Please.
Let me be the chairperson for once.
It's been so long since I was one myself.
- Who is it? - Who is it?
- No way. Goodness. - Who...
- Who is it? - Congratulations!
Mr. Yu!
- Goodness. - Darn it!
Darn it!
Goodness. Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Mr. Yu.
- I almost drew his name. - Congratulations.
- I hope we get along. - Sure.
- Thank you, sir. - Welcome to the dark ages.
Watch what you're saying.
- Earlier... - Who knew a day this good...
would come?
Put your old wig back on.
It was wrong of you to run wild like that.
You should switch back to it right away.
- He should. - What do you say?
Can you get me the wig?
- Let's eat for now. - Right, let's eat.
- Wait, are you the oldest here? - I should.
You seem like the oldest.
Sure thing. Why?
Massage my shoulders, will you?
Can a chairperson order something like that?
- Of course. - The chairperson can.
- Just do it. - I'm the chairperson.
I would've already been on my feet.
Or else I'll just take ten caramels.
- Why? - Speed.
Cross.
- We'll plan for the future. - Our day will come.
Yes, our day will come.
I'm so annoyed.
- Your wig is here. - This is so annoying.
Okay.
Stop frowning, will you? You're making us lose our appetite.
- You saw wrong. - I've lost my appetite.
- That's nice. - You seem jealous.
It's nice to see you smile.
I had lost my appetite earlier.
- Because of the piled interest? - Yes.
Where are you going?
He's going to fill the box.
- The box is already full. - What?
How can the box already be full?
And as we speak...
- Has it been filled? - Yes?
- The suggestion box is full. - Get back here!
Jae Seok!
- Jae Seok. - Who managed it so fast?
Hold on.
How many more do we need? I should go there unnoticed.
- I'll add ten. - Sure.
- Have some pickled radish. - Thanks.
- That's 10. - I'll add 10.
Jae Seok, please draw a name.
I'm good as long as it's not Seok Sam.
Who added the rest? I put in quite a lot myself.
I tried to add some in, but the box had been filled.
Luck is coming my way.
Is it Jee Seok Jin?
The most worthy was chosen.
- Is it Jee Seok Jin? - It's Yang Se Chan.
Goodness.
- It's Yang Se Chan. - Goodness.
Are you sure you didn't see the names?
- I didn't. - All right.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - I'll accept your applause.
- Applaud! - Congratulations.
- Thank you. Applaud! - A lot had his name on it.
First, Seok Jin, I'll take ten.
I'm broke anyway.
- Let's go. - Goodness.
What is this?
Ji Hyo, this really hurts.
- What's this? - Swimming fins.
- Is this... - Hold on.
I should keep this safe at headquarters.
No way. As if that'll make a difference.
- I'll keep mine here. - Sure.
Okay, I know where Seok Jin's is.
- Unbelievable. - I'll keep mine on me.
- Are you kidding me? - I should keep this with me.
- Keep yours with you. - I'll take the whole thing.
I guess I can keep mine here.
- Unbelievable. - I'll take the whole thing.
Haha doesn't have any.
- There's no hassle. - I couldn't keep mine here.
- Unbelievable. - I don't have any either.
- Did you enjoy your meal? - Yes!
The suggestion box has been filled again.
- Okay, nice. - Really?
- That's 11. - Yes, 11.
- I'll put these in here. - Wait, didn't you...
- How many? - Five.
I'll put in 18.
That's 20. Didn't you put in 18?
- They're quick to act. - The current chairperson...
- Yes, they're fast. - will draw a name.
You didn't even bother to wear the armband.
Forget it. It's meaningless.
- Here we go. - He took it.
Did he?
Mix all the balls in there.
I'll do that.
I wonder how many people...
- put in caramels. - Here we go.
Please tell me to stop.
- Stop. - As if you have the right.
Stop.
- I added two. - The chances are slim.
- They won't even let me do that. - I added two.
I added two. Would that be enough?
As if.
- Will it be a miracle for Seok Sam? - One, two, three.
I hope it's a miracle. Jee Seok Jin.
- It's Jae Seok. - Of course.
- No way. - Congratulations.
Of course.
- Congratulations. - He'd already put in 18...
- when I got there. - Congratulations.
- Overall... - Wasn't that a good draw?
- Yes, that was a great draw. - Yes.
- Overall... - And now...
If you keep adding caramels to the box,
this will just keep happening.
Why bother throwing jabs?
- Right. - I suggest you restrain yourself.
It's better to live like this.
- Just acknowledge the defeat. - Exactly.
This is the second mission where you can earn more caramels.
Go All In on Your Jeoktoma.
All in?
You'll become a horse and run an obstacle course...
- with bets placed on you. - Are we betting on the race?
- Only three of you will be horses. - Okay.
- The rest will place bets. - We'll place bets.
- This sounds like fun. - If...
- It sure does. - you bet on the winning horse,
you'll win double what you bet.
However, if the horse you bet on...
- has the fewest bettors... - Yes?
- If it has the fewest bettors, - We win more money.
you'll triple what you bet should your horse win.
- Exactly. That's... - Just keep...
- this one thing in mind. - What is it?
Please bring in the menu board.
- I hope there's a huge twist. - There's a catch.
The chosen one, a piggyback ride, and more.
- There are some options. - What on earth is this?
There are benefits and penalties.
Time Reduction Card. That's major!
- What's that for? - Removing an Obstacle.
It'll reduce the horse's record.
- Time Increase Card. - How much time will it add?
You can add five seconds to whoever you want.
- Five seconds? - That'll result in a twist.
Give the chosen person a piggyback ride.
It can even be a staff member.
- It'll be the Jimmy Jib cameraman. - Then we'll lose.
- The Jimmy Jib cameraman. - We can't possibly win.
The Time Reduction Card will take five seconds off.
The final record minus five seconds.
Remove One Section with Obstacles.
You'll get to remove...
- either the hurdles or the cones. - The cones?
Only one of the two.
- That... - That'll cut more than 5 seconds.
- Of course. - That'll be even better.
Each one...
will cost you 20 caramels.
- That's too expensive. - After one person buys it,
- it won't be sold anymore. - It'll be sold out.
That's right. The horses competing will also receive caramels.
- Really? - They should aim to win.
So if you're broke, you can be a horse.
Haha and I.
- I should be a horse. - He has to be one.
- So... - That's your only option.
You'll win 30 caramels if you win the race.
- Nice. - For coming in first.
- Second place wins 20. - Winning really matters.
- Third place wins ten. - The horses should aim to win.
- They'll have to do their best. - Of course.
- I should be the one betting. - Players can rig the game.
- That's not it. - You should at least win 30.
- I should take out a loan... - You can take and give some...
- and bet everything I have. - And by betting...
What's going on over there?
- What are you scheming? - Well, Haha...
Haha thinks he should bet on a horse.
- This is my shot at a comeback. - He thinks it's an opportunity.
He's saying he can't be a horse.
- I'm at minus 150 caramels. - Hold on a second.
- What good would 20 do? - Haha.
This is a show that children watch too.
- But he... - Watch something else for a moment.
Watch EBS.
- You need to stay logical. - You can't lose it like this.
- Exactly. - Keep it together.
- Don't gamble like that. - Don't take out a loan...
that crosses the line.
Don't be neck-deep in debt.
Yes, don't be neck-deep in debt. It won't be good.
- You should've done better today. - Exactly.
When the camera wasn't rolling...
What now?
- What is it? - You said comforting words to me,
patting my back.
Did you just swear?
- He's lost it. - Seriously.
- He's like a zebra. - Are you a prisoner somewhere?
Has he been imprisoned?
- He looks like a drunk. - A drunk?
His belly's sticking out after lunch.
- His belly's sticking out. - You're the worst.
- He looks like Hae Mosu. - You're right.
- You all act differently on camera. - He must've had a big lunch.
The horses for the first race...
will be Ji Hyo, Ye Eun, and Seok Sam.
- Okay. - Let's win this.
- Let's check it out. - I'll come in first.
- Let's watch this game. - Winner gets 30 caramels.
- Of course. - I'll do my best.
- You should do your best. - Me too.
- I'll do my best. - I'm low on caramels.
I don't have a lot either.
- Unbelievable. - Me too.
Please help me out this once.
I want to join the game too.
- This is no fun. - I know, but...
- I feel like I'm being left out. - What are you getting at?
I don't know how this happened to me.
- Quit whining to the chairperson. - Unbelievable.
It's getting annoying. Can't you take a hint?
Stop going to the chairperson to whine about your situation.
Unbelievable. Mr. Yu, hold up.
How much can I borrow right now?
- As a loan... - The maximum is 200.
- Okay, 200. - Speed.
Right.
- Wait, hear me out. - Ye Eun, don't you work out?
I've been working out. Pilates.
But you're like...
a paper doll.
Hold on a second.
When the race comes down to them, to win the bet...
- Maybe I should bet on Ye Eun. - Ye Eun...
If she wins, we could triple our caramels.
Ye Eun, show us what you've got.
That's it.
She tires herself out by moving around for no reason.
- Don't do that. - After this,
she won't have any energy during the actual game.
Gosh, she's out of breath.
But if that's the case, we won't be the minority.
- It'll blow up. - If we all bet on her, you know?
- How many are betting now? - I'm fast.
- Let's do this. - Three.
- Look... - Four people are betting.
What's up with that lonely gambler?
- Hey, Haha. - Excuse me.
- The lonely... - A pot-bellied gambler.
He has bet his life on this.
What's with that lonely gambler?
The pot-bellied gambler.
- His belly is full of poop too. - Look at his face.
- Get lost. Go inside, man. - His face...
Where would I go? I took out a loan.
- Seriously, what's up with you? - I don't have to bow down to you.
I've never taken your money.
What's up with him, really?
The maximum number of caramels you can bet is 50.
Jong Seo.
- Yes, because the lonely... - Jung Bae...
- The lonely gambler... - I think Jung Bae...
Excuse me. Everyone.
Lonely Gambler, hurry up.
Pot Belly, hurry up.
- Have you all placed your bets? - Yes.
Will you tell us the betting results?
Among those who have placed their bets,
- Did someone use penalties? - someone has bought penalty cards.
- There is? - It was him.
- Who was it? - Someone bought it.
- It's not me. - Jee Seok Jin.
- You must carry someone wth you. - See?
- Gosh, seriously? - I knew it.
- He did it. - Haha did this.
- Who was it? - It was him.
- He bet everything he had. - Ye Eun.
- Haha, please choose the person. - Please win.
- Win and show everyone up. - Pardon?
The person he will carry on his back.
- It was you! - Haha.
- Hey, why would you mention me? - I thought it wasn't you.
- You should keep it a secret. - Why, that...
- That little... - You didn't name anyone.
Gosh, seriously?
- This won't do. - For real?
Darn it, Speed.
I choose...
- Myung Jae. - Pardon?
What?
Myung Jae is pretty light.
I was going to choose the Jimmy Jib...
Will you carry him or Myung Jae?
- My gosh. - Myung Jae.
- Lonely Gambler, this is too much. - Gosh, come on.
- Also, - There's more?
- in Ji Ye Eun's lane, - What?
we'll remove a section of the obstacles.
Wait, what?
Then, I pick the cones!
- He went all-in. - Yes.
- He did. - He did everything he could.
- He bet on Ye Eun. - Oh, he bet on Ye Eun.
He bet on Ye Eun.
I've bet everything I've got.
- But... - Then, the zig-zag...
- You never know. This could be... - You could...
- Hey, Ji Hyo could win. - This is easy.
Ji Hyo, win this. Gosh, he gave Ye Eun a boost.
A plot twist. Hey, if you win, I'll really give you...
- Okay! - Right.
We'll start when you get Myung Jae on your back.
I have to spin while carrying him?
- Even when he spins? - Yes, with him on his back.
- We'll start after that. - How much do you weigh?
- About 70kg... - Darn it!
I might get hurt.
- All right. - He picked him up.
I picked him up. What are you doing?
She's removing her earrings.
Hey, Ye Eun is determined.
- Ye Eun, be determined to win. - I'm determined for sure.
- Go! - Ji Hyo, you can do this!
- I can do this! - Ha Song!
Ready, set...
All right.
- One. - One!
- Two. - Two!
- Three. - Hurry up!
- Two. - Hey!
- One. - One!
One!
- Two. - No!
- Hey, keep going! - Two!
- Let's go. - Three!
- Seok Jin... - Darn it!
Four!
- Three. - You have three more to go.
- Four. - Keep going!
- Five! You're done! - I'm done with five.
You did it. Go!
- Hurry up, Ye Eun! - All right. Go!
- You did it. Go! Hurry up, Ye Eun! - All right. Go!
Just go, kid.
Stop goofing around and hurry up!
- Stop goofing around and hurry up! - Hey, hurry up.
- Go. - Hurry, Ye Eun.
Run. What are you doing?
- Take it off. - Stop goofing around and hurry up!
- Hey, hurry up. Go. - Hurry, Ye Eun.
Run. What are you doing?
- Take it off. - What?
Take it off.
Hurry up, Ye Eun.
- Take it off. - Hurry up, Ye Eun.
- Ji Hyo won. - Take it off.
- Ji Hyo won. - What's this?
Darn it!
Hey, I can't do this!
Ji Hyo won!
Hey, did Ji Hyo win?
- She won. - Gosh, I won.
- Ji Hyo won. - Good job, Ye Eun!
I mean...
- Really, this is so funny. - I thought...
My gosh. Ji Hyo won. Really...
Hey, how low can this guy go?
- That guy... This is so funny. - How low is he going to sink?
- Ye Eun, how did you... - By the way, everyone...
- What? No way. - We have...
- You never know. - a Time Increase Card for Ji Hyo.
- You never know. - A Time Increase Card...
for Ji Hyo.
- Really? - You used all of them, didn't you?
- Did you buy that too? - Who?
So, as a result...
- Did Ji Ye Eun win? - The Time Increase Card?
- The Time Increase Card... - Originally, Ji Hyo won...
with 24 seconds, and Ye Eun was in 2nd place with 25 seconds.
But Ji Hyo got the Time Increase Card,
so Ye Eun is in first place.
- He bought everything. - He did.
- This is how games can be fixed. - Yes!
- Seriously, Ha Dong Hoon! - Therefore, the winner is!
- So, with his bet on Ji Ye Eun... - Nice!
I should just bet 30.
Haha gets three times his bet by himself.
That's insane.
We'll give you 150.
This means no one can beat him.
But then, his loan is...
Several people have to use different cards.
- If one person uses everything... - All right.
The chairperson can turn things back, right?
- Yes, you can. - But...
Darn it.
The chairperson can turn things back, right?
- Yes, you can. - But...
Darn it.
Oh, you're right.
Hey, go easy on me this once.
- But... - Why are you doing this today?
- Oh, dear. - What's wrong with you today?
- Nice one, Chairperson! - Chairperson!
- Chairperson Yu! - Chairperson Yu!
If he gets 150, how many will this guy have?
Well, Haha has taken out quite a big loan, so...
Then, how many does he have? Is he still in debt?
- I'm still in debt. - You have so much debt.
- He's still in debt. - I'm still in debt.
- I won, but I'm still in debt. - Yes, he won, but he's in debt.
But I have now found hope. Yes.
But Jae Seok, you have to nip this in the bud.
You know? Guys like this will rise up later on.
- He'll hold us back. - He's right.
Nip it in the bud, once and for all.
- How many times has he... - Nip it in the bud!
- He's upset. - What's wrong?
- Keep him from rising up. - He's really upset.
- Yes, spin. One, two, three. - One.
- Two. - My gosh!
- Three. - Four.
Shoot!
- That hurts so much. - What are you doing? Run!
Gosh, my...
Are you crazy?
- Gosh, that hurts. - Betting on...
Horse Jong Kook, Haha and Seok Jin win...
- Double. - double their bets.
- Yes! - Okay!
- Okay! - Yes!
Finally, it's our time!
- Don't be too happy. - They each bet 50.
- So, do they win 100? - You'll each get 100.
Finally, it's the board you've all been waiting for.
- For real. - Let's move.
- We're going to the board now. - Okay!
- Okay! - Let's go!
Gosh, we came here to do this.
We must play the final game.
Let's enjoy the board.
Shall we do this?
The board is nice.
- Finally, we're here. - It's tasty.
- Seriously, everyone... - We're here after two years.
- A chance has come after so long. - Yes.
Really, as the chairperson,
I'd like to win and end this neatly...
- That would be nice and neat. - Yes.
Gosh, it's been so long. Pow!
- Okay. - Okay.
I'm sitting in front of the board after two years.
- It's been so long. - So...
- Well... - Let's see how things go.
- Yes, let's see. - Have a seat.
- Yes, I'll take a seat first. - All right.
Well, the chairperson will seat us for this too.
- That's right. I'll seat you. - Chairperson.
- Okay, we have... - Yes.
- only the final card game ahead. - Let's go. Yes.
I'll give you the caramels you've won in the previous missions.
For now, we won't calculate your debts.
- Oh, I won some earlier. - We'll give you what you won.
- All right. - I won 20. I blew 10.
- I got 10. - I got 20.
- Gosh, yes. Thank you. - My gosh.
- Gosh, Haha. - My goodness.
Haha, you're amazing.
- Is this mine? - But...
- Is this it? - I won ten from the horse race.
- Is this all you have, Ji Hyo? - This is all I have, really.
Let's do this! My gosh.
The final mission to determine who the real Card Shark is.
It's the 2026 Upgraded Card Game of Wits.
There will be four players.
The rules are the same as before.
- There are ten forehead cards. - Yes.
You can't see it yourself, but let others see...
by putting it on your forehead.
Also, you have ten hand cards.
- So, only you can see those cards. - Yes.
The person with the highest number from adding the two cards...
or the final person standing will win all of the caramels.
- But there's one change this time. - What is it?
The forehead cards and hand cards...
- each include a Joker. - Oh, really?
So, the Joker can become an irregularity.
What happens?
If you draw a Joker and a number card,
then you get double the number on your card.
Gosh, no way.
Also, if you get two Jokers, you win, no matter what.
That's awesome.
I'm sure the chances of that are slim.
- But you never know. - You don't know that.
However, if you get a Joker and the ten card,
- you blow up. - My gosh.
- You end up with zero. - That's a bad thing.
That's crazy.
Also, if someone gets...
a sum of 14 with just number cards...
- and someone gets 14... - They get 14.
- with a Joker, then the player... - Does the Joker win?
- with the Joker wins. - Oh, I get it.
If we go bankrupt, can we be revived?
- We can't be revived, right? - Or is that the end?
You've all won quite a lot,
- so we weren't going to have loans. - All right.
- Get rid of loans. - All right, then.
Then, we'll get started now. It's up to the chairperson...
who the players will be.
Hang on. First, let's have those with lots of caramels...
Shall I go in first?
- How many do you have? - If you give me a chance...
You should take a break. You're too...
- Oh, are my eyes going mad? - Yes.
I can see too much white in your eyes.
- Right. - You're in danger now.
- But Ye Eun and... - I don't know how to play.
- Do you want to watch first? - Yes, I think I should watch.
- Then, you should move back. - Me too.
- Let's have the rich players go. - All right. Let's go.
Gosh, I'm rather nervous.
Chairperson Yu!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Good luck!
I couldn't become a chairperson once.
Let's have the final match.
It's finally time to play a game.
It's time.
This is what I'm here for.
I'm sitting here after two years.
- Let's collect the entry fee. - The entry fee.
- This is it. - The entry fee.
If your caramel goes into the wrong section, pay again.
- Be quiet, okay? - It went into the wrong section.
- This man... - Why is he acting up? He's poor.
- This man can't wait to join... - Why is he acting up?
- because he has debt. - I see.
- He's acting up too much. - Seriously.
- What's wrong with the magician? - All right.
- Let's begin. - Okay.
It's time for your forehead card.
- Let's select one. - Okay.
For goodness' sake.
- Don't look at it. - Of course not.
Who would look at it?
Now, pick the hidden card.
Pick the hidden card.
All right.
Alright. Let's play this game in earnest.
This is no joke.
Let's proceed with this round.
Hidden card.
- Let's go counterclockwise. - Chairperson.
Jong Kook first.
- Five, of course. - Five?
- People will bet five or more. - Really?
- Five? - Five.
Is it a call?
Call.
I'm reminded of the game I played in Macau in 1985.
The situation was the same as this one.
At times like this,
- I'll match your five... - How many more?
and bet ten more caramels.
I'll match your five...
Life is short, okay?
Okay. That's good.
- Ten more. - That's good.
Gosh, today isn't my lucky day.
I don't think I can do this.
- Really? - It's impossible.
- Are you folding? - I'm folding.
Se Chan, you aren't acting like yourself.
I understand, but this is impossible.
- Put it down. - Put it down.
- Put it down. - I'm done.
- I fold. - What will you do?
- The number is too small. - Ten more.
- So... - What will you do?
- Ten more? - Ten more.
Jong Kook, do it.
I'll bet ten caramels.
- Ten? - Take that and raise the bet!
Are you trying to make a spot for yourself?
What are you doing?
- Stop doing that. - Seriously.
- Is it obvious? - You don't know who'll win.
- How many? - Ten. Call.
- Call? - Ten?
Yes.
How is my number?
Does it look easy?
Don't talk to them.
- You can't do that. - Don't talk to the audience.
- What now? Match the bet. - Ten?
I fold.
- Do you fold? - He wasted five caramels.
Now, the two of them will open the cards.
All done?
- Gosh. - For goodness' sake.
- What is it? Nine? - Now, the hidden cards.
- The hidden cards. - One, two, three.
Three.
One, two, three.
- Six. - I knew it.
Eight.
- Isn't it the same? - It's the same.
- It's the same. Let's split them. - I guess we'll split them.
- Six. - If the totals are the same,
the one with the bigger number on the hidden card wins.
No!
That makes no sense.
- It makes sense, okay? - It has to be done differently.
- The producers make the rules. - That's right.
- Yes. - That's right.
- That's right. - The hidden card is revealed later.
- All right. - I should've kept going.
- Why didn't you do that? - I bluffed.
- I thought that I'd win. - Haha's comments threw me off.
Thank you.
Jong Kook, hurry up and give back the container.
- Okay. For goodness' sake. - For goodness' sake.
- Let's go. - How many caramels did I lose?
- Not many. - I lost so many caramels.
I need to settle the score this time.
In this round,
I'll play without checking the number.
I'll play blind.
Playing blind is the scariest.
- I know. It's the scariest. - I'll play blind.
I'll play blind.
- Here. - They're the tiger moths.
- Put it on your forehead. - Is that your card?
- Then... - Here I go.
- I won't check the number. - I won't check the number.
- Seok Jin, put it well. - Won't you check it?
- Won't you check it? - It's shaking.
- It's shaking. - Yes.
- All right. I'll play blind. - I'll play blind.
All right. I'll play blind.
- Then... - Here I go.
I won't check the number.
- Won't you check it? - Don't check the hidden card.
- Here I go. - Will you really not check it?
I won't check the number.
- This one. - Don't check the hidden card.
- I won't check it. - Will you really not check it?
Any card will do. I won't check.
- I won't check it. - I won't check it.
It's a great match.
They'll go all-in.
I can hear the viewer ratings go up.
Any card will do. I won't check.
- I won't check it. - I won't check it.
- Any card will do. I won't check. - I'll pick one.
- I'll pick one. - I won't check it.
It's a great match.
- Won't you check it? - I won't.
Who is going first?
Jong Kook.
- Jong Kook is going first. - He won the last round.
I'm revving up.
- Is it my turn? - Yes.
- Five. - Five?
- Five. - That's a safe bet.
- It's weak. - It's weak.
Seriously.
- Didn't you check your number? - I shouldn't have done that.
- I didn't. - You didn't?
- That's what makes it scary. - I didn't check my number.
Jae Seok is betting blind.
It's scary.
As for me,
- I match the five-caramel bet. - Okay.
Then I'll bet 20 more.
- What? - Five and twenty.
Bet 25 caramels each.
Five.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
- Jae Seok has guts. - He has guts.
All right.
He'll be on the streets soon.
- Seriously. - On the streets.
- Twenty-five. - Twenty?
- Twenty? - Twenty.
- Our cards... - We can't do this...
- all day long. - Jae Seok, you bet 20...
- after checking our numbers. - I bet 20.
- You didn't check your card. - No, I didn't.
- Did you see my forehead card? - Yes, I did.
- And you bet 20. - And I bet 20.
It's so strange.
- You didn't check your card. - No.
- If you're scared, fold. - There he goes.
In 1967,
I faced off against Takamura in Japan.
Exactly how old are you?
- You must be 100 years old. - He's 2 years old.
- He's two years old. - Back then,
I bluffed in the same way.
- However, I could apprehend you. - Okay.
Isn't this mustache fake?
- What's wrong with you? - Twenty.
- Bet 20. - I need to bet 20, right?
- Hurry up and do it. - Fifteen more.
- Two. - You're dropping the caramels.
- Four. - You must be intimidated.
- Are you intimidated? - Six.
Hey!
- He's aware of his surroundings. - Eight.
- Ten. - He keeps dropping them.
- Is it 25? - I need to throw in 5 more.
It isn't 20.
- All right. They're in. - The number is a bit high.
- Okay. Let's go. - As for me,
I'll check my card.
Hey!
- You're weak! - Listen.
- Play blind until the end. - You're weak!
- You're weak! - It's my card.
- You're weak! - Play blind until the end.
- That's the rule of this scene. - Hey.
If you're going to play that way, get lost!
Can't you see that so many people are waiting?
- I want to check it. - Get lost!
- I want to check it. - Why would you check it?
- For goodness' sake. - Hey.
I'm a bit nervous.
- Hold on. How many? - I'm a bit nervous.
Was it 20?
- It's 25. - It's 25.
So many big numbers are out.
The current bet is 25 caramels.
- So... - It's a lot.
- the current bet is 26 caramels. - Yes.
- All right. - Will you call it?
- Okay. - Come on.
- Ten. - Come on.
- Look at his front teeth. - It's a big game.
- Look at his front teeth. - His front teeth are showing.
- Bring it on. Come on. - They're showing.
- Bring it on. - How many?
- Twenty-five? - Bring it on.
- This is a big game. - Five.
- Okay. I call the bet. - Okay.
What will you do, Muscle?
What will you do, Trainer Yang?
Trainer Yang Chi Seung.
- We have that rule. - What rule?
- We must enter a big game. - Exactly.
- We must. - Enter the game.
Why is everyone happy that I'm entering the game?
- My number must be low. - Enter the game.
- Everyone is happy. - Hurry up.
- Enter the game. - Here I come.
That's how it is.
- They're cool. - That's what people say.
- Seriously. - They enter for the money.
- The members don't play around. - Come on.
- They enter for the money. - Life is all about challenges.
Let's make it electrifying.
- Let's make it electrifying. - Electrifying.
One of them should've folded.
- Seriously. - I called it.
- The forehead card. - Who will go last?
- The forehead card 1st. - The forehead card 1st.
- In 1, 2, 3. - The 2 of them are good.
- Ten? - Se Chan!
- Ten? - Take it off.
- Is my number eight? - If it's a Joker, it'll break.
- I got a ten? - I bet he has a Joker.
With 8, his number is 16.
No?
- If it's a Joker, it'll break. - Is my number eight?
- If it's a Joker, it'll break. - It'll break.
- If it's a Joker, it'll break. - Eight.
All right.
- Reveal it first. - Hey.
It's so nerve-racking.
- Oh, no. Is it a Joker? - I can't win.
- If it's a Joker... - Then it'll be incredible.
- If it's a Joker, I'll win. - I told you so.
In terms of entertainment, this is number one.
I had a game like this in Japan back in 1946.
- Wasn't it 1967? - Here!
Here!
My total is 20.
- Are you serious? - I mean...
- My total is 20. - It isn't a Joker.
Are you serious?
- In 1... - In 1, 2, 3.
It's 4, so the total is 12.
- What's your score? - It's 16.
- It's 16. - It's 16.
I had good cards.
How did he get 10 and 10?
- Seriously. - Thank you.
- Let's reset the game. - Reset the game.
- Ye Eun! - Reset the game.
Let's reset the game!
No.
- What? - We're resetting the game.
- For goodness' sake! Come on! - Okay!
- I knew it. - We're resetting the game.
For goodness' sake! Come on!
- We're resetting the game. - Okay.
That's ridiculous.
- All right. - Take the caramels.
- For goodness' sake! - He didn't disappoint.
- Let's reset the game. - Let's reset the game.
- Let's reset it. - Gosh.
- Let's reset the game. - You used the card.
- It's gone. - Okay.
- Back to the beginning. - It was such a big game.
Do we lose the cards then?
- Yes, we do. - You lose the cards.
Do we lose the cards? That's too bad.
- My Joker is gone. - Do we lose the cards?
The Joker and ten got taken out.
You guys had 8 and 10.
It was a huge game.
- It was incredible. - It was a huge game.
- I lost my cards. - Ten and ten are gone.
I'm so annoyed.
- If I weren't the chairperson... - I lost my ten.
- How did he get 10 and 10? - I would've gone bankrupt.
- Well done. - It would've ended badly.
The forehead cards.
- My goodness. - Let's put it on the forehead.
Good.
Okay.
- Good. - All right.
Let's go.
Let's check our cards.
I won't check mine again.
- Really? - Will you play blind again?
- Won't you check yours? - It'll be nice if you check it.
- Won't you check yours? - No.
Then I won't either.
- Okay. - That's life.
I'll check.
- Why would you do that? - Won't you check yours?
Won't you check yours?
- No. - I'll always check mine.
- Let's go. - How many? Tell us.
Two. I'll bet as many as I have in my hands.
Two, four, six... Eight.
- Eight? - Eight.
- Eight? - Stop asking, you fool.
Fool?
I'll match the bet and add eight more.
- What? - Didn't you check your card?
- Did you check your card? - Fourteen, fifteen, sixteen.
You didn't check your card.
- I did. - He did.
- If you're intimidated, fold. - Did you check?
- Yes. - He checked. Okay.
- That's life. - I'll check.
Then I'll fold.
- I'll fold. - How many?
I'll put 16 caramels in the container.
What? Gosh, we have a customer.
Put them in the container.
- Will you be okay with that? - Put them in.
- Put them in. - Go ahead.
Put them in.
Check your card if you can.
In 5 minutes, 1 person will be on the streets.
Here are ten.
I'll put them in the container.
- I'll put 16 in the container. - Okay.
Then I'll add more.
- More? - On top of the 16 caramels?
I'll add...
- ten. - Ten.
He became a bit timid.
Did you raise the bet by ten caramels?
- Yes. - Then two, four...
- Ten. - They'll run dry.
Eight caramels, right?
- That mister... - Will you bet more?
- He's rich. - Will you bet more?
- He has many caramels. - Will you bet more?
Life is all about challenges.
- Challenges make you cool. - Good.
- I'm ready. - On top of that...
Fifteen.
Two, four, six, eight.
- Seok Jin. - He's using caramels to act cool.
- Did you check your card? - No, I didn't.
- You didn't? - No.
- I added 15 more caramels. - Okay.
It's an awkward number.
- Twenty-five. - When you place a bet...
I can't go on. I fold.
- You fold? - I can't go on.
- Se Chan folds. - Yes.
- As for me, - Are you serious?
I'll put the caramels in here.
- Okay. - You'll put them in there.
He's a tiger moth.
You can stop.
- I... Yes. - Are you serious?
How many caramels are there?
Thirty-two.
Will you go all-in?
I'll go all-in.
He has guts.
You have to take chances.
You can't do this forever.
- Two, four... - I...
- Is it a call? - It's a call.
Thirty-two.
I'm so curious about the result.
What a game.
Neither one of you checked the card.
- No. - No.
- The forehead cards. - The forehead cards first.
- All right. - I didn't check the card.
- He was undeterred by that card. - I don't know what it is.
Here! What?
It's a Joker!
Exactly.
- It's a Joker! - Exactly.
- It's a Joker. - I didn't check the card either.
Seok Jin, you're still in danger.
- That's right. - You didn't check your card.
If it's a small number...
If it's a small number, you'll be in trouble.
If it's a small number, you'll lose.
- It shouldn't be small. Right. - The Joker copies the number.
- That's how it is. - If it's a small number, I'll lose.
Please.
- I hope it's 10 or 9. - That's right.
- This is a big game. - Please.
- It should be a Joker or one. - Please.
A Joker works too.
- Is it a Joker? - It's nine.
- It's a big number. - It's a big number.
- It's a big number. - Nine.
- The total is 12. - Seok Jin!
- Is it a Joker? - It's nine. It's a big number.
It's a big number.
- Nine. - The total is twelve.
- The total is 12. - Seok Jin!
Jae Seok is incredible.
- He didn't check. - Six, seven, or eight.
- It's incredible that he got nine. - Please.
- Nine. - The total is twelve.
- Seok Jin! - Come on.
If I get six, I'll win.
- He has 12. - Yes. Then you'll win.
- That's right. - Six, seven.
- If I get 5, I'll lose. - Get 6 or bigger to win.
- Get 6 or 7. - If it's 6 or bigger, I'll win.
If it's six or bigger, the Joker will win.
Gosh, this is... Hey.
This is intense.
- Gosh. - What will they do?
Nine is a big number.
Please.
Jae Seok won!
- Wait. - Jae Seok won!
- Jae Seok won! - He didn't even check his card.
I didn't have a chance. This was my card.
- I didn't have a chance. - Right.
- What was the hidden card? - How cool.
Jae Seok, you're the best.
Thank you.
How did I get five?
- Seok Jin, the way you played... - Why did you do that?
His forehead card was three.
That's right.
How did you do that after seeing a Joker card?
I can't believe I did it.
It won't be easy to get more caramels than him.
You went all-in, so you can leave.
- Hurry up and leave. - Leave.
For goodness' sake.
The next person can enter.
- Too bad. - I'm so annoyed.
- I did it. - Here he comes.
- I'm sorry, but Zebra One left. - Okay.
- Zebra Two entered. - Just now,
- Vertical Zebra left. - Yes.
- Horizontal Zebra entered. - Horizontal Zebra entered.
Seok Jin, I'll avenge you.
That's right. Avenge me.
Will the cards change since we have a new member?
That's right. Shuffle the cards.
The cards will change. But before that...
Will there be a performance?
The suggestion box is full.
- What? - Really?
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen.
- Are you submitting more? Hey! - I'll submit 15 caramels.
Four.
Ten.
Then the game will be reset.
If Jae Seok becomes the chairperson, he'll get another card.
The suggestion box is full of new balls.
Should I pick one?
- That's right. - Chairperson Yu, please pick one.
- I'm so annoyed. - Who will it be?
This will be the last time.
Jee Seok Jin.
- Let's see what happens. - Jee Seok Jin.
If I get on the chairperson's good side...
All right.
- Jee Seok Jin. - It's Jee Seok Jin.
Yes!
No way.
- Yes! - No way.
- Bring it here, you punk. - For goodness' sake.
But that man can't enter the game anyway.
- Why not? - But he can reset the game.
- That's right. - Then...
- he'll just gain entertainment. - He can't play anymore.
I'll reset the game.
What good will that do?
- For goodness' sake. - Well...
For fun? For your entertainment?
Yes, for my entertainment.
I'll do it for my entertainment.
It won't help him in any way.
For goodness' sake.
Shall we have Ji Hyo or Ye Eun play?
- Let's do that. - I'll sit out.
Ye Eun, try it. You haven't done it once.
- Ye Eun, go on in. - Yes.
- He has many caramels. - I won many caramels.
It was so much fun.
- Go on in. - Let's pick our target.
- Let's pick our target. - Okay.
- Ye Eun, have you done this? - Do you know how to play the game?
Yes, I got the hang of it.
The player with the bigger total wins.
You have many caramels.
Ye Eun has more than you think.
Ye Eun has many caramels.
I have more than you think.
All right.
Let's put on the forehead cards.
I could've gotten them.
- Put on your forehead card. - Please.
- That's Se Chan's card. - Okay.
- Gosh, that's Jong Kook's card. - Let's see.
My goodness.
That's Ye Eun's card. What's Haha's card?
Oh, no.
Let's see.
- Let's see. - Okay.
Five? I'll take out one.
Now, the hidden cards.
- You said you wouldn't check it. - The hidden card.
- When did I say that? - I won't check it.
- I won't check it. - She won't check it.
- Won't you check it? - No.
- Won't you check it? - No, I won't.
- Really? - Yes.
- Will you check it? - Yes.
I'll check it since you said you wouldn't.
You complained when I checked mine.
I won't check mine.
You should follow through if you decide not to check it.
I'll bet eight.
- Eight? - Did you check your card?
Yes, I did.
- I checked my card. - Okay.
- What are you going to do? - I'll take this to the end.
- Come on in. - I'll fold.
Take your time, okay?
- He folded. - Did he fold?
- I... Eight? - Yes.
- I need to match the bet. - Yes.
- Eight. - You can bet more.
- Eight. - There you go.
Eight. Two, four... I'll bet six more.
- Six more? - Six more.
Six more?
- Fifteen. - Are you going all-in?
- She's adding more. - There you go.
- Put them in there. - And here are 30.
There you go. You should put them in there.
And here are 30.
- There you go. - You should put them in there.
- What? - Did you check your card?
I didn't.
- Didn't you check the card? - I didn't.
- You know the rules, right? - Of course, I do!
This is amazing.
That's our Ji. So cool!
- She's bold. - She didn't even check.
That's how you do it.
That's our Ji. So cool!
- She's bold. - She didn't even check.
I'll fold.
- You'll fold? - I'll fold.
Hold on. She's just a newbie. Why did you get scared?
- Why are you scared? - She didn't check her card.
You have to put in around 30-something caramels.
Eight, nine, ten. Two,
- four... - I guess you're confident.
- Five. - I can do one more game. I call.
- Let's see. - Really?
She doesn't know her forehead card.
- Right. - I know her forehead card.
- Our forehead cards first. - Okay.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Your forehead cards. - It's nine.
- It's nice. - It's nice.
- Nine? Six? - It's six.
It's not bad.
I guess he has a high card.
- Should I go first? I checked mine. - Okay.
- I have my favorite number. - Ten?
- Eight. - Hey, then...
- Fourteen. - You can win with five.
- If yours is higher than 5. - If Ye Eun's is higher than 5,
- If it's higher than five. - she wins.
- I win if I have five. - If Ye Eun's is higher than 5,
- She wins if it's higher than 5. - She wins if it's higher than 5.
- What's that? - She'll win.
Low.
- She'll win. - One, two, three.
Joker!
Ye Eun! This is awesome!
- Well done. - You surely shouldn't check.
Joker!
Well done.
- Goodness. - Goodness.
- What was yours? - I lost. It was six.
- Goodness. - So it was a joker.
- It was a joker. - Seriously.
- This is why... - Ye Eun!
- The beginner's luck... - This is great.
You had an eight, Se Chan!
- I'm happy. - My forehead card was low.
Let's do this now.
- The chances of having a joker... - The beginners always do well.
They do well, but in the end, it gets ruined.
But Ye Eun, you got the best...
- You got the best combination. - It was the best combination.
- This is scary. - Seriously.
- It's over now. - The forehead cards.
- It's over now. - Still, it's lower than 10 and 10.
- Right. - Yes. It's lower than 10 and 10.
- My forehead card. - Did you stick it?
- Forehead cards. - I'll put one. Forehead card.
- Did you pick that? - I picked this.
- Did you pick that now? - Did you pick it already?
Yes. This is my forehead card.
- This is my forehead card. - Okay.
- She's having fun now. - This is fun.
- She's on fire. - "This is fun."
- Nice. - This is fun.
- You should pick. - This is fun.
She's on fire.
She's...
- This is nice. - This is fun.
Would I be able to win?
This is funny.
Ye Eun.
- Go. - I should pick one of these.
Pick one each. The cards below.
- I won't look. - You won't look again?
- Right. You shouldn't check. - Let's give it a go!
Ji Ye Eun.
- I should check. - I should check as well.
- I have to check as well. - Let's give it a go.
- Come on! - They're weak.
- Even the newbie isn't checking. - Seriously.
- That zebra. - Goodness.
- First... - You go first.
Two, four, six, eight. I'll place ten first.
- Twenty? - No. I'll place thirty.
What?
- That's bold! Yes, you're... - Six,
eight...
We can't beat Ye Eun.
- Yes, you're... - Six, eight, ten!
- She's feeling it now. - Four...
- Okay. - She's feeling it.
- Six, eight, - I think she's going to win today.
- I know, right? - ten.
- She might win. - I placed 30.
Do you know what you're doing?
Yes.
Did you check your card?
I didn't. I never check.
- I'm getting scared. - She has crazy energy.
The veterans...
- Look at his face. - I've never seen anyone like her.
- Are you scared? - Are you scared?
- Are you scared, Jong Kook? - Are you scared?
I'm out. I'm scared.
At least one of us should...
- That's right. - She's only a newbie!
- Right. - The veterans...
- shouldn't lose! - That's right!
- I'll go all in. - How many are those?
- How many are those? - I'll go all in.
How many are those?
- That guy. - You should adjust to this.
- What? - You should adjust to this.
- You won't easily lose. - How many are those?
I should continue. Two, four...
- They're 56. - This is a big game!
This...
- Then... - I'll match the 56.
- It's going to be more. - Let's go.
- How many? - Fifty-six. I'll match your all-in.
- I have another bunch. - Ye Eun.
Me too. One, two, three, four...
She has more.
Twenty-six?
- Okay. - She still has many of them.
We shouldn't lose to a newbie!
Let me turn my life around tonight!
You never know how this is going to end.
- It's big. - But...
- I can't tell who's going to win. - You never know.
- I can't tell. - I can't tell who's going to win.
I can't tell. Haha also has a strong card.
- No one is saying mine is good. - You never know.
- Yours is strong. - Yours is strong too.
- You all have good cards. - It's strong.
Let's check our forehead cards first.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- It's neck and neck. - You never know.
There's a joker.
But Ye Eun...
But Ye Eun doesn't know what card she has.
- If her card is 8, 9, or 10... - Please.
- Open your cards one at a time. - I'll go first.
- If it's ten, - I'll start.
- Go. - All right!
Guys, I've done this...
- a number of times. - It's a ten.
- It's not bad. - It's not bad. Sixteen.
- Sixteen. - It's a high card!
You never know how this is going to end.
It's a high card!
- Is it me? - Did you check?
- He didn't check. - You didn't check?
- Haha. - He didn't check.
- You didn't check? - He didn't check.
- Ten, ten! - What?
- This is unbeatable. - Ten, ten!
- Did he check? - You can't win that.
- It's over. - This is...
- You can't win this. - It's over.
It's unbeatable.
- You can't win this. - You can't win this.
That's right!
- You can't win this. - That's right!
- He got a 10 and 10. - He got a 10 and 10.
Ten and ten.
- This... - But Haha has to pay back his debt.
- He has to pay back his debt. - He has to pay back his debt.
- What? - It's not a big game.
He can't use them.
Just how much debt does he have?
- All the cards were high. - Ye Eun's was also high.
- She picked the best combination. - That's right.
- It was the best combination. - This...
She had nine.
Ye Eun has very good cards.
- Se Chan is done, right? - I'm broke.
- He's out. - Yes. He's out.
I had fun.
- All right. - It was a fun game.
- I had fun. - Go home first.
- Ji Hyo can... - You can go and get broke.
I'll get broke.
You can go in.
- The former chairman can come in. - I'll...
- I'll join. - Shouldn't we redo the setup?
- I won't check this time as well. - Me neither.
I won't check.
- Are you going all in? - Yes.
- What? - I'll just go at once.
- All in! - But...
- Nice. - You're going all in?
They're gamblers.
If you're scared, fold.
It's a big game.
- Ten, twenty, thirty, forty, fifty. - I really didn't check.
- All in! - Sixty-four.
I think Ji Hyo is going to win.
He won by just one.
- He won by just one. - Two and four.
This doesn't make sense.
I went all out.
Bye.
- Bye. - It was fun!
- Let's end this! - I'm done too.
You had fun.
- This is... - Ten!
- It's over. Take everything. - It's over.
- That's right! - Okay.
He's rising up from being in debt.
- From being a debtor. - From being a debtor...
Today is such a fun day!
The three of you will play with the remaining cards.
- With the remaining cards. - Okay.
- With the remaining cards. - We'll play with what's left.
To me, this looks like the last game.
- Yes. - I think this is the last game.
- I learned a lot. - Yes.
It's a fight between these three.
- All in. - You're really going all in?
- He won. - He won by one.
- This is unbelievable. - I went all out.
We have to determine the winner. We can't keep playing.
The fact that I'm taking on the challenge...
is already a sign of improvement.
I normally don't do such things.
I'm out. I'll fold.
I'm out. I'm scared.
Two, three! Here!
- Jee Seok Jin. - What's going on with me today?
- Let's not talk about this. - I can't just give it to you.
This is good. Very good.
Let me turn my life around...
tonight!
- Ten, ten! - This is unbeatable.
Ten! That's right!
- This... - This is a big game.
- It's a big game. - This is the biggest game.
- The game of three. - If you win, Haha,
- Seriously. - it's going to be amazing.
Your life would turn around...
if you win.
- Forehead cards. - Forehead cards.
I need a big one.
I think this will be the last game.
Let's go.
- The forehead cards. - The forehead cards.
Just go bold with it.
Just choose any card.
Okay. The hidden cards.
- Not looking again? - I won't look.
- You won't? - You shouldn't check.
The hidden card. I won't look.
- I also didn't look. - I won't check.
- This is getting interesting. - Don't check!
- I don't check. - We decided not to check.
- I also won't check. - Right.
Will you place them?
- Well... - Place them.
- All in. - Place them.
Place them.
- How many are they? - There are many.
- I don't know. - Okay. Let's do this.
I'll put everything.
Put everything you have. You have to play this.
I'll just push these.
The person who wins this game...
- You all didn't check, right? - We didn't.
- We didn't check. - It's a big game.
Nice. Let's end it with this.
The forehead cards.
- Okay. - One, two, three.
- This is the last game. - They have similar cards.
- They're similar. - They're similar.
- They're similar. - Four.
This is crazy.
- Five, four, and four. - Five, four, and four. Similar.
- Oswa. - Oswa.
- Oswa! - Give me some luck.
- Let's end this. - Oswa!
- Oswa! - Oswa!
You should win. If they win, I'm definitely getting the penalty.
It's you and me.
- We'll get the penalty... - Horizontal and vertical zebras.
if I don't win.
- Right. - Horizontal and vertical zebras.
- They're similar. - Nice.
Please.
I didn't need the luck before. I need it now.
This is the time. I used the least today.
That's right.
- He used so much today. - Please!
- Two. Goodness. - He used too much.
Two. Goodness.
- It's over. - He used too much.
- Bye. - It's over.
The luck you have at the beginning may not last.
He used up too much of his luck at the beginning.
- Darn it. - He even won by one.
- You have similar cards. - It's done.
We have the same number.
Will we see a miracle again?
Horizontal zebra!
- One... - Goodness.
I win if they get two.
- Right. - You win if they get two.
Jong Kook has the highest chance here.
- I think Haha will win. - I think Haha will win.
They might get 1 or 2.
- One... - You never know.
- Two... - You never know with this one.
- Three! - Three!
Please.
- Nine... - Ten!
Ten!
He's really lucky.
See?
You shouldn't rely on small luck in normal times.
This is the best one.
- Unbelievable. - This is how you should live.
- By the way... - Okay!
I don't think I'll get the penalty.
- Just wait. - I won't.
I'm in trouble. I'll get the penalty.
The no-look round is great.
- This is so funny. - Because I didn't see it...
The winner of the 2026 Card Shark Association...
- is Kim Jong Kook. - Congratulations.
- He deserves it. - Right.
I can't believe I didn't have my luck at the end.
I guess this is how the game is played.
- This is how it should be played. - Right.
- You shouldn't use your brain. - You're right.
You should do this to win.
I always fail to win at the last minute like this.
- Good. - So, Kim Jong Kook, the winner,
- will get the Korean beef set. - Congratulations.
I'm getting protein.
- Jong Kook. - Congratulations.
Trainer Yang.
Congratulations, Trainer Yang.
- I'm getting protein. - Right.
- Thank you so much. - Congratulations.
I should pick the people to get the penalty now.
- Trainer Yang. - And now,
Jong Kook should pick two members...
- to get the penalty. - Two members? Okay.
- Haha has some outstanding debts, - Yes.
so he will get the penalty.
- Oh, dear. - He's picked automatically.
Oh, dear.
- Horizontal zebra is gone. - Pick him.
- Then, vertical zebra? - Vertical zebra?
- And... - One, two?
- You can pick one more person. - Speed and Power?
- Vertical zebra. - Help me this once.
- Jong Kook, Power and Speed. - Vertical zebra?
I'll tell you about today's penalty first.
- Okay. - Not zebra.
Today's penalty is Sightseeing in Seoul,
which will shock the card sharks awake.
I see.
- What's that? - This thing?
Yes. Pulling the sideburns.
- Who'll do it? - The winner will pull them.
I like leopard print too.
- Actually, - Today...
- Zebra... - they played as a team today.
- Like a tag team. - Yes.
- Horizontal and vertical zebras. - Yes.
- Horizontal and vertical zebras. - Black and brown.
- They have the same hairstyle. - Or you could pick her.
- They have the same hairstyle. - Please.
- These two. - Okay!
- It was so close. - Who will do the pulling?
- Se Chan will do it. - Come here.
Haha.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
Three.
You darn punk!
Darn it!
- You darn brat... - Is it that bad?
- Vertical. - One,
- two, three. - Don't do that.
Hey!
It really hurts.
How did you do that?
Thank you.
This is hilarious.
Did you see my hair get pulled out?
We're an event management company.
The makeup came out really well.
- We're an event management company. - This is the best.
Good morning.
- Hello. - Hello, Director Jee.
- Hello. - She's my friend's daughter.
- Be nice to her. - Film it.
Doesn't this company offer coffee?
Coffee?
What?
Hello. Run and Fun Event Company.
Come to the office pantry now.
- What? - What?
What is this?
They're looking for something.
This isn't an ordinary company.
What? Did Ji Hyo find out something?
Don't let them in.
What? There's something.
Let go of it!
What is he doing?
- What's wrong with this old man? - What's with him?
Pull yourself together!
Here I go.
- Go! - Ji Hyo!
- Ji Hyo! - Can you believe this?