Is it today? My goodness.
I prepared this for you.
Welcome.
It's been 16 years. I'm so proud.
You never thought this day would come.
He pretends to be fine, but he's feeling very nervous now.
- I'm very nervous. - Yes.
- It's been a while. - Seok Jin.
Seok Jin, seeing you from here...
- He is... - Do I look great?
- He can't be that strong. - Seok Jin...
- Keep running. - You're so cool.
- There you go! - Run!
Are we really only six years away?
Yes. His 60th birthday is just around the corner.
- We have four years left. - Seriously...
We should throw a party.
Seok Jin's Early 60th Birthday Trip.
Seok Jin!
- Seriously, we will throw... - Please.
his 60th birthday party.
Do you want your 60th birthday party?
I'm telling you here.
Don't throw a party on my birthday.
- His 60th birthday party. - Seriously, don't do it.
It will say 60 here.
You're invited.
- Okay. - Okay. I look so young.
Peekaboo.
Eat it all.
I prepared this for you.
Cheers.
There's sushi. What a feast.
It feels like I'm melting to death.
You're invited.
All right. For now,
I'm clapping alone here,
but I'm a little embarrassed.
I told you not to do this. I said that many times...
during the openings.
"Don't do it." This is embarrassing.
We weren't sure if you really meant it or not.
I was feeling the same way.
While saying that, I wondered if I'd be disappointed.
I wasn't disappointed at all, though.
This is how I felt. "Should I actually do it?"
People around me said, "It's the first time in a variety show."
"Don't you think it's right to do it?"
But I was feeling too shy.
My goodness. I didn't even think of...
I don't think about my age at all.
I have the face of a man in his 40s.
Hey, Old Man.
You. Shut it.
"Living Legend." It's the first time in a variety show.
- The 60th birthday. - My goodness.
- You're right about that. - By the way...
The first time in a variety show.
- This is impressive. - Yes. I'm...
- Grace... Grateful. - You're graceful?
- Thank you. - This is truly amazing.
It truly is.
- It is the first... - I know.
- in the history of variety shows. - I know.
It's not just a birthday party. For the past 16 years,
he has been with us in good health with no trouble.
And now he's celebrating his 60th birthday.
Thank you.
I'm sending you a round of applause with respect.
Thank you. I'm very shy.
These days, being 60 isn't that old.
- What? - The ice sculpture...
- That thing is... - It's melting.
- I saw it earlier. - It turned into Gargamel.
It feels like I'm melting to death. My forehead is gone.
The forehead has melted away.
Seok Jin.
Why are you guys making me...
It's not the forehead. It's the hair.
- My goodness. - This is meaningful, though.
This is really me.
- It's meaningful. - This is my old hairstyle.
- Seok Jin, you should eat. - Yes.
I prepared this.
- You did? - You sound like you did.
- Can I have a drink? - Sure. Go ahead.
- I'll have this. - All right.
- Okay! - You're here.
- Happy birthday! - You're here.
Happy birthday!
- Thanks. - Seok Jin.
- Finally. - Hey.
- Kim Thug. - Yes?
"Happy birthday" sounds so lame.
- Why? - What was that?
- I mean... - Kim Thug?
This is very meaningful.
- Right. - We already talked about it.
- I mean, it's... - It's very meaningful.
It's not like he's done this show for a couple of years.
- It's been 16 years. - It's unbelievable.
- With no trouble. - I know.
- That's not an easy thing to do. - Actually...
- Can you believe this? - It's really difficult.
You've set a new milestone.
That's true.
- Congratulations. - You know how careful I've been.
- Of course. - We do know that.
- Like him... - Instead of going outside...
You've faced a few crises, but we covered for you well.
He's a man with a lot of desires, but he's suppressed them.
- Trying not to go outside. - Right.
It was just home and work.
- Exactly. - That's why you're where you are.
- You're right. - That's not easy.
- Hey. - Hey.
Hey.
- Ye Eun. - Hey.
- It's not in order of age. - Hello.
As expected, you're quite big.
- Hello. Happy birthday! - Hey.
- Hey. - My goodness.
- It's all thanks to you. - I can't believe this.
- It's amazing, isn't it? - It's amazing.
- It's truly amazing. - It's unbelievable.
- Right. - We used to...
- joke about this, right? - Yes.
I didn't know we'd be doing it for so long.
- Right. - Honestly, back then,
I didn't think we'd be doing this until I turned 60.
- We didn't think so. - We had no idea.
- Exactly. - What's amazing about me...
is that my face hasn't changed at all.
- Right. - You look even younger now.
- Since 2010. - Impressive.
Compare my faces.
Running Man. Bang!
Running Man! Bang!
That was a long time ago.
- I haven't changed. - You got younger.
- You did something... - You look younger.
- to your face, right? - Honestly.
I did a few things.
But I couldn't do anything strong.
Because I have to do this show every week.
And power. You're really strong.
- Right. And you're fast! - My goodness.
This is crazy.
As expected. I'm so satisfied. Someone's coming.
- What's that? - They're coming.
- Hey. - Hey.
- Look at Ssaebssaeb. - The fraud is coming.
- That fraud. - The hustler is coming.
Nice.
Alright! I sincerely wish you
A happy birthday
Se Chan looks so cool with sunglasses on.
- He looks amazing. - Right.
- He looks amazing. - Ssaebssaeb looks...
so frivolous even when he's dressed up.
- Yes. - Seriously.
- It can't be helped. - That's better.
- He looks like a hustler. - That's true.
- Yes. - He needs a mask.
- Anyway, he's the living legend. - True..
- Running Man's... - That's a bit too much.
- eldest member... - You are a living legend.
in the history of variety shows.
Seriously, I feel like crying.
It's Seok Sam's birthday. Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
The race starts!
- The race has begun! - The race starts!
I just got here!
I just got here! Hey! Ji Sung!
It's been only two minutes.
Big Nose is annoyed,
but trying his best is Big Nose's thing.
- It's over! - Seok Jin!
Seok Jin!
- You should break it. - Right away.
It's only on his nose!
How does his nose look like that?
- Oh, no! - That's absurd!
- What was that? - Seok Jin, don't try to stand out.
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
All right. He's bowing deeply.
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!
Health, blessing, and love!
This is really crazy.
We should get him a floral palanquin.
Thank you. I'm making a deep bow.
Let's greet Seok Sam together.
- Let's do that. - Shall we make a deep bow?
- We should make a deep bow. - Let's do that.
- Come here. - Don't do that. Come on.
Stand right here.
Don't do that!
- Stand here, Seok Jin. - Come on.
- We will make a deep bow here. - Stop it.
- Seriously, don't do that. - Stand here.
- Come on. - Just do it.
Seriously, stop it.
- Let us make a bow. - Accept our bow.
- All right. - My goodness.
Seok Jin.
- Stay healthy. - Stay healthy.
Why are you being like this?
- Live a healthy life. - This is why.
This is why I didn't want to do this.
These guys are...
They're enjoying this.
They will start enjoying it.
Except for Kang Chan Hee,
you all should come here and make a bow.
- Okay. - Stop it!
Hey!
Stop it!
This is the beginning. He's trying to annoy me.
- They should do it. - Stop it.
They should make a bow later.
- They'll do it later. - Before the shoot ends.
Isn't Chan Hee here today?
- He didn't come? - Stop it.
Then, you all should come here.
- Those under 60. - Come here.
- Hey! - Those under 60.
- Don't do that. - Those under 60.
- Stop it. - We have to do this.
- You should come out here. - Those born after 1967.
- Come on out. - Seriously, don't do that.
- I'll run away. - We have to do it today.
- All right. Come here. - Okay.
- All right. - Come here.
It's a party.
- This is amazing. - Let's have a drink.
- Can I eat them? - This is pretty.
This is insane.
Today is the 60th birthday special for Jee Seok Jin,
the first variety show cast member who has made a great achievement...
This is a great achievement.
of turning 60.
It's called The Great Gatsby Jee.
- Gatsby Jee! - It's so cool.
- It's perfect for him. - So,
- It's so touching. - to celebrate the special day,
we've issued commemorative coins called Big Nose Coins.
Big Nose Coins?
The world is mine!
The feeling of wealth.
- Please show them. - All right.
- Okay. - Let me see.
- They're specially made. - This is how they look.
You should've made them better.
All you did was put some stickers on them.
That's it.
The production staff must have worked hard.
They could've been made in 3D.
They aren't specially made.
- Right. - The stickers were applied by hand.
- They were applied by hand. - They were hand-made.
- They were hand-made. - Right.
- Seok Jin. - Yes.
While enjoying the party,
you can hand out the Big Nose Coins...
- to the members you like. - My goodness.
- I will... - I don't think I'll get many.
Only the coins I have here?
There will be more chances,
- but hand out what you have now. - This?
The more Big Nose Coins you have,
the better off you are for today's race.
So, it's important to get on Seok Jin's good side.
Because today is his birthday.
We've always been nice to him.
All right. Since it's a good day,
- you can enjoy your meal first. - Okay.
Thank you.
Is there anything you want to eat, Seok Jin?
- What do you want to eat? - Anything you want.
I like bread.
- Bread? He likes bread. - And fruit.
Seok Jin, stay seated. I'll get you some food.
Don't tell him to stay seated.
He should walk around and eat whatever he wants.
Do you need my help, Seok Jin?
- You should have some vegetables. - Okay.
- Stay seated. - Get some rest.
I'll do it myself.
Those sly brats. My goodness.
What? Sly brats?
- Excuse me. - What?
Are you upset?
- No, I'm not upset. - Okay.
They sound so crafty.
- This looks delicious. The olives. - We should eat this.
What's this thing?
Is it fish?
- This looks delicious. - I like sandwiches.
This is so good.
It tastes so good.
Try this.
This is good.
The sandwich is good, isn't it?
Wait. I...
Grapefruit juice.
- Ye Eun, I'm thirsty. - Okay.
- I'm a little thirsty. - Okay.
- Are you thirsty? - Yes.
Darn it.
- He gave up on receiving coins. - I can't stand this.
Do you want to give me something?
I'm so upset.
- Thanks. - Seok Jin.
I...
Is it tomato juice?
- Hey. - This isn't enough.
You brought only one thing.
- You did this for coins? - No.
- Of course, she did. - That's not true.
- This isn't acceptable. - What?
- Who? - Are you on the same team?
Just give me some.
- I'll throw this. - Ye Eun.
Don't be like that.
I'm only telling you.
What's that?
- Throw it, Seok Jin! - What?
Hey!
- What? - Seriously...
- Bring it back. - Anyone who takes it back...
- Why? - will get two coins.
I'll give two to the person who takes it back.
- You get two if you get it back! - Stop right there.
Two coins!
You get two if you take it from him.
I got him.
You get 2 if you take it from him. I'll give you 1 more.
- I'll throw this. - Okay.
One more.
Okay. You get one more.
He's getting a lot.
All right.
Hey! Everyone.
- Everyone. - Please.
I can't believe this.
- Do you want this? - We do!
What is my name?
- Jee Seok Jin! - Jee Seok Jin!
- Who am I? - Jee Seok Jin!
- There you go! - Jee Seok Jin!
There you go!
- Good. - There you go!
Good.
- Come on. - This is so upsetting.
- He's lucky. - Wait.
You can't just give them out like that, Seok Jin.
When Jong Kook...
- took it from him... - You can't give them out like that.
Why not? It's my choice.
You should give them to the person who works hard.
- Seok Jin, why aren't you... - Here's the thing.
When Jong Kook was...
What was that?
- Did he hit me? - By the way,
- Did I get hit? - it sounded so good.
- He hit you. - Did he hit me?
I heard a loud slap.
Really? About him...
Take him over there...
and tickle him.
I'll give you 1 coin if you tickle him for 1 minute.
I'll give one to the person who tickles him.
Loyalty!
- By the way... - Did you hit me?
- Wait. - I've got too many coins.
- Jong Kook, come here. - Hey.
I can't believe this. Hey.
- Did you just hit me? - I will...
I'll hold him. You tickle him.
- Okay. Let Jong Kook do it. - I've got many coins.
- Can I tickle him? - Wait.
Wait.
Here comes one coin.
- Me! - To the person who worked hardest.
Me!
It's going to the person who tried their best.
I'm giving him a wedgie.
Me!
- I should get one. - Me.
- Okay. To Speed. - Me.
- Okay. - He's done many things for me.
- Come on, Seok Jin. - Wait.
- This is really... - Sorry.
- Speed is... - Unbelievable.
- How could you do this? - The thing is...
- How could he do that? - Seriously...
Today is his 60th birthday. He deserves to do this.
- Did you hear the slapping sound? - Yes.
- It was really... - My goodness.
About Jong Kook, I...
- He deserves many coins. - Right.
- He repays what he receives. - Of course.
- Right? That's what you do. - Sure.
- You're right. - He returns my favor.
I return as much as I receive.
Hey!
What are you doing?
- You got a pointy nose. - Stop it.
Stop it already.
I'll call the guys again.
- Do you want me to call them? - What...
I'll call them.
My nose looks strange. My gosh.
- Listen. - Yes.
Seok Jin, we can eat this cake.
Do you want me to cut it for you?
We should eat it.
- Let's take a picture, Seok Jin. - Take a picture first.
- All right. - You should cut the cake.
- All right. - I'll take a picture of you.
Cut the cake, Seok Jin.
Kimchi.
You look so pretty.
You look really cool.
So pretty. You look like Park Seo Jun.
- She's making fun of you. - She's mocking you.
- No. - Park Seo Jun is mocking me.
- Obviously. - And...
You look good when you do this.
- I will... - Like an old man with a hump.
- You should cut the cake. - You look so cool.
- All right. - My goodness.
Okay.
Thank you.
Who clapped the loudest?
- Who's the loudest? - Okay.
Don't cry, Haha.
Seok Jin, Haha is crying.
- What? - Haha is crying?
If you shed tears, you get one.
- Tears. - He's not crying.
- Show me your tears. - Seok Jin.
No. No tears.
Let me see your tears.
If you shed tears, you get one.
If you shed a tear, I'll give you one.
There are no tears.
If you shed tears, you get one.
- Tears. - Seok Jin, look at me.
If you shed tears...
- She's about to shed tears. - By the way...
If you shed tears, you get one.
Is this your funeral? Why do you want them to cry?
- Why is that? - They are moved to tears.
- Why are they crying? - Why is that?
- If one of them sheds tears... - Don't cry!
Shed tears.
You get one coin!
- She's an actress. - An actress is different.
- Ji Ye Eun. - Tears fell from her eyes.
- I'm so sad. - What were you thinking about?
- I'm really sad. - That was unbelievable.
- Thank you, Ye Eun. - Unbelievable.
- That was beautiful. - I'm really sad.
- You even shed tears. - She cried.
- I'm so upset. - That was...
- Aren't you eating the cake? - This is for the preview.
- Tears fell from Ye Eun's eyes. - Yes.
Korea National University of Arts!
How could she cry so quickly?
Give me one now.
Why would I? Give me a reason.
They all have at least one each.
- You have to do something. - You should be nice to him.
- Do something. - You did...
You can tell us just one good story about Seok Jin.
- A good story about Seok Jin? - Yes.
- So that everyone knows. - Let's do that.
- Something beautiful. - You should do it today.
A beautiful story that will make us burst into tears.
- A good story people don't know of. - There has to be one.
- A heroic story. - Share something nice I did...
- that they haven't heard about. - An untold story?
That's right.
Did he do anything thoughtful back in your clubbing days?
- Was he a good wingman? - A wingman.
Did he ever set Yong Man up with anyone...
or even Soo Yong?
He never did that once.
He always told me to go home early.
- Go back home? - Yes.
"Jae Seok, hurry home already."
- The numbers didn't match. - Right.
- The guys outnumbered the girls. - That's right.
- It's... - He's out of his mind.
There were three women...
- and four of us in total. - I see.
So Seok Jin told me to head home early.
- That's a sweet story. - Stop right there for a coin.
- That was sweet of him. - Okay.
- If you stop talking. - I'll stop.
- I'll stop. - I bet you sent him home...
- to spare him the heartache. - Right.
- The women won't choose him anyway. - That was nice of him.
- That's why I brought it up. - That was sweet of him.
He was worried I'd get hurt at a young age.
- Exactly. - I believe that's why he did it.
- Of course. - Right.
How thoughtful of him.
- Stop there, and I'll give you one. - I'll leave it at that.
- Here. Goodness. - Thanks.
You should be grateful.
You all got one. Wait. Shouldn't I keep one for myself?
- It's little. - What a meaningful day.
It's not like we received anything though.
Today,
we're celebrating Seok Jin's 60th birthday.
The celebratory Big Nose Coin...
doesn't have to be collected only through Seok Jin.
- What? - Is that so?
- You'll get chances to win more. - Of course.
The others will compete in the Big Nose Golden Bell.
We'll be answering questions about Seok Jin.
- That's right. - Sounds like fun.
- Do the others have to answer this? - Yes.
A lot of them would know this.
- Really? - Yes.
Are you sure about that?
Director, come on.
For every correct question,
- you'll receive two coins. - Sounds good.
Jae Seok has the upper hand.
Exactly. This is a game for Jae Seok.
- Sounds good. - He knows a lot about Seok Jin.
Here's the first question.
- Answer if you can. - Got it.
What is Seok Jin's nickname stated on the SBS official website?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Se Chan, go ahead. - What is it?
- Big Nose in English. - Incorrect.
- Let me answer. - Haha?
- Big Nose in Korean. - Incorrect.
- Let me answer. - Jae Seok?
Impala.
Yes, that's the one.
- Incorrect. - No?
- Let me answer. - What is it?
- Even I don't know. - You seem lost,
so here's something that might help you.
- It's not about his nose. - When did I...
Please fill in the blank and complete his nickname.
- Trying... - Is it "loving?"
- What's my nickname? - What's the answer?
- Trying... - Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Se Chan, go ahead.
The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong, trying to look young.
- Yes, that's the one. - Incorrect.
- Incorrect. - What is it then?
- Let me answer! - The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong,
- trying to be sweet. - Incorrect.
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
Trying to be in love and romantic.
Yes, that's the one.
- It's very similar. - Let me answer.
This is Seok Jin.
He doesn't know himself.
He has no idea he's the Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong,
trying to be sweet and romantic.
I love it.
- Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong. - I love it.
- Let me answer. - Jae Seok, go ahead.
Trying to be romantic.
- That's it. - That's the one.
- You're almost there. - Isn't that it?
- That's not it? - Is that wrong?
- Let me answer. - What?
- Pretending to be a doting husband. - That's the one.
It's not exactly about his wife.
- Not my wife? - Maybe it's her name.
Let me answer. The Hugh Grant of Jamwon-dong,
- pretending to love Su Jung. - Incorrect.
What on earth is it?
It's awfully close. You're almost there.
- Pretending... - This is tough.
Gosh! Pretending?
Let me answer. Pretending to love his family.
- That's it. - Correct!
- How did you get that? - It was his family.
- Even I didn't know that. - His family!
- I remember someone saying that. - I do too.
We all came up with different nicknames.
- This next one might be tough. - This can be challenging.
- I prefer that. - Challenging ones are better.
During the pilot episode...
- of Running Man on July 11, 2010, - I like this one.
what was Seok Jin's first greeting...
after everyone gathered?
Since this is the first episode, let's greet the viewers.
Seok Jin, we'll start with you.
Hello.
Recently...
- It's suddenly raining. - Why is it raining?
Why does it rain whenever I talk?
It might even hail...
- What was it? - What did I say?
- Let me answer. - Was it with that expression?
- Yes. - Right.
- Haha? - Let's go.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. Hello, - Sure.
I'm MC Jee Seok Jin.
- I wonder what he said. - That is incorrect.
- It's captioned "out of the blue." - Out of the blue.
- When they first gathered? - What did he say?
- The pilot episode? - They had met for the first time.
- I wonder what he said. - I got it. Hi, I'm Jee Seok Jin.
- It's something like that. - He did introduce himself,
- but he said something else before. - "Something" Jee Seok Jin.
Hello. You know me. I'm Jee Seok Jin.
"You know me?"
Let me answer. I'm your sweetie, Jee Seok Jin.
- Incorrect. - Isn't it something like that?
I wonder what it was.
- Let me answer. - Go ahead.
Hello, everyone. I'm Jee Seok Jin.
Let me answer.
Go ahead.
It's me, Jee Seok Jin.
- You're almost there. - Let me answer.
Let me answer. This is it.
It's me, guys. I'm Jee Seok Jin.
- It's similar. - Let me answer!
You know me. I'm Jee Seok Jin.
- That is correct. - Really?
"You know me. I'm Jee Seok Jin." Is that what I said?
Did he say that?
He really was brazen.
I was kind of rude back then.
- But... You were young too. - I was rude.
Weren't you in your 50s?
- I was younger than Haha is now. - He was 45.
He was around 46.
I was four years younger than Haha is now.
You look way younger today.
- Really? - No way.
If only I had extra coins.
- He's out of coins. - I see.
He's out of coins, so don't bother.
Arrange these photos of Seok Jin...
in chronological order.
In chronological order?
I think I've got it.
- Hold on. - I don't have a clue.
I think number three comes first.
- Hold on a second. - I don't have a clue.
I think I've got it.
Let me answer.
- Sure. - Do I have to guess the year?
- No. - No, right?
- No. - Number three comes first.
Three, four, two, and one.
- Incorrect. - Let me answer!
- Let me answer! - Go ahead.
Three, two, four, and one.
- That's it. - That's correct.
- Correct. - Got it.
- That's what I initially thought. - Of course.
- It's 2010, 2025... - Darn.
- That's what I initially thought. - I've gotten old.
- Three, two, four, and one. - Seok Jin.
- You looked so young in 2010. - He looks so young.
- I look noticeably younger. - You look like a kid.
- You look like a kid. - Right?
- I looked young in the beginning. - He looks like a kid.
His skin has a shine to it.
- I look different. - Your skin is glowing.
- It's oilier. - I look different.
- This is so sad. - This next one...
might be easy for you.
Sounds good.
Which direction does Seok Jin's belly button shift toward?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
Jae Seok?
- To the right. - Correct.
The right.
That's correct.
Exactly. It's shifted to one side.
I revealed my belly button on the show.
- Yes, he showed it to us. - Right.
It's shifted slightly to the right.
- Really? - It's on the right.
- Actually, my belly button... - What?
To be honest, my belly button...
- He's making this up. - It's slightly on the right.
- All right. - Come down.
- Your belly button? - Which direction did you say?
- It off the the right, right? - It's for real!
- It's true. - Really?
- Is it true? - I was so shocked!
- That shocked me! - It's true.
It's over here.
Seriously?
- Is it true? - I knew that one.
- It's at five o'clock. - Five.
It's angled at five.
- It's at five o'clock. - Yes, at five o'clock.
This is 15 years of friendship at its best.
This will be easy for anyone who knows what Seok Jin...
- is usually like. - Really?
This will be easy for us.
What did Seok Jin...
have for breakfast today?
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Go ahead. - Pureed tomatoes.
Pureed tomatoes.
- Let me answer. - Pureed tomatoes.
You need to be more specific.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Haha? - Detox soup.
- That is correct. - Why did I say that out loud?
For today's breakfast?
That's the same as pureed tomatoes!
- I know you, Seok Jin. - When did he tell us that?
- You meant tomato juice. - Detox soup.
What I have is tomato soup.
Tomato soup?
Jae Seok has natto for breakfast.
- That's right. - Right.
I didn't even manage to get one right.
You all know Seok Jin is famous for misspeaking.
- Right. - Of course.
In life, you can get brought up with bad things.
- That's how it is. - You must've been flustered.
That's mint chocolate.
Me is the only one who can match Tom Cruise's age.
Shouldn't it be "I?"
Here's an important piece of information.
In late 2019, COVID-19...
- was released. - Released?
Is it a pop group or something?
Here's a question...
- about his slip of the tongue. - Sure.
He once messed up a guest's name...
- on the show. - Right.
Whose name?
- Please guess what he called him. - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Let me answer.
- Go ahead. - Choo Sa Rang.
Let me answer. Choo Shin Soo.
- That is correct. - See?
- I remember this. - Did I really call him that?
I don't recall.
It was during...
- That's right. - the mudflat wrestling.
- That's right. - Right.
Choo Shin Soo and Kim Jong Kook!
Choo Shin Soo?
Slam him into the mud.
But it's cold.
Here's the next question.
Seok Jin in 2021,
during Episode 561...
- I know. - Let me answer!
During Episode 561...
- I know this one. - What is it?
Haha, go ahead.
The human Burberry.
- Incorrect. - I got it. The human preservative.
- Incorrect. - No, that's not it.
- I know what this is. - The human...
I remember this.
The human artificial person.
Incorrect.
Artificial person? Are you kidding me?
Let me answer.
The human wax doll.
Incorrect.
That actually makes sense.
- A wax doll? - It makes sense.
Wasn't it something like...
- "human BB cream?" - Let me answer.
- Let me answer. - Yes?
- "Human BB cream!" - No.
- Correct. - Right?
That's the actual answer?
- I got lucky. - That's it?
I remember now.
- Yes. - I knew the answer.
I remember saying "human BB cream" when her nickname was Barbie.
Han Chae Young.
She's the human BB cream.
She's really...
We met for the first time.
- It's bringing back memories. - This is hard.
- I'm reminiscing a lot now. - My gosh.
- I'm tearing up. - It's quite...
Why are you tearing up?
- Honestly. - Anyway,
answering questions about what Seok Jin...
- said and did... - Yes.
Seriously, the time...
It's so...
It's hard to believe. I'm getting emotional.
- I did this for 16 years. - It's impressive.
Okay. Here's the next question.
You were trying to guess movie titles.
You had to name Youn Yuh Jung's movie "Minari."
- Yes. - I remember that!
- Seok Jin got it wrong. - Jong Kook explained the plot.
- Let me answer. - Yes?
- "Meojeori." - Incorrect.
Let me answer! "Gaenari."
Incorrect.
Let me answer. "Julgeori?"
- Correct. - For real?
Does that even make sense?
For real?
- Does that even make sense? - That's right.
Does "julgeori" make any sense?
It's the southern dialect meaning a stalk.
I think that's what I meant.
Jong Kook got so many right.
You need to think way out of the box to get it right.
- Let me answer! - Yes.
"Trauma?"
- Correct. - For real?
- It can't be! - I said that.
He really said that?
- Blue. - Correct.
- I thought it was sky blue. - He wore blue a lot then.
- He wore a lot of blue. - That's right.
That's right.
I didn't get a single one right.
I don't know anything about Seok Jin.
- I got zero points. - Why... I'm hurt.
Ssaebssaeb. You don't care about Seok Jin at all.
Zero, basically.
So Jong Kook won a total of ten coins.
That's too many.
- Haha won six. - Okay.
- Jae Seok got four. - Gosh.
And Ye Eun got two.
Ji Hyo and Se Chan got zero.
Oh, no.
What's that?
- My gosh. - Why? What's wrong?
- What's going on? - This is an emergency.
- What? - This is an emergency.
- For real? - This is an emergency.
- What's this? - Gatsby Jee's safe was raided,
and all the Big Nose Coins inside were stolen.
- Who took them? - This is an emergency.
This is an emergency.
Gatsby Jee's safe was raided...
and all the Big Nose Coins inside were stolen.
- Who took them? - Who is it?
It's one of you lot.
- Is it you? - Who is it?
You Antenna fools!
He's overreacting. It's him.
There's a spy?
Do you have to steal from me today of all days?
Who is it?
Hints that will tell you where to find the stolen coins...
are scattered in the park surrounding L Tower.
- In the park? - In the park.
You can either find actual hints hidden around the park.
Or you can go to the Hint Room that's somewhere in the park.
- You can spend your coins... - Buy a hint?
to buy a hint about the location.
That works for me.
A few kinds of hints are available in the Hint Room,
and one of them is called a high-grade hint.
It contains crucial information,
and it costs more than the other hints.
The first person to find the stolen Big Nose Coins...
wins the race and gets to keep all the coins,
- and is exempt from the penalty. - Okay.
- All who fail will be penalized. - Let's do this.
Everyone?
Seok Jin, you must look for the coins too.
Me too?
Considering how today...
It's my day. Don't I have an advantage?
Your birthday party is over.
- It should come to an end. - Happy Birthday.
Yes. Do I get a basic stash of Big Nose Coins?
- No. You must find them. - You're out.
- No? - We can stop brown-nosing, then?
Your reign is over.
- Get changed to start hunting. - Okay.
- Okay. - Let's go!
I'd have kept a few coins if I'd known I'd need them.
I gave them all away.
Someone stole my stash, and we're off to find it.
I must find what's mine. Gosh...
I'm in a terrible position. I need coins to buy hints...
and get an advantage.
I shouldn't have given them all away.
I'd have kept 3 or 4 if I'd known.
I need the coins.
Those who have a lot have, like, ten coins.
I won a lot of Big Nose Coins early in the game.
I have a good chance today.
I won't be stingy. I'll change this year.
Ye Eun's calling.
Sir Jong Kook.
Yes, hi. Goodness.
We're a team.
Are we? When did we become a team?
I really want to team up with you.
- Oh, do you? - This is me sending you love.
- Is it? - Yes.
I'm serious.
Do you see the look in my eyes?
Yes. What...
Let's see how things pan out when we get out of the car.
When we reach the park, okay? I'll find the Hint Room...
and see how much the hints cost.
Don't betray me.
Okay.
Bye.
- My dear bro. - Yes, bro.
The two of us haven't shown much friendship...
or chemistry in a while.
- That's true. - We should work together.
- Okay. - Yes.
Sure. Bye.
This is how you know you're on the same page.
Flies keep circling because they know...
I have coins to spend. Maybe I should...
buy a high-grade hint right away.
And memorize that hint and keep it to myself.
Where am I to find this safe?
Do I get out here? Okay.
How do I find it?
Honestly. How do I find it?
The elderly are exercising at this time of day.
I see they're exercising hard when it's pretty cold out.
This is my first time in Ogeum Park.
I don't know where the boundaries are.
The park seems pretty big.
It's way too big.
How do I find it?
Where could it be hidden?
- We'll begin... - Okay.
the Find the Stolen Big Nose Coins race.
- Let's go. - Five,
four, three,
- two, one. - Two, one.
Race start. Let's go.
Race start.
I bet Seok Jin said it.
Okay. There he is.
- Seok Jin. - What?
I said "race start" for once after a while.
I thought so, so I said it too and then said...
I bet you said it.
Did you? Good job.
- You're the star today. - Hey. If you were...
to help me out...
Your friends are right there.
Exercise with them.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Seok Jin turns 60 this year.
- Keep quiet. - It's unbelievable, right?
- They know. - I see. Thank you.
It's his birthday.
Thank you, Big Sis.
- "Big Sis?" - Why not?
She seemed older.
- Seok Jin. - Help me, and I'll treat you.
- Listen. - Seriously.
- You have no coins. - Right.
- You can't get any hints. - Right.
Why not? What am I today, then?
- All you can do is... - Yes?
- help us deduct or search. - What am I today? Okay.
- If you help us, we'll... - I see.
He can't help us today.
- What am I, then? - He has nothing.
Then you're just...
There seems to be a rumor that I stole my own coins. I didn't.
- But you... - They wouldn't give you...
- a big role involving that plot. - That's right.
You're pretty weak overall.
- That's not... - So...
- I didn't steal the coins. - You can't have.
I happened to give away all my coins.
I should've kept 5 out of the 10 I got.
You had to give them all away.
- I'll go to higher ground. - Me too.
What? Can we go this way?
- Call when you find something. - Okay, I'll call you.
- I need to find hints. - Yes.
Let's go higher up and look around.
Do we search the whole park?
Are the hints in envelopes?
Let's find hints.
Where are the blue envelopes?
Shall I go this way?
Where are the hints hidden?
It hurts.
I don't think I can show this.
It's a topless Seok Jin.
He's not wearing clothes. I can't show this on TV.
Seok Jin planned it himself.
Jee Seok Jin. Honestly...
Where are the hints hidden?
What in the world am I doing?
The hint... Oh, here!
I found the hint.
- Seok Sam! - Yes?
- I found one right here. - Did you find anything?
There's one over here.
What is it?
Oh, I can't show you this.
It's an individual match.
Right here.
Gosh, it's right here.
My gosh. Really?
- What is this? - My gosh.
What is this?
It's bungeoppang and egg bread.
Did you find anything?
- What is this? - My gosh.
What is this?
What did you find there?
I found it, but I can't tell you.
- Just tell me. What is it? - No, I can't tell you.
It's just a few pictures.
- Is that right? - Yes.
Gosh, where could it be?
Oh, this...
- What? - Why?
- It's here. - Oh, you found one.
- Yes, I found it. - Shoot, it was over there.
What is it?
Oh, it was right here.
Gosh, it was in between.
- Darn it. - This is an important hint.
- Shoot. - This is awesome.
- Then, do you want to share hints? - Shall we?
- Of course. - That's a good idea.
- We should find it quickly. - Okay.
- That's a good idea. - Show me.
- Together. - Okay. It's right here.
- Okay, so together. - It's right here.
- How about we switch? - Sounds good.
- Let's switch since I've seen it. - I've seen mine too.
Wait, let me take a picture.
Gosh, there's no need for that.
But still.
- Wait. - Seok Jin, hurry up.
- That's it. - Okay.
- Here. - Together.
- Give me that. Let go. - Okay, 1, 2.
Okay, I'll give it to you for sure.
- Let's give it to the cameraman. - All right.
I just can't trust... Okay.
- Give it to him. - Switch with each other.
- Hey, let go of that one. - But...
- Let go. - Let go of it.
- Let go. - Well, grab each other's.
- Come on. Let go. - Wait.
- In 1, 2, 3. Okay. - In 1, 2, 3. Nice.
Hey! A dud?
Hey!
Gosh, this is so annoying! This is a dud!
It's a dud.
Hey! You crook.
This is a dud. I thought...
How can there be such a thing?
Is this kind of thing happening today too?
But how could this happen?
It's as if you guys planned this.
Gosh, I'm so mad!
What is this? Bungeoppang and...
What is this one besides the bungeoppang?
Oh, it's not a dud.
It's so easy to spot.
It's bungeoppang and... What is this?
What is this?
Is it egg bread?
Bungeoppang and egg bread.
Bungeo and egg. They're both breads.
Right? Bread.
Let's get going. Gosh, the hints are unexpectedly...
Oh, what is that?
That blue thing.
The blue thing.
Will it be bread again?
Hey, still... Gosh, this is...
Hey, this...
Gosh, seriously...
This is crazy.
I should go to the Hint Room.
Where is it?
I'm really going to find it.
- Oh, my. Hello. - Hello.
I'm a fan of yours.
Same here.
You're from "Attack on Titan," aren't you?
- I enjoyed "Attack on Titan." - Come on.
It was so scary when you ate people.
I really enjoyed it.
- I'm a fan. - I'm a fan.
I'm a fan of yours.
As soon as you turned around,
how could your expression change in an instant?
- I'm a fan. - Did you find anything?
- Did you find anything? - I can't seem to find anything.
Really?
- Let's share. - Sure.
Oh, dear.
It's the Hint Room. In the Hint Room...
When you go to the Hint Room, you can get a hint.
But I don't have any coins right now.
They're expensive.
I'll come back after I get five more coins.
I'll come back with five more coins.
I don't think I'd understand a hint lower than medium-grade.
Okay, then.
I really want to find it.
Gosh, where are the blue envelopes?
Yes, Se Chan.
You're spotting them so well today.
Really? This is so annoying.
A dud.
"I, I..."
"I, I, H, H?"
What could this be?
"H, H..."
It's a Korean "eh" sound.
What could "I, I, eh, eh" be?
"I, I, H, H."
Shoot.
I don't think I can show this. It's a topless Seok Jin.
- What is this? Bungeoppang and... - Bungeoppang and egg bread.
"I, I, H, H?" I think there's something here.
Gosh, I have no idea.
What could this be? "I, I, H, H."
The director likes me doing this.
What was that?
Watch your step.
While messing around like this,
I...
I've gotten hurt lots of times while messing around.
It's right here.
What is this?
Gosh, what is this?
Monkey, monkey, sheep, sheep?
What could this be?
Monkey, monkey...
Seok Sam was born in the Year of the Sheep.
Am I wrong? Hang on.
He was born in the Year of the Horse.
Wait, what could this mean?
What on earth is this?
Which location could this hint be about?
Oh, it's here.
Gosh, this is awesome.
"Cha Tae Hyun, Ju Ji Hoon, Jang Do Yeon?"
Parking lot?
Could it be the parking lot?
Parking lot.
These three people don't have very much in common,
so I thought it could mean parking lot.
This must be a location hint.
Anyway, I'll try going to the parking lot.
Here is the parking lot.
I think it's the parking lot.
Is there something among the cars?
I've gotten as far as the parking lot,
but the bungeoppang...
and egg bread?
Zero-zero.
Wait, is it 9900?
Isn't it?
The plate numbers are... Wait a minute.
"Jin," "Nose,"
"Run."
The plate numbers are... Wait a minute.
"Jin," "Nose,"
"Run."
There's "61 Jin," "5454..."
"Big Nose?"
Wait, is it one of these?
What could this be?
Ja, chuk, in, myo, jin, sa, oh, mi,
sin...
Oh, eight.
That's 8, and the monkey is 9.
Then, it's 9988.
This is 9988.
Here's 9988.
I think it's the parking lot.
Jin, sa, oh, mi. That's 8, and the monkey is 9.
Then, it's 9988.
This is 9988.
Here's 9988.
It won't open.
It has to be 9988.
I think 9988 is right.
I know that's the van, but I don't know how to open it.
How do I figure this out?
- What do you have? Here's mine. - Let's see it.
Check this out.
- Six Os? - Yes.
- I see. - What do they mean?
What's this?
This is pi.
No, it's a K.
- What? Isn't it pi? - No, it's a K.
Oh, it's a K.
- I thought it was pi. - Right.
- Do you know that it's 3.14? - Seriously.
- Did you know that? - Guys like him think they're smart.
- I was just asking you a question. - I hate it.
- Of course I know that. - What equals 3.14?
- Pi. - What is pi?
The number.
- What? - The number.
What exactly is pi?
That thing you multiply. Pi is 3.14.
- Multiply what? - It's always guys like him.
Guys like him always act like know-it-alls.
Tell me what pi is.
It's that number.
- What's the number? - The number 3.14.
- What is it exactly? - What do you mean?
It's the ratio of something.
What, like the share?
Like the share?
Share? Are you kidding me?
There's no knowledge in that head of yours.
Hurry up with this.
Okay, here we go.
I'm an empty head, so tell me what this means.
What you have is a K, right?
- Yes, a K. - A K.
What could this mean?
Seriously. How do I unlock the car?
Jong Kook's out.
Jong Kook's out?
What did I just hear?
Things were going great.
How was he eliminated?
Jong Kook's been eliminated?
I was aware that this could happen.
Kim Jong Kook has been eliminated.
- Jong Kook's out? - Jong Kook's out?
No way.
I should've visited the Hint Room.
I had enough coins to spare.
Someone ripped off Jong Kook's name tag.
- How? - I don't know.
Someone else must be out here.
- What do you have? - Are you going to take mine?
Guys!
How was he eliminated?
What's happening today? What's going on?
- Ji Hyo. - Seok Jin.
- Yes? - What...
- What's with you? - What do you mean?
Did you stage this whole thing?
I didn't.
- Where's the R money? - Is it over there?
- What is it? - What's going on?
- What's the matter with you? - What's happening?
Stop it. I'll give up my hint.
I'll really give up my hint.
- Darn. - Sorry.
I'll really give up my hint. Darn.
- I'm sorry. - Seriously?
- Please stay quiet. - What the...
What's going on? What's your mission?
Sorry.
I'll look for more hints.
- Good work. - I'll give you some money.
Do you have money? Okay.
Hurry up and find more hints.
Then give them to me.
Thank you. Hey, Haha.
- That was great. - You were awesome just now.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
Is there something else for me?
There is, right?
- Today, - Yes?
since we're celebrating your 60th birthday,
- you'll get a special advantage. - That's what I'm talking about.
- You can choose one person... - Right.
to be your ally.
The Big Nose Coins owned by that person...
will be yours instead.
If you win today's race,
that ally will also be exempt from the penalty.
I see.
I get to choose an ally.
Jong Kook has the most coins at the moment.
However, there's someone I have a past with.
Hey, Speed.
- Today, you're... - Hey, Seok Jin.
Today,
I get to choose one person to team up with me.
What?
I chose you over Jong Kook.
What do you say we shake things up today?
Power, is today the day?
It is!
Let's do this!
You're officially my right-hand man now.
I swear my allegiance to you!
Power!
Speed!
- Cross. - Cross.
It took me 16 years to get here.
Everyone.
This isn't a glory that has been...
developing overnight.
This isn't a story that has been developing overnight.
Power and Speed.
We've finally joined forces.
It took us 16 years.
Speed and Power.
At the beginning of Running Man, we asked for a chance...
to eliminate everyone else.
No one took us seriously.
Hyo Jin,
Bo Pil, and Hyung In.
Sixteen years later, on his 60th birthday,
we're finally getting our chance.
The duo has finally come together.
Power...
and Speed have come together.
Power.
Hey, Speed.
Power, cross.
Cross.
We'll defeat them all today.
One, and go.
- Where are you? - We should meet up.
I'm called Speed, but I've lost my speed.
They've been hidden away like this.
What's this? Elimination ticket?
"You may eliminate a player by removing their name tag."
"If you do, you'll win a high-grade hint."
"The ticket will expire after five minutes."
Haha, keep in mind...
you can only help Seok Jin eliminate other players.
Hey, don't make a big deal out of this.
Make it look like we randomly met.
- Read it when I'm gone. - Got it.
I can eliminate people?
Or just one person?
I'll really give up my hint.
- Darn. - Sorry.
Please stay quiet.
How was someone eliminated?
- Ji Hyo's been eliminated. - Ji Hyo's been eliminated.
Ji Hyo's been eliminated?
What's going on?
My gosh. Thankfully, no one saw us.
- Seok Jin. - Yes?
We're looking pretty sexy today.
- Darn. - Unbelievable.
We shouldn't be showing this side of us.
Speed, it sure is reassuring to have you on my team.
This is great.
Let's go over the hints.
- Egg bread and bungeoppang. - Egg bread.
- And what else? - I, I, H, and H.
Since you took Ji Hyo out,
- you'll receive a high-grade hint. - Right.
- Let's see what it is. - Yes.
Since you took Ji Hyo out,
- you'll receive a high-grade hint. - Right.
It has to be this 9988.
I know that's the van, but I can't get the door open.
Since you took Ji Hyo out,
- you'll receive a high-grade hint. - Right. High-grade hint.
- "Twerking somewhere." - "Twerking somewhere."
Where do we need twerk?
Twerking somewhere?
What's the most famous spot in this area?
Where do we need twerk?
I, I, H, and H.
- What? - I, I, H, and H.
- I, I, H, and H. - Hold on.
Genius,
give me everything that comes to mind...
when you think of I, I, H, and H.
This is for a mission on Running Man.
I, I, H, and H.
How you identify yourself and your current path...
Seok Jin, wait. What if H and H stands for...
- Haha? - Haha?
Maybe you have to twerk in front of me.
Should I stand in front of you?
- I'll give it a try. - "I" means "me."
I should twerk in front of you.
You're quite good at twerking.
- Twerk. - Do I get something for this?
Twerk.
- Twerk. Good. - Good.
Now, hand it over.
Sorry, Jong Kook.
I couldn't help it. Sorry, Jong Kook.
I couldn't help it. My hand acted on its own.
Just sit.
What's this?
"The ticket will expire after five minutes."
- But... - We need to be aware...
- of that as well. - Right. When did...
Jong Kook, I'm sorry!
Did anyone else get eliminated?
- They'll soon join us. - I hope they get here soon.
Stay in the sun like that.
That's your punishment.
Ji Hyo's out?
Se Chan, we're just chess pieces on a rigged board.
Exactly. We didn't know about this.
How can anyone be eliminated?
Why were they eliminated?
It doesn't make sense.
Why and how were they eliminated?
Hey.
What's this?
Haha. No, not Haha.
Jae Seok, if you know anything, do tell.
Share what you know.
- Hold on, Seok Jin. - Yes?
- What are we supposed to do? - I've had nothing...
- but duds. - Were all of them duds?
- Have you found any hints? - I haven't.
What else did you find?
Share what you know.
- What... - Okay, just one.
Show me what you found, and I'll do the same.
It's only for extra coins.
Let me see.
- Here. It's for extra coins. - Let me see that.
Show me the rest.
Let me read the whole thing.
- It's just for extra coins. - There's more to it.
What else is there? It's just for extra coins.
- Let me confirm that. - Here. Big Nose Coins.
I just get one Big Nose Coin.
This gets me one Big Nose Coin.
What? Hey.
- Hey. - What's going on?
What's going on?
Hey, you. What did you get?
He's acting strange and suspicious.
- What's going on? - He was trying to take my name tag.
- What is this? - Hey, get over here.
- You didn't rip it off, right? - What's this?
- Oh, sheep. - Monkey, monkey, sheep, sheep.
- What is this? - Darn it.
Monkey, monkey, sheep, sheep?
Gosh, he tried to take my name tag.
- My goodness. - Darn it.
Gosh, I tried to take his too, but I failed.
I have to do it within five minutes.
Gosh, Haha is here now too.
Because Haha is here as well...
Shoot. That's a shame.
Se Chan, even if we get a hint, we won't know what it means.
What?
Hey, there's a hint here.
- My gosh. - You're lying, aren't you?
- What? Where did you find it? - It was right here.
- What? K... Se Chan. - "T..."
- "T," "R," "U?" - This.
Why does it have to be in English?
Let's put these together. T, R, U...
T, R, U?
T, U, R, K?
It's a topless Seok Jin.
I don't think I can show this.
Come here.
What is this?
- Let me see. - But we can't speak English.
Let's try it.
Root?
- The 3.14? - Oh, the 3.14 is right.
Root and pi.
Root.
Root?
- We must be wrong. - Isn't this root?
They're laughing at us.
- Isn't this root? - Se Chan.
- Root and pi. - What, root and pi? Hang on.
- This... - Hey.
This really is pi.
- Wait. - Grab everything.
- I'm sure it's pi. - Okay, grab everything.
- Hey, tell me if you get a hint! - This is hard.
- Wait, but... - They're here.
They're here.
- Hey, did you find anything? - What?
- Jae Seok. - Jae Seok!
What did you find?
We found a hint, but we can't figure it out with our brains.
- We found it. - Let me see.
Oh, what's this?
- With those... What is this? - Wait.
Jae Seok. "R, U, T." Root.
This isn't root, is it?
Root is R-O-O-T.
- It's R-O-O-T? - I see.
- I knew it. - Yes, I knew it.
What is this?
Tru... What about this?
Was there something like that?
Truck?
Truck! Hey.
Ye Eun, you're out.
Why am I out?
- Go to the jail. - What is this?
- What is this truck, then? - T-R-U...
What is this truck?
Se Chan, that doesn't matter right now! I've been eliminated!
- That doesn't matter right now! - You can go.
- I've been eliminated! - Go! I survived.
- This punk... - What's up with this guy?
What's up with you two?
- No. - No.
- Hey, you got a hint, didn't you? - I got a hint.
- Those two... - Ye Eun.
- It was "truck." - Just go now. Sorry.
What is this, seriously?
- Ji Ye Eun has been eliminated. - I was totally blindsided.
"Twerk in?"
Do I have to twerk in front of that car?
This is 9988. It has to be 9988.
"Twerking somewhere."
Is there another one? Really?
- Gosh, it was here? - Hey.
It's better to get two low-grade hints, right?
- No, go with the high-grade hint. - I don't have ten coins for that.
- These R coins... - You don't have ten coins?
I have eight coins.
- Eight coins. - Then, five and three...
- Should I go and get two? - Let's just get everything we can.
A medium-grade and a low-grade.
- Those two? Okay. - Let's get those hints.
- Medium and low. - Let's spend it all.
- Spend everything. Okay. - With 5 and 3,
I'll take a low-grade and medium-grade.
- Seok Jin, I'm so nervous. - Me too.
- We got this chance after 16 years. - After 16 years.
- Power. - Speed.
We finally got this chance after 16 years.
- This one is... The low-grade? - This is the low-grade hint. Yes.
The low-grade hint.
"Cha Tae Hyun, Ju Ji Hoon, Jang Do Yeon."
- Gosh, Cha Tae Hyun... - I'll take the medium-grade now.
- Ju Ji Hoon. - Here's the medium-grade hint.
Jang Do Yeon.
"Pigeon and G-DRAGON." My gosh. Pigeon?
- Peace? - G-DRAGON.
- Pigeon. - Is this the medium-grade hint?
- This is the medium-grade one. - Pigeon...
- Pigeon and G-DRAGON? - and G-DRAGON.
"Cha Tae Hyun, Ju Ji Hoon, Jang Do Yeon."
- G-DRAGON was born in 1988. - And twerking somewhere.
Tae Hyun was born in 1976.
What year is that?
Year of the Tiger?
Okay. It's parking lot. Let's go.
It's parking lot.
Let's go.
"Ju, Cha, Jang." Right?
- There... - Gosh, he's a genius.
- It's the parking lot. - I'm right, aren't I?
Say that I'm wrong.
- You're right. - Okay.
- The parking lot. Okay. - It's the parking lot.
- Twerking in the parking lot. - Okay.
Seriously, I'm so glad that I chose Haha.
Gosh, you're totally...
- a brainiac. You know? - G-DRAGON, pigeon.
- You figured out the parking lot. - Pigeon, G-DRAGON. P, G.
- Pigeon, G-DRAGON. - G-DRAGON.
What's Pigeon and G-DRAGON?
- Gugu? - Pigeons say "gugu."
- Also, 99. - Or 9 times 9 is 81?
- It's 99. - So, 1981. Ji Hyo was born in 1981.
- No, 9988. It's 9988. - Or 99...
- It's 9988, Seok Jin. I bet 9988... - Is it?
- is the license plate number. - The car?
Right? We have to find the car.
Number 9988?
- G-DRAGON was born in 1988. - And twerking somewhere.
- No, 9988. - Or 99...
It's 9988.
It's 9988, Seok Jin.
- The license plate number. - The car?
Right?
"I, I, H, H?"
What could this be?
Six Os. What is this?
I'm so bad at deductions.
- Where is it? - Let's see.
- Oh, it's an elimination ticket. - Okay.
- It's an elimination ticket. - What is it?
- An elimination ticket. - An elimination ticket?
- Let's eliminate someone. - Okay.
- For five minutes, you can... - Okay.
- So, I... - Jae Seok.
I should eliminate Jae Seok.
- Hey, if I see him... - Just do it in the open.
- Eliminate him in the open. - Yes, even if I do that,
he can't eliminate me without an elimination ticket.
- Hey, be honest. - What?
You eliminated Jong Kook and Ji Hyo, didn't you?
- Eliminate him and immediately... - Where is he? There he is.
Jae Seok is over there.
Keep quiet.
Hush. Quiet.
Here we go.
- I thought he was done. - He's doing that thing.
- He's doing it because of the hint. - This is a hint, right?
You think this is the I, right?
- Gosh, this is driving me crazy. - Be honest with me.
- Hey, why... - I'm right, aren't I?
What is this, you two from Antenna? Are you guys a team?
- What's this? Are you a team? - Are you a team or what?
- Why are you... - Hey.
- Hey, I'm going to fall. - Right? You're a team.
You two. Antenna.
- "You two?" - Why are you doing this thing...
What were you talking about as you were on this thing?
Why, you punk.
- What? - Hey, watch out.
- What were you talking about? - Watch out.
- Behind you. - You were talking about this...
- Why are you doing this? Stop. - Careful.
- What were you talking about here? - What is this?
- What is this? - Hey.
- What is this? - What?
What? Why are you doing this?
- You're going to rip it off, right? - What's wrong with you?
I don't know! Why are you all acting like this?
No, I came to keep an eye on what you were up to.
What are you two doing? What are you talking about?
- I mean, we're allowed to talk. - Aren't you afraid of each other?
- Wait a minute. - I just kept...
Let's just end this quickly.
- Jae Seok, look. This hint. - What?
- They fell for it. - Why?
My gosh.
- Jae Seok, this. It's this team. - Yes?
- What is it? - We can't show you.
- What is it? - Why not?
Jae Seok, it's the two of them.
- Why? What is it? - Why?
Be careful. Don't do it.
- Stay away. - Watch it.
- Hey, what are you doing? Let go. - Hang on.
- Watch out. Why are you doing this? - What?
Hey, wait. Haha...
It's these guys! Hey, it's them!
Hey...
- Got it. - What's that?
- Haha, you're out. - What?
- What's up with you guys? - Can he take name tags?
- Yes, he can. - He can take name tags?
Gosh, why am I finding hints so well today?
- Ssaebssaeb! - Yes, Jae Seok?
- I mean, we're allowed to talk. - Aren't you afraid of each other?
- Wait a minute. - I just kept...
- Let's just end this quickly. - Jae Seok, look.
- What? - They fell for it.
- Why? - What is it?
- Jae Seok, this. It's this team. - Yes?
- Why? - Why?
- What is it? - We can't show you.
Jae Seok, it's the two of them.
- Why? What is it? - Why?
- Haha, you're out. - He...
You can't stay here. Go to prison.
He ripped...
Okay, let's split up.
- Darn it. - Haha is out.
I should've pushed harder.
Gosh, Haha was eliminated.
I should've ripped it off earlier in that moment.
Gosh, this is bad. Haha is...
I never thought Haha would get eliminated.
I didn't think Se Chan would have an elimination ticket.
Se Chan, you had an elimination ticket.
- What? Yes. - You had an elimination ticket.
I never even thought of that.
Yes, thank you.
"Twerk in..."
Twerk where?
I think it's a truck, but I don't see any cars.
But this is... In the end...
In the end, only one person will be left.
You know?
Right, there isn't much time now.
So, one person will get it in the end.
But what about Ji Hyo and Jong Kook?
- Who eliminated... - Yang Se Chan is out.
- What was that? - Yang Se Chan is out.
Did Seok Jin rip off his name tag?
Did he?
- Se Chan. - Yes?
You're no match for me when it comes to strength.
- Just go. - Help me this once.
- With what? - Help me this once.
- Are you really going to do this? - Yes.
- Then I won't say no. - You don't have it anyway.
What don't I have?
I don't have an elimination ticket, but...
Jae Seok!
Okay.
- You had an elimination ticket? - I had it.
Okay. Go.
Jae Seok and I remain.
Seok Jin must be overjoyed.
Okay.
"Open..." Do the twerking dance and say,
"Open sesame." That's right.
I'll go to the parking lot.
"Open..." Do the twerking dance and say, "Open sesame."
That's right. I'll go to the parking lot.
Do the twerking dance and say, "Open sesame."
This is...
Pigeon corresponds with 99.
G-DRAGON was born in 1988.
So, the number is 9988.
Let's find that license plate. "Open sesame." Twerking dance.
Then I'll be done. Okay.
Seok Jin doesn't have an elimination ticket now, right?
Maybe he does.
Where is it?
I retraced my steps, but this isn't the place.
For goodness' sake. I don't know.
- You don't know? Se Chan is out. - I don't know.
- What? - Se Chan is out.
That's right. I eliminated him.
You have something, right?
- Right? - I can eliminate you,
- Of course. - but I'll let you go.
What?
How many elimination tickets did you have?
Several.
I had them by default.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Then why are you running away?
- What? - Then why are you running away?
- Why am I running away? - Yes.
Let's find the hints.
- Why are you running away? - Let's find the hints.
There aren't any more hints.
Yes, there are.
- All right. - Do you want to have a showdown?
- What choice do we have? - Why do you say that?
No one has an elimination ticket.
I have it.
- If we want to wrap this up... - I figured out the hint.
I figured out the hint, so I'm on my way to the finale.
I know a lot too.
I know a lot. That's why I'm headed somewhere.
- So hurry up and... - So it's meaningless to fight.
Hurry up and tell me.
- It's meaningless. - Be careful.
- Tell me. - I just need to go and do it.
So tell me.
- I'll rip off your name tag! - Go ahead.
I'll rip off your name tag!
Listen. I figured out the hint.
- I'm so near! - Come on.
Speed! Power!
Cross!
I think 9988 is a license plate number.
You're good. Twerk.
Do the twerking dance and say, "Open sesame." That's right.
- I'm so near! - Come on.
- Seriously. - I'm so near!
All right. I'll twerk!
Open... Open sesame!
You aren't twerking right.
I've never twerked before.
Here it is.
An elimination ticket.
It's nearby! I'll tell you!
- Do you know the location? - In front of a car.
Do the twerking dance and say, "Open sesame!"
- Did you know that? - Yes, I did. I was on my way.
You aren't twerking right.
I've never twerked before.
- I'm so annoyed. - Open!
- Open! - It opened.
Hold on.
This is it.
My treasure.
Penalty exemption card!
I was on my way here to do it.
- I was so close. - The race has ended.
- We'll go back to the party. - Let's go.
In any case,
I solved all the mysteries today before anyone else.
I applaud you.
Where did he get it?
Jae Seok had an elimination ticket.
I'll give you the result of the race,
- Find the Stolen Big Nose Coins. - Okay.
The final winner is...
- Yu Jae Seok! - Yes!
- It's too bad. - You were so close.
- Seriously. - I'm jealous of him.
The license plate number of the car you had to find...
- was 01NOSE 9988. - The 2nd part was 9988.
- "Nose." - There is a meaning behind it.
"Running Man's 1st Big Nose,"
"live energetically until the age of 99."
Do you want him to live only up to the age of 99?
- Once you turn 100... - Jae Seok.
- "Energetically." - Live energetically until then.
From the age of 100...
- You'll be bedridden? - He'll be bedridden.
- Hey. Take that back. - I mean...
That's what it sounds like.
Thus, Jae Seok...
opened the trunk...
- I found them. - and took the Big Nose Coins.
- Currently, - How much are they worth?
- they're worth... - One thousand dollars.
one thousand dollars...
- One thousand dollars in cash. - In cash?
Thus, he acquired 1,000 dollars and the penalty exemption card.
- No way. - We asked Jae Seok...
what he'd like to do with the prize.
"Would you use it for yourself..."
- "or Seok Jin, the birthday man?" - Jae Seok, seriously.
He won't take everything. He's Yu Jae Seok.
- Will you use the prize money... - Okay.
for yourself or...
on Jee Seok Jin, who welcomed his 60th birthday?
Gosh, this is...
For goodness' sake.
If I take it,
it'll be entertaining.
It can't be helped.
I'm sure anyone would do the same.
- I'm tearing up already. - Hey, the sunset...
is making the atmosphere insane. I'm tearing up.
You should just use it.
Jae Seok said that he wouldn't hesitate...
to use it for Seok Jin.
It would've been funny if he had kept it.
He had to think for a second.
He was torn between laughter and loyalty.
I'll use it for Seok Jin, of course.
I can't keep 1,000 dollars for myself.
Today is Seok Jin's day,
so I won't hesitate to use it for Seok Jin.
If it hadn't been his birthday, I would've used it.
- That's right. - That's right.
- So I'll get 1,000 dollars. - As your 60th birthday present,
you can use 1,000 dollars.
- My goodness. - Okay.
But we were so moved by Jae Seok's loyalty...
that we prepared a mission everyone has to succeed in.
Everyone has to participate in this mission.
- If you succeed in it, - Okay.
we'll double 1,000 dollars.
We'll double 1,000 dollars.
- Two thousand dollars? - So...
Seok Jin's 60th birthday present will be 2,000 dollars.
- We have to do it. - However,
- it'll be zero dollars if you fail. - We have to do it.
- If all of us work together... - Zero dollars?
- Zero dollars if we fail? - Zero dollars if you fail.
- Let's bet 1,000 dollars. - Let's do it.
- Go. - Let's bet 1,000 dollars.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- We should do it together. - You like something like this.
- It'll be fun. - Let's go.
- All-member mission is a must. - Seok Jin.
- I wouldn't use it alone. - We'll succeed in it.
- Of course. - I'll pay for a meal...
at an eel restaurant.
We'll succeed in it.
We've never failed a group mission.
Seriously. We've never failed.
- What's that? - We won't lose.
It'll be hard.
What's this?
- Scissors. - I see a jegi!
- I guess it's a shoe-throwing. - My bowels...
aren't in their best condition.
The last group mission with Seok Jin,
the man who welcomed his 60th birthday, is...
Challenge 61 Seconds.
- Sixty-one seconds? - Sixty-one seconds?
- Do we only get 61 seconds? - It has to do with the age of 61.
- Don't be like that. - Usually, it's 99 seconds.
Seok Jin has done well in these missions...
- in the past Running Man episodes. - Is it a collection?
- A collection of seven missions. - Really?
Level One is shoe-throwing.
You must put a shoe inside the success square.
Level Two involves...
jump roping five times on a balance ball.
Yes! Success!
- Well done. - How did he do that?
Level Three involves...
the signature game of the unlucky member, Seok Jin.
It's the Pirate Roulette Game.
- You pass if the pirate pops out. - No way.
Level Four is Alkkagi.
Knock out one piece.
Level Five is mental arithmetic.
It's 897.
Level 6 involves flipping over 3 tiles in a row.
Okay!
The last one is jegichagi.
Kick it six times using both feet.
Five!
Each member has to take a game.
It's like "Dad's Challenge."
Talk among yourselves and take a mission you're confident in.
- Now, do we get 61 tries? - I think I should do that.
You get ten tries.
- Ten? - Yes.
Let's say your feet get caught...
while jump roping.
Then go back to jump roping five times.
- Right. - Can you jump rope five times?
We don't need to start from Level One.
See if you can do it five times.
Keep going until you succeed in it.
You need to put it inside the success square.
Go!
- I did it. - It needs to hit this part.
Yes.
If you pass the slippers quickly...
I'll do this. Keep passing the slippers.
You need to do the mental arithmetic.
I'll take this mission.
Will you take this mission?
- Ji Hyo, you're good. - I did it.
- Take that mission. You did it. - All set.
Ji Hyo, how are you so good at it?
- Take the Pirate Roulette Game. - I'll stick in the knives.
I'll stick the knives in expertly.
I'll move my hands quickly and stick in all of them.
Se Chan, do you want to take alkkagi?
Alkkagi is hard.
- All set. - How is he so good at it?
The mental arithmetic comes between these two missions.
- Seok Jin is good at it. - Do the mental arithmetic.
- Shall I do it? Okay. - Yes.
Flip over three tiles...
in a row.
- In a row? My goodness. - It'll be hard.
In a row?
- One. - One.
- Two. - That's insane.
- Gosh, the last shot... - Does he need to start over?
Let's say he flips over 2 tiles and fails to flip over the 3rd one.
- Then he needs to start over. - Jae Seok, then you start over.
- Three tiles in a row. - You need to start over.
It'll be hard to kick a jegi with both feet.
- I did it just now. Yes. - Really?
It's easy.
- Okay. - I can kick it six times.
See if you can do it five times.
I just need to relax.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
We have 10 tries, so let's finish it on our 1st try.
Listen. We'll finish it in 59 seconds.
- It'll be dramatic. - Don't worry.
- Let's go. - Seriously.
I'm sweating already.
- Let's do a cheer. - Let's gather around.
Let's do a cheer.
- Let's gather around. Haha, come. - Let's do a cheer.
We haven't had a group mission in a while.
- Okay. We'll succeed in it. - It'll be a success.
We are...
- Seven people! - I was going to say, "One."
I didn't know.
You guys have no teamwork.
All right. We are...
- One! - One!
Say, "Seok Jin, Seok Jin!"
- We'll say, "Power!" - Why? It's embarrassing.
- Seok Jin, Seok Jin! - Seok Jin!
- Let's go! - Power!
- Everyone said a different thing. - Everyone said a different thing.
- We have the worst teamwork. - We do different things.
- We aren't in sync. - We're like that.
- We aren't in sync. - We aren't in sync.
- Are you ready? - Yes!
- I love you, Seok Jin! - Okay.
We're one!
- We need to do it in ten tries. - I'll begin.
Good luck!
- Here we go! - Here we go!
Here comes the first try. Set...
Go. It's okay. Go.
- Go. - This is bad.
- He'll use up ten seconds. - Go.
- Go. What's going on? - For goodness' sake.
Don't get nervous.
Do it with confidence, you punk!
- Don't get nervous. - I did better earlier.
I did better earlier.
- Just do it. Throw it. - For goodness' sake.
- I can't believe him! - Use your own shoe!
- What's wrong with you? - I did better earlier.
How many seconds have passed?
- I can't believe him! - Use your own shoe!
- What's wrong with him? - What is he doing?
Gosh, I can't believe that jerk.
Twenty seconds have passed.
- He used up 20 seconds! - Okay!
- Okay! - He did it. Go.
Okay. Go.
- One, two, three, four... - One, two, three, four...
My goodness. Go up there.
- Go up there. - Slowly.
- Here I go. - Slowly.
- Good luck. - Stay calm.
- One, two, three, four... - Ji Hyo, stay calm.
- For goodness' sake. - It's okay. Stay calm.
- I'll stay calm. - We'll never succeed in it.
- Ji Hyo. - Her energy is drained.
- One, two, three... - One, two, three...
- Oh, no. - Ji Hyo.
- What's wrong with me? - Ji Hyo, stay calm.
Your core keeps moving backward!
- That's right. Go forward. - Go forward.
- Two, three, four, five. - Two, three, four, five. All done.
- All right. - Ye Eun.
- We're ruined. - Haha!
What was that?
- Hey, Ji Hyo. - The first try failed.
Go for the further square!
You got scared and went for the closer one.
Aim for the further one.
- All by yourself... - You need to succeed in it quickly.
Don't get nervous, you punk!
- Why do you become so timid? - Se Chan should do it.
Is he out after just one try?
- Give him one more chance. - Take Alkkagi.
- Just one more chance. - Don't get intimidated.
- He's a scaredy-cat. - We wasted one try.
Brother Thug and Brother Antenna keep giving me a hard time.
They're older than you, so listen to them.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
You little...
Guys, we...
Hey, we're...
- One! - One!
- Only Ye Eun answered. - Stop doing that.
- We aren't in sync. - We're seven people.
Okay. Go.
- Here I go! - Okay.
Set...
That's it! Gosh.
It's okay. Don't get intimidated.
- Do it quickly. - Don't get intimidated.
- Gosh. Do it quickly. - Don't get intimidated.
- Keep throwing. - You got this.
- I did it! - He did it.
I did it. I did well.
One, two, three, four, five.
- Okay. - That's good.
- Oh, no. - Do it quickly.
- Do it quickly. You got this. - Slowly.
- Okay. - You did it.
- You did it. - We'll succeed in it.
- Twenty seconds have passed. - Twenty seconds have passed.
- He did it. - Let's go!
Hurry up and give me the question.
- What's 12 multiplied 14? - What's 12 multiplied by 14?
What's 12 multiplied by 14?
If I multiply 12 by 14... It's 120 and...
Four times one is four. Four times two is eight.
- It's 168. - Correct.
- Okay. - Okay.
It's 168.
Okay.
- Nice! - One. Mind the time.
- Two. - Nice!
- The last one! - Nice.
The last one!
Nice.
- Nice. - Nice.
- No. Start over. - Start over?
- No. - Start over.
- Start over. - Start over?
- Slowly. - One.
No.
- It's okay. - Don't get worked up.
Come on.
- He did it. - He did it.
- He did it. Prepare the jegi. - The last one.
- The last one. - The last one.
One.
- One. - For goodness' sake.
If you had done it in one go, we would've succeeded in it.
Things were perfect up to Seok Jin.
- I'm sorry. - Seriously.
Who kicked the jegi? I'm so upset.
- He should be ashamed. - This time...
Hey, you punk.
We ran out of time after I kicked it once.
- I'm sorry. - Focus, okay?
- I'm sorry. - The tiles were the problem.
Can you give me a meal? I can do better after a meal.
I'm hungry too.
- Let's see. - Let's go.
- Here we go. - It's the third try.
- Here we go. - Set...
It's the third try. We need to succeed in it.
It's okay.
- Stay calm. - Good.
Don't get intimidated. Throw it far.
- I did it. - There you go.
Everyone is...
One, two, three, four...
- It's okay. Start over. - It's okay.
- Go forward. - Go slow. Go forward.
One, two, three, four, five.
- She did it. - All done.
- Slowly. - Slowly.
- Ye Eun. Slowly. - Slowly.
- She did it. - I did it.
- Nice. - I did it too. Go.
Well done.
- Hurry up and give it to him. - Hurry up.
What's 13 multiplied by 18?
Since it's 13, it's 260...
It's 36, so... The answer is 234.
- Correct. - Okay.
- Go. - Okay.
- Good. - For goodness' sake.
- Hey. - Slowly.
One.
- Slowly. - Come on.
Slowly. Don't get worked up.
- One. - Okay.
- Two. - It's okay.
Jong Kook is good.
- Good. - One.
Good.
Who flipped over the tiles?
There isn't much time.
Who flipped over the tiles? He must be bad at it...
- since he gets flipped off often. - The mental arithmetic...
Gosh, we were so close.
It isn't easy to flip over...
- three tiles. - It isn't easy.
- It requires strength. - But you did it earlier.
I can't do it.
- It requires strength. - You can do it.
You got this.
I keep getting multiplication problems.
They're hard. I can't even do it...
- manually. - I'm really good at it, right?
You're really good at it. I can't even do it manually.
Seok Jin, are you a mathematician?
- You're really good at it. - Let me tell you how I did it.
It was 18, right? I multiplied it by 20.
I multiplied it by 20 and then subtracted 26.
How did you do that?
- Twenty-four. - Business majors learn...
- a lot of math. - I'm so bad at math.
- This is the fourth try. - Seriously.
- Let's go. Let's say it together. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's do this.
- Guys, I wouldn't use... - We can do it.
the doubled prize by myself.
- Of course not. We know that. - I'll use it for all of us.
Let's double Seok Jin's prize money.
- We'll have a get-together. - Let's double it.
- In 1, 2... - We are...
- Seven! - One!
In 1, 2, 3...
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- We aren't in sync. - We aren't in sync.
It isn't easy.
- Let's go! - I'm nervous.
Blow the whistle.
- Here I go! - Let's go.
This is the fourth try. Set...
It's only the fourth try. We can do it.
That's it!
- Okay. - He did it. That's it.
There you go. One, two...
There you go. One, two, three, four, five.
- Nice. - She did it.
- We'll succeed in it this time. - I did it.
- We got this. - What?
- We got this. - Why isn't it popping out?
Will Ye Eun use up many seconds this time?
Why isn't it popping out?
- Why isn't it popping out? - Ye Eun, you did well earlier.
- I did well earlier. - Hey, Ye Eun.
Okay.
- I did it. - Okay.
What's 25 multiplied by 16?
- What's 25 multiplied by 16? - It's a hard one.
- What's 25 multiplied by 20? - It's a hard one.
It's 500, so... Was it 16?
If it's 16...
- It's 436. - Incorrect.
- It's 426. - Incorrect.
The last number should be zero.
Seok Jin, since 6 times 5 is 30, the last number should be 0.
- It's 436. - Incorrect.
The question was 25 multiplied by...
- Sixteen. - Sixteen?
So 25 multiplied by 20 is 500.
If it's 16, the number is 4.
Four times one is four. Four times six is twenty-four.
Sixty-four.
Count it as a correct answer if he's in the ballpark.
It's 446.
Is it 434?
- It's 430. - It's Seok Jin's money anyway.
- It's okay. - Four hundred... What's the answer?
- Four hundred. - It's hard.
- Four hundred? - It's hard.
Since 6 times 5 is 30, the last number is 0.
- Are you mocking me? - No.
- Maybe you should do this mission. - No.
- Do you want to do this mission? - I can't.
Seok Jin is the only one who can do mental arithmetic.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Let's go! - We're getting better.
- This is... - Haha and Ji Hyo are doing well.
- Earlier... - We can do it.
Haha, let's get that applause.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
No one will complain if you do badly this time.
- That's right. - Why is it so nerve-racking?
We'll begin when Haha says,
- "Here I go." - I'm so nervous.
At this point, it's natural to be nervous.
- I'm nervous. - I'm nervous.
- The calculations... - I'm nervous.
- Let's go! - Let's do this!
- Let's go! - We are...
- One! - One!
Okay. Go.
This is the fifth try.
- Here I go! - Set...
Set...
- Yes! - Good!
- You're doing well. - I'm done.
- Go. - Come out!
- Come out! - Come out!
- Come out. - Please.
- Please. - Come out.
- It's not coming out. - Come out.
- Come out! - Come out!
- Come out! - Ye Eun is unlucky!
- Why is it not coming out? - Come out!
- Why isn't it coming out? - Why is it...
It's out.
- Okay. - Nice.
Twenty-four multiplied by fifteen.
- Twenty-four. Two hundred forty... - Forty.
Five times two is ten, five times four is twenty.
Twelve. Two hundred forty?
- Twenty-four multiplied by fifteen. - Three hundred sixty!
Correct!
- Nice. - It's okay.
How many seconds are left? Tell us quickly. How many?
He did it.
- Nice. - We can do it.
We can do it.
Ttakji isn't easy.
Ttkakji isn't easy, but you can do it!
- Okay! - Let's do it!
The last one!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Let's go!
- How many are we? - One!
Okay. Go.
- The last one! - You got it!
- Jong Kook. - One, two,
three, four, five,
six!
We did it!
We did it, right? We did it!
We did it.
- How many seconds did we take? - How many seconds?
- How many seconds was that? - How many seconds was that?
How many seconds was that?
Exactly 61 seconds.
- Sixty-one seconds. - Exactly?
- How many seconds? - Amazing.
Goodness.
- Jong Kook. - One, two, three,
four, five,
six!
We succeeded in one go.
Well done.
- It's crazy. - It ended at 61 seconds?
- This... - You'd think it was planned.
- Goodness. - Unbelievable.
We would have failed if any one of us made a mistake.
Right. If even one person...
- had been just one second late... - We did well today.
We are one!
- Seriously. - We get 2,000 dollars.
Congratulations. You earned double the amount...
- I'm so happy. - for Seok Jin's 60th birthday gift,
which is 2,000 dollars.
- I'll... - You earned the money.
- Okay! - You'd be happy.
If you tell us what gift you'd like, up to a value of 2,000 dollars,
we'll purchase it and present it to you...
- at the next recording. - Can we all...
go and eat something together?
- Shall we use it like that? - Yes.
- You can think about it. - Okay.
- Nice. - Also,
everyone, except for the person who found the coins,
- was supposed to get a penalty. - Yes.
- But since this is a good day, - How many?
- Right. - let's choose...
two penalty receivers...
by randomly picking balls with your names.
Two penalty receivers? That's really good.
Jae Seok earned the exemption card,
- Yes. - so he's exempted.
The rest...
- Seok Jin can pick the balls. - You can pick both of them.
- I'll pick them. - Okay.
- As for today's penalty... - Yes.
There are beautiful lights outside.
You will go there...
and ask people to film a congratulatory video for Seok Jin.
- That's bothersome. - Goodness.
- It's a bit... - It would be funny...
if Seok Jin gets picked.
- If he gets picked... - Seok Jin will...
If he gets picked, he has to ask people to congratulate him.
- That's right. - "Some words for me."
- Pick them. - I surely wouldn't...
- pick my name. - Draw the balls.
The first penalty receiver...
- I'm picking the penalty receiver. - Yes.
- I don't know. - Okay.
- Go! - Please.
The penalty receiver.
Jee Seok Jin!
- Is this true? - No way.
- This is funny. - Is this true?
- Does this make sense? - This is really interesting.
- How does this happen? - How...
This is really interesting.
- It's funny. - One more person.
- People would think I planned this. - If he draws my name,
- it would be crazy. - Power and Speed.
- Speed. - Today...
Draw Haha's name.
One more person.
- Please. - People would think we staged it.
- Please. - It's not me today.
It wouldn't be funny if I get picked. It would seem staged.
- Right. - Please.
Please show us.
Ye Eun.
Ji Ye Eun.
Jee and Ji!
- This... - "Milkshake!"
Drink the milkshake
Things aren't so bad today.
The rest of the members can get off work.
Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
- Thank you. - This is so funny.
- It's so beautiful. - Look at this.
Goodness.
- It's so nice. - It's awesome.
You should quickly get a boyfriend...
- I know, right? - and come here with him.
It would be great to come here as a couple.
Right. It's perfect.
- There are many couples here. - There are many of them.
It's a real photo spot.
Quickly get a boyfriend...
- and come here. - I should. A boyfriend...
Hi.
This is really...
- I see a couple there. - Here...
I think you'll get really pretty pictures here.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Can we interview you?
Can we interview you? You're holding hands.
- A couple. - You're lovers, right?
- Yes. - How long have you been dating?
- Around... - A bit more than 200 days.
- Two hundred days. - Two hundred days.
I hope you celebrate your first anniversary well.
- You know... - I... You can tell them.
It's Seok Jin's birthday. It's his 60th birthday.
Which birthday do you think it is?
- Sixtieth birthday. - You said it.
It's his 60th birthday.
It's a rare thing in variety shows.
- Yes. - Could you say a few words?
Could you say a few words to congratulate him?
You're the same age as my father,
so I knew already.
What's your father's name?
Lim Won Mook.
Won Mook. We're friends.
- Friends. - Congratulations!
- Happy 60th birthday! - Thank you.
My father...
and actor Jee Seok Jin...
Actor!
Happy 60th birthday!
Thank you!
- Thank you. - I wish you the best!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
There are foreigners there. Hi!
Hi.
Hi. Where are you from?
Germany!
- Germany! - Germany!
- Germany. - Germany.
- Auf Wiedersehen. - Yes!
Auf Wiedersehen.
- Hi. - Hi.
- I used to speak German. - Can you...
speak Korean?
- A little. - A little.
- A little? - Yes.
Do you know Running Man?
Yes.
Do you know me?
He's turning 60 tomorrow.
It's his 60th birthday.
- Yes. - Okay.
- A congratulatory video. - Congratulatory words.
- Congratulations... - Yes.
- Okay. - Video?
- Alright. - German is fine.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Have a good day.
You too.
I guess you're finally admitting that you're 60 years old.
I wish you a happy birthday.
I wish you a long life,
and take good care of your health, especially in this cold weather.
My birthday is February 10, too, just like Seok Jin.
It's an honor to share the same birthday.
I wish you a happy birthday!
- I wish you the best! - All the best!
Happy birthday, Big Nose!
Happy birthday, Seok Jin.
Happy 60th birthday, Seok Jin.
Please continue making Running Man fun for many years to come.
- I wish you happiness. - I wish you happiness.
All the past producers...
of Running Man came.
- Should I take it like this? - Yes.
Yes!
- Be healthy! - Be healthy!
"He didn't pay for it myself."
"This was really sent by his fans." It's written here.
This is amazing.
- Thank you! - Thank you!
Thank you. Say a few words to thank them.
Thank you!
- We'll get going! - Happy birthday!
- Thank you! - Happy 60th birthday!
Thank you, everyone! Be happy!
It feels like something amazing is about to happen.
I'll really do well today.
- Is it my turn? - Asura balbalta.
All the weak people have gathered here.
- Goodness. - Yu San Seul.
- Sing us a song, Park Wan Kyu. - Park Wan Kyu.
- Because I love you - Love you
- A complete life change. - Let's end it with this.
Life is about making challenges.
You can't win unless you have the Joker card.
- Please! - Will they get triple?
We have to do it.
What are you doing? Run!
- It's a bomb. - It's a bomb!
- The golden key! - What's that?
- Forty! - This is really big.
- Look at his wig. - He was a fake.
- Half of them? - Who is that lone gambler?
He's a gambler with a belly.
- All in. - Is that ten?
If you're scared, you can just leave.