I don't want them to think that
they can bully you.
These people are monsters.
I grew up with them.
- I'm Rebecca.
- We've met already.
- When?
- Yesterday.
I can't remember.
If someone hurts you
or if your husband's family oppresses you,
just let me know.
It's the effect of his chemo.
Santiago is so far away from Manila.
I won't be at peace if they're going back
and forth to the hospital without me.
Right. Why don't they stay
with us at our place?
Use that anger to get ahead of her.
In business.
In life.
Show Sam that you're the better person.
The better wife.
The better woman.
You know the rules, Sam.
You're permitted to roam around
the common area,
but the third floor is exclusively mine.
The mother is immoral,
so it makes sense that
the children are too!
- You can insult me, but not my children!
- Well, it's the truth!
You are termites!
You destroy houses!
They are turning my house
into a wrestling arena.
Let them leave now.
That woman is my wife!
Don't make me choose
because you won't like my choice.
I am here because of my husband.
I love Paco.
But you know, Mother, I'm also surprised
by how much he loves me.
He is willing to give up all this
just for me.
George and I had a casual talk.
Nothing is ever casual with you.
If you and Sam really love each other,
then you shouldn't be bothered.
Nothing and no one can ruin your marriage.
Not even me.
PREVIOUSLY
Hon?
I've already checked on Francis
and Mother in their rooms.
They look comfortable.
Francis is already snoring.
What's wrong?
It's Mama.
It seems she's planning something.
If she makes a move,
there's nothing I can do.
Never mind.
I don't want to think about it.
It might ruin the…
Hon…
You know, you…
should relax.
Your night might be wasted.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have a better idea.
Enjoy the party.
Thank you.
Meow.
I thought you wouldn't come, but you did.
Yeah, well, there was
a slight change of plans.
Welcome. Enjoy the party.
We will.
So this is a masquerade party?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Some sort of a masquerade party.
Hey…
Meet me upstairs.
Okay?
Paco…
What are you doing?
Paco, there are a lot of people here.
Someone might see us.
Paco, no, no, no, no!
That's even better.
They will be envious
of how delicious my wife is.
- Come on.
- Paco…
What are you doing?
It's okay. She's a friend.
"Friend"? She's hitting you
with a whip. What's wrong with you?
Because she's here to teach you.
Why…?
Sam…
Hit me.
- No.
- Please, hit me!
- Come on.
- Paco, let's go home.
What's your problem?
Why are you being so rude?
- Come on.
- Now you're calling me rude?
It was who brought me to this place.
Is this your idea of fun?
Are we going home together,
or will you go home alone?
Sam, grant my request.
Sam! Sam!
- Please! Please, grant me this, Sam.
- Paco! Paco!
- Grant me my request. Please.
- Paco!
- Crawl!
- Paco! You're…
- Let me go!
- Sam!
Sam!
Sam.
No! What are you doing?!
- Let me go.
- Wow!
This is wild.
I like it.
No! Let me go!
Let me go!
You're such a pervert!
No!
Hey!
You're all disgusting!
Sam…
What was that?
Doesn't your wife know?
Sam!
Give me the key.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
- Give me the key.
- Sam!
Here you go.
I'll take you home, ma'am.
Ma'am…
Sam, wait! Sam!
Sam!
Busy.
I'm busy this whole month.
Okay.
I'll free up one weekend for you.
Goddamn it, George!
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry, love.
It's your fault! You're startled me.
Sam!
Sam, let's talk!
I said let's talk.
All right!
Okay, go ahead and explain.
Let's talk in private.
Why? Are you ashamed that people might
hear about your disgusting ways?
Not here.
Let's talk here
because I want to understand.
Go ahead and explain!
- You're disgusting!
- I said not here!
Sam.
- Let's go home.
- No.
Sam?
Paco's all the talk
at the Indulgence right now.
Oh, Paco.
Can't seem to keep his pants on
for one woman.
Indulgence?
A sex party.
Paco brought Sam,
and naturally,
Sam went berserk.
What? Why do you know this?
I got the invitation last week.
Don't worry, love.
I don't attend those kind of parties.
It's not my style.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you,
but why are you such a war freak?
Now it's my fault?
Huh? It's my fault?
I was violated, Paco.
What do you think of me?
That I'm like a prostitute
you can pass over to anyone?
Of course not!
Then why are you treating me like one?
Paco, I'm your wife.
What, am I not enough for you?
You're not happy with me? Is that it?
No, Sam.
Don't touch me!
I'm disgusted with you!
Paco, I'm not trying to be righteous.
But I saved myself for the right man!
For you!
- But you're going to do this to me?
- I…
I'm so sorry.
I don't need your apology!
What I need are answers.
I need an explanation.
I didn't know it would be
that kind of party.
The truth is, I was shocked too.
What?
I was just invited.
It was my first time there!
That Paco has been to those parties
quite a few times.
I'm lucky my husband is not like that.
Yes.
You are very lucky.
You married the right Palacios,
not the rotten one.
If Sam only knew
what kind of guy she's married…
Is Paco hiding more secrets?
Let's just say Rebecca
is not the only sick one in this family.
If anything, Paco is sicker in the mind.
What do you mean?
If Sam finds out everything that
Paco's done in the past…
she'll go crazy.
First time?
You knew all the people there.
You knew your way around, and now
you're saying it was your first time?
It's the truth. It was my first.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, stop lying.
Please, I'm giving you the chance
to explain here.
Stop lying.
I am telling you the truth, Sam!
I would never lie to you!
You just did!
And you're standing by it!
Sam…
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Sam?
Leaving.
No. You're not leaving.
You're staying here.
Sam, you're not leaving.
No!
No, you're not leaving!
If you leave, I will kill myself!
Watch me!
Don't worry.
I will go to your funeral.
Sam!
Sam…
Paco, what's with you?
Paco, what are you doing?
Have you gone crazy?!
- Stop it.
- Sorry, Sam.
Sam…
Stop that!
Sam, sorry.
Just listen to me, please.
Listen.
If you love me, you'll forgive me.
I only committed one mistake.
I didn't even mean it.
Don't use my love for you
to force me to forgive.
- Stop that.
- Sam, please. Sam!
Here, Dash.
Have some food.
Come on.
Come on and eat.
Aurora.
I can't wait to turn that thing
in my collection of taxidermy.
Have you heard?
Your son and his wife had a fight.
No.
But am I surprised?
Not at all.
And I don't care
because I know that's
where they are headed.
They hardly know each other.
Well, if you think about it,
Sam doesn't really know her husband well.
What if she finds out
what Paco did five years ago?
Shut up, Galvan,
or I will seriously turn
that stupid bird of yours
into a taxidermy.
Where are you, Dash?
My beautiful Dash.
Amando, find out where Paco is.
Paco?
Oh my God.
What happened?
Did Sam do this to you?
I hate to say this, Paco,
but if you hadn't married Sam--
Ma, please.
Don't nag me.
All I need…
All I need right now is support.
Your support.
Okay.
It's okay.
Sam…
What's wrong?
Good thing you told me this.
When it comes to love problems like that,
you should tell your best friend.
But good.
It's a good thing you broke things off
with that Gian.
But that's not enough.
Come on, let's take revenge on him.
No, I don't want to see him.
I don't want to.
Don't show Auntie Mercy your bruise.
You know her. She'll worry.
You know our mothers.
They overreact.
Come here.
Mother…
What is it?
I just miss…
I just miss Papa.
- You're disgusting!
- I said not here!
Mother?
What's happening?
Well, she dreamt of Father again.
Your father's death anniversary
is coming up.
It's been almost six years,
but it still hurts.
Especially now
when I see Mercy
and her children every day.
She reminds me every day
of all the pain and hardship
we went through
because of them.
George.
The bank is throwing us out.
They've sent an eviction notice.
This is all the Castillo's fault.
If it hadn't been for them,
our lives wouldn't be like this.
We still have a one-year
redemption period.
I will redeem our house.
And where will you get the money?
What if you go abroad?
What?
I know someone
who sends caregivers to Singapore.
But I'm a nurse.
But you're still qualified.
Do you want me to leave?
George, don't leave me and Mother.
Your sister needs to go abroad
so we won't lose our house.
This is your father's only remaining
legacy. Right, George?
But what about Abdul?
What will you get
from that poor boyfriend of yours?
You should break things off with him.
Mother, stop crying.
Stop crying.
Sam and Paco are fighting right now.
It won't take long.
The Castillos will eventually
leave this place.
You don't deserve to be pitied, Sam.
I hope Sam will like the breakfast
that I made for her.
What happened to your head?
I know you two are having issues,
but I didn't force Sam
to tell me the details.
Don't worry, I'll talk to her later.
Okay.
What's this?
Are you conniving with Mother?
Do you want her to feel sorry for you?
Hon, it's not like that.
My children,
whatever your problem is,
just fix it, please.
Mother, I don't know if we can.
Francis?
Francis, what took you so long?
What's wrong? Francis?
Francis!
- Francis!
Francis.
Wait. Hold on! We need
to bring him to the hospital now.
- I'll call the driver. Hold on.
- Francis, my son.
You ran out of morphine,
and so you worked in a call center
as a side hustle?
I don't want to depend on Sam
for all my medicines.
Francis, I have money.
Didn't I tell you that
I'd take care of all the expenses?
Don't go back to your call center job.
Staying up late is bad for you.
No, I can still manage.
No, you can't.
Francis, no.
I'll find you a better job.
An easier one.
An office job.
You need to get better.
Mother needs you.
Sam needs you.
And I need you too.
Why is that?
I need someone to guide me.
I'm not a perfect husband.
I make mistakes, and…
I just want a brother who can guide me
with my wife, okay?
Francis, Mother,
I'll just call DJ.
He'll take you home, okay?
Hon…
Mother, how is Francis?
He's already sleeping.
Okay.
Let me tell you something.
Your father once wronged me in the past.
He fooled around
and I got hurt.
I wanted to separate from him,
but I thought of you and Francis.
That's why when he said he would change,
I forgave him.
Even though it hurt?
It hurt so much.
It really did.
But I was able to overcome that.
It is difficult to be alone.
It's hard without a husband.
You saw me, right?
When your father died,
I became weak.
I was only happy
when I was with you and Francis.
It's different when you have a husband.
You have a partner in life.
You have someone to lean on
so you can create a family.
Do you still love Paco?
A lot.
Even if my mind says…
"Enough."
Can I still do it? Is it still right?
Paco basically grew up with me, Sam.
I am like his father figure.
That's why I know him so well.
He is not perfect,
but he's not a bad person.
And most importantly,
he loves you very much.
He fought for you against his mother.
That's why I hope…
you'll fight for your relationship.
You need professional help…
so we can fix our marriage.
I also want marriage counseling
so we can address your problem.
Our problem.
Dash, where are you?
Dash?
Dash!
Who killed my pet?!
Paco!
No, Gema.
Paco likes to partner beer
with grilled meat, not whisky.
Kindly change it, please.
- Okay, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Hi, love.
I have something for you.
Love, you've given me
a lot of pieces of jewelry.
I know, I know,
but when I saw this earlier,
I thought that
it would look really good
around your neck.
See?
I was correct.
Thank you.
It's just my way of showing
my appreciation
for the special things you do for me,
like this one.
So, the Castillos are still here.
Sam is clinging to Paco.
She will not leave him
even though he is hurting her.
Okay.
Let's give it
a month or two.
If they don't leave,
I will find a way to make them.
You will do that?
Well…
Paco loves Sam.
If Sam leaves, Paco will be miserable.
He won't be able to function.
That's when I'll step in
to take his place in the company.
What you do?!
Daddy hates flowers!
I'm so sorry, madam.
- I didn't know.
- No, no, no, no.
You! You, you, you are stupid.
Madam, I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry, madam! I'm so sorry!
- Stupid! Stupid!
- Madam, I'm sorry.
- You are stupid!
You are! You are stupid woman.
You are so stupid!
Hello, Mother?
How are you?
I'm okay.
My bosses are okay.
George!
Madam! Oh! Madam!
You leave Daddy alone?!
- I'm sorry, madam.
- He almost fell out of bed.
I only left him for a moment
to throw the flowers.
No! No! No, you can't!
No! No, you can't!
Love?
Love, are you okay?
I remembered
what happened to me in Singapore
because of Sam's family.
If it hadn't been for them,
Father wouldn't have died.
I wouldn't have had to work
in a different country.
Love…
Oh! Rebecca.
You startled me.
Rebecca?
Love, don't cry anymore, okay?
Let me take care of the Castillos.
All right?
But for now…
just focus on us.
All right?
Don't cry anymore.
I can't wait for us to have a baby.
Papa said he wants to have a grandchild.
He hopes it's a boy
so someone can continue
the Palacios family name.
Let's eat.
Okay.
Great job, by the way.
Thank you.
Rebecca?
Why did you call, Salvi?
You know the rules, Sam.
You're permitted
to roam around the common area,
but the third floor is exclusively mine.
I'm going to your party
even if I don't want to.
Of course, you don't need to remind me.
What's with you?
Yeah.
There's still plenty of time.
Yes.
I'll be on time, I promise.
Oh my.
I know, right?
- You might change your mind.
- Paco!
Paco!
Aurora, is your son here?
No. Why?
Your son is such a killer.
He killed Dash.
Dash?
Who is Dash?
We don't have a helper named Dash.
What's with you?
Dash! My pet peacock!
He ran over it.
My goodness, Galvan. What's with you?
That's all?
Give it to me, it's mine.
I will taxidermy your peacock.
Look at Diego.
See? My first cat. It's so cute.
It still looks alive, right?
Don't change the topic.
Your son is a jerk!
He ran over my pet!
Don't blame my son. I saw what happened.
It was Amando.
It was Amando who ran over
your pet, not Paco.
Really, Aurora?
You're going to cover for Paco again?
Just like you covered for him
after what he did to Dr. Orly?
Based on the initial medico-legal report,
Dr. Orly died from a heroin overdose.
No.
Papa was not a drug addict
and he would never commit suicide.
All you do is cover for your son!
For his sins!
Don't you ever mention that doctor again!
Why?
Why? Are you scared that
they'll find out the truth?
Is there someone in here with you?
No, I'm alone.
- What happened?
- I'm okay.
I had nothing to do with
Dr. Orly's death!
He didn't commit suicide, Paco.
- He was killed!
- Why the hell would you think that?!
Because I heard your mother
and your uncle!
Sam heard it directly from
the Palacios family
that Paco did something to Papa.
Calm down, Francis.
I won't calm down. I need to do something.
NEXT EPISODE
You killed my son!
I didn't kill him!
I love Paco.
I love him.
I also came to see you.
I want to talk to you.
The investigation is over, right?
It's about us.
It's the investigator. It's Abdul.
- What?
- He is mad at me.
I don't know why you gave me
that kind of investigator.
Replace him!
And don't accept any statement
from Basil. He's a liar.
Pa, do you already have
findings about Paco?
Did he really do it?
- Did he commit suicide?
- Shut up, George!
Aside from Mr. Palacios,
there's another person's shoe print
that we found here
at the crime scene.
Stop the investigation!
There's no need for it!
It was me!
I killed Paco.