Give me back my child.
- You have no right.
- Order.
Stop it already, Rebecca.
You're not really healed yet.
Don't use my condition against me
because I'm already healed.
We already know where the children are,
and my client will be filing
a separate petition for habeas corpus.
Do everything you have to do
to stop what
that small Attorney's camp wants to do.
Sam started going into labor earlier.
She could give birth anytime.
Do you think, Rebecca,
that Aunt Aurora will keep her promise
to give you back the children?
George, I think I'm leaking.
It's like there's something's leaking.
But, don't worry.
I saw a nearby structure
that we can go to.
So that you and the baby
don't get too stressed,
forget about Auntie Aurora for now.
‪PREVIOUSLY
Just happy thoughts, okay?
Sam… Sam…
So you don't think about the pain
and get her out of your mind,
just close your eyes.
Think of something else.
Focus on something else, okay?
Inhale, exhale.
Take a deep breath. Just relax, okay?
Relax.
Inhale, exhale.
Inhale, exhale. That's right.
Just relax, okay? Take a deep breath.
Inhale, exhale.
I've done so much wrong to you, George,
and it all started when I let
our friendship get involved
in a fight that had nothing to do with us.
Get out.
You're such a flirt.
- Get out.
- What's that?
Mother? What happened here?
It's your mother.
I caught her sleeping with my husband.
That's not true.
Your husband's body hasn't decomposed yet,
and here you are stealing my husband.
It's my husband.
He forced me. Bert threatened me.
Wait a minute.
My mother told me she wasn't at fault.
Well, maybe…
Maybe it's your husband's fault?
Father, is that true?
Mercy wanted what happened to us.
I wouldn't have wanted it, but…
I'm just a man.
My mother is not a liar,
so I'm sure if something happened here,
you abused her.
You raped her.
You're a rapist. I'll sue you.
Sis, watch your words.
My father is not a rapist.
Maybe it was really your mother
who approached my father
because, you know, she's mourning and sad.
Wait a minute, George…
George, the victim here is my mother.
Victim?
Isn't my mother the real victim here
because she and my father are married?
They are in love.
But, this old woman ruined it.
Wait a minute. Don't hurt my mother.
- That's enough.
- Then I'll hurt you instead.
George…
What are you doing here?
Do you want to make sure
that my father is dead already?
George, believe it or not…
I'm here to sympathize with you.
When my father died,
you were there to mourn with me.
Sam, this is my father's wake.
You are the ones to blame
for my father's death.
George, Uncle Bert had a heart attack.
- It's nobody's fault.
- It's because of you.
Nothing will happen
if we blame each other.
Actually, I'm here because…
I was hoping that our friendship
would be restored.
George…
whatever the misunderstanding
between our parents,
let's not let it affect us.
Should we just throw away
what we had together, George?
George…
It's a mess, Sam.
Father is gone already.
He is gone.
- George…
- Father is gone.
You're so shameless for coming here.
Do you want me to kill you too?
Really, George?
Are you going to patch things up
with this woman?
Her family is the reason
your father is gone.
- Auntie…
- Get out. Get out.
Get out.
And instead of making an effort,
I let us drift apart
because of our families.
All the men who were close
to them are dying.
Poor Paco.
He was like father back then.
He died because of a Castillo too.
Not now, George.
My husband just died.
It was your fault…
because you killed him.
- Hey.
- How dare you.
George.
Let go of me.
I'll fight with you.
Let me go.
How dare you, no lifers
to turn this place of grieving
into a circus.
Don't you have respect for time and place?
You have no manners.
My son is dead.
Someone killed him.
And then you're turning my house
into a market again.
What happened?
- Huh?
- Oh, my God.
Mother, what happened to you?
Are you hurt?
What? What happened?
Ma'am, it's because…
- George…
- Sam.
What did you do to my mother?
Come down here.
- It was just an accident.
- You don't want to come down?
If you're angry with me,
you should hurt me, not my mother.
You should fight me,
not my mother, not my family.
Talk to me, George.
Come here. What's your problem?
It's your mother. She's so meddlesome.
Instead of apologizing,
you're the angry one.
Why should I apologize?
How dare you.
- Your mother.
- Hey, ladies.
- Ma'am…
- Let me go.
It's your mother.
Tell your mother.
Sam, wait. Sam.
That's enough, Sam.
Let me go.
And when Basil blackmailed me
to kill you, I agreed out of fear.
How dare you upstage me
at my own birthday party?
You really want to go to jail, don't you?
Don't release the video.
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't.
Because George…
is going to die tonight.
Poison?
Make sure you do it properly this time.
And even though
I didn't push through with my plan,
Basil and I still experienced karma.
Why did you agree?
Samantha, answer.
Why did you agree to what Basil wanted?
Because he filmed what happened
on the cliff.
What video?
What cliff?
Mother, I accidentally pushed Paco
off the cliff.
What?
Mother, I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to.
But, in the video…
it's like I did it on purpose.
That's why Basil is using that
to blackmail me to kill George.
Is that why you poisoned Basil?
Mother, no.
It wasn't me. I didn't kill Basil.
I don't know. I don't know who.
I don't know, but…
but I think its Francis' morphine
that they used to kill Basil, Mother.
Mother…
Did you steal Francis' morphine?
You got your brother involved
in this mess you got yourself into?
You put your brother in danger.
You're the reason he went to jail.
You are the reason.
Mother, forgive me.
Forgive me. Forgive me.
I will forgive you…
when you get your brother out of jail.
I did everything I could
so Francis would be acquitted.
Even Beverly's appearance,
I used it against you.
You again.
How did you get in here?
George, I'm not here to make a scene.
Sir Galvan and I will just talk.
You will do no such thing.
Guard.
- My stomach…
- Guard.
Guard.
George, what's going on?
We have an unwanted guest, Mother.
Beverly?
Do you know her?
But, of course.
She's our media relations officer
who resigned months ago.
Now we all know why you left.
Who's the father, Beverly?
Do we know who the father
of the baby you're carrying is?
Is it someone from the company?
It's Basil.
How did you know this?
She told me and George last night.
Right, George?
She was claiming
to be Basil's former girlfriend.
Basil has a mistress?
Beverly, is this true?
Did you have an affair with my son?
Go ahead, tell them
what you said to us last night.
- It's okay.
- Sam, please.
Don't meddle here.
Beverly, speak up.
I didn't intend
to reveal the truth this way,
but it's true.
Basil and I are in a relationship.
If it happened to me,
I'd be angry.
I mean, there's no sense of peace,
no diplomacy.
If it happened to me,
I would definitely make her pay.
Her?
Do you think a woman did that to me?
George denies doing anything about that.
A piece of advice
from one pregnant woman to another…
Please protect yourself.
Protect your child.
It's difficult.
Is George barren?
Oh, my God…
Don't tell me you don't know?
Beverly. Please, please.
Promise me you won't tell George.
I won't.
Now I understand.
She can't have children.
That's why she's mad at me.
I did all that against you.
So, George, forgive me.
Is George barren?
That's not true. Beverly is just lying.
Since when did I lie?
When I said Basil and I were going
to have a baby,
I was telling the truth,
and the DNA test confirmed it.
I may be a mistress, but I'm not a liar…
unlike you.
Both of you, let's discuss this privately.
It's embarrassing for the guest.
It's more embarrassing for George
because she's lying to all of you.
Shut up.
Your daughter is barren
and she can't give Basil a child.
You, shut up.
You don't know what you're talking about.
But I do, George. I do.
And that's the thing about the truth.
Let's go.
The rumor must be true…
that when Basil found out
that George couldn't give him a child,
he wanted to leave her…
That's why you killed him.
What?
Don't fight with her anymore. Come on.
Let's go first.
Come on.
George.
George, please listen to me.
Please, let go. George, please.
Beverly, are you okay?
- Yes.
- Do you want water?
What do you want?
Wow…
that's quite a scene she made there.
It seems like George
is more than capable of killing.
What do you think, Amando?
Sam…
Sam, you're fully dilated.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Inhale, exhale.
On the count of three, push.
Raise your head
until your chin touches your chest, okay?
Ready?
One, two, three. Push.
Push harder, Sam, okay?
One more time.
One, two, three. Push.
Push harder, Sam. Push.
You can do it.
I'm tired. I can't do it, George.
What you are saying is not acceptable.
You have to keep pushing
until you deliver the baby.
If you stop, the baby might suffocate.
So, push. You can do it.
Push as hard as you can.
Okay, ready?
One, two, three. Push.
As hard as you can, Sam. Push hard as…
Push.
George, if I don't survive,
you take care of my baby.
Die if you must,
but not until you deliver my baby.
Sam, you can't die and you must not die.
You will see your baby.
You will still watch everything
that will happen in his life.
So, you have to push the hardest, okay?
One, two, three… Push.
Push. Sam.
As hard as you can, push.
Push.
At last…
you're here.
Thank you, Son. You didn't fail me.
Just like what that woman did to me
again and again.
That started when her family killed dad.
- Bert?
- Dad.
Bert.
Dad. Dad.
- Dad. Dad.
- Bert.
Dad.
Bert. Bert. Bert.
Help. Help, please.
Call an ambulance.
- Dad.
- George! George.
George.
- George, what?
- Dad.
Bert. Bert.
Call an ambulance, please.
Ma'am, letter for Bert Balay.
He's already gone.
Kindly receive this letter from the bank.
Just fill this in.
Thank you.
What's that, George?
Did father make a loan in the bank?
I have no idea, George.
If we fail to pay,
they will be forced to take our house.
George, wait a second.
Let's talk first. Don't leave me, please.
I'm begging you.
Please, George.
Wait.
George, talk to me.
George, please.
Get down from there. Talk to me.
George.
I'm sorry…
I'm sorry, madam.
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry, Mrs. Palacios,
but it would really take a miracle
for you to bear a child.
There's really nothing we can do.
George, where's my baby?
I want to embrace him. Can I have my baby?
Wait. I'm still cleaning him.
No matter when you are
a nuisance in my life.
Just when I thought
I had recovered from you
after I married Basil Palacios,
you suddenly entered my life again.
- This is Basil.
- Hi.
- He is my cousin.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
The eldest child of Uncle Galvan.
Paco told me that you had just
come back from your honeymoon.
- Yes.
- I'd love to meet your wife.
- Where is she?
- Let me go and get her.
There she is.
- I'm here.
- Wife.
George?
Since then, you didn't only
slowly destroy Basil and I,
you even tried to kill me.
GEORGE, BE CAREFUL OF YOUR HUSBAND!
HE WANTS YOU GONE!
Sam, wait.
Where did you come from?
I almost got run over earlier.
Are you okay?
Did you see who did it?
And when you failed to kill me,
you attempted to pin Basil's poisoning
on me.
Whose drawer is this, Ms. Georgina?
That's mine. Is Basil's cellphone there?
- No, but we found something else.
- What?
Morphine tablets.
Weren't these used to poison your husband?
What is that morphine tablet doing
in my drawer?
Well, that's my question to you.
What is morphine doing in your possession?
Mrs. Palacios…
why do you have morphine tablets
in your drawer?
I don't know. That's not mine.
Look, I wouldn't be that stupid
to let you see them if they were mine.
Well, then how do you explain this?
Someone might be framing me.
Maybe it was Basil's killer
who placed that in my drawer.
But when your brother had karma
because of the things you were doing,
you still picked on me.
Why would I poison my own husband?
You were suspecting
that Basil has a mistress, right?
Maybe that's the reason you killed him.
Are you having an affair with my husband?
What?
Are you flirting with Basil?
Or, maybe he's about
to find out your secret
that you can't give him a child.
That's why you poisoned him.
I'm so sorry, love.
I'm sorry I wasn't able
to give you a baby.
But, you still promised me
the rest of your life.
How I wish you fulfilled
even half of that.
You fool.
Animal.
Take back what you said.
Let go of me.
You're so shameless.
I didn't kill your husband.
My brother didn't kill
your husband either.
What's wrong with you?
Fool.
I can forgive all that you did to me,
but to accuse my brother
and have him beaten up,
that's what I can't forgive.
I will just apologize to you.
No, Sam. You will only hurt me again.
- No, Ward. I will not hurt you.
- I don't want to.
- Wait.
- Mom. George.
- Ward, hold on.
- Ward, stand up. Come here.
- Why are you hurting my brother?
What did this woman do to you?
George…
Who did this?
It's Cairo, George.
Sam ordered him to do this to me.
Because of your evil ways,
my baby died too.
George, wait. Please, let's talk first.
George, I'm sorry.
What?
Is that a clear answer to your sorry?
Okay.
I deserve that.
But, don't think for a second
that you're the victim here, George.
We are the real victims here.
My brother died, George.
Can you blame me
when all the evidence is pointing at Ward?
You did the same thing to Francis.
You even had him jailed, remember?
Do you think
I have forgotten about that, George?
Take back what you said.
That's the truth, George.
- You're really a fool.
- What now?
- Take back what you said.
- George, let me go.
I said, take back what you said.
- Let go of me.
- You fool.
Let me go.
George…
George.
That's why now that I'm holding your baby,
I will make sure to return
all the pain you caused me.
George, my baby.
My baby.
Hold him first,
while I clean you.
My baby…
Oh, my God. My baby.
Maybe the reason he was born on Christmas
is because he has a gift for me.
Peace and harmony.
Go ahead, Samantha.
Pour all the love you have for him.
Because after today,
you will never see or hold him again.
Who else did
the two Mrs. Palacioses talk to
after 8:25 this morning?
No one else even through
text, online call, or chat?
Sarge, it was Mom. George called her.
Mrs. Georgina called you?
Remember, George called you
around 10 a.m.?
Oh, yeah. That's right.
She said… we would eat out,
but she didn't text again.
I was so pissed off.
That's what I told Mercy… Right, Mercy?
Did Ms. Georgina mention
what place or restaurant
she plans to dine in?
Okay.
I'll have her number pinned by the network
so we can trace where she was
when she called you,
so I can deploy
my search and rescue team right away.
Sarge, just tell me what area
so I can inform my colleagues.
Okay.
Sis, thank you.
Even if it was difficult,
you didn't give up.
Of course.
With our long wait for the baby,
would we give up at the end?
You helped me give birth.
You are his mother
as much as I am his mother.
Despite everything that happened to us,
I am happy…
because we remained friends.
You came here to taunt me.
- George, I am here to comfort you.
- No, Sam.
You came here
because you're looking for a fight.
So come on, let's fight. I don't care.
George, I know
what you're going through is painful
because you lost a husband
But, if you're looking
for a fight to grieve,
George, don't involve me. Please.
- Don't turn your back on me.
- George, please.
I said don't…
Let go of me.
- Come on.
- What now? Fight back.
I don't want to fight with you.
Go back to your husband.
Cry over him.
Embrace him.
This is the last time
you will be able to do that.
What are you doing here?
The killer has no right
to sympathize with the deceased.
Get out of here, Sam.
Auntie Ruth, please. I'm begging you.
Even if we just stay here.
We'll just stay here.
Sam.
Can't you understand?
Don't you dare go near George.
And I don't want her to see your face.
I don't want to fight any more.
I don't want any trouble.
I don't want any lawsuit.
What? No, George.
Let's end this memorial.
It's embarrassing to Father.
- But…
- Dad, please.
I've already made up my mind.
I'm so confused already.
I don't want to add to it.
I just want to be able
to mourn my baby's death properly.
Fine.
But, we're not yet done talking.
And you, leave.
George…
I'm sorry if I was forcing myself
on you before.
It was just that I didn't want
to give up on you.
I want you to know
how important you are to me.
And now, we are both his mothers.
Go to sleep so my baby and I can leave.
I hope the Palacios killer did not kidnap
Ma'am George and Ma'am Sam.
I don't think they were kidnapped.
It looks like Ma'am George and Sir Galvan
have an evil plan for Sam.
Why are Evelyn Lucia and Marlo Reyes
our names here?
Why does the baby have a passport?
Do you have a suspect
for who the mastermind is?
Sarge, why are you looking
at me like that?
Maybe you know something
and you're not telling me.
Hi, baby Gilbert.
Mommy is here.
‪NEXT EPISODE
George?