Help me!
You can't leave this place.
This whole place is locked.
What Sergeant Royales said is true.
I know Juliet.
Your daughter is in danger.
Forget about your anger.
You need an ally.
I don't need your support,
you're all fake.
What's with you? Stop it, Mom.
And she also admitted
that you're her next target.
- Why me?
- She knows that I love you.
She also wants to seek revenge on me
because I failed to help her before.
I'm sorry if I didn't believe
you right away.
And thank you
because you wanted to protect me.
PREVIOUSLY
- I'm sorry.
- I need to use the bathroom.
I know George needs more prayers.
Despite our fights,
she is still my friend.
I don't want something bad
to happen to her.
Thank you.
George… George, please open the door.
We understand you, Ruth.
I am also a mother.
And I will not stop praying for her
until she is safe.
Liar.
You and Basil did have an affair.
You fool. Liar!
George. George.
George…
If Iñigo is the Palacios killer,
could it be that he already killed George?
Please don't say that.
Iñigo will not kill George.
Please, don't think that way.
I'm sorry, Ma'am Ruth.
- Let's go.
- Let go of me.
Inigo.
Sergeant, have they seen
anything in the CCTV?
Please, just do everything that you can.
Yes, sir.
Dad…
I know you're worried
about your grandchild.
Me too.
I am worried about my nephew.
I'm not just worried
about my grandson, Sofia.
I'm also worried for George.
I have grown to love her…
even if I don't show it to her.
But when Iñigo kidnapped her,
I got so worried.
I saw how much she loved
your elder brother, Basil.
Someone did this to my husband.
Basil is allergic to morphine.
He wouldn't just take it on purpose.
Someone poisoned my husband.
Who did this to him?
I'll have this incident investigated.
We need to know who did this to Basil.
Whoever poisoned my husband
will pay for this.
Basil.
Dad, I will find out
who did this to Basil.
That's what I promised him, Dad.
And I won't stop until I find
the demon who poisoned him.
No, Dad.
I won't let this slide.
She needs to pay
for smearing Basil's name.
I don't want to lose her.
She's like a daughter to me now.
I think George
is really lucky to have you, Daddy.
Because you're not like Auntie Aurora.
She's only after her grandchild with Sam.
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you make me believe
that you loved me
if it's my husband you really love?
That Iñigo fooled your husband.
He extorted money from Basil.
It's a good thing
I was able to separate them.
Because if not,
that Iñigo would have gotten
all of Basil's money.
Stay away from him. He will not love you.
He will just extort money
from you and you will get hurt.
Believe it or not, George,
I don't want you to get hurt.
Maybe Dad is right.
You only extorted money from Basil.
But you failed to get what you wanted
because he was able to stop you.
And then, you made me believe
that you loved me
to get Basil's money from me.
You're bad, Iñigo.
You're so evil. You fool.
George. George.
I didn't extort money from Basil.
We really loved each other.
George, I wanted to tell you
that I fell in love with you,
but I got scared.
I got scared
that you might stay away from me.
George…
I didn't plan to fall for you…
but I did.
George, I love you.
I love you so much.
And I hope you can still accept me.
Sir, just a little more
and we'll be able to trace him.
Ruth.
If George comes back,
be a better parent to her.
Don't be like me.
I was a bad father to Basil
when he was alive.
Sir Galvan…
I'm sure you weren't a bad father.
You might have your shortcomings,
but you're not a bad father.
I can't afford to lose George.
I won't survive.
I'm willing to lose everything,
but not her or Ward.
I hope she gets home safe, Ruth.
It's hard to lose a child.
The pain is beyond compare.
I don't want to experience…
what happened to me before
when Basil died.
I don't want to lose George.
I hope her daughter dies.
Sarge, we have a lead.
We've connected every CCTV footage feed
from the different stations.
Attorney Morales' car is headed south.
It was last seen
at Station Quiteria Nuevo.
And then it went into Paso Verde.
He only has one place to go.
Everybody, ready? Let's rescue Georgina.
Sarge, do you already know where they are?
Yes, sir. I know the Paso Verde.
There's only one way in and out
of the property.
I'm sure Attorney
is just in the vicinity of the property.
Galvan.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you!
Ward.
Your sister will be rescued.
George, believe me. I love you.
Stop it.
I don't believe you anymore.
You're a liar!
George…
I said stop it!
You already made me believe
in all your lies!
Men, all set?
Yes, sir.
Sergeant Royales,
I leave my daughter
and grandson in your care.
Please save them.
Royales, I'm begging you.
Bring George and my grandson home safely.
Yes, sir. Yes, ma'am.
You're going with them?
What's this, Royales?
Are you serious?
He will only cause trouble.
Sir Galvan…
what if he can help out?
What is he proud of?
His skills as a tanod.
Mr. Palacios, he is not a tanod.
He's a soldier.
What?
Here's the proof.
I pity Ruth.
I can't imagine what she's going through
with what happened to George.
If that happened to any of you,
I don't know what I'd do.
Mother. Mother, don't worry,
because Sam and I will not be gone.
We will still be together
for a very long time.
Sam, why?
I can't stop thinking about George.
I'm worried about her and her baby.
When I was investigating
all the people surrounding
the Palacios Estate,
I discovered that he was a soldier.
And he is not just an ordinary soldier,
he's a scout ranger
with experience in search
and rescue operations.
You lied to all of us.
Why did you work here as a helper?
Because I wanted to know my family.
What other secrets do you have
that you haven't told us yet?
My concern is the safety
of Ma'am George and your grandson.
I'll go ahead.
Sarge.
Men, let's go.
Earlier, I was just trying to encourage
Auntie Ruth and Ward.
But the truth is, I'm scared.
Iñigo might do something to her.
Don't cry anymore, Sam.
George will be saved. She will be saved.
Yes, Sam. She will be saved.
And with her return,
I'm sure you'll be able
to patch things up.
The truth is, I don't know if we can
iron things out
after everything that happened to us.
But for her to come home…
safe, that would be enough.
Stop crying.
Let's pray for her.
Were you able to talk
to the person I asked you to contact?
Yes, ma'am.
What's the number?
Here.
Thank you, Rico.
You can leave me now.
Okay.
I want an update
on what I asked you to do.
Sam, are you okay now?
Sam, don't worry. George will be saved.
We're close to the Lord.
Look at me. He healed my cancer, right?
Come on.
- Our mother is so sweet.
- Yes.
Mother is sweet now.
I'm just happy
because I'm with my children.
We're complete.
And I love you. I love you.
- I love you, Mother.
I don't want you to fail.
I want you to do your job well.
I won't pay five million pesos
for a sloppy job.
Good.
Update me right away.
What the hell Amando?
Can you please make a sound
if you're coming in?
What do you need?
Francis. Remember my reminders.
Take care of yourself.
Just because you're healed,
you will ignore yourself
and won't be cautious.
That's right.
Yes, Mother.
And I don't want my cancer to return.
And I will still be the best uncle, right?
That's why I will really
take care of myself.
And you, Sam.
You should take good care of yourself
while looking for evidence,
so you can give your father justice.
Be careful. The opponent
you chose is very difficult.
Yes, Mother.
Don't worry about me, okay? Okay.
Mother, why do you keep on hugging us?
You've been doing that for a while now.
Give me a kiss.
That's a lot of kisses.
Who are you talking to, madam?
Some guy.
Are you…
Are you planning something, madam?
Wait for a second.
I will buy Sampaguita
for our altar at home.
The ones we have are already dry.
- Mother, I'll do it.
- No need.
It's just there.
- I'll go with you, Mother.
- No, I'll go.
Sam, I'll just call the driver.
Mother!
Francis!
Oh my God. Francis.
Francis. Francis.
Oh my God. Help us!
Loving you…
was never part of my plans.
At first, I thought…
I just pitied you.
But the more I got to know you…
the more I fell in love with you.
I want to stay away.
I can escape.
But…
I can't…
I can't stay away from you.
George.
George, we have to go.
George… We have to go, George.
- Where are you taking me?
- Let's go.
I won't go with you.
- Let go of me, Iñigo!
- We have to go. Let's go.
- I said let go of me.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
Team Alpha, go that way.
Team Bravo, go that way.
Be alert and keep constant communication.
If you see something suspicious,
use the radio right away.
- Yes, sir.
Team, split up.
My team, be vigilant.
It seems you're used to this.
How many operations have you had?
I've lost count, Sarge.
Team, please proceed
to the east side of the woods.
That's where the possible location is.
Proceed with caution.
Go.
George, please.
Please.
Please, let go of the gun.
You don't know how to use that.
I know how.
Abdul taught me before.
Move over.
My baby and I are leaving.
Francis!
Francis.
Francis. Oh my God!
Help! Help!
- Francis…
- Help! My God!
- Help!
- Help! My God.
Let's go, ma'am.
Francis! Help!
Help! Help!
- Francis!
- Hurry up!
All right.
Francis… Francis…
Help. Help us.
- Francis, Francis…
- Francis.
Francis, don't.
Help! Hurry, Mister!
George, please.
Give me the gun.
- I will explain everything to you.
- No!
It's just me and my baby who are leaving.
So move over!
Because if you don't, I won't think twice
about shooting you, Iñigo.
What are you looking at?
George, we really have to go.
Sergeant Royales is here already.
Please, let's go.
Let's go.
Let go of me, Iñigo.
- Let's go.
- Let go of me!
Go, go, go.
Check upstairs.
Sofia. Sofia.
Come here. Come here.
You're even holding hands.
- Come here.
- Mom.
What are you doing?
Are you letting that guy flirt with you?
Didn't I warn you already?
And his mother, she's doing nothing.
She's not saying anything
even if she sees you.
She's tolerating you.
Check the doors.
They are not here.
Mom, we're just praying for Auntie George.
Praying for Auntie George?
And since when is it your
obligation to pray for George?
Come on.
Nothing will happen with your prayers,
so just reserve that for other things.
Hey, Vivian.
You really have a bad attitude.
Are you sure Sofia is your daughter?
Because she has a heart while you don't.
And what are you talking about?
George.
George!
Javier, Cruz,
come with me.
Hurry!
Not now, Miss Samantha.
We're rescuing George.
Sergeant Royales, help us.
Help me.
The Palacios killer ran over Francis,
my brother.
What?
That's your karma.
What's happening to you is your karma!
- Hey, you're too much.
- And why?
My daughter is in danger!
Well, serves you right.
- That's true.
- So, you've changed now?
- Of course.
- We are all praying here.
- And you're doing something!
- Praying, really? I saw the two
- just flirting around.
- They're not flirting.
- They're just praying!
- What do I care about her?
What do I care about George?
There's a third Palacios killer?
He was wearing black and a mask,
just like the one who attacked George.
Francis is not a Palacios.
Why is he the target?
I don't know.
I don't know. Please help us.
Yes. Text me the details.
I'll call the station
and send an investigator there.
Okay.
Lord…
I'm begging you.
Please save Francis.
Oh, why did you stop?
Continue.
Since I'm already used
to your cheap fights.
What are you waiting for?
Ah.
Do you want a knife?
Rico. Rico.
Get two knives.
I will watch
these uneducated women kill each other.
Lord…
Please don't take him.
He is still young.
Just take me instead.
Not my youngest.
Not my youngest…
Francis…
Iñigo, why are you escaping
from Sergeant Royales?
If you are innocent,
why are you running away?
- Can you still see them?
- Not anymore, Sarge.
It seems the suspect knows the place.
That's why he can lead us astray.
Team, let's split up.
Go there and we'll go here.
- Yes, sir.
- Go.
Okay, I will tell them.
I hope Francis will be saved.
Okay.
Ma'am, it's Francis.
Why? What happened to Francis?
Someone ran him over.
- What?
Francis?
Ms. Mercy was the target.
She was about to get run over,
but Francis saved her.
So, he was run over intentionally?
Yes.
Doc…
how's my brother?
Francis sustained significant head trauma.
There's a fracture in his skull
because of the severe head injury.
We immediately did what we could
to relieve the built-up pressure
because of the swelling.
So we performed an emergency craniotomy.
But he is safe, right?
Tell me please that he will survive this.
Maybe it's true
that you're Juliet's accomplice.
that you are the Palacios killer.
What are you smiling about?
Are you happy
about what happened to Francis?
Me? Happy?
Of course not.
Maybe it's you who is happy, Aurora.
No, no. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Wrong word, wrong word.
What's the right word?
Disappointed?
Disappointed because…
it was Francis
who got run over and not Mercy.
Mom.
I wish I could give you
a definite answer now.
But with brain injuries like this,
things can be unpredictable.
Why are you killing the Palacios?
Damn it, Iñigo. Answer me.
Because they are monsters.
So, what's that supposed to mean, Vivian?
You malicious gold digger.
Are you okay now, madam?
I don't know, Amando.
But I still want to get rid of that Mercy.
Nothing.
Nothing, Aurora.
I just remembered something.
Sofia, let's go.
Let's go.
Doc…
please save my son.
Don't forsake him.
I'm begging you, Doc.
Doc…
Francis' vitals are stable for now.
But we need to observe him
over the next day or two.
If he continues to improve
and there's no increase in pressure…
Well, his chances will improve.
They have destroyed a lot of lives.
They have destroyed a lot of families,
including my family.
That's why you're seeking revenge?
Yes.
Their evil ways must stop.
They must disappear from this world.
They killed my parents.
They destroyed my life.
I am not Iñigo Morales.
My name is Antonio Beringuela,
son of José Beringuela,
owner of a once thriving
small-scale mining company.
Doc, what do we need to do?
Right now, the best thing you can do is…
be there for him.
Stay positive.
We'll give him
the best care possible in the ICU:
ventilation,
medication to control the swelling,
and around-the-clock monitoring.
Excuse me.
1995.
Aurora and Galvan went to Daddy
to buy his small mining company.
They promised him
that they would make him a partner,
but that wasn't their plan.
When Daddy sold the mines to the Palacios…
Chief. Wait, Chief.
I am innocent.
I didn't steal that gold.
Aurora, Galvan…
Why are you doing this to me?
Why are you framing me?
We are not.
You stole that gold from us.
We have proof. We have witnesses.
You demon.
After we trusted you
and made you a partner.
This is how you repay us?
- Arrest him, Chief.
- Yes, ma'am.
This is not acceptable.
- I am innocent.
- Sir.
Sir, my husband!
You… You are the demons.
You only want our mines,
but you have no plans
of making my husband a partner
of Palacios Mining.
That's why you're doing this.
Let's go, Aurora.
Mom.
Antonio.
Francis, my son…
Francis, please fight.
Fight, my dear.
Francis, you said,
you'd be the best uncle to my baby, right?
Please fight.
Fight, Francis.
Aurora and Galvan succeeded in their plan.
They got the mines,
and put Daddy in jail.
But things didn't end there.
They had Daddy killed…
so he couldn't go after them.
And what happened to Mommy…
Well, she didn't die of a heart attack.
Mom…
Mom?
Mom!
Antonio? Antonio?
Zenaida.
Zenaida…
I was so young then.
But ever since that day,
what happened to my parents…
has never left my mind.
Every day…
I always think about them over and over,
and even in my dreams.
It seems like everything
happened yesterday.
My God.
My God. I need you, Francis.
We'll still give Dad justice, remember?
Francis, I need you.
Francis, can you hear us?
Francis…
Godmother Almira adopted me.
At that time she lost her son…
Iñigo, because of cancer.
She helped me forget everything.
Everything that happened in my family.
She raised me as Iñigo Morales.
But I haven't lost who I am.
I wanted revenge.
I searched for an ally.
And I met Juliet.
We planned our revenge
against the Palacios.
We will kill all of them.
We planned our revenge.
I infiltrated the Palacios Estate
through Basil.
I found out about his gender.
And befriended him…
And I seduced him.
You're an animal.
Basil didn't wrong you.
If you are mad at Auntie Aurora and Dad,
why did you involve him?
- Basil was a good man.
- No!
Basil was as evil as his father.
Sam was telling the truth.
Basil ordered her..
to kill you because he found out
that you can't have children.
No. That's not true.
It is the truth.
Charge 250 joules.
- Everybody clear?
- Yes, Doc.
One, two, three…
No, Francis!
‪NEXT EPISODE
- Francis…
- Ms. Samantha said
it was the Palacios killer
who ran over his brother.
Attorney Morales is saying
there's another Palacios killer,
the mastermind.
Mom, I don't want to go to jail.
Are you behind the mask
of the Palacios killer
or someone you hired?