Sofia, what really happened?
Sofia, please. Tell them the truth.
- Please.
- Mommy, I'm so sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
Let's not change the story
and just admit the truth.
Is Rebecca your daughter with Orly?
Yes.
Orly and I have a daughter,
and it's Rebecca.
I am not the Palacios killer
and I'm not the mastermind.
I have nothing to do with those killings.
Believe me. Don't turn the tables
on me, Sofia.
I am innocent.
Sofia…
PREVIOUSLY
You can clarify the story now.
I want to end this.
Sofia…
So, I'm a problem to you now, Sam?
Mother, that's not what I mean.
What I mean is
let's not make any decisions
that we haven't thought about
because I have a lot
of problems right now.
And there's a possibility
that Ms. Vivian killed Francis.
What?
Is it Vivian who ran over Francis?
And you're focusing
on your Dad's illegitimate daughter?
What kind of sister are you?
Mother, what do you want me to do?
Attack Ms. Vivian, is that it?
She's now being investigated
by the police.
I don't want to accuse anyone anymore
like I did to Ward.
Because what happened?
George and I only fought.
She had a miscarriage, right?
I'm not telling you to attack Vivian.
But, my point is,
your brother died
and yet you're focusing on someone else.
It seems you don't care about Francis.
Mother, I care about Francis.
Not a single day goes by
that I don't think of him.
What I want is to give him justice.
But, Mother…
I don't want to pinpoint anyone else.
Especially as I know that the person
behind all of this is Mom Aurora.
And, Mother,
Rebecca is not a stranger to me.
She's also my sister.
She's a product
of your father's infidelity.
If you're not hurting
and you accept Rebecca, fine.
But, I can never accept her.
Mother… Mother?
I want to be alone.
Let's talk some other time.
Sofia.
Sofia, get out of there.
You don't have to answer Sergeant Royales.
Open this door, Sofia.
Hey, you. What are you all looking at?
- You're all gossipmongers, huh?
- Ms. Vivian. That's enough.
- Get out.
- Ms. Vivian, stop it.
You're happy with
what's happening to me, huh?
Ms. Vivian, stop it.
Cairo…
Give me the key to the door.
Come on, I need to get Sofia.
Come on, Cairo.
Ms. Vivian, Sofia volunteered
to talk to them.
There's nothing we can do about that.
You too.
Ma'am Sam…
Did you and Ma'am Mercy fight?
We just had an argument.
Jericho…
Mom Aurora already confessed
that Rebecca is her daughter with Dad.
So, my suspicion is true.
Rebecca is Ma'am Aurora's daughter.
What?
Sam…
I have known for a long time
that Rebecca and I are not siblings.
When we had a DNA test,
it showed that Rebecca and I
are related, but not siblings.
That means we have different parents.
Sofia… Sofia…
Sofia, my child. What did you tell them?
What did you do inside? What?
You. What did you tell my daughter?
I just repeated the questions
to her, Ms. Trano.
And she told the truth,
that you didn't see the gas mask
inside the box together.
What's that?
What's that box behind you?
Nothing.
You're clearly hiding something from me.
It's a holiday gift.
My surprise for you
because it's the holidays, right?
And you forced her to agree to lie
to convince us that you were set up.
Go ahead, Ms. Trano.
I'll give you a chance.
Let's talk again,
but I want you to tell the truth.
Even if I had doubts about Ma'am Aurora,
I didn't correct the DNA test results.
In my mind, I was protecting Rebecca.
But, it's wrong
because it seems I'm protecting
Auntie Aurora.
If only I had known the truth,
then maybe…
the truth about her daughter
with Doc Orly would come out…
It's Rebecca.
Sam, I'm sorry.
It's right that you protected Rebecca.
But, I hope you didn't
involve her in your lies.
And Jericho, I asked you
why the DNA results showed
you were siblings, remember?
And you said you didn't know.
I'm sorry, I really didn't know
that you are Rebecca's sibling.
That's why I didn't say a word.
But, Sam. I'm on your side.
I'm not the enemy here.
You and Rebecca are still my family.
No. I don't want to.
Mommy,
Sergeant Royales is giving you
a chance to come clean.
If you do not cooperate,
they will file obstruction of justice
and coercion cases against you.
I understand you, Miss Trano.
I have investigated
a lot of innocent people.
They lie because they are scared
to be pinned down.
That's the reason we are here,
for us to investigate,
so the truth comes out.
All you have to do is be honest.
I will no longer allow you
to talk to us without a lawyer.
Let's go.
What's happening?
Are you okay?
Sam, the baby.
Sit down first.
I told you, you're stressing yourself out.
This is not healthy anymore.
Come on. Let's go
for a checkup with Dr. Flores.
Isn't it late?
Didn't I tell you
that my OB is available for me anytime?
That's why we should go.
I need to make sure that my baby…
my godchild is well and fine.
Let's go. Don't object anymore.
I will drag you.
I'll drive for you.
No need, Jericho.
I'll take care of this.
Bill is there. He can drive for us.
Let's go.
General Alejaga, please…
Do everything you can to find Rebecca.
And if you find her, bring her to me,
not to Aurora.
- Mom, please.
- Thank you.
Please, just talk to Sergeant Royales.
No, Sofia. I said, no.
What are you two fighting about?
Well,
it's because this good daughter
of yours betrayed me.
That's why now, Galvan,
you need to help me.
You need to give me a good lawyer.
Mommy I didn't betray you.
I was just telling the truth.
I believe you.
I know that you're innocent.
But, just like Sergeant Royales said,
we don't have to lie
just to prove that you are innocent.
Wait.
You made my daughter lie for you?
You're really a worthless mother.
Amando.
For not protecting me from Galvan.
For allowing that vile hag, Mercy,
to come near me and threaten
to spit on my face.
You deserved that.
Mercy should have spat on you.
Amando…
Did I freaking hear you right, Amando?
Yes.
You really deserve that
because you're too much.
Rebecca is your daughter with Orly,
and you kept it a secret.
You introduced her as your niece.
What kind of a mother can do that?
Don't question my motherhood, Amando.
I didn't lack love for Rebecca.
How can you call that love
when you can't even tell her
that you're her real mother?
You hid it from her…
that she's your daughter
with that jerk, Orly.
You fooled Rebecca.
You fooled the people around you.
You fooled me.
No, Galvan. I'm sorry.
I just panicked.
Yes, I made a mistake.
I didn't mean it.
But, you need to help me, Galvan.
Sofia, help me.
I need someone who can testify
that piece of evidence
was planted in my things.
Vivian…
You don't need someone to help you.
The truth will come out.
So, you'd better confess.
No one framed you.
It was you who ran over Francis.
You're the Palacios killer.
You're the mastermind.
No, Galvan. No. No.
How many times must I tell you
that I was just framed?
I am not lying.
Please, help me. I need a lawyer.
I need to prove myself.
No, Galvan. Help me. I need a lawyer.
Dad, let's give Mommy a chance
to come clean.
Please, help her.
God.
This is just not about Rebecca.
This is about the fact
that Orly and I had a child
that you can't accept
because before and up to now,
you're so jealous of him.
I don't deny that.
I loved you…
and I almost died…
whenever I saw you together.
But, this is no longer
about Orly and Rebecca.
What Amando?
What else is your issue here?
What?
Galvan…
- Sergeant Royales.
- Sir?
Do what you have to do with this woman.
Arrest her. Sue her.
I don't care.
Just take her away from me
and my daughter.
What, Amando? Go ahead and talk. Tell me.
What else is your issue?
It's about our son.
If you didn't…
tell Rebecca that you're her real mother,
with Paco,
you never told him…
that I was his real father.
Why, Aurora?
Why?
I will not arrest you, Ms. Trano.
Just come with me.
We will just talk to clear things up.
I will not go with you…
until I have a lawyer with me.
Do you understand?
Are you are really heartless, Galvan?
Maybe this is really what you want…
For me to rot in jail.
Well, I'm sorry
because you're not the only one
I can ask for help.
- Mom…
- Hey, let her be.
I will reschedule the interview tomorrow.
You should have a lawyer by then.
Yes, I will have one.
You know the answer
to that question, Amando.
We needed to keep it a secret
that you got me pregnant because for sure,
Dad would have you killed.
But, your dad has been dead
for a long time.
But, Galvan is still here.
He would have used our secret
to overthrow me.
God, Amando. Just be thankful…
that you saw your son, Paco, grow up.
Together…
as a servant,
as a helper…
as a slave who just followed orders,
and not as a father.
Do you know how painful that was, Aurora?
I wanted so much to approach Paco…
embrace him,
and call him my son.
But, I can't do it.
How do you think Paco would feel
if you did that?
Yes, Amando, he cared for you.
But, I don't think he would have accepted
that you are his father.
That he is the product of a mistake.
Mistake?
- I loved you, Aurora.
- Yes, Amando.
But, you knew I could never love you.
I am a Palacios
and you said it yourself…
you are just a mere helper.
So, Jericho is really a Palacios.
He is Uncle Rodolfo's son.
Yes, he just didn't expose it
because he had a deal with Mom Aurora.
Hi.
Sam, here's your ultrasound result.
Thank you.
By the way, I spoke to George.
She actually mentioned
that you've been through a lot of stress…
before your pregnancy, Sam.
But, did you know?
You're so lucky. Your baby is so strong.
Thank you, Doc.
How could you, Amando?
I should have done that a long time ago.
I should have told Paco
that I am his real father.
I should have taken my son away from you…
Maybe…
Maybe he'd still be alive now.
Amando.
Amando, come back here.
Amando, I'm not yet done.
Amando… Amando…
I'm taking good care of my baby.
I've been trying to be healthy
and I take my vitamins regularly.
Of course, as much as possible,
you should avoid getting stressed.
Remember…
your pregnancy is still
in the second trimester.
There's no guarantee
that there's no risk in your pregnancy.
Sam, let me repeat this.
Do you really not want to know
if your baby is a boy or a girl?
Call me traditional, Doc, but…
I think I'd rather find out
after I give birth.
Okay, no problem.
Wait.
I need to use the bathroom.
Excuse me. Sorry, George.
Thank you, Kate.
No problem, G.
I can now push through with my plan.
Plan?
Sam…
What plan?
I left my bag.
George, what plan?
I asked Doc if the baby was a girl or boy.
I wanted to have a gender reveal party.
Sam, I hope you don't mind
that I told her.
Sorry, please don't be mad.
It's okay. I wondered what
the plan was about.
But a party?
George, let's not have a party.
I don't think it's right
with everything that's happening.
Please grant my request.
I'm just excited.
Because you know,
I wasn't able to give my baby boy a party.
So, I'll just throw one for your baby boy.
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry. I didn't mean it.
I'm having a baby boy?
My baby with Paco
is a boy…
I'm having a baby boy.
We're having a baby boy.
It's not our baby, Samantha.
It's my baby.
My baby.
So, what now?
Do you know a good lawyer?
You don't know one
and yet you talked too much.
I have to go.
You have nothing to contribute.
She's annoying. She wasted my time.
Hey, Ruth.
Ruth…
Do you know…
Do you know a good lawyer?
Yes, I do.
I have a classmate who is a valedictorian.
I'm so close with her.
She's an excellent lawyer.
- Really?
- Yes.
Ruth, can you recommend me to your friend?
Introduce me to her.
She's busy.
You know, you're really a witch.
You told me you know a good lawyer,
but you don't want to help me.
You asked a question and I answered it.
You know, Vivian, I will never help you.
Because if it's true
that you ran over Francis,
there's a possibility
that it was you who framed Ward.
I am innocent.
I don't believe you.
Being a killer stinks
out of your character.
- Really, now?
- Oh, go on.
My fist will hit your thick face.
- Go ahead.
- What?
- Make the first move and I will finish it.
- No.
I'll let you go first
so you can score a punch.
Because if you let me make the first move,
You will wake up tomorrow.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Yes, go ahead and try. Come on.
There's a possibility
that she killed Francis.
What?
Francis!
We've given him
the last dose of epinephrine,
but there's no response.
- No…
- Sorry for your loss.
Condolences.
No… no…
What? Come on. Let's go.
- Make a move.
- I will.
Vivian.
Vivian, was it you who ran my son over?
Go ahead, Mercy. Beat this woman.
What? You would gang up on me?
Come on.
Go ahead and try.
Come closer. Come on.
What now?
Ms. Vivian, that's enough.
- No.
- What?
- They started it. They're accusing me.
- Come on, that's enough.
- Oh, no.
- Ms. Vivian, that's enough.
Hey, I'm not done with all of you.
You fools.
What, Sarge?
Do we have evidence
that we can use against Vivian Trano?
How about the car she rented
that we secured?
Did the crime lab conduct
a chemical analysis
on the rubber particles
that were taken from the skid marks?
And were they able to compare it
with the materials from the car tires?
How about wear patterns?
These were the skid marks
taken on the Sto. Niño Parish Street
and the chemical composition of the tire.
This is the tire
of the car Ms. Trano rented,
Including the unique wear
and tear damage of the car.
Hold on…
It's a match.
The car rented by Ms. Trano
was indeed the car used
to run over Francis Castillo.
Yes, Sarge.
What? Aside from that,
did we get any other evidence?
- You're all ganging up on me.
- Mom, what are you doing?
- You don't want to help me.
- Where are you going?
I will leave you.
Why? What do you want me to do?
Just wait here
until the police arrest me?
I will leave you guys. I will go away.
Because the car was washed
before it was rented to someone else,
and was exposed to the different elements.
A few days before we secured the car,
we encountered a problem
with the forensics.
So, they weren't able to get blood traces
of the victim in the car?
When the forensics used luminol compound,
we were able to recover
a few traces on the bumper.
What's the result of the cross-matching
of Francis' blood sample?
We're still waiting for it, Sarge.
You can't leave.
I will think that you're not innocent.
Tell me the truth,
are you guilty or not?
You talk too much.
You're so talkative, Sofia.
You know, everything I do
is for you,
so you'll have a better life.
Up till now,
I have suffered nothing
but oppression in my life.
When I was still in my mother's womb,
people did nothing but oppress me.
That's why I promised myself
that if I had a child,
she would never experience
the hardships I went through.
Your daddy, Galvan,
he did nothing but insult me
from head to foot.
He spoke badly of me.
And that Basil when he was still alive,
did the same too.
And especially that witch, Aurora.
She has nothing else to do but belittle me
and degrade my character.
She looks down on me and insults me.
I don't want it anymore.
Sir, from the forensic.
Thanks, Sarge.
The blood samples found on the car
belong to Francis Castillo.
Okay, Sarge, I'll secure a warrant
for the immediate arrest of Ms. Trano.
Okay.
That's why that's not acceptable.
Mom, you haven't answered my question.
What?
Are you innocent or not?
Tell me.
Yes, Sofia.
Because I'm fed up
of being oppressed.
That's why, yes,
I ran over Francis.
But, it should have been Mercy.
Because I wanted them…
to accuse Aurora
and put her behind bars.
I wanted to get revenge on that woman.
But what did Francis do?
He tried to be a hero.
He wanted to be a smart aleck
and blocked the way.
So there, he was hit.
That's not my fault.
But, Sofia. I am not the Palacios killer,
and I am not the mastermind.
I only killed Francis.
Mom, just please tell me
that you're lying.
Tell me that you're lying. Come on.
You want the truth, right?
There you go.
I'm giving you the truth.
Why does it seem like…
you don't believe it?
Isn't that what you want? The truth?
Cairo, Ma'am Vivian confessed to Sofia.
Please tell me, Mom,
you didn't kill Francis.
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it, Mom? Why did you do it?
Tell me.
Shut up.
You, shut up.
You know what?
If you want to help me,
help me escape.
That's what you can do for your mother
who made sacrifices for you.
Help me escape.
Stop crying.
I will not help you.
- I won't allow you.
- What do you mean?
You have to tell Sergeant Royales
what you have done.
You have to explain to him
and admit to him.
Wow, admit to him?
What do you think of me?
That I'm stupid like you?
Hey, Sofia. I'm not stupid.
You. You're the stupid one.
And what do you think?
If I do that, what will they do to me?
They will arrest me and put me in jail.
That's why I won't allow it.
No, they can't.
I won't allow it.
You're not leaving. You have to stay.
This is bad, Mom. You have to stay.
- What do you mean?
- Mom, you can't leave.
What do you mean bad, huh?
Go bad your face.
Damn you.
I'm fed up with your excuses.
Find Rebecca and bring her to me.
I'm serious, Susan.
I'll shut down your facility.
Good morning, Ma'am.
Here's your coffee.
What are you smiling about, Rico?
Cairo called me.
It's confirmed that it was Ma'am Vivian
who ran over Francis.
You'll be cleared
of Ma'am Sam's accusation.
And should I be happy, Rico?
I'm really innocent.
That Sam is just pissing me off.
I don't care about that.
What I'm concerned about now is Rebecca.
Now scram. Go.
I'm sorry.
Rebecca, my child. Please come home.
Come home safe.
I've already lost Paco and your dad.
Don't tell me I'll lose you too, my child.
Okay?
You're so sweet there.
I'm sure you've received my text
in our group chat.
What now? There's a winner in our bet.
Wait, what do you mean there's a winner?
Our deal is guessing
who the mastermind is.
Ma'am Vivian only confessed
to running Francis over.
Yes, that's our bet.
That's automatic already.
She's holding the mask
of the Palacios killer.
Hey, no cheating here.
Wait.
What do you mean cheating?
Let's just wait
for Sergeant Royales' investigation
on who the mastermind is
before you collect payment.
You're a bunch of fools.
- Give me my money.
- Hey, what's with you?
You, where's my money?
You're a jerk.
Are you hungry for money, Bill?
What did you say?
That's enough. That's enough.
Stop it.
Hey.
You're stubborn!
You're so stubborn.
Hey, Ando. Stop it.
You fool.
Hey. Why are you fighting?
Hey, Ando.
Boo.
The hell?
Damn you, Barry.
Do that again and I'll have you exorcised.
What are you doing here?
Oh, God…
I'm here to pick you up
because we have a meeting.
Don't tell me you've forgotten about it.
Anyway, you little liar.
So…
It's true that Rebecca is your daughter
and I assume with Orly?
Simon…
Leave us.
My goodness, Aurora.
I feel so offended.
All this time,
I thought I was your most trusted friend
for you to tell all your secrets to.
I always ask you about Rebecca
and you always deny it.
I had no choice before, Barry.
I had to.
You had to?
Auro, let me remind you,
when you had
the illicit love affair with Orly,
your father was already gone.
You were already a full,
independent, single woman.
But, I was annulled at that time, Barry.
Orly was still married to Mercy.
I can't afford…
to involve the Palacios name
in any scandal.
That's why…
I had to hide the truth about Rebecca.
Ando. Stop that.
- Ando.
- You fool.
I said stop it. What's with you?
Cairo. Bill, that's enough.
Why are you fighting here?
Bill is a jerk.
He's collecting payment for our bet.
Fools.
Instead of sending your money
to your families,
you use it for gambling?
What are you betting on?
Who the mastermind
of the Palacios killer is.
And Bill here,
when he found out that Ms. Vivian
was behind Francis' death,
he asked us for payment.
What?
It was Ms. Vivian who ran Francis over?
Yes, she confessed to Sofia.
Does Uncle Galvan know?
Son of a…
Stop that.
Well, if you really have to hide the truth
about you and Rebecca from the public,
then you have an obligation
to tell me all your secrets
because I am your best friend.
Remember?
We even made a pinky promise…
You, me, and Larry.
And it was also a part
of our lifelong friendship's oath.
Remember that?
Tell no lies, keep no secrets.
Remember?
That's why when I asked you
if you had something to do
with the rumor
about my husband having an affair,
you told me
that you had nothing to do with it.
And I believed you.
I'm sorry.
Uncle Galvan.
- Uncle Galvan.
- What, Jericho?
Did you find Rebecca?
Not yet, but where is Auntie Vivian?
She's in her room. Why?
She already confessed to Sofia
that she ran over Francis.
What?
Vivian.
Dad…
It's Mommy. She escaped.
What?
Jericho, alert all security. Now.
Yes.
Where are you going?
You are still under investigation, right?
Go ahead and come closer.
So, you already know that it was Vivian
who ran over your brother?
I told you it wasn't me.
Apologize to Aurora now.
Auntie Aurora distributed my babies
to Auntie Larry and Auntie Barry.
Oh, my God.
I thought it was only Auntie Larry.
How can she do that?
What did you say again?
That Aurora can't hurt you?
I'll do it for her.
And I will avenge her.
You have no right to hurt my friend.
My God, my children…
Do you know where they went?
Do you know where
my children are, Attorney?
Rebecca.
My children…
Will you let them destroy your character,
so you can never recover your children?
Don't give them the power.
Think about your children
that they took from you.
Focus on that.
NEXT EPISODE