- You animal.
- Ma'am, stop it.
Don't do something that you'll regret.
I'll give you my word.
I'll dig deeper into this case.
Aside from what Ms. Samantha mentioned,
I also saw a discrepancy
in Sergeant Casas' report.
In my watch, I'll make sure
that no detail will be missed.
If my grandchild comes out,
the baby George is pregnant with,
and you continue to taunt her family,
I'll send you back to Baguio.
No need. I just agreed
to this stupid DNA test
to prove that I am carrying Basil's child.
But, I won't agree
that he'll grow up here with you.
I swear to God, Sam.
I will find evidence
to prove that you pushed my son.
Francis, we need
to find Basil's cellphone.
We need to find it.
Miss, last time you approached me,
you were asking me about the twins.
I'm sorry, Ma'am.
I made a mistake.
Miss, I'm begging you.
Please tell the truth.
I'm really sorry. I'm telling the truth.
Hello, Sir Amando.
I already talked to Ma'am Rebecca.
I did what you ordered me to do.
Get Basil's laptop in the other house.
I'm sure the report is there.
- Yes, Madam.
- Go, now.
What, Francis? did you find the cellphone?
Sam, not yet.
Maybe it's better if we recall
what happened in the party.
Maybe we can think of a clue.
Sam, could it be
Basil's cellphone is in the…
…motorcycle.
Here's the key.
Here it is.
What is Basil's password on his laptop?
This is Basil's cellphone. This is it.
‪PREVIOUSLY
I just emailed the compliance reports.
Send them first thing tomorrow.
I did not kill Doc Orly.
You know I couldn't.
My God…
My God, Paco…
I swear, you didn't know your father well.
You're so shameless.
Sam, you didn't know your father well.
He took advantage of the miners,
he gets money from them.
All just to sustain his own addiction.
How dare you.
Just to save yourself,
you will ruin my father's memory?
- You're so shameless.
- Sam, I'm telling you the truth.
Your father was a bad person.
He hid a lot of things to you.
He's a liar, a fraud.
It's you and your mother who are frauds.
Your family hides a lot of secrets.
Sam, don't turn the tables on us!.
I'm not lying.
I know what I heard.
I know that your mother is covering you up
for what you did.
You killed my father.
- We're done.
- No, no.
Let go of me.
Don't.
I won't let the police arrest you for now
because I don't have an evidence.
But, I promise,
you'll pay for what you did.
I will kill myself. I will jump.
Go ahead and commit suicide.
I don't care. Do whatever you want.
You don't believe me, do you?
I'll show you.
I'm going to jump. I'll take you with me.
Oh, my God.
Let me go.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, Paco. My darling. Darling boy…
My God.
My God…
You're an animal.
You're a demon.
You're an animal, Sam.
You will pay for what you did to my son.
You're an animal.
You're a demon,
Mother, we already found
Basil's cellphone.
No one will see Sam's video.
Your sister said Basil told her
that's not the only copy.
What if someone finds it?
Mother, that won't happen.
No one is looking for it.
What the police are looking for
is Basil's cellphone.
And, Mother, I think,
Basil only said that to Sam to scare her.
Samantha.
Oh, Sam…
My child…
George, are you really sure
of your decision?
We need the Palacioses.
Can you raise my grandchild in poverty?
Mom, we won't go poor.
George, where will your savings take us?
We haven't gotten anything
from Basil's death
because the case is not yet solved.
If we leave now, even if the case is over,
Sir Galvan will no longer give it to us.
Mom, there you go again.
All you think about is money.
Not only that, George,
but your security too.
What if the Palacios killer follows you?
How about your baby?
Mom, the Palacios killer
will no longer follow us.
He will find out
that I don't have an interest
in introducing my child as a Palacios.
You're so shameless
for visiting my son's altar
after you pushed him off the cliff.
George…
What do you need?
The DNA results came.
- Let go of me. You're hurting me.
- Let go.
Stop it, Ma'am Aurora.
- That's enough. Stop it.
- Stop it, Ma'am Aurora.
Sam is pregnant. My sister is pregnant.
Stop using my grandchild.
This woman deserves to be punished.
How dare you.
Will you not stop, Ma'am Aurora?
Mother.
Sir Armando, help us.
Stop, Ma'am Aurora.
Stop accusing Sam.
It's not an accusation anymore, Mercy.
It's the truth.
I have a proof.
I saw the video of you, Sam,
pushing Paco off the cliff.
And?
The baby you're carrying…
It's Basil's child and it's a boy.
Look.
You got ahead of me
in finding out my baby's gender.
Anyway…
it's just right
that we're packing out things
because we're leaving now.
Why are you leaving?
I told you yesterday.
I will take my son away from here.
I don't want him to grow up with you.
I don't want him to grow up knowing
that his own grandfather doubted him.
Come on, George.
That was just my initial reaction.
You can't blame me for that.
George, maybe you can think it over first.
Mom, we're leaving.
You and Ward should pack your bags.
You're not going anywhere.
I won't allow it.
My grandson stays here.
He will be born here. He will grow up
and grow old here.
You have no right to dictate to me
what I will do with my child.
- I am his grandfather.
- No.
Ever since you accused me
of all the killings here on the estate,
you ceased to be my father-in-law.
When Basil died, I felt so alone.
But, what did you do?
You accused me of being a murderer.
Even with Beverly's death.
I've decided to cut my ties with you,
with the Palacioses.
Is that why you're mad at me?
Fine.
I will call Royales
and tell him to stop investigating you.
It was he who said that…
you're not yet a suspect,
and he couldn't find a piece
of evidence against you.
You are not leaving. You're not leaving.
You will pay for what you did to my son.
I will have you jailed
and you will die there.
You will rot there.
You're a shameless woman.
- Ma'am Aurora, stop it.
- Let go of her. Stop it.
Ma'am Aurora, stop it.
- Stop it, please.
- No one leaves the estate.
- We are leaving.
- Georgina.
Let's go, Sam. She's going crazy.
Go after them, Amando.
What are you doing? Go after them.
Don't let them escape.
Go after them.
George, please.
Basil is gone.
My grandchild with Beverly is also gone.
Don't include my grandson
with those I lost and those who left me.
I don't want to be left again.
George…
I will do everything…
just tell me.
Just don't take my grandchild
away from me, please.
George, maybe you can give Sir Galvan
another chance for the baby.
I will think about it.
Dad. Dad.
Auntie Aurora is accusing Sam
of pushing Paco off the cliff.
Again?
But, Paco's case is already closed.
She said she had a proof. There's a video.
The incident was recorded.
George…
promise me you're not leaving.
Let's talk later.
I'll just go to Aurora.
Don't follow them anymore.
- But, Mommy…
- Just listen.
Just stay here.
Don't follow.
You're pregnant.
There might be shooting there
and we'll get involved.
Think about your baby, okay?
Rebecca.
I've been looking for you.
Sam and Auntie Aurora are fighting in the…
I know, I know.
I saw them before I went here,
and I don't care.
They can kill each other if they want.
They are still our family.
And so?
If there's something
we can fix, let's do it.
That's why you're looking for me…
to intervene in their chaos.
Rebecca, you're the only one who
can calm your Auntie Aurora.
I hate her.
She's a liar.
Jericho, I begged her.
I begged her until she tells me the truth,
but she still denied
that I got pregnant and had babies.
Maybe she's telling the truth.
No.
Rebecca, you have no memory.
You can't remember.
So, don't force it.
Just believe your Auntie Aurora.
Do you believe her?
She's a liar.
She lived as a liar,
she will die as a liar.
But, you don't have proof
that you got pregnant or gave birth.
Well, I just don't want you…
to hope for something that's not real.
You will look for your babies and then…
there's really nothing.
Let us out. We're begging you.
Please let us pass.
- Please let us pass.
- Let us out.
- Please.
Samantha.
Do you think
you can escape what you did to my son?
- Hey, stop it.
- Stop it.
Let go of me.
Please let us leave.
- Let us leave.
- No, Mercy.
You're not leaving.
Until this case is over,
you will stay with me.
You will only leave
if this woman goes to jail.
Your daughter needs to pay, Mercy.
- Get that woman.
- No. Not my mother.
- Don't touch my mother.
- Don't. Don't.
- Don't.
- Sam.
What now, Sam?
- Mom, please.
- Ma'am Aurora…
Will you confess now?
You better confess
because if not,
your family will be involved too.
Have you forgotten what I told you?
I will kill the family who pushed my son.
- Sam… Ma'am Aurora…
- Sam, don't.
You have nothing to confess.
- Stop him.
- Sam, don't.
Stop him. He's so talkative.
- Make his mouth bleed.
- Don't.
Francis.
- Francis.
- Don't.
Don't hurt my brother, please.
Don't, please. Not my family.
Sam…
Will you still be stubborn?
I will hurt your mother next.
- Don't.
- Amando.
- Sam.
- Don't.
Don't.
Sam…
I will count to three.
My dear, dear murderous daughter-in-law.
- Sam.
- Don't.
- Don't, please.
- If you still won't confess…
you won't have a brother
or mother to call.
- One.
- Don't.
- Two.
- Three.
- Don't.
- Yes!
- Sam.
I killed Paco.
Yes, I pushed my husband off the cliff.
Yes.
But, everything was just an accident.
I didn't mean to push him off the cliff.
- Mom…
- So, it's true?
Yes. It's true, Galvan.
This woman pretending to be a saint…
did push my…
my darling boy, Paco, down that cliff.
I didn't mean it.
Please forgive me. I didn't mean it.
Damn you, Sam.
Whether you did it intentionally or not,
you still pushed him and he died.
How could you do
that to the man who loved you?
To the man who fought for you
against his own mother?
Uncle, he wanted me dead.
He wanted to take me to die with him.
That's why I accidentally
pushed him off the cliff.
I didn't mean it.
Liar.
Sir Paco would not do that.
Why would he kill himself?
- Because I was leaving him.
- That is bullshit.
He would commit suicide because of you?
I know my nephew.
He would not die
just for someone like you.
Do you know Paco?
So, you also knew his monstrous ways,
the nephew you are bragging about?
Animal.
After you pushed my son,
you will destroy his image?
My son is not a monster.
He took me to a sex party.
Isn't that disrespectful?
Maybe you're as filthy as he is.
All right.
Since we're all exposing everything here…
yes, he took me to a sex party…
to share me with his friends.
But, I let that slide.
But, I can't forgive him
for what he did to my father.
Yes, Francis.
It was Paco who killed Father.
Don't accuse my son.
Your stupid father died
of a drug overdose.
My father didn't commit suicide.
Your son killed him
and you covered up for him.
How dare you.
You would even make up stories about me?
I heard you.
I heard you and Sir Galvan. I heard you.
You were talking on the third floor.
Don't blame my son. I saw what happened.
It was Amando.
It was Amando who ran him over, not Paco.
Really, Aurora?
You'll cover up for Paco again…
like how you covered up for him
with what he did to Dr. Orly.
I don't want you to hope
for something that's not real.
You'll only get hurt, Rebecca.
You know…
Jericho, it's me.
Delia?
Why are you here?
I just came back for my things.
I will leave, but I saw both of you.
I can get in trouble
with what I'm about to do…
but I'm also a mother.
I can't bear…
not to tell the truth.
You indeed…
got pregnant before, Ma'am Rebecca.
I saw this in the library.
Ma'am Rebecca got pregnant?
Who gave you the right to feast
on Rebecca's private life?
I didn't meddle with her things.
Pack your belongings.
You leave this estate.
And I confronted Paco for it.
I did not kill Dr. Orly.
I know what I heard.
Yes.
Your mother has long been defending you.
Your family has been covering
for you for a long time.
You killed my father.
And I saw…
I saw the truth in his eyes.
And I know. I know.
That's why I told him…
that I'll expose
your family's filth to everyone.
I will tell everyone that he's a murderer.
That's why he pulled me.
He wanted to involve me with his suicide.
That's it.
That's the truth.
Liar. Liar. Liar.
No matter what you say, Samantha,
even if you make up stories,
no one would believe you in court.
Do you know why?
Because you have no proof while I do.
So, prepare yourself to rot in jail.
Why would I wait?
I will punish you now.
I will lock you up.
Are you telling the truth?
Yes.
I saw your picture
while you were pregnant.
Sir Amando saw us.
That's why Ma'am Aurora fired us.
Ma'am…
promise me
you won't tell them
that I told you…
that you got pregnant.
Please, promise me.
Ma'am Aurora will kill me.
Where are you going?
To Auntie Aurora.
Don't worry, I will not betray you.
- Rebecca, wait.
- What?
It's you who said
that your Auntie Aurora is a liar.
She was born a liar and will die a liar.
Do you think she'll admit it to you?
But, I want to see my children, Jericho.
She's the only one who knows
where they are.
Rebecca, you will see them.
I promise.
But, don't rush.
Let's plan the things
we'll be doing carefully.
Calm down, okay?
Let go of me. Let go of me, you animal.
- Sam. Sam.
- Let go of me.
Let go of me. You fool.
Let go of me.
- Come here.
- Let go of me.
- Sam.
Sam. Ma'am Aurora.
Ma'am Aurora…
Francis. Francis.
Francis.
Ma'am Aurora, my child.
My child.
Go ahead and continue that.
Just one touch
and this will go live on social media
and what you're doing will be trending.
This will reach the police.
Okay, I'll stop now.
Amando.
Francis. Francis.
Don't. Francis, give that to him.
Francis, don't.
Let me go.
No Castillo will…
leave this estate.
Do you all understand me?
Yes, ma'am.
Amando, make sure…
that there is no video.
Yes, ma'am.
You are all animals!
By the way…
we'll see you in court.
Mom, I'm sorry.
It looks like the trouble is over.
They're all going home.
Dad. Dad.
Dad.
Is what I heard true?
Did you try to hurt Sam?
Sofia, shut up.
I don't want to talk about it.
So, it's true?
You've hurt Sam.
How could you, Dad? She's pregnant.
I said, shut up.
You're just like your mom.
You're meddlesome.
You're ruthless.
You're like monsters.
What did you say?
Oh, you heard me the first time, Dad.
But, let me repeat it.
You and Auntie Aurora,
you're like monsters.
Dad, don't.
It's Paco who killed dad.
That's why you fought on the cliff
and accidentally pushed him.
He was denying it to me over and over,
but I know it was him.
He killed dad. It was him.
Your suspicion was right, Sam.
And now they'll hurt us?
They're animals. I'll get back at them.
Francis…
Francis. Don't. What's with you?
- Didn't I tell you…
- No.
They killed Dad.
- Francis, stop it.
- They're abusing us.
What kind of a person am I
if I do not seek revenge
- for my family, huh?
- Give me that, please.
Francis, I've committed a lot
of sins in my life.
You already got involved.
I don't want to involve you again, please.
Please give me that.
It's true that I killed Paco.
What, Sam? Is your conscience
bothering you?
You just defended yourself.
You're innocent.
He was pulling you.
He wanted to take you with him.
He also wanted you to die.
They are all animals. They will all pay.
Francis, that's enough.
Yes, they are animals,
but they are monsters.
Dad, don't hurt Sofia.
The next time you meddle again…
What's that, Dad?
You will hurt me too
just like what you did to Sam?
You have the nerve to answer back.
Please.
Sofia is just a kid who answers back.
Just let her be.
Sofia, you shouldn't
be answering back to your parent.
Ward…
go out.
Are you okay?
What happened, Cairo?
Auntie Aurora sent a message.
To me too.
Me too.
It was Sam who pushed Paco.
Sam, move aside. I said move aside.
I said no, Francis.
What's with you? Do you think…
they'll be scared
of the gun you're holding?
Mom has a shotgun.
Just one shot at you
and your head will explode, Francis.
And if you get lucky and make one shot,
what will happen to you?
You will go to jail again.
Is that what you want?
Sam, I don't care.
I am sick. I have cancer.
I will end up
either in the cemetery or jail.
Even if I go to jail, it's okay.
As long as I can seek revenge on them.
- I'll eventually die there.
- You will not die, Francis.
You'll get well and you won't go to jail.
You know, just to end all this,
I'll do it.
I'll go to jail. I don't want
this anymore. Let's end this.
What's with you, Sam?
What are you talking about?
What will happen if you go to jail?
What will happen to your baby?
Do you think you'll be
with your baby if you go to jail?
For sure, Ma'am Aurora will hide
the baby away from you.
Sam, you just defended yourself.
It's not your fault.
That's why you shouldn't go to jail.
You shouldn't go to jail.
I don't know how to defend myself.
I have no proof.
- Mother?
- Let me do it.
I will confront Ma'am Aurora.
That Samantha is something else.
It was she who really pushed her husband.
She acts very well.
Her performance is award-winning.
So, what Ma'am Aurora said is true.
She should go to jail. She's so shameless.
Why, George?
I'm just thinking.
If Sam pushed Paco,
could it be that she was the one
who poisoned Basil?
- Mother…
- Mother, please.
- Let go of me.
Let me.
- Let me fight with Aurora.
- Mother, please.
Please, I don't want
my child to lose his grandmother.
I don't want my child to lose his uncle.
Please, let's stop this. I'm begging you.
Please! Please!
Please, for my baby.
What are you doing here, huh?
- Francis!
- Francis…
No, we didn't come here for trouble, okay?
Sam, Auntie Aurora sent me a video.
And I think she sent it to everybody.
Maybe you've seen it already, right?
You pushed Paco?
What happened was an accident.
I didn't mean it.
I just defended myself.
Sam, give me your hand.
Rebecca…
Please, please…
Maybe Sam poisoned Basil.
Maybe she's the real Palacios killer?
She first killed the cousins
and then she killed Beverly.
And then she killed Peter.
She kills the Palacioses
so her child will benefit from it.
With Beverly, it's possible.
But, Peter. She was with me at that time.
It's easy to pay and order someone.
Well, she got a lot of money
from Paco's death.
With just five thousand,
you can get a killer.
You have a point, Mother.
That woman is an animal.
Maybe she did poison Basil.
Sam…
everything you said is true.
Just tell Auntie Aurora,
so she knows the truth.
Auntie Aurora will not believe that.
Because she will only believe
what she wants to believe
and that's all her lies.
Just like how she lied to me.
Sam, I feel sorry for you.
I really am.
We're both victims of Auntie Aurora.
I'm sorry.
Be careful.
Just let me know if you need my help.
I'm ready to protect you and your baby.
You're also my family now.
Ma'am Aurora thought uploading
this video would help her.
What she didn't know
is that she just gave me
a weapon against her.
What do you mean?
The video that Basil showed me,
that video was cut short.
But, this one…
This video that Mom Aurora
is spreading around,
this is the whole video.
It clearly shows that Paco wants
to take me to my death.
That I only defended myself.
She should be ready.
After all this,
I will sue her for slander and harassment.
Why do you want to do it now?
I can't sleep, Jericho.
And I keep hearing my babies crying.
That's why I want to know the truth now.
What if your Auntie Aurora wakes up?
No, she's a heavy sleeper.
Your Auntie Aurora is not here.
What?
But, it's late.
Where is she?
You really should have listened
to me, Paco.
About what?
About marrying that woman.
Did Sam do something to you again?
Not to me, Paco.
But, to you.
It was her, Son.
She was the one
who pushed you off the cliff.
What?
Paco, I found this evidence.
Look.
I did not kill Dr. Orly.
No one did.
Because your father killed himself.
I gave you a chance
to defend yourself, but…
Aren't you even shocked at all, Paco?
Your wife pushed you off the cliff…
Then that's your reaction?
What do you want me to say?
Oh my God.
Don't tell me…
you knew all along, Paco?
So, it's not true that you
didn't know what happened?
Are you still protecting
that leech wife of yours, Paco?
Are you still covering up for her?
Mom, no.
I can't remember.
But, why is your reaction like that, Paco?
What should my reaction be, Mom?
You have evidence
that I was pushed by my wife, so?
I am here now.
Stuck in this hellhole.
You should get mad.
You said it yourself, Paco.
You're stuck here because of that woman.
Do you know what she said?
She said you were going to jump
off the cliff and take her with you.
What?
I would never kill myself.
I know you won't!
Son, I know you won't!
So, please.
Don't sit there
and act as if Samantha did nothing to you
because she did.
I will miss you.
- Why are you holding my daughter's hand?
- Mom.
That's not allowed.
- Don't hurt my brother.
- Hey, how dare you!
Pack your things now.
I threw Vivian out.
You chose George over your mistress? Why?
All of you, listen
to what I'm going to say.
George is pregnant.
What? Another Palacios?
Another threat to your throne.
Spread it so it will reach
the Palacios killer
that George is pregnant.
You're right, Sam.
We can fight this for self-defense.
My useless lawyers.
They all agree that Sam has a strong case.
Where did you get the video?
From the laptop of Basil, your son.
Did he take the video?
Did you and Basil plan this?
You paid Sam to get rid of my son?
Let the killings begin.