(Ji Chang-wook)
(Won Jin-a)
(Melting Me Softly)
(This program includes
indirect advertisement.)
(All characters, organizations,
places, cases, and incidents )
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(2019 Grand Prize Winner
for Korea Medical Healthcare)
"2019"...
What?
You... You're Hyun-gi?
Yes.
Hey, wait.
What about Ha-young? Where's Ha-young?
Where do you think?
She's at the broadcasting station.
Ha-young is the news bureau chief.
"The news bureau chief"?
(2019 Student Recruitment
for Entrepreneurship)
What?
What's going on?
"2019"?
(1999, Domestic Science College)
(Professional education
to secure research ethics)
(We accuse the student council!)
(Hanguk University, 2019)
Excuse me.
Can you tell me
today's date?
What...
What year are we in?
2019.
What? "2019"?
Is it really 2019?
(Episode 3: The Days We Lost)
(Professor of the Psychology
Department, Hwang Dong-hyuk)
(We have an announcement.)
(Ko Mi-ran from
the Chinese Literature Department.)
(Ko Mi-ran, please come
to the broadcast studio.)
("An Invitation to Your Subconsciousness")
("Basics of Abnormal Psychology")
"Ko Mi-ran".
I haven't heard that name in ages.
We repeat once again.
We'd like Ko Mi-ran to come
to the broadcast studio...
Mi... Mi-ran.
Can you hear me? It's your mom.
Where are you?
I'm trying to find you!
-Mi-ran. Mi-ran!
-My goodness, Mi-ran!
-Mi-ran!
-Nam-tae!
Nam-tae!
Mi-ran!
(Nam-tae. If anything happens,
blow this whistle, okay?)
Then I'll come running.
Nam-tae.
-Mi-ran!
-My goodness.
-Oh, dear.
Mi-ran.
Mi-ran!
Nam-tae.
Mi-ran.
Mi-ran!
Nam-tae.
Are you really my brother?
Let me take a look.
Yes, it's me.
It's me, Nam-tae.
Nam-tae, you've grown so much.
Yes, Mi-ran.
Get on my back.
(If you don't want me to,
then I'll stop growing.)
(I don't need to grow up anymore.)
(Don't be ridiculous.
You must hurry and grow up a lot.)
Why are you so late?
I waited so much for you.
My dear Nam-tae,
when did you grow up so much?
I grew up a lot.
I ate a lot and grew up a lot
to see you again.
Do you believe me now?
Episode 67 of "Infinite Experiment
Paradise" from 20 years ago
was titled "Can You Really Fly
with Balloons?"
During the shooting, we didn't have
any action cameras or drones.
I got that scar from
falling down the tree,
trying to shoot the scene
with my video camera.
You even put medicine on me.
20 years ago?
Oh, no, 20 years...
Close your mouth.
Ko... Ko Mi-ran.
What happened to her, sir?
-Ko Mi-ran?
-Yes.
Why are you asking me?
I thought you knew.
Wait.
She wasn't there when I woke up.
What is this? Is she all right?
-You. It's you.
-Mom!
-You! I won't let you live.
All of you jerks at the TV station. You!
You didn't even look for my son.
You had a great life, didn't you?
Look at how plumpy you are.
Mom, please. One second.
Mom, can you go somewhere else?
I have to talk to them.
Father, I mean... Can you take Mom
and go somewhere else?
Okay, Dong-chan.
-You jerks.
-Let's go, Mom.
-You!
-Mom, calm down.
-Why are you so strong?
-You jerks.
Let's go.
First off,
let me just speak casually with you.
Are you really Hyun-gi?
Of course, you saw this.
Fine.
Okay.
Find Ko Mi-ran's address for me.
How would I find it?
That happened 20 years ago.
Do you know how much I tried to find you?
But I couldn't even find any clues.
We tried our best too.
I mean, Professor Hwang Gab-su
suddenly died.
Wait. Professor Hwang died?
He did. He's not the only one who died.
Michael Jackson died,
and so did Kim Jong-il of North Korea.
Whitney Houston died too.
Who else died? It's...
Mr. Mo Soo-young of Production Team Three
also died of lung cancer.
And my mother-in-law passed away too.
Anyway, that's the current situation.
Of course, during that time,
I had two sons,
and our chief became the president.
He got caught for having an affair
and had to get divorced
just 20 days before the abolishment
of adultery as a criminal offense.
Can you charge this phone?
What is this?
Do you think
this phone will work, Dong-chan?
Really? Then give me your phone.
Come on, give it to me.
Where is the keypad on your phone?
What do you do...
Hey, what's with this phone?
How do I...
Tell me the number.
It's 0173491563.
You're still the same.
You're still good at memorizing numbers.
But I guess you memorized
Ko Mi-ran's number.
He remembers something from 21 years ago.
That's amazing.
It's not 21 years ago for him.
It was yesterday.
Right.
(The phone you have reached
is turned off.)
(-Leave your message...)
-The number isn't...
Dong-chan.
-Goodness.
-Should we go home?
Dong-chan, let's go home.
Hey, wait. Mr. Baek.
I mean, can you call Detective Baek?
I divorced him, Dong-chan.
But we do stay in touch.
We haven't settled on the division
of assets and the alimony.
He's been paying me monthly.
You got divorced?
Yes, twice.
It has been 20 years.
How can I live with just 1 man?
Why is everyone divorced?
It's me.
It's me! Can't you hear me?
Get your ears cleaned.
One second.
Dong-chan, you can ask him
whatever you want.
Ko Mi-ran's current address.
Well, her resident registration number
begins with 760214, but...
Why is it so hot in here?
Can you get me some cold water?
Okay?
Wait, where have they gone?
Yes, hello?
Yes, right.
I was about to drop him off at home.
Yes. Right. Yes.
Dong-ju asked me to bring you home.
(Haengdang-ro)
I have the key here.
Here is the key.
Wait, I thought our home was...
-Let's go inside.
-Come in.
What are you doing? Let's go in.
What?
Come in.
What happened?
Did you win the lottery?
Of course.
It's as if we won
the first place of the lottery.
It's all thanks to
the bank book that you gave me.
The bank book?
Yes, the money you got for the experiment.
Your dad and I started a business
with the money that you left for us.
And we made some money.
That was the price of your life,
so I guess the deities gave us a favor.
They let us become so wealthy.
Excuse me, Mr. Jo.
Yes?
Can you do me a favor?
Of course, something like that
wouldn't happen,
but if anything happens to me,
can you
give this to my family?
(Ko Nam-tae)
"Ko Nam-tae"?
(6.5 million won)
(Ko Nam-tae)
(The passcode is Nam-tae's birthday.)
Mi-ran, your room is over there.
Go on.
Thank you.
Mom. Dad.
And Nam-tae.
Thank you for having a good life.
Don't thank us.
We're thankful to you.
Now you've come home alive.
(Korean Style Restaurant Jinsagalbi)
What is this?
What are you doing? Come inside.
What on earth happened?
These two
wasted so much of our fortune away.
-Let's go in.
-Come on.
Let's go in. Come on.
That man stepped on it!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Don't call him "that man".
He's my big brother.
What? How can he be older than you
when he looks so young?
Just call him your uncle.
Hello.
Dong-chan. This is my wife,
and this is my daughter.
Take your toy and go to your room.
I'm sorry, Dong-chan.
No, no. It's okay.
Here, wear these for now.
Do you have anything else, sir?
I mean, do you have anything else?
All of your stuff are in the storage,
so we have to go get them tomorrow.
You should use Dong-ju's room
for the next little while.
What about me?
You can sleep with me
or sleep in Seo-yoon's room.
Your brother doesn't have
a place to sleep.
Fine.
Dong-chan, sleep well.
Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
(Looking for a missing person)
Where's Dad?
Where is he?
Dad?
Gosh.
I was planning to report you missing
if you didn't come home today.
-You were alive after all.
-I attended a seminar.
Stop lying, punk.
I went on a trip since living is so tough.
What's so tough? Are you in agony?
Are you doing research?
Are you supporting a family?
If I'm ever born again,
I want to live like you.
I'm tired. I'm going to bed.
Hey. By the way...
-Don't talk to me.
-Mi-ran...
Is Mi-ran a girl whom
you're interested in lately?
I'm talking about Ko Mi-ran
who went to the US 20 years ago.
My first love, Ko Mi-ran.
"Ko Mi-ran"?
Your friend from college entrance
preparation school?
Yes, that Ko Mi-ran.
She hasn't contacted you
since then, right?
No.
Why are you asking?
No reason.
I wonder if she made a family
and is living well over there.
You're so random.
Do you have nothing better to do
but to reminisce about your first love?
There's only so much my father can do
to prevent you from getting fired.
You should write dissertations
and go to seminars.
Show some effort, will you?
Stop living like a parasite.
What's the point of changing your name
when you're still a fool?
Did you call me a fool?
That's ridiculous.
You should talk more elegantly.
Why should I listen to you?
Why should I? Why should I?
Where did my life go wrong?
Both of us were ruined
because of Ko Mi-ran.
If you didn't make that mistake
after getting pathetically drunk
over Mi-ran...
Why do I bother?
I miss
Mi-ran.
Darn her.
Hey.
The moment the world finds out
that our station
kept quiet about Dong-chan going missing,
both of us will be fired.
We'll really be done for.
You know that, don't you?
Of course I do. What should we do now?
We have to pretend we don't know
anything until the end.
We covered up the mouths of every staff
who were involved in the experiment.
And the professor who worked
on the experiment is gone.
All we have to do is keep Dong-chan quiet.
Do you think it'll be easy
to keep him quiet?
That's what I'm worried about too.
He's crazy.
He's insane.
By the way, where did Ko Mi-ran go?
Whatever happened to her?
What's giving me the real headache is her.
She's worse than Dong-chan.
She's really crazy.
I mean it.
Don't tell me she's alive.
What are we going to do?
I knew this year was unlucky for me,
but this is driving me crazy.
I really don't feel like living.
Who on earth woke them up?
Where were they all this time anyway?
How is it possible
for him to look exactly the same?
What could've happened?
I'm speechless.
Is he really your older brother?
With all seriousness,
he looks like your son.
He strangely feels like someone else.
How is he different?
Compared to Dong-chan,
the back of his head looks different.
He has wider nostrils too.
His eyes look super cold, just like ice.
Doesn't he look extremely rude?
He was never nice.
Didn't he used to have a mole
under his left eye?
I couldn't see one earlier.
Why are you all talking nonsense?
If he isn't Dong-chan, then who is he?
When they investigated his phone,
they found a strange text.
It said, he would make sure
to succeed with the experiment.
He talked about "the experiment"
in several places.
Right.
I'm certain that Dong-chan
was involved in an experiment.
So? What kind of experiment
are you saying he did?
What are you thinking?
Clones.
She's right.
Anyway,
before Dong-chan talks to us first,
don't ask him anything.
Okay.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I couldn't send you on a cruise
like I promised.
I wasn't there
for your last moments either.
Dad...
Dad?
Dong-chan, what are you doing out here?
Aren't you going to bed?
Gosh. You surprised me.
I just...
What are you looking at?
Dad?
Dong-chan. Goodnight.
(When are you coming back, Mi-ran?)
Mi-ran.
(Mom cooked Mi-ran's favorite food.
She said Mi-ran's always with us.)
(Honey, when are you coming back?)
(Why aren't you coming?
I'm waiting for you.)
(Honey, I'm waiting for you to come back.)
(Dong-chan.)
(I miss you.)
Do you feel okay?
We'll take you to the hospital
once you're done eating.
No, it's okay.
I feel so much better
now that I got some sleep.
Must you go back to school?
Why don't you get some more rest?
I rested for 20 years.
I should get back to my daily life.
We always had hope that you'd come back.
So we filed for a leave of absence
every single year.
We've also kept your number alive.
But I came back a little late.
-Didn't I?
-Don't say that.
You didn't come back late.
My gosh, even if I end up
dying tomorrow, I'd die a peaceful death.
Why would you say something like that?
The new semester just started.
And there's not much time
for me to achieve
everything I should've done
during the past 20 years.
I should live a diligent life.
I need to graduate and get a job.
Yes, you're right.
You can do everything you want.
But before that,
there's something I need to take care of.
Director Ma.
-I'm so glad you're...
-What in the world
happened here?
Professor Hwang got into an accident
two hours before the experiment
was supposed to end.
Then how were we able
to wake up in 20 years?
Was Professor Hwang
the person who woke us up?
Dissociative amnesia.
He woke up from a coma in 20 years.
And with his subconscious tenacity,
he woke you guys up
and lost consciousness again.
(You could say his body reacted
faster than his brain.)
(His subconsciousness that's been
dormant for 20 years)
(is what caused him to wake you up.)
(You could say it's similar)
(to a sleep disorder.)
They why does everyone think he's dead?
His car exploded.
(Someone tried to kill him.)
(If he found out that Professor Hwang
managed to stay alive,)
(he would've tried to kill him again.)
So we made it seem
like he was dead.
Professor Hwang and I went
to the same medical school.
(I don't know why,
but he was always nervous.)
(Right before the accident,
he called and desperately asked me)
(to handle everything
if anything bad happened to him.)
Did you find the culprit?
I guess we can't ask the cops
to investigate since the statute
of limitations has already expired.
I'm sure it has something to do
with the cryonics experiment.
We'll only be able to find out
once Professor Hwang wakes up.
I couldn't tell this to anyone
for the past 20 years
because I couldn't trust anyone.
Did you meet Ko Mi-ran?
No, not yet.
Mi-ran's mother knew
that she was taking part
in the cryonics experiment.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell your parents
that you were participating
in the cryonics experiment.
I was worried that the experiment
might get exposed
and put Professor Hwang in grave danger.
I'm really sorry.
Hey.
Dong-chan, did you sleep well?
Ha-young.
I want to meet Ha-young.
-Thank you.
-Good work, everyone.
Thanks.
Hello?
Aren't you Na Ha-young, the news anchor?
Can I get an autograph?
Thank you.
Dong-chan.
Have you been well?
It's been 20 years already.
Yes, I know.
I'm really late, aren't I?
I should've listened to you
and gave up on the experiment
had I known that this was going to happen.
It's all in the past.
I already forgot about it all.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep my promise.
What did I tell you?
I told you not to do the experiment.
Why did you do that? Why?
You told me that you won't regret it.
But look what happened!
I'm sorry.
But I am
thankful that you are
still alive.
I have to go back to work.
I'll call you later.
Is there no way of resolving
hypothermia of the two people
who woke up?
Nothing for now.
During the first experiment,
the dolphin died
because we couldn't resolve
the problem of hypothermia.
Professor Hwang researched for years
to resolve this problem.
And in the end, he created
a medicine that returns
the body temperature to normal.
Professor Hwang is the only one
who could bring back
the two frozen people to life.
That means
if Professor Hwang doesn't wake up,
the two of them will remain in danger.
(Promissory note)
Is she
Ko Mi-ran?
Oh, no.
That's Ma Dong-chan. It's definitely him.
Mi-ran.
I looked everywhere for you.
Are you all...
What are you...
Give me back my 20 years.
Give me back my life that you took away!
-What's going on?
-Who is that?
Let's talk somewhere else.
Cut! Okay.
We're rehearsing.
Go on, everyone. Get moving.
Cameras, come on out.
Isn't she that woman
who took part in that experiment
with Dong-chan?
What?
Yes.
Explain yourself. How can this happen?
Twenty years?
Wait, did you say it's only
for a day when it was 20 years?
What are you talking about?
I woke up with you.
I can't believe this.
I'm sorry, Mi-ran.
I'm also frustrated that this is
the only thing I can say to you.
But... But I'm a victim too.
That's your problem!
How will you pay me back
for the 20 years I lost?
My parents and my brother also
waited for me with frustration.
How will you compensate them
for that pain?
I know how you feel.
I feel the same way.
This is driving me crazy too!
Well, you know,
this is what happened.
Professor Hwang got into an accident
a few hours before
we were supposed to wake up.
We ended up sitting in there for 20 years
when it was supposed to be a day.
How am I going to live now?
How can I jump over 20 years
and live my life?
I hope this is a dream.
But this isn't a dream. It's reality.
I didn't get to see my brother grow up.
I couldn't get married or get a job.
I just slept in the capsule for 20 years.
That's my problem too. I suddenly woke up,
and I'm now 52 years old.
I mean, do you think I'm in my right mind?
We're in the same situation.
But wait.
We're alive.
The experiment was a success,
and we came back alive.
Think about it. Isn't this amazing?
We made history.
Isn't it amazing how we're the first
to survive the cryonics experiment?
Mi-ran, let us remember that glory
while living the remaining life.
Let us overcome this hardship together.
No!
No?
Anyway, Mr. Ma.
-Yes?
-Why do you speak casually to me?
What?
(Director Ma Dong-chan of TBO is)
(still missing after 50 days
without any traces.)
(There is no evidence or trace left
regarding the incident,)
(which makes
the investigation much harder.)
(-The missing...)
-President Kim!
Wait.
(The best TV show
chosen by the viewers...)
What is it? What's going on?
This is bad. There's another one.
What do you mean, there's another one?
I mean that there is
another one who was frozen.
Is this buy 1 get 1 free?
Why do they keep showing up?
-This is driving me insane.
-It's Ko Mi-ran.
-The woman who joined...
-She showed up?
Yes, the frozen female showed up.
But she has been thawed.
This is driving me crazy.
What are we going to do?
What do you think?
Should we hold hands
and run away together?
Why should we hold hands?
I'll come up with a follow-up
measure and call you again.
-Don't you dare run away.
-How can I run away?
Ms. Ko. I'm sure my passport has expired.
How can you joke around at this point?
I'm not joking.
I'm telling you
that I don't intend on running away.
What a jerk.
What? Wait
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
I'm glad.
I mean, I'm glad that the woman
from the experiment is okay.
Yes.
Ha-young.
Do you want
to meet up tomorrow?
Let's meet at the restaurant
we last saw each other.
That restaurant
closed down a long time ago.
Has it been 15 years?
I see.
The newsroom staff are having
a team dinner tomorrow,
so it won't work.
I see. Okay.
What's wrong with me?
I came to register
as I want to return to school.
You can do it at home on your computer.
What's your major and student number?
My major is Chinese Literature,
and I enrolled in 1996.
My name is Ko Mi-ran.
"Chinese Literature". "1996"
I'm sorry? "1996"?
By the way, did your name
used to be Hwang Byung-sim?
You received mail from
your high school alumni association.
It's under the name Hwang Byung-sim.
-Hello.
-Hey, there.
-Hi.
Hello.
Ko Mi-ran?
Excuse me.
(Women's Restroom)
I'm sorry.
(Mi-ran, why can't I reach you?)
(Did you really go to the US?)
(The number you have dialed
is not in service.)
(Mi-ran, I'm sorry.)
(I'm to blame.)
(Please forgive me.)
(I heard you moved to the US.)
(Did you leave because of me?)
(It's bad to ghost people.)
(You need to fix that.)
That idiot.
-What?
-Say that again.
What's wrong with you?
What can you do in your state?
What's wrong with the state I'm in?
I'm healthier than you.
You're not all there.
You were frozen then thawed,
so you're not very fresh.
I'm fresher than you.
Wait, Dong-chan.
I'm looking into a job for you.
Why don't you work in Programming Team
for a few months and take it easy
before you return?
I'll just get back to work right away.
Do you think this job is a joke?
If anyone takes broadcasting
more seriously than I do,
then I dare them to step up.
Do you take it more seriously
than I do? What about you?
I almost died while working.
Of course I don't think it's a joke.
Dong-chan, you should take a break.
I took a break for 20 years.
Do you want me to rest more?
I need to finish the program
I never got to finish
20 years ago with my own hands.
Since I started it,
I should see it to the end.
It's been 20 years.
"Infinite Experiment Paradise"
ended 20 years ago.
What do you mean?
I never said it could end,
so who ended it?
Hong-suk, be honest with me.
Are you scared?
Gosh, scared of what?
If people find out that a director
who disappeared 20 years ago
has come back,
they'll realize
that the station covered it up.
-When that happens...
-Stop, stop!
No one covered up anything.
If you won't take me in,
I'll go to a different station.
I'm Ma Dong-chan.
They'll fight over me.
-Dong-chan!
Where are you going?
-Yes, where are you going? No.
-No.
(Please Help him.)
(Father... Father!)
Hurry up and get out.
Just do your business.
I'm your dad, it's okay.
Dad, there are boundaries you must keep
even with your family members.
Get out now.
I said, hurry up!
Gosh. I was in here first.
Hello, Dad.
Dong-chan, it's me.
Yes. Right.
I'm glad I ran into you.
Can you dye my hair?
I have so many grey hairs.
Okay.
Honey, hurry up and eat.
Dong-chan, come and eat.
Dong-chan, let's eat.
Come along.
My gosh.
Grandma, let's move to a place
with two bathrooms.
This place is too cramped for me.
Plus, Uncle Dong-chan is back.
Okay, let's do that.
I'm going to live diligently from now on.
I'm going to work really hard
now that my son has come back alive.
After what happened to you,
Mom totally gave up on everything.
I only lived because I had to.
I didn't live because I wanted to.
-Eat up.
-I'm sorry, Mom.
Why are you sorry?
Eat up.
Uncle Dong-chan, where were you
all this time?
My dad keeps saying
you're his older brother,
but you're young enough to be his son.
-Well...
-By any chance,
did you become a vampire?
There's this show on Youtube
called "Vampire Love".
And the male lead doesn't age
because he's under a spell.
Is that what happened to you?
What? "Youtube"?
Yes, you should quit work
and start a Youtube channel.
Elementary school kids
don't watch TV these days.
Dong-chan, she doesn't
take after her dad at all.
So she's very straightforward.
You seem a little flustered.
She's crazy about dramas.
We were always so busy,
so we let her watch TV a lot.
And she learned about life through dramas.
So she's a little overloaded.
Uncle, you should broadcast
our restaurant on TV.
Then we'll get a lot of customers.
There's this show where they help
unsuccessful restaurants.
I thought you didn't watch TV.
How do you know that?
Even if I don't watch TV,
I still need to know the trend.
I already know TV shows have
written scripts beforehand.
Just eat your food.
Did Dong-ju spend the night out again?
Dong-ju spent the night out?
She rarely comes home.
That darn brat sleeps outside?
You should shave her head
and stop her from going outside.
-Dong-chan.
-My gosh, you startled me.
Dong-chan, welcome.
I missed you.
I missed you, my brother.
You reek of alcohol.
Do you have any idea
how much I missed you?
Okay, I get it. Will you please let go?
Because of what happened you,
I can't live a single day without alcohol.
Will you stop drinking, you brat?
I got a call from the rehab clinic
for alcoholism.
They told me you missed
three days of treatment.
I went there and got my treatment!
Then we had some drinks afterward.
My goodness, you crazy brat.
I don't think it was a good idea
to send her there, Mom.
What's the point of going there
when she drinks after her treatment?
My goodness.
Dad.
I'm sorry.
Okay, ready?
-1, 2, 3.
-Let's take another one.
-Sit down.
-1, 2, 3.
-You look pretty.
Really? Let me take a look.
("Miss You Much", Leslie)
Excuse me.
Do you have Leslie Cheung's latest album?
How many albums has he released?
That album was released
to commemorate his death.
-What?
-Leslie Cheung's dead.
He died 16 years ago.
Leslie Cheung
is dead?
("Miss You Much")
Leslie Cheung!
(Ma Dong-chan)
Finally.
Okay, okay.
Now that I take a proper look,
you've aged so much.
Did you live recklessly?
I forgot to take my botox,
so my skin looks a little saggy.
Plus, I'm the chief,
and I'm pretty old now.
Yes, I know. So what?
-Hello, sir.
Hey, guys. Keep up the good work.
Always focus on sincerity
rather than the ratings.
A director isn't a salesman.
You know that, right?
-Yes, sir!
-Good.
What a joke.
You'd better teach them
how to get good ratings.
Okay.
And is this the army or something?
Why are you being so strict?
(The main anchor for the
nine o'clock news will get replaced.)
(Let's just cover this up.)
We can't do that. We should check
if he's dead or alive.
What if something went wrong and he died?
He's probably dead already!
(I didn't have a choice.
There was nothing I could do.)
Dong-chan.
(Let's kiss each other
until we break our front teeth.)
I'm free on Friday.
Would you like
to meet?
(Melting Me Softly)
(You're a new face.
Have you worked in this field?)
(What do you think you're doing?)
Let's have celebrities go to an island
and make them cook
three meals a day there.
(I'm afraid your creativity
got frozen that day)
along with your brain.
Are you serious?
(-This is Ko Mi-ran.
-Ko Mi-ran wishes to meet us.)
(I ask for compensation.)
Be quiet!
(Aren't you cold, Dong-chan?)
(You haven't aged at all.
You look exactly the same.)
I was frozen in the freezer, okay?
Director Ma, can you get me a job?
A job?