=Intense Love=
=Episode 20=
Honey.
Who's that?
A friend.
Hello, Mr. Wu.
This is Zhou Shiyun.
Yes, my brother had dinner with you.
I want to talk to you
about some of your projects.
Okay, see you.
Long time no see, Mr. Li.
For the spokesman project
you mentioned before,
we can discuss it.
Me...
I'm Wu Di, the celebrity
agent of Su Jinbei.
What?
Signed it.
Can you...
Hello.
Painful.
What's the matter?
Let me give you rub.
How is it?
It's comfortable.
You just give me a message every day
for two hours from now on.
Two hours.
Is it necessary?
We have money,
we can hire professionals
I think you are professional.
Here.
Harder.
Too hard
I said I'm not professional.
You mean it.
No.
-Yes.
-How can I?
Yingying, I made soup.
Do you want some?
No.
The popular actor Xu Jiawei
exposed a lot in a live video.
Because of the video,
he was affected greatly.
The personality his company
shaped for him collapsed.
Jiawei.
Are you okay?
Do you like that?
I like it very much, thank you.
Fool.
You are so happy for a balloon.
It's a present from you.
You're right.
You will be shut out by all media.
You have to take the consequence.
You're not a child,
you should know this.
The traditional logic is
expressed by natural language
while the modern logic
uses symbols as its major carrier.
So we call the modern logic
symbolic logic.
I knew that you wouldn't listen to it.
You are afraid of losing.
I am not afraid of losing.
Well, in three minutes,
if you don't fall asleep, I lose, okay?
Yingying.
Give up.
You're not my opponent.
Impossible, my Wuxiang magic skill
is on the ninth level.
It must have a result today.
Xiaoyu'er.
Actually.
I don't want to fight with you.
I just want to.
I want to see your face.
Don't be afraid.
I'll pass my strength of 500 years to you.
I want you to live.
It wouldn't help.
Why?
I will be shut out by all media.
I don't want to live.
Jiawei.
Wake up, Jiawei.
No, I have to save Jiawei.
Please.
No problem.
Okay.
Where are you going?
To my hometown.
For what?
It is an emergency.
Don't mind me, brother.
I've ordered a car.
Be careful.
Text me when you're at home.
I know.
This kid.
Sorry.
Go on.
You went to the book store with Dr. Zhou.
How can you be spotted
by a reader passing by.
I really don't know.
I remembered there was no one there.
It's okay, Mr. Wang.
Everyone is blessing them.
Don't worry.
Did you see the reviews?
Yes.
I'll read it for you.
Listen.
What a happy couple.
I believe in love again.
Beibei must be happy.
They are all positive.
And this.
I've watched the plays of
Beibei since I was young.
Now she's engaged,
I suddenly realized
that I'm no longer young.
See.
No longer young.
What's that?
This is a very dangerous signal.
Jinbei.
You centered at youth operas.
Now you are a mature woman to the public.
You will have less and less opportunities.
Be careful.
Okay, I know.
According to all,
the suspense detective drama The Pursuer
booted today.
The leading actress is the popular
young actress Gao Zitong.
Gao Zitong started her career
from the women's League.
Her comprehensive quality is strong.
In the popular love
developing variety show.
Heartbeats,
she attracted many fans.
Now Gao Zitong...
It's okay, Beibei.
We have other projects.
Don't worry.
This is the script, Zitong.
Something's wrong.
Come here.
-What's wrong? Let's see.
-Okay.
Come on.
Zitong.
Sorry,
please wait for a while.
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Producer Jiang?
Don't mention it.
Zheng Ying got hurt in
the movement shooting at Group B.
She's sent to the hospital.
Is it serious?
Can she continue the shooting?
Probably not.
Talk to you later
I have to contact another actress.
Hold on.
Producer Jiang.
I've got a good person.
Look at the camera.
Left.
Right.
Nod.
Okay.
What's the matter?
I put your face recognition
in my phone,
you can use my phone
whenever you want.
Give me yours.
Put mine in,
so we can see each other's phones.
There's will be no secrets.
Okay.
Why should I see your phone.
I won't see yours
I just think in this way,
we would be one person
with no barriers.
Whatever.
Hi, Didi.
Do you know who just called me?
Who's that?
Jiang Tao.
The producer of The pursuer.
Why did he call.
He said
the supporting actress had an accident.
He wanted you to fill in.
I got angry and scolded him then refused.
Gently.
Why did you refuse?
Have a try!
Serious? Su Jinbei.
What a shame.
You can only play the supporting actress.
You are Su Jinbei.
Isn't it hard to shoot plays lately?
A few days ago you and Wang told me this.
You forget?
No.
It's two different things.
You can't lose your dignity, can you?
And who's the leading actress.
Gao Zitong.
We don't have to please her.
I think it's okay.
Gently.
What are you doing, Wu Di?
Can you stop calling me
in times of this.
You.
Do you feel shame.
What are you thinking?
I'm having a message.
Xiao's doing message on me.
Say something.
Hey, superstar.
This is Xiao Yuansong.
I'm giving her a massage.
Are you sure?
You're not bullying her?
You...
What's wrong with you?
Is Dr. Zhou here?
Dr. Zhou.
Yes.
Look at your Jinbei.
Her mind is full of nonsense.
Let's get to the point.
Are you sure you want this role?
Nothing I can't accept.
What do you say, honey?
It's not bad.
Then please discuss this for me, Didi.
Okay, I'll handle this.
Bye.
I finally have to work.
I'll work hard.
Come on!
Hello, I'm Wuque.
I'm back.
Master.
Now you're finally here
for live streaming on Shuabao.
You are great.
I've decided.
You can sign the contract anytime.
Great.
Money will be transferred
to your account on time.
Mr. Shui.
Jiawei, where are you?
At home, what's wrong?
Nothing.
About the termination of contract.
I want to talk to you.
Termination of contract.
Jiawei.
What's your plan?
I haven't made up my mind.
I may take some rest
and concentrate on my music.
It's good to pursue your dream.
Jiawei.
Although there's some setbacks,
you can get through this
with your ability.
I trust you.
Anyway.
We've been working together for so long,
I wish you can go further.
Thank you.
By the way,
the person...
that paid the liquidated damages for me
doesn't want to see me?
What's his name.
He didn't say.
He said he's Wuque.
Wuque.
Jiawei.
Mr. Shui, I want to ask
when did you meet him yesterday.
Yesterday afternoon.
Specific time?
About 3:00.
Stop, that's her.
Aren't you cold in so little clothes?
No, I wear more than you.
Producer Jiang.
-Producer Jiang, hello.
-Producer Jiang.
Zitong.
Producer Jiang.
-How do you feel?
-It's good.
-You've been working hard lately.
-What a snob.
They are all like this.
I need to take this call.
You go busy.
Hello.
Don't worry about being annoying.
Tell Su Jinbei I need to
read the script with her.
Go.
Jinbei.
Zitong wants to read the script with you.
Okay.
Give me the script...
I've drawn out the lines for you.
Beibei, I'll leave for a while.
You go busy.
I am busy now.
Be careful.
Don't worry.
Zitong, Jinbei is here.
I had a cold.
It's pretty bad.
I'm afraid I would infect you.
You just stand outside the door.
Okay.
I improved the script.
You read it first.
Okay.
You also have today.
Enjoy the pain I used to endure.
It's so cold.
I said don't come in.
It doesn't matter.
I'm not afraid of being infected by you.
But I don't like you.
What?
Su Jinbei, who are you?
Because you're lucky?
Everyone has to circle around you.
Everyone has to sacrifice for you.
Who do you think you are?
Have you ever suffered for work?
Will work hard on shooting
and dedicate all to work like me?
Why can you succeed?
You're a pest.
You...
Because of Xu Jiawei?
I had nothing with him, really.
I know.
Even if there's nothing between you,
he's willing to sacrifice
everything for you.
And I, who's willing to
sacrifice everything for him...
became a clown in front of you.
Get out.
Get the hell out of here.
Why is Zitong still not here?
We've been waiting for two hours.
Miss Gao is here.
Miss Gao. Zitong.
Director Zhao.
I improved the script.
Miss Gao.
You are enemies for life
and she is the ultimate villain.
First time you meet,
she was beaten to death by you
and she can't fight back.
That doesn't make sense, right?
I think it's okay.
I'm the female detective,
representing justice.
I'm rubbing the evil under my feet.
Isn't it fun to watch?
From the perspective of drama,
it's fun.
But it's your fist meeting.
First,
I can't continue the rest.
Find a script writer.
I can find one for you if you can't.
Easy! Easy!
Director, Gao Zitong is so popular now.
Even the investor wants her in this.
Please endure it.
-It's just a scene.
-No.
You have to make sure
Su Jinbei is willing to act.
It's okay, director.
I'll do it.
Stop!
It's you.
How did you know?
See how I tidy up you!
Stop.
Who said that?
Brother.
So handsome.
Who are you?
Why are you interrupting here?
He knows Jinbei?
Are you okay, sister-in-law?
What are you doing here, brother?
Let me introduce to you.
This is Mr. Zhou of Haohan Group,
the investor of The Pursuer.
Let's give him a round of applause.
Investor.
He is the secret boss.
Right.
It's said that filming is
only a small part of business...
of the Haohan Group.
He seldom takes this up personally.
I don't know why he came here in person.
Something's happening.
Guys.
The Haohan Group will support
the project as usual...
and I will invest more...
to make The Pursuer into a fine art.
Great.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
There's no need to thank me
because it has nothing to do with you.
I hereby announce that...
Gao Zitong is cancelled
because she is not qualified.
Effective immediately.
Why do you say I'm not qualified?
You don't have the moral integrity of art.
Funny.
Moral integrity of art.
Don't be sarcastic here.
You just want me to leave.
Okay.
But you have to pay me liquidated damages.
No problem.
But now,
please leave.
Okay.
I don't even like this senseless play.
There are other people out there
begging to get me.
Su Jinbei.
Let's wait and see.
Zitong.
Finally.
Jinbei.
What else help do you need?
No.
Bu brother,
is it unfair for Gao Zitong to fire her.
Jinbei, you are too kind.
Did you know...
a bunch of things of yours
were made up by her.
What?
She recommended you
as the supporting actress,
so that she can humiliate you here,
and the video that...
caused misunderstandings between
you and Shiyun was also sent by her.
Even the earlier news
saying that you hit her...
was created by her.
There is such a thing?
The world is not as simple as you think.
Some people is afraid of the light.
They can only hide
in the darkness quietly.
But brother,
how do you know this?
Why did you investigate this?
I didn't investigate.
I did nothing.
I was just listening to the arrangement
and showed up here.
Then...
Who?
Okay, I have some business to do.
Let's have dinner together some other day.
Okay.
Thank you so much for everything.
It's my duty.
Are you busy, Mr. Shui?
I'm free lately.
Can you give me more projects?
I can't take care of your projects now.
Why did you say this?
Did I do something wrong?
You did it yourself.
How dare Zhao...
said that I changed the script
lost my temper and disrespected them.
Nonsense.
Is it?
You bad name is spreading.
Do you know?
No director
wants to cooperate with you.
How could this be?
From now on,
I can't help you anymore.
I'm sorry.
Is Wuque online today?
No.
Prepare to destroy the tower.
Have you seen the live broadcast of Wuque?
Your tactics are very much like his.
I've seen the skills.
The skills are almost the same.
Follow me, quick.
What's going on?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I didn't have a good rest.
I can't sleep at night.
What's wrong?
I can't forget something.
I really miss the days
in after-school classes...
I could sleep tight when
the teacher began his class.
The traditional logic is
expressed by natural language.
My friend gave me
a music with good hypnotic effect.
The moment I hear it I can fall asleep.
I don't believe this.
Okay, you can listen to it yourself.
If you don't feel sleepy, I lose.
How did Yingying know
the conversation between me and Wuque.
Did she...?
Hello.
You found the license plate?
Wuque.
Su Jinbei.
You don't let me live.
So won't I.
I hereby announce that...
Gao Zitong is cancelled because
she is not qualified for her job.
Effective immediately.
No.
Why do you say I'm not qualified?
You don't have the moral integrity of art.
Su Jinbei.
Let's wait and see.
Zitong.
The more you treat me like this
the harder I want to succeed.
I will never give up.
Zitong.
Director Zhang is in
the office of Mr. Shui.
Which Director Zhang?
The famous Director Zhang.
And it seems that he has a project
and wanted to cooperate with us.
So...
Zitong.
Mr. Zhang, I'm Gao Zitong.
I've seen your movies since childhood.
No... No.
Director Zhang.
Nice to see you.
I like your Flying Clouds best
and Red Bean.
I want to recommend myself...
to be the leading
actress of your next movie.
You can do this, Gao Zitong, come on.
Director Zhang.
This is our favorite
young actor Ouyang Minghao.
Director Zhang.
Nice to meet you.
Let him act with Su Jinbei.
With your guidance,
this project will be a success.
I agree.
Zitong.
What?
What's the matter?
Zitong.
Zitong, open the door.
I need to talk to you.
Zitong.
My house is this simple.
Laugh if you want.
I don't care.
These are the promises
you made for yourself.
So what?
Because of you,
now I can't even be an actress.
Why do I care about this?
Zitong.
Let's talk.
I don't need it.
But I need an explanation.
Why a person I take as my friend...
would do
such surprising things behind my back.
She has her respectful dream,
but why did she waste
her time in hurting me.
Why?
You hide so many things in your heart,
but you solve problems
in such a way that hurt us both.
You see me as your friend,
I thought you were pretending.
Why would I?
Yep.
You seemed to have everything.
You don't have to win others' respect
with fake emotions.
You can win your love
without sacrifice.
How can you feel...
the pain of wanting
something but can't have it.
See,
how close we used to be.
We laughed so happily.
Do you know why...
even when I'm successful
in front of everyone,
I still choose
to live in this simple house.
Because I have to save money.
I have to pinch and scrape.
Me and Jiawei all came
back from abroad training.
We need a lot of money
to plan our future.
Ridiculous?
You've taken up all his heart...
and I'm still planning our future
as a one-sided wish.
I think every tear for him
is mocking me.
Even the air I'm breathing is mocking me.
Why did I treat you like that?
Because you are rich in love.
Everyone loves you...
and I own nothing
I don't want to take these alone.
I want you to join me.
Is this reason good enough for you?