=Intense Love=
=Episode 17=
You are so happy for a balloon.
It's a present from you.
Yingying.
I still feel that the present
is too simple.
Then, Jiawei.
Can you help me realize a small wish?
No problem.
I want to take a picture with you.
It's okay.
No problem.
Come here.
One, Two, Three.
You are back.
Brother.
You are still up?
I'm not sleepy.
Your job as an assistance.
Is it busy?
As I thought...
It's special today.
By the way.
After I left,
did my eldest brother say something?
He didn't.
But...
How long are you going to play?
You think I'm just
playing around with him?
Otherwise.
I have my plan.
Think about your future.
Don't get in too deep.
The master's online, let's do it.
Little fish, can I ask you
a question first?
What?
If someone you trust deceived you,
what would you do?
I won't forgive him.
What if it's a white lie.
That depends who it is.
The emerald earrings are passed
on from generation to generation...
by Zhou's daughter-in-laws.
Grandma gave it to my mother,
now it's given to you.
I see, my second brother
must see you as his Ms. Right.
Then I'll send him a present.
Mr. Zhou.
There is a gift at your door,
please check it.
Surprise!
The present is you?
What? You don't like it?
Why did you get up so early?
My honey gave me something important.
I want to give you a present as well.
One moment.
There is one for you.
I'll take your present.
This one was given by my mother
when I was young.
Yours.
My mother asked for it from the temple.
They are a pair.
Why didn't my mother tell me.
Honey.
It means that we've been connected
to each other a long time ago.
What a world?
Did you eat?
Hold on.
Recently, in a popular
love developing variety show.
Heartbeats.
Gao Zitong received the affection
of many male participants...
because of her cheerful
and challenging personality.
During the interview, Gao Zitong said,
no matter in life or in the show,
she always took work
and love life seriously.
She hoped that her contribution
could be rewarded.
Gao Zitong really works hard.
With these efforts,
she could definitely
expect the same in return.
Thank you.
You sure you want to ride on this?
Yes, I am.
If you want to drive,
you can take my car.
That's different.
What's different?
You might see me like this now,
but I grew up in a very traditional
and doctrinal environment.
Whatever I do,
I have to follow my parents' rules.
I loved these trains when I was young,
but my parents only
allowed me to play once.
It's disappointing,
so I was always dragging
home while crying.
You haven't told me
much about stories of your childhood.
You like it?
I...
I can tell you when I have time.
Show me the tickets.
-It's our turn.
-Give me the ticket.
Who will take the train?
He.
Are you serious?
It's a mini-train for children.
We really want to.
I want to take this.
Yes, yes.
If you want to play,
you can try the Ferris wheel
and pirate ship over there.
Go.
No.
We are here for this today.
But we have a rule
that adults can't play this.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
No, you came here for this.
Hello, mom.
Beibei.
How are you doing with Shiyun?
It's good, what's up?
Nothing, I'm just asking.
Shiyun is really considerate.
After he came back from the mountain area,
he went here
to apologize to me and your father.
He explained a lot.
I see.
Mom.
Do you remember
the peace talisman you gave me?
Why did Shiyun have one as well.
Peace talisman.
I almost forget.
That's right.
Why haven't I heard you...
mention a lot about Shiyun's mother.
I have mentioned her.
Because you didn't
care about this marriage at first...
and you forget.
It's all my fault.
Tell me about it.
We've been good friends since childhood.
You know this.
We grew up in the same Lane.
Then she married to another city,
so we seldom met afterwards.
After she had Shiyun,
she went back to our home town once.
You were young.
You don't know.
His mother saw you are a little girl.
She liked you very very much.
So we decided a child betrothal
for you two kids.
Really?
I have no recollection of that.
Because Shiyun's mother died young.
Shiyun is a poor kid.
If his mother could see this in heaven...
and knew that his son was so excellent...
and was so happy and sweet
with my daughter,
she would be really happy.
Yes, she would.
Of course.
-Will you?
-Yes.
-Let's go.
Watch out.
Watch out!
Slow down.
Quick reaction.
I got it from escaping from
the reporters with Beibei.
You have to grasp these
when escaping from reporters?
Of course.
Hurry... Hurry.
You have to come as well.
I'm going to have to pass.
No.
Go! Go! Go!
I'll turn on the electricity switch first.
Okay, okay, okay.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Watch out!
Close the door.
Good.
Let's go.
Here we go.
-It's funny, right?
-Yes.
Cool!
Funny.
What are you doing?
-Let's go.
-Hurry up!
Hurry up! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Quick.
Go! Go! Go!
Hurry up!
Stop!
Exciting?
Hey.
Dr. Zhou.
The director wants you
to take Dr. Xiao's shift.
Okay, coming.
What happened to Dr. Xiao?
I've never seen him since I came back.
Dr. Xiao asked for leave, don't you know?
I see.
Ms. Su.
You don't look good.
Do you need some rest?
Thank you.
Please hand me my phone.
I had my period. It hurts.
Okay.
Thank you, Doctor.
Please wait outside.
I'll give you the case in a moment.
Isn't Wu Di here with you?
No, I can't get in touch with her.
It's weird, where are the two people?
I'll go pick you up after work.
Fine.
Okay, Dr. Zhou
I'm off work.
Okay, cut.
Everyone!
We are now coming to a wrap!
Thank you for your efforts, director.
-Thank you, director.
-Ms. Su.
You've done good.
You finished shooting
when you don't feel well.
It's my duty. Thank you all.
-You are welcome.
-Thank you, thank you.
Okay, just put them there.
Thank you all.
-Don't forget your things.
-Okay.
You are really here.
Um, I brought you brown sugar ginger tea.
That's very kind of you.
Why do you wear so little?
You have to keep warm.
I need to work.
Come here.
Arm.
Come on, it's warm in the car.
Where's Wu Di?
I need to,
I've never seen her since I came back.
It's weird.
Xiao didn't come for work these days.
What a coincidence.
But Didi is not a kind of a person
that would leave work behind.
Anything happened?
Let's go.
I win.
You learn so fast.
Of course.
My name doesn't come from nothing.
Again?
Who's it?
I'll answer the door.
Wu Di.
Wu Di, are you home?
Coming.
How did you come?
What happened to you?
I can't get in touch with you.
Is it your home?
Xiao, you are really a walking virus.
Everywhere you go is affected by you.
Thank you for your praise.
You want to give up your life?
He's a doctor.
He knows much more than me.
I don't want to see him suffer.
All these years,
I've been alone...
and I've been more and
more picky towards men.
I also feel less and less secure.
When he broke into my life,
I didn't know what to do.
Because he is a trouble.
Then,
I realized that I'm just afraid
to get hurt again.
I'm afraid that once I open my heart,
it will never be closed again.
But it doesn't matter now.
That's it.
What the hell are you
looking at me like that for?
Late stage of uremia.
I don't believe you.
You can,
but you have to believe the report.
Anyway.
This is something I can't overlook.
You know it and I know it.
Curing this disease is really painful.
I've seen much,
so I don't want to torture myself.
What about Wu Di?
Have you thought about that?
She supports my decision.
She may not want you to suffer.
But have you thought about it.
If you gave up the treatment now,
she would lose you forever.
It means she have to
accept this cruel fact...
and send you off with a smile.
Professor Ma.
I'm sorry to trouble you about that.
It's fine.
I've understood the situation of Dr. Xiao.
However, I suggest he have
another through inspection.
Xiao Yuansong.
For all these years,
I've been afraid of stepping
onto the same path in relationship.
I finally accepted him,
but now.
I just hope I can be with
him for one more day...
even just one more minute.
Tomorrow is his birthday.
Maybe I should be thankful...
that I have the chance to
spend his birthday with him.
He loves surprises.
I'll prepare a last surprise for him.
Isn't this a nice place?
It's my first time here as well.
It's well and
I heard the food is good as well.
How's the result of Dr. Xiao.
-Is there a result?
-It'll be out till tomorrow.
Tomorrow is Dr. Xiao's birthday.
Wu Di prepared a gathering
in secret for him.
She wants to let him say
goodbye to some friends...
in case he has regrets.
Can you secretly
inform his friends for me?
Xiao doesn't know?
It's a surprise.
How could he know.
It's Wu Di's little present.
Just help me.
You don't have to inform too many people,
just some close ones.
All right, I got it.
Thank you.
Why is there a new advertisement board?
Yes, we changed it yesterday.
Why the spokesperson changed?
Wasn't it Su Jinbei?
Why is it Gao Zitong now?
Who is Gao Zitong?
You don't know Gao Zitong?
Do you watch Heartbeats?
She's hot on that variety show.
She's now almost as popular as Su Jinbei.
Su Jinbei has come out for many years.
She's really not as popular
as new actresses now.
Yeah.
Honey, I want this.
-Okay?
-Just order it.
This looks nice.
Order it.
I'll order more dishes.
What do you want to eat?
As you wish.
Zitong, this is the latest activities.
Do you want to see?
I don't know what happened to
the celebrity agent of Su Jinbei.
She has done nothing.
She just gave away all these work to us.
My opportunity was given by Su Jinbei?
No, I didn't mean that.
You earned it on your own.
Dr. Xiao.
This is a big joke.
Xiao.
Are you sick?
You should be serious.
You don't know you are sick or not?
I'm not serious at all.
The first day you know me?
And.
That is a good thing.
You should be happy for me.
Didi asks us to have dinner together.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
You made such a big joke.
Do you have any idea
how it's going to end.
Do you think I should tell her
the good news now?
-You.
-Forget it.
Such a big deal,
I should tell her in person.
I'm not sick.
Thank you, Julie.
You're welcome.
I want to do something for Dr. Xiao.
It's so cold today.
They are coming.
I wore too little.
Wu Di.
Yes.
Hello.
I always saw your picture
on the WeChat moments of Xiao.
It's the first time
to see the real person.
You look much prettier than the pictures.
Thank you!
I heard that you are
the celebrity agent of Su Jinbei.
Yes.
Is Jinbei here today?
-She is...
-I mean I'm her fan.
It's the birthday of Dr. Xiao.
I shouldn't steal his thunder.
Jinbei.
Jinbei is really here.
Okay, don't mind me.
It's the birthday of Dr. Xiao.
It must be hard...
looking after him, right?
Not bad.
It's weird.
He doesn't look so bad.
It's true.
He always has a good body.
When we were in college,
he was the prince of sports.
We didn't expect
that he could catch this disease.
He was not only the prince of sports.
He was also the most handsome boy.
The most handsome? He?
He gave himself that title.
He was so proud of himself.
Well, yes.
He's still like this.
At that time,
the ripped jeans were not so popular.
He was fashion enough
to cut some holes on his jeans...
and wore it to show off.
Yes, yes.
He even went to the downstairs
of girls' dorm building of Art School...
and sang love songs.
Yeah.
What are you talking about?
Wu Di's here.
Don't listen to them.
It never happened.
Sorry, Sorry.
Back then at college we were poor.
We could only eat instant
noodles at the end of each month.
Every time
I would split a bowl of noodles with Xiao.
Now.
I want to have another
bowl of noodles with him.
Don't be too sad.
It's his birthday.
We should be happy
and leave him a happy memory.
-Right!
-Yes, yes.
Be happy.
Cheer up.
Wu Di.
Where should we put the presents?
Here.
Okay.
When will you arrive?
How long?
We're almost there.
Coming right up.
Almost here.
Let's prepare.
Okay, come on.
That... yes.
Here you are.
Put it here.
Xiao.
I see.
You must be really exciting
seeing me coming back from death.
You must want to hug me hard.
Come on.
There's something I want to tell you.
Dr. Xiao, you are here.
Ms. Wu is waiting for you inside.
You came out to pick me up in person.
-You're welcome.
-Come inside.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
You all come.
Yes.
Song.
You are so cruel!
You disappeared for so long.
What did you do recently?
We?
Just busy.
Look!
Do you like it?
Surprise!
What's wrong with you!
You said it's a simple meal,
but you made it so grand.
I hate to say it,
but I have to thank Julie.
-It's romantic.
-Yeah.
But it's your birthday,
I should prepare this for you.
I want to spend your birthday with you.
This is my birthday wish.
Today everything here belongs to you.
So romantic, we can't stand it.
Totally.
Why do you stand so far away?
Are you afraid
that you are so handsome...
that you would steal Dr. Xiao's thunder.
Let's go.
Didi.
I need to talk to you.
We have plenty of time to talk.
Everyone today came for your birthday.
Don't keep them waiting.
Yeah.
Don't stay here.
Totally.
I'm full of your romance.
Leave me some appetite
for the birthday cake.
Totally.
Well.
May I have your attention.
I thank you all.
Thank you all.
In this life, I can have such
a grand birthday party,
I have no regrets.
Nonsense.
I...
It's okay.
What are you doing?
I'm fine.
-It's real, I'm fine.
-Okay, Xiao.
We are buddies for so many years.
I know you are tough.
But you see, today.
I...
All of your friends and families are here.
Don't take this alone.
If you keep doing this,
we would feel terrible.
No, I mean...
What's up?
You really want to make us cry?
I see.
I am rude and strict to you.
You must feel wronged.
Today in front of everyone,
I, Wu Di, promise...
I will no longer be so
strict with Xiao Yuansong.
He can do whatever he wants.
I'll never be mad.
Really?
It's my birthday gift to you.
A word spoken is past recalling.
Good.
Deal.
Okay, Xiao.
I came with a present as well.
That five hundred yuan,
you don't have to return to me.
Five hundred yuan?
What? Want to default?
I don't know who he was?
Bro.
Brother.
God.
Save me.
What are you doing? Xiao.
You do the math.
How much is it with interest.
Do you like the present?
Okay.
Stop it!
Your presents are here.
This guitar is from Song.
What are you doing?
Just coming here is good enough.
See.
Showing off.
Game machine.
Liangzi, is it from you?
Right?
We are buddies for so many years.
So many years, you've not changed.
Yes.
Still the same.
Have a look.
Bro.
Brother.
God.
You always repeat this
sentence when you're begging.
Save me.
Why don't you say it?
I did.
They don't believe me.
I'll say it for you.
Okay, I admit.
I'm a little selfish.
I hope that temporarily, temporarily
this can be a secret.
Why is that?
Isn't this a good thing?