You're being so dramatic!
I'm gonna pay you, right?
Sir, take it easy.
You're groping my breast!
What if I did that to you?
What's going on here?
You need to talk to your people!
Sir.
That's not allowed here.
Not allowed? What do
you mean not allowed?
I don't want him anymore!
His breath stinks!
This bitch!
- Sir, just take it easy!
- Hold on a minute.
Sir, stay right here.
And you! You've been at this for a while!
You're taking it too far!
Sir, you're totally wasted.
- I haven't done anything to you.
- Get him out of here first.
Just get him out.
You all need to talk to your staff!
Are you okay?
Yes, Mama.
She's just being so dramatic!
She acts like she's a princess here.
Even I got my nipple bitten,
and I just dealt with it.
Well, at least I demanded
a huge tip from him.
Honestly, sometimes...
I get into fights because of all of you.
Please, don't be too picky.
Whatever the guests want,
you do it.
Just make up for it
with the drinks. Right?
How else are we going to
make the big money, huh?
That's right, Ma.
Me, I'll do anything for the money!
It's up to us if we
accept the guest.
We can tell just
by looking at them.
Maybe I should pinch all your nipples!
Berna, what they mean is...
you need to learn to
talk nicely to the guests.
You never know, maybe he
just looks like that, but he's loaded!
He looked like a piece of
dirt that grew into a person.
True, Mama! That
guy had a thick wallet.
Only got big bills.
He's just cheap with his tips.
You stole some, didn't you?
You didn't even share any with me.
- Hey, that's enough!
- Mama was the one who took it, anyway.
I just returned his wallet.
That's enough now.
From the moment they sit down...
you need to tell them
what's okay and what's not.
and if they ask for something extra,
they have to match it with cash.
Preach!
Jeez!
I grew old in this bar.
I've been through all of that.
I'll always defend you
as long as I can.
But if you're too uptight about it,
there's nothing I can do, got that?
This bar needs to make money, too.
Good thing Sy isn't here.
If he were, he'd be
cursing all of us out.
Why didn't you put up
with the guest last night?
He's nothing compared to you.
Even if you're sweaty,
you still look enticing.
That's what I like about you.
Just take me home
with you, alright?
How about the register?
It's already planned out.
- Hey man, cheers!
- There we go! Cheers!
- Here, have some food as a chaser, man.
- Yeah, he's already wasted.
- Dude, that's enough.
- You're being embarrassing.
Is it going to take much longer?
Can't you see we're
still having a good time?
Go ahead! You go first.
I'll follow you later.
Hi, Myrna!
You're going to get it later!
[chuckles]
Hey you!
Hey!
- Shhh!
- What are you doing here?
Is your girlfriend here already?
She just got here. But...
she's already asleep. Why?
You haven't come
to see me for weeks!
I'm dried up, daddy!
Wait, wait.
Myrna might see us.
Tomorrow, I promise.
I'll visit you in the afternoon, okay?
She's asleep!
She's asleep.
Did you miss me?
I did, so much!
I was so exhausted last night.
But when I woke up,
you were already snoring.
What are you cooking there?
Hotdogs... and eggs.
What if you just ate my
hotdog and eggs instead,
while I'm banging you up.
You really have the libido of a rabbit!
Only for you.
I’ll hook you up
with a job at the bar.
I'll handle talking to Sy.
We need to hire another bouncer anyway.
Yes! Finally, I'll have
something to do with my life.
Not just sitting around the house!
[chuckles]
Just don't hook up with
any of the girls there, okay?
If I catch you,
I'll chop that off!
Come on! I'm loyal—and this too.
Oh, really?
Where's my coffee?
- Oh!
- I'll just have some water for now.
You're really messing with me.
Don't make me lose
my trust in you, got it?
Uh, sir.
Is Ma'am Myrna here?
What do you need to see her about?
Oh, alright, come in.
Ma'am, she's an applicant.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Have you ever danced in another bar?
No, if I get the job,
this will be my first time.
How old are you and
where are you from?
Eighteen, from Samar.
Samar, huh?
You really came all the
way to Manila just to dance?
To work.
My father passed away.
And I don't know where my mother is.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
Are you a virgin?
Yes, ma'am.
[scoffs] The thing I hate most is a liar.
I actually don't know.
How many boyfriends have you had?
Two.
Two? And none of
them ever touched you?
No. The first one wanted to,
but I refused, so he broke up with me.
The second one forced me.
He tried to go inside, but it hurt.
So I left him. I was scared.
Oh, tell the boss I'm
waiting for his wire transfer.
Just always watch
the cash register.
Because if anything goes missing,
you're going to get in trouble.
The key is hidden in my crotch,
so no one else can get it.
Right, Mama?
We’ll be back in a week.
The boss is still in Taiwan,
he's not back yet.
Alright.
Have a seat over there... sit down.
Have you been paid yet?
- Me?
- Hmm.
Not yet. Sy is always
late at giving out salaries.
He wants us to
always be in debt to him
but there's 30 percent interest.
So when payday comes,
it's all cuts and deductions.
That Chinese man is a swindler.
I saw that Berna has the key, right?
That woman is a suck-up.
She starts rumors about every cashier here,
so be careful of her. Okay?
So... when are you free to start?
Anytime, ma'am. I can start whenever.
Alright, then observe tonight.
If you like it, you
can start tomorrow.
- Really?
- Yes, I'll teach you.
Thank you, ma'am.
Ma... Ma!
Is she available?
Ah, no, she's not working a shift yet.
Why not? What a waste.
Because we're going
to launch her properly.
Don't worry, we'll invite
you to the launching.
You should come!
- You promise?
- Of course!
I'll be back.
Yes, just don't skip it.
- Cheers!
- Enjoy!
Be a little more flirty!
Sexier!
What the hell is that?
Hey, you girl. If you really
want to be a dancer here,
you can't be doing
that TikTok dance!
It needs to be sexier, more provocative.
Your body needs to be aggressive,
like that! That's what the guests want.
And if you want to
get tabled by a client
and get a big tip, you
need to turn them on!
Jeez! You're just wasting my time.
Teach her!
Fix her up, she's dancing like a log.
She's fine, though.
What do you mean "fine"?
She can't just be "fine."
She needs to make
the guests' dicks hard.
Come on? She just started.
You want her to be good immediately.
But don't you see potential in her?
You know, I see myself in her.
If she follows everything I say,
she'll be the star dancer of this bar.
The hottest model that
all the men will come for.
But if she's a pushover,
she'll end up stuck on a table.
Calm down.
Bro, did she pass Ma's test?
It's not that she didn't pass,
it's just a bit touch-and-go.
She should dance for me instead.
I’d make her feet
straighten out with pleasure.
Her feet are both left.
Damn you bro, you're
going to beat me to it.
Do you want to do it together instead?
I'll be the one to straighten her out.
The most awaited launching
of our newest, hottest...
Alluring star of the night,
the one who will warm up your cold night!
Let's all welcome Sassy Pinky!
The men need to be completely
consumed by lust for her first.
Well, I've been consumed
by lust for a while now.
What do you mean?
For me, or for...?
What are you thinking?
Of course, for you!
Don't you dare touch Pinky, okay?
If you touch her, you'll
have to deal with me.
What are you thinking?
Come here!
- Hello!
- Hi!
Is she available?
Uh, I haven't let her be tabled yet.
That's Pinky, she
just turned eighteen.
And she has no experience yet.
She's dancing that good,
without experience?
She's our newest one here.
She's from the province,
so she's fresh and new.
How much?
The price is different just for a table,
and it's also different if
you happen to be her first.
The price is also different
for the private room.
Whatever the cost. Send
her over here, right now.
I'm the one you're talking to,
so I'll handle it.
That's what I like about you!
Don't worry… I'll take care of you.
Alright. Have a seat here,
and I'll call her.
Do you really want to be tabled?
I told you, Ma, I can handle both.
Alright, I'm going to
introduce you to someone.
He rarely comes here.
He's a businessman, rich... and
he's very picky, but he likes you.
But it has to be table only, okay?
If he wants a private room,
then you have to ask me first.
Why?
Well, of course,
you're a star now.
I should be the one
discussing your price.
And he thinks you're completely clueless.
Okay? You're innocent.
Don't make any crass movements.
You need to be completely virgin-like.
And when he touches you,
you have to play hard to get, understood?
But don't do anything that will annoy him,
you have to be sweet.
Then, pretend to hold his arm,
going lower and lower.
Down to his thighs,
then to his crotch.
Cuddle him, make him horny.
In this job, you have to
think like you're an actress.
The most beautiful, sexy star.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, good. Come on.
He wants to bring you
to a private room.
Are you ready?
I don't know.
Dindo is a rabbit,
just like this one.
Okay, ma'am, I really need the
money anyway to pay for my rent.
If that's the case, then go ahead.
Do a great job,
he's a huge tipper.
Let's go
Ah, this is Dindo.
Dindo, this is Pinky.
- Dindo.
- Pinky.
Ah, there. Hey, Jun! Come here.
Take them to the private room.
This way, sir.
I thought you didn't
want Pinky to be tabled.
Well, he kept on bugging me.
Besides, I know Dindo. He pays well.
You know, lots of people
want to be with your girl, right?
How about I watch her for you?
You know?
Like her bodyguard.
To make sure no one disrespects her.
Trying to pull a fast one?
Hey, Carlito! Just watch
the whole bar, that's your job.
Come on, already jealous?
Are you really trying to fool me, huh?
Just chill.
- What chill? Stop messing with me.
- What's wrong?
I'm just concerned
about your girl, okay?
- What are you talking about?
- I know you. Stop it.
Is this your first time?
In this bar? Yes.
Doing this?
Sort of. We're just going to talk, right?
Hey, Dindo looks completely
satisfied with you, huh?
Your kid is good!
Until next time.
Thank you!
Wow, it looks like...
you did a great job, huh?
Well, you told me to do a
great job. With the acting.
You really impressed me.
If you keep this up, you'll
make a ton of money here.
I'll be the one in charge
of who tables you,
who takes you to a private room,
and who takes you out.
Yes, sis.
Just call me Mama. Mamasan,
that's what everyone calls me here.
Mama? Mother? Mommy?
Something like that.
Thank you, Mama.
Here's your tip!
But, he already gave me one.
No, that's your tip, from me.
Add it to what you
need to pay for your rent.
Thank you, Ma.
Oh no, no, no.
- Hi, girls.
- I hope they're not late.
- Coffee.
- Oh, wow.
- You're so sweet, Tolits.
- Of course.
Ma, this is for you!
- Oh!
- I have a gift for you.
Where did you get that?
- You're so sweet.
- Just open it.
Oh, I definitely will open it.
Oh, siomai!
How did you know
this is my favorite? Huh?
- Secret!
- Oh, really? A secret? Thanks!
Hey, bitches!
Where are these bitches?
Hey, you girls! Come over here.
Pinky brought a treat!
Come on! Dig in!
- You know huh?
- Come on.
Thank you.
- Oh, okay, pass through here.
- That looks delicious!
- Is it good?
- Go, take some.
Can I have some?
You don't want any?
Here. Save some for me, okay?
For makeup, you should choose
something that suits your skin.
I'll put it on you.
Here, Ma, try this. It's new.
Oh, yeah. I only see this on
the dancers. On the internet.
Looking good!
Wow! It suits you so well!
Yeah!
There! Your face really stands out.
Really, Ma? Thank you.
Miss?
This looks pretty.
Miss, how much is this?
It's only 380, ma'am.
Hey, come here. Turn around.
This will look good on you.
Wow! Perfect fit!
Do you want it?
I'll take care of it.
- Really, Ma?
- Yeah.
It's so pretty!
Thank you, Ma.
What about this?
Does this look good on me?
You look better without one.
You're so harsh to me!
Well, because with
the size of your junk,
if you wear that, it'll
stick out over the garter.
That's true!
Idiot.
What the hell!
Oh, what is it?
- Nothing, Ma.
- Huh?
It's nothing. I just saw that bra,
only the nipples are covered.
[chuckles] Okay.
So, do you want this?
I'm buying it.
It'll be perfect for your dancing.
It's only 380, sir.
Can't it be...
- 300? 300.
- You've already bought me so much.
- Thank you, Ma.
- Don't worry about it.
That’s nothing.
Ah, Ma, can I take tomorrow off?
Why?
My landlady found out that I work at a bar,
so there's that.
And her son has a crush on me.
Then the owner said...
I was seducing her son.
And, I don't want to
get into an argument.
That's why I need to find
a new place tomorrow.
Is that so?
Yeah.
This is my apartment, come in.
I just rent here too,
but it's cheap.
Oh, by the way,
is it okay with you
if your room only has a fan?
But it does have a bed.
That's fine. In the province,
the electric fan was broken
and I was only using a
hand fan until my father died
So, this is much better
than my first rental.
Okay, good. Come on.
Let's go upstairs, and
I'll show you your room.
Alright.
You can rest for now.
We'll all go into the
bar together later.
There! More hips!
There! Throw it to
the left, to the right!
Yes! Down, down, down!
There you go!
Okay, here, here, come down the stage...
There, hold your boobs.
Yes, get close to the customer.
Yes, touch him. Then caress him.
Then, move to the next customer.
Yes, then touch your pussy.
Yes, then smear it on
the guy's crotch! There!
Then dance again. Go back
to the stage, fondle your tits.
There, there! Then,
shake your tits! Like that!
Flirt more, flirt more!
Like that! Bite your lip.
There, like that.
Then split! Perfect!
You're so, so good! Of course,
this is for our big night!
You're so good,
I'm so proud of you!
- Ouch!
- Oh, Berna!
Oh, sorry.
I'm starting to catch on to you, huh!
I didn't mean to,
I already apologized.
What apology? You're even starting
a fight with the dancers here too.
And the customers are
getting annoyed with you
because you're acting
so high and mighty.
What is it? Do you still
want to work here, or not?
Get your act together!
Let it go, Ma.
Maybe she's just tired.
She's always in a bad mood.
All of us in the dressing room
are just holding back with her.
She's just jealous!
Who would she be jealous of?
Don't worry about Berna.
Pinky is clearly better than her.
Right, girls?
- Truth!
- So true!
Okay, practice again.
Do a great job!
Sweetie, the hips.
Right, left. There!
There! Down, down.
Lower, lower.
There! Yes!
- Oh, Pinky.
- Yeah?
I'm leaving for a bit, okay?
I'm just going to pay the
water and electricity bills.
Later, you and Tolits
can go to the bar together.
I'll go straight there later. Okay?
Sure, Ma. Is Tolits ready?
Ah, no. He's over there,
still snoring.
- Well, okay then—I'm leaving.
- Take care.
Oh, hey, I didn't notice you there.
Mama left first. She said,
she's paying the bills.
Then, we should just
follow her to the bar.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Oh, by the way,
this is my gift for you.
It's embarrassing,
but... thank you.
Go on, try it on.
I'll just go to the comfort room.
No, try it on here. Why
go to the comfort room?
Are you shy around me? I see you
like this in the bar all the time.
Go on, let me have this.
Promise, Mama won't find out.
Wow, you're really sexy.
What do you think?
Will they like this?
Your customers will double.
Wait...
You know, the first time I saw you,
I really, really liked you.
Tolits...
You’re really pretty.
You’re making me hard again.
Let’s do it again.
No, please. Mama might catch us.
If you don't give in to me,
that's your problem.
Remember this, a secret
doesn't stay a secret forever.
Ma, let’s eat.
Ooh, this dish is great.
Who cooked this?
I did.
You?
Dig in, go ahead.
You jerk, why do you have this?
I didn't agree to that! Delete it!
I'll only delete this if you
help me with my problem.
I have a friend that
I owe money to, and I haven't been
able to pay him back for a long time.
I don't have the cash either.
Maybe you can take care of it.
He said if he gets to taste you,
he'll forget the debt.
Come on, just help me with this.
Nobody else will know.
It will be our secret.
Now, if you need a
favor from me next time,
I promise I'll give it
to you, I'll help you too.
You're the only one he wants
because you're so beautiful and sexy.
Let go of me!
Well, are you going
to help me, or not?
It's up to you.
Come on in, bro.
Is Myrna here?
She left. Go on, head
straight over there.
Did she really agree?
Of course, she did.
For real?
Bro, I don't owe you
anything anymore, right?
Yeah, I got you.
Tolits? Tolits!
What is it? What happened?
Huh?
Come on.
Shit!
Mr. Sy, can I get my salary now?
Oh, hello. Good evening.
Is Sexy Pinky dancing tonight?
No, she's not around.
She's the only one we came here for.
Oh, really? Berna and
the other dancers are here.
They're all good too.
Maybe next time,
when Pinky is here.
Hey man, let's go to Golden Bar?
Myrna!
What is happening here, Myrna?
I thought you said business was great?
Why are there no customers?
The business is losing money!
Our star model is absent, sir, she's sick.
There are no guests, just
because she's not around?
There are plenty of women here, right?
What? Are they useless?
The guests only look for Pinky, sir.
Then why don't you hire
a girl as good as Pinky?
It's tough to do
that these days, sir.
Lots of girls applied, but
none are on Pinky's level.
Are we just going to wait?
Find a way.
If it keeps being like this,
I'm going to fire you.
You're old anyway!
I'll find a replacement!
That's harsh, sir.
I've been working here
since I was eighteen.
I used to be the one bringing in
all the money here, remember?
With how good I was at
dancing and entertaining guests.
No credit at all?
Don't take it personally,
this is a business.
It needs to make
money to pay all of you.
Unbelievable, I grew old working for you!
I don't care if you can't
make the bar profitable.
Find another job if
anyone will still hire you.
I'm leaving! You're all
giving me a headache.
Sir Sy, relax. Watch your heart.
I'll walk you out.
[indistinct chatting]
Hey, how's the bar?
I got into a fight with Mr. Sy.
Because there was no one there,
so he got mad.
Get rid of my erection first.
What? I'm tired!
Come on.
- No way.
- Let's cool your head down.
- Just relax.
- What are you doing?
It's not happening! I'm tired!
You bitch!
Damn you!
I said I'm tired!
What's wrong with you, huh?
When I say I want it,
I want it. Okay?
Stop it!
I said I want to rest!
I'm so exhausted!
Hey Myrna! Get down here!
You piece of trash!
You ungrateful pigs!
Son of a bitch!
- Didn't I tell you not to mess with her?
- Myrna! Myrna, wait! Calm down.
- Not to touch Pinky? What did you do?
- Just calm down. Myrna, wait!
- You disgusting pigs!
- Wait, hold on!
- You make me sick!
- Calm down!
Damn you! You piece of trash!
- Myrna, wait!
- We're done! Get the hell out of here!
Damn you! Get out!
Get out of here!
Don't you ever come back!
You scoundrel! You're so ungrateful!
He forced me to.
And I'm not really ungrateful,
because I have nothing
to be grateful to you for!
Since the day I was born,
and my father died,
I never saw a mother who
took care of me, or guided me
because you are a worthless mother!
I couldn't handle
your father's life there.
That's why right after
I gave birth to you,
I immediately came back to work.
To save money,
and get both of you.
At my father's grave,
I promised I would find you...
To rub your sins
against us in your face!
Why did you leave us?
Why didn't you come back?
Forgive me, Abel.
I just got buried in debt,
so I couldn't go back.
I had no face to show you.
Since I was a child, all I've
had inside my chest is anger!
I planned everything
just to find you.
That feeling you have?
It's not even a fraction of what
my father and I went through.
Forgive me, my daughter!
Forgive me!
You know...
You were always on my mind and
in my heart, no one else, every day.
My daughter! If only you knew how I felt.
My child...
That would be 3500.
Oh... Here.
Ma'am, this is too much.
- Ah, that's okay. Keep the change.
- Thank you.
A fresh start?
Let me make it up to you, in
any way I can, my daughter.
For as long as I can.