=Summer In Love=
=Episode 13=
(Can I Hold Your Hand?)
Darling,
what happened?
Why did you faint?
Mother.
What year is this?
Did you hit your head?
2008.
Mother,
I'm a bit hungry.
Can you buy me some food?
Sure.
Good that you can eat.
It means you're fine.
I'll buy it for you.
Let me go.
Father, please stay with me.
Stay with her.
I'll go.
Father.
Is your mistress
checking on my death?
Shanshan,
listen to me.
No need.
She's scamming you?
Does she want money, a car or a house?
Shanshan,
you...
Enough.
First of all,
abort the child
and give her some money,
but never bring this to the family
or let my mother know.
(Iced rice wine)
Here, Xia.
Have you read the Dating Dictionary?
I realised that
this book is not reliable.
Where did you get this book?
I've spent RMB20 on this book.
I bought it from a guy in the dorm.
When you and Shi Yi are dating,
you need to pay me back.
(Girls Dorm Building Two)
Miss,
you've been trying for two hours.
Those who know
will think you're going
to Jay Chou's concert.
Those who don't know
will think you're dating with Jay Chou.
Check this out.
- Which one is better?
- All is ugly.
Which one is better?
What about
you try that?
This?
No, this is too mature.
What...
What about this?
Let's have a happy weekend.
Hello,
my friends.
Hello.
- This is Xiaoyu.
- Hello.
Shanshan,
didn't you say
this is our class gathering?
Who are they?
We're from the same university.
They're from our next class.
But I don't know them.
I should leave now.
- It's okay.
- Beautiful girl,
don't go.
Since you're here,
have a drink with us.
I don't drink wine.
You...
Just one glass.
I don't drink wine.
She doesn't drink.
Don't touch her.
I'll drink it.
I'm sorry.
Drink something else then.
A beverage is fine, right?
You're leaving as soon as
you've arrived?
That's no fun.
Xiaoyu.
What do you think?
Why not you have a drink first?
Yes. Give her a drink.
Okay.
Come on.
Let me pour you a drink.
(Jay Chou's concert ticket)
It's crowded.
10 years later,
Jay Chou's concert will be
so much merrier than this.
We can't even get a ticket.
(Jay Chou)
I wonder if
Jay Chou's abs is still there
or not in 2008.
Come on.
Drink this.
Happy weekend!
Here.
Cheers.