=Summer In Love=
=Episode 7=
(Oh No, I've Messed This Up)
Sir,
(Zhongjue Luxury Car)
thanks for the ice cream!
Thank you!
It's tasty!
Safe trip, gentlemen!
If there's anything,
just contact me any time!
You...
Look at you.
Do you know what it means by
don't look down on a young man?
You're stupid.
I know I was wrong.
You sold our client's car
just like that.
You must think of a way
to compensate the client.
We can check the score today.
I'm nervous.
Why do you need to be nervous?
Even if you didn't score well,
I'll retake the subjects with you.
Don't simply say that.
How can you retake the subjects?
Also,
your parents will not agree to it.
What's wrong with that?
Even though we're 30 years old,
life can start all over again.
After all, we've graduated.
Why not we get changed?
Let's go.
Let's go!
What are you thinking?
Are you worried that
you didn't score well?
(I'm worried about you,)
(silly girl.)
Can you stop going to the school?
I'm becoming a laughing stock.
If you can study well
like Shi Yi,
do I need to be so worried?
Yes,
Xiaoyu.
Your father is studying on
the schools for your ambitions.
Ambitions?
What ambitions?
Shouldn't you ask me about my ambitions?
What do you know?
Your mother and I are doing it
for your own good.
Why are you so immature?
I'm going to the tier-one university.
I must tell my parents now.
I didn't score well for
my science subjects.
Xia He?
Are you really sick?
Are you possessed by Yang Xin?
(Oh no.)
(I've messed this up.)
(Shi Yi doesn't like this style.)
(I'm stupid.)
Hey.
Shi Yi,
you're too petty.
Xia actually prepared
this surprise for you.
He just bought this car.
And these.
He prepared these for you.
- This is the latest...
- Shut up.
(He's being mysterious lately.)
(So, this is what he did.)
What are you two doing?
Let's go, Xiaoyu.
So weird.
Xia,
we must have bought too little.
I shouldn't have listened to you
who have retaken the subjects
for three years.
Is this not surprise?
What's surprise then?
Shi Yi, what's wrong?
Why are you not happy?
Xiaoyu,
go check your scores.
I'll wait for you.
Shi Yi.
I'm sorry.
I've made you misunderstood.
I'm...
Why can't you learn something else?
Why did you learn from Yang Xin?
It's awkward.
I don't like to see Yang Xin disturb you
just because he's rich and he has a car.
I was thinking
I can have
what he has.
Then I can be your driver
every day.
Then
he won't disturb you anymore.
I didn't know
you'd dislike this.
I'm sorry.
I was too silly.
Why didn't I think of this?
I didn't think about your feelings.
(He's usually boring.)
(Why is he so honest today?)
I'm sorry.
Why am I so silly?
Xiaoyu!
How did it go?
Is the result out?
Shut up.
What's wrong with her?
Obviously,
she didn't score well.
Xiaoyu,
it's just an exam!
Do it again next year!
Enough.
You didn't make it for three years.
Why are you so optimistic?
Where are you going?
Xia,
won't you check your score?
Don't worry.
We'll discuss about
how to tell your parents.
If I didn't get into
the tier-one university,
they'll scold me.
Now, I didn't even get
any tier-two university.
They must be disappointed.
Don't worry.
I'll stay with you.
Two Global Flavor Buffet.
Two Chocolate Heaven.
Hold on.
Xia,
you're ordering so much.
What about the dinner?
What do you know?
When the girls are sad,
they want something sweet.
How did you get to know all these?
Shut up.
Please get them ready.
All right.
Xia,
something is wrong with you.
You're talkative.
Where are they?
Why are they taking so long?
Shi Yi.
Did you see Xiaoyu?
Xiaoyu is missing?
Wasn't she with you?
I went to the toilet.
She's gone after I came out.
Let's go.
We'll look for her.
Okay.
What's going on?
(If only Xiaoyu had done better)
(and made it to
the tier-one university.)
(She didn't even get
a tier-two university.)
(What tier-one university?)
(Why did she score so terribly?)
(What was she doing in school?)
(Xiaoyu's not smart.)
(Look at her classmate, Shi Yi.)
(I heard she's scored around 600 marks.)
You'll go this way.
I'll go that way.
We'll find her very soon.
Okay.
Hello?
Shi Yi.
Xiaoyu.
Where are you?
I'm at the valley behind our school.
I feel like
someone is following me.
I'm scared.
Hello?
(The number you've
dialled is powered off.)
(Sorry.)
(The number you've
dialled is powered off.)