YoYo English Channel YouTube
Episode 2
What a coincidence, we meet again.
It's you again.
Yes, fate is so wonderful, isn't it?
I knew that day that you were Ding Nanxing's friend.
My partner showed me the pictures of your gallery.
Said you wanted to sign with her, right?
You know I signed a contract with Nanxing?
Just a few words.
Then how did she tell you?
She said she was impressed with the contract.
Really?
Yes.
But she rejected me later.
Maybe because she couldn't let go of her baking business.
Is baking so important?
Of course.
She has been doing this business for a long time.
She must have feelings.
But I have to say,
I think if she doesn't do this baking business,
she will definitely choose to sign with you.
Everything will change.
You don't have to worry too much now.
Oh, right.
Actually, I am also one of the shareholders of this bar.
So we have a special bar here
specially made for the shareholders.
It's very good.
Do you want to try?
Wait a minute.
Ok.
What are you doing?
I am fixing the lock.
The lock is broken.
Why don't I help you?
No need.
I'm afraid you'll be not familiar with the technique.
You'll break my door.
Who is not familiar with the technique?
No need.
I can fix it myself.
Forget it.
I'll go to see the master of Kaesuo.
Master of Kaesuo can do it.
Don't move.
I'll go to see the master of Kaesuo.
Hello, master.
Master.
Okay.
Hello, speak.
Master.
Are you familiar with the second-hand washing machine?
No.
He made fun of me again.
Okay.
You're good.
Not bad.
Ding Danxing.
Do you want to consider following me?
You said you wanted me to follow you.
You want me to follow you to work here?
Yes.
You're so talented.
Why don't you use it well?
We lack people in the studio.
You can come to the hardware studio.
I believe our cooperation
can make a unique game.
Xu Bayan.
I'm really stupid.
That's why I promised you to come here.
What's up?
Nothing.
You're reading these books.
It's helpful to you.
Do you want to listen to yourself?
Stupid man.
If you say so,
I have something to do now.
I'm going home to make a cake.
Is it so important to make a cake?
Of course.
Goodbye.
Xu Bayan.
You're a flower roll, right?
You like to roll inside.
Why don't you be a sushi chef?
I'll make you roll enough every day.
I understand what's going on.
I'll give you a very loyal advice.
That's to keep the money from now on.
Then?
You'll live in the studio.
And you'll take care of the company.
I don't want to stay in the studio.
I just want to be able to talk about it.
Don't be afraid.
I'm a man of my word.
But...
I'll save money now.
Then,
I'll find a comfortable nursing home.
What do you mean?
It's not easy to get beaten
by a comfortable one.
Why should I go to a nursing home?
It's a matter of experience.
How can you find a boyfriend
like you?
You don't even have a baby.
I clearly...
What do you clearly understand?
I've already worked hard.
Really?
Then you don't mind
working harder, do you?
Come on.
What do you mean?
My father,
my mother,
and even younger.
If we take her down,
our development speed
can be at least half.
Our development speed
is already at its peak.
Yes.
But who will be sorry
for the money?
If we can't,
we can take this budget
and renovate our studio,
okay?
Okay.
You're persuading me.
But I have a problem.
You're always
in charge of such things.
I've definitely tried it.
But she doesn't like my style.
Don't misunderstand.
I didn't mean that.
I mean, Mr. Jin
likes to talk about business.
But I can't do that.
I have to depend on you.
Come on.
Hello.
Sorry, I was busy.
We're from the Market Supervision and Management Bureau.
You're reported to be
unqualified for hygiene.
Please cooperate with the investigation.
What?
You're so talented.
Why can't you use me?
We're short of people in the studio.
You can be the finalist.
If you say so,
I'm busy now.
I'm going home to make cakes.
Is it that important?
Of course.
I'm leaving.
Xu Ben Yan.
Where's Xu Ben Yan?
He's not here.
He went out.
Where did he go?
He went to do some work.
If you're not in a hurry...
I'm in a hurry.
Can't you see that?
Where's his address?
Tell me now.
At Banxin Hotel.
Thanks.
I'll give you two bottles later.
No.
That's expensive.
He's going to the table?
No.
Don't change my business.
You said the sea is blue.
The silence of deep breathing
needs to be replaced with heart
when the sun shines through the sea.
You said the romantic sky
will meet the sea.
The warm sea breeze
is worth your love.
I hide out in the clouds
to prepare for my confession.
You said the romantic sky
will meet the sea.
The sudden feelings
are all because of you.
I'm leaning on the evening breeze.
Waiting for you to pass by the window.