True Beauty
I, Im Ju Gyeong, am a goddess.
But... only before I remove my makeup.
Facial recognition failed
Phone? It's me. Can you not tell?
This jerk, Im Ju Yeong, messed with my phone!
Yeah. Living with two faces is extremely exhausting,
and it's continuously humiliating.
Facial recognition success
Episode 2
This is it.
There is no other place with more horror books than here.
Where is it?
Oh! I found it!
I got here first.
I grabbed it first.
You are the Devil
Lee Su Ho?
You...
Who?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Did he recognize me?
That book... I grabbed it first ... Ma'am.
Oh. Then, please look at it first.
Here.
Ju Bal, eat some ramen.
What? I never ordered it.
It's on me since we've met after such a long time.
Next time. I'll eat it next time.
I got organic eggs put in here. It was ₩700 per egg.
I'm going to be sad if you don't eat it.
Can't you just eat it yourself?
I'm on a diet.
Yeah, let's just eat quickly and go.
That's mine.
I'm sorry.
You must like red ginseng juice. I'll buy you a new one.
No need.
You can look over it first.
No. I'm okay.
After you flew over my body to snatch it?
Quickly look at it.
You are the Devil
He really didn't recognize me.
Do you... live around here?
I'm not trying to get information about you, but your visuals are very noticeable to the eyes.
I haven't seen you around this neighborhood.
If you haven't seen me around even though I have a unique appearance, that probably means I don't live in this neighborhood.
Then why did you have to crawl out all the way here...
What do you mean crawl?
I've been able to walk upright since I was 11 months old.
Oh, I see.
- I'm 18.
- What?
You seem my age. The honorifics are bothering me a bit.
How old are you?
I'm 15. Middle school, second year.
You don't look younger than me, old lady.
It's a joke. I'm 25. A lot older than you, right?
We must be the same age.
No one would doubt that you're first place at school.
Wow, I'm full. This is fun. Here you go, have fun reading it.
- Already?
- I'm a master of speed.
I'm talking about this.
Especially eating. Bye now.
Prince Comics
I came like this!
Why did I meet Lee Su Ho of all people here like this?
How dare you treat your sweet younger brother like this?
Hey, what about the comic book?
I don't know! Seriously, because of you, I almost...
Why? Did you go to the comic store bare faced and then meet a handsome guy from your class?
Well, I mean, this isn't even a drama.
How could something so coincidental like that happen?
Wow, are you for real? Hey, I don't even have to release the photos for your goddess life to end.
It's not like that. He didn't recognize my bare face.
Today, he was unsure. But, tomorrow, if he happens to see you...
"You're the pimply girl from the comic store!"
- He might do that, you never know!
- What?
W-would he really? What should I do then?
This is why a person should be honest.
Noona, that whole goddess thing is a scam.
Just be open about it confidently.
How long do you think you'll be able to hide that face?
- Hey, Im Ju Yeong.
- Yeah?
- You said you were flirting with someone at your academy, right?
- Yeah, why?
She's freaking pretty.
I'm sure her bare face is the same as mine.
Hey, no, it's not!  Even her breath is fragrant!
How could we meet here?
But why did she ignore me? After going through all of that?
She didn't leave a drop of soup. Our Ju Bal eats so well.
- Her name is Ju Bal?
- You don't know Pandora's daughter, Ju Bal?
You've also come here for a long time. Did you never see her back then?
Why? Are you interested in her?
No, I'm not.
Yesterday, I was lucky.
But no one knows if that luck will extend to today.
Only with a perfect disguise will I survive.
I need a bit more paring down.
Good thing I saw you! Take me to school.
Hey, you still haven't gone to school yet? You were late again because of makeup, huh?
- No! Please, hurry!
- I'm taking my kid sister.
Why do you look so happy looking at someone else's husband?
If you want him, take him.
What a joke.
I feel this every time I look at him.
He is worth the price of admission.
Please, if I had to pay a price, I don't have such a wish.
He's just a person. Not worth a damn.
Look at him.
Looks like I'll have medicine expenses.
- What's wrong, Dad?
- Have a good trip, my daughters.
Drive safely!
You! Study hard and don't sleep.
- Okay.
- Pandora.
Besides Hui Gyeong and Ju Gyeong, did you have another daughter who is that pretty?
Disguise, success!
Nowadays don't you get caught being madeup like that?
Back in my day, even if I just put on bb cream, I'd get called out.
That "back in my day."  If you use that phrase, you're going to be called a boomer.
What boomer? I'm cool.
And I don't like lattes!   (T/N: 'back in my day' sounds like 'latte' in Korean.)
Even if I freeze to death, Iced Americano.
I got it. I'm going. Thank you, Unni!
- Work hard!
- Okay!
Oh... Hi!
What a relief. He didn't recognize me.
Su Jin!
- Delete it.
- W-What?
Delete it before I throw this.
I'll delete it. I will, so give it back.
What a scary guy.
If you get on his bad side, you're dead that day, right?
Didn't they know that he hates getting pictures of him taken?
But his temper is really something else.
Let's go.
Hello, can I get a cup of latte—
No, an iced Americano, please. Even if I freeze to death, iced Americano.
Got it.
- Why aren't you going?
- I don't want to.
- All your friends left, but you won't?
- No, I want to stay with you, Mom.
You have to go. You shouldn't stay here like this.
Tada! Hi!
♫   Through the endless daydreams, I saw you on the way back   ♫
♫   There I walked with you in my arms   ♫
♫   Through the blurry darkness    ♫
Come here!
♫   Who's veiling on the twilight   ♫
♫   We've been far away from my fears   ♫
♫   Somewhere else I'll see you, our days be like a blossom   ♫
♫   Blooming all around you so bright   ♫
♫   By and by I'll miss you and your laugh like a sunshine   ♫
♫   Fading into shadow of tears   ♫
Your iced Americano is here!
Would you like a coupon stamp?
Yes, please. I think I'll come here often.
Can I have the strongest cover-up cushion?
- You can look at this first, and I'll get you the strongest cover-up.
- Yes, please.
- Look at this.
- This looks so pretty.
- It didn't wash off!
- So ugly!
Oh, what are we to do with your face and all of this?
Are you okay?
Just a joke! A joke.
- How funny.
- It's funny?
What are we to do with this nut?
I'll show you the product.
Safety first
Hey, stop where you are!
Han Seo Jun!
Stop right there!
Hurry!
Excuse me, are you okay?
What should I do?
Are you not hurt?
Hey! Stop right where you are!
- Stop right there! Han Seo Jun! Hey!
- Hurry and catch him!
Catch him right now!
Hey! Hey! Stop right there!
Hey! Han Seo Jun! Stop!
Hurry, hurry.
Hey, hurry!
Stop right there!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Stop right there!
What are you running for?
Come here.
Are you okay?
Catch him right there!
Han Seo Jun. Kim Cho Rong said you went to study abroad.
Did you think we'd believe that?
I'm sorry, you bastard.
Oh, this lunatic.
Hey, when I think about how, because of you,
I have no money left, I just...
Hey.
You didn't come out that day intentionally to backstab us, right?
Did you think we wouldn't do anything if you ignored and avoided us?
Don't hit the face.
Yes, you avoided it.
Okay, you're dead today.
Hey, the cops are here.
Let's go quickly!
We'll meet again, Han Seo Jun.
Let's go.
Are they gone?
What's with you?
Uh, about that...
Oh, there!
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
Run...
Oh, oh, bye!
Saebom High School?
Wait, my helmet! Hey!
I almost got entangled with gangsters after trying to avoid Kim Se Mi.
What's this? Why did I take this with me?
What if he followed me to get it?
It's you! The pimply girl from the comic store!
- It's not me.
- Hey, Im Ju Bal. Were you scared?
Im Ju Yeong, do you want to die?!
Hey, come here! You!
- It's loud.
- It's better you die with me.
Be quiet, you guys!
- Ju Heon is on.
- Hey, if you hit me with that, it's attempted murder.
Ju Heon my ass.
- You little...
- You're heavy, you pig!
Hey, you! Come here right now!
It's been seven years.
Hui Gyeong is so lucky.
She's so lucky to work under a handsome boss.
Handsome, yeah right.
How does it feel to return to filming a drama after seven years?
While I was abroad all those years, I couldn't take care of my son very well.
From now on, I want to spend more time with him.
I'm not the best dad.
Son! It's hard to see you just once.
This place is the same as always.
When I was body-building,
I came here so often as if I lived here.
Director Choi is good to you, right?
Why are you back all of a sudden?
There was a lot to do at work, and I've gotten busier after the companies merged.
I thought I'd be forgotten if I only worked overseas.
You're very thorough at managing your fans.
Su Ho, I was afraid I'd be forgotten by you.
You're leaving already?
I want to loosen up my muscles. I haven't done it in so long.
You can do that and go.
You can't be knocked down so easily!
Wow, it looks like you learned properly.
Oh no.
Wow, you're a real man now.
I must've aged now.
I'm not a match for you anymore.
It's your birthday tomorrow. Do you want to go somewhere fancy to eat?
No.
Is there anything you want?
Did you think about moving back in to my house?
I told you I don't want to.
When you become a senior—
Wouldn't you feel uncomfortable living with me?
You have to go on dates.
Don't just come without notice from now on.
I don't want to be known as Lee Ju Heon's son.
No...
Which one is better for my Hoon's 100th day of dating present?
I like the left one.
100 days? You were so excited I thought it was the 100 years anniversary.
I was excited for my own 100th day celebration.
Hang in there, Kang Su.
Friends, I like you guys so much.
I'm happy to have a goddess friend like you.
What goddess?
If I'm a goddess, you're a fairy.
Im Ju, how can you be so pretty AND so kind?
What goddess?
I'm getting an allergic reaction from makeup. What is this?
This won't do. I've got to do this so I'll have better makeup.
Hey, return this. The Prince guy said to do it immediately.
When did you rent one?
Hey! Why do I have to return it?
I haven't deleted your bare face pic.
I just want to- Whack!
If Lee Su Ho saw it,
"Delete it! Delete it before I throw this!"
I'm borrowing these. The rest are yours to keep.
Present for you.
Sir.
Hey, Ju Bal, you're here.
- Shh.
- Was Lee Su Ho here today?
Who?
That indifferent, chic, tiny-faced, jumped-out-of-comics guy.
Me?
That guy who likes red ginseng juice.
Oh him. He doesn't come often on the weekends.
Really? That's a relief. This is for return.
- Ju Bal.
- Yes?
- Do you have some time?
- For what?
I have a situation, so can you take care of the store?
Sir, what if there's a customer?
Gosh.
That book is still here?
Curse in the Dark
Wow.
I used to collect these when I was little.
No one took it.
This is for my pay.
We meet again.
Dang!
Why aren't you coming down?
I'm looking for a book.
Then can you get that book over there?
- This?
- Next to that.
- This one?
- Move a little more.
- How much longer are you going to pretend?
I know you know me.
Thanks, Ju Bal.
You always jump on me every time you see me. It's become a habit.
You have to keep your balance when you're up there.
You have zero athletic ability,
People with no athletic ability should be forever banned from using step stools.
You surprised me by acting like you knew me.
My acting is not good enough to keep pretending to not know you.
Then did you recognize me when you saw me here last time?
I'm blessed with an exceptional memory.
Is being able to recognize a matter of a good memory?
Does he have hawk vision or what?
It's obvious it's you. What do you mean?
That face and this face are totally different.
Are you finding hidden pictures?
I mean it's a different picture.
Oh, eyes are different.
Eyes?
Right, the eyes are the most different.
Am I wrong to recognize you?
No, you aren't.
I just can't believe the reality.
Are you going to tell?
- Tell what?
- That I'm like this.
You're like what?
You saw me so you know that I'm messed up.
If people know, I won't be able to walk around with my head up.
Is she talking about that time she tried to jump off from the  rooftop?
Why would you be like that?
It's like that for me.
Please, can I ask you to ignore it?
Please.
But this is Lee Su Ho, the sociopath.
Fine.
Yeah, of course you won't—
What? Really? So easily?
You think I'm free enough to just walk around talking about you?
Not really...
But how can I trust you?
What would you do if you don't trust me?
Confidentiality Agreement
Do you really have to go this far?
That's how desperate I am.
Sign here.
I don't feel like it.
You say you're desperate yet you copied everything from 'The Hell Duty'.
I was  rushing it...
You know 'The Hell Duty'?
That's the classic of classics. Not a lot of people know about it.
How could I not know?
Pictures that are not tacky even after 30 years,
the first in the nation to graft occult horror and sci-fi. It's the best of the 20th century.
Wow, it's fascinating to meet someone who knows about it.
But rather than 'The Hell Duty', I like the author's previous piece...
- 'The Cursed Mask!'
- Awesome!
- You know 'The Cursed Mask'?
That's what got me into horror comics. I have a signed copy of the first edition.
You have that?
Yes. Why?
I've been looking for two years to find the first edition of  'The Cursed Mask'
and you have one?
I've been a long time fan in the horror division.
How much would you accept?
I don't feel like it.
You say you're desperate, yet you're trying to resolve it with money?
Party B: Lee Su Ho
Good? What more do you want?
He's totally different from school.
Isn't he unexpectedly a little heodang ( a clumsy and sloppy person )?
I'm kind of thirsty.
I feel a little empty.
- So what?
- Are you desperate?
I shouldn't have done that back then.
Im Ju Gyeong's spot.
Sitting without permission will cause hair to grow on your butt!
- You wouldn't dare to do this to me at school.
- Huh?
You said you'd hand over 'The Cursed Mask' with two bowls of ramyun.
No, I'll hand it over with one bowl.
- This is my bribe to you.
- A bribe?
It's for you to keep the secret well.  Go ahead and eat.
Eating ramyeon in a comic store with Lee Su Ho. My friends would be so surprised.
I was wondering why there were ramyun soup spots whenever I rented comics.
Hey, you know how good ramyun is at a comic store? You'll regret not eating one.
Do you not want to see 'The Cursed Mask'?
How is it? Isn't it good?
It's good considering it's the first meal of my birthday.
It's your birthday? Today?
Then what are you doing here?
Do you like looking at people eat?
Hey, don't breathe it in.
Don't look.
What do I do?
- Take it out.
- Take it out?
- No, breathe it in.
- Ew.
My nose hurts.
I'll bring 'The Cursed Mask' on Monday for sure.
Okay.
- Here.
- Another  bribe?
No, it's a present.
This is a 20-year-old rare item.
I found it but will grant it especially to you.
You're a friend I shared my secret with.
Of course I have to take good care of you.
Happy birthday.
It got cleaned up very well.
The Cursed Mask
Thanks for keeping my bare face a secret!
This face looks so different from my natural one.
How did Lee Su Ho know?
So strange.
Please stop, bus driver!
Hold on a second!
Thank you!
A goddess descended.
Wow, for real.
I'm glad I took the bus.
Hi.
Wow, she's no joke.
Goddess.
- Give me the phone.
- Who are you?
You pervert, I saw you taking a picture!
Ju Gyeong, report him to the police right now.
What?
Move aside.
That bastard... Hey!
Su Jin!
Stop where you are!
Stop while I'm being nice!
Hey! Are you not going to stop right there?
Stop right there, I said!
Take this pervert away.
- You'll see it in his phone.
- Let go!
I scanned my bus card earlier.
You were shocked, right?
Yeah. You were so cool.
No, I'm asking if you are okay.
Su Jin, I wish I had a boyfriend like you.
What are you saying?
I'm not even surprised. She even taught middle schoolers who were smoking a lesson last time.
She's a total girl crush.
What are you saying?
I was so shocked this morning when I couldn't button my skirt this morning.
Gosh, why can't they change our skirts to have elastic waistbands?
Oh, right, Im Ju. What did your uniform look like before?
I'm curious. Do you have a picture?
Oh, that.   I never took a picture.
What a lie. Your uniform sucked, huh?
Let me see!
Well...
- Well...
- Move.
Move, I said.
Thanks to you, I survived just now.
Lee Su Ho, you should talk nicer.
- Anyway...
- Ddu Ah, Ddu Ah, Ddu Ah.
Honey!
A motorcycle! A motorcycle!
What the?
He's...
He's from our school?
How can there be such an unbelievable coincidence?
- Han Seo Jun is back.
- Why is he here?
Why's he here?
Han Seo Jun?
Like how there are the Bermuda Triangle in the Atlantic and black holes in the universe,
there are two charming boys at our school, whom if you fall for once, you can never exit and get out.
What to do?
Oh, what do we do?
This is crazy!
Oh my god!
What do I do?
The chic, cold beauty God Lee Su Ho, and the rough, wild horse God Seo Jun.
Just like deciding between jjajangmeyon ( black bean noodles ) vs. jjampong ( spicy seafood noodles ) and pizza vs. chicken
is so mindblowingly hard, they're the two gods at Saebom High School. The two top ones!
The space and time cringed.
Then, honey, what about me?
Our Hoon, you're my top one!
Forget the top two nonsense, I hate them both.
I almost barfed.
Han Seo Jun returned!
They'll get into a fight again.
- It's already so loud.
- I love it!
What's with them? They don't get along well?
They used to be best friends, but they somehow fell apart.
When they meet, the atmosphere gets so cold.
So annoying.
- Hello!
- Hello.
Hello!
Hello.
- Alright, Seo Jun is back now. Good to see him, right?
- Yes.
Let's give him a round of applause.
Bravo.
Seo Jun, just sit next to Su Ho.
What?
You go.
- Me?
- This was originally my spot.
Oh, Ju Gyeong has weak eyes, so she's sitting there.
Tae Hoon. Our handsome Tae Hoon, can you switch spots?
Me?
Really? Yes.
Bros! My friends!
Yes, Tae Hoon, nice one!
Teacher!
- Sorry.
- Should we start now?
Yes.
To have a friend
is to have another life.
What is it, Mr. Han?
He started it again.
I want you guys to...
I've seen her before.
have a more prosperous life.
Teacher, that's cringey.
Teacher, call 119, please.
My hands and feet won't straighten out from how cringey that was.
- Hyeon Gyu, I have medicine.
- Medicine?
What kind?
They straightened out.
Fighting!
Lee Su Ho, what are you thinking about?
The English teacher wants you to come to the staff room really quickly. Let's go.
Hey, are Su Jin and Lee Su Ho close?
Yeah, they're pretty close. Their families have known each other since they were young.
The only girl Lee Su Ho has actually talked to is our Su Jin.
Oh, really?
If he's close with Su Jin, then he must be nice.
The smart kids always hang out together.
They're even handsome and beautiful.
They're so inhuman.
Honey, that's why I'm adjusting my grades.
Because I would be too inhuman otherwise.
Your smile makes my guts break dance which then gives me a stomach problem.
Han Seo Jun.
If you returned, you should've shown your face and said hi.
Hey, brother. Today's such great weather for you to die.  (T/N: a famous quote from movie "New World")
Are you guys a girl group or something?
Why are you standing there like that?
Why? Are you going to hit us?
Okay, come in. Come here!  (T/N: another famous quote from movie "New World")
Kim Cho Rong!
Your joke was a bit too much.  (T/N: another famous impersonation of Lee Jung Jae from movie "New World")
Han Seo Jun!
Hey, great acting for a trainee.
This is so childish.
How much longer do I have to play around?
Hey, brother!
It's honestly fun, you know?
- Have you guys been well?
- Yeah.
Kim Cho Rong, I think you gained more weight.
Did you bulk up?
I lost 10 kilograms!
I see the muscles.
- Is your mother better?
- Yeah.
She's a lot better.
What a relief. I'm sorry I couldn't make a munsang   (T/N: condolence call on a mourner).
Hey, what do you mean by munsang, you fool?
It should be munbyeong   (T/N: visiting a sick person).
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Smart!
Then what's munsang?
A gift certificate.
It's refreshing.
Han Seo Jun is a bit scary.
He's got that bad boy style.
There's a terrible rumor that he beat a student
until he was nearly half-alive, so that's why he took a break from school.
- Really?
- Yeah.
How do I give his helmet back?
Gosh, I keep getting myself into terrible situations.
What are you saying? They say he took a break from school because of things going on at home.
You don't know about that.
- Is that her? The goddess student?
- Yeah.
She's so pretty, right?
That's amazing. She looks pretty eating, too.
Their class is so lucky.
Hey, hey, hey. Look at her.
- They say she's the goddess-like transfer student of the second year.
- She really is a goddess.
What a scam.
- What's this?
- You like this.
Can't believe this.
Come to the rooftop.
She's crazy.
You came?
What are you? An attention seeker?
Hey, nobody is here. You can relax.
I washed your uniform, and the thing that I told you I'd give—
- Or do you like me?
- No!
Then why are you pretending to be close to me when we've never met?
We... met before. Why are you like this suddenly?
I don't care what you imagine by yourself,
but you should properly differentiate what's reality.
Don't make someone who isn't doing anything angry.
Excuse me. Then have you really never seen me outside before?
It seems you want to grab my attention by doing this.
But if you ever touch me as you please...
I won't stand still.
What? Then at the comic store...
He didn't recognize my bare face?
The Cursed Mask
Thanks for keeping my bare face a secret!
No! No!
You wouldn't dare to do this to me at school.
Why did I act up for no reason, seriously!
Excuse me! Wait!
Excuse me. Wait.
This... I brought the wrong thing, so let go.
It can't be ripped.
These are sanitary pads.
I'll give it to you again tomorrow.
But what exactly is the secret Lee Su Ho is saying he'll keep?
Has he seen me before?
Oh, I don't know!
Oh, what should I do?
And I acted up so much to him like that.
It'll be the end if I get caught, right?
You all researched about the poets we talked about last time, right?
Yes!
It's a group project, so discuss it and make a presentation.
Okay!
Hey, Han Seo Jun.
Do you know how to do a PPT?
Oh, fitting?
Of course.
I used to be a fitting model, you know.
Okay.
-  I'm screwed.
- What are you doing?
- It came.
- It came?
How about we research about resistance poets?
It's easy to find information, but it feels like other groups will pick that too.
- And I don't feel we're smart enough.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Did you forget that the school's number one, God Su Ho, is in our group?
Ju Gyeong, what do you think?
"Oh, the animal that's saddened by the long neck."
"Always rather gentle."  (T/N: a quote from the poem 'Deer' by No Cheon Myeong)  "
The silent Ju Gyeong, are you sleeping?
- No.
- That's a relief.
Let's go, you jerk! Yeah, that's right!
Kill him! That's right!
Go, go, go!
You're at it again.
You came? Hey, at your school,
is there a teacher that is exactly a 7:3 ratio of Jung Woo Sung and Brad Pitt?
No.
Think well. He went inside your school.
Even if I think about it well, there's none.
Is he not a teacher then?
Did something happen? You look defeated.
Just...
Life is hard.
What even? You 18-year-old.
What about being 18?
Is 18 years not even a life?
Did you not have 18 years? Is 28 years any better?!
Come here. Come here, you brat!
You're not coming, you brat?
Hello?
It's me.
Who?
How do you know my phone number?
- I found out.
- Why?
You said you had something for me. Bring it out to me.
S-something to give to you?
What would that be?
Are you joking?
I'll text you the address.
Right now?
I'm not feeling well.
Can't I give it to you tomorrow?
Then I'll come over to you, so give me your address.
No! I'll go! I should go.
Come by 9 pm.
Saebeom Park Cafe, 9 pm
But Lee Su Ho...
Who are you calling?
Bare face Im Ju Gyeong or makeup Im Ju Gyeong?
What is he saying for me to bring?
Okay. He said to throw away the uniform, so there's no need for me to bring this out.
It's probably the comic book!
But it would be easier to get my number from the school kids...
Then is it the uniform?
You were Im Ju Gyeong?
You dare to trick me?
You were the pimple girl from the comic store?
You...
You...!
Why? Do you have a problem?
Psycho.
What is he saying I should do?!
Unni!  Unni!
Where did she go?
Hey, Im Ju Yeong.
What's with your face? So freaking funny.
- You're not busy right now, right? Listen to my request.
- A favor?
If you just do this one favor, I'll be your comic book shuttle forever.
No, I'll be your younger sibling. Please.
Yeah? That's a rather tempting offer.
Thank you, Oppa. My request is—
But what should I do? This oppa has an appointment.
I'll listen to your request next time.
Oppa, is an appointment more important than me?
You're saying something that's obvious.
Let go. Let go!
I'm not wearing it.
What do I do?
- I'm not late, right?
- What's with the helmet?
Doesn't everyone use this when they ride a bike?
My face will be all shredded if I fall the wrong way. It's as dangerous as a motorcycle.
You said you weren't well. So why the dangerous bike?
My body isn't well,
but I rode it to quickly give you this so I can rest at home.
Then give it to me quickly.
Where is it?
I wonder where it is~
Is it that hard to find it in there?
- The comic book.
- The comic book!
Give it to me.
It was the comic book!
You know this is a very generous offer? You got to know that. Then good bye.
I ordered a warm drink. Drink it before you go.
No, it's okay. I don't have to drink it.
Then should I throw it away?
It's really okay, though. I wonder why you did this.
You're going to drink this with that on?
- I can drink it with a straw!
- Must you? It looks hot.
It's cold sweat. So I can get better.
Everybody is staring.
Then they can stare!
You're a bit weird today.
I'll go to the restroom to take it off and then come back.
What? What is this?
Let's get out. Let's get out!
I'm sorry.
What's this suffering?
I'm already upset about being ugly...
Isn't he so handsome?
Isn't he a celebrity?
I washed my face because I was sweating.
But how did you know my phone number?
Prince Comics.
You must have really wanted to see that to call me out at this time.
Yeah.
But... the secret of mine that you said you'd keep...
There is.
If I asked you again what that secret was, I'd seem like a psycho, right?
Probably.
Should we ask each other something we're curious about?
No, let's not.
What a relief.
I didn't get caught.
I need to change my phone number.
Thinking about having to avoid him tomorrow
is making me restless.
Ju Gyeong!
Excuse me. Your uniform.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What's with her?
Oh, woah!
Yes!
Han Seo Jun, out!
Hey!
You've seen me before, right?
What are you saying?
You ran off with my helmet. Did you not?
Over there!
I didn't fall for that last time either.
- Damn it!
- S-S-Sor...
T-t-t-the class president! It was the class president.
I'm sorry. I'll give it back to you tomorrow.
Gosh, seriously. Im Ju, are you okay?
That jerk.
He should have caught her.
That's right. Even if I'm bleeding, don't pay me any attention.
It's better than getting caught.
What is your boyfriend doing that he's not eating?
He said he's doing the assignment, so he's just going to grab something from the convenience store.
Really? Then should we buy him something?
I don't know. He can starve.
What? Did you guys fight again?
We didn't even have the time to fight.
He kept ignoring my calls cause he wanted to sleep early yesterday.
I don't think he knows it's our 100th day. So annoying.
No way, do you think Tae Hoon really forgot about it?
I don't know. If he really did forget, then we're breaking up today.
He's the only boyfriend I've dated for 100 days.
"Tae Hoon and Su Ah's 100 days"
I love you, Su Ah.
Do I really have to make a flower path for your girlfriend?
When my life is a poop path?
Poop path, okay. Okay.
- You up for a blind date?
- B-blind date?
I'll finish this prettily.
Is Su Ah coming?
She's coming.
Oh my god.
Su Ah, who is prettier than Suzy in my eyes.
Even when I'm old and wrinkly
I'll love you.
♫  Just thinking about you makes me feel good.  ♫
♫  This feeling, only you can make me feel like this  ♫
♫  I want to feel this way until I die. If you stay by my side, I'll cherish you.  ♫
♫  I'll cherish you.  ♫
I like you, everything about you.
♫  From your head to your toes,  ♫
♫  Every little thing you do.  ♫
Come on, what's this?
♫ I like it, I like everything about you ♫
You're so cool!
Su Ah, I'll probably go to hell.
Since I stole you, an angel, from heaven.
Flutter.
Flutter, flutter, flutter.
I've embraced you into my heart.
I love you, my angel!
Thank you!
Kiss! Kiss!
Kiss!
It's cringy. Do it in moderation!
Ju Gyeong!
Ju Gyeong.
Oh no! What to do!
I didn't tell you to throw it!
You want to die?
What to do? Let's wipe, first.
Will a wet tissue be enough? It looks like you'll need to wash your face.
If I wash my face, my bare face will be revealed. No.
Yeah, let's wash your face. Let's go.
Stop!
Nobody touch me.
Ju Gyeong!
Wait.
Move!
What's with her?!
- Im Ju Gyeong?
- Ju Gyeong!
Do you have a death wish?
Seriously, what the hell?!
You startled me!
I'm sorry!
Ju Gyeong, let's hurry and wipe your face!
Ju Gyeong, are you okay?
She said to not touch her!
Why did you have to throw it?
Gosh.
Sorry, I'm sorry!
Ju Gyeong, let's first wipe your face. I'll wipe for you.
Don't.
- Apologize properly. Hurry!
- What's going on?
- Who is it?
Isn't she the transfer kid?
The one known as the goddess?
Who?
Who are you?
Guys, it's me, Ju Gyeong.
Im Ju Gyeong, it was you?
Was it all makeup?
Do you not have any shame? You're freaking ugly.
What was with the goddess act all this time?
Your bare face is freaking ugly.
What happened to your face?
I think I'm going to throw up.
- Why are you like this? We're friends.
- Friends?!
If I knew your face looked like this, I wouldn't have befriended you.
Can't believe this.
Look at those pimples.
What the?
♫  I'm in the mood for dancing, romancin'  ♫
♫  Ooh, I'm givin' it all tonight  ♫
♫  I'm in the mood for chancin'  ♫
♫  I feel like dancin'  ♫
♫  Ooh, so come on and hold me tight.  ♫
♫ Ooh, I'm dancin', I'm in the groove, babe  ♫
♫  So get up and let your body sway.  ♫
♫ I'm in the mood for dancin', romancin'  ♫
♫  You know I shan't ever stop tonight  ♫
♫  I'm in the mood for chancin'  ♫
♫  I feel like dancing  ♫
♫  Ooh from head to my toe  ♫
♫  Take me again.  ♫
True Beauty
Does he really know?
There's someone who is similar to you at our school.
Why do you keep running away?
This is for me to eat?
Even though you can postpone studying, dating should not be postponed.
Im Ju Gyeong, are you dating Lee Su Ho?
Why is he here?
- Don't look elsewhere.
- You must be happy.
Our Ju Gyeong is having a hard time because she's pretty.
I love you.