♪Lonely moon♪
♪Long street♪
♪The cold star failed to grant my wish♪
♪We all strayed into this world♪
♪My heart is like a wilderness♪
♪You laughed that the comings and goings
in this life is too deliberate♪
♪The silent waiting figure is far away♪
♪If the vast sea grows old♪
♪One unfinished game remained♪
♪We all cheat
because we're afraid of getting hurt♪
=Love Endures Eternally=
(Adapted from I'm Shameless'
Quick Transmigration: Defeated Again)
=Episode 21=
We must take action
to restore peace to Nanling.
We're willing to follow you
and create peace together.
It's unusual.
For the sake of the people,
we must plan carefully
to succeed in one go.
First, we must ensure
that the military's morale is stable.
Then, divide the troops
into three groups
to attack the capital.
Time is precious.
We must act fast.
Yes.
May we succeed in our expedition.
May you be safe and sound all your life.
I hope our expedition will go smoothly.
If we fail,
I don't want to live alone.
But we'll be together in the next life.
No need for the next life.
We'll be happy in this life.
For you and for our baby,
our crusade will surely succeed.
I used to live
in the shadow of my background.
Going against His Majesty
and alienating General
are all because of my hatred.
But since having you,
my life has lit up.
I'll fight for our love.
I also believe
that god will help us.
I believe you.
Chi Yuan.
Thank you.
Thanks to you.
I have a complete family.
(Favorability: 90)
(Shen Residence)
Shen Yi intends to rebel.
The Shen family
is to be killed on the spot.
Shen Xin will be taken back
to be detained and await her punishment.
I've severed ties with the Shen family.
(Shen Residence)
You can't arrest me.
Let me go.
It's pointless to make excuses.
Wait for your trial.
Take her away.
(Shen Residence)
Arrest Shen Zhaomu.
Why arrest me?
(Shen Residence)
Everyone.
This battle is important.
We must succeed
and eliminate harm for the people.
I never held my unborn son.
I want to create
a peaceful world for him.
May all of you return triumphantly.
We must win
for the sake of the people.
We're willing
to follow General till death.
Follow me and check out the terrain.
When I return triumphantly,
we'll have a grand wedding
to celebrate the world and our baby.
Before that,
take good care of yourself.
I'll wait for you.
You must come back safely.
Ms. Chi Yuan, please eat.
Where's Ruyi?
She usually delivers the food herself.
Ms. Ruyi knows some medical skills
and has joined the crusade with the army
to treat the wounded.
Take a bite first.
Someone tried to poison me before,
so I became more cautious.
Please forgive me.
War is imminent,
and everyone is in danger.
Ms. Chi Yuan.
It's good to be careful.
Leave.
Someone, come.
Come.
You probably didn't expect it.
This poison is placed
in the most inconspicuous place.
Are you awake?
Where am I?
Why kidnap me?
Rumor has it
that you're carrying royal blood.
I was so generous
to make you Mu's adopted sister,
hoping you can behave yourself.
Yet you went against the will of heaven.
Is Prince Zhou not good enough for you?
Zhaomu and I are true love.
We're not bound by empty titles.
How dare you?
How dare you, a mere guard,
be with a member of the royal family?
Do you really care about Zhaomu?
If it weren't
for your behavior back then,
how could he
have been stuck in this chaos?
He couldn't acknowledge
his birth father.
His adopted father alienated him.
His adopted mother abused him.
Who am I to make him
go down this path?
What a smooth-talking guard.
Do you believe I'll kill you?
Yes.
You're the king.
Killing a mere guard like me
is nothing.
Your Majesty.
We have a problem.
The rebels have surrounded the palace.
♪I forgot you were so serious♪
♪Memories opened the door♪
♪The more sincere your promise♪
♪The deeper the wounds♪
♪Fate has written our script♪
♪We're destined to separate♪
♪The more innocent
the smile in the dream♪
♪The purer the tears♪
♪When our fate ends
and becomes unreachable♪
♪The person I can't find♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪