♪Lonely moon♪
♪Long street♪
♪The cold star failed to grant my wish♪
♪We all strayed into this world♪
♪My heart is like a wilderness♪
♪You laughed that the comings and goings
in this life is too deliberate♪
♪The silent waiting figure is far away♪
♪If the vast sea grows old♪
♪One unfinished game remained♪
♪We all cheat
because we're afraid of getting hurt♪
=Love Endures Eternally=
(Adapted from I'm Shameless'
Quick Transmigration: Defeated Again)
=Episode 15=
If he cares about you,
he should stand by you
without hesitation
and fight against everyone,
even if the whole world
doubts you and abandons you.
Chi Yuan, watch out!
How are you?
Why take the stab for me?
It happened suddenly.
Don't worry about it.
We have to hurry back
and find a safe place to heal you.
Let's go.
Alright.
You're alright now.
Bear with it.
Doctor, be gentle.
Your injury isn't fatal,
but you need to take good care of it.
Madam,
Change his dressing three times a day.
Eat a light diet
and eat more eggs.
It helps with healing his injury.
Doctor.
I'm not...
Thank you, Doctor.
Your Highness,
you took a stab for me today.
I'll keep it
in mind.
Here.
Chi Yuan.
I often wonder
whether I can replace Shen Zhaomu
if I have met you earlier.
Whether he appears earlier or later,
I'll fall in love with him.
My meeting, separation,
love and hatred with him
are all gifts from God.
It doesn't matter if we get a lifetime
or a short sweet time together.
From the moment I fell for him,
it doesn't matter
if others are good.
It's fine.
You'll find your true love.
I already met her.
What did you say?
Chi Yuan, go back to the military camp.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
No, you got hurt because of me.
I can't leave you alone.
It doesn't matter. I...
Stop talking.
Drink some porridge.
Do you want a room?
Two good rooms for tonight.
Sure, I'll arrange it for you.
We'll reach the military camp
tomorrow night, right?
Alright. That way, please.
Take care.
Qingyun?
Why are you here?
Young Master Zhaomu
wants to catch up with you,
find out the truth, and find you.
Hasn't he pinned
the blame of poisoning General
on me?
Why bother?
I'll investigate it myself.
If there's proof that she poisoned him,
I'll punish her according to the law.
Young Master Zhaomu, Miss.
You two have feelings for each other.
Why are you so harsh toward each other?
How have you been lately?
I was so worried.
How about having a meal together
after we put away our belongings?
Sure.
No need.
Indeed.
I'm just here to get some porridge
for Young Master Zhou.
You're not even Princess Consort yet.
And you're already so virtuous.
How impressive.
At least Young Master Zhou
isn't like some people.
At least he knows what trust is.
Ms. Chi Yuan.
How about I accompany you?
Sure, let's get porridge
for Young Master Zhou together.
What are you doing here?
I...
Shouldn't you
be accompanying Prince Zhou?
I'm just worried
that it would be dangerous
for you to walk alone.
I just came out to stargaze.
I also don't want to hear
any more explanations from you.
I can investigate it myself.
I didn't plan to explain to you either.
Why are you still following me?
The starry sky isn't yours alone.
What's wrong with me admiring it?
Are you the Chi Yuan I know?
You hit me again.
Do you think I can still trust you?
I don't know.
(Favorability: 30)
I'll trust you one more time.
My legs are numb.
I can't stand.
Do you want me to carry you on my back?
Hold me.
Don't let Shen Zhaomu
get to the military camp alive.
Let alone
let him return to the capital alive.
If you meet Chi Yuan on the way,
kill her as well.
♪I forgot you were so serious♪
♪Memories opened the door♪
♪The more sincere your promise♪
♪The deeper the wounds♪
♪Fate has written our script♪
♪We're destined to separate♪
♪The more innocent
the smile in the dream♪
♪The purer the tears♪
♪When our fate ends
and becomes unreachable♪
♪The person I can't find♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪