♪Lonely moon♪
♪Long street♪
♪The cold star failed to grant my wish♪
♪We all strayed into this world♪
♪My heart is like a wilderness♪
♪You laughed that the comings and goings
in this life is too deliberate♪
♪The silent waiting figure is far away♪
♪If the vast sea grows old♪
♪One unfinished game remained♪
♪We all cheat
because we're afraid of getting hurt♪
=Love Endures Eternally=
(Adapted from I'm Shameless'
Quick Transmigration: Defeated Again)
=Episode 17=
What's wrong?
The cakes are...
Qingyun.
Qingyun, wake up. Help!
Get a doctor.
I'll get a doctor.
Qingyun.
Wake up.
Qingyun, how are you?
Qingyun, wake up.
(Zhang's Century-Old Pharmacy)
Qingyun.
I'll find the murderer
and avenge you.
Young Master Zhaomu,
I need a toilet break.
Chi Yuan.
Let me send you back
to Prince's Residence.
Shen Residence is now dangerous.
It's too risky.
I don't want to drag you down.
I'm fine by my own.
It's late.
And you're pregnant.
How could I not worry?
How about you settle down
at Prince's Residence first today?
Tomorrow morning,
I'll enter the palace
and find Eunuch Quan for you.
What do you think?
Alright, I'll follow your lead.
Your Highness.
Thank you.
Miss.
Miss, we have a problem.
Madam Cui is gone.
Mother's injury hasn't recovered.
Where can she go? Find her.
I've searched
all over the residence,
but I still can't find her.
Send someone
to Minister Cui's Residence.
If they find Madam Cui
colluding with someone
from Minister Cui's Residence,
report to me immediately.
Yes, Miss.
Mu.
You finally woke up.
Father.
You're not poisoned.
How can a little trick hurt me?
According to my investigation,
the people after us
are Shen Xin and Prince Zhou.
I thought it was His Majesty at first.
Who knew I raised Shen Xin
to be an ingrate?
Is Shen Xin trying to get rid of us?
Chi Yuan?
The secret report said
she already knew your identity
and the contents of the letter.
She probably worried that the rebellion
will involve her,
so she struck first
to gain the upper hand.
Chi Yuan must be in danger.
Father,
please send troops to rescue her.
Take good care of yourself first.
We'll discuss other matters
in detail later.
No.
Please take action immediately.
Mu.
Shen Xin,
how dare you break our agreement
and attack Chi Yuan?
Just like Shen Zhaomu,
are you hopelessly in love
with a lowly woman?
She was lucky
to escape
from being poisoned to death.
I warn you.
If you attack Chi Yuan again,
no need Shen Zhaomu,
I'll kill you first.
Kill me?
If you kill me,
who's going to kill Shen Zhaomu for you?
If you kill Shen Zhaomu yourself,
will Chi Yuan be with you?
Chi Yuan has fallen in love with me.
She's pregnant with my baby.
Is that so?
Are you that confident?
Guess
who Chi Yuan would help
if you and Shen Zhaomu
turned against each other?
What do you mean?
Prince Zhou.
You're just Chi Yuan's savior.
She's just grateful to you.
Do you really think
you can replace Shen Zhaomu
in her heart...
Shut up!
You have no right to comment
on what happens between Chi Yuan and me.
Calm down.
As long as you're willing
to continue cooperating with me,
I promise
that you'll be the only one
Chi Yuan loves in this life.
I don't need anyone
to teach me how to do things.
We can continue working together,
but please stop crossing the line.
Prince Zhou.
Since you care so much about Chi Yuan,
I'll give you a big gift.
♪I forgot you were so serious♪
♪Memories opened the door♪
♪The more sincere your promise♪
♪The deeper the wounds♪
♪Fate has written our script♪
♪We're destined to separate♪
♪The more innocent
the smile in the dream♪
♪The purer the tears♪
♪When our fate ends
and becomes unreachable♪
♪The person I can't find♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪
♪Passes through endless waiting.
Time goes by and things change♪
♪Yet I still guard the empty city♪