・～
(Ichiro) Saburo Jiro Come quickly
(Saburo) Hmm...
・～
・(Takeo) Hey! You guys!
Jiro! Saburo!
(Jiro and Saburo's frightening voices)
(Takeo) Jiro! Saburo!
(Jiro) Ah... Wow!
(Takeo) Ichiro!
This shitty brat
Uh uh
(Takeo) Drop it!
Ichiro!
・～
This kid
Hmm! Ah!
Ah! This... this
Wow!
Damn brat! Ah!
(Groaning)
Wow! Ah!
(Jiro and Saburo's cry) (Takeo) Who did it?
(Jiro and Saburo's cry)
Who is it?
Saburo! Tell me!
Who did it?
Saburo! Who did it! (Crying voice)
Hey! Jiro! (Crying voice)
Tell me! Who is it? (Jiro and Saburo crying)
Ichiro! Is it you? (Groaning)
Did you do it? Uhh uh ah!
Hey!
What? What is those eyes!
Do you hate it? Do you hate me?
I wonder who he looks like!
Damn brat! Ah! Ah...
(Three cries)
big brother! big brother!
(Takeo) Ichiro! Ichiro!
Hey Ichiro! Ichiro!
(Jiro Saburo) Big Brother! (Takeo) Ichiro!
(Jiro Saburo) Big Brother!
The damn brat...
Saburo Jiro Leave it alone
(Iida) This time... Ah, thank you very much
(Suzuki chant)
(Strait) Erlangjun
a little bit
At times like this,
Outlet malls scheduled to be constructed next year
It looks like it's going to overlap with the land that my father had held.
I think the city will buy the land.
Here, only inheritance is solid
yes
People who live there will do something over here
Hey (Wakabayashi) Ah
Construction plan
So please
yes
Thank you very much for Professor Oizumi today
I think my dad is happy too
(Oizumi) Grandpa was a great person who made this town bigger.
I have to become a great politician once I grow up.
Would the mayor be good? Ahahaha...
(Miki) Daichi: See, what's "Yes"?
Sorry this kid...
(Kishi) Are you shy like your father? Haha
Well, please
thank you very much
(The sound of the door opening)
(Kanshi) Good morning (sound of door closing)
(Hiroshi) Manager Good morning
Good morning
Come on, wake up, come on, wake up, yes
Yes Good morning
Yes yes yes yes... yes yes
(Aya and the others)
(Hiroshi) Manager, it's the phone
Manager
Manager Jiro has called me.
(Slap sounds) Manager!
Manager, yes
Come on, yes yes yes yes please prepare
(Aya) Hey Sabu-chan Where are you coming?
A little
It's been a while Jiro-chan
It was 3 o'clock, you're still the same
Bad Bad
Why did you send an email saying that the funeral and burial didn't come?
Can't go, why are you going?
Come on this for you
I don't need my father's bones
Anything like that is just a father
(Aya) The cheeks are really soft
Tw...
Jiro-chan How much has he been thrilled by this guy?
I guess I didn't forget
He's dead Saburo
He's dead
(Miki) Daichi, come over here
It's more about his legacy
I want this land at Shimobashi to give it to me 3,200 tsubo.
If there's something you want in the heritage
I don't mind if the others are given priority to inheritance.
Only here is it really necessary for this job
It's bad but...
I don't need it
I don't need that thing
Haa...
There are a lot of contracts and documents
Well then, see you later
Um... I'm Iida, a lawyer.
thank you
Saburo
Come and eat at home once in a while
So I have work
(Aya) Ah
Ah, Sub-chan, take this
(Momo) Like (Aya) That's good
♪(Car Steleo)
♪～
(Sudden Brake Sound) (Aya Momo) Oh
(Aya) What's wrong? Sabu-chan (Momo) was surprised
(Aya) Ah, I'm coming (Momo)
(Momo) A little... Sub-chan?
Wait a minute (Momo) What?
・(Saoli's gasp)
(laughter)
(Saoli's gasp)
(Moderator) So now...
(Citizen) It's making me wait too long It's making me wait too long!
(Moderator) Construction scheduled for next year
Regarding commercial outlet malls
I would like to start a talk session with citizens
(Citizens' squeals)
(Moderator) Well, then
From City Council member Oizumi Genjiro:
I would like to hear your opening greetings
Eh, please be quiet (citizens' heckling)
(Moderator) Please be seated and quiet.
The meeting will never start (vibrators).
Eh, please be quiet
There may be opinions for each of you.
First, I would like to decide after discussing the matter.
Please be quiet
I wish I had entered first
I told you because there's someone there after all
I didn't expect to come again so I felt nauseous
(Saol) Wow, I was surprised
yes?
・～
You Kamito Ichiro?
Who is it? you
Kamito Saburo This is Jiro-chan
Sorry for the inconvenience
Itte! Who is it? you
And... It's Kamito Jiro Jiro
Who is that guy?
My younger brother, Saburo Kamito Saburo
a little bit…
What...
I will inherit the inheritance
picture?
what? Notification
Even the father's name...
Why…
(Shatter sound)
I'll get the inheritance
Hey
Jiro-chan
Hey!
・～
(Iida) This is effective if it's real
(Miki) What?
(Iida) Notarized documents are official documents.
It is highly binding as a suicide note
I wonder if I'll be able to win even if I take it to court
(Miki) No no
"My father died so I'm back after 30 years."
"I'll get the inheritance"
That's not going to be allowed, right?
I'm a lawyer, so I'm somehow hiring him for another person.
(Iida) But I met my dad during his lifetime.
The names of the two are written
(Miki) Is she really a big brother?
Well, I don't know what the face is
Big Brother was when I was in fourth grade.
It's Ichiro (Miki) Why don't you know?
When I was scarred, I was hit by my father
(Miki) Haa...
But, you still don't know, right? That's Ichiro's big brother
(Iida) I'll go to that notary public office and check it out.
I think it's probably real
(A sound of shaking)
(Miki) Who has been taking care of that crazy guy for so long?
Hey…
Why don't we have the right to inherit the inheritance?
Hey
What did you sleep with him?
♪(Steleo)
♪～
(Hiroshi) Good morning
(Aya and the others' fuss)
♪～
(Kanshi) Wow
(Aya and the others) Whooo!
♪～
Manager: Has the manager's father passed away?
I asked Yamashin's old man today
My dad isn't talking
Yes (stomping the music)
(Miki's gasp)
Ah... I'm cumming... I'm cumming
Wait a minute and cum inside!
Uhh... ah...
Ah... ah... ah... ah...
(The two breaths)
I'm not a college student anymore
(Hard breathing)
You're going to work as a vigilante?
ah
It's a course to promote leadership, so do your best
I know
♪(Speer)
♪～
♪ (Vigilantes) In the land of Musashi
♪ Our footsteps resonate
♪ Protect the happiness of your family
♪ Proceed together
♪ Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,
Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Proceed together
♪～
♪ The sadness that has been engraved in my heart
♪ Stick our vows
♪ Blood Alliance Umbrella Conflict
♪ Join together
♪ Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,
Hallelujah!
(Amemiya) My Keyaki Crime Prevention Association
Founded in 1969, when the University of Tokyo was in conflict.
Up until today, we have protected our city for about 50 years.
Be aware of being a member of a traditional crime prevention association.
Let's be careful not to be embarrassed by our seniors
I look forward to seeing you again tonight
(Vigilantes) Please! (Amemiya) So, the leader
Eh, last week
An incident in which a high school girl is attacked while returning home from cram school.
It happened in the Shimobashi area
They split into forces and patrol with a focus
Oh, then
Starting this month, young members will be joining us.
So one at a time
(Rikuto) Umm...
Recently, there have been more crimes among foreigners.
Look closely on social media
I thought I had to do something myself too
thank you
(Cheers and applause)
Thank you very much (vigilantes) Ui
(Vibilants) Follow me
(Vigilantes) Be careful (Vigilantes) Yes
(Vibilants' talk)
(Vibilants) There were quite a few trash scattered around the garbage dump, right?
(Energy stop sound)
・Wait this amateur!
・(Saol) Stop it and let it go!
Let go! What is this guy
Don't be kidding me, hey! (Saol) Kyaa! it hurts!
Where are you going?
· picture? Hey! Where are you going? ・(Saol)Crow!
(Enzyme start sound)
(Saol) Just take it easy!
Hey! This guy, Saori!
Where are you going this guy!
Why not take me to the station?
Why early...
quickly! Hey, I'm coming, so please let it go soon Hey, hurry up!
Yes, thank you for the call, it's "Honey Heaven."
yes
How many minutes would you like?
picture?
(Soul's sob)
(Saol) Seriously the worst
In fact, in Saori:
I thought it might be a bit dangerous in terms of money
He's kind and smart...
(Sound of slurping)
I thought it might be okay to go in Saitama.
Chased like a yakuza
I'm running away to drugs
Bakaichiro... Bakaichiro!
What was he doing in Tokyo?
Yokohama
Sakuragicho
I came with the company went bankrupt
・～
There's still an uphill to Tokyo
(Sound of slurping)
(Saol) Thank you
do my best
Come on, don't grab the weird guy and say you can't go quickly
Well then
bye bye
(Kanshi) This house
So, I'll come and pick you up in two hours.
(Aya) I'm coming (Hiroshi) I'm coming
ah…
・～
Hmm...
Wow... ugh
・～
(Aya) Eh, oh, a moment...
Hey! Just what?
Hey... no!
I don't like it anymore
Hey... stop it! Hey!
(Aya's throbbing voice)
That's it!
a little bit
Ah, ah, uh, ah!
Ugh! Ah! Ugh!
Uh uh
Year! Yes
Uh, uh, year!
what up?
a?
That's the address?
Don't be kidding me, hey!
I'll be there soon, wait a minute
(Female student) Go home! (Male student) It's not us
(Male student) You shouldn't take a photo
What about (female students)? Stop (vigilantes) Go home, go home
Accident Barka
Accident Accident Accident Accident Accident Accident...
Accident
Accident Accident Accident Accident
So, let's head to the Shimobashi area next.
(Vibilants) Yes
(Nakura) High school students are really not listening to what they say
That's a problem
(Hiroshi) Sorry, Manager
I don't know... sorry!
(Aya)
(Hiroshi) Sorry...
I'll take you to the hospital but...
It's fine, go quickly!
yes
Hey
Hey!
You're really Ichiro
(Chinese roars)
(Ube) Hey hey hey hey don't eat outside
(Nagamine) It's getting excited
Sorry (vigilantes)
(Coin) What is it?
Um, us
He's a patrol around the city, but (yen)
There are people around here making a fuss in the middle of the night.
There's a complaint
(Coin) Huh? It's still 8 o'clock, isn't it?
Do you do this every day?
Well, if it doesn't rain
(Chinese)
(Ube) Uh, you know, a high school girl was attacked around here last week.
There are also complaints about people making a fuss outside and people saying they're scared.
Do you know your position? Hey
(Coin) What... What? position…
(Ube) What? (Liu) Huh?
(Nagamine) Please stay calm, please stay calm
(Zen) Yes, you know (Nagamine) I understand.
(Coin) Wait a second, wait a second
You guys are working properly
Yeah, I'm paying rent too
It's fun to eat together like this at night
(Changmine) Calm down, calm down (Liu) Huh?
(Nagamine) No, I'm drinking too much (sigh)
(Liu) Hey
An illegal foreigner like you is the best
(Vibilant) Hey! What are you doing? Stop it
(Comment)
(Shatter sound)
(Riku-jin) Hey, damn Chinese! Everyone dies! Everyone dies!
Everyone dies! Everyone dies! Hey, let's be Chinese!
Hey! Take it easy, take it easy!
Let's go early
(Chinese anger)
This caused a situation that blew the history of vigilantes into muddy.
I'm very sorry
Take responsibility for the leader...
(Oizumi) Well, that's good
If they leave the Shimobashi, it's two birds with one stone
Is there anything else to see? (Ube) Yes
(Oizumi) Write an article
The other side came out first
(Secretary) Yes
Ube-san, a bit
(Oizumi) I need you guys to get stronger too
Sorry I'm embarrassed to my ancestors
(Oizumi) I'll call an acquaintance of Iruma, huh?
Let me train you?
(Strait) Erlangjun
Ah... yes
What's going on with the land at Motobashi? inheritance
That's a bit... there's a problem
I heard that my eldest son is back
Sorry, um...
My eldest son returned to the house and had a notarized certificate.
What do you mean?
yes
That's not good
Can't you give it up?
That's that kind of troublesome brother.
What's your name?
picture? Oldest son
Ah, it's Ichiro
Ah, it's been a while
(Sawaki) Yes... Yes
Yes, I'll let someone find it
Yes yes it's okay
Yes Yes Hello
(Peeing sound) (Osako) Yes
Yes I understand, thank you very much
Yes, I'm sorry
(Choi) Yeah... I'll give you a dad! (Mochida) Oh
(Daijima)YoishoYishoHaha...
(Mochida) Oh oh oh oh oh (Kajishima) Hey hahaha
(Osako's spitting sound)
(Daijima)Yay (Mochida)
(Peach) Bamboo shoots I want to eat bamboo shoots
(Teaked) Bamboo shoots? (Momo) Yes
(Tell) Yes, is one okay? (Momo) Thank you
So maybe I'll have some meat too
(Sakura) Thank you for the soup too (momo)
Aya quits the store
(Kanshi) Haa...
(Sakura's sob)
Eat it
(Kanshi) Sorry, please give me oolong tea and a bottle of beer.
(Shop clerk) Yes
(Aya) It's fine, so take it with you
Because it's not needed
thank you
(Sakura) Ah... Aya-chan
(ランチ)
Excuse me
It's last month's worth
(Osako) (Choi) Yes
(Osako) Apparently one person has quit
Why don't you report it?
Sorry it was sudden
Why did you quit?
There's a bit of a boring problem
(Osako) We've decided whether it's boring or not.
Oh, do you know what it means to have a butt?
Sorry, go away
Haa...
Hey
Ah...
Hey, my eldest son seems to be back
Let the rights of Shimobashi be waived
picture?
(Osako) Even if you inherit... (Cheek Sakura) Sorry
(Osako) Even if my second son inherits
Either is fine
I don't need to wear a towel
(Sakura) Sorry, it's too...
That kind of meaning...
(Osako) Let's talk this week
If I can't, I'll go straight to you
Itte!
(Sakura) Ah, sorry (Osako) tick
Um... sorry
Go it's this week
There's no time!
Hey, dirty ass, head over here
(Sakura) Yes... It's...
Hi...
Ugh...
(The sound of the door closing)
(The sound of the car door closing)
(Groaning)
Who are they?
Is it true that you have 400 million yen in debt?
(Groaning)
My woman who was pounded by you has quit
Ha
Hey
Please let go of the land of Shimobashi that I was looking at the other day
I'm fine, please give it to Jiro-chan
Why isn't it?
Anything
The rest is good, but that's not good
Hey wait a minute
Hey!
Wait a second!
Wait a minute!
Do you remember when I crossed here a long time ago?
The day my mother died
You stabbed my father's neck
The three of us went to fill in the knife.
You know, "Scary, scary" doesn't pass at all
Why did you leave and Jiro-chan leave?
Because it's going to have a head
Even in this shitty countryside, just looking at odds makes me feel headed
If so, don't come back
If you don't come back then nothing will change
Even if you plunge into the hole in your ass, you don't have to plunge
You know, nothing's going to change
I thought I'd give you medical expenses with the inheritance.
I don't need it anymore, huh
a…
Ah...
Haa...
Hmm
You!
Ah!
(Groaning)
(Hard breathing)
(laughter)
(Strong voice)
(Voices between Ichiro and Saburo)
Come on, come
Come on, come on!
Hahaaaah!
Hey! Hey! a little bit!
You! Hey!
Ah... stop it for a moment, I get it, I get it, stop it!
Is my father's notarized certificate so frustrating?!
Hey! Stop it for a moment, no good Saburo!
(Hard breathing)
Hey, go across, go across, go across
No, what are you doing?
Okay, ah, ah!
It's also yours!
You know, you couldn't face anything, but what?
I guess they couldn't protect anything, but hey!
Stop it...
Hey
Stop it!
Stop, I know I know
Stop it... Ah! ah…
Hey, it's painful, it's
(Scream)
Hmm
Understood!
Ah ah ah!
Ah wow
Ah
(Koibuchi) Once you grab it, defeat it immediately!
Faster!
more!
(Rikuto) Eeee!
(Koibuchi) Oh, that's good
(Rikujin) Thank you (Koibuchi) You guys, let's put in the special forces.
Take the Ground Self-Defense Force, because the Ground Self-Defense Force is young, what?
(Ono Rikuto) Thank you
(Riku-jin) Come
(Amemiya) It's effective to destroy Self-Defense Force members.
Apparently there's a dojo near Iruma Air Base.
I'll take the 2nd squad today too.
picture? Shimobashi area
You should focus on turning, so you can get it from Professor Kishi
Huh? Didn't you hear it?
(Vibilants) Please
(Amemiya) Yes, please
Yes, thank you very much
(Vibilants) I'm so motivated
(cheek) I like to add lotion
(Momo) Why do I have to do it?
Help me
(cheek) No no no no no no no no no no no no no
(Sighing sound)
(Vibilants' talk)
(Rikuto) Ugh... Itte...
Ha... Ha...
(Chinese)
(Rikujin) Itte...
(Vibilants) What's wrong? Hey, what's wrong?
What's wrong, hey
(Ono) Hey hey!
(Vibilant) It's bloody (Ono) Hey Rikuto! Hey!
(Vibilants) What's wrong? Are you okay?
This is crazy...
What happened, hey (Rikujin) I got it, I got it...
(Ono) Ambulance! (Vibilants) Are you okay?
(Vibilants) Call the ambulance, it's dangerous, it's dangerous...
(Vibilants' panicking voices)
(Ono) Hey!
Wait!
Hey wait!
(Vibilants) Follow me, chase me
(Ono) Wait!
Wait!
(Vibilant) Hey! (Ono) Wait!
(Vigilante) Ono-kun Take care (Ono) Wait!
(Vibilants) Wait, come on! (Vibilants) Better to stop the bleeding
(Nurse) I'll come again when I finish
forever?
Ah I understand yes
(Nakura) What did you think?
(Reporter) It's a huge fuss
Even blindness
(Nagamine) Ah... Is that so?
Sorry, there's a parliament (Nakura) yes
(Nagamine)Thank you for your hard work
(Reporter) It's a big stir
(Protest group roars)
(Chairman) 23 votes in favor
(A rustling of pros and cons)
(Chairman) 9 votes against
As I just reported
Proposal No. 1, with a majority vote
In large-scale commercial facilities in the Shimobashi area
The proposed land readjustment business plan is:
It was passed as proposed
(Kishi)Thank you for your hard work Congratulations to Mr. (American)
Congratulations (Kishi) Thank you for your hard work
Oizumi-sensei
Congratulations to you (Parliament) (Oizumi) Ah
Congratulations to you (Parliamentarian)
(Oizumi) Thank you, hard work
(Male) Teacher came Teacher came
(Male) Teacher Teacher! Congratulations (male)
Starting this weekend, a mall executive committee will be established with young people in the midst of the weekend
Those who cannot inherit the land cannot enter
Do you understand?
yes
Foreign villages will be here
You just have to do the ground!
Tw...
If it were your dad, it would be easy
yes
I don't need incompetent people from my group.
Yes (injection)
(Voices of applause and encouragement)
(Cough)
(Miki) Don't make that kind of face
I'll do something
Hey Daichi Daddy, isn't it okay?
(Daichi) Yes (Miki) Yes "Daddy, do your best"
(Day) Daddy, do your best
(Miki) Uuuuuu well done
Hmm...
Tw... hmmm...
Why can't you give up on the land?
Other lands are good, the moto bridge is bad
Why is it?
The old man who went to war over there
This is the first land I bought when I returned from Manchuria.
With the money I picked up scraps of iron
There are good lands and bad lands to sell
There are Chinese people living there?
ah
It's been a long time
Don't pay off your debts?
The Yokohama number I came to the other day is collected.
The yakuza are moving around this big approach too
I won't sell there
I don't know if it's a mall or something...
If you drive, you can find something like that in Kumagaya and Ota.
Woo
Understood
The story of heritage is fine
There's something else I need to talk about
Let's go out dinner together with Jiro and the three of us
Hey
ah
That's right
Can you go home today?
Okay, go home
quickly
I'll go out to eat soon
(Eleveter arrival sound)
(Miki) Ah
It's not very good, but this is a condolence from the vigilantes
I'll leave it here
Sorry, the culprit hasn't been caught yet
Such a village
I hope it's gone soon
(Choi)
(Shop clerk) Excuse me
welcome
(Kaiseshima) Osako-san (Osako) Huh?
I don't have any contact at all, are you okay?
It's not possible after all, sorry
(Osako) Huh?
Land matters I can't do it
Sorry
Do you know what you're talking about?
I'm quitting the store already
Why is it?
Sorry
I'm not going to quit
Monthly sales are also rising
Hey
I've already decided
Sorry
(Osako) Hey
Who do you think he's been looking after you so far? This guy
Thank you very much to Osako-san.
I've been able to continue working forever...
Ah... haa...
(Scream)
(Groaning)
Ah!
(Osako) That's a crap, this brat (sound of hitting chopsticks with an ashtray)
(Osako) Hey hey! Does this guy hurt? Hey!
Hey! Let's put it in a neat shape (scream)
This guy isn't enough!
(Daijima) Osako-san... (Osako) Oh?
(Daijima) Osako-san, a little... (Osako) What's going on?
Hey, what's going on! Hey huh? This brat
Hey this guy
Hey, I won't finish it like this
Hey, what's going on (Daijima) Osako-san...
(Osako)Oi (store clerk)C
(Osako) Hey, kidnap all the women
Pack it in a container (Choi) Yes
Hey, brat, listen carefully
I'll abandon the land title, let my eldest son write the memo slip
If you can't do it tomorrow, the woman will sink into the soapland
Once the time passes, I won't go directly
(Shop clerk)C
Damn... ha ha ha...
(Sighing sound)
(Groaning)
Haa...
Ugh...
(Scream)
(Shop clerk) Ahhh...
(Cough)
(Hard breathing)
(Nurse) Ishihara-san, the lights are off now, so I'm looking at it too much...
♪(陸人)
Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
(Ono)Oh (Rikuto)Oh
This (Ono) Huh?
I got it (Ono) Yes
♪(陸人)
Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,  Hallelujah!
♪ Glory,  glory,
Hallelujah!
Oii oi
(Hiroshi) Ha
(Groaning)
(The sound of the door opening)
(The sound of the door closing)
Oh it's 5 o'clock tomorrow
a? "Sorry"? (Cheeks' screams)
(Osako) That's fine, I'm fine
But there are a lot of stuff in our group too
Do you understand? Oh, "Wait"? (Daijima) Come on, go up
(Osako) You, how many more years should I wait?
It's not even a second late, tomorrow at 5 o'clock
Do your best oh
Hey, let's go
(Checks and the others)
(sound of breath)
I can't
(Rikuto's laughter)
・(A sound of hitting the door)
・(The sound of hitting the door) Ah...
(The sound of turning on the light)
Hmm
I'll take a look (Miki) Yes
・(A sound of hitting the door)
Hey... a little
I get it, I get it, a bit...
teeth?
Jiro-chan
yeah?
Go with me, big brother
teeth? If the three of us don't talk
Saburo?
・(Fire truck silen)
Thirty years ago, the three of us went to fill in the knife.
Yeah
I'm going to see you all shit, my dad hit me every day
I'm at my limit now
Yes yes...
After my mother died
Ichiro's big brother
On behalf of us, stab our neck...
・・
Let's talk together Jiro-chan
you…
I don't care about heritage or shopping malls.
There's something more important
Hey!
(Miki) Come early in the village of Shimobashi!
teeth?
Jiro-chan says there's something even more important...
quickly! Professor Kishi is coming too!
There's something more important...
yeah?
(Miki) Quick!
Big Brother, it's no good if you don't persuade me...
Being killed...
Jiro-chan... Jiro-chan
(Sobbing)
(The sound of the door opening) Ah ha ha ha ha...
Saburo
That time
I stabbed my father's neck
It's you
(A sound of the door closing) (Locking sound)
(An ambulance silence) (The fuss of the heckling horses)
(Male) It's on fire, call me a firefighter
(Men) Run away, run away, run away...
(King's Chinese)
(Two people's Chinese conversation)
・(Sound)
Damn Chinese...
Hey, I won't let you get away
(Two people's Chinese conversation)
(Ono/Rikuto) Oh!
・(Fire truck silen)
(Wang and Liu's Chinese conversation)
(Sudden Brake Sound)
(Cryings from Ono and Rikuto)
(Rikuto) Don't let him get away! Hey!
・～
(Hard breathing)
(Oizumi) Foreign village is wiped out
(shore) And then the ground
・(ラット)
(Secretary) Please (The sound of the door opening)
(Katakura) Excuse me
Two Chinese people who were fleeing were seriously injured after three months of recovery.
The two who assaulted each other were arrested this morning.
He also acknowledged the fact that the arson was fired
(Oizumi) My eyes were hit first
Please don't blame too much
(Katakura) Yes
(Oizumi) I'll call the chief too.
Thank you for your hard work
(Katakura) Excuse me, I've come
(Kishi) Please keep me waiting
(Parliamentary) Excuse me
Excuse me (Parliament) Excuse me
(Oizumi) Mall executive committee members will be announced at tonight's celebration
Please be sure to be selected by anyone
(Parliament) Yes
So it's okay to go down, thank you for your hard work
(Parliamentary) Excuse me
(Parliament) Excuse me
(Councillor) Teacher: You were pretty motivated
He was a lawmaker
(Miki) Daichi (earth) Huh?
(Miki) Wait (Daichi) Yes
(Miki) Excuse me
(The sound of the door closing)
・(Footsteps) (The sound of the door opening)
(Saol) I'm here
Wow, it's gone
picture? Why haven't you cleaned it up?
Ah! This is mine already!
The worst
Eh... a bit
It's finished, huh?
(Cough)
(Shaking breath)
(Saol) Good luck
Okay, it's cold...
You... Wow, I was surprised
why…
What about Ichiro?
I went out
shopping
♪ Shopping
♪ Start a new life
♪ (Saolari's humming)
・(Footsteps) (The sound of the door opening)
(Saol) Welcome back
...Please write that you are waived to the land at Shimobashi.
Are you still saying that you're not selling that?
Hey, please make something with this, what time is it?
What time now? You can do some curry
Yes you can't cook?
Yes it's okay
Hey, please write it right away... Write it right away...
Let's go
・(Car braking sound)
Wait... just wait a minute...
Just a moment... Please Please Please Please...
(Mochida) You're shut up
Let the land of Motobashi go
I'll give up, write a letter
See
Take off your shoes
a?
Who are you telling me?
It's you, take off your shoes
(Osako) I'll kill you, I can erase this guy.
Try it, who are you?
Shall I stab you? Can you stab me like my brother?
(Daijima) Hey! Ah...
・(Car driving sound)
(Cough)
(Minato) Huh?
(Osako) Huh? what up
Who is it?
(Minato) I'm a creditor
(Osako) I'm a creditor too, do it later
No, we have a long history with him
I'm coming from Yokohama
(Osako) That's why
Let it go
a? (Osako) Twitch...
Who is the otaku... where?
(Osako) Huh? It's the Ishibe group
Tw... where is she?
Shall we talk a little further?
(Osako) Huh? (Minato) This is
(Osako) Hey hey hey hey hey hey wait a minute here
Hey stop
Hey, hey, kid! Wait here
(Oizumi) Oh, I'm busy today.
We are very grateful that many people have come to visit us.
As you know, the other day the outlet mall plan was
The city council passed the decision with a majority vote.
First of all, to all of you who have given us strong support and cooperation.
I would like to express my deep gratitude
(Sakurai) Hey (Daijima) Huh?
(Sakurai)Hey (Choi)Huh?
(Mochida) Don't slurp away, glasses
(Daijima) I'll kill you, yeah, this
(Choi) Are you shaking? This guy
(Daijima) Hey, are you licking me?
(Mochida) Oi (Daijima) Oi
Have you heard this (Mochida)?
(Daijima) Huh? (Mochida) Hey, damn it
It's you, you
(Daijima) Let's do it, this guy
(Voices entangled by the Jijima Islands)
(Mochida) It's disgusting
It's a place for women
You can go
(Kajijima)Hey... (Osako)We've already talked about it
We'd be fine if only we could get Motobashi.
Hey, collect documents
(My subordinates) Yes
(Osako) Hey, write a letter quickly, I'll kidnap that woman.
Take off your shoes
Oh my goodness, this guy I'll just say it messy and fill it up here
Sorry, big brother... big brother
(Osako) I'll fill in your memory as well, don't you go quickly
(Mochida) Go!
Hey, go!
(Oizumi) Oh, so now, towards completion in the year after next
An executive committee to promote this plan vigorously
I would like to launch it here today
We have selected a wide range of talent, from veterans to young people.
I will take this opportunity to make an announcement
First, the first person is Aoki Keiichi, a city council member
(Cheers and applause) (Aoki) Yes
Kishi-sensei, please
(The sound of the window opening)
(Sakurai) Wow, damn it!
It smells like a pig This town (Yamashita) Hahaha
(Sakurai) Please forgive me
I'll write the documents quickly, this guy
(Choi) Listen to Osako-san's story!
(Osako) Hey, do you have bad ears? Get quick
Chi... Get quick (Choi) Get quick quick Here
(Osako) Hey, where are you looking? This guy
For me, come quickly
Look over here, this guy
(Daijima) What are you doing, you should hurry up
(Osako) You're licking me
This guy is writing this
(Daijima) Get quick, do you (Osako) Are you listening? This guy
Are you licking it? (Daijima) Hey, he's doing his best
(Choi) Get quick, this guy (Osako) Write quick
I don't have time, are you listening? This guy
(Daijima) Get quick (Yamashita) It's over
(Sakurai) Ah, your nose is really stinky
It smells like pork, let's get out soon
(Daishima) Hey, what are you laughing (Sakurai) I'm sure I'll get my nose off
I'm sorry (Osako)
Have you been saying something silly for a while now? Huh?
Come to the land of people and be proud
He'll say something he's licked a lot, fat
(Sakurai) I guess the smell is stinky, but (Osako) Isn't it fine?
Will you die at once? Fat
(Sakurai) Try it, huh? (Osako) Let's put your head out here
(Sakurai) Come here (Osako)
(Sakurai) is it (Osako) Is it a bull?
Take off your shoes
(Groaning)
(Daijima) What are you doing? Here it is!
(Choi) Are you in your mind? This guy is sane
(Small voices)
(Saol) Ah
・(Voices that thrive)
(gunshot) (Saolai's scream)
(gunshot)
(Hard breathing)
(Groaning)
(Saol) Ikchan... Ikchan
Ik-chan... Ik-chan! I'm chan!
Year! I'm chan!
(cry)
Ik-chan... Ik-chan! Hey, I'm cum!
No... I don't
(cry)
Hey, I'm cum! No... I don't
I'm chan!
I'm chan! I'm chan! Ik-chan, no!
Ikchan... Ikchan... Ah, ah...
Ugh... I'm
(cry)
I'm chan! It hurts, let it go
I don't like it, let it go, cum!
I'm chan! I'm chan! No way
Let it go! I don't like it! No way...
I don't like it, I'm cumming! I'm chan! No!
No... I don't...
(cry)
Ikchan...
(Minato) Wipe the blood too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too, too,
(Yamashita) Yes
(Minato) Twitch...
What are you looking at?
Do it too
You do it!
(Sakurai) Ah... Yes!
(Minato) Don't leave it, make everything beautiful.
(Yamashita and others) Yes
(Minato)Tch... Haa...
Ah, sorry if it's not good
Something unexpected happened
Yes, the land is fine
Yes, I'll make the documents later
Yes, don't worry
It's okay, again
(Sawaki) Oh, if it's me
Are you OK with the phone now?
(Kishi) No
yes
Ah, is that so?
So I'll leave that to you
yes
Huh... So, continue yes
(Member of Councillor)...Thank you very much for your cooperation
(applause)
Thank you (Member)
(Oizumi) Wow, the other vice-chairman is...
He passed away unfortunately the other day.
The beloved of the rare politician Kamito Takeo
It's Kamito Jiro
(Applause and cheers)
The land is OK
Brother, he's gone somewhere again
Eh...
I've just been invited to introduce you
I'm Kamito Jiro, a city council member
This time, we will be looking at our city's...
It's a memorable thing to go down in history...
Outlet Mall...
(Buzzing)
Mall construction plan...
Executive Committee・
I was selected as vice president...
(Buzzing)
I am truly honored
(Sound of slurping)
Haa...
Wataru is about to change dramatically now
At this important time
As a city council member, for all of you...
For the future of Wataru City
I was given a place where I could put my strength into it.
I sincerely appreciate it
Wait a minute
・～
・(Sound of trying to open the door)
(The sound of the door opening)
Get in the car, hurry!
quickly
(Sakura) Ah...
(Sakura's frightening voice)
・～
Get on, ride
(Cheek's frightening breath)
Where are you going? Sub-chan
I have to go out here
・～
me too…
Do not be ashamed of the name of the Kamito family in Wataru City.
I want to do my best to flourish myself...
I'll do my best to risk my life.
What a...
Thank you very much
(Applause and cheers)
thank you very much!
・～
(Sakura) What's wrong?
Shonben
Wait a minute
(Enzyme start sound)
(Minato) Huh?
Big Bro, what's wrong?
a?
picture?
(Stinging sound) (Men) Oh my goodness!
(Minato's moans) (Minder) What are you doing?!
(gunshot)
(Minister) Take it out, bring it out, bring it out!
Isn't it late?
Isn't it poop?
(Misa) Ah, Sabu-chan, you came to help me.
It's here
He'll protect me after all
Yes 1000 yen
(Misa) 5,000 yen
What... Now?
My wallet is
Pay later (Misa) Yes
I understand
sleepy…
(Check) Yes...
I wonder if he'll come home early, Sub-chan
(Groaning)
ah…
・～