In the first round of tests,
all you Special Agents shone.
But this is only the cruel prologue.
The final number of Agent Badges
and the skydiving challenge
will be decided by this lakeside.
After testing everyone’s
disguise skills,
the second round
will now test
your one‑on‑one
head‑to‑head combat
attack and defense skills.
This mission is called
The Person in the Wind.
It’s also An Yu’s brand‑new single
just released today
at twelve, written by himself.
Sorry, thanks.
So he even writes lyrics.
The eight members will battle
each other one on one.
Each pair of players
holds a candle
and a fan.
They must follow the music
and dance,
while making sure
their own candle stays lit,
and fan out the other’s.
The winner advances
to the next round.
The final champion will win
an Agent Badge.
For our first battle,
these two “Great Generals” go up.
Bring the candles.
It’s out.
Won.
Come on down.
Bring the fans.
These two really are evenly matched.
Forget the game, they’re posing first.
Convinced now?
“General.”
Chengcheng, come on.
You’re giving him cupping marks.
Come on.
Let’s go.
Bing Ge.
Teach him a lesson.
Let him see clearly
how Northeasterners play this.
Come on.
Start fanning.
Magic trick.
That was crisp.
Come on, Jingyu.
Come on, big Jingyu.
Sir Huang.
Sir Huang, only you can stop him.
The guests are going to crush us.
No hitting people.
We really can’t beat them.
I’ll blow you out now.
Come on.
Okay.
It looks like
nothing’s happening,
but they’re secretly straining.
Defend.
This is
a dance.
Looks pretty good.
Yeah, fan him as a person too.
Fan him till he catches a cold.
Can this really decide a winner?
They’re stirring, here they go.
Blow with your mouth.
Wrap it up soon.
They’ll fall in love at this rate.
Attack.
Out.
Finally burned it down.
So it was slow‑burned out.
Finally boiled off his wax.
Xiao Hu.
Okay.
The style has changed.
See who gets a fever first.
Out.
Won.
You beat Brother Jingyu.
What, it’s finally me and Jin Chen?
Pick Teng Ge.
Pick me.
Let me deal with Daxi.
Fan him till he catches a cold.
Bro, you know…
Is this the candle‑blowing game?
I’m gonna fan you into a fever.
Still can’t blow this out?
Come on, Xiao Hu!
Teng Ge is out of breath now.
Honestly, even this doesn’t work?
It still hasn’t gone out.
You were about to sneak‑attack me?
No.
It’s not that kind.
Like those fake supermarket candles.
The rechargeable ones.
I fanned it like crazy twice,
and it still didn’t go out.
You try fanning it yourself.
Yours really won’t go out.
You see how hard it is for a veteran artist.
“Teasing the old man,” right?
“Teasing the old man.”
You blow out his, then.
Okay.
I’ve no faith at all.
No faith at all.
Awesome.
Been waiting for you forever.
Two fans and my legs feel ancient.
We blew it out together.
It’s a tie.
A tie.
Congrats.
In this round we’ll hand out
three Agent Badges.
Teng Ge and Daxi from the tie,
and the one with the most wins,
William.
Now we’re heading
back into the house
for our final round of tests.
What are you doing there?
I’m using Taobao Pailitao.
Look, same style found in seconds.
You can even buy Italian stuff here.
Of course.
With Pailitao you can also find
our Let’s Go Now family outfits.
For real?
Let me try.
Don’t tell me your top has a match too.
It really does.
Search “Let’s Go Now” on Taobao now
for a chance to get an 888 bonus.
I’ll try it too.
So much food!
Reflex reaction.
These guys are hilarious.
Xiao Hu didn’t react.
So he’s got no reflex.
He has no reflex.
What are you talking about?
Normally if you poke a guy like this
he tenses up hard right away.
Shows off his muscles.
Pretty much men everywhere
are like that.
Every inch.
Welcome to
my home in Italy.
Let’s not skip any dish.
Try a bit of everything.
Everything’s good, really.
Xiao Hu.
All this way,
have I treated you badly?
Not at all.
Bring me the pasta.
One fork and I’ll finish it.
Never thought
never in my life thought
pasta could taste this good.
Back then,
I invited this
Repin Academy of Fine Arts
Lifetime Honorary Professor
to paint this here.
They hung the middle one upside down.
Felt just like being home.
Next,
we’ll do our final round of tests.
We’ll test each Special Agent’s
judgment and language skills.
Soon we’ll battle in teams.
We’re already splitting teams, right?
Yeah.
My left side looks better.
I’ll stand on this side then.
Let me show you a stunning photo
I took of Teng Ge yesterday.
You’re annoying.
After two o’clock.
I was still pretty used to it.
Woke us right up.
It’s already past two.
This test is called
All members are split in two teams.
The two teams will take turns
Only The Knower knows the answer.
You must ask the Observation Team in English.
The Observation Team can only say yes or no.
When you guess the answer,
the team with fewer questions gets 1 point.
If they find The Knower, they get 1 point.
Do you know how this game works?
You haven’t told me yet.
Translate it for me.
Simply, it’s the four of us.
If you’re the one with the word,
you must guide the other three of us
to ask your team faster.
Then we have to guess the word
that’s written on your card.
Whichever team uses fewer guesses
is the team that wins.
But the one with the word
must really protect themselves
and not let the others find them.
Okay.
If you’re sure, say “yes.”
If you’re not sure, say “no.”
If it’s in‑between, could be or not,
if you’re unsure, say “both okay.”
When unsure I can’t say “no”?
Oh.
In the Northeast we say “ngh.”
That works.
Okay, it’s clear now.
Come on.
Let’s guess first.
Everyone, close your eyes.
The Knower, hold up one finger.
Everyone, open your eyes.
Ask quickly.
Come on, ask.
Should we ask if it’s for use
and then if it’s food,
and then if it’s a person?
Or ask if it’s a drink?
Is it food, not a drink?
Food, not drink.
No, just ask if it goes in your mouth.
Isn’t that better?
Some people even eat crap though.
Should we ask
if it has three characters?
In Chinese.
Three Chinese characters.
Or three English letters?
Chinese, of course.
Then it must be Chinese.
Let me ask then.
You ask.
Is it three Chinese characters?
Yes.
Daxi.
The spy got exposed so fast.
No.
Remember,
Teng Ge said “three characters.”
I still think we should ask first
whether it’s something you use.
Chengcheng wants to ask “Is it used?”
That’s too far‑fetched.
I think
that’s too far.
I think ask if it’s used first.
You ask then.
Next one.
Start.
The one with the word
really has to protect themselves
and not be found by the others.
Something to eat.
Just one.
My name is Fan Chengcheng.
What’s your name?
Both are okay.
After all those questions,
he asked Brother Jingyu,
“What’s your name called?”
Why?
Then I’ll ask properly.
I’ll ask Jingyu.
We’ve already finished asking.
Chengcheng
Next question.
Ask if it’s something you use.
Is it something we can use?
Yes.
But that question was wasted.
Honestly that question was trash.
It was a totally useless question.
Exactly.
This one is really—
trash.
Trash.
You’re like soldiers on the front line,
you yell, “Charge!”
so I charge forward.
After the first “shot,” you go,
“Who fired that stupid shot?”
No, we tried to stop you.
Ask if it’s something you use.
We couldn’t hold you back.
And you even sigh.
Ask if it’s a person’s name.
We already asked if it can be used.
He said it can be used.
“Sir.”
Some can be used, some can’t.
You’re the kind that can’t be used.
Nice to look at, useless in action.
Is it Fan Chengcheng?
No.
We didn’t ask.
We’re just venting among ourselves.
Yeah.
We’re just—
venting.
You got an idea?
This round,
it should be a person, right?
We already asked if it can be used.
Forget it, fine, whatever.
We already used that one.
The one we just asked—
Got any intel on your side?
Who asked that?
William.
Yeah.
Yeah, it was William.
It had to be William.
Is it clothing?
You ask.
Clothing.
Clothing?
No.
You asked that.
You asked and answered yourself.
I didn’t ask.
I didn’t answer either.
You said “Clothing” then “No.”
Did you ask or not, seriously?
I didn’t.
Then you didn’t.
Didn’t ask.
So no answer either.
You think I can’t handle you?
Even Teng Ge is taking that back.
There are tons we can use.
For cooking.
You can ask if it’s an appliance.
Is this a machine?
No.
I asked him, “Is it electric?”
He asked, “Is it a machine?”
No.
No, I said, “Is it…?”
Is it?
It’s not Aunt Ma.
Ma—
Ma Li.
Sister Li.
See that?
They all talk about you like this here.
It’s not clothing.
It’s not a machine.
But it’s something you can use.
Ask if it’s a pot.
Three characters.
pressure cooker.
Daxi
Ask if it’s for cooking.
Can you cook with it?
Ask who?
Xiao Hu.
Yes.
Just shout “pressure cooker”
right out for me.
pressure cooker.
Yes.
Yeah.
Of course.
I didn’t—
didn’t get any hints at all.
I came up with “pressure cooker.”
Such an obscure thing, a pressure cooker,
and I still guessed it.
“Kitchenware,” three characters.
Nothing much was left.
A big ladle.
We just play on a higher level.
Vote for William.
No.
How did you decide it was me?
You kept stopping us asking some things.
Three Chinese characters.
Is it a person or not?
That really wastes a question.
I say don’t ask about appliances.
You teach him how to say it.
This round, it’s William.
It’s him or Chengcheng, one of them.
I think so.
It’s a lady.
I didn’t get it at first.
I thought they were calling you Madonna.
I also think it’s Chengcheng.
Is it something usable?
Ask if it’s an appliance.
Ask if it’s a pot.
No.
He never made me feel
he was the spy.
He—
his first question was,
“What is your name?”
We send out two reps.
Play rock-paper-scissors.
We follow whoever wins.
You guys just
tear into each other.
Slap each other’s faces.
Whoever—
whoever stays last, not fainted,
we follow that person.
Trust me this once.
This afternoon, you and I,
didn’t we make some promise?
If I point out these two wolves right,
from now on, you back any vote I raise.
Deal.
Okay.
Yes, I’ll listen. You decide.
William.
Okay.
Yes or no?
Yes.
Nice.
That’s impressive.
We got it in just one guess.
Then from the very start,
we need to keep eyes on them.
Right.
We start watching now.
Who are you watching?
What’s wrong?
It popped right into my eye.
Feels like—
What shot into his eye?
A fart.
A fart blasted his eye all blurry.
No, his eyes got hit just now.
Let me blow on it.
Better now?
Careful, you’ll blow his eye out.
Keep your eyes on them.
Keep watching them first.
I’ll read it first.
I’ll read the word.
You guys watch them.
Everyone, close your eyes.
Chengcheng.
Got hit.
He’s stunned from the hit.
He can’t shut them.
He can’t close his eyes now.
His eyelids are swollen.
Knower, please show a one.
Okay.
Okay, everyone open your eyes.
Got it.
Who is the…
Chengcheng.
No.
I was asking Jingyu.
You already asked.
What are you trying to do?
No.
Not your turn.
I wasn’t asking you.
Question.
First, he used Chinese.
“Who is…”
You’re the only one on earth?
Chengcheng’s English name is Chengcheng.
My English name is…
Alright.
Take a break, bro.
Rest a bit.
I’ll ask first.
Go.
Teng, is it two characters in Chinese?
No.
It’s not two characters.
Ask if it’s three characters.
No problem.
If it’s not,
then it’s four characters.
You’re right.
On this little card,
you can’t fit many words anyway.
Then ask if it’s three characters.
Or just ask the answer outright.
Or we could just ask
whether it’s something we use.
Chengcheng.
Is it something you use?
Yes.
No.
That hit made you stupid.
It’s not two characters.
Which of you is the spy?
Give us a bit more info.
Yeah.
You spies…
Spy.
It’s not me, bro.
Acting. They’re acting.
An Yu, is it you?
Give us some info.
Just give me a little hint.
I’ll stump him with a question.
We only have two questions left.
Can I think of it this way?
It might not be an item we use.
It’s either a living thing
or it’s something to eat.
Let’s confirm if it’s food.
Ask if it’s edible.
First confirm if we can eat it.
Xiao Hu looks a bit like it.
Xiao Hu kind of fits it.
He’s pretending.
Can we eat it?
William.
Yes.
We can eat this.
Should we ask if it’s a fruit?
Then we’ll run out of questions.
Are you really this competitive?
We still don’t have enough answers.
Let’s just ask first.
Who cares how many questions?
Hey, can someone please save me?
This...
Am I the only one here who wants to win?
We’re facing one problem now.
Who’s going to guess this one?
I like being on your team.
Who’s guessing?
Why would we even get it wrong?
We’ve got a Spy, how can we miss?
You Spies, all of you...
First of all, I am not one.
Just give us some useful info.
All right?
Knower, please show one finger.
Yes, you.
Just give us something useful, okay?
Bro, if the Spy speaks up,
and gets exposed,
they still get extra points.
Relax.
We won’t find them out.
You three right now—
I haven’t spotted any of you.
The one who shouts out loud
definitely isn’t the Spy.
Just shout it out and be done.
What are you saying?
Why?
I don’t get what you’re thinking.
Teng Ge just shouted “pressure cooker.”
Did you suspect him?
Daxi shouted “pressure cooker.”
Did you suspect her?
They got straight eliminated, right?
How about this?
Let’s just rely on luck.
Bing Ge, what’s your fave food?
Let it just pop out.
Let the answer just pop out.
Just call it out.
Stop acting.
If something pops into your mind,
if it’s right, we win.
Might even be right.
Yeah.
What’s your favorite food?
Kung Pao Chicken.
Three characters.
Who said it’s three characters?
They said it’s not two.
Right.
Are you acting now?
It’s just ice cream.
One of you say it.
Somebody say it.
Time to see your acting.
Go on, say it.
Is it ice cream?
No.
No, Sir.
Please sit.
Daxi.
Is it a fruit?
No.
It’s not?
Then it’s a dish.
So is it a cooked dish?
You—
Yes.
It’s a dish.
Guide them toward “dish.”
Yeah.
Guide them.
You lot are pretty “dish-y” too.
No.
Right now we’re
back to the same problem again.
Who’s guessing this dish?
Yeah.
Hurry up and ask.
Don’t waste it.
Guess early, finish early.
Before the last question
You could’ve guessed it right
Let me put it this way
Di San Xian
I told you already
I
Liu Rou Duan
Do we have a spy in our team
Yeah
That’s so selfish
Did the spy forget the word
Your spy is too timid
This spy is way too timid
Guess which of them is the spy
All six of us guess together
Which one of them is the spy
How about this
Since you joined our team
we’ll show you two the word
Bro, listen to me
With my temper
if I were really the spy
I’d have confessed long ago
So now you rule yourself out too
He’s the only one left
If you don’t say it
we really can’t guess it
I’m gonna lose it
I’m really losing it, man
Tap me, I’ll ask
You really hate getting voted out
Your favorite three‑character dish name
Tell me three
I’ll pick one
Could it be Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
You guys… Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
How am I supposed to hint that
Give a hint
Hang on
How do I tell you
that it’s Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
Come on
Three two one, point at him
Three two one
No
Nope
That really is too brutal
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall, that one
How do you even hint that
Just now I secretly
did this to Bing Ge
Well
How’s that
Like this
What does this mean
Buddha
If you just blurt one out
and it’s right, we win
It might actually be right
Yeah
You should’ve tapped me
I didn’t see it
An Yu is so cute
It was so intense just now
If it were me I’d jump right up
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
Act out that “light‑bulb moment”
When you asked if it’s a dish
or a kind of fruit
I thought you were awesome then
But man, I still “died”
and couldn’t guess Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
Seriously
I don’t even
I just
I really didn’t know how to tell you
that it was Buddha Jumps Over the Wall
All I could do
If you’re the spy this round
just shout it out within two rounds
Okay
Can they give us a question
with similar difficulty
Okay, I accept that
Everyone close your eyes
Knower, please show “one”
Everyone open your eyes
I got it right away
We’ll do this for the first word
That thing I told you about
you ask this one directly
I’ll ask first
You go
Me then
The dish I told you about
could it be
It is
Who asks?
An Yu.
Me.
You’re right.
That feels great.
Look how that spy plays it.
Next time I draw it, I’ll just—
Is it Buddha Jumps Over the Wall?
Just watch me this round.
If I’d been this bold earlier,
I’d have exposed myself already.
Then Chengcheng must be the spy.
Who else could it be?
It’s still him.
I think it’s Chengcheng.
Chengcheng, is it you?
Yes.
They want us to think in reverse.
But we’re not.
They really didn’t.
They even acted a bit just now.
This time we won’t even act.
Who’s asking?
Seriously.
For real.
Just say it.
Who asks? You say.
You ask.
I’ll ask.
Go on, you ask.
You ask.
Fine, I’ll really ask.
Could it… could it be—
Let me.
If you know, tell me.
You know—
If you know, then you ask.
If not, don’t ask.
Could it be Peking Opera masks?
Peking Opera masks.
We won.
We won, An Yu!
Ask them, quick.
Ask.
Pick someone to ask.
Pick.
Guess who the spy is.
I can’t guess.
It’s too hard.
Way too hard.
How did you think of it, tell us.
This word is so hard to guess.
It’s way too tricky.
But whoever shouts out the answer
definitely isn’t the spy.
Who?
You still need to discuss this?
Who is it?
Buddha Jumps Over the Wall.
I thought I heard Huang Jingyu say
“Just say Peking Opera masks.”
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Guess wrong, okay?
An Yu.
Minus one point.
Sorry.
No.
Yes.
Doesn't it feel really great?
Just say it straight out.
Feels good.
Feels so damn good.
That Buddha Jumps Over the Wall killed me.
Congrats to Teng Ge and Chengcheng,
and to William and Daxi.
Each of you gets an Agent Badge.
I’ve got three now.
You’ve got three now.
Three already.
She’s got three as well.
Now William and Daxi have the most.
They’ve earned a skydiving card.
You can pick anyone you like.
Okay.
To skydive, or skydive yourselves.
You can’t pick me.
No.
Isn’t that how the game works?
I can pick anyone I want to jump.
But our bond won’t let you do that.
We can’t make him jump, right?
We…
Our bond won’t allow that.
But isn’t this just…
You lost, so you should obey me.
William, bro…
Pass it on.
They went so quiet, suddenly.
Power.
They’re so well behaved.
It feels great to hold the power.
Now you suddenly care about winning.
I’m so happy.
Tomorrow.
I’ll answer you tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
I was just testing your reactions.
In case tonight…
either of you gets a red envelope,
go ahead and accept it.
I’m giving you a chance.
You have one night to take it.
Today,
we're doing the Special Agents' final task:
skydiving.
The Let's Go Now team leaves Lake Como
and heads to the skydiving base
near Bologna.
It was founded over twenty years ago
and is one of Italy's main
skydiving centers.
It’s famous in the global
skydiving scene.
I heard
you're going to jump.
Are you jumping or not?
I’m definitely not jumping.
You’re not jumping?
I just want to see who’s brave
enough to actually jump.
You’ve done it before, right?
Once in a lifetime is more
than enough.
You’ve jumped before, right?
Yeah, and you’ll never want
to do it a second time.
An Yu, are you jumping?
Me…
I’m kind of scared to jump.
To be honest.
Daxi, you jump then.
I’m also
not really daring to jump.
Mainly, this weather’s a bit…
It feels
not really...
not really encouraging.
I always feel your first jump
should be
with clear mountains
and fresh water,
right.
breezy and sunny,
exactly.
bright sunshine,
yep.
and every shot looks amazing.
Yeah.
Actually, once the chute opens,
there’s no weightless feeling,
right?
Just that bit in front,
the first drop.
Yeah, anyway it’s only about
something like fifty seconds,
a minute.
About a minute.
I forgot, I don’t remember.
Xiaoyu, Xiaoyu.
Play the song
“Nothing Is Really That Bad.”
I still…
Sorry,
that song is not in the library.
This weather doesn’t really feel
great. A clear day’d be fine.
Then I’d be okay to jump.
We’re here anyway, right?
Get out.
Let’s go.
Let’s get on the plane.
I’ll take you up there, come on.
Who’s flying?
I’ll fly.
It’s fine.
I already learned for three
minutes yesterday.
Hop in. With me
we’ll be up there
in five minutes,
then you guys should jump.
Up there… forget it.
The cockpit’s too cramped.
You film first,
I’ll go make one run.
I’ll check what the
temperature is up there.
Can’t carry it.
If someone jumps, I’ll jump.
Today,
we didn’t take my blood
pressure.
Because of blood pressure issues,
Bing Ge wasn’t advised
to bungee jump.
That’s actually true.
Ever since I lost weight,
my body’s been like a baby’s.
Good morning,
my friends.
You three look like
you just got off a plane.
Here, let me fix that for you.
That big coat of yours is nice.
Looks perfect for skydiving.
Windproof.
Keeps you warm.
Did he stash a chute in there?
For emergencies.
You jumping?
If you jump, I’ll jump.
My jacket…
My thermals, my warm underwear…
Sir Huang is already ready.
The pilot is in position.
Got any thermal underwear?
We’ve got thermals.
Brought it.
They brought it for me.
I’m telling you,
if you tell him right now,
“I want to see my parents,”
he could even get them here.
I’ve trained before.
But I never actually jumped.
Why jump at all?
Change into long johns.
You change first.
I’ll see how you look jumping.
You do the first jump.
Aren’t we waiting for Teng Ge?
When he comes I can’t wear long johns?
He’s just putting on long johns.
He’s even got a flight jacket on.
Looks ready to jump down.
Welcome, pilot.
We were waiting for you, bro.
Waiting for you to hop on.
Welcome, both pilots.
Let’s go.
Come on, let’s go.
Jump, then.
No, you sit a bit longer.
Darn it, we’ll Photoshop a chute.
You’ll stand in
and represent us as having jumped.
Easy to key out this blue, too.
Let’s practice first.
You act like you’re a grenade.
As everyone knows,
a qualified Special Agent
must be ready to drop from the sky
and get close to the target.
So,
our final mission today is
a high-altitude skydive.
Here in Bologna,
with its open plains,
and stable weather,
it’s ideal for skydiving.
Next, we’re going to
experience for ourselves
this thrilling, extreme activity.
I hope everyone here can
gain a truly unprecedented
high-altitude adventure.
Let’s go.
Jump, then.
Just jump.
Bro, you jumping?
Yeah, I’ll jump.
Let’s go.
Go.
Come on.
We’re here anyway.
I’m scared.
It’s fine, come on.
You jumping?
Everyone’s jumping.
I’m definitely not.
Everyone,
the pro coach at the drop zone
just told us
that given the current weather
and the drop zone conditions,
we can only do one flight.
The number of people on board
is limited.
At most, three can skydive.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Okay.
Winner has to jump.
Come on.
So, winner jumps?
Rock.
Scissors, paper.
Rock, paper, scissors.
One more.
You go down.
Am I jumping or not?
Jump.
You jump.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Okay, the three of us.
You three.
We two will go with you.
Okay, we’ll go with you.
I bought this jacket 3 months ago.
Didn’t get to jump.
Didn’t get my wish.
Think of those two who bungee-jumped.
They’re skydiving again now.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
Put your hands on the harness.
Hold on and lift your head.
Look at the sky.
Then, when you jump,
imagine you are a banana.
Okay.
But keep holding on.
Then, for landing,
in the last 4 or 5 meters,
lift both legs together.
Land on your butt.
Got it.
Okay.
We can gear up now.
Is it okay this thick?
Too thick.
Too thick? All right.
No.
Your clothes won’t work.
He says mine is too thick.
Then wear mine.
Flight jacket.
Teng Ge, you wear mine then.
When you land on your butt,
lift my jacket up a bit.
Don’t scrape my jacket.
Okay?
Okay.
Perfect.
All right.
All right, thank you so much.
Nervous?
I’ll be nervous up there.
I’m fine for now.
Once the door opens, I’ll be nervous.
You got this.
Okay.
Bing Ge.
Are you a bit nervous today?
I’m fine.
Nothing’s wrong with me.
Coach sits in back.
You sit here, you hug him to jump.
Am I first to jump again?
From this seat, looks like it.
How about we switch seats?
I’ll go, I’ll jump first.
Okay.
First.
Let’s start, Bing Ge.
Okay.
Bye.
An Yu, mind your hands.
Will I suddenly faint midair?
No.
Not likely, right?
Free fall is only
45 seconds.
Forty-five seconds is not
a small number.
We still have to cook tonight.
Bing Ge.
Come back and start cooking.
By the time we see them,
will they already have opened?
Yeah.
We won’t see free fall then.
I can’t even hear the engine now.
They must’ve flown pretty far.
They must be really high up.
We’re at five hundred meters.
Five hundred meters.
Yeah.
We can already see the ground.
How high do we go?
Four thousand two hundred.
What do we do?
I really don’t dare look down now.
We’re up here already, too late now.
Sir Huang, why so quiet?
I’m scared too.
You two are such scared kids.
Bing Ge is still the brave one.
So many protect you, why so tense?
Only past the clouds is the sunset.
So beautiful.
Bro.
The sunset.
It’s gorgeous.
So beautiful.
This is amazing.
How high now, sis?
Three thousand three.
Nine hundred meters to go.
So I’m jumping first.
Let Bing Ge go first.
I’ll go first.
Bing Ge asked to jump first.
He’ll be second.
That’s confirmed now, right?
Then I’ll be the first to go.
Bing Ge.
Actually,
I wanted to share this for you.
It’s fine.
We two bros will guard him in center.
Bing Ge.
Sir Huang.
Three, two, one.
I suddenly got nervous.
What height now?
Four thousand two hundred.
At what height do we pull?
One thousand eight hundred.
What is it, an alarm?
Okay.
Let’s go!
Bing Ge.
Sir Huang.
Come on, is it that bad?
I’m scared.
My heart rate’s at one twenty.
Only one twenty for you?
My heart rate is—
Is that okay?
You got this.
Who’ll be first?
I guess the first
will be Bing Ge.
Should be An Yu.
Come on.
It’s so cold.
Everyone,
let’s go!
You only live once.
Everyone,
go!
We’re alive,
you only live once, friends!
Let’s go!
So awesome!
They opened!
Up there!
I see them!
Where?
They opened.
All three chutes are open.
Yeah, they’re open.
That one did a flip, see it?
That one.
What was that about, over there?
What’s going on here?
Look at that.
It did a backflip in the air.
See that?
No, that one kept flipping.
That one.
That one too.
No.
Thank you, coach.
Perfect.
This is a beautiful sky.
Yeah.
Are those your friends?
My friends.
And these?
Let’s go.
How did he end up there?
Come back.
That one’s heading for the treetops.
That’s not An Yu, right?
When you skydive down from up there,
there are people below catching you.
It feels insanely good.
Here he comes.
Who’s this?
Bing Ge.
Bing Ge!
That was amazing.
How was it?
It just…
It felt like I became immortal.
He’s here.
Who is that?
His face is so pale.
Darn it, the jacket.
The jacket.
My jacket.
Wang Anyu.
We’re still alive!
He’s crying.
Scary or not?
Thank you, coach.
Thanks.
No, I just…
Never seen your face this white.
Are my friends over there?
Yeah.
Yes.
Felt crazy good, huh?
Was it awesome?
Awesome.
Felt crazy good, huh?
It was insanely good.
When we went through the clouds,
my face almost froze solid.
I covered my face with my hands.
Yeah?
Lots of moisture.
Yeah.
You can see the sunset up there.
Bing Ge.
Really?
Yeah.
Above the clouds there’s a sunset.
It’s really beautiful.
I’m telling you,
the sunset up there is stunning.
Hurry and take your gear off.
Hurry.
Come on, let’s go again.
Let’s go again.
I’ll even give you my flight jacket.
My lucky jacket.
Pretty good, right?
So good.
Fits really well.
Totally worth it, bro.
Worth it, right?
The plane’s back.
Why’s the plane flying like that?
Now it’s showing off.
It was just an exhibition jump.
A show jump.
We’re just putting on a show.
He didn’t get to enjoy it up there.
So he’s flying for fun now.
Thanks.
Thank you.
The more I hear, the more I regret it.
Nothing to regret. A bet’s a bet.
A bet’s a bet.
I was checking my heart rate.
Over one hundred twenty.
That’s just normal,
like when you’re walking.
Up there it was just me
chatting with Bing Ge.
Sir Huang didn’t say a word.
Watch the replay later.
He never said a word.
Only before we jumped
I said, “Bing Ge, Sir Huang,
three, two, one, let’s go!”
Just that. Then nothing.
Impressive.
But it’s really great, not like—
I think this, compared to bungee,
is way more fun.
With bungee you have to get
yourself scared first,
then the weightlessness,
then coming back up,
then weightless again.
I was also there going,
“Ahhh” for a while.
My teeth were freezing.
So I clenched them shut.
But without long johns, no way.
It’s really chilly up there.
Your hair right now is
“post‑skydive” hairstyle.
Don’t wear a hat.
That’s the hair of your bravery.
Why cover it up?
You make a good point.
Have you ever been in a cloud?
It’s so cold in there.
Feels full of tiny ice chips.
They whip against your face.
And then—
A Northeasterner hasn’t felt that?
When I bike a bit faster,
I already feel that.
This is Bing Ge’s first skydive.
First time.
How did it feel?
Just pure fun.
Worth all this fuss after?
All this promotion for it?
If I choose again, I pick this.
I won’t pick bungee jumping.
Bungee is about challenging yourself.
When you jump off,
you feel you’ve broken your limits.
This one really opened my eyes.
And while I was flying up there,
I wanted to do the Superman pose,
but I felt that would
probably throw off our balance.
We started spinning in circles.
So satisfying.
And when I was up there,
I was not nervous at all.
Not nervous at all.
But when I came down I was pale.
It’s chilly up there.
It’s cold in the sky.
I was freezing.
So cold.
I really was freezing.
Yeah.
Our video is already out.
No, wait.
What video?
The video of your jump just now.
Did you manage your face well?
Then we’ve got it.
We’ve got it.
Wang Anyu, want to step aside?
I kind of want to leave first.
But then I thought,
didn’t I just now also
brag a bit about it?
Down there with the guys,
I was boasting like crazy.
Said I wasn’t scared at all.
Then they played the video.
Let’s watch Sir Huang’s first.
No, watch Anyu’s first.
Sure, either way, go in order.
An Yu, Bing Ge, then me—
that’s how the three of us jumped.
We can follow that order.
Me.
I’ll embarrass myself first.
Show them the moment the door opens.
When the door opens,
it’s super nerve‑racking.
Look at An Yu’s reaction.
Such a change from door closed to open.
An Yu studied English so long,
and in the end he only shouted,
Watch An Yu.
Everyone,
An Yu—
“You only live once!”
He wouldn’t let me shout it.
“You only live once,” see that?
He didn’t even finish.
“An Yu, you only live once!”
The coach said, “What are you doing?”
“Get your hands back here!”
That felt amazing.
This part looks the best.
A once‑in‑a‑lifetime shot.
Why don’t we see Bing Ge’s face?
Bing Ge is just enjoying it.
Bing Ge went up for a free
what do you call it—
a lift…
Pilates.
Not Pilates.
What’s it called then?
Feels like his skin
is getting yanked loose.
Look how calm I am.
Sir Huang.
Why does it look like
you struggled going down?
Was I struggling?
You’re unbelievable.
What is this from you?
You got down and pretended.
Turns out you’re the biggest poser.
Was it really like that?
I remember during training
they told me to keep my head up.
Head up?
Was I that pathetic coming down?
In my mind I was like this—
Let’s go.
But actually…
I’ve never seen you anywhere
this shy and bashful.
You three were awesome.
Next season, it’s Jingyu’s turn.
He should learn that…
a pilot’s license.
I’ll fly the plane and take you up.
Will we even make it back, bro?
We'll be experiencing
European manor life here.
You can all give your gifts now.
Mine is for Teng Ge.
I think this
height
really suits Teng Ge's long legs.
Mine might be a bit shorter though.
Yeah, because your upper body’s long.
Darn it.
And your arms are short.
I got one for you too.
Wrapped it together.
It's not just air, right?
They upgraded this game.
All because last time you said
you’d cracked the code.
I even forgot that.
You take what he says too seriously.
Why is everyone so quiet?
Not saying a single word.
All here pretending to be smart.
Just brains whirring everywhere.
Three, two, one, everyone close eyes.
Bro, let's team up, bro.
You won't “kill” me, right?
I opened my eyes.
I'm heading this way now.
Xiao Hu.
Xiao Hu is “dead.”
Call the cops.
My first instinct is to vote Chengcheng.
I don't think Chengcheng
is that sophisticated.
After all, he's
a kid born in 2000.
Let's join up and take him out.
If this works,
we’re the smart ones.
If it doesn’t,
then I’m just dumb.
You two with these—
what is this, nunchucks?
Come, a duel for dignity.
Please vote.
Next, the challenge levels up.
With Jingyu, I feel our team can win.
I don’t really get this word now.
Come on, little bro.
Night of Ulan Bator.
Does this still involve the old lady?
Ulan—
Was that part of the act just now?
You can't even hear the wind.
Can't hear it.
From behind I saw his cheeks were—
Okay, that’s enough.
Sir Huang got them all wrong.
Sir Huang can’t even change them now.
Give us a super hard one.
This one?
Don't tell me it's this.
Yeah.
For this, your facial muscles
must be controlled so well,
to pull off that twisted smile.
You can’t do it on purpose.
And still sing?
That twisted, crossed-up smile.
Who’ll show it for me?
I’ll bow three times to you.
Wish you brilliance.
That’s terrifying.
I wish you wealth.
I wish you brilliance.
Why is no one playing “Spy”?
Where did the Spy go?