Nature
is carved into the genes of human civilization
as a primal pulse
At this stop, the group flies across the ocean
deep into the breath of Italy
to seek the spirit of water
It's so beautiful
Look behind you, it's so pretty
the freedom of the wind
Brother Bing
Sir Huang
Three, two, one
Let's go
Good brothers
for life
We've been to the sky
and down to the sea
the gift of the earth
Husband
The literal meaning of Arezzo is
the city on the hill
This is their most famous
antique market
This is so pretty
Xiaobai would love this
This is for Xiaobai
Fan Chengcheng
What are you doing in that little hat?
How much is this?
Five
Five times eight is forty
Forty thousand for one, bro
Worth it
So worth it
and the imprint of light
It looks like a painting
That moon is so bright
Together we encounter those
happy and eternal moments
Let's start from Milan
and welcome a new friend here
Let's go
Let's go, Tengteng, Bingbing, Tingting
Italy
Hello
Hello, hello
Italy
Who's here for the first time?
It's actually my first time
My first time too
It's my second time
Three or four times
It's quite warm here
So comfortable
Isn't our color scheme a bit too generic?
The four of us are all in one color
Yeah
The four of us are all in the same color palette
We're F4
The fashion capital
*To watch the meteor shower with you*
Let's go
Huang Jingyu
I love you, Huang Jingyu
I love you too
Grown men
Have they arrived already?
Who knows?
So that's Xiao Bai, Brother Teng
Brother Bai isn't here
Xiao Bai didn't come this time
Didn't come
Chengcheng, Brother Teng
Speaking of William
Brother William Chan is here
How is it?
The feeling of being a daddy
After I became a daddy
it's my first time out working
Really
First time leaving home
A little
a little reluctant
Yeah
But I only came because of you, right
We are going to
a restaurant next to the Milan Cathedral
Eat first
Brunch
Do you know what brunch is?
"Not allowed, not allowed to eat"
Brunch
Explain it, explain it to them
Even though it's a restaurant, "not allowed to eat"
What is brunch?
Brunch is breakfast
Right, because their food starts with the letter B
Breakfast-lunch
Right
What's the English for breakfast?
Doesn't matter
English for lunch
Lunch
So it became brunch
Nobody asked you, okay
Beautiful
This is worth visiting
Milan Cathedral
This is indeed quite magnificent
This is a must-visit spot
Amazing
This is very, very beautiful
Okay, that's about it
Show off. Done showing off
My Eng...
My English show-off is done
Translate for us
Find a manager and ask about this
How much is it?
To buy it, right?
How much to take it over?
*The Richest Man in Xihong City*
Are you queuing to go in
to shoot the sequel?
How much money?
Or what?
Brother, speak clearly
Ticket
How much for a ticket?
Come on
How do you say pigeon?
Brother
This...
Useless
Ask something slightly deeper
Ask something at a second-grade level and everyone freezes
*Oh friend, goodbye*
*Goodbye*
How many more?
What about the unimportant ones?
This is a famous landmark.
But I think I've been here before.
We're here.
We've arrived.
This is just too beautiful.
But I think I've been here before.
Me too.
I've taken photos here.
During Fashion Week, right?
Right.
So many pigeons.
Pigeons.
Come here.
If I keep my hand out like this...
Will any fly onto my hand?
Unlikely.
Why don't we try it?
I really think it's possible.
Will they?
No.
You need...
You need to have food.
Just watch.
I'll hold my hand out like this.
A pigeon will definitely come.
There are so many pigeons here.
But not that much pigeon poop.
They probably have designated spots.
I smell poop.
We're here.
We've arrived.
You four are wearing the same color.
Are we splitting into teams today?
Brother Bing.
So handsome.
Brother William.
Long time no see.
"Old Money Brother"
Hello, Da Xi.
Hello.
You guys are wearing the same color scheme.
Really, but we didn't plan it.
We came down all in the same color.
Assembly complete.
Facing the Milan Cathedral.
Hello.
Let's eat then.
Let's go.
There's already food.
Congratulations, brother.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Yes, congratulations, brother.
Thank you.
You've moved up a generation.
Congratulations, brother.
Answer the phone, Yanyan.
Yanyan, answer the phone, Yanyan.
This meat filling...
Dumpling filling.
Come on.
Chicken steak.
Wang Anyu.
Thank you.
It's really tasty, brother.
Do you want some?
What?
Steak.
Delicious.
Hurry up and eat, Bing.
Stop bustling about.
That...
Just eat a piece.
I'll pass it around.
Here, pick a big one.
Delicious.
It smells so good.
Not bad.
Here, you three kids share this.
What is this?
Beef.
Super delicious.
Why are you wearing kids' clothes?
Tucked into the pants.
Isn't "tight top, loose bottom" the trend?
You'd better put it on.
No need for "tight top, tight bottom".
No need to expose so much either.
"Damn" old man.
Do you want Chinese tissues?
They're hard to come by.
As soon as I got here
I felt the rhythm of this show
It really has a vibe
Just eating
No need to do any missions
Just small tasks
Like, there's another mission
But it doesn't go all the way
No, mainly because I can't remember
I forget by the end of the game
Our show is all about "when in Rome"
Since we're in Italy
We need to be even slower than the locals
I'm full
William
When you arrived today
Didn't you hold a...
..."press conference" at the airport?
You had some very "respectful" comments about everyone
Come on, let's play the clip
You guys really know how to play on this show
Do you know why they invited me to Italy?
Why?
Am I afraid of them?
Do I need to be afraid?
I...
...afraid of them?
Bro, he's even more two-faced than me
This is the scary part about misunderstandings in showbiz
They just cut the beginning and the end
Right?
You guys judge for yourselves, okay?
The later parts were even nastier, right?
I watched the whole clip
The beginning and end were even more exaggerated
This year marks the 55th anniversary of China-Italy diplomatic relations
And welcome everyone to Milan, Italy
Since we have a Greater Bay Area...
...contestant who actually knows a bit of Cantonese
He instantly raised our Cantonese level
I knew when the production team sought me out
I guessed it was for the Cantonese
Charge forward
Let's charge forward together
No difference
Also, before I came, my agent...
...specifically told me
"Smell Anyu for me, see what he smells like"
She loves him to death
Which one is your agent friend?
The one with the two blocked nostrils
Our first mission...
...is called the Two-Person Cantonese Whisper Challenge
Members will pair up
The first pair
Will receive a classic movie or TV clip
You need to memorize the lines
And using Cantonese...
...reenact it
Pass it on to the next pair
The final pair
If more than half the words are correct
It counts as a success
If the challenge is successful
Everyone can unlock...
...the world-famous...
...tour experience of the Milan Cathedral
Okay
The first leg starts with the pro, William
You can choose anyone as your partner
I think...
What? I think...
Hasn't Anyu always said...
...his Cantonese in the show is very good?
That his Cantonese is professional?
It's time to challenge...
...real Cantonese
Okay
Am I afraid of them?
So looking forward to it
Really looking forward to it
William, winning or losing doesn't matter to us.
Right, it's really just for fun.
I'm not afraid of you guys.
Come on.
So I'm playing...
Is it this one?
Am I playing Lusi?
Or you play Lusi and I play you.
Okay.
Color, quality.
Taste.
Are all bad.
This suit.
A semi-permanent three-piece suit.
What's wrong?
Are you bedding?
And the glasses.
Are you nearsighted?
Why do you wear them every day?
What are you pretending?
Pretending to be "Old Money"?
The food you make.
Food.
Did I say your lines right?
Yes.
Let me teach you.
Let me tell you.
Listen first.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me.
Not bad.
Wrong!
Every piece of clothing you picked for me.
Every.
Every piece.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me.
Okay.
None of them satisfy me.
None satisfy.
"Mei" means "none".
None of them satisfy me.
Let me tell you.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me.
None of them satisfy me.
Okay, got it.
Sure?
Yes.
Color.
Taste.
Quality.
Are all bad.
Right.
Taste.
Not "lecherous".
"Lecherous" means...
The meaning of "lecherous".
No.
Color.
Taste.
Quality.
Are all bad.
You forced it down.
Food.
In Cantonese, it's...
Force it down.
Hard.
Just hard.
Force it down.
Force it down. I force it down.
Okay, I remember. Come on.
We're ready to start.
You haven't passed a single line yet.
Brother, practice again from the start.
Okay.
Don't.
Let me tell you.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me...
I'm not satisfied with a single one.
Practice again from the start.
I really learned a bit of Cantonese.
Brother William.
Because I have friends who speak Cantonese.
Alright.
Let me tell you.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me...
Picked every piece of clothing...
Not bad.
One Thousand Sad Reasons.
First time at the Milan Cathedral...
holding a solo concert.
Hope everyone likes it.
So long.
Acting for so long.
I don't know. What?
Do you not need us for this part?
Is this scene that long?
You do it.
How do you say "force it down"?
That's simple.
Force it down.
Force it down. Right.
After you left...
Brother Bing, find another one.
Okay.
Come on, another one.
Go act on stage. Stop practicing. Come on.
Done.
The two of us.
Let me tell you.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me...
I'm not satisfied with a single one.
Every piece is so bad.
What are you doing now?
You're acting so old.
What are you doing?
This suit you're wearing...
Bedding.
Semi-permanent three-piece set.
Why are you wearing glasses? Are you nearsighted?
Why are you faking "Old Money"?
My Cantonese was totally thrown off by him.
Faking "Old Money," you...
Sorry, I sounded off.
I completely...
What I just said wasn't Cantonese.
Pure Cantonese.
Really went off-track.
Give me one chance, okay?
Okay.
One more time.
Otherwise...
people back home will laugh at me.
Too scary.
Come on.
What are you doing?
Why are you wearing glasses?
Are you nearsighted?
Faking "Old Money," you...
Honestly,
it sounds about the same to us.
You have the nerve to talk about me?
I understood that part.
"You have the nerve to talk about me."
Do you understand?
You understand.
Every single dish you make is...
tastes terrible.
I have to force myself to eat it.
Force... force it down.
Force it down.
I always...
just like that.
Anyway, my part was standard.
I passed.
Every dish you cook tastes awful.
And you have the nerve to criticize me.
He's saying something about you buying...
buying something.
Buying everything, I think that's what he means.
Darn it, you say... you're still lecturing me.
The food you cook isn't good, right?
Actually, you guys guessed his part correctly.
I got it all wrong.
Because you weren't standard.
William is "going crazy".
Yes.
Do you want me to translate it into Mandarin?
Translate it.
Speak some authentic Cantonese. Come on.
There isn't a single one I'm satisfied with.
The quality.
Are you ready?
Ready. Go ahead.
Let me absorb it.
Start.
Let me tell you.
Every piece of clothing you picked for me...
I am very dissatisfied with.
The color.
The quality.
The taste.
I don't like any of it.
I'm very dissatisfied with it all.
Your turn.
Better than you!
What stinks?
What?
Look at what you're wearing.
And also...
why are you wearing glasses?
What "Old Money" style are you pretending to have?
That's terrible. Come on.
Too...
Now you know what I was saying, right?
Is it clear now?
"Pretending to be Old Money." I understood that.
A Hong Kong, China local speaking the dialect...
isn't all that special.
William has already...
started to get the hang of it, I think.
I have too much room for improvement.
Daxi.
Time to work.
Come on.
Sitting there like a kid no one picked up after school.
Let me tell you.
Every time you buy...
clothes...
I'm very dissatisfied.
It's all...
Wipe it off for me.
It's not about the clothes.
It's about you.
Wearing glasses all day long.
Pretending to be "Old Money".
The food you cook tastes terrible.
You people from the Jia family...
are really hard to please.
The lines are so long.
It's a completely different story.
That was good.
Anyway, they said everything we said.
They said everything we didn't say too.
Even what we didn't say, they said.
They forced a whole scene in there.
Come on.
What kind of state is this?
Why so coquettish?
And...
was that part included?
Wipe it off. Wipe it off.
Wait, is this all content?
Yes.
So high maintenance.
Try Shandong.
This is Cantonese.
What you bought me...
This and that...
...have absolutely no taste.
Not as bad as your cooking.
My cooking is bad?
You Jins are so hard to please.
Wearing glasses all day long.
Poser.
I remember this scene.
I think I remember it too.
Wearing glasses, acting all "Old Money."
So brilliant.
What was the start? The lines before.
Yanyan.
You can call me that.
Let's go.
Makeup.
Shampoo.
Body wash.
Hair dryer.
Toothpaste.
Toothbrush.
All three yuan.
You took them all away.
The makeup and bags you bought me...
...really have no taste.
I don't like a single one.
Then throw them all away.
Wipe it off for me
Help me wipe it off
You wipe it off for me first
Mine is worse right now
You spat on me first
You have no manners
Wearing the same suit every day
Wearing sunglasses
Pretending to be "Old Money"
Even if I pretend, it's not as bad as your cooking
My cooking is bad? You're full of it
Then let's break up
The two of them started fighting
It's too scary
That scene became...
Scared
Really scared
I'm not scared of you guys
Brother William's biggest confusion is
Why we can understand each other
In this language
Right, the scariest part is
The first time I'm on a show
Speaking Cantonese
Feeling that I'm not standard
Unable to communicate
While everyone else speaks standard Cantonese
They communicate smoothly
After recording this episode
You'll forget your mother tongue
The final line recitation accuracy
Did not exceed half
Mission failed
How did they dodge that?
Round two, our Taiwan, China accent
We're not speaking Cantonese
Can't switch to the Taiwan, China accent that fast
Really
It's hard to switch
Speaking the Taiwan, China accent makes me want to speak Cantonese
Brother Teng is okay with the Taiwan, China accent
Huang Sir, you're up
From my side to your side, five steps in total
How do you know?
One, two, three, four, five
Almost got hugged by you
Some people just like that
You seem to have very few friends, huh?
Nobody likes me
How is that possible?
Then do you like me?
I like you
Who plays which role?
Which one do you want to play?
Me
Are you playing the female role?
I'll play the female role
Okay
Pick two people who can replicate our performance
The two of us
Can only perform it once
Then I'll stare over there first
Okay
From my side to your side
Five steps in total
How do you know?
Don't believe me? I'll walk it for you
Five, four, three, two, one
One
Almost got hugged by you
You seem
To not have many friends
Nobody likes me
How is that possible?
Then do you like me?
I like you
That last part wasn't there
William
Cantonese didn't work
Put some effort into the Taiwan, China accent part
Okay
Mainly remember the feeling
Remember the feeling
We didn't get a single word wrong
Really
It's only five steps from here to there.
You know everything, don't you?
I want to kick him off the roof.
From me to you, it's a total of five steps.
Don't you believe it's just five steps?
I believe it.
If you believe it, there's nothing left to do.
I don't believe it.
Since you don't believe it...
I'll show you by walking.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Almost let you hug me.
*Secret*
I remember this movie.
Okay.
You just remember Daxi's part.
Almost let you hug me.
We don't have many friends lately.
Maybe nobody likes me.
But maybe someone likes you.
Then do you like me?
I like you.
The five, four, three, two, one part.
If the locals in Italy see this...
This is a big chunk of grease from Hong Kong, China.
Five, four.
These five steps are the essence of this scene.
One.
Two.
Three.
It's so painful to watch.
Four.
Why is there an action scene?
I got it.
This is that Gao Qisheng.
Gao Qisheng.
Let's start over. Let's restart.
Three, four, five.
Almost got hugged by you.
You, around here...
Don't have any friends, right?
Yeah.
Maybe nobody likes me.
Do you believe someone likes you?
It wouldn't be you, would it?
Then do you like me?
Guess.
I like you.
Okay.
One, two.
Three, four, five.
Almost let you hug me there.
Dodged it.
Do you not have any friends here?
Yes.
Seems like nobody likes me that much.
Someone will like you.
Then do you like me?
I like you.
You really have no restraint.
Dialogue accuracy is over 50%.
Mission success.
It's over half.
The episode with the highest success rate.
We are now heading to...
Milan Cathedral.
Let's go.
Let's take a group photo here.
Hello everyone.
Hello.
Welcome to the Milan Cathedral.
The "Heart of Milan."
I'm the one showing you around today.
The official guide of Milan.
The Milan Cathedral is called...
Have you heard of it?
It means "home."
The name of the Milan Cathedral...
Up here.
There are two lines of text up there.
It is...
Cathedral of the Nativity of Saint Mary.
Check out my Italian.
So standard.
This cathedral...
Is the third largest Catholic church in the world.
And the largest Catholic church in Italy.
Its total surface area...
Is 11,700 square meters.
The height of the entire church...
Is 45 meters.
But it also has a spire.
There's a little Madonna on top.
The height of this little Madonna...
Is 108.5 meters.
Maria.
Its entire construction material is...
Piled up with marble.
It peels off.
So every single stone...
Every 100 years...
To 150 years...
Must be replaced.
So, this is...
A cathedral that is never finished.
This spire...
Is typical Gothic architecture.
There's a little figure on every spire.
Yes.
Placed on top.
On top of the spires...
Are people who contributed to Milan.
I thought it was a chess set.
We can see...
There are many small sculptures inside.
Right?
These sculptures...
Are actually not just...
From the Bible stories we talk about.
There are also some very important...
At that time...
People who paid for this church.
Can you get up there if you pay a lot?
Of course.
If you pay less...
They might write your name on it.
But there will be some recognition.
How much?
I want to get my buddy up there too.
34,000 Ducat gold coins.
Will get you a big spire.
How many grams is one gold coin?
Manhattan Island in New York...
Was bought with gold coins.
Bought with 14 Florin gold coins.
But he's different.
We are real people.
38,000 coins.
Hang a real person up there.
Hang me up there.
Let him go up and pry off the gold coins.
They can hang you up there yourself.
We're going to the roof now.
Is this the tile from the saying "hit the roof"?
Yes.
But these tiles are marble.
Okay.
Solid blocks of marble.
So it will...
Are we not allowed up?
We can.
We can go up.
Falling is prohibited.
Right, falling is prohibited.
Tripods are prohibited.
Stepping is allowed.
Going up is allowed.
Up here,
we can see
all the typical elements of Gothic architecture.
One is the flying buttress.
It's suspended in the air.
Do you see it?
Also,
do you see?
That window arch
must be pointed.
Pointed.
It can't be round.
So, pointed.
And,
a very important feature is
there are many waterspouts up there.
Waterspouts.
They are made in the shape of monsters.
It's like warding off evil spirits.
This is the one we couldn't afford to put up there back then.
Darn it, it ended up here.
I just want to say,
us brothers got this for you.
Put it right here for you.
Just look,
Xiao Hu is there with his mouth open,
acting as a waterspout.
This is the front, right?
Yes.
What can you see here?
It's black.
Can you see?
Did you put a coin in?
You have to pay.
The photos here are amazing.
Brother.
You can look up a little.
Get Maria in the shot.
Who is Maria?
Over here.
That one.
The light is good here, right?
Chengcheng is blocking Brother Teng.
Just snapping away.
Just one angle.
Inside this cathedral,
doesn't it look like a...
what we call a "forest of stone"?
It does.
Like many small pillars pieced together.
So it's called a clustered column.
Clustered column.
Clustered columns are typical of Gothic architecture.
Inside here,
there are fifty-two of them.
It also corresponds to the fifty-two weeks
in a year.
Everyone, come over here.
Look.
A copper line.
This copper line runs from the south
all the way up the wall over there.
What is this line?
During the summer solstice,
on June 22nd,
the sun...
Up there, where we can't see,
there is a very small hole.
It's called the Gnomon hole.
The sunlight through this hole
will hit right here on June 22nd.
It hits exactly on this spot.
It moves forward a little bit every day.
But at what time each day
does the light return?
At twelve noon.
It's called the meridian line.
On both sides, there are the twelve signs of the zodiac.
Which are the constellations.
Look what this is.
A crab.
Crab.
What is the crab in the zodiac?
Cancer.
Crab.
Leo.
Virgo.
Is this me?
Is this Libra?
Libra.
Yes.
You.
Aquarius.
Step on it then.
This is Libra.
Libra, Aquarius.
Libra.
This is Libra.
How can Libra be together
with Aries?
Exactly.
This is Pisces.
This is Scorpio.
Then isn't that mine?
It is Libra.
You stepped on mine.
Wipe it off for me.
Take a picture of me.
Come on.
Take a picture of me with it.
I'll take one with that one.
Get this Libra sign and me,
and the depth of the hall in the shot.
Don't you have to lie down there?
I'll get lower too.
Don't get lower.
Wait a second.
Don't move.
I used to think that saying was really cliché.
But seeing the cathedral,
I really...
feel no other words can describe it.
This architecture speaks.
The carving is so exquisite.
Very unique.
Very beautiful.
The cathedral
really is like a "Gothic forest."
I'm so happy to appreciate
such a magnificent work of art.
It's already evening
Evening is the most
uniquely charming golden hour in Milan
It not only preserves
the traditional essence of Italian slow living
but also integrates
the modern rhythm of an international metropolis
It is the time after work
to reunite and relax with friends and family
soak up the city atmosphere
and the best moment to work up an appetite
Milan, I love you
That is Mei Lan
We should be there, right?
Let's go
This Italian architecture
is truly exquisite, like a work of art
It really has style
I have a direction for my home decor now
I'm just afraid it'll be very expensive
It's fine, search on Taobao now
"Go Now"
Get national subsidies for appliances and home decor
Subsidies up to 20%
It's a great deal
I suggest you hurry and give your home
a try at remodeling
a little Italian-style corner
There's also a chance to win an 888 red packet
Hurry and take a look
That settles it then
I just checked this shop
its name is Prince
Then only I can eat it
Bro, that plate is yours
That's from the Northeast
Those are pickled cabbage dumplings
There are dumplings too
Isn't this it?
Dumplings
Ravioli
Northeast chef
This meat is super tough
Just one spoonful right off the bat
Do you have to add sound effects while eating?
Bro
You take it away
You take it and eat it, okay?
It's choking me
I feel like my throat needs to be
this wide
This piece of meat is going to choke me to death
Forced it down
The contents all spilled out
Does this shop have
that very rustic kind of bread?
Dry bread
That stuff is tasty
Wolf down two pieces of this dry bread
I love eating it
Eat some more of this beef
and going to the toilet tomorrow
will be exhausting
My physical exam this year
my body is just like a child's
What's wrong?
Hasn't it developed yet?
William Chan is going to be a regular
No
What I meant was
my indicators are all very good
Bro, from your Northeast dialect
to William's brain
it has to go through Mandarin first
now it's going through Cantonese
After going through Cantonese
it's already a different meaning
Today William
is going to overturn all his previous Cantonese
Dual system
Everyone done eating?
Let's play a game.
To digest.
In Italy,
there is a kind of improvised
and passionate traditional dance
called the Tarantella.
It often appears in
Italian movies, operas, and festivals.
This dance tests
not only individual dancing skills
but also the partners'
extreme chemistry and instant reaction.
Next, we will also have a challenge
that tests everyone's dancing skills
and reaction speed.
Split into two teams for rock-paper-scissors.
The winning side
will start as the attackers.
After the music starts,
all members need to
imitate and replicate the attackers' dance moves.
During the dance,
the attacking members can at any time
shout "Grab!"
The member who grabs the sandbag
placed between the groups
can attack any member of the opposing team.
The hit member is eliminated.
When a team is fully eliminated,
the other team wins.
So, the four of us.
Us four, you four.
Alright.
Okay, split in half.
Is this floor hard?
Not hard.
There's a carpet.
Do we have to do high-difficulty moves?
Rolling around again, right?
Somersaults again?
Don't do somersaults.
Brother, let's play a round.
Let's play.
You go to the front, Sister.
You dance the best.
Rock, paper, scissors.
We attack.
Come on.
I can't even keep up.
Nice.
Beautiful.
Go up quickly.
Go up.
"Psycho."
A sports student is here.
Go.
Grab!
Bing Ge was so cool!
Not really.
That was really cool just now.
Very swift.
He hit him into a pose.
Hit Anyu into a shrimp in one go.
Come on, music.
Peacock.
Peacock spreading its tail.
Grab!
He got stuck there himself.
It's bad enough to dance ugly.
And he falls too.
Where is he?
That's a move too.
I pulled my arm.
Pulled it.
You help him.
Come here quickly.
Can we go out of this?
Outside the carpet?
You can't go outside the carpet.
Missed.
Didn't hit.
Point blank and didn't hit.
You didn't even cheat right, brother.
Brother, wait a moment.
Clown.
It's Qiqihar after all.
Left you with
a deep impression.
Hit him!
I added another player.
I revived him.
I caught this.
Go!
Revive.
Revived.
What?
What's wrong?
We've been like this since childhood.
Bro.
You're back in.
When will we finish?
It's like this.
Yeah.
Then I'm leaving too.
Go rest a bit, get off.
Let's go.
It's just the two of us left.
Two against four.
Come on!
Jin Chen's face is red from dancing.
There's more.
Grab it!
Such a good chance.
Sorry.
Hong Kong, China version "General".
Hong Kong, China version.
Wang Anyu's rival is here, I tell you.
How is he playing?
Grab it!
It's their turn to attack, right?
Right.
Okay.
Can't attack anymore.
He has too many little moves.
That works.
Yangge.
Tibetan dance.
Here he goes again.
Again.
Grab it!
Did it hit me?
It hit.
Served it up.
I thought I dodged it.
Block.
You took the bullet, bro.
Really.
I thought William...
...snatched the sandbag away.
"The General".
I think you're about to...
...be usurped.
Hong Kong, China version.
Come on, Chengcheng.
Come on.
Play a song, come on.
What's this?
Grab it!
Want to see the full version?
Go watch my short videos.
He hit my face.
So young.
Reactions are fast.
I didn't even react in time.
Hit my face.
Come on!
Grab it!
Beautiful!
He wove it into his moves.
Hard to react to that.
He hit my face.
He won't succeed in a 1v4, will he?
Come on!
Grab it!
Beautiful!
It's done.
Sent him off.
Not bad.
The key is...
Anyu left too early.
Just now when William was dancing
I really wanted to dance with him
William's part was so awesome
Let's go another round
I know how to play now
You seem to know a bit more
than the seven of us do
Just now you already
seemed to really know
how to play this game
Once William started dancing
I felt like I...
I felt like I couldn't do this at all
I couldn't handle it
Come on
Let's do it
Okay, I'll go first. Stand in front
Let's practice a bit
I'm ready
Who's attacking?
You. You attack
Okay, come on
Let them attack first
This one
Bing
Grab
Brilliant
I know how to play now
Bing actually did it
Nice
Brother Bing actually succeeded
Brother Bing, you actually
You actually know street dance
Don't, or he'll keep making me show off my talent
Forget it
Am I being too competitive
Don't you think
Everyone is standing so far away now
No
It's not that we're scared
I'm just not worthy of this stage anymore
This has nothing to do with fear anymore
That move of his
How did that move go again
How did he do it
It's actually quite simple
Come here
You come here, right
You jump
Jump once
I studied it for ages just now
I'm here
You insist on learning it
Yes
Alright, brother, you rest a bit
We'll go up now
Okay, come on
Don't go yet
I'm afraid you'll "die"
Right, you have to be saved for last
Saved for last
We'll go first for you
You go
You come
You take the next round
Can't follow that
The two of us
I can't follow that either
The two of us can't follow that
This, I really
I could feel it even from the back
The tremors were obvious in the back too
Even Beijing felt the tremors
Where are we going back to tomorrow
That Milan Cathedral
Maybe the tiles will fall off again
How about this
I
I invite
I invite myself and Brother William
We'll do it together
And the other side also sends out two people
Two against two, sure
Good, good idea
Sure
Doubles
Who
Us
Which of us
You guys go
You two
Go, quick
No way, I'm scared
Quick, you can do it
You can
I can't handle this
They're scared
Momentum is key
Scared
Come on, brother
I can only say
If you two lose this round
Darn it
Just be done for
Whatever
I'll dance with you
Okay
That's much simpler
Come on
You even need a run-up
Don't tell me...
we're redoing what William danced to?
You do one.
Isn't this that one?
What on earth is this?
Grab!
Smash it, quick!
Hit him in the face!
Hit you in the face!
I can't believe it went like that.
How did you "die" again, Anyu?
Fan.
Fan is really in the zone.
Those feet are agile, Jingyu Bro.
Right.
Too fast.
It's too fast.
Chengcheng.
Your turn.
Xinjiang style.
Where's the itch?
Grab!
Then you're the only one left.
One backup dancer and one lead dancer.
It's your turn.
Come on, Bro.
Give me something else.
You definitely won't grab the ball.
Grab!
William.
The final "General."
It's too hard.
Come on.
Huang Sir.
Backup dancer ready.
William Bro is gonna twist me to "death."
Come on.
Warm up.
Come on, Huang Jingyu.
Come on!
Come on.
One Finger Zen.
Pinky finger.
Grab!
Hit my face!
Face slap!
My thigh just cramped up.
No, he...
I can't do his moves.
You can.
You're ten years younger than him.
Bro.
Just watch how Bro destroys me, darn it.
What is this?
Not bad.
Grab!
Beautiful!
Da Xi, you attack.
You just attack.
I see you.
I'm a bit scared.
This song suits Bai Bro.
Cockfighting.
Grab!
Wonderful
That was beautiful
I can hardly imagine
standing opposite William
how I would feel
I'll give you this chance
No
Next time
One-on-one
Come on
Does he want to or what?
I don't know
He wants to
You want to
Next time
Come
If you want it, come out
If you want it, Brother will give it to you
Look how happy Anyu is
He didn't need asking twice
He wants it
High difficulty or...
High difficulty
Maximum difficulty
Give him the hardest one possible
I accept
I accept the challenge
Brother, you come
Come on
Anyu
Anyu is really enjoying this
He's learned this
Third move now. Watch me
Watch me
Scrambling
Anyu
He gave it his all
What a spirited performance of
"The General Dismounts"
But
I want to give the title of "General Chen"
to William
This show hasn't had fighting spirit for a long time
You know?
Everyone has been listless for too long
Today is the only
scene with fighting spirit
I once thought
without Anyu
this show couldn't go on
I didn't expect
it could still go on
Leave right now
So awesome
As long as you guys don't bully me
Apart from verbally
bullying you
it's hard in other aspects
Over the next few days
Each and every person
unreservedly
will teach William five sentences of Cantonese
so when he goes back he can become
half a Hong Kong, China local
We've turned William into
a "rookie"
Among the eight of you,
there are two blanks.
No words.
Just pretending to look.
Their acting is so hollow.
Huang Sir, this round,
looks a bit like Sir Blank.
What are you doing?
Actually, I already know who it is.
One of them must be Jin Chen.
Why?
What did I do?
Great acting.
It's so hard to guess.
William, you're truly the "General of the Pearl River Delta."
So sumptuous.
Delicious.
Smells great.
Let's play a round.
Jingyu's question.
Self-discipline gives me freedom.
First, the person who wrote this must be
someone who uses that fitness app.
So it's not Brother Teng.
He uses it too.
To check his blood pressure or something.
Check blood pressure.
There must be at least three people
saying it's foot binding.
This person wants to use Brother Teng to
stitch.
Fan Chengcheng.
Aren't I embarrassed?
Definitely you.
It's me.
That's too imaginative.
Why didn't you block my sword?
Only by not blocking your sword
will you believe me.
Do you understand what they're saying?
Of course I understand.
I won't pull it out.
I don't understand your Cantonese.
Although I don't get it,
it feels brilliant.
I think we should think about this ourselves.
What did he say? Won't pull it out?