Let’s play a game,
an upgraded emotional-singing game.
Singing with emotion words.
Let’s keep the game going.
What’s the score now?
Our team should be way ahead.
Yeah.
Our team’s really crushing it.
Half for this side.
Half for that side.
Right?
Yeah.
The score is now three to four.
Okay.
Then I’ll guess this round.
Is that okay?
Bro, you guessing?
Then I’ll do it.
How do you sing “Love You”?
You don’t even know this?
This is “Love You,” you know.
I thought it was that other one.
Love you a thousand times, never tired.
Oh bye, say a little less.
I want to be with you more than a day.
A bit more will let me
love you with all my heart.
Love you.
Start.
Chengcheng.
Chengcheng, keep an eye on me.
Ho baby.
Sweet talk me a bit more.
If you miss me, look a bit more.
Show it just a little more.
So I can really see it.
Oh baby, say a bit less.
I want to be with you more than a day.
A bit more, I’ll give my whole heart.
Love you.
Inexplicable anger.
Got it, okay.
Come on, Weiting Bro.
Ho baby.
Sweet talk me a bit more.
If you miss me, look a bit more.
Show it just a little more.
So I can really see it.
Oh bye, say a little less.
I want to be with you more than a day.
Please return, “Great General.”
You’re really mad, seriously.
Hurry and calm him down, quick.
This guy…
Ho baby.
Sweet talk me a bit more.
Why do you act everything the same?
A partner I can talk with.
Turns out I’m just a
Happy birthday to you.
You cried and said to me,
wild and unruly.
Show it just a little more.
So I can really see it.
Oh bye, say a little less.
I want to be with you more than a day.
So sweet.
A bit more, I’ll give my whole heart.
Love you.
No, bro, listen—
Shouldn’t our acting be richer?
This isn’t rich enough?
It’s just always
exactly the same.
Ho baby.
Sweet talk me a bit more.
If you miss me, look a bit more.
Show it just a little more.
So I can really…
I’ve already guessed it.
really see it.
Fan Chengcheng.
Oh bye, say a little less.
I want to be with you more than a day.
One more day, I’ll give my whole heart.
Love you.
Really, really great.
Ho baby
Say a bit more sweet talk.
If you miss me, steal one more glance.
Show your feelings a bit more.
So I can really see it.
Oh bye, say a bit less.
I want more than just one day with you.
Angry vocals are my strong suit.
Tengger
Willing with all my heart
to love you.
What a good young guy.
Came on the show and ended up like this.
And still can’t sing this song.
I’ll follow your key, Bro.
Brother Bing can’t sing it,
but he can dance.
Ho baby
Say a bit more sweet talk.
If you miss me, steal one more glance.
So I can really see it.
Make me willing with all my heart
to love you.
Okay.
Spot on.
Everyone was really spot on.
Wang Anyu.
Inexplicable anger is Huang Sir.
Murderous intent is Xiao Hu.
Sulking is Brother Bing.
Bristling with anger is William.
Frustrated disappointment is Daxi.
All correct.
I’m the same way.
So accurate.
Esteemed performing artists,
Ho baby
Say a bit more sweet talk.
You haven’t sung enough yet.
My craving to sing kicked in.
You want to guess?
Let me guess.
William, go on.
This one is brutal, really.
What is a slight smile?
Feels like an awkward smile.
No.
Like…
A gentle smile, like this.
Like this.
A slight smile.
Bator’s night
So quiet, so quiet.
You can’t even hear the wind.
Can’t hear it.
Clouds drifting to the sky’s edge,
please, slow your steps.
I’ll run to tell you
I won’t look back.
Night of Ulan Bator,
so quiet, so quiet.
Even the wind doesn’t know.
Doesn’t know.
Let me go first.
Weiting Bro,
watch my performance.
That’s enough.
Night of Ulan Bator,
so quiet,
so quiet.
Bro, your mouth’s leaking air.
Mine is really accurate.
He must have guessed it.
He must have guessed it too.
You guys go first.
Let me think about mine.
I’ll do it.
Ulan—
Was that part of the act just now?
Now I’m officially starting.
What I did just now doesn’t count.
Night of Ulan Bator,
so quiet, so quiet.
Big Bro,
even the wind doesn’t know.
Even the wind doesn’t know.
Can’t hear it.
Call it quits.
That was a flying umbrella, right?
Your turn, Bro.
Done memorizing? Let’s start.
Night of Ulan Bator,
so quiet, so quiet.
Quiet.
You can’t even hear the wind.
Can’t hear it.
From behind I saw his cheeks bulge up.
Daxi said,
just from the back view,
his cheeks were like this.
Teng Ge’s sides here
are incredible.
So incredible.
Come on, Daxi.
Let me do it.
Night of Ulan Bator
So quiet, so, so quiet,
Old-timer, I’m serious.
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t hear it.
But it’s whooshing now.
Right now this phrase,
I don’t really quite get it.
Who? I’ll go.
Night of Ulan Bator
So quiet, so, so quiet,
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t—
hear it.
Come on, little bro.
No.
Can’t act it, or don’t know the word?
It’s hard.
Night of Ulan Bator
So quiet,
so quiet,
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t hear it.
A ninety‑year‑old elder.
Why’s there a granny here now?
Come on.
With Brother Jingyu here,
I feel our team can win.
Everyone, let’s all sing together.
Okay, three, two, one—
Night of Ulan Bator
So quiet, so, so quiet,
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t hear it.
Sorry,
I have a question.
I think Teng Ge and Brother Bing’s
performances later on were the same.
So can they both act one at once?
No, aren’t we doing it together?
Okay, fine.
Night of Ulan Bator
So quiet, so, so quiet,
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t hear it.
Get the hell out, you two.
I can’t hold my laughter.
They’re too adorable.
I wasn’t confident to begin with.
Here, pick it up.
You can’t even—
you can’t even hear the wind,
can’t hear it.
Devilish grin
Okay.
Who wants to give their answer first?
For A city-toppling smile,
I put Teng Ge.
Proud and exhilarated
is Xiao Hu.
Family happiness
is Chengcheng.
Slight smile
is Brother Bing.
Beaming with happiness
is Daxi.
Laughing at the World
is An Yu.
All correct.
Huang Sir got them all wrong.
Huang Sir had no time to change.
I had A city-toppling smile as Teng Ge,
Proud and exhilarated as Xiao Hu,
Family happiness as Brother Bing,
Slight smile written as Chengcheng,
but for him this was fill‑in‑the‑blank.
It was the last one left.
So I just wrote his name.
It had nothing to do with his acting.
Beaming with happiness: Jin Chen.
Laughing at the World: An Yu.
Two of them were wrong.
Okay, last question.
Let’s do a super hard one for fun.
This one?
Don’t tell me it’s this one.
Yeah.
Forced smile,
Flesh smiles but skin doesn't,
Skin smiles and flesh also smiles,
and No smile at all.
Sneaky laugh,
Crisscross Smile.
You…
this Crisscross Smile thing,
this one…
you need a master performer for that.
You must control your facial muscles
to such an extreme degree
to pull off a Crisscross Smile.
Maybe the mouth tilts this way first,
then tilts that way.
So doesn’t that mean our side already won?
Yeah.
Who thinks they can guess this one?
Step up and try.
You go guess.
I’ll go guess.
Come on.
Teng Ge.
Daxi.
Are you two guessing?
I’ll guess.
You’re guessing?
Sneaky laugh,
Crisscross Smile—
who’ll act one out for me?
I’ll bow three times to you.
This one—
I’m good at this one.
That’s what a master is.
Huang—
Watch him act.
Watch his performance.
Huang Jingyu, Crisscross Smile.
So brilliant.
No, without the song,
you can’t even do it just sitting here.
And you’re even singing,
still singing along.
You get rich.
I wish you prosperity—brilliant.
The best ones, please come here.
If not, please step aside.
You can never be too polite.
I wish you prosperity
I congratulate you
Okay, down
Lower it more
Down
Still push it down
That works
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
You can never be too polite
Pull the corners down
Playing this on such a big day
is kind of off, you know
Mine is easier to do
You get rich
Congrats, you’re amazing
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
You can never be too polite
Weird
Mine here
Mine should be like yours
Congrats, you’re amazing
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
So scary
You can never be too polite
No way anyone can guess me
I don’t buy it
Do it again
One more time, bro
I think you should smile bigger
It’s the flesh
Raise the two fleshy bits
Yeah
Wishing you prosperity
Wishing you brilliance
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
You can never be too polite
Okay
My apple muscles hurt
I want to watch, too
Wishing you prosperity
I wish you brilliance
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
Oh, you can’t be too polite
I don’t know what it is
But the acting’s great
This is so tough for him
Huang Sir’s one is hard to guess
This mainly depends on acting
Come on
It’s wrinkled already
Wishing you prosperity
Wishing you brilliance
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
You can never be too polite
Teng Ge, your turn
We still need other flavors
Wishing you prosperity
I wish you brilliance
The best ones, come here
The bad ones, go away
You can never be too polite
That's terrifying.
Why is no one doing "sneaky"?
What about "sneaky"?
Where did "sneaky" go?
This whole row is scary.
This should be really scary.
Turn your back.
Wishing you prosperity,
wishing you prosperity,
wishing you brilliance.
If you're great, come over.
If you're not, please leave.
Politeness never offends.
We definitely got them all.
I'm very confident.
Daxi is confident now.
Got confident.
Okay.
Forced smile.
Hey, Chengcheng—
that's wrong.
Flesh smiles but skin doesn't.
Seems you swapped these two.
He's flesh smiles but skin doesn't.
He's the forced smile.
I drew an arrow.
Then I flipped these two.
Skin and flesh both smile is Brother Bing.
Right.
No smile at all.
An Yu.
Sneaky laugh in skin and flesh.
Teng Ge.
Crisscross smile.
Huang Sir.
I got all of them right.
I can't believe we acted this out.
Human potential really is endless.
All forced out of us.
I just couldn't find the sneaky one.
In the end, I used elimination.
Not finding it is exactly "sneaky."
No.
You have to act out "sneaky."
You're really sneaky, that's so—
No, I really—
I'm laughing sneakily.
Pretty sneaky.
Huang Sir's crisscross smile was so clear.
Front and back.
Congrats to us.
Brother Bing's team wins.
We get first pick of the rooms.
Priority room selection.
Was this shot with a wide angle?
Do the four of us get that too?
Who gets first pick?
Should the four of us battle for it?
So not united.
It’s down to the four of us.
I don’t care, you guys pick first.
I don’t care either.
Same, I don’t care.
I don’t mind either.
Let’s do rock paper scissors, four of us.
Winner gets first pick.
I’ll take the highest floor.
The smallest room.
No, let him pick first.
Then our side lets him pick first too.
Okay, room 10 goes to Brother Bing.
Give the biggest one to Brother Bing.
No need.
I’m fine with whatever.
I can just be the doorman.
I’ll be doorman.
You pick first, bro.
You go first.
The three of us will battle.
The smallest one.
Yeah, that smallest one is fine.
Okay.
Small rooms gather qi, good sleep.
Rock paper scissors.
Okay.
He picks first.
Then I’ll take…
Room 9 then.
I’ll take this one.
Room 7.
Once they finish choosing and get to the hotel,
they’ll see us four tearing into each other.
In front of the cameras
and behind the cameras,
we’ll settle it with force there.
We’ll have a duel.
Solve it by force.
The one most badly hurt sleeps lowest.
Because he can’t climb up.
The total winner goes to the top.
Showdown at Ziqing Peak, right?
We’ll see soon.
We’ll see when the time comes.
Okay.