I bet none of you have tried the garlic here.
What? What is this?
Did we just time travel?
What? Are you going to "steal" my idea?
Now it's his.
We went through so much hardship.
And now the credit is stolen.
Let's play a game.
Who's talking?
The rules are simple.
Who wants to be the first two Identifiers?
What do the Identifiers do?
The Identifiers are...
Two people identify together.
Right.
Then they give one unified answer, right?
You give your own.
Yes.
Let's identify. Come on.
I'll go up and identify first.
Who else is identifying?
I will.
I'll go with you, Huang Sir.
This is what they sound like after the voice change.
Yes.
Why does my voice sound like this?
Here we go.
Alright, let's start the timer.
Please introduce yourselves one by one.
Starting with number one.
Introduce yourself.
My name is Only Drinks Herbal Tea.
Sun Qian.
That's it?
That's your self-introduction?
We're going by numbers, right?
Yes.
Number two.
No, number one, say a bit more.
It's just called self-introduction.
You only drink herbal tea?
I didn't ask that.
This voice sounds so much like me.
It sounds too much like her voice.
It's a girl.
Yes.
Sun Qian.
Right.
Next.
Two.
Should we make some noise or something?
I'm Chengcheng.
This is number two.
Say a bit more.
I just ate three heads of garlic.
What are you wearing today?
Pink.
What are your usual hobbies?
Fifteen twenty.
Yes, it's the real Chengcheng.
Next.
We can all hear.
Hello, teachers.
This is the...
Is this the third one?
Please introduce yourself.
I'm Shen Teng.
Number three, what's your name?
What's your name?
He said Shen Teng.
My name is Wang Anyu.
How old are you?
Forty-seven. Very familiar with Teng Ge.
Who among those present...
...should be eliminated first?
Who?
You.
Come on, first self...
Let them finish their self-introductions first.
Okay?
He said his name is Shen Teng.
Number four.
Hello, two teachers.
I'm from Chongqing.
What number is this?
Did they switch?
Number four.
Still number four, right?
My name is Wang Anyu.
Little Hu.
You can call me Stick Bro.
Call me Stick Bro.
Little Hu.
Number five.
Hello, two teachers.
Number five, what's your name?
Wang Anyu. You can call me Stick Bro.
You can call me Stick Bro.
Did they switch people?
They switched.
Number six.
Wait, number five, say a few more words.
Number five, say a bit more.
Two sentences.
What does number five like to eat most?
What I like to eat most is...
Garlic.
Eating garlic.
What thing?
Four cloves of garlic.
How many cloves of garlic can you eat at most?
How many cloves did you just eat?
I can keep eating.
Number six.
What?
They won't say much in their self-introductions.
We need to make them sing a song or something.
Let's start with number six.
Contestant number six, please sing a song.
Your favorite song to listen to.
No floral scent.
Who's dreaming?
Talking in their sleep.
Number five.
Number five, sing a song.
A little donkey pulling a millstone.
What number is this?
Number five.
It can't break out of that circle.
A frog in a well.
A donkey turning a millstone.
"Donkey turning a millstone" is Teng Ge's signature piece anyway.
But I think...
...it doesn't seem like him.
Number four.
Today I...
...watched the snow drift by on a cold night.
With a heart grown cold, I drifted far away.
Chasing through wind and rain...
Right?
Number four sounds a bit like Teng Ge.
See, he coughed right after singing.
Guessed right! Number four is Teng Ge.
Number three.
Their game is too low-level.
Sorry, we don't play.
I turned the volume up to max.
Don't know what she...
...said.
We don't play.
This is Chengcheng's song.
Alright, number two.
Yes, teacher.
Dear Anyu...
...fly slowly.
Beware of the...
...thorny roses ahead.
Dear you...
...you slowly...
Who does that sound like?
...fly.
Three days and nights, three days...
...in the dead of night.
Dancing without stopping.
Three days and nights...
...in the dead of night.
This hotel is completely checked out.
Looking forward to it.
Stop singing, stop!
Let's switch people.
Yes, teacher.
What number are we on now?
Number one.
I gently...
...take a sip.
As you said.
Alright, that's definitely Sun Qian.
Love me.
Now, each of you say a sentence in Cantonese.
Let me hear it.
Say "Wishing you prosperity, now give me the red envelope!" in Cantonese.
Starting with number six.
Wishing you...
...prosperity.
Red envelope...
...now give it to me.
Wishing you prosperity.
Now give me the red envelope!
Everyone sounds a bit weak, everyone...
...seems to have weak energy.
Next.
Wishing you prosperity.
This one...
...Fan Chengcheng.
Fan Chengcheng.
This is definitely Fan Chengcheng.
Wishing you prosperity.
Now give me the red envelope!
Sun Qian.
Alright then.
Let's just go with that.
Okay, that's settled then.
Enough! I've had enough!
I can't hold on anymore.
Decided.
It's decided, that's it.
Let's go.
Number one...
...Sun Qian.
Sun Qian.
I also say Sun Qian.
Number two...
...Number two, Chengcheng.
Chengcheng.
Number three, Little Hu.
I also say Little Hu.
Number four, Teng Ge.
Number five, Sister Yan.
Number six, Brother Bai.
Four correct.
Next, the difficulty increases.
The distance is greater.
Let's do another round.
Who's coming with me?
I'll go with you.
Let's go.
Go.
What are you getting hyped about?
"Pressure Cooker."
Two "Pressure Cooker Boys."
Once you sit down, no looking back.
We've switched positions.
Okay.
Move forward a bit.
I...
...I'll move forward a bit.
I'll lean back a bit.
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Let's begin.
Numbers one through six, please introduce yourselves in order.
I am a bee.
Going "bee"-zerk for you.
So cheesy.
Wang Anyu.
Number one, say a bit more.
What do you want to hear?
You're Wang Anyu, right?
Couldn't hold it in.
If you were an animal...
...what animal would you be?
What
The one that flies the highest
Eagle
If you were an animal, you'd be an eagle.
Next.
I'm a bee.
Going "crazy" for you.
Next.
No need to go "crazy" now.
I am the next one.
You're also going "crazy".
I am the second little bee.
The second little bee.
Is that Teng Ge?
Feels like Teng Ge.
Suddenly started singing.
Okay.
Give it
to number three first.
Hello, you two.
I am
number three.
I...
You tell me who I am.
This also sounds like Anyu.
Super idol.
Feels like
Huang Jingyu.
Brother Jingyu's Cantonese also has this tone, I think.
Bullfight.
Are you Huang Sir?
It's mine.
Alright, you give it to number four.
Hello, I am contestant number four.
May I ask who you are?
My name is Iron Egg.
Guarantee your safety.
Iron Egg.
Your name is Iron Egg?
Yes.
How iron is this egg?
Super iron, bro.
Rate your own Werewolf playing skills.
How did you analyze it just now?
Huang Jingyu.
Afraid to rate it?
At least top three.
Is that counting from the bottom?
Of course counting from the top.
You two are no good.
Huang Sir doesn't seem like he'd suddenly put us down.
You evaluate Shen Teng.
Handsome guy.
What is that?
Teng Ge is a handsome guy.
Feels like a smokescreen.
Right?
Evaluate Teng Ge's
partner, Sister Ma Li.
I dare not.
Then it's definitely not Teng Ge.
What's your outfit today?
A blue sweater.
Alright, give it to the next one.
Hello.
My name is Garlic.
Called what?
Garlic.
Called Garlic.
I love eating garlic.
I eat eight at a time.
Sister Jiang Yan.
Jiang Yan.
Does it sound like her?
It should be Jiang Yan.
Do you think you're good-looking?
Of course.
Who do you think is better-looking, you or Shen Teng?
Wang Anyu is good-looking.
Who's better-looking, you or Wang Anyu?
Shen Teng is good-looking.
This seems like Sun Qian.
You give it to the next one.
Hello, two teachers.
I am number six.
I am a little bee.
I am a bee.
All day.
Please evaluate Teng Ge.
Right.
That's it.
Of course there are many.
Besides being straightforward, what else?
Loyal to friends.
You're not close with him.
We are close.
We often record shows together.
What, you want to deny it?
Speak.
You evaluate
Teng Ge's
partner, Sister Ma Li.
I don't dare.
Now, sing a song within three seconds.
Three...
Two...
Arirang...
Teng Ge.
He can't think of a song.
To number five.
List five of your own strengths.
Handsome.
Genuine.
Loyal to friends.
Generous.
Humorous.
Now list five weaknesses.
That's hard to say.
How about this.
What?
You tell me.
No, I'll tell you.
How to tell Sister Yan and Sun Qian apart?
If you ask her to tell a joke now,
the one who laughs is Sister Yan.
The one who doesn't is Sun Qian.
Is it possible
she can hear your mic?
She heard your secret plan.
Just ask her.
She has to tell one anyway.
Then you ask.
Tell me
the funniest joke you know.
You two are a joke.
Sun Qian.
It's Sun Qian.
Correct, Sun Qian.
Iron Egg is here.
Iron Egg, such a tough-guy name.
Wang Anyu.
That's right.
Very clear self-awareness.
Wang Anyu.
Thank you.
Is it Wang Anyu?
Wang Anyu.
It's definitely Iron Egg.
Sing a song.
Iron Egg.
I love you,
my home,
my paradise.
Yala Suo!
This is definitely Wang Anyu.
So that means...
The Qinghai-Tibet Plateau.
List five of your own shortcomings.
No shortcomings.
Wang Anyu.
Okay, to number three.
I am number three.
Where do you usually live?
Where do you live?
Not far from the South Pole.
What?
I live on a mountain.
Then list five of Teng Ge's shortcomings.
Handsome.
Genuine.
Loyal.
Sometimes...
I don't know.
Do you think you're stupid?
Hard to say.
Who's smarter, you or Wang Anyu?
Both are smarter than you.
Rate your Werewolf skills.
Above you two lads.
One thing you most want to say to us.
You guys are hilarious.
There are only fifteen questions total.
Do you two have no brains?
Can't you think of your own questions?
Huang Jingyu.
He's already maxed out.
Okay, to number two.
Hello, I am number two.
You...
I am a Little Bee.
This is...
Sister Yan.
Feels like it.
Sing a song.
Tell us a joke.
Tell us one,
the funniest joke you know.
I can't.
Because I am a little bee...
Sister Yan.
She's already breaking character.
Then, with that...
To number one.
Where in Beijing do you usually live?
I don't live in Beijing.
I am...
a local from Xizang.
A local from Xizang.
Right.
Say "Happy every day" in Cantonese.
Happy...
joyful...
every...
day.
What else?
Evaluate Shen Teng Ge.
Not straightforward.
Not loyal.
Then he's just truly handsome.
Bai, meaning Brother Bai.
Should be.
Can't figure it out.
Alright, then we...
We're done like this.
That's it.
Number one is...
Brother Bai.
Number two is Sister Yan.
Sister Yan.
Number three is Huang Sir.
Huang Sir.
Number four is Anyu.
Anyu.
Number five is Sun Qian.
Number six is Teng Ge.
Those two are easily confused.
Two are wrong.
Which ones got mixed up?
Just number one and two.
One and two got swapped.
Alright, I think the guesses were pretty accurate.
Very impressive.