Situational acting
Let me briefly explain the rules
There are two prompts on the field, A and B
Those three people are the Undercover
Right
Everyone gets one line of dialogue
Then you perform it
We will do a practice round first
Hand out the roles for the first round
Let us first pick a Leaf Master
Let us choose Chengcheng
Leaf Master
You decide the order we perform in
Brother Bing
You are serving the dishes now, bro
Come on
One side is hanging down
You are lucky
You will get a full pair of gloves
Is this leaf okay, bro
This leaf of yours
You are really such a “leaf,” you know
Come on, Daxi
What kind of vibe do you want for the leaves
I want
I want something gentler
With some twigs on it
A softer one
It should spread out like a carpet
Are you trying to guard against me
What do you think
What else
Okay
Chengcheng is tossing them more and more realistically
Like someone in the family has “passed away”
Take care
All done
No useful info
Next one
What kind of feeling are you going for
I need to adjust the staging a bit
Can I get a blower here
I will just stand here and keep throwing
The leaf effect only works in this area
This special effect
The effect stops once you leave this spot
Only in this patch
Then how about this
I will start, I will move over from here
Okay
Remember, when I swing the first strike
Throw the leaves
Let us do it
Draw the sword
See you in the next life
No, do not take his acting too seriously
It might not match the actual prompt
Tengteng
Chengcheng, how about this
Tell me, bro
I only handle tossing the leaves
I know
Do it like this
You just throw them
Bro, the stage area is here
That is the props team’s spot
But these, all of this is my stuff
All these are my props
Then I will make some room for you
Do you need this basket
Yes
It has started
Dad is right here
Protect Mom well
But now I know I am with the majority
What are you doing
That last throw was the priciest effect
My supply is almost gone
You act
Just toss a little for me
Wait till I walk over, then throw
Which position do you want it in
I will walk over next to you in a bit
Is this not the sequel to Wang Anyu’s scene
It is
A pure sequel
Did you not say you would throw after I walk over
Throw it upward
Do it again
You threw all my emotion away, man
With this farewell
Who knows when we will meet again
Take care
Mine is simple
Throw three leaves for me every eight seconds
Let us start
One two three four
Five six seven eight
You have an accountant behind you or what
One two three four five six seven eight
It is a pity
That we met in this era
Farewell
“It is a pity we met in this era,” right
No need for that many
Less
I still could not see it
Come
Scan it
Scan me
Take care
Finished performing
These two are not even friends here
I think
I kind of feel like I am in a faction of one
Bro
To be honest, I am a bit confused now
I will help you toss them
I will toss the leaves for you, come
That is not enough
Use the ones on the ground then
Our scene is
Inside the eye of a tornado
Do you have any wet, smelly leaves
Give me some of those
Okay, let us go
You all
Wait for me
My husband
We will meet again in our next life
Your vibe fits this atmosphere the best
I have been sneaking glances here for ages
What it basically means is
My husband
Let us meet again in our next life
Help him, he still has a few leaves on his head
You call that a few leaves?
That is a few kilos of leaves
Everyone, we will now announce
the scenarios for majority and minority
The majority scenario is
Martial World in Chaos
Twin Evils
a tearful farewell
The minority scenario is
Chaotic Times Descend
Star-crossed Lovers
a tearful farewell
But I know I am in the majority
I have even forgotten which lines were mine
What are you talking about
I just acted a chaotic era
Then that means you are
Then you must be in the minority
I am in the majority
The majority did not have chaotic times
But your acting was super chaotic
I was not acting Chaotic Times Descend
You played Martial World in Chaos
Right
Child, daddy is right here
Dad is right here
This is what you call Twin Evils, bro
You saw the Martial World in Chaos just now, right
My kid and I were forced apart
I could not get across at all
I hurried to find a way out
so I could come back and save my whole family
During the time after I leave
I do not know how long it will be
my eldest son must take care of the whole family
And how does that relate to Twin Evils
I actually played the Twin Evils too
I am both male and female in one
I played both of the Twin Evils myself
And the tearful farewell goes without saying
Then he is no longer a suspect
Next one
Right
Huang Sir, you are definitely in the minority
You are here
Bidding farewell with tears
You forgot the prompt, you are here
That is exactly what I just acted
I said to my female Evil
Sadly, we met in this era
It is such a shame
To have met in this era
We have to part ways
Because the Martial World in Chaos is too messy
I think this wording makes it very clear
What you played was just straight war turmoil
Jingyu is obviously
He is about this era
Complaining about that era
It should be Chaotic Times
Is the Martial World in Chaos not chaos too
Martial World in Chaos
The common folks are still doing fine
I am the Evil
You are
You, Evil
Evil
You are the Evil
I am the Evil
I do not know
Mine is definitely the majority
Twin Evils
Just by the way I stood there
You can tell I know martial arts
Then you guys can imagine the rest
My handkerchief
It flew out
Shot out with inner power
Then she caught it
I said, if fate allows
It will match into a pair of handkerchiefs
Star-crossed Lovers
Would he not cry
Can he even afford gloves
So I am definitely in the majority
I am also in the majority
I am that female Evil
That male Evil pointed at him
I held a sword
Take care
It is very obvious
I am definitely in the minority
Does anyone suspect me
All right, we suspect you now
Now we are starting to suspect you
One hundred percent we suspect you
Yours is all like
Yours is not even a tearful goodbye
You are tearful
Tearfully getting to know each other
Scan it
Mine is definitely the martial world
Mine is not Chaotic Times
I even dragged in those costume drama lines
It is like, after this farewell
Who knows when we will meet again
I hope you take care
This, mine is definitely the common one
You still cannot tell from mine
My husband
Twin Evils
Mine is
I played a female Evil
My tornado move blew him away
I said goodbye to my male Evil
I still do not get this
Why did An Yu with one slash
Turn himself
And stab that female Evil to death
It has been three seasons
When did he ever
Being separated by life and death is also a tearful goodbye
I was the first to do a costume drama
Mine is definitely correct
I think it is Brother Bing
Jingyu bro and Weiting Bro
Are the minority
I will take that first round
I choose myself
No, this
We need to pick a driver, bro
I know, I will drive that car
No, drive where
Back to Beijing
Bro
Drive back to Beijing
Teng Ge is the first round driver
Or let me drive it
Is that okay
Xiao Hu will drive
Okay
For the first round I choose
Teng Ge, An Yu, Sister Da Xi
I get in the car with Chengcheng
The five of us
Game over
Is there an undercover among us
Yes
There is one
Not saying how many, there is
There is an undercover
Who did you pick
I picked those three over there and us two
Did you choose Teng Ge
Teng Ge is chosen
What is wrong with taking me
We will check the second round scenario cards
I want to get on the car every round
So can I be the first to act
That should be fine
I hope the majority can see
How well I can do
Just a bit of info is enough
A bit of info
Then I will divide it into three parts to act
I like you
Well done
Just well done
Let me do it
You all do not believe me
I will perform second
I will let you see it clearly
Okay
Here we go
I like you
The English version, right?
I do not know if you are on my side
But I know you just copied me
There is not a bit of originality
Listen, Hu
You went first with that act
Now all the undercovers know it
It really was a bit too obvious
Not necessarily
You do not even know the undercover word
You basically did not act this at all
This has to be an undercover
No
Huang Sir
Look at Huang Sir first
Look, these two are already exposed
They do not get anything, these two
Undercover
These two undercovers are already out
We just need to find the last one
Why am I exposed
I just acted exactly the same as you
Right
You cannot act exactly the same as me
I like you
Yes
Undercover
Weiting Bro seems possessed by something
For this while
He is acting a bit crazy
Who is it, get out
Get out of Weiting
Weiting Bro is like a wolf has entered him
Right now
I am a bit confused, bro
I am kind of losing my judgment
If you get confused
Then your Weiting Bro has achieved his goal
It is that I see a big difference
Between your acting and ours
Mainly Huang Sir
Could not see it
Even though it is so obvious
Sister Da Xi, go
Look at her
Okay, she has time traveled
On the way back
She turns into her younger self
Go
Okay
She is not an undercover
Can I be your girlfriend
Okay
She is not an undercover
He is
Weiting Bro
What is wrong with you
Bro, do you understand what I am saying
I can
Only Teng Ge should understand
You only know your own lines, right
No
I know you are an undercover
Sister Da Xi is on our side
Let Brother Bing go first
Okay
Bing was a bit ambiguous in the first round
No
Did he not say the first one cannot be too obvious
Go
Just today
Even if I fail I will not regret it, retreat
Brother Bing’s lines are all so powerful
Let us try a romance route
An Yu
There is no more info we can act out
True
Now we can only show our acting skills
I like you
Well
They are all the same
Homogenized performances
Indeed
Hurry, go
I like you
That was wonderful
I really do not have any innovation left
I have no way to innovate anymore
I like you
How many people, bro?
Why does it feel like you are surrounded by people?
Both of you are fully in the frame
Announce it
The majority’s scenario is
You are a middle‑aged magician
You travel through time and space
to help your younger self confess to your ideal love
The minority’s scenario is
You are from magic school
a poor guy who just graduated
confessing to a classmate you have secretly loved for three years
It has to be Jingyu Bro
Where did my acting go wrong?
I could beat you to death, curse you to death
What is it
Time travel you to death
But Jingyu Bro’s is more suspicious, right?
Come on, Jingyu, put the knife down
I cannot put it down right now
Can I bring people onto the car?
Yes
You pick
I pick Daxi
Do I count myself as a seat?
Yes
Two
Brother Bing
Three
Four
We did not agree he could drive
We just said we would hear his picks first
Trust me this once, okay?
Give your guest time to get to know you
and see what kind of person I am
All right?
You all misunderstand me
I think it is a big misunderstanding
You can give this time or not anyway
I will give it
I will give it too
No, bro
If you pick three people who are fine
Then you must be the undercover, do not
No
Stop talking
If after you pick, there is an undercover among them
then it can only be you
Right
Yes
Give me one round to prove
what kind of person I am, okay?
Everyone who agrees Weiting Bro is the team leader
please raise your hand
Give him a chance
Okay
Xiao Hu, Brother Bing, Daxi
and me
This round
The four of us have no undercover
You are dumbfounded now, huh?
Nice
I am telling you, I am really dumbfounded
These four people are not undercover
These four
Stunned now, right?
So Chengcheng, me, Teng Ge, and An Yu
three of us are undercover
Not me
I am definitely with the majority
What are you, you are a good guy?
One, two, three
No
Chengcheng, Huang Sir, and Teng Ge
I am definitely a good guy
Stop acting, bro
The majority has one last chance
You must find
the last majority player
and bring him onto the car
for it to count as a success
And in this final round
the four of us are confirmed good people
We absolutely cannot perform first
We have to let their four perform first
Hand out the prompt cards
Everyone, close your eyes
Weiting
As the one who in the last round
picked four good people as team leader
you can designate someone you want to watch
I want to watch Teng Ge
I also want to watch Teng Ge
Weiting, this is what they call
killing the donkey when the millstone is done
and tearing down the bridge after crossing the river
I already take you as one hundred percent
an undercover
but I just want to see you play one round
I just think it is fun
But I did not expect
you would turn around and send me up first
It is not that I cannot go up
but after I go up
I am afraid those three among us
will learn from it
It is fine, just do not give too much information
Just give a little
I will give a little
What are you talking about?
You big bad guy, what are you saying?
Big bad guy
All right, go on, little rascal
Just act a bit
I just want to see your first reaction, okay?
Okay
I want to see two info points from you
First
Just act so we see two info points
No
Just do a short bit of acting
and show two info points
Your acting major
your performance factor is a bit
Show two info points, all right?
Okay
It is you
I will go
Wait
It is you
Good guy
You are really a good guy
Then these three wolves are exposed
What, what is the difference between you and him?
He does not seem like a good guy
No
Chengcheng should be a good guy
I do not think so
Right, I do not think so either
These people are all confused by the game
I am definitely a good guy, bro
Now among the four, there is only one good guy, right?
Yes
Let me show you what a good guy is
It is you
This really does not look like a good guy
You should not have gone up front
You should just sit right here
Are you trying to show me what a lazy person is
You are not even thinking about it
Your acting was way too restrained
If he were a good guy
he would have acted more open, right
Yes
Yeah
That little clue is very important
That confirms it, he must have already...
An Yu
I am certain
Then I am just
I just acted out everything I saw
Then you have a huge advantage
You perform last
Darn it, you were over there
Then look
No, you
I am a good guy
See if I acted out all the key points
Wouldn not that be enough
Right
You are right
If that is not necessary
I could just stand with eyes closed and still act it
You totally ruined it
You are
Good
a good guy
I have basically guessed the Undercover prompt
Come on, reveal your prompt
We do not need to act anymore
The rest of us
You four together
do that final reaction, okay
It really is you
Brother Bing is
I am more reserved
More reserved
The majority side scenario is
Autumn wind blows fallen leaves onto your face
You wake from a short nap
and find your idol lying beside you
The minority side scenario is
Autumn wind blows fallen leaves onto your face
You wake from a short nap
and find the person you secretly like beside you
So the Undercover word was secret crush
It is obvious now right
Then An Yu should be a good guy right
Yes
So what now
It is just these three
For sure
It is not me
Okay, third round, we lead the train
I will
Weiting Bro and I will lead one round with An Yu
Is that okay
Here is the plan
I will be Team Leader this round
I will be it this round
Where does Second Bro get that confidence from
Is it just because we are at your place
I am running for Team Leader
Raise your hand if you want Xiao Hu as Team Leader
I kind of want Teng Ge to be Team Leader once
I pick Teng Ge
But just for fun
Purely from a for fun angle
Bro is not here just for you to play
Bro is here to prove us
If we want to win the game
then of course I let Xiao Hu lead
Raise your hand if you want Teng Ge as Leader
Everyone raise your hands
Fan Chengcheng
Can you not even be united with us
That is not me
I can not achieve anything big
Come on, Xiao Hu takes the last group
Me and Weiting Bro with An Yu
Do we have an Undercover among us
in your last group
There is no Undercover
Okay
So the three Undercover players are called out
Teng Ge, Jingyu and Chengcheng are Undercover
Right
William Chan messed it all up
How could I have agreed to let him be Team Leader
Do you really think he is on your team
Of course I do