ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
YEAR 2017
Hi Hye-mi.
Oh, hi. Hello Gyu-young.
-Hye-mi!
-Hello.
ASUNG HIGH SCHOOL
SCHOLARSHIP EVENING PARTY
I express my sincere apologies
to the parents and students
of Asung High School
who are here with us tonight.
The recent news coverage of our school
has probably been a bit upsetting.
Our school is portrayed as a place
for the privileged class.
Most people call it…
"chance" nowadays.
Influential moms, dads, grandparents,
or principals from the privileged class…
All of that is true.
Asung High students are high achievers,
thanks to having such privileges.
Competition to get into top institutions
has always been fierce.
During the Qing Dynasty,
there was a scholar who kept failing
the imperial examinations.
So he decided to commit suicide
by hanging himself.
But before he did it, he complained
to the Great Jade Emperor.
"I tried so hard to pass the exam
but why couldn't I pass it?
How can people who are lazier
and less smart than me pass it?"
Hearing this complaint,
the Jade Emperor summoned two Gods.
The God of effort and the God of fate.
The emperor made the two Gods
compete in a drinking contest.
Who did you think won?
The God of fate drank seven glasses
while the God of effort
was only able to drink three.
From this fable, came the saying,
"Unchil gisam."
The success of a person depends
on luck rather than talent or effort.
Bullshit.
People describe the luck
that Asung High students
were born with as "privilege."
Which one would people pick
if you gave them two options?
If they could have "luck" or "effort,"
which one would they choose?
Luck trumps effort in today's world.
That's nonsense!
Lucky, privileged people
already rule the world.
That's bullshit!
-Oh, my!
-What's her problem?
Doesn't she have any shame?
How could she show up here?
Don't tell a false story, Director.
It wasn't the God of effort
who competed against the God of fate.
It was the God of justice.
The real lesson from "Unchil gisam"
is that although luck plays
a part in life,
justice underlies our society
and thus, luck alone
cannot determine everything.
It can't be helped
if the teachers and parents here
reject what I just said.
But
I wish…
the students…
will remember this.
Many people say that.
Losers who don't have
the courage to carry out justice
or use the luck that comes their way.
Weren't you summoned
by the police for questioning?
Bye, Ms. Ji Yoon-su.
-Take her away.
-Let's go.
Hurry.
How dare you come here?
Ms. Ji!
Block him.
I'll prove it.
I'll prove it myself.
Take her.
-She was a good teacher.
-A good teacher?
Then why did she do such a thing?
There are things you do in life
that don't create a problem
as long as they're swept under the rug.
But it's just that Ms. Ji
wasn't able to keep it hidden
from view.
-You call yourself a teacher?
-Say something!
-Don't you feel any shame?
-You're not saying sorry?
Oh, my. Ms. Min.
Her special feelings for him
and her eagerness to help
led to this incident.
Ms. Ji Yoon-su.
Did you sleep with him?
Did you sleep with your student?
Paik Seung-yoo, a junior at Asung High.
4 MONTHS AGO
Oh, no!
Oh, my goodness!
It's a hit-and-run!
Hello? There's been an accident
at Cheongju station.
A motorcycle hit a lady
and fled the scene.
The license plate number?
VROOM QUICK SERVICE
010-891-0276
Did anyone see the license plates?
Chungbuk Cheongju, Cha 2418.
That's the plate number.
I also saw the phone number
on the side. It's 010-891-0276.
Damn it.
That's not how you solve it.
Give it to me.
Let me try.
You can solve it like this.
You're no better than I am.
You can't solve it either.
-No, turn it that way…
-This way?
-Hey kids.
-It's Mom. Mom's here.
Come on.
Didn't you forget anything?
-My pyraminx!
-Why did you forget it?
What the?
Hey, it's solved.
-Hey.
-Hi. You came.
Let's go in.
-Welcome, ma'am.
-What's all the fuss about?
Take care of my luggage. Make sure
it doesn't get mixed up with theirs.
Yes, ma'am.
Ms. Min.
-Get up.
-Why?
-This table is reserved.
-For who?
-Hye-mi.
-Hi.
Oh, my. Ms. Min, it's been a long time.
So it has, Ms. Yoo.
-Gosh, she called her "Ms. Yoo."
-How could she say that?
Ms. Min, it seems like
you don't know that this table is reserved
because you don't come often.
This table is reserved?
But I don't see any nameplates.
Well, they're not reserved in our names.
-How?
-Based on the academic rank of your child.
So the seating is determined
by where your child is ranked
in the school.
I think your seat is over there.
That's where Seung-yoo is ranked, I think.
But you can sit here if you want.
If she's not smart,
she should at least be quick-witted.
-Hye-mi, sit here. Hurry.
-Okay.
That's your seat.
Yes?
Yes. Did you get there?
I'm here.
Don't hang up. Keep your phone on.
Okay.
HUSBAND
She's here.
Oh, my. She's here.
-Hello.
What's the occasion?
Is this a school parent get-together?
-We came for the lobster lunch.
Gosh, Ji-na looks so pretty.
May I have your attention?
Today, we, the school parents
of Asung High,
came together to have lunch.
By sheer coincidence,
it so happens that today is also
Director Noh Jung-ah's birthday.
All right. Shall we have a toast?
-Sure.
Director Noh, Happy Birthday to you.
-Happy Birthday to you.
-Happy Birthday.
-Live long and prosper.
Director Noh, please give a speech.
Thank you for wishing me a Happy Birthday.
As the director of Asung High,
I'd like to talk about a few matters as
we're about to begin the second semester.
The changing educational policy
is quite concerning to all of you.
Any news about educational policy
is cause for alarm.
Elimination of charter schools,
rolling admission restrictions,
or equalizing high school education…
These are all efforts
to dumb down education.
However, Asung High students
won't become average by such policies.
Our children are special.
We'll implement a curriculum
that will differentiate us from the rest.
But will it be okay to totally ignore
the educational policy?
Of course not.
So Asung High will participate
in a new initiative
announced by the Ministry of Education
called the high school credit system.
-We'll be participating?
-Yes.
But we will do it our way.
The Asung High School way.
DAD
Math.
It's a subject that instills fear
and despair among many Korean students.
But math is also a differentiating factor
in the college entrance exams.
We will be introducing
a special advanced math class.
So we have recruited
a special teacher to teach the class.
We will hire a math teacher
who has taught talented students
who have gone on to win
math competitions including Math Olympiad.
She graduated from Asung High,
Class of '05. Her name is Ji Yoon-su.
She received a B.S in mathematics
from Hankook University.
Since 2012, she's been teaching
at Cheongan High in Cheongju.
In the last few years, her students
have gone on to win Math Olympiads.
And what's notable is that
these students didn't go to cram schools.
They only relied on regular math classes.
They prepared for the Math Olympiad
just through regular math classes.
Really?
It's hard to believe though.
You mean students from
a public high school beat students
from science high schools
in the Math Olympiads?
That's correct.
And their secret is…
This.
I'm on my way. I'll see you soon.
Okay. Get here safely.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
How old are you?
-Six?
-Yes.
DAD
Hello.
Welcome, Hardy.
Today, you'll be giving
a math problem, right?
Yes.
I'll begin right away.
I came up with a problem
where you don't need to use a formula.
A six-year-old girl living on planet Earth
takes a train from her home
that goes south for 1km.
And then, she spots a bear
and chases it by going 1km east.
Then she goes 1km north,
where she returns home.
So the question is,
what color is the bear that the girl saw?
-The bear's color?
-Does that make any sense?
She went south, east and north,
but ended up back home?
Think carefully. It'll come to you.
-I can't figure it out.
-It's too hard.
White.
Correct.
CORRECT
Could you hurry, please?
I'm sorry.
White? A polar bear?
Why is it a polar bear?
Could you explain your answer, 3cut?
Since 3cut isn't replying, I'll explain.
You have to start with the premise
that the Earth is not flat
in order to solve this problem.
Oh, so that's why you said
the girl is on planet Earth.
That's right.
You go 1 km, another 1 km, and 1 km again.
Since it's the arctic circle,
the girl saw a polar bear.
TEACHER! THANKS TO YOU, MATH IS SO FUN!
I'M GOING TO STUDY HARD
AND GO TO THE SAME COLLEGE YOU WENT TO!
I WANT TO BECOME A MATH TEACHER LIKE YOU!
Oh, my.
A train is approaching.
We have arrived at Seoul Station.
Please make sure
you have all of your belongings with you.
Oh, I forgot!
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Sorry.
What?
Oh, thank you.
Yes. I just arrived.
Get in.
You must be tired, right?
I'm sorry that I couldn't pick you up.
I had a hectic day.
I just got off work now.
It's all right. The train ride was nice.
Me too.
-What?
-I mean, it's nice that you're here.
The seat belt is holding me back.
Let's go.
Do you have all of your belongings?
Yes.
Okay. Watch your step in the dark.
Stand right there.
One, two, three.
Surprise!
Should I sing that song?
Okay. I guess I shouldn't.
These are the boxes you sent ahead.
You packed a lot.
You'll have to organize them.
But you already bought furniture.
Yes, my mom bought it.
There's so much to prepare
for the wedding, you know.
I see.
What? You don't like the furniture?
It's not that.
-The place is already fully furnished.
-Fully furnished?
Well, if you open the cabinets,
they're bare.
So it's our job to fill them up.
Okay. I'll do that.
Teaching at Asung High
will help your career.
It'll be reorganized into an Academy
of Mathematics and Arts for the gifted.
An Academy of Mathematics and Arts
for the gifted?
What a fancy name.
-What?
-What now? You lost something?
What? Oh, thank you.
The guy wearing the 1729 cap?
He's here.
Seung-yoo.
Where have you been all day?
And why weren't you answering your phone?
You missed your counselor appointment too.
Answer me! Where were you?
-I went to Cheongju.
-Cheongju?
Why did you go there?
It's the anniversary of his death.
Why would you go there?
That was a long time ago.
You didn't need to go.
Come and sit over here.
Seung-yoo.
Just sit here for a minute, okay?
There's something important to discuss.
Sit here for just a while.
Honey, don't raise your voice.
You're getting another chance
after eight years.
So start over again.
Really?
Could you give that person
my number if he calls?
Okay. Thanks.
-They don't have it at the Lost and Found?
-No, nobody brought it.
You're so forgetful.
I knew you'd lose something.
How could you constantly
forget your things?
My notes and laptop were in the bag.
What will I do now?
Why are you touching his camera?
I'm just having a look.
What's going on with these pictures?
-Hold on.
-What?
They're Mersenne primes.
-What kind of primes?
-Mersenne primes.
A prime number
that is one less than a power of two.
Ms. Ji, I don't understand it at all.
Sorry, I get nauseous
when you talk about math.
Is he a mathematician?
What? Oh, thank you.
Did you leave your number
at the Lost and Found Center yesterday?
Hello.
We got our bags mixed up, right?
Yes. When do you have
time to exchange bags?
I'm sorry for taking the wrong bag.
I'm so clumsy.
Do you have time
tomorrow in the afternoon?
SOUNDS FINE
What time can you meet?
It's a bit old-fashioned, isn't it?
My father, who is the chairman
of the Asung Academy
enjoyed this hobby and now I do too.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Will you also teach calculus
at our school?
I'm planning to.
I wonder if you could teach it
to this group of students.
STUDENT RECORD
SUNG YE-LIN
They're high-achieving students.
STUDENT RECORD
JANG HYE-WON, JANG GYU-YOUNG
I would like to test them.
To determine their level?
Of course. You should select the best.
You heard that we'll be reorganized
as a school for the gifted, haven't you?
I think you'll be very excited about that.
STEAM education is important these days.
So we're trying to develop skills
in math, arts, and creativity.
Isn't that similar
to the curriculum you teach?
It's similar to my method,
but it's not compatible
with our current education system.
We can't keep letting students fail math.
I have high hopes for you
to bring positive change.
Thank you for the tea.
Bye then.
Why aren't you answering?
I'm sorry. I just saw your text.
How about 5:00 p.m.?
Where do you live?
Hangok-dong.
I live there too.
How about we meet
at Hangok Art Hall at 5:00 p.m.?
Okay.
NAME: 1729
NAME: ECO BAG
SCHOOL CLUB APPLICATION
How could the math club be more popular
than our dance club?
Wait a minute. But you know…
I practiced dancing a lot, right?
So isn't it my duty to spread
my passion to the freshmen class?
Okay?
I'm not going to study math
as a school club activity.
I'm going to join the dance club.
Let's be in the same club.
PAIK SEUNG-YOO
1ST CHOICE
Submit your applications if you're done.
SCHOOL CLUB APPLICATION, PAIK SEUNG-YOO
CALCULUS - MATH
2017 MATH CLUB
CALCULUS APPLICATION TEST
Teacher, these are the math problems
for the math club application.
Please solve them for me after school.
Ye-lin.
-Hello, Mr. Han.
-Oh, gosh. Ye-lin.
You have to study
and do school president duties.
-It's tough, isn't it?
-It's not tough.
But you didn't sign up
for my math class this semester.
Okay. See you.
All the best students have left
and I'm stuck teaching the laggards.
I couldn't get into
the advanced math class this semester.
-So I have to get into the math club.
-Get lost.
"Prove that Ab, bcca are
perpendicular to each other
when the new vector ABC
which is not a non-zero vector
satisfies the absolute value XA
plus YB plus ZC,
which is greater than
or equal to the absolute value XA
plus the absolute value YB
for all real numbers XYZ."
What does this even mean?
Are you in the hip-hop club?
-You can rap pretty well.
-This is calculus.
Stop talking about calculus.
You're making me vomit.
You can't even dance.
What is it?
What is that?
-Hi.
-Hello, ma'am.
Ma'am, what are those paintings?
I wonder what they are.
How are they related to math?
Let's figure that out together.
My name is Ji Yoon-su.
Nice to meet you all.
And also thank you
for signing up for the fearsome
advanced math class.
Ms. Ji, I finished solving
the math club test.
-Can I submit my answers now?
-What? You finished it already?
What? Seriously?
Really?
SOLVE THE PROBLEM BELOW TO JOIN CALCULUS
QUESTION:
-All right. Let's begin, okay?
-Yes.
Turn to page six.
-Okay.
You learned how to determine convergence
or divergence in a sequence, right?
-What are those pictures?
-Yes.
Therefore, the dot product
of vectors a, c and vectors b, c is 0.
Likewise, the dot product
of vectors a, b becomes 0.
So vectors a, b, c
are perpendicular to each other.
That's how you get the answer.
Did you understand it?
-Yes.
-Okay.
-Ask me if you have any questions.
Don't be bothered by the noise.
They do that a lot.
You proposed to the school board
to create an advanced
math class, didn't you?
Yes.
Why did you do that?
You know that Ye-lin lags in math.
So that she'll get
a presidential award.
What? A presidential award?
What did you say?
What is this presidential award about?
-Help me lift this.
-Oh, okay.
Tell me more.
What is this presidential award?
Be patient. I, Senator Sung Min-joon,
will make Ye-lin a recipient
of a presidential award.
A presidential award.
Please…
No, I'll get it.
What are you calling about?
Did you arrive there?
Okay, I'll join you soon.
Okay.
How is the Mathematician Olympics
coming along?
The committee is positive about
hosting a high school math competition.
It'll be co-hosted by the Math Council
and the Ministry of Education.
What's your impression
of the new math teacher?
Do you think she'll cooperate?
I'm not sure. I don't think she will.
Why not?
-You said we needed her.
-Get the competition organized first.
I'll take care of the next step.
MATH CLASSROOM
You all worked hard on the math problem.
But…
nobody got the answer right.
My answer was wrong too?
I'm sure I solved it.
No one among the entire junior students
including this advanced math class
got the correct answer.
-What?
-That's impossible.
-Seriously?
-But that's not possible.
So I'm thinking about
giving you another chance.
You'll have until tomorrow 8:30 a.m.
to resubmit your answers.
Any questions?
-Could you give us a hint?
-A hint?
In a plane,
given a line and a point not on it,
at most one line parallel to the given
line can be drawn through the point.
For over 2000 years,
mathematicians believed
Euclid's fifth postulate to be inevitable.
But in the 19th century,
a young man questioned
whether it was obvious.
The man's dad dissuaded him
from proving Euclid's parallel postulate,
but he wrote to his dad,
"Dad, I have discovered
such wonderful things that I was amazed.
Out of nothing I have created
a strange new universe."
His name was János Bolyai.
That is how non-Euclidean geometry began.
NON-EUCLIDEAN GEOMETRY:
GEOMETRIES THAT DIFFER FROM,
BUT ARE VERY CLOSE TO EUCLIDEAN GEOMETRY
So go back to the beginning.
Look at all possibilities.
That's my hint.
Let's start class.
-Hey, look.
-What's this?
Hey, look at this.
-What is it?
-Look at this.
Ye-lin, look at that.
-There's no explanation to his answer.
-Ms. Ji.
-Yes?
-Look at that.
Who solved this?
It's not me.
Not me.
Hey, you were the first
to leave the classroom.
It wasn't me. It was already there.
For real.
Who is playing a prank then?
THE PROPOSITION IS WRONG
THE MARGIN IS TOO SMALL
TO INCLUDE THE PROOF
This is amazing.
You mean…
Yes, that's the correct answer.
-What?
-The proposition is wrong?
-Yes.
-But I solved it.
If you solved it, it means
you misunderstood the proposition.
Remember the hint I gave you earlier?
But who solved this?
None of you did this?
-Not us.
-Nobody saw the poster?
I didn't see anyone.
-You didn't see who did it?
-No.
Did anyone notice
when it was pinned there?
What's going on?
-Hello, Mr. Han.
-Hello.
Sir, is that the correct answer?
What's the math problem?
THE PROPOSITION IS WRONG
Nobody is showing up there, Teacher.
Okay.
Oh, have a seat.
Is this the correct answer, Ms. Ji?
Yes, that's the answer.
The proposition is wrong?
That's the answer.
You played a little joke, I see.
A joke?
You gave the students a problem
that was too obvious.
Since you're new here,
you don't seem to know.
But the students at Asung High
are serious and pure.
Why did you play a joke like this?
Is this amusing to you?
Does this help them
improve their math skills?
I'll excuse myself.
I'll leave you two
to discuss this further.
Give them a different problem.
This problem isn't appropriate
for Asung High students.
How is it not appropriate?
The answer is "the proposition is wrong."
That's a rejection of the question itself.
Asung High students
don't give answers like that.
The students are already good
at finding the right answer.
Sometimes they need to experience
a problem without an answer
or one with the wrong proposition.
Do the students need to know
that there is a theorem
that cannot be proven?
What?
Our students don't have time
for such problems and it's unnecessary.
You'll understand that…
over time.
Aren't you curious to know
who answered it correctly?
How can we be sure it's correct?
Whoever wrote it could be bluffing.
-Bluffing?
-Take a look.
The student didn't offer
any proof or explanation.
Thank you, Director.
Thanks to you,
I think I can find the student.
Paik Seung-yoo! Is it you?
Did you write down that
the proposition was wrong?
It's you, right?
Why did you apply to the math club?
-I don't know what you're talking about.
-What about this then?
You didn't see this?
I think it was meant for you to read.
IT IS VERY LIKELY THAT
THE SOLVER IS BLUFFING
HE OR SHE QUOTED FERMAT
"Bluffing"?
What did she write?
Well, you see…
So it's a reference to
Fermat's Last Theorem, which is famous.
Fermat proposed many arithmetic theorems,
but there are few records of his proof.
He left a note saying,
"The margin is too small
to include the proof."
His Last Theorem
was proven 350 years later.
So people questioned
whether Fermat could have known the proof.
Many mathematicians doubt he did.
Fermat's Last Theorem was proven
using 20th-century techniques.
Experts doubt that Fermat knew the proof
as he lived in the 17th century.
Thus, it is very likely that
the solver is bluffing
and does not actually know
the mistake in the proposition
as he or she quoted Fermat.
MATH APTITUDE COMPETITION
GRAND PRIZE, PAIK MIN-JAE
ELEMENTARY MATH COMPETITION
GOLD MEDAL, PAIK MIN-JAE
-Hello, Ms. Ji.
-Hello.
Bye!
Goodbye, Ms. Ji.
…THUS, THE PROPOSITION IS WRONG
Did you solve it?
Great work.
That's the proof.
You did well.
It's you, Ye-lin. Sung Ye-lin.
Why didn't you say it earlier
that it was you?
Well…
I thought I shouldn't.
Because it didn't seem right
to point out something wrong
in a problem you gave us.
I see. That makes sense.
But you can write down
an answer like that anytime.
I welcome it.
Okay, Ms. Ji.
I'll go home now.
I'm almost there. Hangok Art Hall.
Oh, I forgot.
What?
You're wearing that number. 1729.
Last time, it was on your cap.
It's the smallest number
expressible as the sum of two cubes
in two different ways.
It's what Ramanujan told Hardy
when he remarked that 1729
seemed like a dull number.
G. H. HARDY: BRITISH MATHEMATICIAN
SRINIVASA RAMANUJAN: INDIAN MATHEMATICIAN
If you look at it that way,
all numbers look meaningless, don't they?
Here's your bag.
I looked through the camera to find
any clues to track you down.
You took interesting photos.
Do you like math?
No, I don't.
Thanks.
Did you see a button? It was right here.
This small.
-No, I didn't see it.
-Okay.
Bye.
Wait.
It's wonderful proof.
Hello?
It was raining earlier.
Did you get home safely?
What? Oh, yes.
And you got your bag back?
Yes, I gave his back and I got mine.
-But you know what?
-What?
I think there's a Ramanujan at our school.
Who?
Yoon-su, I'm sorry,
but I just arrived at my destination.
I'll call you after.
Thanks to you, the MoE will be a part of
the International Mathematician Olympics
that will be held in Korea
for the first time.
In the Olympics,
the high school competition
will get a lot of media attention.
I'm sure Asung High
has received state funding
after being chosen as a school
under the high school credit system.
I was told that Asung High
was selected after
a rigorous screening process.
Is that not the case?
What? The school
qualified fairly, of course.
As an education committee member,
I cannot be seen as using my influence.
When it comes
to the education of children,
I try to be
as transparent and fair as possible.
You sure
take after your father a lot.
He was a man of principle
when he served in the Blue House.
Your guest has arrived.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for being late,
Vice Minister and Senator Sung.
…THUS, THE PROPOSITION IS WRONG
My little princess.
Have a snack.
I want a new math tutor.
What? Why?
She's not that good.
She isn't?
All right. I'll find you a new tutor.
Well, you know…
Gosh, your dad told me not to tell you.
You might receive a presidential award.
You know that competition…
The Mathematician World Cup
that'll be held next month.
It's not called the World Cup.
It's Olympics.
They're both the same.
What is the award for?
Did you call for me?
Was it you?
Yes?
Did you get the correct answer
in the math club test?
Well…
It has to be you.
Ms. Ji, the new math teacher,
is different from Mr. Han.
She won't give you preferential
treatment or be lenient.
So you have to perform well
in order for her to like you.
I'll try my best.
Ye-lin.
You're pretty and get good grades.
But why do you lack confidence?
Lift your chin. Stand straight.
Otherwise, they'll find out
that you didn't earn
your standings in school.
You're dismissed.
What is it?
You fooled everyone.
You said it wasn't you.
You said you couldn't go back
to being the person you used to be.
Tell me what you're thinking!
-Why are you getting upset?
-You have to ask?
I'm asking you if you're my competition.
That won't happen.
Then why did you do that?
Why did you write down the proof?
-I don't know.
-What?
Tell me.
What?
How did you prove it?
Please.
What happened at MIT?
After you came back, you became stupid.
Why are you pretending to be dumb
when you can solve a problem like that?
Do you want to know
the proof or my story?
It must have been amusing, right?
A problem like this is a cinch for you.
You must have felt superior
when you saw us studying
and competing so hard.
I wonder why you became like that.
You don't remember?
When I was little, my parents
scolded me and compared me to you.
I tried so hard to get
better grades than you.
But then you'd outscore me.
I wanted to give up.
-You're blaming me for that?
-Yes, it's your fault.
I wasn't doing badly.
You were exceptionally good.
You're special.
You're exceptional.
Where are you going? Hey, Paik Seung-yoo!
Hello.
-Hello, Ms. Ji.
Let's talk about the math club first.
As you all know, the answer
to the problem was, "Wrong proposition."
I know that you're not used
to solving problems
without an exact answer.
But it's like our lives.
Life is full of wrongs.
There are life problems which you
can't resolve or quite understand.
Are you going to give another problem
like that for the math club test?
I haven't decided yet.
By the way, a student
in this class got the answer.
Really?
Ye-lin.
Can you explain the proof to everyone?
Why is the proposition wrong?
Wow, Ye-lin.
-Really?
-Amazing.
-That's amazing.
-Awesome, Ye-lin.
Ye-lin.
You don't remember it well, I see.
No.
I'm sorry. I suddenly forgot.
Go back to your seat.
I'll explain the proof to you.
What's going on?
Ye-lin.
I have
never been told
that I did well.
I grew up being told that
my answer was wrong a lot more.
Ever since I started learning math.
I'm sorry for lying to you.
Who solved this?
Hey!
All right. Tension.
-Okay.
-Eye contact.
Hey!
-Double, Double flip!
-Flip!
One.
What? Ms. Ji, What's up!
Ms. Ji!
-Hello.
-Hello!
Our group is called Project D.
Since you appear in the video,
you've automatically become
a member of Project D.
Congratulations!
Ms. Ji, do you want to see our video?
This dance is more
about the vibe than technique.
Look at our expressions.
Okay.
He looks alive.
We're preparing
for an upcoming creator contest.
-So we're always practicing.
-Show you a different one.
Wait a minute.
When did you take this video?
What did you choose
for your extracurricular activities?
Why are you asking?
I don't want to be in the ones you're in.
I'm not in the math camp so don't worry.
You didn't solve that problem, right?
You couldn't have with your skills.
Then who solved it?
-Ms. Ji is watching our video intently.
-Because we look cool in it.
You're wearing that number. 1729.
Do you like math?
Ms. Ji, please fill out
the club application.
All right. Stretch. One, two, three, four.
-Hello, Ms. Ji.
Paik Seung-yoo.
Paik Seung-yoo!
I found you.
Paik Seung-yoo?
Can I see his student record
from the last semester?
But you still have to try your best.
Otherwise, I'll drop you.
We're adding a high school category
to the International
Mathematician Olympics.
Ms. Ji spent the night with that student.
-No. I'm not going there!
-Fill this with trophies again!
Until you do as I say,
you can't do whatever you want.
You know how it feels and so do I.
There's nothingness in that moment.