ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
A math proof is either true or false.
Those are the only two things that matter.
You can't call a math proof
true if it's not.
Nor can you call a proof false
when it's true.
Mathematicians cannot lie.
However, in the messy world we live in,
sometimes what's false
is considered to be true
while what is true
is considered to be false.
That's exactly
what happened here at Asung High,
the predecessor of Asung Academy,
four years ago.
There was a rumor about a teacher
having an inappropriate relationship
with a student.
This so-called scandal rocked Hangok-dong
and it was sensationalized.
The truth was buried by false claims.
And a false narrative became the truth.
I was at the center
of the teacher-student scandal.
I was the high school student.
You need to see this.
I was at the center
of the teacher-student scandal.
I was the high school student.
This isn't the time or place
to bring up your personal story.
I'm speaking as a mathematician.
Like I said earlier,
you cannot lie in math.
I believe in the power of logic and proof.
Today,
I will present to you
a new project to seek for the truth.
What were the facts and lies
behind the scandal that unfolded
at Asung High four years ago?
Who was behind pushing the false narrative
while burying the truth,
and what was their purpose?
I will lay out my proof.
Are you claiming that someone defamed
another person's character?
That's correct.
Why did Seung-yoo say those things?
He's gone crazy.
-Is this why he became a teacher here?
-But who defamed who?
Perhaps he's talking about the time
Ms. Ji accused Ye-lin
of cheating on the midterm--
Hey, So-jung. Don't talk about something
you're not sure about.
What the? Why are you picking on me?
-What's gotten into him?
-He's acting crazy too.
You've ruined my event.
How so?
Asung Academy of Mathematics and Arts,
Asung High,
National Math Museum
are the trending terms right now.
This is great publicity
if you were to ask me.
You're picking a fight with me,
aren't you?
If this bothers you…
Principal Noh, prepare yourself
for a fight like me.
At this point, whoever makes threats
or tries blackmail is the guilty party.
My gosh. Really.
He's totally gone mad. Seung-yoo.
Ye-lin, don't worry.
Your dad and the principal
will take care of this.
Okay?
Gosh.
Let's hold a press conference too!
Don't send the reporters away.
Let's do it!
And then what?
So we'll tell them we didn't frame anyone
and it's not about us?
Shall we?
Come to your senses.
He didn't mention us by name.
It's just a matter of time
before people find out.
How will you respond then?
Is an apple seed a fruit?
Or is it not a fruit?
-What are you talking about?
-A seed is not a fruit.
But if you plant a seed,
it'll become a fruit.
So a seed isn't a fruit,
but it can also be a fruit.
What are you talking about?
Why cannot it appear false
when, in fact, it is true?
You really don't?
You need to know.
You should be explaining yourself.
That's the right thing to do.
I wish you'll explain everything to me.
Have some hot coffee. Here.
-What if…
-Yes?
If I'd admitted what I did was wrong,
what would've happened after?
What? What did you do wrong?
You know.
I cheated on the math exam
with the answer sheet you gave me.
-But then Ms. Ji found out--
-Why is that your fault?
Then whose fault is it?
Ye-lin.
You need to get your head on straight.
None of us did anything wrong.
I only did what was good for you--
Please stop saying that!
Did anything you do for me turn out well?
Ye-lin. How can you say that?
I've always done what's best for you.
Do you think I did it for me, then?
I'll ask you one last time.
You have nothing to say?
Oh, my! Ye-lin!
Try to breathe. Calm down. Okay?
Could you tell me
where I can find Sung Ye-lin?
Over here, Honey.
What happened to her?
She went into shock.
She suddenly couldn't breathe.
Honey, you can fix the matter, right?
What did Principal Noh say?
-Is it true what he said?
-What?
Did Ye-lin cheat
on her exams in high school?
Be quiet! Are you crazy?
Come here. Who said that?
PAIK SEUNG-YOO, "I WAS INVOLVED IN
THE TEACHER-STUDENT SCANDAL"
WHAT'S THE TRUTH BEHIND
THE ASUNG HIGH SCANDAL?
What the hell was that?
Do you know what you just did?
I told you I made up my mind.
I know why I have to do this.
This isn't the right way.
You're risking your bright career.
It's not smart.
-Why would it ruin my career?
-Do you have to ask?
You're a mathematician.
What's more important than that?
You don't need to prove my case.
Why did you have to do this
while putting your reputation on the line?
It's not the most important thing.
There are more important things
to me than math!
Why did I do math?
How did I become a mathematician
and win the Lucifer Prize?
Because I'm super smart?
Or because you were a good teacher?
No.
I was at the center
of the teacher-student scandal.
I was the high school student.
Is it funny to you?
Look at their expressions.
They're mad and shocked,
but they can't show it on camera.
He's so reckless.
Yoon-su told you to leave
Seung-yoo out of the plan, right?
But Seung-yoo made it clear
he's going to be a part of it anyway.
Let them handle that past scandal.
Meanwhile, we'll work on
what we can attack her with right now.
He is quite serious
with his intentions
when it comes to Yoon-su.
So what if he is now?
He should give up on her.
I guess weighing things out
is not considered love.
To Seung-yoo, I mean.
For the past four years,
I worked on math proofs like crazy
because that's all I had left.
It was the only way to protect my sanity.
And now I've finally found you. But why…
Why are you telling me that
math is all that matters to me?
Why can't there be something
more important than that?
I have…
never wanted to be more important
to you than math.
That won't change.
The case you told everyone you would prove
isn't more beautiful or worthy
than one equation in a geometry proof.
Wouldn't it be a waste
to ruin his reputation now?
Why do you look so shocked?
You've seen it before.
The photo of you two at the airport.
NOH YEON-WOO
I'm sorry for calling a meeting
at such an early hour.
As the principal, I would like to address
what Mr. Paik said yesterday
and also inform you
about an important matter.
In regards
to Mr. Paik's statements yesterday,
we will conduct an investigation
and take action against him.
Is it true that
there was cheating going on
at Asung High?
Why are you looking at me?
What did you hear?
They're all baseless rumors.
Baseless rumors? I'm not making this up.
Now…
This is Asung Academy, not Asung High.
And midterms are coming up soon.
Maintaining a high GPA is important
when applying to Ivy League schools.
I have set up a meeting
with a top educational consultant.
He will provide us with
the latest admission criteria and trends
that were obtained through his contacts
among admissions officers
at Ivy League schools.
Let's go meet him now.
These are the list of students
in the global gifted class.
LIST OF STUDENTS
PARTICIPATING IN THE PROJECT
What's wrong?
Is it because Ms. Ji might learn
of our pay-to-play admissions scheme?
I've kept this a tight secret.
But I’m nervous
because she worked closely with me.
That's Minister Kyung Woo-min,
Senator Sung Min-joon.
Hankook University Professor,
Son Seung-yeon,
And Myungjin Daily chairman, Kim Yeon-jun.
Those are the parents
of the global gifted class.
So even if we were to get caught…
These high-powered individuals
are backing us.
So what's there to worry about?
Come in.
Asung Academy school parents are here.
I was at the center of…
Dear, what is he talking about?
I was the high school student.
Why is Seung-yoo doing this?
Seung-yoo.
-What's going on, son?
-I know you're shocked.
Let's sit down first.
I need to tell you something.
Principal Noh, what should we do?
Is there any way I can help?
Ji Yoon-su is such a devil.
It turns out she's a famous instructor
at a math clinic in Hangok-dong.
I almost sent Yoo-chan to that clinic.
It gives me chills just thinking about it.
I'll see you afterward.
You bought this for me in Italy, remember?
Director Noh had
the same accessory on her handbag.
It must be a similar item.
I didn't sleep well last night,
so I don't look so great.
How is Ye-lin?
Oh, yes.
She's also in bad shape.
Ye-lin has had it tough
for quite some time.
For how long?
You didn't know?
She knew about the relationship
between Ms. Ji and Paik Seung-yoo.
She knew what?
What does that have to do with Ye-lin?
Then…
what you're saying is true?
Someone spread false rumors
about you and Ms. Ji to cover up
Ye-lin's cheating scandal?
-Yes.
-Forget it.
We pressed charges,
but the judge dismissed them.
Bringing it up now won't change anything.
So I have to handle it
before it's too late.
I said forget about it!
Quit teaching there.
-Dad.
-Why can't you stay out of this?
Why are you messing up your career?
You're still young and this is
the most important period in your life.
You've got so much to accomplish.
I'm not messing anything up.
I'm resolving an unresolved problem.
Are you still seeing her?
Answer me! Are you?
It's not what you think it is.
Then what is it?
I'll tell you everything later.
I have to go work now,
so I'll come by again.
Was this your plan all along?
You sent us your thesis paper
and came over for dinner
-for us to soften us up, right?
-How can you say that, Dad?
Then make a promise.
That you won't see her again!
Who'd believe someone
who's trying to prove there was no scandal
if you're still seeing her?
Am I wrong?
If you see her again,
I won't see you ever again.
If you keep seeing her, I'll disown you.
What? My goodness…
Jeez…
-Don't be bothered by what your dad said.
-It's okay.
-I'll come again.
-Okay.
Why does he have to be so…
He's a liar.
My mom says they were all over each other.
-Like how?
-How?
-They stayed late together at school…
-At night?
-They were in an empty classroom…
-That's crazy.
Stop gossiping about them.
You don't know anything.
You weren't even there.
So? What do you know then?
I know more than you do.
You went to that cram school, didn't you?
Ji Yoon-su is the math instructor there.
My mom told me everything.
No wonder she made every student sign
a confidentiality agreement.
Because she has a dirty past.
She was fired anyway.
Seung-yoo and that woman
should be driven out of this neighborhood.
Watch your mouth!
-Don't tell me what to do.
-Be quiet!
Everyone, sit.
Mr. Paik Seung-yoo won't be here.
So study by yourselves.
Open your books.
You're relieved from all of your duties.
You won't be teaching any classes.
Your conduct was inappropriate
for a teacher and you broke our rules.
Read it and then sign it.
SIGNATURE: PAIK SEUNG-YOO
A disciplinary committee
will open an investigation.
You can't stop what I'm doing
by firing me.
You're aware of that, right?
You'll prove love through math?
Is that even possible?
What about proving that there is no love?
Can that be proven by equations?
I like your spirit.
This might be the most difficult problem
you've ever tried to solve.
What do you mean?
To prove what you want,
it might be unrelated to defamation,
but rather, more relevant
to the definition of love.
Seung-yoo might quit his teaching job.
To be more precise,
he's getting fired, I think.
How are you going to cope
without someone on your side?
Hey.
I once said
you were a scary person, didn't I?
I take that back.
-You're pathetic.
-What?
Your mom is the school principal,
so why do you feel the need to pick on me?
She's got power and
I have nobody like that behind me.
You don't like your mom that much, right?
Yet, you enjoy all the privileges
that come from being her daughter.
You're a hypocrite.
Hey, hurry up and come out!
Hey, hurry up! Come out!
I know you're in there!
You're shameless!
You thought I didn't know
you had a relationship with him?
You seduced him when he was a teenager.
And you seduced him again
now that he's famous?
Open up!
I said open up!
Isn't that actress Yoo Hye-mi?
What is she doing here?
You're an embarrassment.
You better be prepared, because you're
going to pay for what you did.
Come to school.
The principal would like to see you.
Why did you want to see me?
Sit.
There's something
I would like to share with you.
Do whatever you want with it.
I'm paying you back
for the photo you gave me.
The one you took at Jeju Airport.
I picked out the best ones among hundreds.
Make good use of it.
-Hello?
-Where are you?
Why did you want to see me now?
I'm busy. We could talk
about it at home later.
I went to Ji Yoon-su's apartment.
-Did you see her?
-No, she refused to open the door.
What are you planning to do?
Principal Noh is going to handle it,
so don't worry about it.
How can I not worry?
Did anything you get involved in
have a good outcome?
Be careful and don't do
anything reckless this time.
You can't do anything
without Principal Noh, right?
What?
See you.
After the audit is finished,
let's enjoy some wine too.
What is this?
Are you having an affair with her?
What is the meaning of this?
How dare you spy on me?
Tell me what's going on right now.
What's going on with her?
We do a lot of deals together.
-What? Deals?
-You don't know what that is?
Thanks to Principal Noh,
Ye-lin and Yoo-chan have benefited
a lot from her school.
So, in return, I funnel information
to her and try to please her.
You didn't know about that?
So you give her information
and also your love?
-Hey, Hye-mi!
-Oh, my.
We shouldn't be arguing over this.
Come to your senses!
Instead of spying on me,
keep an eye on Ye-lin.
Is Yoon-su still hanging out
with that younger guy?
How could that incident resurface?
Mother.
Hurry up and marry Yeon-woo,
the daughter of chairman Noh.
You need to project a wholesome image
before things get out of hand.
What if another wild rumor
goes around that involves you?
I'll do what I think is right.
Really?
You were humiliated by a woman
whom we never approved of.
And you keep telling us that?
End of discussion. Get married.
Please sign there.
Goodbye.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
Hurry up and marry Sung-jae.
I'll leave that to you.
Sure, Mother. Don't worry.
Come in.
-Please bring our order.
-Okay.
You'll find this useful
in the board meeting.
Check the names
of the shareholders' list first.
I will.
This is exactly what I needed.
And if I can prove that she stole profits
from the foundation
to line her own pockets,
then I can bring her down.
You must hurry.
Once she loses her position,
it'll help Seung-yoo
with his fight against her.
By the way,
I also brought a present for you.
LEARNING WISDOM OF LIFE IN NATURE
JEJU VERTA SCHOOL
If you want,
I'll give you a recommendation.
If you're interested in the job, tell me.
Come and join us.
I called him to join us for lunch.
Is that okay?
Sit down.
You were with your mom, right?
She texted me, saying she
wants us to get married soon.
We're getting married.
Karmic connections
are quite strange, right?
It's hard to predict
how things will turn out in the end.
You also have a special connection
with Seung-yoo.
Yoon-su.
Are you two finished talking?
-I'll get going.
-You're not going to wish us well?
Congratulations. To both of you.
How could you look upset
in front of Yoon-su?
Couldn't you maintain your composure?
Are we talking about me
not being considerate?
Were you showing
any consideration towards me?
I showed great consideration, actually.
I didn't mention to her
that I haven't decided to marry you yet.
This better be the last time…
you ever bring Yoon-su
into our relationship.
That is, if you're interested
in marrying me.
Yoon-su handed me some key evidence.
Jung-ah will never become
the next chairman of Asung Foundation.
So do the calculations in your head.
Then decide how we'll move forward
with our relationship.
If our relationship
is based on calculations,
I don't understand why you waste energy
on doing this to me.
She still forgets things.
-Hey, Seung-yoo!
-Over here.
Yesterday was really intense.
My knees got weak and I almost fell.
-Hi.
-Are you feeling all right?
-There had to be repercussions.
-I got relieved from my duties.
I'm really curious about something.
What's going on between you and Ms. Ji?
Do you like her?
What are you talking about?
You had a crush on her
back in high school.
Do you still like her?
What? What do you mean?
-Have you met Ms. Ji?
-He sure has. They're really close.
-Is that true?
-That can't happen. It's wrong.
-Why is it wrong?
-What?
-Well…
-Hold on a second.
You said you were framed.
That the scandal involving you
was sensationalized.
But you're seeing her now?
What's happening?
You both like each other?
Hey, let's not talk about it.
-Hey, Seung-yoo!
-Hey!
He's crazy.
-Ye-lin?
-Hey, why is she here?
When did she get here?
Seung-yoo!
I like you.
I said I like you.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You didn't want me.
You wanted my confession, right?
So you played with my emotions, right?
I was hoping you'd tell me
why you did that back then.
I did it because I liked you.
I got jealous.
I wanted to break up
your relationship with her.
Then why are you crying
and getting upset if you like me?
If you like someone,
you feel happy around them.
And you hope that
person will be happy too.
You don't like me.
Then what?
You couldn't get what you wanted
for the first time in your life,
so you wanted to make me miserable
along with the person I liked.
Follow me.
LEARNING WISDOM OF LIFE IN NATURE
JEJU VERTA SCHOOL
SCHOOL LIFE AND CURRICULUM
I'll get going.
PAIK SEUNG-YOO
Hello?
Isn't this Ji Yoon-su's phone?
This is Ryu Sung-jae.
Why do you have her phone?
Did Yoon-su agree
to what you told everyone yesterday?
If you fail to prove your case,
who will be harmed the most?
You're a hotshot mathematician,
so you'll be able to move on,
but Yoon-su doesn't have that option.
What are you trying to say?
If Yoon-su disagrees,
then take a moment to think it over.
Ask her
what she wants.
Don't push her into doing something
and don't impose your way
of doing things on her.
Are you giving me advice?
What if I had acted like that?
It's a murmur of regret.
I'm not cheering you on or anything,
so don't get the wrong idea.
Even if I fail to prove my case,
I'll make sure that Yoon-su
will not be harmed in any way.
I won't let that happen.
Did you know this?
The deepest cut comes
from the person you're closest to.
-Where are you going?
-There was a car following you.
-Right now?
-And he's also taking pictures.
Act normal and go home.
Stay here.
-How did you get this?
-Ryu Sung-jae gave it to me.
I'll call you. Stay inside.
The door is closing.
I'd like to report a suspicious vehicle.
Let go!
Who are you? Who hired you?
-Let go!
-Who are you?
Sir! Are you okay? Wake up!
Paik Seung-yoo.
He's being treated inside. Bed number two.
Seung-yoo.
Are you his guardian?
Is his injury serious?
He suffered a mild concussion.
The scans show no brain damage.
But his condition needs to be monitored.
Call me when he wakes up.
Okay, Doctor. Thank you.
Are you awake?
I'll call the doctor.
I'm fine.
Just wait a minute.
Are you really okay?
Does your head hurt?
He was driving an unregistered vehicle.
They're looking for him.
-What about the camera?
-I think he ran away with it.
How long has he been following me?
Go in.
If you don't feel well,
go to the hospital.
I don't know how to proceed
without making this hard for you.
I don't want that to happen.
Should I stop…
what I'm doing?
Go home first. Get some rest.
And get some sleep.
Take care.
UTN NEWS
These are interesting photos.
Would you like me to air this on the news?
Not right now.
We'll give you an approximate date.
So please air it on the news then.
Principal Noh said that
she is making this
special request only to you, Mr. Park.
-Gosh.
-And this…
As you requested.
FRIEND AND FRIEND
Hello, Mr. Han.
I met with Ms. Park, a school assistant,
who worked at Asung High four years ago.
She agreed to give a witness statement
on what happened and who ordered it.
So what?
You could tell the truth with her
or you can refuse to.
Regardless of what you decide,
I'm going to expose the truth.
You're threatening me?
I got fired by the school
and prosecutors
are building a case against me.
I'm offering advice
and also asking for a favor.
If you take the witness stand,
the judge will take that
into consideration.
But if you decide not to,
then you'll probably take the fall
for all that unfolded at Asung High.
The situation will become worse
for you than it is now.
You're the only one being prosecuted
over the admissions scandal
at Asung Academy, aren't you?
I'm asking for your help, Mr. Han.
-Thank you.
-Have a good day.
Hee-sung.
We need to talk.
-Get out.
-What?
Don't call me by my name and just leave!
-Get out! Didn't you hear me?
-My gosh.
Get out!
I heard everything.
To cover up what your daughter did,
the school framed my son.
So get out.
Why are you getting mad at me?
Listen to me.
We shouldn't be arguing right now.
You and I have to join forces
to chase that woman out
of this neighborhood.
What are you talking about?
They're so much in love.
Seung-yoo goes to see her every day.
It's really intense.
-What?
-She lives in this neighborhood!
-Please leave.
-What did you say?
-Get out now!
-Oh, my. What's your problem?
I told you to leave.
You shouldn't be treating me
like this. Gosh.
I'm not lying!
Where does she live?
Do you have her address?
You don't like me.
You couldn't get what you wanted
for the first time in your life,
so you wanted to make me miserable
along with the person I liked.
Make good use of it.
SUNG YE-LIN
Hello?
You told me it's not true that I like you.
Well, you're not in love
with Ms. Ji, either.
You won't give up on her
because of your guilt.
I'm going to the authorities tomorrow.
To press charges against Principal Noh
and your dad for their involvement
in the cheating scandal.
You need to do what's right.
Ms. Ji and I are not
your problem right now.
You need to come to your senses.
She's using you
because she knows how guilty you feel.
Ye-lin!
Do you know who you're like?
Principal Noh.
She'll brainwash and gaslight people
to get what she wants.
Do you want to become like her?
It's not too late.
You can change.
-I met Ms. Ji.
-What?
I told her to stop seeing you.
But she said she wouldn't.
Instead, she's hiding behind you
and using you.
So snap out of it!
You're being played for a fool!
I'm warning you.
Don't ever do that to her again.
If she's not using you, then what is it?
Did she say she loves you?
You don't care
if she uses you like a tool?
Because you're in love with her?
Yes.
I'm in love with her.
-Hello, Ms. Ji.
-Hi. Come in.
-It's cold today, isn't it?
-It's fine.
It came as a shock, didn't it?
A lot of shocking things
are happening lately.
I'm fine. I'm worried about you.
Here.
You made this yourself?
Yes. It's to prepare you
for your midterms.
Wow. Thank you, Ms. Ji.
Hello?
You're Mr. Ji Hyeon-wook's
guardian, right?
Yes, I am.
MS. JI YOON-SU
CHOI SHI-AN
Hello?
There's bad news, Mr. Paik.
Dad.
What happened?
He suffered insulin shock.
He hasn't been eating well recently.
His pneumonia has worsened
since he isn't getting enough nutrients.
He's been working obsessively.
Writing notes and reading.
That's what he does every day.
Dad.
Why are you getting up?
Dad!
Why aren't you eating?
Why are you obsessed with these notes?
No. That's not it.
I'm not.
Did you solve the problem?
You need to solve it
even you don't want to.
I'm scared.
Because I feel like
I'm falling in love with the problem.
Sometimes you can only solve
a problem when you love it.
There are problems
you can't solve unless you go crazy.
Only a problem like that
has the right to shatter my life.
What if the premise has an error?
Then you have to get rid of it.
If you work on it despite knowing
it's wrong, then you'll hit a wall.
However,
the life of a mathematician is
searching for answers in the dark.
Sometimes, it's not necessary
to find the solution.
Are you okay, Professor?
Why did he take that off?
I'll go tell the nurse.
Just wait a little longer.
I'll finish this quickly.
The people who did this
to us will pay for it.
I'll set the record straight about us.
And let's reset our relationship
without any more guilt or remorse.
It'll just be the two of us.
Let's have a fresh start.
Do you think we can
start over our relationship?
The premise is that we weren't in love.
But can the conclusion be "love"?
Our hearts are true.
-So how can you say it's false?
-No.
This isn't a problem
that says what's true is false.
There's an error in the premise.
Your proofs…
were always beautiful.
Clear and clean.
A proof with numerous errors…
doesn't fit you.
Sleep now.
And don't skip your meals.
I'll come again.
Mathematics is bold…
and harmless.
It doesn't have any purpose.
It's virtuous.
Like a kid running forever.
It really is.
You brought me something very useful.
You're crying?
Oh, my.
Why are you crying?
You're settling this. You've done it.
Do you think
Seung-yoo ever felt pained
for you at any moment?
They believe their love is pure and noble.
That doesn't exist.
And you're proving that to them.
That such a thing doesn't exist.
I guarantee that people will prefer
your proof over theirs.
INCOMING CALL
Hello?
The fourth board meeting
of Asung Foundation shall begin.
I would like to add another item
to the agenda.
It's a serious case of fraud
committed against the foundation.
It needs to be expedited, because
it may result in disciplinary action,
such as the termination of Principal Noh.
It's Paik Seung-yoo!
Paik Seung-yoo!
Are you here to press charges
against Asung High School?
Yes, I am.
You are still claiming
that you were framed to cover up
-a cheating scandal at the school?
-Yes.
You mean you had no relationship
with the math teacher, whatsoever?
You're claiming that you two
are completely innocent, right?
Then could you explain this?
I received a tip.
You don't care?
Because you're in love with her?
Yes. I'm in love with her.
-What did he say?
-Mr. Paik, could you clarify?
Are you in love with
your former math teacher, or not?
This isn't a problem
that says what's true is false.
There's an error in the premise.
How have you been?
I wanted to have them apologize to her.
Yoon-su.
But it didn't work out
because I fell in love with you.
When will you stop being afraid of me?
You don't scare me. I find you disgusting.
You were never a member
of high society nor do you fit in,
but you pretend you are one
and won't give up.
I don't regret anything
that happened after I first met you.
Why don't we go somewhere? Anywhere.
All right. Let's go anywhere.