[The Princess Royal]
[Adapted from Mo Shu Bai's novel,
The Princess Royal on jjwxc.net]
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Episode 24]
[Princess's Mansion]
That's all?
Yes. That's all for now
Recruiting talents?
Young Master.
[Recruiting talents]
I need to tell you something.
The Su Family is hellbent
on recruiting talents.
They even asked the Right Chancellor Su
to join them for a while.
Everyone flocks toward them.
But look at us...
Su Rongqing strongly opposed
the imperial examination before.
But he changed his mind all of a sudden.
He's clearly trying
to steal talents from me.
What did you say, Young Master?
Before?
That will cost a lot of money...
Hush now. Just go.
Go.
Okay.
Everyone. Everyone.
Well.
Her Highness and the Prince Consort said
that no matter whose article
was selected
would be awarded with one silver tael.
- One silver tael?
One silver tael.
This is better
than meeting the Right Chancellor.
Of course.
The Prince Consort
used to be a commoner,
so he knows what commoners
like us want better.
- That's right.
I wrote this today.
Is this the place for signing up?
Yes.
Everyone.
Queue up.
My friend.
They are so passionate.
Money sure is more persuasive
than meeting the Right Chancellor.
Of course.
Oh my.
The expenditure here
will be paid with your wage.
I'm leaving.
Please no. My wage will never
be enough for this.
This is Prose Poem
of Discussing the Idea
that the same nature varies on nurture.
Whether people harbor
good or evil intentions
is determined
by their dispositions and habits.
Habits change as things change.
It can be especially shown
in their actions.
Disposition is an innate quality.
Calmness and contentment predominate.
This is the main point of this essay.
What a well-written passage.
Your Highness,
do you know that it is written
by a candidate who's going to attend
this year's imperial examination?
Your Highness,
you'll be counting on them
in the future.
Consort Rou has arrived.
Your Highness, today's lesson
shall conclude hereafter.
Please finish your assignment.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Su.
Your Highness.
Cheng,
I wish to speak with Mr. Su in private.
You may leave now.
Sir, Mother,
I shall take my leave.
Pei Wenxuan
is offering the candidates money now.
It has had a big impact on us.
We should do something.
Calm down, Your Highness.
Just make sure your men
don't make any mistakes.
I will handle the rest.
You will be notified
immediately of any changes.
Thank you, Mr. Su.
I will do my best.
We are now waiting for great timing
before we can ask Prince Su
to recruit talents for us in person.
What brought you here, Mr. Su?
Mr. Shangguan, do you perhaps
have a candidate in mind
as the imperial examination's
chief examiner?
That's a decision
for the Ministry of Personnel.
It is a thankless job.
Ask Liu Hangchun to do it.
Liu Hangchun?
He's not trustworthy.
He often makes a lot of mistakes.
If someone reports him,
it'll be...
Who do you suggest, Mr. Su?
My son, Rongqing,
is very interested in this matter.
I wonder if it's possible
to let him...
Mr. Su, His Majesty
promotes the imperial examination
to contend
against the noble families like us.
The chief examiner cannot be one of us.
Therefore, we must find someone
who isn't from a noble family
but is willing to do our bidding.
Your Highness, how is it?
You asked me to give you the signatures
of those handsome scholars.
But Pei Wenxuan isn't willing
to cooperate.
Forget about it now.
Just give me Liu Hangchun's case file.
Your Highness,
you can't break your promise.
When did I promise you
that I'd bring the signatures back?
I did try for you.
Don't be insatiable.
But I told my friends
I would give them the signatures.
They were all so excited.
The case files you want are all there.
Any updates? Tell me.
[Liu Hangchun]
It's not just Liu Hangchun.
Su Rongqing
wants to do this job too.
Su Rongqing?
He used to look down on this.
Why the sudden change?
Right.
The noble families looked down
on the examination candidates.
But now, everyone wants them.
Based on what happened before,
this year's imperial examination
will be full of talented people.
Pei Wenxuan's disciples
will fill the imperial court
and he will become fully fledged.
So why is Su Rongqing meddling
in this suddenly?
Your Highness.
It seems like
I have to secure Pei Wenxuan's
position as soon as possible.
When will you carry out your plan?
Now.
[Qingmei Restaurant]
Mr. Liu, I'm here.
Come and catch me.
I'm over here.
I'm coming.
Mr. Liu.
I'm over here, Mr. Liu.
Beautiful ladies, stop playing this
and come to me now.
If I catch you,
I'll punish you.
I...
The Inspectorate Office
even cares about this?
Her Highness wants to see you.
Please come with me.
Greetings, Your Highness.
I did not know that you were here.
Please forgive me for the lack
of appropriate reception.
Mr. Liu, why are you so tense?
I'm here
to have tea with you.
No need to be so anxious. Please rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Take a seat.
You must be very busy lately, Mr. Liu.
It's all right.
I can tell.
I heard your spouse
recently gave birth to a son.
This is my gift to you.
Open it.
Please spare me, Your Highness.
Please don't give me a hard time.
Mr. Liu,
I'm not trying to give you a hard time.
I just need a favor from you.
I've heard you are in charge
of the mobilizations of officials below
the fifth rank
in the Ministry of Personnel.
I'd like to recommend someone,
Mr. Liu.
My consort is a talented man.
If no one plays a dirty trick,
he can easily excel in the role
of a secretary of examinations.
So don't be scared.
I just want you to pay attention to him.
I know someone
might have talked to you already,
but I hope you
can make a sound judgment.
Your Highness,
I do not have a final say in this.
The Prince Consort must
rely on his talent
to earn that position.
I will handle this
with fairness and impartiality,
so please rest assured, Your Highness.
I am relieved to hear that
from you, Mr. Liu.
As you as you're satisfied,
Your Highness.
If there's nothing else,
I shall take my leave.
Take care, Mr. Liu.
Your Highness.
In a few days, the list
of staff mobilizations
within the Ministry of Personnel
will be out.
Once Liu Hangchun
adds The Prince Consort's name to it,
it'll be too late for Wang Houwen
to do anything
even if he gets hold of this.
Indeed.
Once the Ministry of Personnel
produces the list,
Ministry of Justice will release
its list of staff mobilizations soon.
Pei Liming is doing the follow-up work
to Xie Lanqing's case.
So he should by right
be the Minister of Justice.
Young Master.
Any news from our informants?
Yes.
You asked them to keep an eye
on the Princess's Mansion.
They went to see Liu Hangchun.
It must be to get an in
with the Ministry of Personnel.
I need to know
whether it's Her Highness or Pei Wenxuan
went to that person.
It's Her Highness.
I see.
I was looking for an opportunity.
Now,
it presents itself.
Your Highness,
Second Young Master Su
sent a message saying
that he was setting up a trap.
Let me read it.
He asked you
to follow his plan.
He added that this operation
would test if you two can be allies.
Your Highness, just tell me the truth.
Are they handsome?
I didn't pay attention to them.
Why not? They are charming.
Your Highness, Miss Shangguan,
my young master asked me
to deliver this to you.
He did it!
Many handsome bachelors came
to Huajing for a forum.
I asked Su Ronghua
to get me their signatures.
Many noble ladies
are coveting their signatures.
It won't be a bad thing
to do them a favor.
Su Ronghua is Huajing's
most handsome man.
Su Ronghua is charming.
Su Ronghua is not only handsome
but also talented.
You may hang this portrait
of mine in your chamber.
It will brighten your day.
You want to do those ladies a favor?
Tell Su Ronghua
he's done for.
I shall relay this message verbatim.
Both of you want to see me today.
I am so honored.
May I know
what I can do for you.
Come on, Mr. Wang.
Thank you, Second Young Master Su.
Mr. Wang.
We came
to recommend someone
for the Ministry of Personnel.
Is that so?
You can just dispatch a messenger
to me.
No need to come to me personally.
But the Ministry of Personnel
can only offer the position
of the secretary of examinations now.
It's a sixth-ranked position.
I'm afraid you may
look down on it, Second Young Master Su.
Mr. Wang.
Isn't the Vice Minister
of Personnel pending too?
You're right, Mr. Su.
Many people are coveting
that position.
I wonder who you'd like to recommend.
Mr. Wang.
The list of nominees for the position
of the secretary of examinations
is here.
Please give written instructions
or comments.
[Pei Wenxuan, Cui Shuhe,
Shangguan Yu, Shuangguan Minzhi...]
[Pei Wenxuan]
Your Highness, to tell you the truth,
I saw with my own eyes that Mr. Wang
circled the Prince Consort's name.
Good.
When he's been officially appointed,
you will be rewarded again.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You may leave now.
I'll take my leave, Your Highness.
Your Highness, you seem happier
handling the Prince Consort's affairs
than your own affairs.
Of course.
I'm used to handling my affairs.
It's my first time doing so much
for someone else.
You're odd, Your Highness.
Men often
feel happy
when they help women.
When the Prince Consort spoils you,
you don't feel too thrilled.
Yet you are elated
when helping the Prince Consort.
Listen up.
Being spoiled is nothing to be proud of,
but spoiling others shows
that you are a capable one.
Someone can like you,
but you will lose your good looks
as age.
However, it's different
when you pamper someone.
You can spoil him when you want,
and leave when you no longer like him.
You can feel free
to do whatever you want.
How enlightening, Your Highness.
Don't believe what Her Highness says.
She's just being stubborn.
How am I stubborn?
Your Highness,
one doesn't need a specific reason
to feel happy
after helping someone else.
Maybe it's just because you like him.
This isn't something embarrassing.
That's right.
It isn't something embarrassing.
Don't tell me
you didn't sleep last night.
Yes. I'm so nervous.
You don't actually believe
that I could get things done for you,
do you?
Of course, I do.
But this is my first promotion
and you helped me with it personally.
So of course, I am nervous.
All right.
Enter the hall!
See you later.
- Boundless fortune to Your Majesty.
- Long Live Your Majesty.
Please rise, everyone.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Minister Wang,
tell me about the staff mobilizations
by the Ministry of Personnel.
Your Majesty.
The new Minister of Justice
will be Su Rongqing.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
He actually
took my second uncle's place?
Just how many dirty tricks did he play
to get that position?
The new
Vice Minister of Personnel
will be Pei Wenxuan.
Him?
Oh my!
It's supposed to be a sixth-ranked
position, secretary of examinations.
How come it's a fourth-ranked position?
- Mr. Pei.
- Your Majesty!
Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei has fainted.
Pei Wenxuan?
What is happening?
Your Majesty, my consort has fainted.
May I take him
to rest?
Bring him to the side hall.
Summon an imperial physician
to check on him.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Hurry.
How's he?
Your Highness,
the Prince Consort suffers
from exhaustion
and his injuries are yet to heal fully.
He has fainted
because his mind is overwhelmed
and gets impaired.
He will need a few days to recuperate.
Anything else to note?
Are there any herbs he needs to avoid?
There's only one thing.
He shall not restrain himself
from conjugal consummation...
That's enough.
I understand.
Anything else?
Sleep more. Eat more.
He should go out for a stroll more
when he's free.
Relaxing his mind can be beneficial too.
Okay. Thank you.
- I'll take my leave.
Your Highness.
Right. Ask them to investigate
what happened
to the staff mobilizations.
Yes, Your Highness.
He fainted at the court.
Isn't it great
to be the Vice Minister of Personnel?
Did he faint from anger or happiness?
Anger, of course.
Pei Wenxuan is a cunning man
who cannot be underestimated.
It isn't a good news to him.
He received such a huge promotion.
Why was he angry?
Other ministers will not agree
with him
to be the Vice Minister of Personnel.
Not only will he not get that position,
but His Majesty
will begin to doubt him too.
Additionally,
His Majesty will grow wary
when the Inspectorate Office
grows too powerful.
When he puts his guard up,
so ends Pingyue's influence
in the imperial court.
I must say,
Mr. Su's plan is ingenious.
Mr. Su is so amazing.
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Do you want water?
No need.
Your Highness.
Did you catch the rest
of the staff mobilizations?
I'll get the list
from the Ministry of Personnel later.
Your Highness, I know you're
acting in my best interest,
but promoting me
to the Vice Minister of...
I asked for the position
of secretary of examinations.
I didn't ask for the position
of vice minister.
Then...
Pei Wenxuan sure rose quickly
through the ranks.
He's lucky.
Did you see His Majesty's
face just now?
I did.
His Majesty is getting mad
because Princess Pingyue
is meddling in everything.
I'm afraid that the Prince Consort can't
get the position of vice minister.
What brought you here, Mr. Su?
Mr. Shangguan, do you perhaps
have a candidate in mind
as the imperial examination's
chief examiner?
Who do you recommend?
Pei Wenxuan.
Second Young Master.
You jest.
He's our enemy, isn't he?
Think about it, Mr. Wang.
With His Majesty's temperament,
Pei Wenxuan
will never get this position.
Because
he wouldn't dare to take it.
Mr. Su,
I know you are capable,
but you represent the interests
of those noble families.
Your Highness.
What if I tell you I can
give you the Inspectorate Office?
I heard
that you used to fancy Princess Pingyue.
That is the past.
You just have to tell me
if you trust me or not.
What do you want me to do?
Go to Wang Houwen
and ask him to appoint Pei Wenxuan
as the Vice Minister of Personnel.
Rongqing.
No matter what they say about you,
in my eyes, you're the best
and the most excellent one.
I trust you to take
good care of our family.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Congratulations, Mr. Pei.
Mr. Pei, I shall see you
in the Ministry of Personnel.
You flattered me.
It's just a list.
And I am too inexperienced
to take the position.
Don't be modest, Mr. Pei.
I have faith in you.
Your Highness.
What's the matter?
I feel dizzy.
Let's go home. I'll feel better then.
Mr. Pei.
Congratulations on your promotion.
Thanks.
Come on. Slowly.
That was a lousy act.
I know.
You're heavy.
Pei Wenxuan.
This is just the first gift
I'll be giving to you.
Your Highness.
Mr. Liu, why are you kneeling here?
Did you do something wrong?
You may rise.
Just speak then.
Your Highness,
last night, someone gave me the list
of staff mobilizations
of fifth-ranked officials and above.
He asked me
to remove Mr. Pei's name
from the position
of secretary of examinations.
I didn't want to defy your order.
But that person said
it'd be beneficial
for the Prince Consort.
I thought
being the Vice Minister of Personnel
was better than being
a secretary of examinations.
Moreover, the list of the mobilizations
concerning fifth-ranked positions
and above would be submitted
to His Majesty in advance.
If His Majesty first saw
that the Prince Consort
was one of the candidates
|for the Vice Minister of Personnel,
then he saw the list I wrote,
he might think
that I failed in my duties.
Therefore, I...
Therefore, you removed his name
from the position
of secretary of examinations.
Isn't it great that my consort
is now the Vice Minister of Personnel?
Why are you so scared?
Who came to you?
What did they tell you?
It was Mr. Wang Houwen.
He told me
Consort Rou wanted someone else
to be the secretary of examinations,
and he wanted me to arrange for it.
I didn't dare to do that for him,
so I told him
that someone already took that position.
He asked me who it was
and I told him
it was the Prince Consort.
He then told me that the Prince Consort
had been appointed
as the Vice Minister of Personnel.
I thought it was odd.
But if he was already appointed
as the Vice Minister of Personnel,
I supposed there was no point in making
him the secretary of examinations.
But unexpectedly,
the Prince Consort fainted
at the court today.
Everyone thought it's said
that he was simply overwhelmed
by happiness,
I knew
that I must have done something wrong.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
Stand up.
I now know what happened.
You may leave, Mr. Liu.
I'll take my leave.
In our next lesson,
I hope you can explain to me
how to enhance one's self-cultivation
and be a self-disciplined ruler.
Yes, sir.
Greetings, Mr. Su.
Your Highness.
May I
speak frankly, Your Highness?
Please do.
I believe His Highness should volunteer
to be the secretary of examinations.
As his mother,
you are from a humble family
which is perfectly justifiable.
The imperial examination
only recruits commoners.
Why would I need individuals
without any foundations?
Mind your manner, Cheng.
Some of them are very knowledgeable.
You can pick and train them.
In time,
they will be one of the noble families
who will work for you.
You're brilliant, Your Highness.
It's all your foresight, Mr. Su.
Cheng, thank your tutor
for his guidance.
Thank you, sir.
Answer me.
Is Pei Wenxuan very experienced now?
How dare you
appoint him
as the Vice Minister of Personnel?
I rarely meddle in affairs
in the Ministry of Personnel
because I have faith in your judgment.
But what are you doing here?
How can you give
such an important position
to Pei Wenxuan?
Your Majesty.
Mr. Pei might be young,
but he is the Prince Consort.
Her Highness...
So what if she's a princess?
Can a princess be above the laws,
the state principles, or even me?
Tell me.
Who helped Pei Wenxuan
get the position
of the Vice Minister of Personnel?
Tell me honestly.
Your Majesty,
Princess Pingyue seeks an audience.
Reject her request.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Wait.
Summon her in.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Leave now.
Reflect upon yourself at home.
I'll have others investigate
the truth later.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Mr. Wang,
you're a third-ranked minister,
who's served in the court
for a long time.
No need to extend such formality to me.
A minister is just nothing.
The former Minister of Justice,
Xie Lanqing,
also the master of the Xie Family,
was even taken down by you.
If I may advise you, Your Highness,
your honor
is contingent upon the Shangguan Family.
After all,
the noble families are your allies.
Don't pick
the wrong side.
I'll take my leave, Your Highness.
Your Highness, please.
Your Majesty, Princess Pingyue is here.
Greetings, Father.
Rise.
Pei Wenxuan has been
officially appointed.
What other complaints do you have?
Father, please choose another one
to take the position
of the Vice Minister of Personnel.
Why? Isn't it a great thing
that Pei Wenxuan
is a vice minister now?
Why reject the offer?
Father, I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
Speak.
In fact, I helped
Pei Wenxuan in secret
to secure his promotion.
How else could he become
a vice minister then?
But I wasn't going
after the position of vice minister.
I wanted him to become
a secretary of examinations.
You're saying
someone's framing you
by making Pei Wenxuan
the Vice Minister of Personnel?
Yes.
Why would they do that?
Isn't it obvious?
They want to drive a wedge between us.
How is appointing Pei Wenxuan
as the Vice Minister of Personnel
an act to create a divide between us?
Father, you asked me to establish
the Inspectorate Office.
I solved many cases
and gained more power.
If I used my power for my own good,
then for both our country and people,
you would want to eradicate me.
It seems like the mastermind
of this scheme
harbors no good intention.
Father,
while I did make a mistake,
I couldn't bear it anymore.
I have had enough of the mockery.
Who mocked you?
After I was betrothed,
I was mocked by my younger sisters
in the palace.
Huayue said
that it's because Pei Wenxuan held
a lowly background and was powerless
and because you didn't like me
so you made me marry him.
Nonsense!
Why would Huayue say such words?
Father.
Do you mean to say
that Huayue wouldn't say that,
or that Huayue
shouldn't have said it out loud?
Father,
why do you think I'm so scared
and come to see you in a hurry
to revoke the decision
to remove Pei Wenxuan
from his position?
Do you think
it's only because he is too young?
In terms of age,
Su Rongqing is also young.
How come he could
be the Vice Minister of Justice,
and now, even get promoted
to the Minister of Justice?
Yet my consort
can't even be a vice minister.
However, I still have to come today.
I'm afraid If I did not,
Father might believe
that I would continue
helping Pei Wenxuan in secret.
I was so scared.
I fear that you and I will drift apart.
What makes you think I'll do that?
Because I know...
I'm not Huayue.
I am the daughter
of the Shangguan Family.
You are my daughter.
But Huayue said
that you grew wary
of the Shangguan Family,
so you made me marry a commoner.
She's gone too far!
Pei Wenxuan was ranked first
in the Royal Selection.
He is handsome and kind.
I'm sure you know how excellent he is.
I do.
So please, Father,
do not doubt me.
I'm not that capable.
I did everything
to seek justice.
I just hope my consort won't be denied
the opportunity to work
as a sixth-ranked official
because of me.
Father.
Please grant my request.
I need to think about it.
You may leave now.
Yes, Father.
Your Majesty.
All of them are playing tricks
to fool me.
And they are doing
a remarkable job at it.
Pingyue was right.
When Pei Wenxuan was announced
to be the Vice Minister of Personnel,
I questioned their fidelity.
Your Majesty.
I believe
something more sinister must be at play
behind Mr. Pei's new promotion.
Send someone
to investigate the truth for me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness, a letter
from the Northwest.
Is it from Zhenzhen?
Your Highness, it's been a while.
The distance between us is vast.
I wonder when you'll receive
this letter.
Perhaps you'll receive it
in March when swan geese
is flying back to the north?
The soldiers in the Northwest
believe that the returning swan geese
carry with them the yearning
of their families.
When I see them,
they remind me of you
and my family in Huajing.
Thus, I named the sword you gave me
Hongyu.
I was like a swan goose's feather,
carried by the wayward breeze.
Fortunately, I met you and Her Highness.
I was given the chance to take
destiny into my own hands
and pursue my ambition.
I hope this feather can convey
my blessings and longings to you.
May this feather remind you
of my presence
and this letter brighten your day.
Zhenzhen, I am sure
we will meet again one day.
Hongyu.
Hush.
If I'm getting married,
I definitely won't marry someone
like Pei Wenxuan.
He's good for nothing
except for his pretty face.
He's from a humble background
and married Pingyue.
Yet he couldn't even secure the position
as the secretary of examinations.
Pingyue has been arrogant all her life.
To have a husband like him...
Father.
Your Majesty,
why did no one
inform us of your arrival?
Is this how you raised your daughter?
She's a princess yet she's talking
behind others' backs.
It's all my fault
for not disciplining her well.
Huayue, apologize to your father now.
Apologize?
Is she the one who should apologize?
Get out!
I'll take my leave, Father.
Everyone else should leave too.
Your Majesty,
Huayue is young and naive.
She must have picked up
bad habits in the palace.
I was about to lecture her.
Was it your idea to let Pei Wenxuan
be the Vice Minister of Personnel?
What do you mean, Your Majesty?
I mostly keep to myself in the harem.
I can't possibly decide
on such an important matter.
Perhaps the rumors mislead you
into misunderstanding me, Your Majesty.
Rumors?
I know very well
what you're capable of.
Otherwise,
how could a lowly person
like you
can be who you are today.
I know it's because
I'm lucky enough to earn your favor,
Your Majesty.
I truly have nothing to do with it.
There must be a gossipmonger.
Perhaps I can confront him?
Quit pretending!
You can plot schemes.
You can also pull dirty tricks
in this harem.
But don't try to deceive
or take advantage of me.
I can put you in this position
and I can take it away
from you just as easily.
I do not like others deceiving me.
For today's matter,
I can
let it go.
But Xiao Rou,
remember what you said to me.
You said
you'd be my blade.
Don't forget who you are.
If one day,
I realize that the blade
is pointing at me,
I...
will melt it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Highness.
Pei,
my family did send me
an odorless, colorless and chronic drug,
didn't they?
Yes, Your Highness.
You mean to...
Young Master.
Your Highness.
Young... Your Highness!
Young Master.
What's the matter?
Something bad happened.
What is it?
Daoist Hongde was summoned
to the palace at night.
And then?
Then...
What's the matter?
Your Highness,
Daoist Hongde was summoned
to the palace at night
by Consort Rou, or so I heard.
In the palace, he put out
an accusation against you.
He said
that it came from our mansion
that the Crown Prince's marriage
must be postponed till five years later.
What?
His Majesty was infuriated
and he wanted to summon you right away.
But the messenger,
who was going to come out
of the palace to convey the edict,
was somehow brought back in.
Brought back in?
Anything else?
Nothing.
Oh, wait.
I heard His Majesty wasn't going
to look into this affair.
Leave the city
and head to Qingshui County.
Find a laundrywoman called Tian Fang
and give her 300 silver taels.
Tell her that her husband has been found
so that she can bring her mother-in-law
to Huajing to reunite with him.
That much money?
Just go.
Okay.
You're trying to take advantage
of Hongde's scandal?
Yes.
And it must be something
that comes with solid evidence.
Did you talk to Hongde
after you came back?
No.
Neither of us has talked to him.
So he was bought to falsely accuse us.
But with Consort Rou's capability,
she isn't smart enough
to devise this plan.
Who gazes at the sky from afar?
In the night's chill breeze
What is she singing for?
The wind caresses the hills
The wind causes ripples on calm water
Moonlight graces passing souls
Her steps get slower and slower
She's trod a lengthy path
Memories lost then found
Gazing idly as clouds roll by
She holds a red candle
To brave the thick fog
Life can be bitter sometimes
Experience it with grace
Like a fleeting dream
Neither warmth nor cold will last
The moon is reflected in her eyes
In her gaze,
the unwavering faith remains