[The Princess Royal]
[Adapted from Mo Shu Bai's novel,
The Princess Royal on jjwxc.net]
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Episode 21]
Your Highness.
Stop writing.
Your Highness,
if you want to get divorced,
just do so as soon as possible.
If you want the Prince Consort to stay,
then go back early.
Why are you still here?
You're just too young.
Why do you care?
Your Highness, you're still
very young yourself.
In fact, I'm a few years older than you.
Just listen to me.
Go back.
Your Highness,
you've always been so decisive.
Why are you being evasive now?
You can't stay
at the Inspectorate Office forever
and go through these documents
until you die.
You still have to go back and meet him
sooner or later.
Do you think
that I am now indecisive
and unlikable?
If I go back now,
this is the kind of person
Pei Wenxuan will meet.
So what?
Anyway, Pei Wenxuan adores you.
And you also care about him.
Who said so?
Your Highness, before this,
have you ever fed anyone soup?
Have you ever attended to anyone?
Have you ever tried
to care about anyone else's feelings?
Have you ever cared
that someone might like you
or otherwise?
Do you really not care about him?
Back when the assassins
tried to kill you,
you told me to do nothing about it.
But when they tried to kill Pei Wenxuan,
you actually finished them off.
And now, even though it's too risky
to kill Xie Lanqing,
but in order to warn them
and avenge the Prince Consort...
How dare you.
Your Highness, if you keep up like this,
you're pushing everyone who loves you
and whom you love away.
Have you really thought
about how you want to lead your life?
I have thought clearly.
I don't need anyone to care about me.
I have wealth and power.
I can keep anyone I like by my side
and ensure that the people I care
can live a good life.
That's what I want.
Also...
how I will live my life
is not up to you to tell me.
I understand.
You think that everything
needs a result.
Pei Wenxuan is trying
to force me to give him an answer,
and now you're doing the same thing.
Yes, he's right.
I don't want to make any effort
while hoping that he could stay.
This is what selfishness is.
No matter how nice I treat him,
if I can't give him what he wants,
I'll need to make everything clear
and keep nothing for myself.
What happened today is my fault.
I have been evading
his feelings all this time.
That's why I always assume the worst.
Had I been more mindful,
I wouldn't have hurt him,
so I should be apologizing
and explaining everything to him.
I shouldn't presume
that what I do is best for him,
and assume
that by doing so, I can make up
for what he has done for me.
I should give him whatever he wants,
and if I can't,
I should tell him clearly.
Your Highness, why have you
never thought
about being with him for real?
Your Highness, we're here.
Why have you never thought
about being with Pei Wenxuan for real?
Rong, remember
that in the face of power,
all love and affection
are as transient as a fleeting cloud.
It will be gone very fast.
I am a bit worried about her.
Who is she to you?
My childhood friend.
Your Highness?
Got it.
Your Highness, you're back.
You haven't gone to sleep yet?
I have a slight wound.
I'll need to get up at night
and change my redressing.
I'm afraid I may disturb you,
so I'm planning
to sleep at the study
starting from tonight.
I hope you'll approve my request.
It's getting late and cold.
Your Highness, you should get some rest.
I'm sorry.
In the past,
I didn't make myself clear to you.
I was being evasive.
It's my fault.
I let you down today.
It's my fault as well.
Your Highness, don't take it to heart.
Everything is my own decision.
Whether you accept it or not,
that's up to you,
and there's no right or wrong.
Today...
I must have offended you.
I hope you'll forgive me, Your Highness.
Have you really thought
about how you want to live your life?
Your Highness, you want a good life.
You don't want to live the way you did.
You want the Crown Prince to be happy.
You want a complete family.
You want to find someone
with whom you love each other.
You want to be surrounded by children.
You want someone who you can rely on
and keep you company as you age.
Right?
Pei Wenxuan.
Can you...
Can you wait for me a little longer?
I know
I'm not very likable.
Especially when it comes
to romantic relationships,
you could find me abhorrent.
I am unable to trust you
and even myself.
But that doesn't mean
I can't feel your kindness towards me.
I didn't mean to hold off
on giving you an answer.
I know how to show love well.
But I can do none of them.
I just can't...
let my guard down completely
and hand over my heart to someone else.
That's why I need
to constantly confirm
that you won't leave.
Still, despite my flaws,
can you just...
even if it's just a dream,
fate has brought us together
after so many tribulations...
so can you wait for me?
Please don't go.
Forget it.
You must find this ridiculous.
Don't take what I said seriously.
Just...
Just follow your heart.
You can leave if you want to.
Rong.
It's fine.
Rong, 10 years.
Or 20 years. Is that enough?
If it's not...
♪If the past was caught
in the turbulent waves of the storm♪
I can add another 20 years.
♪Will there be arms to hold me
in this lifetime?♪
♪Memories flash back♪
I'm incredibly patient.
♪I am that solitary boat♪
I can wait for a long time.
♪Tossed about in the waves,
unable to escape♪
You can take your time.
I won't get tired.
I won't leave either.
♪Guides me through the worldly remnants
of old dreams♪
Because...
♪Wrapped in the wind's embrace♪
I've liked you
for a long time.
♪Hidden in my sleeves♪
♪No need to imprison myself
in longing♪
I will wait for you.
Just move forward.
What do you see in me?
I have a foul temper,
and I'm always bullying you.
♪In this long and arduous journey♪
♪I'm fortunate to have met you♪
Personally,
I'm into someone with a foul temper.
I like to be bullied.
That's why to me,
you're better than
anyone else in the world.
♪I'll stay by your side
till the end of time♪
This is so embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
How is this embarrassing?
I love seeing you feeling embarrassed.
That makes me happy.
♪We will journey through life together
until the very end♪
What happened today is your fault.
Do you know how much those flowers
blown up by you cost?
♪For with you, each moment is timeless♪
No matter how much they cost,
you're using my money.
I haven't even blamed you
for spending money recklessly,
yet you're telling me
how expensive they are?
Alright, let's put an end to this tiff.
Bundle up.
You wouldn't want to catch a cold.
Come on.
Come on, let's walk you back
to your room.
Mr. Su, whatever you have in mind,
you can just tell me.
Your Highness.
Do you want
to make Prince Su the Crown Prince?
Our dynasty has always made
the first son of the Empress
the Crown Prince.
I wouldn't dare think of it.
Your Highness.
I think that
since you're allying
yourself with my family,
you should be honest with me.
You may assume
that no one knows your motive,
but perhaps the whole world
knows about it.
If we have your genuine support,
then on behalf of Prince Su,
I name you the future minister
who has the highest status
among all the ministers.
Very well.
Now, there is something
that requires your help.
Your Highness, you may go to bed now.
Are you not going to go to bed?
Didn't you just approve my request
to sleep in the study?
Why are you still standing here then?
No, I mean...
you should sleep early
since you'll need to attend
the morning court tomorrow.
Your wish is my command, Your Highness.
I'll take my leave.
What does he mean?
I thought we talked it through.
Why does he still want
to sleep in the study?
Men are weird creatures.
Your Highness.
There's something I forgot.
What?
♪We watch the moon and sun♪
♪We share the fate♪
Good night.
♪We climb the high tower♪
♪Then we light up a lantern somewhere♪
That scoundrel.
When did he learn such tricks?
♪History may repeat♪
♪I know you will be with me♪
Young Master.
I got you another quilt.
Cover your legs
if you feel cold at night.
So, I have something
that I don't know if I should say.
Then don't.
What's wrong with you?
If I don't say it,
it's going to stifle me to death.
Stop being angry
at the Princess, will you?
Must you move to the study?
What if you infuriate her instead?
You should move back after tonight.
You know nothing.
This is called, playing hard to get.
It's a strategy.
Strategy?
You don't have much experience
with strategies, do you?
If your strategy fails,
you're going to regret it.
Just one night.
Enough.
Don't stick your nose in
if you know nothing.
Go and get this room ready.
There's nothing in this room.
Get this room ready?
Are you sure?
Of course.
Fine.
I'll carefully get it ready
for you to stay here permanently.
Let's see how many days
you'll stay here.
This is infuriating.
Tong.
Jinglan.
How's the Prince Consort's wound?
Two imperial physicians have come
to check on him.
They said he was fine,
and just needed some rest.
That's a relief.
But, I heard
that the Prince Consort is sleeping
in the study tonight?
Yes.
Couples should have
no overnight feud, right?
Yes, I agree.
I don't understand
why they are like this.
Right, I just remembered
that Her Highness put it this way.
She said it's called
"spicing things up".
How can a separation spice things up?
[Ministry of Justice]
Sir, we found him.
He's locked up
in the Inspectorate Office.
Didn't you say
that he hid poison between his teeth?
Why is he still alive?
Don't worry, sir.
His life is in our hands.
Even if he's alive, he'll never babble.
What is it?
Sir, it's Mr. Su.
Greetings, Sir.
Let's talk inside here.
What is it?
Are you worried
about Princess Pingyue's
attempted assassination?
This is a serious matter.
Do you have any plans?
I didn't expect
that these assassins would be so brazen.
As of now, I have no solution.
Sir.
Why don't we turn this disadvantage
into an advantage?
Release Lin Feibai tonight.
Why should we release him?
Release him secretly.
I have an agreement with him.
An agreement?
What agreement?
You'll know when it's time.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness,
the Xie Family's butler visited
Mingyue Palace last night.
I'm afraid they might team up.
Okay, I got it.
Your Highness, I'm still worried
that if we push them too hard,
most of the noble families might
shift their allegiance to Prince Su.
Ya.
Do you know why my father
dotes on Consort Rou?
He dotes on her so much
to leverage over my mother, actually.
No matter what mistake Consort Rou
or Prince Su makes,
my father would never abandon them.
And when he does,
there would be only one reason.
They're no longer useful as his pawns.
Your Highness, I understand now.
I'm going to release that bait now.
Get some rest.
When you release him,
return all his belongings
to him,
especially the jade pendant.
Yes, Your Highness.
Sir, we've received some news.
Go ahead.
The Xie Family sent someone
to Mingyue Palace
to deliver a white jade hairpin.
A white jade hairpin?
Does it have any significance?
It's the trendiest accessory
in Huajing lately.
A white jade hairpin?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I heard you have something
interesting to tell me.
That's right.
Lately, everyone in the city is enamored
with white jade hairpins.
They're practically sold out now.
White jade hairpins are nothing new.
Why the sudden craze?
It was made popular by a top courtesan
in Yizhou, who wore it on her hair.
Preposterous.
You may not know
that its price
is even more preposterous.
How much does one cost?
I'm afraid my yearly salary
can't even afford it.
Lately, there's been a plague
in the southwest,
and people are dying on the streets.
Yet, the people in the capital
would rather spend their money
on something superficial.
We need to intervene.
Who's selling the hairpins?
Well...
What is it?
As an imperial censor,
you should dare say everything.
It's the Xie Family.
I want the Censorate
to discuss this issue tomorrow
in the morning court.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Mingyue Palace]
Father, I don't understand
what I have done wrong.
Someone!
Lock this ignorant girl up!
Only release her when she realizes
the error of her ways!
Father, the hairpin is a gift...
Huayue!
Please forgive her, Your Majesty.
I have spoiled her.
Reflect on your wrongdoings, go!
Your Majesty, Huayue is still young.
It's my fault...
Do you take me as a fool?
Do you think this hairpin
is really for Huayue?
Remember.
If you behave like those people,
I will never
visit your palace again!
Your Majesty, I won't socialize
with the noble families again.
You'd better not.
Young Master, Her Highness
had some rest in the morning
in the study,
then had her meal,
and later returned to her room.
Who did this?
It wasn't me.
Her Highness was here alone
in the morning today.
This shows
that Her Highness
is still emotionally unstable.
Did she invite me to eat with her?
No. You wish.
Eat with her?
Young Master, listen to me.
Stop playing coy.
Go and talk to her now.
You need to ease your relationship...
No need.
It's all part of my strategy.
More strategies?
My current strategy
is to get a good night's sleep.
Come on, help me cover the quilt.
You can just be like this.
The coldness will wake you up.
Pei Wenxuan is getting
more and more impudent.
He didn't even come to say good night.
What is he up to now?
Forget it.
The security here is actually so lax.
I should find an opportunity
to remind him.
I thought it was a cat
scratching the windows,
so I got up to check.
I didn't expect to see
such a huge cat.
You are wrong.
It's a little wildcat
that is nothing but ferocious.
You'd better be careful, Mr. Pei.
Your Highness,
if you want me to go back,
you could have just said so.
Aren't you afraid of catching a cold,
coming here late at night?
I couldn't pay you for those buttercups.
So you're still angry at me, aren't you?
I'm not angry.
But you're ignoring me.
I'm not ignoring you.
You are.
You'd rather sleep in a separate room.
That's because you told me
to wait for you.
So, I thought
I should give you some privacy.
I was also thinking
that I should let you decide
how our relationship should be like.
I'm fine with sleeping in the study.
It's just quite cold here.
Stop deliberately
saying something like this.
I finally understand
that you're just playing
hard to get.
You're putting on an act, aren't you?
Just to set me up.
How am I playing hard to get?
Everything I say is true
and comes from my heart.
They're all from your heart?
Fine.
No, I'm wrong.
From your heart?
They're all fake.
I'm so happy
that you would come here to see me.
I'm sleeping here
so that you would care about me.
If you want me to go back,
just tell me,
and I'll go back for your reputation.
For my reputation?
Come back with me then.
Alright.
Quickly.
They look like Young Master
and Her Highness.
I must be getting really sleepy.
It's so comfortable to sleep here.
I need to ask you something.
Huayue got slapped
by my father yesterday.
Was it your doing?
I only told him
about the skyrocketing price
of the white jade hairpin.
The Xie Family owns
a white jade mine in Kunzhou.
They have jade shops all over the place,
most famous for their
white jade hairpins.
However, it's not easy to get one.
Not only are they expensive,
but it depends
on the buyer's status too.
Given Consort Rou's family background,
even if Huayue
can afford to buy one,
the Xie Family might not
sell one to her.
That's why
my father's slap wasn't
just meant for Huayue,
but also Consort Rou.
More importantly,
my father is getting
suspicious of Consort Rou,
that she might be colluding
with the noble families.
Your eyes are filled
with your admiration of me.
That's not admiration.
I'm just thinking
that you're as witty as a devil,
and that's very unsettling.
You're unsettled by that?
Mr. Pei, what other secrets do you have
that I don't know?
Pray tell.
I've got lots of secrets
that you don't know.
Madam Shangguan.
You may leave now.
They will change shifts with you.
But, Mr. Su ordered us
to stand guard here.
What is he saying?
It's just a regular change of shift.
Don't you want to rest?
Thank you for your concern.
Let's go.
Your Highness, it's time to get up.
I may leave for now.
What's going on?
I was still careless.
I forgot to tell her not
to wake me up today.
Your Highness!
Your Highness, bad news!
Your Highness, please forgive me!
I don't want to come in,
but my young master is missing!
He may have run away!
We need to go and find him now!
What's all that yelling for?
I'm right here.
Who's that?
Why is there a man talking here?
It's your young master, Pei Wenxuan.
Sorry for disturbing you!
Oh my.
I took the blame for you this time.
You should give me credit for that.
Sure, I will.
Alright, let's get some more sleep.
You can still sleep?
I'm so sleepy.
Let's sleep a while more.
- Your Highness.
- Mr. Pei.
The Prince Consort is taking over
the military provisions and funds case
as His Majesty has commanded.
Cooperate with the Prince Consort
like how you usually cooperate with me.
- Yes, Your Highness.
- Yes, Mr. Pei.
By the way,
while you were investigating,
didn't Su Ronghua try to stop you?
The Su Family wouldn't
do something recklessly,
including Su Ronghua himself.
Actually, I don't understand
why you're so confident
in the Su Family.
Do you know...
when I first met
Su Rongqing?
Look, Father.
I've got a bamboo-copter. It can fly!
I want to have wings when I grow up
so I can fly to the most
beautiful places in the Great Xia!
Your Majesty, Mr. Su is here.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Your Majesty, I implore you
to rescind your command
and not to start a war in the north.
I, Su Rongqing, hope that you would
rescind your command too, Your Majesty.
Let the war end
so that the people can rehabilitate.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Fulai.
Bring the children out to play.
I need to talk to Minister Su.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Go.
Why do you come to visit my father?
Because he wants
to conquer the northern lands,
and I have to stop him.
But, Father said
that the war
is to beat the bad people up.
Why do you want to stop him?
We have already reclaimed
our lost territorial lands,
and if the war continues,
we'll be invading other nations.
If we win,
the credit goes to the Emperor.
However, the Emperor's achievements
will be achieved by the lives
of the common people.
The South has been experiencing
three years of drought.
The people are suffering.
Rather than starting a war
to conquer foreign enemies in the north,
I hope we can implement policies
that benefit the people,
ensuring that the common people
won't suffer from hunger.
Aren't you afraid
that my father might flog you
or even kill you if you provoke him?
What's so scary about death?
The Su Family
has always lived
and fought for the country.
Actually...
But...
it's not them who are bad,
but the will of others.
A big family like theirs
is bound to have someone
who harbors an evil intention.
Still, I will hold them in respect.
They've got their bottom line,
and it will be fine if I don't cross it.
Tong.
Jinglan, you scared me.
I don't understand.
When Her Highness and the Prince Consort
just got married,
they were such a sweet couple.
Then, they started sleeping
in separate rooms.
But now...
I don't understand what's going on.
This is probably their strategy.
The harder it is for them to meet,
the more they long for each other.
So, should we just pretend
that we don't know anything?
Of course, we have to.
Your Majesty, Princess Pingyue
hired an assassin to kill me!
Please seek justice for me!
Do you have any evidence?
Fortunately,
I was blessed by your grace
to capture the assassin.
I have solid evidence!
Summon Pingyue here now!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Is everything going well
with the Prince Consort?
Yes.
Send some pastries over to him.
Sure.
Tell him not to get too tired.
You may go now.
Your Highness, bad news!
What is it?
Lin Feibai failed and was captured.
What a pity.
Your Highness,
you need to come up with a plan now.
Xie Lanqing will definitely
make an issue of it.
Prepare the evidence that shows
how they tried to kill me.
Your Highness, I don't understand.
Why did you order Lin Feibai
to assassinate Xie Lanqing?
He's the Minister of Justice.
It's hard to get him killed.
Now that Lin Feibai is caught alive,
if he gave you away,
and given the fact that you're
already in so much trouble,
even His Majesty
might not be able to save you.
You're planning to threaten him
with your knowledge of his stronghold?
But Lin Feibai is no fool.
Would he actually
be threatened by that?
He's the one who sees me as a fool,
scheming with Xie Lanqing
to throw me off.
There are many possibilities
for this assassination.
Given how cunning Xie Lanqing is,
he'd prepare a backup plan.
Since you know that,
why did you get him to kill Xie Lanqing?
I only have two choices.
If I believe him,
I'll fall into their trap.
But if I don't,
I'll never be able to trap Xie Lanqing.
By ordering Lin Feibai
to kill Xie Lanqing, I've actually
offered Xie Lanqing an opportunity
to accuse me of that in court.
And by doing so,
he'll have to come out from the dark.
That gives me the chance
to sink my fangs into him.
So, your fangs are...
Really?
Absolutely.
[Hanqiu Palace]
Greetings, Father.
Skip the formalities.
Minister Xie said
you sent this assassin to kill him.
Do you plead guilty?
Father,
I'd like to ask him a few questions.
Permission granted.
You said
I ordered you to kill Mr. Xie.
So, please tell me
how I found you
and how I ordered you to do so.
I am an assassin for hire.
Half a month ago,
Her Highness came to me with a painting
and hired me to kill
a high-ranked official.
Although Her Highness
was wearing a veil
and I couldn't see her face,
I could remember her voice.
You've got sharp ears.
What happened next?
Then, I followed my employer's request
and went to Butterfly Gorge
to kill the man in the painting.
Then, I was ambushed
and thrown into prison
in the Inspectorate Office.
It was there
that I saw the Princess.
After hearing her voice, I knew
that she was the one
who hired me to kill Mr. Xie.
I immediately realized
that the Princess
staged this whole show.
The Princess knew
I was a capable killer,
so she asked me to kill Mr. Xie.
Otherwise,
she'd accuse me of assassinating her,
then have my head chopped off.
Nice story.
Looks like he's prepared.
Is he speaking the truth?
Father, I'd like you
and the other officials here
to observe this man and Mr. Xie.
Don't they look rather similar?
After taking a closer look...
They do look quite similar.
What do you mean?
Father.
Here's the truth.
Half a month ago,
I received a threatening kite
with the word "stop" written in red.
That same evening,
someone tried to assassinate
the Prince Consort.
Your Majesty,
Her Highness ordered me
to investigate this item.
[Stop]
We found out that the red ink used
comes from a stationery shop
in the capital
called Huiming Shop
that caters to the nobility.
I've investigated
their recent accounts
for this half year,
and the Xie Family
is one of their customers.
Of course,
this fact itself
is not enough to prove
that Mr. Xie is related to this case.
The situation back then
was that the enemies were in the dark
while I was in the open.
It was impossible to defend effectively.
That's why I planned to draw them out
by announcing that the Prince Consort
and I would be out on an excursion.
We set up an ambush at Butterfly Gorge,
using myself as bait,
and we caught
a group of assassins alive,
which included this man.
Upon investigation,
this man is adept
at using Seven-star Darts.
He is the Deputy Sect Leader
of the top assassin organization
in the martial world,
Seven-star Sect.
During my investigation,
I found something on him.
What are you doing?
Why are you scared?
Don't you want to know the truth?
♪Who gazes at the sky from afar?♪
♪In the night's chill breeze♪
♪What is she singing for?♪
♪The wind caresses the hills♪
♪The wind causes ripples on calm water♪
♪Moonlight graces passing souls♪
♪Her steps get slower and slower♪
♪She's trod a lengthy path♪
♪Memories lost then found♪
♪Gazing idly as clouds roll by♪
♪She holds a red candle♪
♪To brave the thick fog♪
♪Life can be bitter sometimes♪
♪Experience it with grace♪
♪Like a fleeting dream♪
♪Neither warmth nor cold will last♪
♪The moon is reflected in her eyes♪
♪In her gaze,
the unwavering faith remains♪