[The Princess Royal]
[Adapted from Mo Shu Bai's novel,
The Princess Royal on jjwxc.net]
[This is a work of fiction.]
[Episode 14]
No need to take the whole kit
for a small cut.
Your Highness,
I have an idea.
It might be very blunt,
but it's just a suggestion.
You can keep it to yourself
if it's blunt.
No, I should say it out loud.
What about Su Rongqing
as a potential candidate?
Look at me. Why would I bring him up?
Mr. Pei is here.
You're the Prince Consort, after all.
You can continue.
Mr. Pei is very generous.
Right?
Yes.
Feel free to speak your mind,
Miss Shangguan.
I observed Mr. Su's reaction today,
and I believe he has
some feelings for you, Your Highness.
If we can persuade him
to join the Inspectorate Office,
it will be easier
for us to make moves in the future.
What do you mean, Miss Shangguan?
See?
I offended Mr. Pei here.
It's fine. Please continue.
Feelings can be developed.
If you don't mind, Your Highness,
I can arrange it for you.
Arrange what?
Her Highness's marriage
shouldn't be mixed together
with those things.
Furthermore,
my marriage with Her Highness
is a scheme.
If we had a second chance,
shouldn't we avoid
making the same mistake?
Don't you agree, Your Highness?
♪May time itself ask me♪
Mr. Pei,
I beg to differ.
It's not right to sacrifice love
for power, of course.
But if Her Highness fancies him,
isn't that making use of an opportunity
to help them get together?
We're both Her Highness's friends.
As her besties,
we must act in her best interest.
Unless you have another motive, Mr. Pei.
♪I thought capturing your heart
meant forever♪
♪Yet, it turned out to be
as fleeting as autumn♪
No, I do not have any.
I just don't know
if you have a feeling for him.
♪I'd follow you with no hesitation♪
♪Ready to surrender everything
to this sensation♪
Well,
I have another appointment,
so I must take my leave now.
Your Highness, if you're interested,
you can just send me a message.
I'll arrange it for you.
I'll think about it.
I'm leaving.
♪Grant me a ceaseless passion♪
♪Let me face trials and tribulations
with you♪
♪Let us bathe in love's endless grace♪
What do you think of her suggestion?
I think
that she makes sense.
Nothing
is set in stone yet,
so we might as well play along.
It's impractical
to visit the Ministry of Justice
all the time to make a scene.
We need an intermediary.
I should talk to him.
I can negotiate with him on your behalf.
If you don't want
to visit the Ministry of Justice,
we can seek an alternative.
I'm willing to help.
Why do you keep stopping me
from seeing him?
Didn't you tell me
to give him a chance?
Li Rong.
We got married
because we wanted to gain power.
Even if we're getting a divorce,
I still hope you'll find
a man you like,
not a random person.
If you're
approaching Su Rongqing for power,
then there will be no difference
from the situation we are in now.
Of course, there's a difference.
I'm not saying I'll be with him now.
I'll wait until I know
that I'm in love with him.
Why don't you find out the answer now?
How?
What's wrong with you today?
You are never this temperamental.
Don't they say the older you get,
the more childish you become?
You cut yourself today
because of a recording officer.
That is inappropriate of you.
Don't do this again.
I know.
While people do say
that I carry a noble body,
I'm still a human.
You don't have to patch me up
like this for a small cut.
This is ridiculous.
Not at all.
You have to keep yourself safe.
What are you implying?
Nothing.
I'm just worried that Su Rongqing
might complain about me
in the court tomorrow.
Aren't you two sworn brothers
or something?
Enough.
Don't worry.
Father
will only punish you lightly
and deduct your salary.
You know what?
I'll pay you back
what my father will take from you.
If that's still not enough,
once I really establish a relationship
with Su Rongqing,
I'll ask him to pay you back tenfold.
Should I thank you then?
No need.
Don't worry.
Such a trivial matter
will not bother me at all.
I should go.
Where are you going?
Just do what you're supposed to do.
I'll ask Chuan to communicate
with your superior tomorrow
so that he won't give you extra work.
I won't take no for an answer.
All right.
Don't stay out too late.
Rest early.
I will.
The case files contain three parts.
The first one contains
the background of the Qin Family's case.
The second one contains
the investigation methods
and the reports issued and approved
by the officers involved.
The third one contains
the transcripts of all the witnesses's
testimonies and the evidence.
The testimonies and the evidence
are kept elsewhere.
We won't have access to them
for the moment.
However,
there's a breakthrough.
And that is this case is found
by Wen Ping, an investigating censor
from the Censorate.
Wen Ping received a report letter
claiming that when the Great Xia
and the enemies went to war,
the Qin Family
was defending Huangping County.
Three thousand soldiers stayed to defend
while three thousand enemies
came to invade.
[Military Record]
Yang Ye later asked the Qin Family
to feign surrender and flee the city.
After Wen Ping received the letter,
he retrieved
the official record of the battle
from the Ministry of War.
Three thousand soldiers
defended the city.
Three thousand enemies came invading.
The city was then abandoned.
Someone!
By right,
the invaders can only claim the city
if they outnumber
the defenders.
When both factions are of equal power,
this shouldn't be the outcome.
Luo Juan.
Confess now.
What truly happened in the battle
occurred in Huangping County?
Come clean!
Otherwise, you'll suffer more.
Back then...
the Qin Family could win.
Or at least, they wouldn't lose.
They abandoned the city.
Someone.
Ask the Ministry of War to assist us
in retrieving the military record
of the battle
so we can verify the situation.
Sirs,
this is the conclusion I've arrived at.
All evidence indicates
that the Qin Family
colluded with the enemies,
and betrayed the nation.
Then
seize the Qin's Mansion
and detain all personnel
according to the law.
Yes, sir.
The Qin Family is found guilty
of embezzling military funds,
colluding with enemies
and committing treason
with the Yang Family.
The evidence is clear.
Arrest
the entire Qin Family immediately.
Stop.
Qin Lang.
The evidence is clear.
Will you plead guilty or not?
Continue.
Stop.
Will you plead guilty or not?
Yes.
They've put a lot of effort into it
and tried to take the lives
of the entire Qin Family
with a mere one thousand taels of gold.
What a low price.
There are three entry points.
First,
find out the one who wrote the letter.
Then, it's Luo Juan.
Luo Juan must have
given a false testimony.
We need to find out more people
who participated in the battle.
Then, it's Yang Ye's letter.
We need to see it
to verify its veracity.
Lastly, that 1,000 taels of gold.
We need to locate those
who raided the Qin's Mansion.
Only they know
how the money got inside.
Tomorrow, I'll ask Xun Chuan
to go to Luo Juan and the veterans
who fought in the battle.
As for Yang Ye's letter and those
who raided the Qin's Mansion...
it'd be best if Su Rongqing
could help us with them.
Is she going
to go to Su Rongqing again?
But
what if Su Rongqing
refuses to cooperate?
I believe
we should avoid
having too much interaction with him.
After all, we don't know
if he's an ally or an enemy.
Then
We'll have to find out if we can
find another ally
in the Ministry of Justice.
Or, we take the normal procedures.
I'll give those who don't show us
the evidence a hard time
until they find us the evidence.
This is a much better option
than going to Su Rongqing.
You don't like him, do you?
It's not like that.
It's also...
Young Master?
Your Highness?
Never mind that.
Tell Miss Shangguan
that she can arrange it for me
as she wants
as soon as possible.
Ask Xun Chuan
to gather 12 elite ones
to be Her Highness's guards.
Yes, sir.
[Censorate]
Stop.
Who are you?
Mr. Wen.
I am Pei Wenxuan,
with Wujin as my courtesy name,
a palace attendant in the Censorate.
Oh?
You're from the Censorate?
Why didn't I see you
when I did the roll call today?
I am terribly sorry.
I was accompanying Princess Pingyue...
Are you the prince consort
or a palace attendant?
Both.
For your family,
you are the prince consort.
For your nation,
you are the palace attendant.
What's more important,
your family or your nation?
I believe
I don't need to give you the answer.
Duly noted, sir.
If you do not want to work,
I will write to His Majesty
and have you transferred away.
I am sorry, Mr. Wen.
I will make sure
to perform my duty in the future.
Words
don't hold any weight.
If you mean what you said,
why don't you handle the memorials
submitted by all 78 counties
under the five southwestern provinces?
What do you think?
Thanks for enlightening me, Mr. Wen.
Yongzhi, you're still here.
Wenxuan,
I'll be done soon.
Then, I'll go home.
Did you forget something?
No.
I need to handle these memorials.
There are so many of them.
You'll have to pull an all-nighter.
I am planning to do so.
Wenxuan.
Do you see what's happening?
They are making your life difficult
because Princess Pingyue and you
are investigating them.
I know.
And you're fine with that?
If I can't fulfill my duty,
how can I handle the work
outside my duty?
How admirable.
If you, a prince consort,
work this hard,
an unmarried commoner like me...
I should stay here and work with you.
Yongzhi.
Will you believe me
if I tell you there's a world...
where only your capability matters
rather than your family background?
Everyone there
can compete fairly.
Really?
Yes. We will make that happen.
We can eliminate the unfair system
of the imperial examination
and change the official system
to choose the competent ones
to serve our nation.
[Su's Mansion]
This is my dream
as a commoner.
Ronghua,
you're still as childish as ever.
What's on your mind?
You were so focused.
I was thinking about you.
Father is making arrangements
for your marriage.
You cannot
escape it forever.
Ronghua.
Is there anyone you adore?
If you do, let me know.
I'll help you convince Father.
Like I said,
I can handle the court affairs.
You can just do
whatever you want to do.
Sure.
Don't worry.
I won't go overboard.
You, however,
have been more sensible
than others since young.
You keep everything to yourself.
If there's something troubling you,
just share it with me.
I know.
Ronghua,
it's getting late.
You should go back and rest early.
You too.
I'll lend an ear if you need me.
See you.
Your Highness,
you're back.
Her Highness prepared this for you.
She's still awake?
She said you worked hard today,
and she's waiting for you.
You should have persuaded her to rest.
Don't
let her stay up that late again.
Otherwise, she'll fall sick.
We can't do that.
Why don't you persuade her personally,
Your Highness?
Right.
Let me talk to her.
Suddenly, I've realized
that whether in the past or at present,
what I've been longing for,
missing,
and yearning for
is the feeling of home.
It's precisely this moment
when I come home with a weary soul
to see someone waiting for me.
Rong.
You're back.
Finally.
No need to wait for me next time.
I didn't want you to get angry again.
Let me take the pillow away for you.
Your head.
Can you...
stop getting mad at Su Rongqing
when you see him?
You asked me
to go to him.
But then you got mad at me.
What am I supposed to do?
Then don't go to him.
Pei Wenxuan.
Calm down.
In the past, Su Rongqing
could not have Li Rong
because he came from a humble background
and was castrated.
Furthermore,
Li Rong and he had a huge grudge.
So they could merely
snuggle up to each other at night.
Li Rong
was still my wife.
But it's different now.
The present Su Rongqing
gets all the advantages.
[Jucai House]
I was trying my luck here.
I can't believe I'd run into you here.
You visit a gambling house
this early in the morning.
You sure are a bit insane.
Likewise.
You're a noble lady
who is proficient in four arts.
Yet, you've always
spent your time here too.
Compared to you, Miss Shangguan,
what I've done
is nothing.
Besides, I'm just
a seventh-ranked official.
I'm not an official member
of the Censorate,
so I don't have to attend
the morning court.
It's normal
that I come here to have fun.
Let's cut to the chase.
Her Highness wants to see your brother.
Can you bring him here
for a meal together?
You will get benefits for that.
I know you and Mr. Xie
are having a cockfight next month.
He possesses
the strongest cock in Huajing.
Therefore, you are looking
for another cock that can defeat his.
Coincidentally,
I have the undefeated cock
from Youzhou.
I can give it to you for free.
You'll win easily.
What do you think?
Miss Shangguan,
trading a cock for my younger brother?
Is this a joke or what?
What do you want then?
Let's gamble.
On what?
Big or small.
Best two out of three.
Hold on.
Let's not play that.
Let's play wooden cards.
Sure.
If you win, I'll give you what you want.
If I win,
you'll have to wear women's clothes
for me three days later.
Qian Ning.
Yes, sir?
Wait for Princess Pingyue
at the palace gate.
When she's done with the morning court,
ask her to dress up
because I want to have a meal with her.
Yes, sir.
Are you in?
Distribute the cards.
You lost again.
Your Highness.
Prince Consort.
Mr. Pei.
How's the game?
Miss Shangguan and I agreed
to gamble with wooden cards.
And she lost.
Miss Shangguan,
Her Highness is here,
and you lost many rounds.
You'll keep your promise, right?
Promise?
What promise?
You promised
to wear women's clothes for me
three days later.
No, I will win.
I'll win the next round.
All right.
Let's go.
If you continue,
the game will never end.
Let's go.
What about this?
You can have one round
with Wenxuan.
If you win, you want a meal
with Rongqing?
Yes.
If Wenxuan loses,
Ya will dine with you.
Wonderful.
Mr. Pei, please.
Pei Wenxuan.
Show Mr. Su what you're capable of.
Play it well.
If you win, you'll be awarded.
Mr. Pei,
what do you want to play?
Pai Gow.
Anything.
I'll deal the cards.
Mr. Su,
do you want one?
Ten points.
No need.
You have big points
on your card, Mr. Su.
You too, Mr. Pei.
Prince Consort,
do you want one?
Do you want to win?
Of course.
Two cards.
Two?
How bold, Mr. Pei.
Ten points too.
But each point on his cards
is smaller than yours.
So, Mr. Su?
Mr. Su.
Where are we having the meal?
Let's have it tonight.
Let's have the meal
at Mingyue Restaurant.
Now that we have settled
on the time and location,
Her Highness and I will get going.
See you.
It seems like
my view of the Prince Consort
will be changed.
He is so handsome!
Now I know
why Ya loves to gamble.
When you revealed the last card,
I was so nervous,
and my heart was beating so fast.
Nevertheless,
you were kind of handsome just now.
You actually find me attractive,
Your Highness?
Judging by your face,
you are attractive most of the time.
Anyway, how did you happen to know
that \the numbers
on those two cards were one?
I did the math.
It's not that difficult.
Not that difficult?
I can't even remember the numbers.
You're smart.
No wonder you ranked first
in the examination.
Your Highness, you don't need
to learn this.
Your shrewdness appears
in the grand scheme of things.
What are you doing next?
Returning to the bureau?
What about you?
Are you going back?
Yes, I have to get ready.
Ya finally got us the opportunity.
I can't let her down.
I'll get changed
and dress up.
Must you go?
I mean
the Qin Family's case files...
I've read them.
Then Luo Juan
and the people involved in the battle
occurred in Huangping County...
Xun Chuan is investigating that.
When I meet Su Rongqing later,
we'll see what we can learn from him.
Do you have other concerns?
No.
Don't worry. I'll come home early.
You have to be careful too.
Many people in the court
are keeping an eye on you.
Don't worry.
I will be cautious.
May your plan go smoothly,
Your Highness.
I'll go back now. Enjoy the food.
Mr. Pei.
Young... Young Master!
What are you doing here?
Young Master,
the Pei family sent a message
claiming that your mother was sick.
They want you to go back.
Mother is sick?
Why wasn't I informed?
Right.
You asked me to keep a close watch
and I did.
But there was no news whatsoever.
The messenger said
that your mother intentionally
concealed her illness
so as not to burden you.
An hour ago,
she fainted.
They couldn't get a physician in.
I suspect someone in the family
didn't want to get her any help.
Do you see it?
Let's go.
Head to Mingyue Restaurant.
Once Her Highness is done,
ask her to come to the Pei's Mansion
to pick me up.
I... I...
Ask her to bring more men with her.
Okay.
Go now.
Wait.
Wait for her by the entrance.
Do not disturb Her Highness.
Do you hear me?
Go now.
Yes.
Ronghua, you mean
Her Highness asked you
to invite me to a private meeting?
To be precise,
she asked Shangguan Ya
to make the request.
And
Pei Wenxuan is aware of this?
It seems like it.
Everyone alleges
that Princess Pingyue
betrothed Pei Wenxuan
out of convenience.
It seems like
that is the truth.
I think
you can meet Her Highness.
All right.
Please tell Her Highness
that I'll be there.
What are you doing here?
I am here to escort you.
You just don't want to be left out.
What do you think?
Do I look good?
Yes,
just a bit too formal.
It shows a sense of oppression.
It seems like
you are condescending.
For this meeting,
it's best to present yourself
as equals.
But I am a princess.
No matter how I dress,
I can't hide my temperament.
Your Highness,
I may give you some advice.
Let's start with your way of speaking.
When you talk to a man,
avoid speaking in a bossy manner.
Do not move.
That's it.
You always lift your chin
when you speak.
That's what a princess does.
But for ordinary women,
we lower our heads
and brows.
And when we speak,
- we do this.
- We do this.
I know,
but that's not me.
Your Highness...
Enough.
Your Highness.
Rongqing,
I can't walk further.
You've been browsing for an hour,
and you still can't make up your mind.
It's rare for Her Highness
to invite me for a meal.
I must pick a fitting gift
for the occasion.
I have an idea.
What about food?
The lamb stew
from Hongqing Restaurant is good.
It comes with a fancy package too.
No.
Food is too common.
It lacks sincerity.
Rongqing,
what about an accessory?
You can't go wrong with a hairpin.
An accessory?
No.
Her Highness will refuse
an expensive gift.
Besides, it is inappropriate for me
to give her accessories
with my current identity.
Sirs!
Come take a look.
Fresh flowers I plucked this morning.
Take a look.
Pick anything you like.
Rongqing,
I remember you said
that Her Highness
loved peonies the most.
For a lady of such mesmerizing beauty,
only a peony can match her charm.
All right.
I'll take this one.
Sure.
Greetings, Grandfather.
Greetings, Mother.
Greetings to all.
I was told Mother fell ill,
so I rushed back.
It seems like
you are fine, Mother.
I...
I summoned you here.
I knew you wouldn't heed my call,
so I asked your mother
to bring you here.
Why would you say that, Grandfather?
If the elderly in the family needs me,
I wouldn't dare not to come back.
However,
lying about my mother falling sick
has made me terribly worried.
If you were truly
concerned about this family,
you wouldn't have urged Her Highness
to do those obstructive things.
I do not understand,
Second Uncle.
You asked Her Highness to establish
the Inspectorate Office, didn't you?
I see it now.
You brought everyone here
for this matter.
Second Uncle, you may direct
your dissatisfaction to Her Highness.
Wenxuan,
you are the Prince Consort.
She may be reckless
but you cannot afford that.
Other families have come
and questioned us.
In the past, she couldn't
care less about the state affairs.
After she betrothed you,
she meddled in everyone's affairs.
This must have something
to do with you.
Even if we could believe you,
no one from the outside would.
So,
what do you want me to do?
Wenxuan.
Listen to us.
Talk to Her Highness and tell her
not to be enemies
with the noble families.
If our family is implicated,
Her Highness will remain untouched,
but our family will...
Our family will what?
Mother,
how could you believe
whatever they told you?
I...
What do you want me to do?
Go back
and tell Her Highness
to stay out of the affairs.
Just...
Just forget about the Qin Family's case.
So, it's all about
the Qin Family's case, isn't it?
I see.
Anything else?
You...
What is
that attitude?
Do you have no respect for me?
I do.
But do you?
I...
My sister-in-law,
look at your child.
You must discipline him.
He... He...
How dare you defy us?
Punish him. Punish him.
Someone!
Punish me?
Mother.
Was it that they told you
that by punishing me,
the other noble families
would be appeased,
and that Her Highness would back off?
In the future, if I ever
urge Her Highness to do anything,
you'll punish me again,
until I cease.
Is that so?
I knew this would happen.
I just didn't expect you...
to follow through
with their plan, Mother.
Don't just stand there.
Get him
and punish him.
Wenxuan.
I...
I know you cannot bear
to see this scene.
You may turn around.
Stop!
My child...
just admit that you are wrong.
I am not wrong.
Not wrong?
Come on, Father.
Hit him until he admits that he's wrong.
Continue.
Her Highness was right downstairs,
but she had to leave
because something came up.
Go and tell Mr. Su
so that he won't wait in vain
and get mad at Her Highness.
Quickly.
My poor brother.
No one has ever
taken him for a fool like this.
Perhaps
I should tell him the truth.
Wait.
I'll dine with you three times.
You can pick the restaurant.
Deal.
Young Master told me
not to disturb you, Your Highness.
Where were you doing?
I was waiting for you.
Young Master told me
to tell you after the meal.
Enough.
Your Highness.
They won't let us in.
Move aside.
Barge in.
Let's go.
Master!
Bad news.
Her Highness barged in.
Xun Chuan.
Why is the Prince Consort kneeling?
Help him up.
Yes.
Your Highness.
- Your Highness.
I have some harsh words to say
in front of the ancestors
of your family today.
Your Highness,
perhaps you can keep...
I was having a meal.
And you tricked my consort
into serving a punishment here.
May I remind you
that he is the Prince Consort
and a member of the imperial family?
You've humiliated him like this.
Have you ever thought
about the imperial family's reputation?
Who hit him?
Who sanctioned the punishment?
Come clean at once.
Your Highness,
I know you want
to protect your consort.
But Wenxuan is part of the Pei family.
In this nation, being a prince consort
doesn't mean he is not part
of his paternal family.
I am handling a familial matter.
So I pray for your understanding,
Your Highness.
Understanding?
For what?
For you being ungrateful
and shortsighted?
I know very well
why you brought him here.
You believed that punishing him
could appease other noble families
and issue a warning to me
so that I wouldn't establish
the Inspectorate Office.
You want me to back off.
Your family
is the new rising family
in the imperial court.
Pei Lixian,
you are the Vice Minister of Revenue.
Pei Liming,
you are the Vice Minister of Justice.
Your other kins can also be found
in other civil functions.
Does that make you think
you're part of the noble families?
They want you to give me trouble,
and you're eager to prove your worth.
If I may recount your origin,
the Pei family came from a humble origin
in Luzhou.
Before this generation,
your ancestors had never
risen above a fifth-ranked official.
Pei Wenxuan's father, Pei Lizhi,
brought your kins
to Huajing from Luzhou,
promoting you into the higher echelon.
He died not long ago,
yet you're already bullying
his son and his wife.
Your Highness,
your criticism
is unjustly harsh.
Unjustly harsh?
Pei Wenxuan was the top one
in the Royal Selection.
He is more than capable
of occupying an important position.
If he hadn't betrothed me,
he would've still been
a lowly official
who's inferior to a prison guard.
What did you do?
You used the excuse
that a scion of a noble family
must start from the ground
to silence his mother.
When he was sick,
you actively stopped him
from seeing a physician.
When he needed money
to interact with other officials,
you made his life more difficult.
He works for the imperial court
in hopes of escaping this predicament,
yet you continue to impede him.
He can turn a blind eye to you,
but don't ever think I will do the same!
I want to establish
the Inspectorate Office,
and so does His Majesty.
Even if you kill him today,
His Majesty or I
will not stop.
Remember
your root.
Don't get too complacent
in your lofty position.
Your Highness,
even though you are a princess,
you are nonetheless a junior member
in this family.
Should I inform His Majesty
about your unruly behavior
in my family's
ancestral shrine?
Who hit him?
Xun Chuan.
Yes, Your Highness?
Break his arm.
Yes.
No.
You mustn't do this.
I'll reiterate this.
Pei Wenxuan
is the Prince Consort,
my husband.
If this family doesn't like him,
hurry up
and expel him already.
I'll give him a family.
If you want to keep him,
then, from now on,
treat him
like how you will treat me.
As for you, Mrs. Wen...
if you do not know
how to love
or protect your child,
please stay in the family hall
for worshipping the Immortals
and mourn for your husband forever.
Pei Wenxuan has a new home.
Someone will protect and love him.
If you can't care for him as a mother,
then at least don't hurt him.
He can allow you to do so.
But I won't.
Am I clear?
Let's go home.
Come on.
Be careful.
♪If the past was caught
in the turbulent waves of the storm♪
Xun Chuan.
Cut off his arm.
Yes.
♪Will there be arms to hold me
in this lifetime?♪
♪Who gazes at the sky from afar?♪
♪In the night's chill breeze♪
♪What is she singing for?♪
♪The wind caresses the hills♪
♪The wind causes ripples on calm water♪
♪Moonlight graces passing souls♪
♪Her steps get slower and slower♪
♪She's trod a lengthy path♪
♪Memories lost then found♪
♪Gazing idly as clouds roll by♪
♪She holds a red candle♪
♪To brave the thick fog♪
♪Life can be bitter sometimes♪
♪Experience it with grace♪
♪Like a fleeting dream♪
♪Neither warmth nor cold will last♪
♪The moon is reflected in her eyes♪
♪In her gaze,
the unwavering faith remains♪