(Love knows no age...)
(because it is always born anew.)
During an important period of my life,
I could have gotten married.
But I chose my career over marriage.
I don't remember ever taking a break.
My career felt more important than love.
Then I wondered,
"At this rate, am I going to grow old alone?"
"If only I had someone by my side."
(But don't tell me...)
He's not ten years younger than me, is he?
Does age matter when I have feelings for her?
If someone really piques my interest,
I don't care about the age gap.
It's not easy to find a younger guy like me.
What could you hate about being young?
Isn't it better?
What? This is adorable.
(An older woman and a younger man's...)
(real romance begins.)
Noona, how about a date?
It made my heart flutter a bit.
Should I say he was cute?
He was cute.
That moment itself was really nice.
He kept touching me a little without hesitation.
I noticed it.
To think that a younger guy could feel like a man.
(One by one,)
(the moments that made them forget the age gap.)
It felt like a scene out of a movie.
How old are you comfortable with?
About four years older?
"Am I not attractive as a woman?" was what I thought.
I'm just a child to you.
Laughing in front of you can't be a lie, right?
He was much younger than I had imagined.
I couldn't keep a straight face.
"Age doesn't matter that much."
That was what I thought.
We weren't meant to be.
That was the conclusion I reached.
(Noona Is A Woman to Me)
(Everyone is frozen.)
This is bad.
That just now...
We only watched for a minute or two, right?
- Right now, my heart is...
- Yes?
beating like crazy.
What did you think?
(Hwangwoo Seul Hye)
I liked how they called me "noona."
But for real, I'm serious.
"I really am old now."
Right.
- That really hit me.
- Why? And when
I've always been called "noona..."
- by my younger brother.
- I see.
But that kind of noona wasn't everything.
Being called "noona" by a younger brother...
and him calling me "noona" are completely different.
But that guy didn't call you "noona,"
so why?
It makes me happy, okay?
If you don't mind me asking,
have you dated a younger guy before?
- Of course.
- I see.
I may have dated more younger guys than you can imagine.
That's right.
After entering my mid-30s,
I've mainly dated younger guys.
Do older guys not like me because I'm old?
The participants only know that...
the women are older and the men are younger,
but they don't know their actual ages.
No.
Say that you really like someone,
but they turn out to be 12 years older or younger.
Simply put, there's a big age gap.
How would you feel?
(Sighing)
How old is 12 years younger?
He just turned 30.
- Thirty sounds a little tough.
- For example.
- May I ask the reason?
- Well...
I can't help but think he's too young.
Shouldn't he be at least 33 or 34?
- It's only a three-year difference.
- Here's the thing.
Guys in their early 30s and mid-30s are completely different.
There's a huge difference in their insight.
What about you?
I'm fine with it.
I'm fine with anyone over 30.
- Anyone over 30?
- Over 30?
Among our older women and younger men participants,
Yes?
the biggest age gap is 12 years.
- For real?
- There are participants...
with that age gap.
Will they...
Isn't it the one messing up her hair?
This sounds really fun.
(One day in September)
(Where they meet for the first time)
(A red car arrives first.)
She has an innocent style.
(Park Ye Eun)
Her skin is pure white.
I only worked hard for my future.
During an important period of my life,
I could have gotten married.
But I chose my career over marriage.
I'm lonely.
I'm lonely right now.
(She's here to meet her fated partner.)
She looks quite young.
- I'd say she's in her 20s.
- Totally in her 20s.
- Right?
- Yes.
(Pouting)
(Feeling shy)
I was extremely nervous.
"Who will show up?"
It also made me excited.
(Fate comes at unexpected times,)
(like a sudden shower.)
Is it a guy this time?
(The second participant appears amidst the shower.)
What a nice car.
It's a female participant?
(Walking confidently in high heels)
It's a participant with a different charm.
(Park Ji Won)
I don't remember ever taking a break like this.
I've always worked, studied,
and started a business.
You never really...
get the chance to spend time...
solely getting to know someone...
in your life.
(As it's a precious opportunity, she wants to find someone nice.)
Hi.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you too.
Did you wait long?
No.
It's hot, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
One female participant met another female participant.
- That must've been weird.
- Totally.
(Glancing)
(Glancing again)
How awkward.
(An awkward air flows between the two.)
You're pretty.
You're much prettier.
That's normal when ladies meet up,
complimenting each other on their beauty.
There should be two more participants.
It must be a total of four.
Right? I'm excited.
- Oh, no.
- She's cute.
I was wondering why she looked so cheerful.
She thinks there's little competition.
She believes it's 2-on-2.
(A sedan arrives third.)
(Is it finally a younger man?)
Seriously?
It's like a commercial.
A commercial.
Gorgeous.
(Kim Yeong Gyeong)
To me, dating is an unknown world.
- It's a mystery.
- Why?
It's like an area I need to explore.
Right now, dating...
is at zero.
I spend about 99 on my work...
and 1 on taking breaks, doing hobbies, and enjoying life.
Honestly, looking back,
there were more times when guys passionately pursued me first...
rather than me winning their love.
That's why, if I get the chance,
I'd like to win his heart first.
I look forward to what I will do.
- Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
(Staring)
- Nice to meet you too. Hi.
You made a long trip to get here.
- It was quite far.
- Right?
(They look taken aback.)
They thought it'd be a younger guy.
To think this would happen.
Three women.
What's going on?
Why only women?
What's more, everyone has long hair and is wearing a white top.
You're right.
(The fourth woman has arrived.)
The fourth woman. Another woman?
She's wearing black.
(Gu Bon Hee)
It looks like a commercial whenever a woman walks in.
I was the type who used myself...
as a tool to work.
My career felt more important than love.
But after realizing there are more important things than my career,
I thought this would be a chance to focus only on my feelings.
So I'm looking forward to it. It's giving me butterflies.
(Will she find someone who will make her heart pound again?)
What they say is different from other dating shows.
- How so?
- Exactly.
They can summarize the kind of life...
they've lived in one sentence.
The fact that they can explain...
in one sentence why they haven't...
gotten married or dated until now...
shows how straightforward their lives are.
They have a clear answer.
- They seem confident.
- For sure.
- Hi.
Hi.
I didn't know everyone had arrived.
(Everyone's eyes are fixed on Bon Hee upon her arrival.)
They're studying her.
The older women study her.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
(Nervous)
(The 4 older women have gathered first.)
How awkward.
(Glancing)
- Nice to meet you.
- Likewise.
Everyone here is so gorgeous...
that my eyes...
are feasting.
I'm...
(Reading the room)
I'll stay still because it'd be awkward if I said something back.
You get it, right?
Like when women say, "You've lost weight," and all.
So I won't say anything.
But it's not that easy to tell another woman...
that your eyes are feasting because she's pretty.
- No.
- Exactly.
- People keep it to themselves.
- It shows how nice she is.
It's a story about older women and younger men.
How did you feel after hearing it?
- It felt new.
- Right.
But I thought it'd be fun too.
Have you dated a younger guy before?
Once, when I was in my 20s.
I rarely had the chance...
to meet older men.
It's fun, and they have the energy...
that suits me better.
In general, it feels like younger men hit on women...
more passionately.
(Agreeing)
(Nodding)
Everyone can relate.
Aren't I right?
(Becoming self-conscious)
(Thinking)
I hit on guys first.
Maybe they hit on you first because you're beautiful.
(Embarrassed)
The one time I dated a younger guy, I remember hitting on him first.
(Sharing memories of dating younger men)
But I didn't know his age at first.
I didn't. I only found out...
he was younger as we talked.
Teto-guy versus egen-guy.
But the two are...
- Must I choose one?
- Yes.
Only one.
(Bummed out)
I like crunchy outside, tender inside.
So a teto-guy on the outside, an egen-guy on the inside.
Aren't they the most popular these days?
- Yes.
- Right?
I'll go with her answer too.
You too?
A puppy-like guy.
In short, an egen-guy.
- Yes.
- Right.
They got a message.
Our phone went off.
- "Check the top of the cabinet."
"Here are keywords that are hints about the men."
"Choose one card that you like."
- What?
- It's for you.
(The fateful keyword Yeong Gyeong should choose?)
Crunchy outside, tender inside.
(Crunchy outside, tender inside is included.)
- Perfect.
- How is this possible?
There's even Golden Retriever.
(Golden Retriever, similar to puppy-like)
"Let's go get meat, noona. Well-organized."
(Captivating younger men's keywords)
- "If you're with me,"
- "your ears will never be bored."
- "The day flies by."
Woo Young and SOOBIN. Say that you were to come up with keywords.
What would yours be?
- To introduce myself?
- Yes.
I want to see the person I'm interested in...
continue to laugh.
"Be with me, and you'll laugh your head off."
I'm interested.
- Nice.
- You are?
No? Don't you think he'll be funny?
What's your hashtag?
Have you in stitches.
- It suddenly...
- What is it? Was that a good one?
I'm no longer interested.
"Have you in stitches" was a bit...
Did it drop your expectations? What about you, SOOBIN?
My hashtag would be...
(SOOBIN's keyword to top "have you in stitches")
- a chameleon.
- A chameleon?
- Is it too old-fashioned?
(Embarrassed)
- A chameleon?
- I can become anything.
I like to adapt to my partner rather than expecting them to adapt to me.
- Really?
- Yes.
(At that moment)
Here they are.
(Are the younger men finally revealed?)
(In different locations,)
What's going on?
(the 4 younger men...)
What a nice silhouette.
(are waiting.)
He's got a nice silhouette.
(After choosing the keywords they like,)
(the older women head off to pick them up.)
They go to pick them up?
The older women are going to pick...
- the younger men up.
- Pick them up.
(The first younger man is waiting for the older woman.)
I find older women more comfortable.
Older women are more comfortable than younger women.
If she's my ideal type,
I could date someone ten years older than me.
(Who will come to this man,)
(looking for his ideal type?)
I was extremely nervous.
I wondered what would happen.
I was worried,
but I'm also curious.
(I'm curious about who I will meet.)
(Tense)
(Glancing)
(She eases her tension with a hand grip.)
A hand grip?
I've never seen anyone relieve tension with a hand grip.
She uses a hand grip?
(Clicking)
(She trains her grip strength...)
(and arrives at the place where a younger guy awaits.)
(The tense yet thrilling moment...)
(of a first encounter)
(Who's the woman that picked the first younger guy?)
(Bon Hee's pick)
He's the guy that Bon Hee picked, right?
Yes.
(Hesitating)
(Bon Hee's pick)
He's the guy that Bon Hee picked, right?
Yes.
(Hesitating)
Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- Yes.
- I'll take a seat.
- Sure.
That's Mu Jin.
(Bon Hee picked Mu Jin.)
Have you waited long?
A couple of hours.
- You waited long.
- Yes.
Didn't you have to wait?
Not really.
- He's good-looking.
- He's nice.
They look cute together.
- He's handsome.
- They make a cute couple.
They do.
- They do.
- They're a good match.
They don't really look like a couple...
with an age gap.
- Right?
- Not at all.
Did you see the guy trying to hold...
his smile?
I think the woman is into him too.
- She also looks satisfied.
- Yes.
(A pleasant tension)
I noticed that you almost finished your coffee,
so I thought you had been here for a while.
- Would you like one?
- Sorry?
Should I have one too?
Then, we'll...
- I'll pay for it.
- Hold on.
(Mu Jin hurriedly grabbed his card.)
What would you like?
I'll have an iced latte.
- An iced latte?
- Yes.
- This one?
I'll have another cup of coffee.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Do you sleep well even after having coffee?
Yes.
(Yes.)
- What?
He subtly dropped the honorifics.
This show is wild.
(This older woman is thrilled.)
But they've just met.
(Speechless)
Before...
they went to order coffee, Bon Hee asked,
"Do you sleep well, even after coffee?"
- She did.
- Yes.
I felt a difference from that one sentence.
Right? She was being considerate.
I felt cared for.
- Right.
- That's how it felt.
Do you sleep well even after having coffee?
Yes.
(Grinning)
Thank you for the coffee.
(Spotting the keyword)
Did you pick this card?
I did.
(Twitching his nose)
- The profiles were...
- Yes.
all different.
- That looks like my profile.
- Yes.
- Can you turn to the side?
- Me?
Is it this side? I think it's the other side.
- Is it this side?
- There it is.
I said that the back of your head was pretty.
When I saw this,
I said that the back of your head was very round.
But you look way better in person.
- Do I?
- Yes.
In the shadow, you're more...
The back of my head really is round.
- I also have a round head.
- I see.
Can I see?
- I have a round head.
- You do.
(Staring)
You're really beautiful.
Me? Thank you.
(Goodness gracious)
(Amazed)
- Wait!
- "You're beautiful."
What was that?
- Who is this guy?
- They do that?
I loved the non-honorifics, though.
You can make a clip of that...
and give it to Seul Hye.
Make a clip of him saying, "You're beautiful,"
and send it to me.
I'm cool with just an audio file if you can't get a video.
- SOOBIN, - Yes.
would you be able...
to say that while sipping a drink?
I'm not good at saying things I don't mean,
- so if it's not true...
- But she's actually pretty.
If she's as pretty as Bon Hee,
I wouldn't have a problem saying that.
- Really?
- Yes.
It's also a good way to start a conversation.
Mu Jin is skilled.
- He's no ordinary man.
- Definitely.
You're really beautiful.
Me? Thank you.
You're handsome.
(Twitching his nose)
The way he twitches his nose is very charming.
- I'm nervous.
- Are you nervous?
I'll tell you why I picked it.
Because you like meat?
I must have wanted meat.
And this keyword "well-organized" made me think...
you'd be...
capable and responsible.
- Right.
- Am I right?
My name is Kim Mu Jin.
- It's Kim Mu Jin?
- Yes, Kim Mu Jin.
- And I'm well-organized, so...
- Really?
- Is that why you chose that word?
- Yes.
- It's my nickname.
- Your nickname?
What's your name, if you mind me asking?
I'm Gu Bon Hee.
- Gu Bon Hee?
- Bon Hee.
That's right.
Yes.
- What kind of meat do you like?
- Meat?
Pork belly with kimchi.
- Pork belly with kimchi?
- Yes.
We'll get to have meat together one day, right?
I'd like that.
(Grinning)
She's shivering.
- Oh, my gosh!
- She's so nervous.
- She suddenly got awkward.
- Yes.
She totally lost control.
He's very charismatic.
(His presence overwhelms her.)
Is that bobbed hair?
- Right now? Yes.
- Yes.
It suits you.
Okay.
(Even when he's shy,)
(he can't take his eyes off Bon Hee.)
I was so nervous when I met the other women.
Right.
My face started to stiffen.
I feel comfortable now.
I don't know why I feel so comfortable.
- Now that you're here?
- No, I...
- Did you mean me?
- Yes.
That's good.
I think it'll be fun.
Yes.
Let's go now.
I'm getting nervous.
- Her smile is completely different.
- Oh, my gosh.
It's like he bewitched her.
His vibe is...
nothing like that of a younger guy.
- You're right.
- Bon Hee...
wasn't exactly the gentle one...
- among the females.
- Right.
But now,
I feel like she's behaving that way because of Mu Jin.
Right.
He's the type of guy that makes you act awkwardly.
She knocked her down.
Yes, he has that subtle vibe.
(Another younger guy...)
(waiting for a woman from another place.)
What I was worried about was...
that I would seem too young to her.
I was worried that I would look too childish.
I didn't want to call her "noona."
- Hello.
- Did you just get here?
- Yes.
(Peeking)
(Ye Eun picked Golden Retriever.)
He looks like a Golden Retriever.
(Anxious)
He doesn't know where to look.
I didn't know you'd enter so suddenly.
Do you drink coffee?
Yes, I love coffee.
Thanks.
(Golden Retriever turns to drink.)
The ice must have melted a little.
Why is he turning and drinking coffee?
She's not that old!
Right.
(Laughing)
That was cute.
He's too tense.
He's restless.
- That's so cute.
- Golden Retriever...
- looks so cute.
- He does.
He's completely different from well-organized.
(He's the opposite of Mu Jin.)
May I ask your name?
I'm Park Ye Eun.
- Ye Eun?
- What's your name?
- I'm Kim Sang Hyeon. Yes.
- Sang Hyeon.
Ye Eun. Ms. Park?
- "Ms. Park?"
- He's cute.
(Spotting)
I didn't notice that was here.
(Exclaiming)
- Are you feeling shy?
- Yes.
- Do you...
Why is it Golden Retriever?
I've been told...
that I was like a puppy.
I picked this card.
- Did you?
- Yes.
Can I ask you why you picked it?
It's my type of guy.
You must like guys who are like puppies.
- Yes. I like puppies.
- I see.
That's a pretty necklace.
He should have said she was pretty.
He can't even meet eyes.
Mu Jin didn't just say she was pretty.
He was looking straight at her...
and said it so nonchalantly.
(He had his eyes on her and said it calmly.)
But Sang Hyeon is very shy...
and doesn't know where to look.
The two are the exact opposite...
in terms of the way they speak on a first encounter.
I've been told...
that I looked like a cat.
Right.
Do you like girls with cat-like faces?
Yes, I do.
Are you sure you don't like the puppy types?
No. I think I like a cat-like woman more.
- Really?
- Yes.
I have a cat-like face, so I like a guy with a puppy-like face.
Oh, the opposite.
What types of girls are you into?
I also like the opposite.
Someone cold...
I like a woman with a cold, cat-like face.
I've never heard of a cold, cat-like face before.
I'm usually smiley, and I rarely get angry.
I prefer someone who I can be considerate toward.
Rather than being considerate toward each other,
I like someone who's honest.
I'm very honest.
(Flustered)
Don't be too honest, though.
You might hurt my feelings.
Yes. So, there's that.
(His hands are sweating.)
What's your... I can't quite phrase it well.
Are you usually...
into guys who are big...
and masculine?
Or do you like guys who are small and cute?
Appearance-wise, I like someone with big eyes with monolids.
Big eyes with monolids?
I do have monolids.
You do.
Just saying.
And a guy who looks pretty when he smiles.
I should try to smile prettily.
Oh, my.
(Although he feels awkward,)
(he says what he needs to say to win her over.)
And I prefer...
a man who takes good care of himself.
I take pretty good care of myself.
Goodness.
(The awkward...)
(yet thrilling first encounter ends.)
(At that moment,)
(another guy is waiting for a woman.)
He has a big build. He's very tall.
I've dated lots of older women since I was younger...
because of how I look.
I had dated a lot of older women.
I liked it.
He looks good.
She gives off a different vibe.
Hello.
That height difference makes my heart flutter.
Are you "crunchy outside, tender inside?"
Pardon? Oh, right.
That's me.
So, he's "crunchy outside, tender inside."
(Kim Hyeon Jun)
(Yeong Gyeong picked "crunchy outside, tender inside.")
(Glancing)
(Feeling shy)
I get shy around strangers.
- You do?
- Yes. How about you?
- So do I.
- We're in trouble.
(A "crunchy outside, tender inside" meeting at a rainy train station)
By the way,
I think we're stuck here.
I think we are.
It's showering hard.
It is.
It suddenly started raining hard.
It was more atmospheric,
and it felt like I was in a scene from a movie.
- It does look like a movie.
- It's like a painting.
Come with me.
Will you be all right with those shoes?
It's fine.
Hold on. There's a huge puddle.
- Step on these.
- Okay.
Go on. It's dangerous.
(Hyeon Jun seems naturally well-mannered.)
- Go on.
- Thank you.
This is getting interesting.
(He walks her to her car until she gets in.)
All good?
Yes. Thank you.
Your jacket must be soaking wet.
(His arm is soaked.)
(It's rainier than expected.)
There was lightning.
(Scared)
No way.
(Looking)
I don't think it's going to stop any time soon.
Should we switch seats?
Should we?
(He readily offers to drive.)
I love this type of stuff.
(Impressed)
What does the rain have to do with switching seats?
- When it's raining...
- Shouldn't you...
- hit the road as soon as possible?
- It's harder to drive...
- in the rain.
- Oh, I see.
It's a heavy rain, so it's harder to see.
He's naturally considerate.
(He understood.)
I wasn't hesitant because she was older.
Instead, she was mature,
and I could learn a lot from her.
Our relationship was calmer.
(They meet for the first time.)
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Have a seat.
- Thanks.
- It's nice to meet you.
He can't look her in the eyes.
"The day flies by." I'm dying to find out.
What? Oh, right.
- Is this you?
- It is.
(Ji Won picked "the day flies by.")
- "The day flies by."
- So, you picked it based on that.
- Yes.
- I had no idea.
What's your name?
I'm Park Sang Won.
- Park Sang Won?
- Sang Won.
- What is your name?
- I'm Park Ji Won.
"If you're with me, your ears will never be bored."
That means I'm chatty.
I don't like silence in conversations.
You seem very calm right now.
I know. I'm trying hard to suppress my urge to chat.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
- But you should make my day fly by.
- That's right.
Give me a few moments.
We have a lot of time, you know.
We still have much time.
(Ji Won leads Sang Won, who's nervous, naturally.)
- I see that Ji Won's very cheerful.
- Yes, indeed.
Have you ever dated an older woman?
- Yes, I have.
- I see.
I've dated two older women, both for over a year.
Were the ladies you dated nice?
They were more stable than younger ones.
Before I met them,
I dated some younger women.
- I found them mentally unstable.
- I see.
But it was different when I dated older women.
Since they had already stabled their lives,
there were not a lot of changes in their lives.
So we didn't have a lot of conflicts.
Everything would be fine as long as I didn't cause trouble.
(The romantic first meeting of the participants is over.)
We've watched...
- how all participants met 1-on-1.
- Yes.
Which of those four couples made your heart flutter?
I pick Mr. Yes.
- He spoke casually to his partner.
- Right, Yes Mu Jin.
And the way he wrinkled his nose.
- That's right.
- Yes.
As for the other couples,
- the women seemed to take the lead.
- Right.
Mu Jin was the only guy...
- who seemed to be the leader.
- That's right.
Sang Hyeon seemed like a man who'd be devoted to a relationship.
I think his heart wouldn't change once he falls in love.
He didn't know how to express his feelings.
The way he acted struck me as cute.
- He seemed innocent to you.
- It brings out your affection.
What do you think about Sang Won?
I was excited to see...
how he'd entertain his partner.
- But he seemed unexpectedly shy.
- Right.
So I thought he was a younger man after all.
Was he very nervous to meet an older woman?
- I think he was very nervous.
- Yes, because she's older than him.
- Honestly, a man like Hyeon Jun...
- Right.
makes me feel comfortable.
- I knew you would like him.
- He seemed...
- to be a manly and attentive type.
- Right, he's manliest of all.
- He's very attractive.
- Indeed.
- He's very...
- Hye Jin, your eyes are sparkling.
- I'm completely into it.
- Right.
Show us the rest. I'm so curious.
That must be it.
It looks so fancy.
I think we're the first to arrive.
We're the first to arrive.
- I'm glad it's not raining.
- Right.
This must be it.
(Yeon House)
(The place they arrived at is...)
Yeon House.
I wonder we're the first to arrive.
- This must be it.
- Maybe we should...
(The first couple: Bon Hee and Mu Jin)
(- Impressive.
- It's nice.)
(This is Yeon House...)
(where the older women and the younger men will stay together.)
It's huge.
It has a swimming pool too.
Exactly.
A lot of things will happen here.
(The place where you forget your age and focus solely on your feelings)
(Amazed)
(Exclaiming in awe)
It's practically a castle.
I wonder what will happen in this house.
(The romance in Yeon House is completely unpredictable.)
What kind of wild, crazy things will happen?
Would you like to open it?
(Putting the slippers down)
Thank you.
(Amazed)
It's... Oh, my. It's all furnished like a house.
(1st floor, common area)
My goodness. This place is so nice.
(1st floor, kitchen)
I guess we eat here.
(The area next to the kitchen where they can eat together)
(1st floor, dining room)
These are real flowers. Do you like flowers?
Yes, I like flowers.
I thought they were fake.
I like flowers so much. I can tell if it's real right away.
- You can tell by looking at it?
- Yes.
(Smiling)
I go to a flower market too.
- You go to a flower market?
- Yes.
- Shall we go upstairs?
It's big.
- It's really nice.
- Indeed.
(2nd floor, common area)
I guess this is where we can have a chat.
(The space where honest and serious conversations will occur)
(2nd floor, girls' room)
So each of us will have one.
(3rd floor, guys' room)
- This is the guys' room.
- Right.
Terrace.
(3rd floor, terrace)
The view is nice.
(The luxurious and private space only for the participants)
What color do you like?
- I like neutral colors. Yes.
- Neutral colors?
Colors that don't stand out.
What color would you pick if you had to pick one?
Well... I guess I'd pick green.
Dark green.
Oh, really?
(There's one room they haven't checked out yet.)
It's locked.
- It's locked.
- Sorry?
(The door is locked.)
- What is it?
(What could be the purpose of the locked room?)
(This room is unlocked only once a day.)
(The chamber of secrets)
"The chamber of secrets?"
(They can guess a participant's age in the chamber of secrets.)
I think they can get a hint on someone's age in there.
I guess they can get information about one another.
(Could it be possible...)
(for love to transcend age differences?)
(Who will enter this room? And how will he or she do it?)
I'm so curious.
Oh, my. It's so beautiful.
(The second couple: Ye Eun and Sang Hyeon)
One person must have arrived.
(Staggering)
(Chuckling)
Thank you.
(Impressed)
Can we take a look around?
- Hello.
- Hello. It's nice to meet you.
I'm glad to see you again. Don't you?
Take a look around. There's a kitchen here.
And don't forget to check what's in the fridge.
- Did you have a look?
- Yes, it has four stories.
Really?
- He hid behind his partner.
- My goodness.
- He's so cute.
- He's cute.
- He really is like a puppy.
- How cute.
Let's look around.
(Avoiding eye contact)
- I'm so excited.
- I see.
(Wherever Ye Eun goes,)
(Sang Hyeon goes.)
This place makes me feel comfortable for some reason.
- He's following her around.
- My goodness.
(Following)
What is this?
We have pasta noodles.
(Surprised)
- Hello.
When did you get here?
- We just got here.
- I see.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I'm glad to meet you.
Right. See? Mu Jin is different.
- He greeted them right away...
- That's right.
and came up to them to have a chat.
- He approached them first.
- Exactly.
(Glancing)
Have a look around.
(He already feels at home.)
(After greeting them briefly, Mu Jin goes to Bon Hee.)
- Shall we check if there's water?
- Okay.
I want something to drink too.
(Mu Jin looks for a cup.)
Here's a cup.
I think you can just rinse it with water.
(Here you go.)
(He checks Bon Hee's cup.)
(Glancing)
(Sighing)
(Picking up)
What's that cup?
I think we can use this too.
Are you washing it for me?
(Nodding)
(Smiling)
(The cup she received from Sang Hyeon)
(Surprised)
She put it in there.
He might be subtly keeping Sang Hyeon in check.
- My goodness.
- It's just the beginning.
- Mind if I just wash it with water?
- Not at all.
Thank you.
Oh, he saw that. He saw what happened.
Oh, it worked.
- Hello.
- Go on in.
I see you guys are here already.
- Hello.
- It feels like we're late.
- Exactly.
Can we just sit down?
You can sit on the floor or on the sofa.
Please sit anywhere you want. We did so.
It's nice.
(Mu Jin is the last to join them.)
(Glancing)
(He goes past Ji Won...)
(and sits next to Bon Hee.)
Was that necessary?
He went so far from everyone to sit next to her.
(Satisfied)
Yes.
She seems happy. Bon Hee must be happy.
(Of course, she is.)
May I ask your names, please?
I'm Kim Mu Jin.
- Mu Jin? Oh, I see.
- Yes, Kim Mu Jin.
That's why his keyword was "well-organized."
- Right?
- Yes.
The one who wanted to have meat.
- Yes, that's him.
- "Well-organized."
I'm Ji Won.
- What's your full name?
- I'm Park Ji Won.
What is your name?
I'm Kim Sang Hyeon.
- Sang Hyeon?
- Yes.
The puppy-like one.
- Oh, "Golden Retriever?"
- Oh, you all know our keywords.
I'm Park Sang Won.
Sang Won...
Park Sang Won...
(Awkward)
- We should let them in.
- Oh, hello.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Let's all sit down for now.
- He was watching her.
They finally met one another. They all gathered now.
What were you doing?
- We were introducing ourselves.
- Just now.
Hello. I am Kim Hyeon Jun.
I am Kim Yeong Gyeong. It's nice to meet you all.
It's nice to meet you.
(The older women and the younger men finally gathered.)
But they didn't seem to be much older than me.
I think they're only a few years older than me.
I didn't get that kind of feeling.
Like they were much older than me.
To me, they didn't seem to be a lot older than me.
(The story of the older women and the younger men begins.)
To me, the ladies don't seem any older...
than the early 30s.
- They don't seem that old.
- I agree.
I can't even guess how old they are.
- You don't have any idea?
- No.
Let me remind you. Two of them...
- have a twelve-year age gap.
- I'm worried.
That will cause a huge stir.
- Right. I think it will.
- My point exactly.
There's a lot of stuff here. Can I sit here?
Yes, of course.
I have no clue.
But I think...
that all the guys have a job.
(Laughing)
Being younger than you doesn't mean they have no job.
(As an older woman, she was worried about it.)
They all seem very young.
Right.
They must be in their late 20s..
or early 30s.
You know...
They all seem to be around the same age as me.
I heard they were older than us,
but they don't feel so much older than me.
Right. Don't I look even older than them?
Perhaps, you're the youngest of all.
- Oh, gosh.
- That's possible.
I don't want a man who's 188cm tall to address me like a big brother.
That's possible.
Clearly, both the men and the women...
are very sensitive about the age.
The guys seem rather excited about what could happen.
But the ladies seem more worried than excited.
- Right.
- Yes, I think so too.
Shall we start preparing food?
(Sang Hyeon and Sang Won are preparing a move-in party.)
When this show airs,
my parents will probably scold me.
"You never do any house chores."
I was thinking the same thing. "Why wouldn't you do it at home?"
Exactly. They'll say I'm doing house chores actively...
to impress the girls.
You can tell they're on the younger side...
by the conversation they're having.
They're worried if they might upset their parents.
(Sang Hyeon and Sang Won prepared...)
(the Yeon House move-in party.)
- Come down to the first floor.
- Okay.
Shall we bring 1 bottle of red wine and 1 bottle of white wine?
- Sounds good.
- Hello.
(The older women and the younger men will be together...)
Thank you.
(on their first night at Yeon House.)
Maybe we can open it without a wine opener.
I was right. We don't need an opener.
I think we need one for this bottle. Or not?
Some of them could be flustered in that situation.
The ladies are watching him.
- Oh, no.
- All eyes are on him.
"All right. Let's see how you do it."
Eight eyes are watching him.
(Pressured)
You can start without me.
I'll take my time and open it.
(Sang Won is struggling to open the wine bottle.)
- Goodness.
- Oh, boy.
(Pulling it upward)
(Flustered)
(The wine cork is broken.)
Did he open it the wrong way?
Oh, no.
He's cute.
He made the cork disappear instead of the day.
I can relate to that...
because I've never opened a wine bottle before.
Men around my age...
rarely choose wine when we have a drink.
- I see.
- Right. That makes sense.
(Oh, that makes sense.)
- We have an emergency.
- Oh, my gosh.
- It broke inside the bottle.
- Really?
This is bad. We might not be able to drink this.
You should rotate it more.
(Ji Won helps Sang Won, who's flustered.)
All the way down.
It's supposed to come out. Why won't it work?
- Shall I bring another one?
- I'll bring another bottle.
Let's drink something else.
- Anything?
- Anything would do. Thank you.
(He came to the kitchen to get a new bottle of wine.)
I feel bad.
- It's okay. That happens.
- It happens.
It's not a big deal.
It's okay.
Hang on. Please don't comfort me.
I feel like I caused big trouble. I wasn't feeling that way.
Would any of these do?
Let's drink this one.
This is a sweet, fruity type.
- A fruity type?
- Yes.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know either.
- It says "sweet."
- "Sweet?"
"Sweet."
(When you don't know, choose something sweet.)
Thank you for bringing the wine. Shall we drink it?
Yes, let's drink it.
- It's good to meet you all.
(They start their first evening at Yeon House with wine.)
(Impressed)
(The older women enjoy the wine.)
(Exclaiming)
(Nodding)
(Meanwhile, the younger men...)
(Frowning)
(Looking around nervously)
The guys don't seem to like it.
He seems confused.
(Coughing)
"Well-organized!"
You should drink it in a well-organized manner.
(Gazing)
Like I said, things like that make him cute.
The ladies look at him like they find him cute.
(He has a piece of apple to get rid of the aftertaste.)
- Isn't the wine good?
- This wine is refreshing.
- Yes, it's better than I expected.
- Right.
- He's cute. Yes.
- He's so cute. Isn't he cute?
(With a fresh mindset, he has another sip.)
"Why would anyone drink this?"
He drank wine and reacted as if it were soju.
Tell us honestly. I understand that he looks cute,
but isn't it a little frustrating to watch him like that?
Exactly. That's what I was curious about.
- But he's Mu Jin.
- Gosh, seriously.
He's Mr. Yes.
He's invincible.
How much alcohol can you drink at once?
I can drink up to half a bottle of soju.
It's true.
I can drink one glass of soju-beer cocktail.
- One glass?
Yes. One glass.
- You're unbelievable.
- My goodness.
Yes. About that much.
You probably shouldn't be drinking then.
Right. My face is starting to burn.
My face is burning a little.
Yes.
The girls are surprised.
But I drink soju quite well.
I can handle 2 to 2 and a half bottles of soju.
You can drink.
I can drink about 1 and a half to 2 bottles.
But I am not a big fan of soju,
so I rarely drink soju.
- What do you like to drink then?
- Which liquor then?
I like whiskey.
You must drink really well, I mean you must love to drink.
(Thinking)
It tastes like wood, though.
- Whiskey is expensive.
- But you can't drink.
Do you like it?
- She adores him.
- He's adorable.
- She adores him, whatever he says.
He says whiskey tastes like wood.
It tastes like wood, though.
It tastes like wood?
He's the serious type.
I know.
Their eyes locked.
(Bon Hee and Sang Hyeon lock eyes with each other.)
She's staring right at me.
I guess I am sitting directly across you.
I was trying hard not to lock eyes with you.
(Looking)
I...
Sang Hyeon is cute.
(Mu Jin was quietly watching.)
That can't be helped.
You got something here.
- Can I get it for you?
- What is it?
You got something here.
- Can I get it for you?
- What is it?
- Dust.
- Dust?
I see.
I couldn't stop looking at it.
(I couldn't stop looking at it.)
That's like, "I can't stop looking at you."
Bon Hee's attention is now on Mu Jin.
It's the first day, and he'd say something like that?
What's wrong with that?
(Infinitely amazed)
- "I couldn't stop looking at it?"
- That's lovely.
(He's the fearless younger man.)
- Stop it.
- I can't help it.
You got something here.
- Can I get it for you?
- What is it?
- Dust.
- Dust?
I see.
I couldn't stop looking at it.
(I couldn't stop looking at it.)
I heard you had to pick...
a keyword in the beginning.
Among the keywords...
What was it at the bottom?
- "Well-organized?"
- Yes.
He looked hard-working and responsible.
That's why I picked it.
She let me have it.
- Did she?
- So he could've had...
the first date with Ji Won.
What was your keyword?
- What?
- What was it?
It was "the day flies by."
- But he didn't make it happen.
- It's midnight now.
The day flew by.
Shall we drink?
Should we go back to what we were discussing?
For the gents, it would be older women.
For the ladies, it would be younger men.
Do you have an experience of dating one?
I've dated older and younger women.
But the two I dated for the longest period were older.
And we had a stable relationship.
It made me think I am a good match with an older woman.
I mostly dated...
men younger than me.
So I don't have any prejudices against younger men.
(Turning)
Mu Jin?
I don't really care about age.
But I got along better with older women.
I don't care too much about the age though.
But I think older women were a better fit for me.
Why were they a better fit?
I don't know. The ones I got along well with...
just happened to be older than me.
I see.
I...
mostly dated older men.
I've dated a younger man once.
(Nodding)
But as I got...
older,
the level of maturity mattered more. It matters more now.
Yes. That's me.
I think I'm similar.
I've only experienced it once.
But age isn't a huge factor.
Having good conversations...
and sharing the same core values...
Those are more important to me.
The person I most recently dated was younger than me.
Even if I didn't end up in a relationship with all,
most of the people I've dated...
were younger than me.
It just happened naturally.
I've mostly dated someone younger or someone of my age.
Yes.
Well.
For me, this is a challenge.
It's not ideal...
to lie, so...
This is a challenge for me.
He hasn't dated many older women.
I guess so.
I guess that's why he was that anxious.
Sang Hyeon is different from the other participants.
His focus is not on who he likes at this point.
But it is on whether he will be able to have chemistry...
with an older woman.
He might be confused.
He said it was a challenge.
I think he might get very confused...
when their age gets revealed.
Is he that young?
- We got texts.
- Did we?
(They receive texts.)
I didn't get a text.
I think only the ladies got one.
In 15 minutes, send a love message...
to the person you are interested in.
Love QR code?
You can send anything to it.
It could be a message, an audio file, a photo, a video.
(But make it anonymous.)
(It's the day the men get to read the ladies' minds.)
(Who is...)
(in the ladies' hearts tonight?)
I got it.
No, let's leave it like this for now.
(After the party, the younger men are cleaning up.)
(Looking around)
(Ji Won hurriedly heads to the stairs.)
(Running up)
How do I do this?
She's thinking.
(Bon Hee heads to the stairs too.)
That's not easy. What will they send to the QR code?
(Spotting Ji Won)
(She retreats.)
(Spotting Bon Hee)
(She gets even further away.)
(Sighing)
Make up your mind.
- Time to use my head, is it?
- Do you have one?
Is there someone you're interested in?
(Curious)
(Sassy)
It's a secret.
Could it be not the one...
they went to pick up?
I think a lot of them have changed their minds.
- You think so?
- I do.
Are you the love-at-first-sight type of a person?
I am the love-at-first-sight type of a person.
Most men fall for the looks first...
- and then slowly get to know her.
- Right.
Is any of them your type?
- Among them?
- I won't ask who it is.
There is one.
(There is one.)
Is any of them your type?
Considering the first impression, there is someone who's my type.
(Who are the ladies...)
(that entered Sang Hyeon and Hyeon Jun's hearts?)
(The messages have been sent. Go to the Love QR Zone...)
(and check the ladies' hearts.)
It's here.
(Love QR Zone is...)
(where they get to check each other's feelings.)
(It's a place where you can check the feelings...)
(that were passed on through the QR code.)
(Hyeon Jun)
(When you scan your QR code,)
(you can check the feelings of the person...)
(who sent a message to you.)
(On the first day of Yeon House,)
(what kind of messages will the men receive?)
We have the Love QR Codes here too.
What?
(They can check the result through the QR codes here too.)
Who are you most curious about?
- Yes Mu Jin.
- Mu Jin?
Should I go check Mu Jin's?
- I'd love that.
- I'd love that too.
We are checking for the messages he received, right?
It's coming up.
It really works!
(They are the Love QR Codes of the participants!)
How many did he get?
(I won't tell you.)
I think Mu Jin would be popular.
(Yes?)
I think Golden Retriever would be popular.
Come on. Show us. We need to see it too.
Show us.
(Mu Jin is the first to come to the Love QR Zone.)
(Sighing)
(Nervous)
(The Love QR Code is placed in front of Mu Jin.)
(Did Mu Jin receive any love messages?)
(It will be continued shortly.)
(What kind of messages would his Love QR Code contain?)
(Two people have sent messages to your Love QR Code.)
- Two people.
- Two people. Goodness.
(Puzzled)
(What's the first message from the Love QR Code?)
It's a video.
(First Love QR message)
(First Love QR message is a video of the living room sofa.)
Who could it be?
(Tilting his head)
(How about the second Love QR message?)
(A photo of a green object?)
- What is that?
(Smiling)
I think I know one person clearly.
But I am not entirely sure who the other person is.
Could it be Ye Eun?
When we were drinking wine,
she was the one who could see me from that angle.
I would be shocked if it turned out to be Ye Eun.
I guess their eyes locked many times.
I didn't see that coming though.
(An unexpected result sends them into confusion.)
(Anxious)
(Sang Hyeon is the second person to check the Love QR Code.)
(Taking a deep breath)
I'm scared.
(He takes a deep breath...)
(and checks his Love QR Code.)
(Did anyone send a message to Sang Hyeon's Love QR Code?)
(One person has sent a message to your Love QR Code.)
(He received an image of a cat.)
(Will Sang Hyeon recognize the cat image?)
I really don't know. I'm puzzled.
(He couldn't figure out who the message was from.)
Wait.
What? That can't happen.
That's not it. I think he had been so nervous...
that he forgot everything.
He must've forgotten everything they talked about during the date.
It's clear that Ye Eun sent the message to Sang Hyeon.
They talked about dogs and cats so much.
- Right.
- We figured it out right away.
- Yes.
- But he can't figure it out.
- That's surprising, isn't it?
- It's surprising.
How can he not know it?
(Frustrated)
(With the mystery unsolved,)
(With the mystery unsolved, Sang Hyeon leaves the zone.)
(Sang Won enters the Love QR Zone.)
(For the first time, see who has feelings for you...)
(through the Love QR Code.)
(What kind of messages would Sang Won have received?)
What?
Who is it?
(Looks around)
(Tilts his head)
(Chuckles)
(What message did Sang Won receive through the Love QR Code?)
Two people?
(You have no message on your Love QR Code.)
(Poor Sang Won.)
What do we do?
(Tilts his head)
(Finding it hard to believe, he checks it once again.)
(The result is the same.)
He keeps refreshing the page, but he still doesn't have any.
Oh, dear.
(Trembles)
(What does this chuckle mean?)
I was frustrated.
I knew it could happen.
And I told myself that I shouldn't get disappointed.
But when it actually happened,
it hit me quite hard.
(After checking the Love QR Code, Sang Won became puzzled.)
It made me think I should approach them more seriously now.
- Oh, dear. He's adorable.
- Goodness.
He looks like he lost the world.
- He looks like he's in shock.
- He's shocked.
- He's very good-looking.
- Yes.
He's never experienced something like this, so he is flustered.
This is what seemed to have gone through his mind.
"Did this just happen to me?"
- That's how it felt.
- Right.
(The last one to check the Love QR Code is Hyeon Jun.)
(He checks the message on his Love QR Code...)
(for the first time.)
(One person has sent a message to your Love QR Code.)
I wonder what he received.
(Hyeon Jun received one photo.)
What's that? It's pasta and a wine opener.
What?
Is it their height difference?
- No.
- No?
- Their height difference?
- Why pasta and a wine opener then?
It's difficult.
(Does Hyeon Jun know who the Love QR message is from?)
I have no clue about who sent the message.
I have no idea. I have no clue.
What's your favorite food?
I like pasta.
- You like pasta.
- I love pasta.
I like pasta too.
You like pasta?
- Pasta.
- They had that conversation.
I thought perhaps he might remember the things...
we talked about earlier.
Oh, dear. They talked about it.
She looked for it and took a picture of it.
She did.
(Yeong Gyeong sent a photo of Hyeon Jun's favorite, pasta.)
He should've known.
Poor Yeong Gyeong.
(Ye Eun sent an image of a cat to Sang Hyeon.)
I am cat-like.
Right.
Do you like someone who looks like a cat?
Yes. I like someone who is cat-like.
(The cat-like Ye Eun expressed herself with the cat image.)
- They had a long conversation too.
- I know.
Things aren't going to be easy for this couple.
(The Love QR message Bon Hee sent...)
(is a framed picture.)
What color do you like?
Well, green, I think? Kind of like a dark green.
Oh, a dark green.
(She didn't forget that Mu Jin likes dark green.)
Honestly, it's not easy to remember stuff like that.
- Right.
- Yes.
It means that the guy keeps lingering in her mind.
(And Ji Won also...)
(chooses Mu Jin.)
I chose Mu Jin.
He sat next to me when I was sitting in the first-floor living room.
His gaze was so soft.
I want to try talking to him.
(They finish checking the Love QR Codes amid confusion.)
I can't even imagine...
- what we'll do from tomorrow.
- Are they roommates, perhaps?
Going on dates for seven days?
- I haven't been on many dates.
- I can't even imagine.
Really?
- Are they?
- They happen to be roommates too.
Was there someone who caught your attention?
(Nodding)
- Really?
- Just someone I met today...
- Me too.
- Was there someone?
There was someone I wanted to talk to a bit more.
That's good.
- Tomorrow...
- That's much better than...
not being curious about anyone.
Gosh, it will be awkward if they're roommates.
They turned out to be roommates.
- Do you know what will happen?
- What will happen?
It becomes so interesting.
- From the viewer's perspective?
- Yes.
(Late at night, Mu Jin gets a text message.)
(Kim Mu Jin, you've received 2 Love QR Codes. You get a Love Benefit.)
A benefit.
(Check the info of someone you want to know about in the Secret Room.)
- The room that was locked earlier.
- The Secret Room?
Didn't they say they'll get hints that help you guess someone's age?
(Mu Jin gets the key to the Secret Room tonight.)
(Mu Jin is the first to check the Secret Room.)
(Open the drawer and guess the age of the person you're curious about.)
(The information you learn must remain secret.)
And you have to keep it to yourself?
Will knowing the age of someone you're interested in...
be a good thing or a bad thing?
You actually don't know about that.
(Who is Mu Jin's heart heading towards?)
- Is that how it ends?
- What? Right here?
(Is this the end?)
Gosh, dating shows are always like this.
I know because I've experienced this a lot.
Yes.
(Meanwhile, in Hyeon Jun and Sang Hyeon's room)
Hyeon Jun, you're also not good at actively approaching someone, right?
I'm not good at it if there are lots of people.
I see.
But when it's just me and her, I think I'm better at it.
But are you confident that you can get someone alone with you?
No.
I just felt like you and I have similar personalities.
Kind of introverted...
So, you're an INFP. I'm an INFJ.
- Just the J and P are different.
- I know.
I hope there isn't any competition.
That's too grand a dream, right?
- Suddenly doing push-ups?
- Suddenly?
(Suddenly doing push-ups?)
How much competition is he going to get into?
(Is he doing strength training for tomorrow's competition?)
Oh, man.
(The younger guy doesn't like competition but prepares for it.)
He's seriously here to compete against himself.
(He even works out in the outdoor gym in the rain.)
(Huffing and puffing)
(Will there really be no competition as Sang Hyeon hoped for?)
(Men, please ask someone out on a date within 5 minutes.)
(The younger men stand up right away without any hesitation.)
(Would you like to go on a date?)
(Do you want to go out on a date today?)
(I'd like that.)
(Why did you choose me?)
(You're so pretty.)
(I'll help you.)
(A sense of giddiness is reawakened for the first time in a while.)
(Older women aren't all that bad.)
(Is this what dating an older woman is like?)
(You're so adorable.)
(How many women do you want to get to know more?)
(Let's put the serious conversation aside for now and just eat.)
(I just didn't feel all that great.)
(I couldn't hide my emotions, so I had a lot on my mind.)
I don't know.
Dramaday.me