♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  Love  ♫
[Cupid's Kitchen]
[Episode 11]
Victor must have told you. That's just great.
Everyone knows my hiding place now.
Yes. Victor is worried about you.
I'm also worried about you.
Is there really a possibility that Oliver can't regain his taste buds?
They still can't find the cause?
It's very difficult. I found a specialist for the treatment.
Everyone thinks that it could be a rare allergy
resulting in the death of nerve cells.
Then, what could it be?
It's very hard to figure out.
He lost his sense of taste about seven months ago.
In terms of the timeline, it should be
when London‘s Yuxuan just got 3 stars,
or in Shanghai when he was in the preparation stage.
So...
Oh, right.
Is there anything in these past 6 months
that he just started using and uses frequently?
Such as?
Such as...
Such as a shampoo or lotion
or perfume. Things with fragrance.
The other things are used by other people too. The essential oil is used by only him.
He has always liked to use aromatherapy oils to aid sleep.
He has maintained this habit for three years already.
I buy it for him from a friend. I also use it.
I'll send you one tomorrow to test.
Okay, but please make sure that you give me an unopened one.
Okay, of course.
Stop drinking. I know that you're very stressed lately.
I can handle even more stress. I'm just in a bad mood.
I remember three years ago
when I visited both of you in London, I feel that at that time
you were much happier.
Yes, but too bad we can't go back.
You and Qianfan are very competitive people.
In order for Yuxuan to get 3 stars quickly, you both...
But I really don't understand.
What's the point of you two wanting so many stars?
There is for Oliver.
For me, without love,
the stars mean absolutely nothing.
- I can still drink.
- You're drunk.
I'm not. I'm not drunk at all. I'll feel better if I'm drunk.
You already drank 20 cups. You can't drink anymore.
I'll take you home.
Okay.
Little Bun, did you burn something when you were baking, right?
Sister Nina, you don't need to use so many fresh flowers even if you are making fresh flower cake.
This is not for eating. Mr. Jiang wants to use the flower petals.
Flower petals? Not for eating?
Scattering them on the bed? Scattering them in the bathtub?
Jiang Qianfan has fallen in love?
What nonsense are you saying?
You are not in the kitchen upstairs, what are you doing here? How's the knife skill practice going?
Didn't you agree to make the party snacks with me?
Honey, rest assured. I will help you.
Honey needs your... h-help.
Did I say "Honey"?
Don't deny it. It's no fun if you are like that.
Why is your face red?
What nonsense are you talking about? I see... When I see you, why would my face be red?
It's red here and here.
My... that... is this... the heat of the oven. If you don't believe it, you can try.
I think you're too immersed in the acting.
Have your friends not eaten any good food before? Do you intend to greet them with these burnt things?
If you don't want me to make you lose face too terribly, then help me.
I'm busy now.
If you help me today, then you are the world's best head chef.
I'll give you a 15-minute massage.
- Then, I can act like a pig, dog—
- Stop.
Save it first. I don't have the mood today.
Little cabbage
in the yellow field.
(T/N: It's the first line of a Chinese folk song "Little Cabbage")
Go get some baguette and bring it over.
What for?
Teaching you to make Bruschetta. Easy, saves time, and delicious.
Okay!
♫  You are the stranger I want to know  ♫
♫  Don't let me go  ♫
♫  I will do little tricks for you  ♫
♫  Only for you  ♫
♫  You are the stranger I want to know  ♫
♫  From the other world  ♫
♫  I will do silly things for you  ♫
♫ We played the note of love ♫
♫ Like work of art  ♫
♫  We sing a song for love  ♫
♫ Listen to your heart ♫
♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  It makes me grow  ♫
♫  I will do little tricks for you  ♫
♫  Only for love ♫
♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  It makes me grow  ♫
♫  I will do silly things for you  ♫
Why is it that when he's beside me, I can do it fast and well?
I can't do it when I watch videos.
He has a magical aura that is especially reassuring.
Could I be relying on him?
I can't rely on him. I need him to rely on me.
Oh heavens! What am I thinking?
I like Song Yiran.
♫  We sing a song for love  ♫
♫ Listen to your heart, to your heart  ♫
Why is my heart beating a bit fast? No, no, no.
I need to calm down. But still...
want to take a look. Just one look.
Whenever he makes a strong action, I feel
like through the chef uniform,
I can see his muscles on his arm.
Why are his muscle lines so good-looking?
Like the Ancient Greek sculptures.
God. Your recent arrangements are making me a little fascinated.
I have no way to repay it. I can only repay you by eating more good food.
So beautiful.
Know how to do it now?
Do the rest yourself. I need to go out for a while.
Have fun tonight.
Won't you go with me?
I have something I need to do.
Who is it?
Express delivery.
Wait for a moment.
Hello. What is this?
Air-flown from London. A cake.
Fridge it quickly. It's cold-chain transported.
Mr. Jiang doesn't eat sweet stuff.
That I don't know. Sign here, please.
Okay.
Here.
Thank you.
Sister Nina, let me do it. Put this inside.
- I think it needs to be put in the fridge.
- Okay.
Be careful.
- What is this?
- It was sent by London's Yuxuan.
- Whose birthday is it today?
- Mr. Jiang's birthday.
Everyone in London must be missing him.
Today is Mr. Jiang's birthday?
He didn't say anything about it.
He doesn't celebrate it.
He doesn't like to celebrate birthdays?
Is there anyone who dislikes birthdays?
If he doesn't like birthdays,
why does he take flowers to visit Elise?
Ask him yourself about this.
Braised Eel and Pork. Of course, the eel is segmented.
This is a traditional local dish.
It is Jiangsu cuisine.
For this dish, the crucial thing
is to highlight four words.
Smooth, tender, fresh, and fragrant.
Can you remember that?
I'm talking to you.
Sorry.
I wasn't paying attention.
Tell me, what were you thinking about?
Something on your mind?
No.
Really?
When you want to talk, I might not want to listen.
No, I'll talk.
Mr. Huang, I'm in love.
Your heart pines for someone, but nothing is assured.
Is it that obvious?
I was also young before.
I know. When I was your age,
there is no pretty woman in the world that I didn't love.
I wasn't picky.
Mr. Huang, I couldn't tell
that you were actually a Romeo. Quick, tell me,
how can I get the girl that I like?
First, be sincere.
I am. I only have her in my heart.
Second, do what she likes.
I'll remember it.
Did you use these two points to get the girls you liked back then?
No.
What do you mean? Didn't you just say you liked all the beauties and weren't picky?
But those girls didn't like me.
What's worse is that the girls I liked
had suitors. I was too lazy to compete.
So I remained single until now.
I don't want to be like you. I don't want to miss my chance with Xiaoyu.
And from what I observe, she doesn't seem to have any suitors.
She's just very difficult to deal with.
Which Xiaoyu are you talking about?
- Boris'?
- Yes.
This Boris,
I met him at an event in Hong Kong.
He had a sullen look as if the whole world owed him.
He even wanted to compete with everyone he met.
Then he met me, so he insisted on challenging me. He even wanted to do a live broadcast.
I didn't accept it.
No wonder Xiaoyu looks sullen all the time.
I wonder what she was thinking when she chose her mentor.
Mr. Huang, what should I do?
Pester her. If a flower won't bloom, then squat in front of it,
until it blooms.
Xiaoyu, Xiaoyu! Come here!
Why are you everywhere?
I guessed that you just finished your class.
This is for you.
What is it? Don't tell me it's jewelry?
You want jewelry?
I'm sorry. That's too early to ask for it.
Too early? I don't even want it!
No, no. Sorry. Sorry. I just don't have a glib tongue.
Does this look like you?
I'm sorry. What did you say just now, I didn't hear it clearly?
The Chinese people are each born under a zodiac animal sign.
Some are snakes, while others are tigers.
You are a tiger.
So you are saying that I am a tigress?
Yes!
Take back your gift and get out of my face!
What's wrong?
Scram!
Okay. Sure.
Then...
See you tomorrow.
Take care. I won't see you off.
No problem. I'll walk home.
He said that he and Elise are just colleagues.
Why does he need to go out with her all the time, then?
He didn't even inform me.
Moreover, it is on his birthday. What's going on?
Lin Kesong, what has it got to do with you?
Jiang Qianfan and you are only linked by culinary skills.
Why would you care about his past?
My dear, you're here. Come in.
How many people are here?
Come in first.
Wow! This is awesome!
Great!
Excuse me.
- How's the taste?
- Old Lin,
be honest. You didn't make this bread, right?
I sliced the bread, okay?
I knew it.
Song Yiran, you're so annoying.
Where is Chef Jiang?
He has something on.
That's great.
Montgomery.
It's been a while.
How are you?
Back then, if you saw me like this,
you'd get mad and kick me out.
You would tell me to get out
and come back when I feel better.
You said
that cooking must make people happy
and joyful.
Therefore, people who cook
should be happy.
But after you left,
no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't get one step closer to you.
Sometimes...
Sometimes, I would even get scared. That fear
is almost like death.
It's much harder than life,
but it's lesser
than death.
I tried the method that you told me,
to empty myself.
Maybe I'd feel better,
when my heart is empty.
But it didn't work.
I couldn't even get close to who I was before,
the one that loves life
and being adventurous.
However... Good things happened too.
Even when things were bad,
I met someone recently.
She's quite special.
Her presence
at least made up
for some regrets in my life.
I'll be all right.
Am I that person? Mr. Montgomery,
I'm visiting you with Qianfan again.
I've only got to meet you at your funeral, but I want to thank you,
for allowing me to meet the most important man in my life.
Although he doesn't think so.
You are very important in my life.
No, Oliver. I want to be the only one.
We are just working partners.
You two are here as expected.
I didn't expect you to come.
I've always remembered what this day is.
- What are you doing?
- What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Nothing? Hurry inside, then. Everyone is waiting for you. Let's go.
Hey! I'll walk on my own.
♪  Happy Birthday to you  ♪
Happy Birthday!
Did I guess your age correctly?
You got it right.
I'm seven years younger than you. Thanks.
Wait.
If you don't eat some cake here, you'll be breaking my heart.
You should know that this is the first time I'm being nice to you.
Forget it, Boris.
- Elise!
- You're up to no good.
Listen up, Qianfan doesn't hold a grudge because he is a forgiving person,
but I am not. You messed with Yuxuan twice. You still owe us.
Who wants to eat your lousy cake.
Miss Quentin, this is between Jiang Qianfan and me. It's none of your business!
Qianfan, it's not like you to let a woman shield you.
What are you afraid of?
What makes you think so?
Okay. Let me ask you, then.
With your professionalism,
how can you just randomly take the Evil Dragon Princess as your apprentice?
I know the official answer given by Elise,
but you and I both know that it's a lie.
Because I know you too well. I know you better than I know myself.
For you, winning is everything.
By accepting Lin Kesong as your apprentice, you know you won't win.
It's uncharacteristic of you unless something else
is more important than winning the competition.
Enough. Bravo, Boris! You have such an imagination.
Even if Qianfan has a problem, I'm here to help him.
There's no need for an apprentice. What a joke!
I want to hear you say it.
Fine, I'll tell you.
You're the reason that I took part in the competition. Even more so, you're the reason
I've accepted Lin Kesong as my apprentice. It's too easy to beat you.
Satisfied now?
You want to make me mad and lose my sense of judgment?
It won't be that easy.
Whatever.
Elise, let's go.
Boris cares more about you than himself.
I wonder how much he knows.
He is probably just guessing. Else, he wouldn't bake the cake.
Thankfully, your quick wit got me out of trouble.
We are an entity, so don't thank me.
Only my mother, Dr. Xie, and I know. Our lips are sealed.
As for Nina and Li Yan,
can we do something so that they won't get suspicious?
Don't do anything. For now, business as usual is the best way.
Without evidence, he can't announce it at will.
Don't worry. I have Lin Kesong.
I'm creating the next season's dishes.
So, Lin Kesong is the first tester.
Oliver, why are you so calm?
Rage and disappointment won't solve anything.
I mean, what if this problem can be solved?
How?
Pray for forgiveness. Think about your sins.
Maybe God will give you a chance.
What sins do I have? I don't need forgiveness.
You have a fever now.
It's okay, I'm fine. I just feel tired.
I'll take you home.
Crap. I forgot.
- What's wrong?
- I mustn't drink.
How can you not drink at a party? Then why did you come?
No. Mr. Jiang said no alcohol during my apprenticeship.
- What are you learning?
- Culinary skills. I'm about to enter a competition.
It's quite late. I have class tomorrow morning.
Have fun. I'm heading back.
- I'll take you home, then!
- Wait!
You can't go. The party is only halfway through.
Song Yiran, you're a bore.
You can't leave.
Let me go. You're hurting me.
- Song Yiran.
- Fine. I won't drag you, then.
Anyway, be good and just sit down.
If you go before dawn, you aren't my friend.
Come on, continue.
Seriously?
I've got it here.
Here. Drink some hot water.
I wanted to cook something, but you have nothing here.
Have some hot water first. I'll call Junbin.
No, I'm fine.
Just stay with me.
It's late. I won't stay. I'll leave. Rest well.
Oliver, wait!
Stay.
Elise.
Don't go. Don't leave me.
We agreed to be working partners.
Don't you miss me?
We tried, but it didn't work out.
So, let me go, all right?
I can't.
I love you. What about you?
I've told you before, what we had isn't love.
This is not love?
We were together,
then you stole my heart and broke up with me. Six months later, you said you didn't love me.
Do you know how hurtful that was?
It was like taking a knife and slashing at my wound.
Only honesty can solve the problem. I never intended to hurt you.
When you're in pain, I feel bad too, but what can I do?
I...
I can only tell you
that you deserve someone better, and it's not me.
Have a good rest. I'm leaving.
♫  I just wait for this moment  ♫
♫  Feel the air that you're breathing  ♫
♫ This feeling with the loneliness ♫
♫  I tell myself there is nothing bad  ♫
[Thank you for putting up with me for so long.]
[You're as beautiful as a goddess.]
[You deserve better.]
♫  Seeing something happened  ♫
♫  How can I escape  ♫
♫  You said don't be afraid  ♫
Jiang Qianfan is so handsome!
He isn't a chef. He's a model!
Jiang Qianfan?
- He is so handsome!
- I was just telling her
whoever becomes his girlfriend
must have good karma.
Hold on, you two. I'll make you jump.
Kesong, come here.
Kesong is the lucky girl.
Heavens! Kesong, did you conquer him?
It's over. My heart can't take it.
No! He's not my boyfriend!
Yes, yes, yes. Don't pretend.
How could it be? You two were so sweet when I saw both of you together.
Chu Ting, you misunderstood.
He was just kidding that day. He's not my boyfriend.
Really?
Yes.
I must leave.
Must you?
Okay. Go before that fool finds out, or he'll make a scene.
- I'm leaving now!
- Hurry up and drink!
Thanks to those gossip girls
who randomly searched for Jiang Qianfan online, an important piece of information was found.
Turns out that four years ago today, Montgomery died in a sea accident.
No wonder he is so depressed.
Why did you leave? Come back!
Stop messing around.
You're back.
Mr. Jiang, you are back.
I know what day is today.
Are you all right?
Am I a very lousy person?
No, of course, you are not.
You're too young. There's something you don't understand.
I'm very experienced. I watched a lot of TV dramas when I was young.
Did you have fun at the party?
Well...
At least the food was good, right?
Of course. They finished it in five seconds.
Ten seconds. Five seconds was a bit exaggerated.
Good to hear.
Go. Get ready to sleep. I'm going to bed.
He appears moody but values personal loyalty.
When I was little and feeling down, my dad would cook these noodles for me.
They are my favorite.
First, stirfry the meat in some oil. Then add
the mushrooms and greens. Season and thicken the soup.
After taking the noodles out of the pot, it is crucial to rinse them in cold water.
This will cool the noodles and preserve the chewy texture.
Finally,
add a little vinegar. Perfect. Dig in!
How's the taste?
I'll add the comments for you. The aroma of the meat
and garlic combined with the mushrooms
warm you up from the tip of the tongue to the heart.
It's so touching.
What a pity.
Adding onion and garlic in hot oil is correct, but the time was too short.
The fragrance was not fully released.
- And this shredded pork—
- If you don't want to eat it, I will eat it.
I didn't say I wouldn't eat it.
Is it tasty?
I can't take this anymore. I cooked, but I didn't get to eat.
You are so uncivilized.
My mom said
you must slurp when you eat noodles. They'll taste better.
Is that so?
Let me try.
Delicious.
How come your slurp is louder than mine?
You try.
Slurp.
Watch me.
♫  You are the stranger I want to know  ♫
♫  Don't let me go  ♫
♫  I will do little tricks for you  ♫
♫  Don't bury your secret heart  ♫
♫  Show them who you are  ♫
♫  We sing a song for love  ♫
♫ Listen to your heart, to your heart  ♫