♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  Love  ♫
[Cupid's Kitchen]
[Episode 32]
Old Xie, come in.
- Mom.
- Good morning, Madam Quentin.
Junbin, it's hard on you that we asked you to come so early in the morning.
I should do it. It's my honor.
Yes, yes, that's what I think too.
My Sister is upstairs. Do you want to go see her?
Is she up yet?
She probably hasn't slept.
Go ahead. Keep her company.
She is in a bad mood. She'll have to face the media in the afternoon.
I worry that she did what she shouldn't have done impulsively.
She really needs you.
Rest assured, I'll do my best.
Breakfast is coming!
Hurry and go upstairs to eat breakfast with my sister.
Okay. Leave it to me.
I'll go up then.
- Morning.
Thomas.
You've worked hard.
It truly is hard.
Yesterday, I just fell asleep
but got woken up by my assistant's phone call. Then I hurried to go to the airport.
I didn't buy coffee for you. I know you can't drink it.
It's a waste to buy it anyway, but I have to drink it.
Because I know I'll be busy with a lot of stuff today.
Can you please help me
say sorry to Madam Baer?
Sorry?
You have to apologize by yourself.
You are right.
My announcement has been released by Yuxuan's official account.
I saw it.
Does it look bad?
Very much so.
Qianfan,
I know that
you are a conceited and aloof person.
But the three words, Jiang Qianfan, to me
has always been a guarantee of quality. It's a golden banner.
But I couldn't have expected that
you are now connected with dishonesty.
Do you know that this is really scary?
I do.
Have you made contact with Boris?
Of course, also with Lin Xiaoyu.
It's by procedure.
Qianfan, when your sense of taste developed a problem,
you should have told me immediately.
Do you know that you've
made it very difficult for me?
I'm truly sorry.
It's useless for you to apologize now.
But I do have a question to ask you.
If Boris hadn't exposed this matter,
how long were you going to keep deceiving?
If possible,
a whole lifetime.
Don't you think that's exhausting?
I'm not qualified to be exhausted.
On my way over here, I kept thinking,
what would I do if this were to happen to me?
Would I choose to tell or not tell?
If I were to tell,
what would I say?
But I thought more about it later.
I think my final decision would be like yours.
I would choose not to tell,
because no one wants to show their incapability to other people,
especially someone so conceited like you.
You must understand that
you are a mentor.
When your body has such a serious problem,
you are responsible and obligated
to tell me or the entire committee immediately.
The competition is serious,
but it's also cruel at the same time.
I know, that's why I'm willing to accept any punishment.
But this matter has nothing to do with Lin Kesong.
Can she continue to compete?
It's not up to me anymore.
I'll have to meet with the six members
of the committee.
At that meeting, we'll see how they
will make a final decision.
Okay.
Qianfan, the competition is a temporary moment,
but it's a part of your life.
Have you ever thought, if this matter continues on,
what the eventual consequence would be?
Elise has already made arrangements.
This afternoon, there will be a press conference at Yuxuan.
Do you have an explanation?
None.
I don't want to lie anymore.
Usually this amount of alkali when eaten,
will be very bitter for people.
Blu, open the door. It's me.
This bowl is Jiang Qianfan's
Old Huang, morning.
Go fishing with me.
When we return, I'll teach you Sweet and Sour Live Fish.
(T/N: a famous dish that is rarely eaten by most Chinese)
Sorry, Old Huang.
I'm not in the mood.
I know that's what you'd say.
I'm not asking if you are in the mood.
This is teaching you.
Old Huang,
I feel awful.
It's like
eating flies.
I understand you.
You are a good kid.
But you didn't know she would be like Bao Si.
(T/N: famously beautiful but despised concubine that caused the downfall of Western Zhou)
Child, I've suffered this kind of loss too.
You like a girl when you are young.
Actually, you like what you imagined her to be, not who she really is.
When the dream is over,
I suffered and felt awful.
But all of this shall pass.
Come on, go fishing with me.
Let's go.
Uncle. Uncle.
- No.
- All of you move aside.
Y-Your back!
Stay calm. Be careful with your back.
Don't block me. Don't block me.
Don't get impulsive. Watch out your back.
You'd hurt your back.
Don't get impulsive.
- Don't get impulsive.
- Don't hold me back!
Be careful of your back.
Dad.
Why are you doing so early in the morning?
Aren't you ashamed to ask?
Great! I raised you for 20-some years, but didn't see
that you would be repaying kindness with revenge. I'm going to kill you!
Uncle, don't, don't!
Oh, goodness!
It's about Jiang Qianfan, right?
You know already?
Dad, we need to make this clear.
I'm not repaying kindness with revenge. I'm upholding justice!
Disgusting!
Upholding justice?
You are tearing down the bridge after you crossed the river.
You are smiling with hidden blades.
Dad, calm down.
I exposed a cheater. What did I do wrong?
What did Mr. Jiang cheat you?
What did he cheat you?
He was kindhearted to help us here. What's the result?
You set him up!
You are using a knife to pierce my heart. Don't you know?
Are you even human? Are you fit to have Lin as your surname?
If I'm not fit to use Lin as my surname? What should be my surname? I'll take Mom's surname!
Get out!
I can't afford to raise this white-eyed wolf.
(T/N: means traitor)
This is not your home. You, get out!
I'll leave now!
Sister Yu! Sister Yu!
- Sister Yu.
- Xiaoyu!
- Uncle.
- Slowly. Slowly.
- Get a cup of water.
Slowly. Slowly.
Who's that?
Hello. I'm a reporter from Chefs Circle.
Is Mr. Jiang at home? We have a few questions to ask.
Mr. Jiang isn't home!
Why did she hang up? What's going on?
It's previously arranged. What do we do?
Mr. Jiang, don't come home right now. Many reporters have shown up at the house.
Okay, got it.
Don't worry.
Hey.
Get some time to rest.
When you wake up, start training. Okay?
I'm hanging up now.
It appears that you don't think you will be disqualified from the competition?
Even if we're disqualified, we shouldn't stop training. Isn't that right?
I'm not concerned that you'll be in trouble.
I'm just afraid that, if you get into trouble,
you won't use the correct method to resolve it.
Go get busy.
You've come at just the right time.
Jiang Qianfan is holding a press conference.
What's the matter?
Who hit you?
Since you're kicked out,
you should sleep comfortably.
Treat yourself well.
When the press conference starts, remember to wake me up.
Fang Chun notified me to come.
- I didn't expect such a hard rain.
- Still haven't seen anyone.
A car is coming! A car is coming!
A car is coming!
Mr. Jiang!
- Mr. Jiang!
Mr. Jing! Please answer our question.
When did you start losing your sense of taste?
Everyone, listen to me.
The rain is heavy. Let's go inside to talk.
- Mr. Jiang!
Everyone, please come in.
Okay.
Put the umbrellas and raincoats over there.
Put your bags anywhere.
I've already notified my partner, Miss Quentin,
to hold the press conference to start in one hour, at 10 am.
Take it easy.
Elise,
change the press conference to be at my house. Tell everyone it's at 10 am.
Oliver, this won't do. I've already arranged some reporters who have a good relationship with us
to come to Yuxuan at three o'clock this afternoon.
I've already notified the staff to come to Yuxuan early.
You are too sudden in doing it this way.
It's too late. They are already waiting in the living room.
Hurry and come over.
Do you want to watch me change clothes?
No, it's not that.
I was going to ask you a question.
It's not necessary now.
I made some snack upstairs. I'll go get them.
I don't need you to appease them for my sake.
I'm not appeasing them.
Let's not discuss this topic. See you upstairs in five minutes.
- Are you teaching me how to cook now?
- Yes.
Oliver, what time is it now? Why are you acting rashly based on feelings?
You've made a mess of my plan!
So what that the media were at your front door?
Is it that hard to tell them to leave?
They are not reporters that you know. What if they report nonsense,
or deliberately smear you? What will you do?
[See you at 10 am]
How can Oliver do this?
Elise,
I know that you are anxious. But we are already at this point.
Don't get fired up by anything.
I'm sure Oliver has his reason to do it this way.
Besides, it's still raining outside.
Why did he become so thoughtful for other people?
Isn't this good?
No, it's not good for right now.
Junbin, please go out. I need to change.
Okay.
Calm down.
This situation now is best described
as "Enemy at the Gate."
I can't imagine if it were me,
could I still cook with steady hands now?
I would have already lost my composure.
But this man's hands are still steady.
His breathing is still stable.
It's like none of the trouble exists.
Is it because cooking has allowed him to forget the whole world?
Or, is he using cooking to calm himself down?
I don't know.
This is unique.
Let's take some background shots first.
- Here, come here.
- Come here.
The lighting is good here.
It's fine. I can do it myself.
The parking is full here. I'll go park the car.
Okay.
[Come out]
Elise is here. I'll go bring her in.
Go ahead.
- Come on in.
- I want to talk to you.
What is it about?
Please disappear. Don't come back until after the press conference.
Why?
To protect this secret from being known to others.
Oliver and I have been very cautious,
like stepping on thin ice, and have been fine with it.
Who would have known that you'd ruin it in the end?
- I-I didn't do it on purpose.
- Don't deny, Lin Kesong.
You clearly knew that Oliver lost his sense of taste.
You also knew that your sister and Boris have bad intentions.
But you still took Oliver to such a risky environment.
Have I accused you wrongly?
I didn't know Xiaoyu would do something like this.
The unintentional person is the most scary. The press conference today is really important.
I cannot allow any mistakes. It's not safe to have you here.
I am Mr. Jiang's apprentice.
If he doesn't tell me to leave, I'm not leaving.
Why?
Sorry.
What are you doing? What are you doing?
[Announcement: The press conference that was originally scheduled at 3 pm at Shanghai Yuxuan is moved up to 10 am at Mr. Jiang Qianfan's home.]
[We welcome media friends to attend.]
What?
Xiaoyu, wake up!
Hurry up!
Jiang Xianfan is being executed ahead of time.
Stop! What are you two doing?
Get up! Get up!
Don't fight anymore.
What time is it now? You're still fighting now?
Don't you know there are many reporters in the house?
Does this help Jiang Qianfan?
Give me the cellphone.
I'm going inside first to attract their attention.
You two come in quickly.
Sorry, I need everyone's attention, please.
I have a few things to say to everyone.
I am Mr. Jiang Qianfan's lead physician.
I am surnamed Xie. My name is Xie Junbin.
Qianfan's illness was just
diagnosed a few weeks ago by us.
But, because his illness progressed a little fast,
we haven't found an effective therapy to treat it.
Of course, I believe we will definitely cure him.
In a while, if you have any questions,
you can ask me directly, and I will answer each of your questions.
Thank you for your clothes.
Wait.
I'm sorry for just now.
I'm doing it for Oliver's sake. He is really having a hard time.
I should apologize to you, too.
I was too reckless just now.
I know that
you also wish the best for him.
You must feel bad too.
Yes.
I feel bad too.
Enough now.
I believe the person who harmed him will have a bad ending.
First, I would like to thank everyone for taking time out of your busy schedules
to come to this press conference.
I would like to clear some things up
with everyone.
I'm sure everyone's seen Boris' video.
Everything that Boris said in his video
is true.
I really can't taste what was added in the fried rice
or what the fried rice originally tasted like
because I lost my sense of taste a few weeks ago.
Next to me is my attending physician, Xie Junbin.
If you have any other questions about my condition,
you can consult him later.
I want to give my sincere apology
to everyone here and the public
for not telling you about my condition
in a timely manner.
I apologize.
If you have any questions, you can ask them now.
Mr. Jiang, Boris questioned your integrity. How do you explain this?
I'll explain. What is integrity?
For Yuxuan, it's to offer the best dishes and service to our customers.
In this aspect, whether it's London Yuxuan or Shanghai Yuxuan,
- I believe that we've always done our best.
- I don't agree with you.
What are the best dishes for Yuxuan?
It's to offer an innovative dish that can bring everyone a new taste experience.
Of course, this is Mr. Jiang's roots, but he's already lost his sense of taste.
How can he bring forth new innovative dishes? And how can he bring everyone a new taste experience?
In this respect, is there really no problem with your integrity?
As the saying goes, "What is a man good for if he doesn't tell the truth?"
Mr. Jiang, integrity builds the foundation of a human being, and it is also the foundation for an establishment to survive.
You said you would assume all responsibility of the consequences.
How do you intend to assume responsibility? Will you be able to assume all responsibility?
Mr. Jiang, did you lie to the public about anything else besides your loss of taste?
Boris claimed in his livestream that Yuxuan's new dishes for the quarter tasted terrible.
Is this also because of your loss of taste?
It's been said that you're not on good terms with Boris. Why is that?
Is it because of your lack of integrity?
Would you leave the food industry due to your lack of integrity?
The reporters are harder to deal with than you are.
Have you heard of piranhas?
They jump on you without hesitation
once they smell blood.
They're about to eat Jiang Qianfan up.
Are you done with your questions?
Are you done? If you're done,
I'll answer it all right here. I'm a very simple man.
I'd admit to everything I've done,
but I won't explain myself if it's something I didn't do.
In the fifteen years I've been in the food industry,
I've never disappointed anyone who's dined at my restaurant.
I respect my profession and every customer.
I've explained everything I needed to. It's your choice whether or not you believe me.
The press conference ends here today. Please leave.
- Mr. Jiang.
- I apologize, everyone.
That's all for the meeting today.
Please leave now. Thank you.
Mr. Jiang, please wait.
Give me a minute. I'll be right down.
I said all I needed to. I don't need to explain myself any further.
I'll explain for you if you won't.
Lin Kesong.
This is the food taste reference table Mr. Jiang asked me to fill out.
You can see that it includes the flavors of sour, sweet, bitter, spicy, salty, and savory.
Each flavor has an ingredient that marks the standard.
Whenever we encounter a new ingredient or flavor,
it'll be compared to the original ingredient and then given a value.
A taste table? Are you using this to prove that your sense of taste is exceptionally sensitive?
Ms. Lin, the final taste of a dish is a result of combinations.
If you can make dishes based on these simple values,
can't anyone be a chef, then?
Don't you think this is ridiculous?
Are you trying to tell us that being a chef is as simple as that?
First, my sense of taste is exceptional.
I can't say it's the best in the world,
but I don't think anyone here compares.
Second, I didn't show you this table to prove myself.
I'm telling you that even when faced with the greatest misfortune for a chef, he still didn't give up.
And that's all because of his love for food.
It's because of this table that you're looking down upon that he can maintain his standards.
Which one of you here can do that?
Even so, that doesn't change the fact that Mr. Jiang lied to the public.
What did he lie to you about?
- Did you eat a bad dish or what?
- Lin Kesong.
It's no use saying all of this. Why don't we show them?
Please give us a moment. Kesong,
come help me grab some things.
I have some ingredients here.
There are more in the fridge. Feel free to use whatever you want.
You're all food journalists. Some of you should know how to cook, right?
Choose one person among yourselves
to make a dish.
Lin Kesong and I will use this taste table
to duplicate the dish.
I'll admit defeat if I can't duplicate it. What do you say?
That's not a bad idea. I'll do it.
But I have to inspect the ingredients first, so I don't get tricked by you.
Sure.
They all look pretty normal.
Since there is both chicken and the seasoning for it here,
I'll make Kung Pao chicken. My family created a unique recipe.
You and Ms. Lin can't be here while I make it.
Of course.
I'll leave my phone on the dining table, so you know I'm not cheating. Kesong, let's go.
I think you're pretty impressive.
You put everyone in shock with your words.
You forced me to do so. You wouldn't tell them the truth, so I had to do it for you.
I was really frustrated by them just now. I never meant to lie to everyone.
But they accused me of lacking integrity
and questioned me like I was a criminal. Of course I wouldn't be able to stand it.
You're too stubborn.
It's fine now. I can go with your method.
- As long as you're not mad.
- Is there any use getting mad at you?
You do whatever you can think of. It's not like this is the first time it's happened.
It's my fault.
What?
It's my fault for spoiling you so much.
How are you still in the mood to joke around?
Do you think his Kung Pao chicken will be really difficult to duplicate?
Kung Pao chicken isn't really difficult to make.
But every family has their own special recipe
so it's hard to say.
Let's just go with the flow.
Brilliant!
How brilliant!
What's going on?
I was worried
Jiang Qianfan can simply copy it but this...
See how this guy turned the heat on high
and put the wok on top.
He stir-fried the ingredients for a while, then removed the wok from the heat source.
Then he did the same thing again.
Why did he do that?
If I'm right,
the temperature of his grandma's stove can't be controlled.
So they used this method to control the temperature.
she even taught him the techniques.
This way, the ingredients won't cook too fast
and absorb more flavor. Plus, the temperature difference
adds to the texture of the chicken.
How one cooks this dish determines the slight difference in texture.
Jiang Qianfan is in trouble.
It tastes pretty good.
If Jiang Qianfan is making this dish, I kind of look forward to it.
Yeah.
That's fine, I know it.
♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  Love  ♫
Try it.
Actually, when you turned the heat on high in the beginning
and remove the wok from the heat, I knew it would taste the same.
But I'm very curious, this is my grandma's unique way of cooking.
How did you figure it out?
I was able to replicate all aspects of your dish
because Ms. Lin has provided a very accurate flavor index
and level of firmness for the chicken.
Sure enough, there's the so-called inspiration.
But Mr. Jiang, here's the question.
You've replicated the dish.
Now what's your take on the flavors?
Yuxuan Restaurant can't stay in business by replicating others' dishes.
Right?
Of course not.
This
is my take on the flavors.
Mr. Jiang, you really didn't have to let the public know you've lost your sense of taste.
You are too skilled.
Losing your sense of taste didn't affect you at all.
I deeply apologize for having said things that question your integrity.
I take them back.
You've won. From now on,
I've a fan of
yours and your Yuxuan Restaurant.
Thank you.
Okay, we have prepared a simple meal for everyone
as a token of appreciation. Everyone has worked hard. Thank you.
Thank you.
That's great.
It was actually a happy ending
if it didn't have anything to do with me
my eyes would have already been welded up with tears
Do you have a backup plan?
That's you.
Boris, you really have let me down.
I finally understand why you taught me anger and hate
because you are useless
only when useless people meet a stronger opponent
do they present their hatred and anger
Are you talking about yourself?
I am of course different from you.
Although I have anger and hatred,
my opponent isn't stronger than I am.
It is just the unfairness of life.
Even if it weren't for you
I would still have the means to deal with Lin Kesong.
That is great.
If you win, that means I have won too.
As for how you see me
I do not care
because you are merely one of my chess pieces.
Sorry to disappoint
but you are also just one of my chest pieces as well
Please leave.
On what grounds?
This is my place.
Because I have to practice, if you don't leave, I will not practice.
You are truly hard-hearted.
As long as you win, you can do whatever you want.
Why are you sitting there sighing?
You are here so early.
Have you seen the press conference?
I couldn't stay at home after what happened.
Yes, I watched it, watched it on the way here.
Have you seen the group chat? They are all talking about this.
Everyone feels like Yuxuan will be affected by this.
Really? I haven't read the group chat, I will go read it now.
Yes, it has already been a month
But at the end of it, the dishes for the new season hasn't even been created
it wouldn't be like that If Mr. Jiang sense of taste was still working.
Without the new dishes
we will have no chance of getting 3 stars this year.
Will the business be affected as well?
That is enough, that is enough, all of you should hold your tongue.
You have all seen Mr. Jiang performance today
It can only be described as brave. What is there to worry about?
[I have absolute faith in Mr. Jiang, even if we ran into some issues.]
[It is momentarily, if we stand together, we can get through this.]
You are actually worried too, aren't you
I just hope that Mr. Jiang
can quickly come up with the dishes
only like that will everyone still have a little bit of confidence in this restaurant
Don't worry.
It will get better.
The committee has already reached a decision.
I asked you all to come over
as I know that you are the ones who are most concerned about the conclusion.
Boris,
can you stop pretending not to care?
Before I announce the result
I want
the two of you
to each pick one.
[Eight Tael]
[Half a Kilo]
I am heavier than you
In the Chinese weight system,
one kilo is 16 taels, half a kilo is 8 taels, who is heavier than the other?
♫ You are the stranger I want to know ♫
♫  Don't let me go  ♫
♫  I will do little tricks for you  ♫
♫  Don't bury your secret heart  ♫
♫  Show them who you are  ♫
♫  We sing a song for love  ♫
♫ Listen to your heart, to your heart  ♫