♫  Love is the food for the living heart  ♫
♫  Love  ♫
[Cupid's Kitchen]
[Episode 39]
Nina,
there's one thing that I've always wanted to apologize to you for.
That time I chased you out,
actually, I've always felt guilty about it.
From the bottom of my heart, I've never thought that you wanted to harm me.
But in that situation then, I can't believe anybody.
I only wanted to find people who are beside me to vent.
Actually, there were several times when I wanted to call you.
But I didn't lower my head.
Sorry.
Mr. Jiang, don't say that.
I've already known you for 10 years. I know you better than you know yourself.
If I say that I wasn't sad when I left then, that would be fake.
But I don't feel aggrieved.
Because I know that you will not think that I did it.
This thing that happened, conflict is inevitable.
Okay, everything has passed.
Sister Nina,
where did you go when you left? I called you so many times but you didn't answer.
How did you find her?
I called Nina's phone in her hometown.
Nina, let me tell you,
actually Kesong was determined to get you back.
So she did not allow anyone to enter your room.
Even I was not exempted.
In the end, she was even more out of line.
She even chased me out of my room and told me to sleep in the study room.
What's wrong with the study room? It's not good?
Didn't you tell me to sleep in the study room previously too?
- No—
- Besides, aren't you sleeping back at your room now?
Yes, I'm sleeping in my room now, but aren't you sleeping in my room too?
I'm sleeping on another bed in your room, okay?
Come, the food is ready.
Wow.
Smells great.
These are from my place, satay,
curry, Bak Kut Teh,
this is Nasi Kerabu.
(T/N: These four dishes are popular in Malaysia, where Nina is from.)
Everyday thinking about it and missing it, I finally can eat Sister Nina's food.
Are you happy?
Happy.
I carried these all the way here.
You both must finish everything.
Guarantee that we will complete the mission!
The spoon is here.
[Welcome to Using Audio Assistance]
Please rent me a taxi.
♫  Rainclouds float above my head  ♫
♫  Wait for lightning come and go  ♫
♫  Colors fading when you go  ♫
♫  Memory is sinking to black hole  ♫
♫  I will keep you warm and fine  ♫
♫  If you're willing to come back  ♫
The oil for deep-fried products is not enough. Hurry, add, add more.
The squid is done. How about the mushrooms for table 21? Hurry up. Need it urgently.
Hello, Mr. Jiang.
Clear station 3 for Mr. Jiang. Hurry up.
This dinner gave me a wonderful experience. Thank you.
Jiang Qianfan indeed has a well-deserved reputation. I love you.
Thank you Mr. Jiang and Miss Quentin.
I love Yuxuan. I love you two.
- The foam is done very well, not bad.
- Thank you sir.
Service.
The sour taste after the fermentation balanced the taste of this dish just right.
I like this improvement.
Good job.
Lin Kesong, how long have I taught you?
Anybody who does not understand my food are stupid!
Anybody who dares to change my food are enemies!
I treat all of you as the pillar.
To Yuxuan, all of you
are essential and not replaceable.
♫  Rainclouds float above my head  ♫
Why didn't you try the dish yourself earlier?
What would have happened if I couldn't taste it?
You can taste it.
I was so nervous earlier, yet you're still so calm.
This is very easy.
Be nervous for a few times, and you won't be nervous anymore.
Miss Quentin,
it is true that zircon cannot become a diamond.
But, zircon also has light.
So, if one day you don't pay attention,
and blinded by the zircon, that wouldn't be good.
♫  Wait for lightning come and go  ♫
The next program,
genius head chef mops the floor.
♫  Memory is sinking to a black hole  ♫
[Baidu Search: Silver Dichorine]
Hello?
Hi, Junbin.
Sorry, I ended up buying Hope #1.
What?! Did you give him the medicine?
Not yet.
I don't know how to confirm if it's real or fake.
Okay, wait for me. I'll go over right now and tell you.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
- Junbin.
- Where's the medicine?
Give me the medicine.
I can't give it to you. You're going to take the medicine away.
I must take it away.
I will destroy it.
Did you know that this medicine wasn't passed by the animal test?
It's very dangerous and it's illegal.
I'm not scared of being illegal. I've already come so far.
You said that this medicine's healing power is theoretically 10%.
This means that there is a 10% chance, right?
Junbin,
this is the only hope for Oliver.
Can't Oliver decide for himself if it can be used or not?
Of course not!
You don't even understand how powerful this medicine is!
I'll give you an example.
You know toothaches, right. The most painful tooth pains
only use 1 million nerve cells of the human body.
Then, how many are there in a body?
There are ten billion! Once this medicine is used,
these ten billion nerve cells will react within your body at the same time
and cover your whole body.
Normal people
can't bear it.
But, the means of medicine are so good now. Can't anesthesia be used?
It can't.
Pain is used to activate the nerve cells.
If you use anesthesia to relief the pain, then what's the point of the treatment?!
Huh?
Strong pain will cause his organs to fail.
If Qianfan uses this medicine,
then I'm afraid it won't be 9 deaths and one life.
But instead, 10 deaths and no life.
And it's because he died due pain.
I don't want him to die!
I just want to redeem myself.
Seeing Oliver in that state because of me,
I really want to kill myself.
But,
I still have so many things I didn't finish.
I can't die yet.
I can only live in guilt every day.
I finally saw just this little hope!
Just this little!
Junbin, do you know how much I want to hold on to it?!
Elise,
I understand you. I understand what you are feeling right now.
But, right now,
we really cannot rush.
Maybe... maybe after 2 years,
after the safety of this medicine improves,
everything will be possible. But right now,
I beg you.
Give me the medicine.
For Qianfan and for you,
don't do dumb things.
Believe in me.
Elise.
I won't give it to you,
and I won't give it to Oliver.
I will keep it for myself.
What will you keep it for?
Just to commemorate it.
Sorry, I'm tired. I will go home.
Boris.
Speak.
Hello, it's me.
Sorry, I will have to stand you up.
You will have to go out to the sea by yourself tomorrow.
What?
You can't let Lin Kesong go again, right?
Yes.
I'm worried about her.
Alright, you take care.
Okay Baozi, you take care too.
Hello?
Where are you?
Don't move, I'll go over to find you right now.
Why do you always like to come here?
There is wind.
Do you know?
When I first came back to Shanghai,
I was looking for houses nearby.
Every time I passed by Suzhou Creek, I would think of London's Thames River.
At that time, I always thought how good it would have been
if I could sit here when I was tired.
There wasn't once when I wanted to get up.
For me,
I really liked the valley where you brought me to dig up wild greens.
It is quiet and comfortable over there.
I wouldn't think it's annoying even if I stayed there for 10,000 years.
But someone must go with me.
Really?
Who do you want to ask to go with you?
- Can I ask you?
- Why?
Because when I'm with you,
it's noisy and happy.
We also always have never-ending things to talk about.
How about you?
If you were to go, who would you pick?
You already picked me,
I can still pick someone else?
- You can't.
- Then that's right.
You don't think I'm annoying?
You really are annoying,
but I don't mind it.
Because I—
With you by my side,
I am at ease.
What are you talking about?
Aren't Elise and Doctor Xie both your good friends?
They love you.
Don't worry, I'll always stay with you.
Let me ask you a question.
If...
I'm just saying if.
If there's a chance that will allow me to get back everything I lost,
and maybe my vision, but at a big cost,
would you try it if it were you?
A very big cost? How big?
Maybe death.
What?
I'm just randomly asking. Answer me randomly.
Hurry.
You also said,
you might die.
I also don't want to die.
But I still have to do something.
Lin Kesong.
You grew up. I taught you.
Yeah.
If it wasn't you,
how would it be possible for me to say these words right now?
Do you believe,
I don't have to see you right now,
and I know that you are moping.
I'll take you to watch a movie.
Okay?
What?
Watch a movie.
I can listen.
Go with me.
What's happened? Why are you crying?
Two people love each other,
but they can't be together, so I feel so sad.
Are you an idiot? What's in the movie is fake.
But they are still pitiful.
Going from strangers to knowing each other,
then until they're together,
they must've gone through many challenges.
Yet they still can't be together. It's so pitiful.
Okay.
Don't cry anymore, I'll gift you something.
What?
Here.
Where did you get this from?
Do you like it?
I like it.
I picked it up from the seat next to me.
This is my first time receiving roses.
You can't say you prepared this for me?
Come here.
I don't believe that someone would throw away a rose.
But, I am willing to believe
that this rose prepared for you by God.
You aren't usually romantic,
but when you are...
♫  Falling until the end ♫
♫ How can I escape it ♫
♫ You said don't be afraid ♫
Did the sun rise?
Yes, it's rising!
It's so beautiful.
I want to see it with you too.
It's actually not that pretty.
The vegetable garden and ocean we went to together
is prettier than this.
Just remember those.
I still remember right now.
But I will forget them one day. I will forget that on Earth there is light,
day and night,
and even the things I want to deeply engrain in my mind,
will be forgotten one by one.
Including what you look like.
If you forget what I look like,
I'll just help you remember.
I'll definitely see you with my own eyes again.
I promise you.
Victor, how are the preparations going?
It's almost ready, mom.
Wait!
You're going to leave?
Yes, what else would it be?
You are right, what else would it be?
This.
What is this?
Endless Knot.
This knot has no start or end.
It represents endlessness.
If you have a chance to wear Qipao in England, don't forget
to wear it on your neck.
It's pretty.
What kind of endlessness does it represent?
Friendship. Don't forget that your friends are still here.
If you have time, come back and visit.
Okay, thank you, my old friend.
I wish you a smooth...
a safe journey.
A safe journey.
♫ Someone steals your heart ♫
♫ The silence you can't find  ♫
♫ Look into your eyes ♫
Pick me up next Tuesday.
What? Where should I pick you up?
Of course, it's the airport. Elise is busy, so she can't pick me up.
You're still coming back?
Of course, I'm coming back. Elise and Victor are both in China.
I will come back often.
I thought... see what this has turned into.
Then I won't return this to you.
Look at what you're saying. You look pretty when you wear it.
What time should I pick you up on Tuesday?
First think about what this represents. I think friendship is not correct.
♫ You're the special one ♫
Bye-bye.
♫ You're the special one for me ♫
If I leave, are you okay on your own?
I'm going to bring gifts back for you.
Don't worry, I'll be here for you to come back.
I'm just going to apply for a visa. I'll be back soon.
I'm leaving.
Little Bun, Mr. Jiang asked me to prepare this for you.
There is hot soy milk and juice. Drink it on your way.
Okay.
Mr. Jiang, I'll send her off.
Sister Nina, take good care of him.
Don't worry. Stay safe on your way.
There's already so much! I can't take more.
- T-T-This... Don't let them bring more.
- Uncle, there's still more in the back.
Yes, yes, don't bring anymore. Oh my gosh, this is too much!
We're going to have to eat it until Chinese New Year.
I don't care when you'll finish them. Just eat, and that's it.
I'm telling you, some things were made by ourselves.
Some are the local special products. You can't miss any of them.
Then won't I eat until I become fat?
That's a blessing!
Even this you're so particular, it's a blessing to be skinny when a person is old.
Sister, when you're in France, don't bring me any
make-up, clothes, or bags. You must not bring me back any.
Okay, just tell me what you want, and I'll bring it back for you.
Actually, I'm worried the most about you. Everything else is not important.
When you're there, you have to attend classes and take care of Mr. Jiang.
Can you do it? If you can't, call me and I'll help you.
You're underestimating your sister.
Right now, it is passed the hardest times. That time, I had to prepare for the final round
and take care of him. Also, he wasn't in a good mood at that time,
and coincidentally, it was that time of the month when my mood wasn't good either.
Then can you handle it?
I can't, but I still have to hold on.
I'm bringing all of them.
Give them to me.
Here, here. I'll leave them all for you.
- All for you.
- Slow down.
You're fighting even for this thing?
You're giving them to me?
Learn cooking well. Once I come back,
I'm going to open up a restaurant right across from yours and steal all your business.
You're not scared that I'll beat you? I'll buy your restaurant
and then hire you to be the front desk manager.
I'll never let you enter the kitchen.
- I'll see how you can be arrogant.
- Right?
Hurry up and go wash your hair. Bye!
I can't take it.
- I'm leaving.
- Bye!
Be obedient, okay?
Mr Jiang. The peppermint water is ready.
What would you like for dinner?
Mr Jiang. Are you in there?
I'm coming in.
Mr. Jiang.
Dongpo Pork is here!
Okay!
Here. Put it here.
Why aren't uncle and auntie here yet?
Who knows? Give them a call now.
- I'll make the soup then. - Okay.
They said they would be here soon.
Give them a call now!
Kesong, someone is calling you!
Coming in a second!
Who is it?
Hello Sister Nina, what is it?
Little Bun. I have searched everywhere. I didn't see Oliver.
What do you mean?
Oliver is gone!
Sister Nina, don't worry.
Go check the security camera footage.
See when he left.
Check if he got in any car. Then give me a call back.
Okay.
What happened? Xiao Jiang disappeared?
Sister Nina said Mr Jiang disappeared. He's not answering his phone either.
Sorry, the user you're calling is not available right now.
He's really not reachable.
Sister Nina.
I checked the security camera footage. He left on his own.
He got into a taxi. But I looked at the time.
It's been three hours already.
Sister Nina. It's fine. Three hours is not that long.
He went out on his own last night too.
You wait for him at home. I'll go look for him. Okay?
Don't worry. I'll hang up now.
He is blind. He's been gone for three hours. That's not urgent to you?
I was just comforting her. I'll take off now.
Eat something before you go!
You are not familiar with this car. How about I come with you?
Kesong. Here are some snacks for the road.
Got it!
Slow down.
I'm going.
The hand brake!
My daughter. Will you be okay?
Hello, Little Bun.
Sorry. Is Mr. Jiang with you?
He asked me not to tell you, but he stood me up.
We were supposed to go out to the sea together today.
He called me last night saying he was not going.
So, he's prepared to leave.
He is not reachable by phone. That means he wants to avoid everyone.
He must have gone to an isolated place.
It must be a place he's familiar with. Even if he can't see, he could find it.
There is only one place.
I just want to find a place with water.
Plants are simple. They grow well as long as there's water.
There's water there.
The bitterness of Okinawa Spinach
cannot be compared with the bitterness of life.
I really like the valley where you took me to dig wild greens.
Freeze!
Police!
Don't move! What's your name?
Li Yan.
Come with us.
Hello? Detective Han.
You caught Li Yan?
That's great. Thank you for letting me know.
Okay.
Goodbye.
♫  You are the stranger I want to know  ♫
♫  Don't let me go  ♫
♫  I will do little tricks for you  ♫
♫  Don't bury your secret heart  ♫
♫  Show them who you are  ♫
♫  We sing a song for love  ♫
♫ Listen to your heart, to your heart  ♫