After meeting you,
my selfishness didn't get any better,
it actually got worse.
I know how to deal with criminals,
how to communicate with them,
but
I don't know how to communicate with you.
I want
to keep you by my side,
I don't want you to leave,
but I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
All these years, I've always
taken your kindness to me
for granted.
I've treated your patience and tolerance
as something normal.
I've let you down.
I want to change, I want to learn.
I hope you'll give me another chance.
Don't rush to make a decision yet.
Think it over.
If you're willing to give it some thought,
I'd already be very grateful.
Let's get a divorce.
Weren't you the one who said it?
I can do whatever I want.
I'll do whatever makes me happy.
Besides,
Have you ever cared about what I do?
He specifically targets those from single-parent families or high school dropouts.
Runaways.
Kids whose parents don't care about them.
He says they're easy to control and manipulate.
He buys them the best phones and computers.
Lets them play games.
He also gives them
lectures about family values.
Says it's for their development.
I'm sick of hearing it.
Li Na.
Be more specific.
What does this Chen Tao usually
do to "develop" them?
I have a phone recording on my phone.
You can listen to it.
Cheng Liang.
Don't just stand there.
Take a knife and go practice.
It's been so long.
You should have made something of yourself by now.
Let me tell you all,
If you're not ruthless, you won't keep your place.
We're a family.
Everyone has to contribute.
That's the only way we can all have a good life.
Did you all hear that?
We heard.
That damn woman.
Why did it stop?
There are several more parts after this.
Don't worry, I'll play the rest for you.
Damn woman.
It’s not that bad.
Look at these kids,
being manipulated by someone like Chen Tao.
Do you think it has something to do with being from single-parent families?
I definitely think there’s a connection.
If their families were more involved, this wouldn’t happen.
And then there’s Li Na.
She can be really ruthless when she wants to be.
Once she turns on you, she shows no mercy.
Even our teacher’s wife is like that.
What does psychology call this again?
Is it related to human reproductive instincts?
Since when do you know psychology?
Do you even have a heart?
I have plenty of heart now.
Really.
I’m actually worried about Diandian right now.
If our teacher really gets divorced,
then Diandian
will become a child from a single-parent family.
Alright, enough.
I’m telling you,
don’t let our teacher hear you say that.
Of course not.
Go, collect evidence from the trash can.
Brother Zhang.
I'm here.
Time of death is no more than three hours ago.
Just one stab.
To the heart.
What's your name?
Lin Jing.
Who is he to you?
My husband.
Why did you kill him?
No rush.
Take your time and tell us.
Ever since we started dating,
he wouldn't let me talk to anyone else.
Every time I got home, he would interrogate me.
It wasn't just men I couldn't talk to,
I couldn't talk to women either.
Sometimes I secretly called my mom.
If he found out,
he would drag me over and beat me.
He even hit me for talking to the neighbors.
I love drinking cola.
But I haven't had a sip in three years.
He never let me drink it.
Just because it was endorsed by a male actor.
So what happened today?
This afternoon, I went out to buy groceries.
When I got back, I lay down on the sofa and took a nap.
When I opened my eyes,
he was holding a knife to my neck.
He asked me again,
"Who did you go out to see?"
"Why were you gone so long?"
"Did you go buy groceries or cheat on me?"
I really couldn't take it anymore.
I grabbed the knife from him.
I just...
Go on.
Then I took a shower,
changed my clothes,
and called the police.
Take her away.
Thank you.
This is spicy, let Auntie eat it.
What did Auntie say?
Look, such a good child.
Daddy.
I miss Mommy.
I want to play with her.
Diandian, eat your meal nicely.
Who does Auntie like the most?
Isn't it Diandian that Auntie likes the most?
How about eating this big piece of meat?
Can you eat it?
This potato.
The shredded potatoes are a bit spicy, right?
Auntie will pick them out for you.
Just eat rice and meat.
Is this bite okay?
Good child, good child.
Going downstairs to buy a pack of cigarettes.
Such a little mouth.
I'm back.
The thing you asked me to think about,
I've thought it through.
I don't want to go through it again.
How is your dad?
He's still recovering.
He's stable for now.
You should find a lawyer too.
Just tell me,
What do you plan to do about Diandian?
Diandian will stay with me.
But you can visit him anytime.
If Diandian stays with me, I'll sign anytime.
That's not possible.
Have you thought about the fact that you have to work?
How will you take care of him?
Think it over carefully.
Let's not meet again until you've made up your mind.
Captain Liu
The body was discovered by that cleaning lady.
She called the police as soon as she found it.
You two go over there first.
Okay, understood.
Let's go.
Excuse me, please make way here.
Thank you, please make way.
Ma'am, this is our Captain Liu.
Hello.
Did you report the case?
Yes.
Did you find it?
When did you find it?
A little after four o'clock.
It was still dark then.
The hallway sensor light wasn't working well.
At first, I thought someone was just drunk.
But when I got closer, I saw a pool of blood.
It scared me.
Is the deceased a resident here?
Do you know them?
No, I don't.
Alright.
Please come with my colleague
to the station to make a detailed statement.
Sorry for the trouble.
Hello?
When do you have time?
I want to talk to you.
Have you thought about the situation with Diandian?
It's about Diandian.
Okay.
Then let's do tonight.
At Brother Lei's restaurant.
The one we used to go to.
Can we change the place to Yuge Restaurant?
Alright.
You didn't hear anything else, right?
Master.
How is it?
The deceased is the owner of 401.
His name is Zhao Tiancheng.
Forty-one years old, divorced five years ago.
No children.
His ex-wife is currently abroad.
His mother is in a nursing home.
What does he do?
He opened a golf course in the eastern suburbs.
He also drove a Land Rover.
The license plate ends with 79.
The car is currently in the parking garage.
Brother Ming
We're done collecting, let's go straight up.
Be careful, stay on this side.
Coming.
Brother Zhang
Time of death is less than six hours ago.
There are three stab wounds, all very deep.
The last stab was here.
A triangular blade.
Haven't seen one of these in years.
This is a strictly regulated weapon.
Each edge has a blood groove.
When it enters the body, it quickly brings in air.
It's very easy to pull out.
Basically, anyone stabbed by this
dies from excessive blood loss.
Do you want to keep looking?
That's enough.
Go get the body bag.
Boss, the two of us will go check downstairs.
See if any neighbors heard anything.
Master
What's going on upstairs?
In this unit,
there are a total of twenty-one households.
Because of planning issues,
many people have moved out.
There aren't many people left.
I knocked on seven doors in total.
They all said they didn't hear anything unusual.
As for their neighbor,
they're not familiar with him either.
They rarely interact.
Is there surveillance in the basement?
There are two scanners at the entrance,
and two more cameras inside the basement.
That's all there is.
You two go to the property management in a bit.
Check what time this car came back.
Okay.
Sis
Uncle, my mom passed out.
Ni Zi, there's a lot of blood on her.
Don't panic yet.
Where are you now?
At home.
Okay, I'll come over right away.
You two go to the property management and get the surveillance footage.
Understood, Master. You go quickly.
Qiangzi, you know where my sister's house is, right?
Yes, yes, go over there quickly.
Right, there are two kids at home too.
Check what's going on.
I'm on my way there now.
About half an hour.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Where are you now?
What? Tell me what's going on.
I... I don't know what's happening either.
When I walked in, there were several pools of blood in the living room.
Is she still breathing?
Ask Nizi if she called 120.
Nizi and Diandian both have blood on their clothes too.
I don't know either.
Don't move her. Has the ambulance arrived?
Because the patient previously took medication and had her stomach pumped,
the ulcer was probably left from that time.
And this time?
This time, she went into shock due to gastric bleeding.
Because the amount of bleeding was too great.
We need to stabilize her vital signs first.
Then we'll locate the bleeding point and operate.
Then hurry, please.
Right now, she needs a blood transfusion.
But our hospital's blood bank
really doesn't have that much blood.
She's lost at least
one thousand to fifteen hundred milliliters.
What should we do?
Take mine.
You can take as much as you need.
No, no, that's not what I meant.
Mutual blood donation means she can only receive as much as you donate.
The maximum for mutual donation is four hundred milliliters.
Given the urgency of the situation,
let's both try to find a solution.
We'll also contact other hospitals.
We will do everything we can to save her.
Alright.
Okay, thank you, doctor.
Hello?
Xiaoqing.
My sister is being resuscitated at the Second Hospital.
She urgently needs one thousand milliliters of type O blood.
Can you help me?
Can we lose?
Everything is ready, don't worry.
Wait outside.
You made me wait for you for another hour and a half.
My sister is being resuscitated.
Can we do this another day?
Mom.
Comrades.
The vehicle has arrived. Secure the scene.
Roger.
Mom.
Alright, don't be too sad.
About this, we police officers
will take care of it for you.
Little girl.
Uncle, what happened to my mom?
This is quite serious.
Can I speak with you privately?
Although this happened suddenly,
we still need you to identify the person.
Please come with me.
Okay, be good. Don't get down.
What exactly happened to my mom?
Calm down, calm down.
Secure the scene.
What exactly happened to my mom?
Mom.
My mom.
Go back and take good care of your little brother.
Ziming.
Mom.
Doctor, how is it?
The situation is stable now.
Go ahead with the procedures.
Prepare for surgery.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
You should be at home watching the kids. Why did you come here?
They're all asleep now, don't worry.
I came to check on you.
I'll go back home in a bit.
What did the doctor say?
They're still trying to save him.
Take this.
What is it?
A hundred thousand yuan.
Where did it come from?
Fang Tingting gave it.
This ten thousand is mine.
Actually, it's not really mine.
I owe it to you.
Last time, you asked me to give money to Li Wei.
I couldn't find him.
I lied and told you I gave it to him.
Actually, I used it for gambling.
I've quit.
I really have quit.
All these years I've been driving a taxi,
it was so hard to save up some money.
I lost it all.
Lost everything overnight, back to square one.
I'm keeping this ten thousand.
This one—
Please help me return this to her.
Keep it, you need the money right now.
Even this might not be enough.
If it's really not enough,
let me know.
I'll figure something out.
I'll borrow it if I have to, I can get it for you.
Take it.
Hold on to it. I'm leaving now.
By the way,
if my sister wakes up,
give me a call, okay?
Okay.
These next couple of days, wait until you’ve settled things at home.
I’ll turn myself in.
Take it slow.
Someone stay behind.
Sis.
Nurse, how is it?
We've already saved them.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Feeling better now?
It's fine, sis.
Everyone's doing well.
Ni Zi and Dian Dian are both fine too.
So don't worry.
Just focus on recovering.
Let's go, let's go. Take it slow.
Okay.
Take it easy.
A family member, please stay.
I'll come over in a bit, sis.
Doctor.
I advise you not to overthink it.
The person has been saved.
From now on, take good care and treat properly.
Thank you, thank you.
You're welcome. But next time, someone must stay.
If it happens again, it'll be troublesome.
Understood, understood.
Go pay the bill.
Okay, thank you, doctor.
Thank you.
Nurse.
I have a green tote bag.
Have you seen it?
I haven't seen it.
Master, Master
Master
Why are you here?
I came to see you and my sister.
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
I... I lost my money.
You lost your money?
Yes.
What money?
Just...
A green... a green bag.
Inside it...
There was 110,000 inside.
Don't worry, sit down and tell me. Sit down.
Let me see your receipt.
Surgery fee.
Don't worry for now.
I'll have Li Yugang check it out.
Hello, come to the Second Hospital first.
Second Hospital, Master lost his money.
Hurry, hurry!
Master, don't worry.
I'll think of something first.
Let's pay the money first.
Go find... go check the surveillance.
I understand, the main thing is to check the surveillance.
Okay.
He'll come and check soon.
That's him.
Master, the camera angle isn't good.
You can't see the face.
But don't worry.
He definitely hasn't gone far.
I'll check the city surveillance.
Don't bother.
No, that's not okay. If I can't catch a thief, I...
I shouldn't be doing this job.
Why did it take you so long to withdraw the money?
Don't mention it. The hospital doesn't accept cards.
You have to make an appointment to withdraw a large amount of cash at the bank.
So I could only use the ATM.
I had to use one card after another.
Why did you withdraw so much?
I was afraid it wouldn't be enough.
And what if I lost it again?
As for my situation,
just leave it to the police station.
You two don't need to worry about it.
How is Zhao Tiancheng's case going?
So far, we've learned
that his debts
and social connections are very complicated.
We're still investigating.
Any other leads?
The forensic doctor estimates his time of death was
between 11 p.m. the night before last
and 3 a.m. yesterday.
His car entered the underground garage
at 11:55 p.m.
He most likely parked his car
and was attacked while going upstairs.
Also, his employees reported
that he had a mistress named Qin Lu.
We've arranged to meet her.
Okay, keep investigating.
Also,
that knife is quite unique.
Lei knows a few military enthusiasts.
You can ask him for information.
See if there are any leads.
Alright, got it.
We're leaving.
Master, you should rest first.
Then we'll get going.
We're off, bye.
We invited you here today
because we want you to cooperate with our investigation.
Is it about Zhao Tiancheng?
Yes.
I heard
he died.
What was your relationship with him?
We were friends.
What kind of friends?
Just regular friends.
The night before last at eleven
to yesterday at three in the morning, where were you?
I was in Japan.
I've been in Japan all this month.
I only came back this morning.
Look,
I landed at nine this morning.
I got your call right after I got off the plane.
Then do you know
if he had any conflicts with anyone?
I just had meals and went shopping with him.
I don't even know where he lives.
I really don't know.
Sir, the person has been caught by the police station.
The money has also been recovered, so don't worry.
My condition is still the same.
As long as you agree,
we can get divorced at any time.
Have you thought about how you would take care of the child?
Do you have time to look after the child?
Do you know about our Diandian
and how many extracurricular classes they have each week?
Do you know the names of their teachers?
What time do they go to school and what time do they finish?
Do you know all of this?
Every week, Diandian
attends three extracurricular classes.
Saturday at 9 a.m.,
English class for an hour and a half.
The teacher's surname is Li, 32 years old.
At 2 p.m., basketball.
One hour.
The teacher's name is Kevin.
Sunday at 3:30 p.m., art class.
Two hours.
There are two teachers.
One is called Liu Xu.
The other is called Li Mei.
There was also a drum class.
He didn't like that one.
I canceled it for him.
Dad, today my sister taught me a poem.
Then recite it for Dad.
Willows are green, the river is calm.
I hear my beloved singing on the river.
The sun rises in the east, it rains in the west.
They say there's no sunshine, but there is.
Thank you for your hard work, Dad.
Do you think I'm being especially heartless?
Leaving without hesitation.
Actually,
I've been hard on myself ten thousand times
before I could bring myself to be hard on you once.
It's all in the past now.
I sold that house.
I can't go back.
If I go back,
I'll just think about the good times we had.
The money from selling the house,
I'll transfer it to you tomorrow.
No need.
I'm not good with money.
Let it stay with you for now.
Just consider it savings for Diandian.
Alright.
I'm going abroad this time to accompany my dad for his treatment.
I don't know when I'll be back.
Whenever you figure things out,
we can put a period to our story.
We can't put a period to our story.
There's still Diandian.
Dian Dian
These days, play with Dad and Auntie.
Mom is going to take care of Grandpa and won't be coming back.
Is that okay?
Why is she taking care of Grandpa?
Because Grandpa is sick.
He needs Mom to take care of him, okay?
Why is Grandpa sick?
In a few days, let your dad
take you to Grandma's place, okay?
Which one?
Take you to Grandma's place.
Mom will be waiting for you there.
What's wrong?
Dad
Eat that banana.
You peel it for me.
I'll take this part off.
Do you want to share some with Mom?
Give it to Dad.
I'm leaving now.
Dian Dian, Mom is leaving.
Then say goodbye to Mom.
Goodbye, Mom.
Such a good kid.
The willows are green, the river is calm.
I hear my love singing on the river.
The sun rises in the east, it rains in the west.
They say there's no sunshine, but there is.
Bye-bye.
Is there anyone among these people who likes to play with knives?
You mean a knife enthusiast?
We did have a security guard here before.
His name was Wu Fan.
He was a knife enthusiast.
He liked to fiddle with knives in his spare time.
Wu Fan?
Is it this person?
Yes, that's him.
Where is he now?
He quit a few months ago.
He quit?
Our property management hires an external security company.
All the security guards
are assigned by them.
There's a high turnover rate.
Basically, they change staff every few months.
That's quite normal.
Did he ever have any conflict with the resident Zhao Tiancheng?
I don't think so.
Can you find a way to contact him now?
From the night of February 4th to the early morning of February 5th,
where were you?
February 4th?
Yes.
What day of the week was that?
Thursday.
I was on the night shift that Thursday.
I started my shift at 11 p.m.
and worked until 11 a.m. the next day.
Is this knife yours?
Yes, it's mine.
But this knife was stolen.
Where did you find it?
How do you know it was stolen?
A couple of days ago, I wanted to take it out and oil it.
That's when I realized the knife was gone.
Really?
Then who do you think stole it?
I'm not sure about that.
Wu Fan, let me be clear with you.
Privately keeping a controlled knife is already illegal.
And this knife has caused trouble.
Serious trouble.
So think carefully before you answer.
What kind of trouble?
You really don't know what happened?
Did someone get stabbed?
Who told you someone was stabbed?
Officer, I don't know.
I really don't know.
I've never taken this knife out.
I just like to look at it at home.
Then who do you think stole it?
Who stole it?
Sometimes some coworkers come over to my place to play cards.
Could it have been them?
Think carefully—before February 4th,
who had been to your house?
February 4th... the 4th...
He Shun.
He Shun had been to my house.
Who is He Shun?
He used to work as a security guard with me at Luli.
We left one after the other.
That was last week, Wednesday.
Yes, I was off that day.
He came to my place and said he wanted to have a drink with me.
He even bought quite a lot of food.
But I can't hold my liquor.
I passed out after just two drinks.
When I woke up, he was already gone.
Where is He Shun now?
Are you still in contact?
He did send me a text later.
He said he went back to his hometown.
But when I tried calling him again, I couldn't get through.
Hello.
The number you dialed is not in service.
Please check the number and dial again.
This is the number.
Write down the number.
Sir, I found it.
The whole night of February 4th,
he stayed in the hotel parking lot and never left.
Yes.
Thank you for your cooperation.
But we still have to act according to the law and regulations
and issue you a penalty.
Xia Yu.
Take him to sign.
We'll contact you if anything comes up.
Don't forget about the phone.
Okay, let's go. This way.
This way.
Check on this He Shun.
Okay.
Master
He Shun, thirty years old
From Chong County
He used to work as a security guard in the victim's neighborhood
He suddenly resigned six months ago
There’s been no news of him since
Let’s go
Master, maybe you shouldn’t go, let’s not go
Diandian is home alone
Hurry up, stop talking nonsense
It’s this house
He Shun
Who is it?
Come out and play cards, we need one more
What’s up, Monkey?
Playing cards, we need one more
Don’t move, don’t move, don’t move
Who?
Get up
Don’t move
We’re from the Haiming City Public Security Bureau
Are you He Shun?
Yes
Do you know why we’re here for you?
Yes, I know