Ziqing
I need to apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
You know, there was a time
I think it was the past couple of years
when I suddenly felt that our lives
were pretty meaningless
Maybe suddenly you have everything.
You have money.
You have a house.
You have a car.
And the child is so adorable.
When everything goes smoothly all of a sudden,
life seems to lose its direction.
It even gets a bit boring.
But after what happened to you this time,
I just realized that
these are our best days.
Can we keep living together peacefully?
No matter how dull life gets,
can we just keep going like this?
Yes.
Mr. Liu, please come this way.
Open your mouth.
Son, look how good your mom is to me.
You're so annoying. How do you know it's a son?
What if it's a girl?
I'm telling you, it's definitely a boy.
Let me ask you something.
The gas company called me.
They said there's no money left in your account.
The payment couldn't be deducted.
I already paid the money.
Then where did your salary go?
I lent it to Liu Yang.
He said he needed the money urgently.
He'll pay me back after a while.
I need to take a work call.
Master.
Hello?
All the legal procedures for the An Pinghai case have been completed.
The death sentence will be carried out soon.
He requested to see you before the execution.
See me?
We'll talk about it later.
Who wants to see you?
It's nothing, just a prisoner.
Don't keep standing.
Go rest, quickly.
Don't tire out my son.
I want to spend a bit more time with you.
I'll come find you after I finish cutting the melon.
Hello
Please show your police ID
Okay
Please register
If you catch me, what level of merit will you get?
Collective second-class merit.
All I got was a collective second-class merit.
You should know it was just a collective second-class award.
Would you still have risked your life to catch me?
Yes, definitely.
You're bragging.
Back then,
you were so scared your hands were shaking.
I saw the situation at the time.
There were so many of you.
Even if I pulled out a gun,
I could have shot one or two more people.
But what's the point?
I'd still end up getting caught.
I'm a decent guy, right?
Are you done talking?
I'm done.
Then let me say something.
Go ahead.
You're right.
I was scared.
And I should thank you.
The day after we caught you,
my wife told me she was pregnant.
If you had shot me back then,
my child would have grown up without a father.
A person only has one life.
Who isn't afraid of death?
I'm afraid too.
I was terrified at the time.
I was afraid my wife would lose her husband.
Afraid my child would lose their father.
Afraid my sister would lose her brother.
And afraid my father would lose his son.
But all of that was fear after the fact.
If I had to do it again,
I would still risk my life to catch you.
Are you out of your mind?
Are you like this just with me, or with everyone?
Can't help it, this is my job.
Are you going to be a cop again in your next life?
That's something for the next life.
Let's talk about it in the next life.
Did you come to see me just to brag,
or is there something else?
I have a mother.
Pension
It's still enough to live on.
It's just that I'm getting older.
My legs are getting less and less flexible.
I live on the fifth floor.
My mom has told me several times.
That I should
move to a lower floor.
But I haven't done it.
Can you
Can you help me with it?
Is the first floor okay?
I went to several places.
I found a few on the first floor.
One of them isn't expensive.
It's similar to the one the old lady is living in now.
You should help him find an agent.
Don't handle the buying and transfer yourself.
As for the move,
if they really need help,
go talk to the local police station and neighborhood office.
Ask them to coordinate and lend a hand.
The old lady hasn't broken any laws.
This is also serving the people.
Understood.
My back these days...
Getting older really takes its toll.
I still can't do it.
No, I used to be able to get up in one go.
Quite charming.
What the heck?
I'm here to ask you out for a meal.
I said I'm not going.
You keep calling—aren't you annoyed?
They're thinking of you, it's your birthday.
Isn't that nice?
Let's get together.
No, I don't want to.
Then let's go shopping this afternoon.
Ask Tingting to go with you.
You stay at home like this every day.
Don't you get bored?
You're actually right about that.
Not boring at all.
I'm really enjoying this moment.
I feel like all those meals and drinks before,
were all for nothing.
You've really reached a new level of awareness.
Then let's celebrate at home.
Sure.
Alright, I'll go take a shower.
I'm all sweaty.
Let's go to the seafood market later.
And buy some seafood.
Why not shower after we get back?
No, I’m too hot right now.
The seafood market is so full of different smells.
Hello?
Zhuzi,
what's wrong with you?
Come back.
I told you, you shouldn't have gone to that lousy place.
Who's supposed to welcome you back?
Me, I promised your sister-in-law.
You have to eat at home today, got it?
What? You...
Why do you always get so worked up? The way you talk...
Stop always cursing at people.
We'll talk about it later.
Happy birthday to you
Okay
That's great
Mom, turn on the light
I always think wearing this looks really silly
You put one on, let me see
Dad, what wish did you make?
I can't say that
If I say it, it won't come true
Ni Zi, let's eat some food before the cake
Eat the food, eat the food
Look, your mom made seafood
There's also fish
Dad, does the food taste good?
They're urging you
It's fine, just stay
It's up to you if you go or not
Just eat a little and then go
Zhuzi finally came back to the country
Go
I'm going
Go ahead
I'll go and come back early
Don't drink too much
Come here, big baby
He's so annoying, isn't he?
Big smooth talker
Bye-bye
Don't drink too much
I won't, I'm leaving
Zhuzi
Brother
Happy birthday
Sixth Brother
Sit down, sit down
We were just waiting for you
Sixth Brother
We have to drink this together
Good brother
Sixth Brother, Sixth Brother, Sixth Brother
Sixth Brother
You’ve become a homebody now
Yeah, staying home is pretty nice
Raising fish and growing flowers at home
Cultivating yourself and your character
Weizi
Good stuff, from Guangdong.
This is for Brother Liu.
Brother Liu.
I don't touch this stuff anymore.
You don't understand, Weizi.
This is an upgraded version.
It's completely different from the old stuff.
Brother Liu, Brother Liu, Brother Liu.
Go ahead, try it.
Really, I've quit, I've quit.
I won't touch it anymore.
A piece or two of this definitely won't get you hooked.
Sorry.
Up to you.
Thanks for understanding.
Come on, cheers.
Come on, let's do it together.
All together, come on.
Happy birthday to Brother Wei.
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
Cheers.
Bottoms up.
The fetal heartbeat is normal right now.
The head circumference is a bit larger than average.
And currently, the baby is in breech position.
A natural delivery would be somewhat difficult.
Last time I came, the baby was head down.
How did it turn breech this time?
That's possible.
The baby keeps moving inside the womb.
The position can change at any time.
My due date is coming up soon.
Is there any way to get the baby to turn?
I still want a natural delivery.
It's hard to say.
You should prepare for a C-section just in case.
Come to the hospital immediately if your water breaks.
Doctor.
Is there any way to make the baby turn?
It's possible.
Tingting
I'm here. Which floor are you on?
You went home.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Alright, alright, I'm going home now.
Sis
Nizi
Okay, I'll come over right now.
Uncle
Sister
I told her not to call you
But she insisted on calling you
What's going on?
He owes too much and can't pay it back.
No, technically this is your only residence.
It can't be enforced.
He has another small property under his name.
The old lady is still living there.
We can't really go through with that plan, can we?
Uncle, my mom said she would take me to stay at a hotel.
But I don't want to stay at a hotel.
Hotels are too expensive.
My mom even sold the car.
We won't stay at a hotel.
We'll stay at uncle's place.
Sis, come stay at my place for a few days.
You can also help me look after Tingting.
Let's go.
Mom, just listen to my uncle.
Why put yourself through all that suffering?
Isn't a C-section still giving birth?
No, I want a natural birth.
Kids born naturally are smarter.
Smart?
That depends on who the child takes after.
If the baby takes after his dad, that's trouble.
Why would that be trouble?
Our Ziming is the smartest.
He's a police officer.
Let's not talk about being smart.
Does he know how to care for you?
No matter if it's scorching hot or freezing cold,
he always makes you squeeze onto the subway alone.
To go for your prenatal checkups.
Has he ever accompanied you even once?
So what?
I can do it myself.
After all these years,
why hasn't he managed to get a car?
Mom, you're so annoying.
Your cousin Jianjun,
he got promoted recently.
He gets driven around in a sedan every day.
His wife never has to squeeze onto a bus anymore.
That car isn't cheap.
Well, I ride a subway train worth over eighty million every day.
Mom.
You're here.
Ziming is back.
What are you doing?
Sis, come here, sis.
Come in, hurry, hurry.
The girl has grown so big.
How old is she?
I'm five years old.
Come here, girl, come.
This is
I asked my sister to come and take care of Tingting.
We don't need so many things.
After Tingting gives birth, she'll stay at the postpartum care center.
It's fine, it won't be a problem.
It's great to have someone to help out.
What's that smell on you?
Oh, that's rotten eggs.
What were you just doing here?
The doctor said our baby is in breech position.
I need to turn the baby around.
Why do you need to turn the baby?
For a natural delivery.
Stop messing around. Let me see. Don't move her.
Hurry up, go wash your hands and change your clothes.
It's okay, Mom.
Hurry, hurry.
I'll go, I'll go, I'll go.
Sis, you sit down. Mom, it's fine.
Don't just stand there.
Grandma.
Here, have an apple.
Thank you, Grandma.
Such a good kid.
How long are you planning to stay?
We just came to see Tingting.
We'll leave in a little while.
You're leaving so soon?
That won't do.
Sis, you've had a child, you have experience.
You have to stay and take care of me.
When you gave birth to Nizi,
was it a natural birth or a C-section?
Natural birth.
See, children born naturally
are both smart and cute.
Isn't that right, Nizi?
Let's go.
Come help your aunt tidy up the room.
Just these two pieces of luggage, right, sis?
Okay.
Don't move, don't move, I'll do it.
It's fine, it's fine.
Come on, Nizi.
Sis, have a seat.
Why are you standing?
Did something happen at home?
Mom, you don't need to worry about this.
Right now, Tingting is the most important.
We should do whatever we can to make her suffer less.
"We"? There's no "we" in this.
What hardship could you possibly go through?
You didn't even give birth to this child.
Yes, yes, I know.
What do you know? Tell me.
That it's painful and exhausting.
So you know how tired and sore I am?
Mom, help me pick up that watermelon.
What do you need the watermelon for?
What are you doing?
I'm going to tie it around your waist.
Let you feel what real exhaustion is like.
Stop messing around, I have to go to work soon.
You can't take it off at work either—keep it on.
Liu Ziming
What are you doing?
It's loose. I want to tie it tighter.
Take it off.
It's fine.
Alright, you can go back.
Go inside.
I'm leaving now.
Why is that guy strapping a watermelon to himself?
Who knows?
Aren't you going back to take care of my dad?
Don't worry, I'm even more concerned than you are.
My sister is here with me.
Alright, alright, I got it.
Let me know when you get home.
Okay, bye.
Are you eating, or is mom eating?
Girl.
What cartoons do you like to watch?
Here, you can change the channel yourself.
Sis.
Watch TV by yourself for a while.
What about the company?
He must have some shares, right?
It filed for bankruptcy just last month.
Even my bank card,
I don't even know when,
he took all the money out of it.
The money for this girl's schooling,
he didn't even leave any for her.
Forget it.
Once someone gets involved with this stuff, it's all over.
The first time he came back from rehab,
I still believed he would get better, that he would change.
And he really did change.
No matter who invited him out, he wouldn't go.
He came home on time.
One day, it was his birthday.
A few friends called to celebrate.
I told him to go.
Have some fun.
Go out and get some fresh air.
It was just that one day.
That very night, I got a call from the police station.
The second time he came back,
I still had hope in my heart.
But I didn't expect it to happen even faster this time.
It wasn't even a week.
The third time he came back,
he was like a completely different person.
He lost his temper every day and smashed things.
I tied him to the bed.
He kicked me.
And hit me.
When I saw him like that, I thought,
Forget it, just let him be.
Sis,
you did your best.
I
Um
This is what you
gave me when I got married before
Tingting, this is from your sister
I can't take it
Listen to me, I haven't spent a cent
I'm giving all of this back to you
Please don't make me upset at a time like this
Just take it
You need money now that you're pregnant
Stop arguing with me
Otherwise, I'll just give birth right here
Take it
This is what Ziming and I want
Sis, take it
You and Nizi will stay in this room later
I'll stay in that room
It's really comfortable for me to stay alone in that room
It's okay
Don't cry
My emotions are already unstable right now
Okay, okay, I won't cry
I won't cry, don't worry
What's wrong?
Nizi, don't move, don't move.
Be careful, don't prick your hand.
Go sit over there.
Aunt
Is this cup expensive?
It's fine, it's not expensive.
Where's your mom?
I don't know. She left when I got up.
Did your mom go out to buy you breakfast?
I've been making breakfast myself lately.
My mom hasn't been sleeping well.
I saw her secretly taking sleeping pills.
Really?
You're amazing, girl.
You can even make your own breakfast. Eat up.
Hello, sis.
Where are you?
I couldn't sleep, so I went out for a walk.
I'll be back soon.
Did Ni Zi cause any trouble?
She's fine, really well-behaved.
She even made me breakfast.
Come back soon, okay?
Alright, alright.
Sis
Let's go up to the third floor.
Please take a look.
Three bedrooms and one living room, with good north-south ventilation.
These two bedrooms face the sun.
How many square meters is this apartment?
This apartment is fifty-nine square meters.
According to your requirements,
this is the most cost-effective apartment in the whole complex.
The layout is very regular.
It has a high usable area ratio.
Although it's on the third floor and there's no elevator,
going up and down the stairs
can be considered as exercise.
How much is this one?
The owner is eager to rent it out—eight hundred per month.
But you need to pay a whole year upfront.
Plus one month's deposit.
You can use this room as a study.
Ma'am, about this apartment,
there are still many clients coming to see it this afternoon.
If you think it's suitable,
you should make a decision quickly.
Otherwise, it'll be rented out soon.
You don't need to persuade me like this.
I'm just being honest.
I used to work as an agent too.
I'm even more familiar with these lines than you are.
This apartment of yours
has been vacant for at least two or three months.
It's not that easy to rent out.
Compared to similar apartments in this complex,
why is this one so much cheaper?
Is there some kind of problem?
A problem?
There's no problem.
As you can see,
the buildings in this complex are generally quite old.
And the appliances aren't fully equipped.
A haunted house?
To be honest with you,
an old man passed away here.
But it wasn't an unnatural death.
He died of old age, it was a peaceful passing.
It doesn't affect anything.
It's fine, I'm not afraid of haunted houses.
What are you doing?
Call the landlord right now.
Ask him if 8,000 yuan a year
can include the property management fee.
If yes, we'll sign the contract today.
If not, I'll switch to another agency.
Alright, I'll get in touch.
These were all classic models back in the day.
They were only worn once or twice.
All the certificates are included.
Appraisal certificate.
Sis, this is the price I'm offering you.
Is this price for everything?
Or just for these two?
It's for all of them.
Are you kidding me, kid?
You can see for yourself.
You handle so many things every day.
These are all good items.
Most of them are almost brand new.
And they all have receipts.
Look, there are even certificates of authenticity.
Altogether, they're worth over three hundred thousand.
You should at least offer a bit more.
That's definitely not possible.
The price I'm offering you
is the highest in this area.
I'm just in a tough spot right now.
Sis, everyone who comes here is in a tough spot.
I know you have difficulties.
I have my own problems too.
Let's try to understand each other.
Why don't you look around a bit more?
How about this, then
You take this one too
And then this bag
Aren't you collecting bags too?
You don't need to look
This is D-level
The best kind
Good morning, boss.
Xiaobo.
Do your best.
Of course.
Xiaobo
What is this?
Where?
This.
It's a dried-up well.
Is there still water?
No, there hasn't been for a long time. We all use tap water now.
Then why is it covered?
O-open it, open it and take a look.
Hasn't it always been covered?
Why does it smell so bad?
Xiaobo
Did you just poop here?
No, I didn't. I don't know what's going on either.
Boss, come look, what is this thing?
I can't see clearly either.
What's inside here?
The smell is coming from here.
A dead body
Call the police right away
Xiao Qin, come over and take notes.
The deceased is female.
Height is 1.65 meters.
Age is in her twenties.
There are obvious strangulation marks on the neck.
In two places.
There is a pair of underwear in the mouth.
Captain Liu
Check if there’s any jewelry on your hands.
Come here.
Check the lower leg and foot more carefully.
Who reported the case?
Me. Him.
Who found it?
I found it.
Li Yugang.
Ask about the details.
Could you come over for a moment?
Hello.
Can you tell me roughly what happened?
It was in the morning.
I just came out to have a look around.
Then I walked over here.
When did you discover it?
Around eight in the morning.
I thought I'd open it and take a look, and then—
Did you know there was a well here before?
Yes, there's always been a well here.
Later, the water dried up.
Now everyone uses tap water.
So it's just been left unused.
Do you usually live here?
Yes.
I've always lived in that house over there.
We keep the door locked here, no one else can get in.
Xiao Lü.
Captain Liu.
Take these two back with you.
Make a detailed statement.
Okay.
Of course.
You two come with me to the station to make a statement.
Check the body.
See if there are any other injuries.
Or any blunt force injuries.
Brother Ming.
Li Yugang, Xia Yu.
Hello, hello.
Cotton.
Don't regret it later.
What's going on?
It rained all night.
All the footprints have been washed away.
There are no signs of dragging or fighting around.
This probably isn't the primary scene.
Are there any personal belongings?
The wallet, phone, everything is gone.
Alright, let's go.
Brother Zhang
Captain Liu
Come
Wait, wait, wait
The deceased is a woman
She is 1.65 meters tall
The main thing is there are clear strangulation marks on the neck.
The time of death should be more than forty-eight hours ago.
Oh, right.
There was also a pair of underwear stuffed in the mouth.
Why are you two standing so far apart?
Come here.
Smell it.
Master, how am I supposed to smell this?
Did you find anything?
Nothing but a bad smell.
Smell again, get closer.
Master, a little closer.
Calf position
It kind of smells like that floral cologne.
Alright.
Come.
How much longer will you be?
We want to go in and have a look.
It'll be ready soon.
We're done extracting.
You can go in now.
Okay, thank you. Good work.
Good work.
Bye.
You two go down and take a look.
Master, didn't the forensics team already collect samples here?
The forensics team is the forensics team.
We are us.
Go down.
I'll do it.
No need.
You go.
You know what to do in a bit, right?
I know.
Search every inch.
Ask one by one.
Xia Yu, climb up by yourself in a bit.
It's fine, don't worry.
I'm here, Master.
Be careful.
Do you think there is
a painless way to die in this world?
No.
There must be some that are relatively less painful, right?
No, every way to die is painful.
Have you died before? How do you know?
I just know.
Then tell me one, if you don't believe me.
Fine, I'll name one.
Sleeping pills. Swallowing sleeping pills shouldn't be painful, right?
A lot of people think taking sleeping pills isn't painful.
But actually, that way is the most uncomfortable.
Because when you're half-asleep,
the drugs irritate your stomach and cause vomiting.
And at that point,
your nerves are numb,
and you can't move.
The vomit can enter your lungs and nasal cavity,
causing a severe burning sensation in your lungs.
This process can last
about fifteen minutes.
Sometimes it comes with convulsions and spasms,
and loss of bladder and bowel control.
In the end, the real cause of death is
Enough, stop talking.
choking on your own vomit.
You just memorized all that.
Just wait, I can definitely think of one.
Just wait.
But let me tell you,
actually, before you even think of one,
you...
You should recharge your brain first.
Here, let me help you recharge your brain.
Judging by the contents of the stomach,
the time of death should be October 2nd,
between 10 p.m. and 1 a.m.
The cause of death is mechanical asphyxiation.
She was strangled.
There was sexual intercourse before death.
But there are no lacerations on the genitals.
So it's impossible to determine if it was sexual assault.
Was any semen collected?
No.
The other party may have used a condom.
By the way,
I found some skin tissue
on her finger.
It's being tested.
About that pair of underwear from before,
judging by the style and size,
it should belong to the victim.
You two,
Zhang has been working hard.
Cut that watermelon for Zhang.
Master, you're being so polite.
There's no knife.
I've got one here.
This one?
You go ahead. I'll do it, I'll do it.
Let Zhang have some to quench his thirst.
Give it to me.
Where's the watermelon?
Here it is.
Can you wash it here?
You're really washing it here?
Is it okay to wash it here?