=Reincarnated Love=
=Episode 3=
Let go of me.
You wretch.
You did such a disgraceful thing.
How am I supposed to answer
your father?
Forgive me for speaking bluntly.
As a lady,
you're pregnant.
That'll disgrace the entire family.
You two truly don't know
how I became pregnant?
Insolent thing.
You're pregnant,
yet you speak rudely to your elders
and slander your cousin.
Force the medicine on her.
Get rid of the kid in her belly.
Let go of me!
I'd like to see who dares.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Mr. Huo, what do you mean?
I want to see who dares touch her.
Mr. Huo,
even as the Duke's son,
you have no right to barge in here
and interfere with our family affairs.
She carries my child.
Do you think I have the right?
Mr. Huo,
you must've made a mistake.
(Betrothal Letter)
The formal rites are all prepared.
In three days,
I'll marry Miss Jiang.
(Betrothal Letter)
During this time,
if anything happens to my wife
or the child in her belly,
I wonder if Mr. Jiang
can bear the responsibility.
Milady, Mr. Lu is here.
Yuan,
did Yanzhi force you
to marry him?
He never forced me.
I knew it.
With your temperament,
you'd never do this.
Ruoli.
I'll soon marry Mr. Huo
and be your sister-in-law.
I'll always remember
our bond
in my heart.
Are you giving up on me
because he's the Duke's legitimate son?
Yunzhou,
I wish you to find a good match soon.
Farewell.
Yuan,
whenever
you need me,
I'll always be there.
(I'm sorry, Yunzhou.)
(I have to avenge my father.)
(Forgive me for not indulging in love.)
(Joy)
♪Gentle rain seeps into the deep night♪
♪Stirring the jasmine from slumber♪
♪Two swallows nest upon the beam♪
♪Bringing fresh mud for the home♪
(Joy)
♪Gazing afar at the roadside
that I once knew♪
♪Lush grass swayed in abundance♪
♪Though beauty abounds,
it answered not your call♪
♪A sudden gust stirs in the night♪
♪The pond ripples in gentle waves♪
♪Most afraid
when the full moon turns to fear♪
Why are you hiding?
♪That same gentle smile♪
Since you used my name,
you should at least pay some interest.
Please behave yourself.
Why are you so flustered?
That day,
weren't you very proactive?
♪Together from dawn till dusk♪
♪Who'd think parting comes so easily♪
♪Yet reunion hardly comes by♪
♪You always cheer me up♪
Jiang Ruoli,
wake up.
Why do you keep appearing in my dreams?
Who are you?
Huo Linchuan.
Huo Linchuan?
Are you crazy?
Listen, Huo Linchuan.
I dreamed
that you were assassinated and died.
My dreams can foresee the future.
(In my previous life,
she mentioned Wuyou Ferry.)
(Could her dreams)
(really foresee the future?)
I can change your fate of death.
But I have one condition.
What condition?
Protect my family's lives.
Using our lives as the wager,
Jiang Ruoli, you are ruthless.
I want you
to marry me.
Fine.
Physician Zhang.
Milady,
this won't do.
Your parents were so kind to my family.
Now that you need my help,
I'll naturally do my utmost to assist.
Thank you, Physician Zhang.
Lady Ruoli's pulse
is smooth and flowing,
like pearls rolling on a plate.
This is indeed a pregnancy pulse.
I didn't expect you to be so strong.
The ceremony wasn't completed.
Drink this nuptial wine.
The nuptial wine
is meant for a real couple.
You and I
are merely allies with mutual interests.
Once everything is settled,
we will go our separate ways.
What a fine saying.
Go our separate ways.
Then I wish my wife...
No.
I wish my ally
peaceful sleep every night
and no dreams of the past.
I'll sleep on the couch outside.
Rest early.
It's the lady's wedding day.
Why do you look so worried?
She married alone
into this enormous mansion.
There is no one here to support her.
Tao,
you must stay alert
and never let her fall into danger.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Help!
♪The dream shattered♪
♪Like illusion, yet true♪
(Ruoli,)
(I know that in your world,)
(each life is the only life you have.)
(But this time)
(is my final life.)
(I must try my best to live)
(and protect you.)
♪How can I turn the tides
of this fleeting life♪
♪When fate falls apart♪
♪Memories return,
carving tears upon my face♪
♪Yet I can't hold on♪
♪Only warmth remains
where longing once burned♪
♪The dream shattered♪
♪Like illusion, yet true♪
♪Like a restless soul♪
♪How vague♪
♪Rain and blood, drifting wild♪
♪A blade of frost in dreams♪
♪Love and hate entwined♪
♪Rise and fall, yet never fade♪
♪How can I turn the tides
of this fleeting life♪
♪When fate falls apart♪
♪Memories return,
carving tears upon my face♪
♪Yet I can't hold on♪
♪Only warmth remains
where longing once burned♪
♪Life after life♪
♪Fated to meet, but never meant to be♪
♪Still, I refuse to bow or yield♪
♪In this life, love becomes my blade♪
♪To break free from reincarnation♪
♪All past affairs tangled with regret♪
♪Now shatter apart♪
♪By fate and karmic ties confined♪
♪Is this fate or calamity♪
♪Is it life, death, or parting pain♪
♪I ask only for a moment of peace,
as devout as my heart♪
♪In the next life, grant me one kiss♪
♪To kiss the snow upon the brows,
and the depths of your gaze♪
♪For once we kissed,
destiny bound us to never part♪
♪This fleeting life feels but a dream♪
♪Sober or indulge♪
♪I only wish to be with you,
with all my heart♪