♫ Anticipating tomorrow, surpassing the limit
because you are by my side ♫
♫ Our beliefs overcame the difficulties, not giving up
to advance bravely ♫
♫ The youngster is running with determined eyes
even in the face of a difficult challenge ♫
♫ Youth is persevering until the end, fearless and
never ceasing ♫
♫ Passion ignites and enthusiasm unchanging ♫
♫ Believe in tomorrow and shout it out ♫
♫ Continuously embrace every new starting point ♫
♫ Continuously pursue perfection in this moment ♫
♫ The dawn of victory, oh~ fluttering its wings ♫
♫ Flying with no fear of the storm oh~ ♫
♫ Pointing towards the direction of my heart ♫
♫ The dawn of hope, oh~ shining boundlessly ♫
♫ Taking off with no fear of the surging waves oh~ ♫
♫ Running towards and pursuing ♫
♫ The brightest place in my heart ♫
[Skate into Love]
[Episode 23]
Dear,
I just remembered something.
Actually, our son started showing signs a long time ago.
What signs?
Since he was little, he's never
shown interest in girls.
When he was in elementary school, his deskmate
was a girl called Tang Xue. Do you remember?
Yeah.
That little Tang Xue was so pretty
and smart. All their classmates liked her.
But our Yubing didn't, and even told me he wanted to change deskmates.
I asked him why.
He said "I just don't like Tang Xue."
So I asked, "Who do you want to be deskmates with?"
And he said... I don't remember, but it was a little boy.
More importantly... did he switch deskmates?
I thought if I let him get a new deskmate just because he didn't like her, it would be coddling him too much.
And it wouldn't help his social skills either, right?
So I didn't tell the teacher.
I thought we'll see how it goes if the two kids spend more time together.
But look what happened.
Six years. Even after six years, they still didn't develop a friendship.
When they graduated, our son even lied to Tang Xue.
Even now, I'm still too embarrassed to see her parents.
Now that I think about it, you're right.
I remember our son was pretty popular when he entered middle school.
But I'd never heard of him being close with any girls.
Dear, I still want to have grandkids.
If we need to, we'll just have a second kid.
You stop drinking starting tomorrow.
Dad. Mom. I'm going out.
Yubing, where are you going?
I'm going out.
- To where?
- To meet my friend.
- Who?
- A classmate.
All of your answers are the same.
Mom, why are you questioning me as if questioning a thief?
I'm leaving.
- This won't do, I have to go and see.
- Wait.
Change your clothes and shoes!
Hello? I'm leaving now. I'll see you at the beach.
Follow that car.
- In front?
- Yes, that one.
♫ The blue sky is gently kissing the sunset glow ♫
♫ The warm coffee by the window sets off your side profile ♫
♫ Opening up the thick album with our cherished
photographs inside ♫
♫ That year’s winter, ♫
This is the first.
The first what?
The first New Year's I get to spend with you.
It's not the first.
Here. Hold it! Hurry up.
♫ Snowflakes are falling, do you see them? ♫
♫ Holding your hand so tightly, I’ll never be afraid ♫
In the future, let's always spend the New Year's together.
♫ Year after year, they stay by your side as a white fairy tale ♫
I'm surprised you remember it so clearly.
Let's spend it together next year, too.
And the year after that, and after that.
And for many more years.
♫ I heard there are no two identical snowflakes in the world ♫
♫ To me, you are irreplaceable in this world ♫
This is our first official kiss.
You kidnapped my dinosaur and you still want to kiss me?
Should we...
try it again?
♫ The summer season filled with meteor showers
heard the star’s response ♫
♫ I opened my eyes and saw the two footprints
kissing the snowy ground ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, do you see them? ♫
♫ Holding your hand so tightly, it’s warm that I’m melting ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, I want to become them ♫
♫ Year after year, they stay by your side as a sweet fairy tale ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, ♫
This is great.
♫ Holding your hand so tightly, ♫
Kids, continue what you were doing.
Dad. Mom?
Auntie, it's been so many years, but you still look so young.
No, I'm not.
Tang Xue, what a coincidence. Today, I even mentioned you to Yubing's dad.
We've always really liked you.
When you were little, you were very clever and smart.
Isn't that right, Dear?
Yes! Yes.
Thank you for looking after me all those years. Looking back on it, I ate a lot of candy thanks to you.
If you like our food,
come over often. Auntie will cook for you anytime.
If you don't mind, you can even live in our house.
What Uncle means is that our whole family welcomes you.
Yes, yes! We all welcome you.
My parents said that it's late and I should head back soon.
- You're leaving so soon?
- We'll give you a ride.
- Yeah, we'll give you a ride.
- Uncle and Auntie, it's okay. I live right next door.
I'll head back now. Uncle and Auntie, goodbye.
- Take your time.
- Be careful on the way back.
How could you guys follow me?
We just wanted to see who you were dating. I never thought it'd be Tang Xue.
Thank goodness it was Tang Xue. We thought it was Xu Feng.
What? Xu Feng?
Did I do something to make you guys misunderstand me?
Isn't this all your fault?
You're a guy, what are you doing putting on eyeliner?
Exactly.
That eyeliner was because I lost a game. Tang Xue drew it on me.
What about the pink dinosaur?
That's hers, too.
Last time, you were talking to a male classmate,
and you said you were dating but couldn't tell the parents. What did that mean?
You guys even eavesdropped on my phone call?
Let's not discuss that right now. Answer my question.
That guy is Tang Xue's good friend.
When I was little, I lied to Tang Xue. Right?
So I was trying to think of how to get her parents to forgive me.
I was just asking for help.
Last question. What is your relationship with Xu Feng?
Yeah.
Xu Feng is also a hockey player; he's my idol. I was thinking that since it's New Year's,
he might come back to Hucheng. And I thought it'd be nice if I could see him.
Thank goodness it was all a misunderstanding. My son, do you know?
How worried we've been the last few days because of this? We've barely slept.
Look at my eye circles. And your mom was so scared of not having grandchildren.
She's started to force me to stop drinking.
What does this have to do with drinking—
You— You guys wanted to have another kid?
(T/N: lit. you guys are responding to the call of the country?)
It's okay now.
The misunderstanding is all cleared up. Your dad and I can stop worrying now.
Tang Xue is a good girl. Be good to her, got it?
Your dad and I fully support you.
We completely support you.
Son, go buy some alcohol for us, so we can decompress.
- Yes.
- The three of us must celebrate this.
There you go again! Not being serious.
Let's go home.
It's good they slept already. Or else, they'd definitely interrogate me.
Mom.
Where'd you go?
I went to see fireworks with my friend.
Xue'er, I know that you're training for short track speed skating again.
It's okay. Your dad's asleep already.
How did you find out?
It's not important how I found out.
Actually, the past few days, I've been trying to find time to talk to you about this.
Xue'er, since you were little, I've never stopped you
from doing the things you like to do.
But this time, I'm really worried about you.
Do you have to start skating again?
After I stopped skating, it was like I lost my soul.
I didn't find anything else
that made me feel interested or passionate.
So I've already applied to transfer departments.
- Starting next semester, I'll focus on short track speed skating.
- You–
How could you not consult with us about such a big decision?
If your dad knows, you're dead. You know that, right?
I really can't understand. What's wrong with studying veterinary medicine?
There's nothing wrong with it,
but I don't like it.
Every day at school, as soon as class starts, I'm waiting for it to end.
But when someone mentions going skating, I'll feel completely energized.
If I don't skate for one day, my whole body feels weird.
You– Do you understand that feeling?
I don't understand. Aren't you scared of getting injured again?
I am scared. But for skating, I'm willing to pay the price.
It's okay if it's tiring, painful, or difficult.
I don't think any of these are a big problem. But for anything else, I can't do it.
The sense of accomplishment and joy
that skating brings me is something that none of the other majors can bring me.
Even our veterinary medicine professor encouraged me
to go do what I'm passionate about, because you can only do something well when you love it.
Is passionately loving it enough?
Do you know how competitive athletes are?
How many athletes can become champions?
How many can stand at the very top? Do you know?
I know.
I really want to become a champion,
but what's more important to me is the journey of getting there.
That's how much you love skating?
Yes. Skating is my life.
I didn't know either, how much I loved skating.
But after I stopped skating, I realized how important it was to me.
In life, whichever path you choose,
it will be difficult.
You might as well choose the one you like.
At least you will enjoy the process of getting there.
Are you giving me your permission?
What do you think?
Thank you, Mom.
I love you to death.
To be honest, I'm really proud of you.
It's rare that you know so clearly what you want.
Life is like...
driving, taking a trip somewhere.
Some people get in the car, but don't know where they want to go.
These people will just always be running around their entire life.
But the people who know where their destination is,
in just a short time,
they will get where they want to go.
The road you've chosen
is going to be full of hardships. It's like when you drive,
you can't only run into green lights.
There have to be some red lights along the way, too. But as long as you don't give up,
you will reach the place you want to go.
Although your dad and I will worry about you a lot,
and we are scared for you to get hurt again.
Daughter, you've grown up.
We need to learn to let go.
You decide your own life.
As long as your choices make you happy,
that's more than enough for us.
But there's one thing you have to remember.
In the future, no matter what happens,
you have to tell us.
Because we will always support you. We are your strongest backers.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I made these big decisions without consulting you guys.
It's okay, it's okay.
You know your dad's personality, he has a stubborn temper.
Let's tell him slowly,.
I trust that one day, your dad will support you.
Hello?
Yubing? Are you dating someone?
Why do you say that?
Let me tell you... I have very sharp eyes.
None of you athletes can get anything past me.
You are the star player of the XDragons team.
I've been arranging so many sponsorships and endorsements for you.
Everyone's eyes are on you.
Make sure you don't cause any scandals. It'll be very troublesome to clean up.
Got it.
Dating will distract you from training. That's a given. Right?
You only have so much concentration to give.
You are going uphill right now.
You don't have any time to spare for dating. Am I right?
Let me tell–
Hello?
Who was it?
A scam phone call.
Thanks.
You were saying that you told your mom about transferring departments.
My mom supports me.
But my dad still doesn't know. We're afraid he won't be able to accept it just yet,
so we've decided to slowly tell him.
I'm surprised Auntie is so supportive of what you want to do. She's very reasonable.
Of course. Why do you think she was able to birth such an amazing daughter?
Okay, let's head home early today. We're going back to school in a few days,
then we'll be able to hang out every day. We should spend more time with our parents while we can.
My little sugar cube is so responsible.
Let's go.
Tang Xue, are you done packing?
Yeah, I'm done!
You filled half a suitcase with clothes, and one and a half with snacks?
What are you doing? Are you going to Africa to save the refugees?
You have no idea how hungry I get every night.
Doesn't the school cafeteria serve three meals a day? If you're hungry at night...
what does that mean?
I expend a lot of energy every day. After practice—
Practicing for what?
That...
English.
Next semester, I'm taking the CET4.
(College English Test Band 4)
She's learning English; it requires a lot of brain power so she gets hungry.
I didn't think of that.
- Wait here, I'll bring you some beef jerky.
- Okay.
I'll bring you half a box!
My god! You almost exposed yourself.
- Son.
- Mom.
Tomorrow, have your dad take you to the station.
It's okay, I can go on my own.
I know you guys are busy, I'll go by myself.
I want to stay at home with you tomorrow. Just let him be independent for once.
Your independence talk again. He can't be independent if you take him to the train station?
[Tang Xue]
I almost accidentally told my dad
about skating training just now.
Did you recover?
Of course, I'm a quick thinker.
I'll see you at the station tomorrow then.
My dad insists on taking me to the station tomorrow.
If anything, let's just come clean. We can't hide everything from him.
That's true.
With your dad's temper, it'd probably be worse if he found out we were hiding it.
Then it's agreed. We'll confess together tomorrow. I prefer ripping the band-aid off anyway.
Li Yubing.
What a coincidence. Did you guys agree to leave together?
It-It's a coincidence.
I'm going to buy some water, should I buy some for Uncle and Auntie as well?
Why are you talking like that?
What's going on?
He's leaving with you? You guys definitely planned this!
It's a coincidence.
Coincidence.
That's good then.
Xiao Xue,
Dad isn't opposed to you having a boyfriend,
but your boyfriend can't be Li Yubing.
That's enough. Let her handle her own matters, okay?
Dad, the matter after elementary school was so long ago.
Just let it go.
I've already let that go.
What I'm worried about now is your present.
As far as I know, Li Yubing plays hockey at school. Right?
Hockey is such a dangerous sport.
If you guys date and he gets permanently injured,
he'll just slow you down.
It's the same as you training for short track speed skating.
I'll say it again, I really don't want to live in fear.
That's enough from you. Everything is dangerous these days.
For example, if you're walking down the street, a vase can fall on your head.
Exactly.
That's enough. She has to have some kind of hobby.
Fine, just do it as a hobby then.
It's almost time. You should get going.
You guys can go home now.
Uncle and Auntie, here's some water.
You really didn't have to.
I'm not thirsty.
I'll drink it! Give it to me.
- Here, Auntie.
- Okay, okay.
- I'll get going too then.
- Okay, goodbye. Safe travels.
Uncle and Auntie, goodbye.
Look how polite he is, and you still rejected him.
[Hucheng to/from Lincheng]
Didn't we agree to come clean today? Why didn't you tell him?
You didn't say it either.
I just thought today was going to be a sure fail so I didn't dare say anything.
It's a good thing you didn't. My dad doesn't just disapprove of me skating again,
he disapproves of my other half being a hockey player, too.
If he found out I was completely going against him,
he would get on the bus right now and follow us all the way to the sports college.
He would immediately force me to transfer back to the veterinary medicine department.
He wouldn't really do that, would he?
I think we should give it more time.
I should at least enter a tournament, win a medal, and prove myself first.
I think that would make it easier for him to accept.
Okay, hopefully, we can make it to that day with no issues.
Why is your dad only like that to me?
Look how nice he is to Bian Cheng, compared to me.
You're just not his type.
- In any case, you're my type.
- My neck, my neck hurts.
The king is back. Receive him.
Did you guys miss me when I was gone?
What do you think?
Where a rose stops, the fragrance lingers.
I get it. Even though I wasn't here,
your longing only became more intense.
Master Tang, that's impressive.
You're the only person who didn't learn anything after hanging out with a genius student so much.
After you register since returning to school, meet at the training center today at 4:00 p.m.
I'm going to the sports college to register, let's talk when I'm back!
Hey!
Follow me.
Why are you being so secretive?
Before I win a tournament, we can't let anyone know about our relationship.
Why?
You're the one that said Coach Chu doesn't allow dating.
Maybe she's not as strict anymore, don't you think?
How do you know?
Okay, but we can at least talk normally. Right?
We were fine before. You're making it even more suspicious by acting like this.
That's true.
But you're aware, too, that I don't have a backup plan.
If I don't win a tournament, how will I prove to my dad?
By then, just wait and see how our relationship will get ripped apart.
Okay.
I'll listen to Master Tang.
Good boy. Let's go.
Before the break, I reminded everyone to maintain their condition.
During the break, you can't relax.
Were you guys just pretending to listen?
Who listened to me, and who was lazy,
your performance will show all of it.
Those who got slower, who lost muscle,
all treated my words like the wind blowing past them.
The days without the Iron Hammer training you,
it seems like you guys had a great time.
You had big feasts every day,
you dated.
It's okay if you block me from your Wechat Moments.
Your performance will not lie for you.
Today, out of everyone, only Zhang Yuewei and Tang Xue are worthy of praise.
Their performance actually improved, and they maintained their condition well.
Starting this semester, Tang Xue is officially in the sports college.
She is officially a member of the short track speed skating team.
She used her ability and her attitude to prove herself.
Welcome Tang Xue to the team.
This semester, the competitions are tough and you'll have important missions to accomplish.
I will only reserve the opportunities
for those who are the most outstanding. You can weigh your own priorities.
Don't come crying to me later on.
Next, I'll talk about the plan for tomorrow.
Tomorrow is the XDragons Club collective team building activity.
The figure skating team is at a competition and can't make it this time.
So, tomorrow, it'll be the short track speed skating team with the ice hockey team.
I want to remind everyone: make sure to be on time tomorrow.
When we're out, be safe, and follow the rules.
We need to show the positive side of the short track speed skating team. Got it?
Got it!
Okay, dismissed.
- Thanks, Coach!
-,Thanks, Coach!
What's the team-building activity?
We're camping, having a picnic, and doing other group activities.
- It sounds so fun.
- Yeah.
Be careful.
Sugar Cube, I miss you.
Dog, I miss you, too.
I want to sit next to you.
The coaches are both here. If you dare, come sit with me.
I have a way to have the coaches ask us to sit together.
You're bluffing.
Watch this.
Coach Xu.
- What?
- Look.
Coach Chu is asleep.
I see that. What about it?
Do you know what a head that has nowhere to settle needs right now?
What?
A warm shoulder to rest on.
Think about when she wakes up and sees you next to her.
- Will it work?
- Of course.
Let's do it.
Little Tang Xue, let's switch seats.
But Coach Chu asked me to sit with her.
I knew you were a smart one.
Everyone, gather round.
Everyone, over here.
Students, today is this semester's XDragons Club
first team-building activity for the On-Ice programs.
Who can tell me what most important is when you're on a trip?
Being happy!
Wrong. It's safety.
You are athletes. You need to always keep this in mind, got it?
Got it!
Being happy is also important.
- But safety is even more important.
- Yes!
We finally made it here. Everyone put your luggage down and let's play a game to warm up.
Great!
- I'll go over there.
- Hey.
What?
Thanks.
For what?
I can tell you've been working out your delts.
I train them every day.
[Bing Dao (Ice skate blades)]
Two words. Shoes.
Skate blades!
Yes, you got it.
Next one, next one.
[Wu Dajing]
Three words.
The first word is five.
(Sounds like Wu)
The second word is big. Wu Dajing!
(Sounds like da).
You're amazing.
Last one, last one.
[Wen Bie (Goodbye kiss)]
Two words.
Singing.
Goodbye kiss.
Their chemistry is amazing.
Captain, you're amazing.
[Kong Jiang Bing (Paratroopers)]
Three words.
Airplane? Jump! Plane crash?
- Diving? Mushroom. A mushroom diving?
- A mushroom diving?
Jump... Jump!
Diving... dwarf? Jump!
- Fighting! Explosion!
- Three! Two! One!
Next one!
[Bai Ma Wang Zi (Prince Charming)]
Four characters.
Jiang Shijia? Three characters.
Take off your clothes, dance,
riding a horse? Hairdressing? Cosmetology?
- If you can't do this, let Old Deng do it instead.
- Two, one!
It's Prince Charming! Me!
Okay, the last one!
[Shui Long Tou (Faucet)]
Twist. Twist. Drinking water? Lake? Ocean? Saliva? Saliva? Fountain?
Three, two,
one!
All right. I announce
that the winning team this time is Zhang Yuewei and Li Yubing.
Let's celebrate getting second place. Give me a high five.
It's quite late now. It will get dark shortly.
Pitch the tents together with your partner on the assigned list.
Okay!
We're so happy! Happy!
Is she jealous?
Tang Xue, help me get the hammer and the ground nails in the toolkit.
Okay.
Hold it.
Don't move your hands.
For Wei-wei?
Does this type of item look like something for a brother?
Which girl is it for?
All right. You can go do what you need to do. I can do it myself.
All right. I'll go to the back.
What happened?
Are you okay?
Captain, are you okay?
Are you okay? Get up slowly. Get up slowly. Get up slowly. Don't worry. Don't worry. Move slowly.
- I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Wei-wei, what happened?
- Slowly. Slowly.
- I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Does it really hurt?
- You're already crying because of the pain.
- It's okay.
It's not a big deal.
Last competition, Sister Wei had a fracture and she didn't cry because of it. It must hurt more than that this time.
Don't talk nonsense. All right, I'm okay now. Go back to doing what you need to do. I'm completely fine.
Be careful. Be careful, Wei-wei.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'll do it.
I'm okay. Continue to set up your tents.
I want to see what was able to make our Brother Wei cry?
How are you?
It's nothing. Just a small injury.
Does it hurt?
Here's some medicine. You'll be fine after you spray it on there.
Thanks.
I'll get going.
Zhang Yuewei, where are you really hurting?
You see, Bing-bing does care for you. Right?
- How's your foot?
- It's okay. It's just a small injury.
Wei-wei, no matter how strong you are, you're still a girl at the end of the day.
Don't actually think of yourself as a strong man.
I'm really fine. Don't worry.
Come on, let's go and help the others.
- My small injury is really no big deal.
- Come on, I'll carry you.
Give me a break! I can't stand myself being that wimpy.
It's okay. Brother Wei has it covered. Let's go.
A long, long time ago, there was a very, very poor mountain village.
There was only one family, which had only two people.
An old man and an old woman.
They were so poor that getting food every day to eat was a struggle.
On one night, when they were fast asleep,
they heard a noise outside that went cling-clang, cling clang as if someone had walked by
and walked into the kitchen. Cling-clang, cling-clang, cling-clang...
The next day, the old man woke up
to find that his pot
had breakfast in it. He was very astonished.
Who did this?
Another day passed, the old man woke up to use the restroom.
Back then, toilets were outside,
and then, at the same time,
he finally saw
who this person was.
From a far distance away,
he slowly walked towards the old man's house...
Are you mad at me? Why do you keep avoiding me?
I'm not.
Why do you keep avoiding me then? Is it because of the game that made you angry?
I admit...
that it's because I was a little too happy when I played the game.
I smiled a little too wide. When I hugged her, I was a little too intimate.
I'm sorry.
Isn't it just a game?
Do I seem like I'm that stingy to you?
Then, why do you keep avoiding me if you're not jealous?
I've already told you multiple times,
don't be too intimate in front of the others.
You can't be like this before I get a medal.
Every time you see me, it's like you're a dog that saw a bone.
All right. You're actually not jealous.
- You're definitely not a normal woman.
- Of course, I'm not!
You're a normal man.
Ah!!!
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- You scared me to death!
You scared the life out of me!
Wei-wei?
Wei-wei!
There's no signal in the mountains. Wei-wei!
Oh, no. She doesn't know the way around here.
Oh, no! Oh, no! Zhang Yuewei went missing!
I can't do it all by myself. Everyone, come help me look!
Wait, wait. Don't worry. Don't worry. Everyone, go and help find her. Go! Go! Let's go find her!
- Hurry!
- Let's go!
- Go that way.
- Hurry up!
- Zhang Yuewei!
- Captain!
- Why don't you go over there and take a look?
- Zhang Yuewei!
- Captain!
- Let's go up there and take a look.
- Did you find them yet?
- Let's go towards that direction.
Let's go this way.
- Zhang Yuewei! Zhang Yuewei!
- Captain!
- Zhang Yuewei!
- You didn't find them?
- Come, come, come. Come over here.
- Captain!
Zhang Yuewei!
Wei-wei! Wei-wei!
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
only you can understand ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ I had the kind of luck as if I plucked a star ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings, I couldn’t
believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise
and take you traveling ♫
♫ In this big world, I’ll hold gently onto the secrets
you are protecting ♫
♫ I’m lucky to receive the surprise that came like a shock,
it’s a promise you’re giving me ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫
♫ The first time I saw your smile, my heart fell for you,
it must be destiny ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand and travel to the rainbow
to pluck a star ♫
♫ Secretly listening to your feelings and let the stars
fulfill each of your dreams ♫
♫ I want to collect every expression of yours, they are
the four seasons that belong to me ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings, I couldn’t
believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise
and take you traveling ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like the sweet sea breeze ♫
♫ it is the signal you are giving me ♫
♫ This moment when your smile is like the sun ♫
♫ As if I’m nibbling a juicy peach, a beautiful love blossoms ♫
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
(only you can understand) ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫