♫ Anticipating tomorrow, surpassing the limit
because you are by my side ♫
♫ Our beliefs overcame the difficulties, not giving up
to advance bravely ♫
♫ The youngster is running with determined eyes
even in the face of a difficult challenge ♫
♫ Youth is persevering until the end, fearless and
never ceasing ♫
♫ Passion ignites and enthusiasm unchanging ♫
♫ Believe in tomorrow and shout it out ♫
♫ Continuously embrace every new starting point ♫
♫ Continuously pursue perfection in this moment ♫
♫ The dawn of victory, oh~ fluttering its wings ♫
♫ Flying with no fear of the storm oh~ ♫
♫ Pointing towards the direction of my heart ♫
♫ The dawn of hope, oh~ shining boundlessly ♫
♫ Taking off with no fear of the surging waves oh~ ♫
♫ Running towards and pursuing ♫
♫ The brightest place in my heart ♫
[Skate Into Love]
[Episode 11]
So pretty.
Huan-huan. Huan-huan.
I think someone's knocking.
It's probably my cousin. Go get the door.
Good morning, cou–
Who are you?
I spent the night here.
With who?
With her.
You slept?
(T/N: referring to if he had sex with her)
I wasn't going to sleep, but I couldn't stand it so I just slept.
Who are you?
Xiao Liao, my cousin's husband didn't mean to.
Hey, handsome guy, don't be angry anymore.
I'll blow on it for you.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Forget it, we might be family in the future anyway.
Huan-huan!
[Female Dormitory]
Zhang Yuewei!
This is for you.
- Who's it from?
- Some guy.
He was pretty tall.
Our team members all have the same phone. I've grabbed the wrong one many times already.
Why not put on a phone case?
Thanks, Auntie.
If I were to barge into the girls' changing room,
you guys would beat me up until I was bedridden.
How come in you girls' eyes, us guys just–
don't have any dignity?
Where's Li Yubing?
I don't know.
After practice, he just left.
Never mind then. I'll tell him next time.
Wei-wei.
Do you like the phone case?
I like it.
This... took quite a bit of effort, didn't it?
Of course.
Stayed up all night, hand-gluing on each stone.
He's pretty impressive.
If you see him, tell him thanks for me. Just tell him...
Just tell him that my lightning bolt will not strike him.
I really like this gift. I'll use it.
- It's not that, this phone case–
- Oh no!
Why is it so late already?
I'm going to head out first, Wu Dajing is coming to give a speech today.
I'll get going! See you later!
Remember to tell him for me!
Forget it.
It's enough that she likes it.
After class, everyone must remember to review this.
This may be an important exam topic this semester.
Okay. Class dismissed.
Tang Xue, stop by my office.
Professor, I have something to attend to right now. Can I stop by your office later?
Later?
Then, can I let you graduate later?
Do you know how many times you've been late this semester? You also did not pass the tests.
As a student in the veterinary medicine department, what can be more important to you than your studies?
[Glory Ice Summit]
[Keynote Speaker: Wu Dajing]
Let's go inside.
Sorry, this seat's taken.
Someone's sitting here?
Sorry, the phone you have dialed is turned off.
Sorry, the subscriber...
Figure skating prince, you came to watch a short track speed skating speech?
The Ice God came, too, didn't he?
What? Did you agree to meet Tang Xue here and she didn't come?
Hello, everyone. Welcome.
Today, we're very excited to welcome the national hero of short track speed skating,
the winner of the Winter Olympics, Wu Dajing, is here as the keynote speaker for our Glory Ice Summit.
Let us give him a warm welcome
to Wu Dajing.
Hello, everyone. I'm Wu Dajing. I'm very happy I can be here at LUU today
to interact with all the students here.
I think everyone knows already, we're about to host the Winter Olympics here in China.
So, I hope a lot of the students here can be proactive
and join the short track speed skating community
so that our sport will keep improving.
There's no way Tang Xue would miss this opportunity.
Li Yubing, why didn't Tang Xue come?
That's between the two of you, why ask me?
I haven't even asked you about this yet, don't get me started.
You guys are so noisy. If you're going to talk, do it outside.
Li Yubing, what are you trying to do?
Me? I came to listen to the speech.
You clearly knew I had plans to come and watch with Tang Xue,
yet you chose to sit next to us. You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
Can you share with us what kind of difficulties you're endured?
At that time, my endurance wasn't very good.
When I first entered the national team,
I was just a training partner for the women's' short track speed skating team.
In long track speed skating, I lost to Zhou Yang, and in short track, I lost to Fan Kexin.
(T/N: both are Chinese speed skaters and Olympic medalists)
So, as a male athlete, I felt very sad and frustrated every day.
But every day, I held it in, went to practice, and gave it my all.
In the end, my hard work paid off and I got a chance to compete.
I even won a silver medal. Eventually, I won a gold medal.
So I want to tell everyone, don't easily let go of your dreams.
Don't be afraid of hardship, take charge and go for it.
Where's Yu Yan?
Regardless if you admit it or not. Anyhow, I admit it.
I like Tang Xue.
If you want to compete in a fair game, I welcome you anytime.
I, Li Yubing–
Wow, they're hugging?!
I'm sorry, I couldn't hold it in. Sorry!
I believe this was just an accident, I'm sure everyone will forget about it very soon.
Tang Xue, this incident is at least half your fault. Didn't you say you would come? Where were you?
If there's anyone to blame for this, it's you.
- My fault?
- It's because of you that I was always late or missing class.
That's why Hawkeye made me stay after class. I almost couldn't graduate because of you!
What's more...
You were the one who made Ice God into Awkward God. Why are you trying to blame someone else?
Tang Xue, I'm sorry.
It's all our fault that you couldn't listen to the rest of the speech.
It's okay, I already met Senior and said hi to him.
Look, look.
Yu Yan was mistreated by you earlier and is still trying to comfort me.
You have to apologize to him today.
I'm also a victim here, okay?
There's no way I'm apologizing to you.
Li Yubing... apologize!
I'm sorry.
That's more like it.
Xiao Tang Xue.
Brother Dajing.
This is Li Yubing. This is Yu Yan. We're all classmates and good friends.
Yeah, I can see that you're all pretty close.
No, no. That was all a misunderstanding earlier.
I'm sorry we interrupted your speech.
Don't worry about it. You were much more interesting than my speech.
How have you been recently?
I've been pretty good.
Do you have some time? Let's catch up.
Sure, let's go. You guys continue what you were doing.
Tang Xue.
Then we...
If you guys don't have anything to do, then go home. I'm going straight to practice later anyway.
Don't you dare mistreat Yu Yan again.
If he bullies you, tell me.
Nothing has changed since you were little. You're still making sure justice is served.
You still haven't told me.
Do you like Tang Xue or not?
Whether I like her isn't important.
To Tang Xue,
you're just a kid.
It's fine. She won't consider you anyway.
Li Yubing, I don't know how things will turn out,
but I'm going to give it my all.
I haven't heard from you in so long, did you forget about me?
Of course not. Am I really that ungrateful?
You took such good care of me back then, how could I forget? It's just that...
I haven't skated in two years and you're a world champion already.
How could I face you?
You've improved, too.
What improvement?
Now you're the junior of a world champion.
So as long as you improve, it's enough?
What are you studying now?
I'm in the veterinary medicine department.
Veterinarian?
Are you looking down on vets? If your pets need medical care later, I'll treat them for free. How's that?
I don't have any pets, and even if I did, I wouldn't let you treat them.
You're really not skating anymore?
I just joined our school's short track speed skating team this year.
Really?
I knew you wouldn't give up that easily.
Especially since I have you as an example.
It's been so long since we've seen each other, let's have a little competition.
Who's scared of who?
I really haven't practiced in so long, I'm so slow now.
World champion, do you accept defeat?
You eat corn faster than you skate, how can I not be okay with losing?
How come I don't feel like you're complimenting me? Old rules still apply, you pay.
This is for you. I hope you continue to work hard.
Bring out this same attitude of refusing to admit defeat,
and quickly join the national team.
Then you'll have to welcome me when I get there.
I'll welcome you with corn.
- It's a promise.
To Tang Xue, you're just a kid.
Hello?
Hello, Yan-yan?
How have you been recently?
Same as always.
You sound kind of down. Is practice too tiring?
Maybe.
Coach Jin told me recently that
he wants you to exceed your limits, so he's increasing the difficulty of your training.
I think you can definitely do it. Right?
No problem.
Why do I feel like your mindset is not right?
You sound so tired, not motivated at all.
Yan-yan, for an athlete, the most important thing is your mindset.
Do you remember when you were little? You loved figure skating so much.
At that time, when you won a competition, you'd hug your trophy and sleep with it for a whole night.
You were able to get to where you are today because of that mindset.
You can't let go of this dedication. You're still young.
I'm already 18 years old, I'm not a child anymore. How come none of you understand that?
Look at how you're talking to your mom.
I'll say it again. I'm not a child anymore.
I'm going to rest now. I'm hanging up.
Yu Yan, you're not a child. You're a mature adult now.
Regardless if you admit it or not. Anyhow, I admit it. I like Tang Xue.
If you want to compete in a fair game,
I welcome you anytime.
To Tang Xue, you're just a kid.
It's fine. She won't consider you anyway.
Li Yubing, I don't know how things will turn out,
but I'm going to give it my all.
You can do it. Shoot!
I'm afraid I'll miss.
Xiao Dong, basketball is like people. You have to understand its heart.
If you have enough faith in it, it will definitely go the way you want it to.
Come on, you can do it. Shoot!
You got this, let's keep going.
I'm leaving for Harbin tomorrow to participate in the national youth team training.
Can you come and see me off? No, no, I can't say it like that.
It sounds like I'm begging her to come.
The Ice God is leaving for the national youth team training tomorrow. Come see me off.
No, no, that's too stiff. Participating in the national youth team training...
come see me off, you come to...
Come see me off. Okay, that's good.
You're too nervous!
Why are you here?
I heard you were doing extra training tonight, so I came to visit.
Coach Chu said, with my current performance, I won't be able to stay on the team.
I watched you for a while earlier.
I think your limbs are too stiff.
When we practice figure skating, the first thing we do is relax and loosen our limbs.
This way, our movements are more fluid.
I think it's also because I haven't trained for so long.
I think you're in too much of a rush; you have too much going on in your head.
I have an idea, but I'm not sure if it'll help. Do you want to try it out?
Close your eyes.
Why?
Just do as I say.
Now, forget your goal.
About joining the short track speed skating team,
wanting to skate faster, forget about all of it.
Remember the time when you first started skating.
Remember what it was like to encounter the ice.
It's like in swimming,
when a person is embraced by the water.
Relax your body.
You and the ice are one.
Now, stretch your limbs,
feel the freedom,
the whole ice is yours.
You need to let go of your heavy burden before you can truly start over.
Do you trust me?
♫ The blue sky is gently kissing the sunset glow ♫
♫ The warm coffee by the window sets off your side profile ♫
♫ Opening up the thick album with our cherished
photographs inside ♫
♫ That year’s winter, our foolish smiles were so sweet ♫
♫ The wishing bottle is waiting for the spring rain,
wondering if the seed will sprout ♫
♫ Next winter, next journey, we’ll wait for the snow to fall ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, do you see them? ♫
♫ Holding your hand so tightly, it’s warm that I’m melting ♫
I feel it.
♫ Snowflakes are falling, I want to become them ♫
♫ Year after year, they stay by your side as a sweet fairy tale ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, do you see them? ♫
♫ Holding your hand so tightly, it’s warm that I’m melting ♫
♫ Snowflakes are falling, I want to become them ♫
♫ Year after year, they stay by your side as a sweet fairy tale ♫
Yu Yan!
How come you're here, too?
Yu Yan, Coach Jin is looking for you.
You should go quickly.
Okay.
Your face is so long, you look like a Scottish terrier.
I'll bite you.
Go away.
Are you done practicing? If you're done, let's go.
Yu Yan just taught me a method for relaxing my body, I want to try it again.
Yu Yan, Yu Yan, all you talk about is Yu Yan.
Do you like Yu Yan?
If I don't like him...
should I like you instead?
Tomorrow, I'm leaving for Harbin to participate in the national youth team training.
Good for you, Li Yubing. You're joining the national youth team? How long will you be gone for?
It's not for that long.
Make sure you practice well. Don't be...
Don't waste time dating or anything like that.
How is that any of your business?
It's not just me saying this. This is Coach Chu's rules.
Don't worry about me. Just worry about yourself.
I'm going to watch your game.
Tomorrow, Master Tang will see you off.
Tang Xue!
Why are you acting like you're the victim? Clearly, it was you that—
That was my first kiss!
Tang Xue.
You're heading back?
I... You're done?
I haven't found Coach Jin yet.
Then I'll head out first. You should go home soon, too.
Wait for me.
Bing-bing. Can't wait anymore, come on!
Hurry up and get up, you have to leave soon.
Bing-bing, you've been holding my hand for so long.
Can you let go of it now?
- What time is it?
- It's almost 9:00. Hurry and get up!
What yummy foods are you thinking about?
I'm not.
You keep pouting.
Get up.
[Dog]
- Hello?
- Hey, didn't you say you'd come and see me off?
It's so early, what time is it?
I didn't sleep well last night.
You sound sleepy. You didn't sleep well? Is it because of what happened yesterday?
Are you joking? That little thing?
Are you coming or not?
I, Master Tang, always do what I say I will.
Wait there.
Where are you going in such a rush, so early?
I have to get going. My planning competition.
Bye-bye-bye! Wish me luck!
Good luck.
Remember to bring specialties back.
Not a problem.
Yubing, don't mind me nagging you.
This time, the one leading the national youth team is Coach Wang.
His capability is strong, temper is even stronger. You have to be more humble.
I got it, Old Xu.
Bing-bing, score a few more goals.
Make us brothers proud.
That's a must.
Take care of yourself.
It's not Bing-bing's first time leaving for training.
Don't worry about him.
Don't worry, I can take care of myself.
You didn't eat breakfast yet, right?
Thanks.
I'm leaving now.
You... don't have anything to say to me?
Have a safe trip.
That's it?
When you get there, good luck,
work hard...
After you go, work hard and you'll improve.
More... well...
As long as you train diligently,
as long as you demonstrate your skills, the government will definitely—
anyway, you... score more goals...
pass more people, score more goals, that's all you need to do.
Okay, I got it.
Yubing, the car's here.
Okay, I'm coming right now.
I'm leaving. Remember while I'm gone, don't date.
If you do and Coach Chu finds out, you won't be able to join the short track speed skating team.
I know, I know. Hurry up and go.
- When you get there, give me a call.
- Okay, no problem.
That hurt so much. I'm leaving. Bye.
Remember to bring presents back for us.
- Okay.
- Be careful.
Bye-bye.
Are you going to the airport?
Yes, to the airport.
What does ice come from? Water.
And the biggest breakthrough point of our proposal is that we were able to invite Jam Hsiao
to be our spokesperson. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Contestant No.15 for his exciting presentation.
Next, let's welcome Contestant No.16,
Team Xia Yu, to present for us.
Hello, judges and students.
Our team's proposal is an "Ice Rink of Dancing."
[Ice Rink of Dancing]
We may need to turn off the lights for our presentation. Would you be able to do that for us?
Okay.
An ice rink is ice-cold; giving a person the feeling of gloominess; like winter in the north.
Cold and lifeless. Our design of the butterfly
will emerge from the cocoon in the ice rink
bringing a gorgeous, graceful splendor; giving new vitality to the ice rink.
Xiao Xia, you spoke so outstandingly.
Do you know that when we left there, the sound of the applause was still reverberating throughout the auditorium?
What use is that, we didn't get an award.
Let me correct that mistake. Even though we didn't get the first place award, we got second place.
Award price of ¥3,000.
But I just want to go to see the sloth.
The sloth, you will eventually see it one day. Don't be unhappy.
Why don't we go have a nice meal, then... then you can buy a pretty dress, some clothes...
So shallow! Is money supposed to be spent like that?
I just texted Master Tang and Old Ye, their advice was to wisely plan how to spend this money.
Should money be used in such a wasteful way?
I just want you to be happy. Anyway, I will not take any of this money for myself.
It's all for you to keep. Spend it on whatever makes you happy, whatever you like.
Did you hear that?
What?
It's a kitten!
- A kitten? Poor kitty. Look how skinny it is.
- Hi.
Let's go to the supermarket, get it some food.
Sure. But we can only save him for the time being, not forever.
It's so tiny.
It's almost winter. The weather will get colder.
It's hard to say whether it'll be able to survive the winter.
Right.
Why don't we use this ¥3,000
and establish a "Home for Homeless Babies"? Let's take all the little animals that don't have a place to stay for the winter to our place.
- To our place?
- Yeah.
Look. Look at our classmate, Xia Menghuan. So kind-hearted.
- So noble.
- I'm serious.
- Okay, okay! I was joking.
Later, I'll do a thorough search at LUU,
from the artificial lake to the rock garden. Not to mention stray animals,
a caterpillar or earthworm won't even be missed.
To realize our goal of no animals left behind without winter shelter. All right?
Well said. Let's do it.
But we only have ¥3000, is that enough to take care of them?
So many homeless animals...
We don't have enough but I have a method.
Your way of saving money is to use me as free labor.
We spent around ¥2,700 on all the materials, we still have over ¥200 left.
You're not... not thinking about adding two more, right?
It's enough. I'll buy you a nice dinner with what's left.
Stop talking about food. I care more than that.
But I think there is a new restaurant behind our school, I heard it's not bad.
Then let's go there. You don't need to make excuses.
Go change into the uniform in the changing room, and then wait in the training room.
Li Yubing, center forward position.
79.4 kg, you are a bit light for the center forward.
Wayne Gretzky was also this weight when he was 18.
Go get changed.
Cai Lei, winger position, 87.5kg.
90.7 kg.
Same as Sidney Crosby.
Go get changed.
Did you see Song Anjie?
It's his second time on the team.
Coach Wang coached him personally. He just returned from abroad.
But this year, we have an Ice God, Li Yubing, who also plays center forward.
There will be a fierce battle.
What battle? We are on the same team.
- Hi, Brother Jie.
- Brother Jie.
Fall in! In two lines.
I don't care how many years you've played hockey, don't care if you've been under me before,
don't care if you've been in the national youth team before.
Starting today, you are all newbies.
Today is your first day of practice. Why don't you all introduce yourselves?
Cai Lei, age 19, Harbin Bears, winger position.
Song Anjie, age 20, Harbin Bears, center forward.
Li Yubing, age 18, LUU XDragons, center forward position.
Jia Chuanzhi, age 18, Hohhot Qilin, forward position.
Zhe Yefan, age 19, Hohhot Tigers, defender position.
Zhang Cheng, age 20, Qingcheng Warriors, defender position.
Li Kun, age 20, Beijing Yellow Sea, defender position.
Run 50 laps as punishment.
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
only you can understand ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ I had the kind of luck as if I plucked a star ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings, I couldn’t
believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise
and take you traveling ♫
♫ In this big world, I’ll hold gently onto the secrets
you are protecting ♫
♫ I’m lucky to receive the surprise that came like a shock,
it’s a promise you’re giving me ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫
♫ The first time I saw your smile, my heart fell for you,
it must be destiny ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand and travel to the rainbow
to pluck a star ♫
♫ Secretly listening to your feelings and let the stars
fulfill each of your dreams ♫
♫ I want to collect every expression of yours, they are
the four seasons that belong to me ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings, I couldn’t
believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise
and take you traveling ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like the sweet sea breeze ♫
♫ it is the signal you are giving me ♫
♫ This moment when your smile is like the sun ♫
♫ As if I’m nibbling a juicy peach, a beautiful love blossoms ♫
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
(only you can understand) ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫