♫ Anticipating tomorrow, surpassing the limit
because you are by my side ♫
♫ Our beliefs overcame the difficulties, not giving up
to advance bravely ♫
♫ The youngster is running with determined eyes
even in the face of a difficult challenge ♫
♫ Youth is persevering until the end, fearless and
never ceasing ♫
♫ Passion ignites and enthusiasm unchanging ♫
♫ Believe in tomorrow and shout it out ♫
♫ Continuously embrace every new starting point ♫
♫ Continuously pursue perfection in this moment ♫
♫ The dawn of victory, oh~ fluttering its wings ♫
♫ Flying with no fear of the storm oh~ ♫
♫ Pointing towards the direction of my heart ♫
♫ The dawn of hope, oh~ shining boundlessly ♫
♫ Taking off with no fear of the surging waves oh~ ♫
♫ Running towards and pursuing ♫
♫ The brightest place in my heart ♫
[Skate into Love]
[Episode 20]
When you were little, your face was almost scarred because of her. It gave me such a scare.
Tang Xue's mother even offered to give me her daughter
as a daughter-in-law to make up for it.
It's okay. It's not a serious injury. Don't worry.
It's nothing to worry about, he just fell into the bushes.
Your son is so brave.
I've been cleaning him up for a while, he didn't cry or complain at all.
This little boy is going to be something in the future.
Tang Xue.
Why are you here?
Auntie, here's an apple for you.
Thank you.
What's wrong? Why are your eyes red? Did someone bully you?
Auntie will punish them for you.
This incident definitely has something to do with her.
- You're all good now.
- Do you know her?
I'm sorry. She's my daughter.
She was being naughty and caused your son to get hurt.
Apologize to Auntie.
Don't worry about it. These things happen when kids are playing around.
This child.
I just want to ask, will Li Yubing's face be scarred?
If his face is scarred, how will he get married in the future?
No, no! It won't scar.
If his face does get scarred,
I'll give you my daughter to be your daughter-in-law.
Okay, sounds good.
Can I say no?
Right. Is Tang Xue dating anyone now?
Dad, can you tell her to be less nosy?
- It's fine.
- You stop talking. Eat more vegetables.
Son, tell your mom.
What fun things have you and Tang Xue been up to at college?
Let's just eat. Let's just eat.
Are you trying to frustrate me?
Mom!
You're back!
Let me get a good look at you.
I'll wash my hands and make another dish for Tang Xue.
Hurry up then.
Let me look at you. Turn around.
Look at your butt, your thighs, young lady.
Your muscles have grown a lot.
Aren't you studying veterinary medicine?
If I didn't know better, I'd think you were at the sports college.
I've been discovered so quickly.
Isn't your mom humorous? Isn't she cute?
I'm just joking with you.
How should I tell them I transferred departments?
Stop standing there! Come quickly.
I made a table full of your favorite dishes.
I spent all morning cooking these for you.
Your dad cooked for you, too.
Whatever. There's still the whole break ahead of us. Let's take it slow.
Yes, yes! This was all you're effort.
Why do you still have this bad habit?
All the germs you got from your trip back home is going to go into your stomach. Go wash your hands.
- Right away!
- This child, really.
Our family hasn't sat down to a meal together in so long.
Exactly. Should we have a drink?
- Let's have a drink.
- This is for you.
- Cheers to Mom and Dad!
- Thanks, Daughter.
I hope you guys are healthy, live long, and are by my side forever.
Drink slowly. I'll propose a toast, too.
I hope my daughter succeeds in her career
and becomes a well-known doctor.
I hope my daughter is always healthy and happy.
Thanks, Mom and Dad!
Did you come back with Xiao Liao again?
No.
Then, who'd you come back with?
Li Yubing.
Li Yubing? It sounds so familiar.
He's my deskmate from elementary school.
I remember now. When you were little, you pushed him into the bushes and he got injured, right?
It's a good thing I was on-call in the hospital that day.
His mom came to me and was worried her son's face would be scarred.
She was worried he wouldn't be able to get married later, so I said,
It's okay, don't worry If he can't find a wife,
he can have our Xiao Xue as compensation." It's him, right?
I'm so pretty now, and there are so many people pursuing me.
If you give me to him as compensation, it's a big loss for us.
It was just a joke.
Xue'er, do you think Li Yubing is pursuing you?
Ask him.
I won't ask.
In the future, don't hang out with him too much.
Why?
Because...
Because I'm your dad. You have to listen to me.
What kind of reason is that?
Yeah, what kind of reason is that?
Eat, eat.
Coach Chu said I need to maintain my condition. Let's go skate together tomorrow.
Okay, tomorrow at 10:00. Let's meet at the mall entrance.
[Polka Time Restaurant]
Here, the information you requested.
Thanks.
Why do you want my uncle's newspaper office's information?
I want to know more about the older generation of the news industry.
You're so humble.
Uncle Tang has worked at the newspaper for so many years.
His experience is very helpful for our generation to learn from.
If an MU genius student like you is learning from him,
he would be really happy if he knew.
I'm really happy, too.
What is it that you want to do exactly?
Learn.
You want to use this opportunity to get closer to my uncle, right?
Uncle Tang, as Tang Xue's father,
must have some influence over her.
Going the route of the father-in-law. Pretty smart of you.
I can't do it without the help of her dear cousin.
Let's talk again next time.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye-bye, Cousin.
Teacher Li had a baby recently. Let's go see her sometime.
[Tang Xue]
Hello, Tang Xue? I heard Teacher Li from our high school had a baby recently.
Should we go and visit her?
Do you have time today?
I'm busy today.
What do you have to do that's so important?
In high school, you were Teacher Li's favorite.
Coach Chu said we have to maintain our condition on-ice so I'm training today.
I'll find another time to go.
Is that so? Okay.
- Next time.
- Yeah, next time.
Skating?
[Ice rink]
There's only one ice rink around your house.
Even if you don't accept my invitation, I can run into you by chance.
Tang Xue, see you soon.
Why are you so late?
My dad made me read the newspaper to him at home. He wouldn't let me leave.
Young man, do you want to buy some flowers?
I'm in a good mood today. Pick one, I'll buy it for you.
- This one?
- This is from my dad's newspaper.
Your dad?
He's a news editor.
Their newspaper is the heart of international news and the life of metro news.
It used to be pretty popular.
They're known for publishing serious discussions.
But nowadays, everyone is mesmerized by celebrity news.
Now, their newspaper has become flower wrapping.
Your dad hasn't considered giving up?
No. He said someone has to carry on. I quite admire him.
You and he are pretty similar.
You don't want the flowers?
[Mangrove Tree Food Hall]
Li Yubing, why is he here?
Hey, Tang Xue.
Why did you come here?
I just wanted to learn about ice skating and experience
what your favorite sport is like.
There are so many people here! Did you think you were at the training grounds?
I know.
Sorry.
It's okay. Tang Xue, everyone who ice skates is like this, right?
Stop standing around and go skate.
Tang Xue,
how about you give me a couple of tips?
After I got on the ice this time, I felt like a dumb log.
All right, I'll teach you.
Tang Xue, go skate. Don't worry.
You're welcome. I'll teach you.
I'll hold you while you skate. Slowly.
Left, right, left, right.
Left, right.
Left. Off you go!
Li Yubing, you did that on purpose. Right?
Yes! What about it?
I like Tang Xue.
Me too.
But for the past three years, the person Tang Xue liked was me.
It's okay.
I've forgiven her already.
It looks like you're not her boyfriend yet.
Sooner or later, I will be.
Where does your confidence come from?
Tang Xue gave it and I think she's quite happy right now.
At least, happier than when she liked you.
What are you guys doing? Did you finish practicing?
Tang Xue, how did your skating go?
Pretty good, but I'm getting ready to go back home now.
We skated pretty well, too.
Coach Li tried his hardest to teach me, and we understand each other quite well.
Isn't that right, Coach Li?
Welcome!
Big Jiang?
- Brother Tie.
- Alone?
Right, I came by myself.
What do you want to eat?
I'm not eating today.
I have a favor to beg of you.
You're not eating and you still have a favor to beg of me? Go ahead.
On Chinese New Year's Eve, make a reservation for me for dinner.
You're staying at Lincheng alone and not going home to celebrate Chinese New Year?
As soon as I go home, my parents will urge me to go on blind dates. I can avoid it this way.
Moreover, when we celebrate Chinese New Year, I think you're probably lonely. I'll keep you company.
Thank you. I'm frantically busy on Chinese New Year's Eve. Don't cause me any trouble.
Brother Tie, just serve me this one time. I beg you.
Fine. How many people? What do you want to eat? I'll prepare it for you.
Not many people. Two people. This time, Wei-wei's not leaving either.
I was wondering if you can make a spicier hot pot. She loves eating spicy food.
It's the New Year celebration. Things should be red and hot.
The key point here is that you can't eat spicy food.
I'll just practice, right?
Big Jiang, if you like a person,
then tell them directly.
What do I say?
Tell Wei-wei that you like her.
It's not shameful when a man's braver and more direct.
But her eyes have never left—
But your eyes have also never left her.
♫ I couldn’t believe in that split second, she who
believed you or I shed tears ♫
Old man, you understand everything.
It's decided then. I'm going to get going.
You're still putting on an act.
Come over earlier on Chinese New Year's Eve.
♫ I still love you ♫
Boss, are you open on New Year's Eve?
I'm taking a one-day break on New Year's Eve. I'm coming back to work on New Year's Day. Sorry.
Oh, all right then.
Tang Xue, don't you think the ice in this ice rink is really stiff?
It's not as comfortable to skate here compared to our school.
Of course. After all, it's a commercial ice rink. It's understandable.
If you're talking about the best venue, it's, of course, the international competition venue.
I heard that in order to maintain the flexibility of the ice,
they added a certain amount of milk in there.
This way it would be especially soft when you step on it.
For such an ice rink, we have to keep up the good work.
Oh right, I heard that Xijiao opened another ice rink. We should go some time.
All right.
Athletes, like you guys, really can put up with things regular people can't.
Today, I experienced your daily routine. It's pretty difficult.
Us athletes have cheap bones.
(T/N: miserable or worthless creatures)
We are obsessed with the feeling of our muscles tearing, it makes our blood flow.
It's the feeling of adrenaline shooting up. Isn't it, Li Yubing?
Then I'll be heading back first.
Today, thank you, Coach Li, for your advice.
I benefited a lot from this.
No problem. You can come and find me anytime you need.
- Tang Xue, I'll get going.
- Bye-bye.
I'll take you home.
- Let's go.
Dad, I'm back.
Hey, you haven't shown up all afternoon. Where did you go?
I skated—
I slid down slides.
Sliding down slides?
Those are for kids. Are you sure you didn't break the slide with your physique?
If I did, how would I be here?
You're still a child at heart.
It's not just a child that is in my heart.
Dad, isn't it weird?
When I went to slide down slides today,
I strangely felt something that I used to experience
back then when I was ice skating.
A feeling where my heart was racing and my blood was pumping.
If you look at me now,
I'm young, strong, and healthy.
If I go back and...
try ice skating again...
is that okay?
You better not be telling me that... you still want to skate?
I'm just saying.
Don't talk about it!
Do you know how distraught we were when you had that accident last time?
In a matter of one night, so many of my hairs turned white.
Your mom has fainted more times than I can count.
Let me tell you, Daughter.
You're our only daughter.
I don't have any extravagant hopes for you.
I just hope that you'll healthily and peacefully grow up.
Really, we have nothing more to ask for. We're satisfied with the way things are right now.
Moreover, skating...
will cause you so much damage. I...
Dad, I was just saying.
Don't get too excited. Don't.
Daughter!
It's good if you become a vet!
Study well and stop thinking about those nonsensical things.
I don't have any extravagant hopes for you.
I just hope that you'll healthily and peacefully grow up.
Really, we have nothing more to ask for. We're satisfied with the way things are right now.
Tang Xue, are you asleep yet?
Not yet. What's up?
Tomorrow, I want to go back and take a look around our elementary school. Let's go together.
Okay.
I tentatively asked my dad
about returning back to learning short track speed skating.
His attitude about this was extremely determined. He rejected me without hesitation.
He's worried that you'll get hurt. Parents, you know,
hope that we live a long life peacefully.
Compared to getting hurt, I'm more scared of living long while being bored.
Then, what do you plan to do?
Anyways, I already transferred majors. I'll keep it a secret from them as long as I can.
I think it's better to tell them earlier than later.
They don't approve now. It'll be even more of a hassle later on.
I just managed to get into the short track speed skating team.
What if I tell them and they don't approve. Do you want me to switch back to veterinary medicine?
All right, all right! Stop stressing out. Take it easy.
I wonder what the school is like right now.
Let's go!
I forgot. It's winter break now, so the school is locked.
Let's go.
[Hucheng City Primary School]
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Climbing the gate.
Climbing over? No, that's too dangerous. Let's go through the back.
I just want to climb the gate. I haven't climbed in so long.
What kind of interests are these?
After so many years, you're still such a good boy.
Did you hurt yourself?
It's nothing.
Let me see.
It's bleeding. Let me blow on it.
You have to kiss it so it won't hurt.
So annoying...
Did you hit your head as well?
It's nothing. Thanks.
It looks the same.
♫ I see you but the nervous one is me ♫
Come. It's our class.
[Year 3, Class 1]
♫ The wind gently blows past my ear ♫
♫ The falling leaves are reminding me ♫
♫ I’ll consider the lost times as ♫
♫ Brushing past you ♫
♫ Don’t want to say much more ♫
♫ I just want to embrace you in this moment ♫
♫ My heart was healed by you long ago ♫
♫ It has started falling into every corner of you ♫
♫ Breathing close to you to be affected by you ♫
♫ My eyes are twinkling and my pulse is quickening ♫
♫ You carefully stand on your tiptoes to tell me ♫
Actually, that time we were all happy.
You were really happy.
And you weren't?
No, I was also happy.
Do you think that thing is still here?
What thing?
What do you think?
♫ Keeping your hands warm in the harsh winter ♫
Do you still remember where it is?
I don't remember.
Let me tell you.
Here. Mine is this one and yours is that one.
Come on.
It's been six years, even I almost forgot about this.
Do you still remember our promise?
When we turn 18, we come here and dig up our wishing bottles.
What did you write?
Whatever I wrote is nonsense. It was from when we were little.
Did you write bad things about me?
No way.
If you wrote bad things about me,
I will kill you.
We've been digging for so long, how come I still haven't dug it out?
I told you it probably won't be here anymore. Let's just leave.
Continue digging.
[I wish my terrible deskmate, Tang Xue will disappear from this world.]
Li Yubing!
Look. I told you that it would be here.
You also dug it out. Is this your bottle?
Where is it?
It's gone.
It probably flew away like a butterfly.
Then I'm the Fragrant Concubine.
(T/N: a character in "My Fair Princess" whose body scent attracted butterflies)
I'm telling you, my piece of paper probably was very fragrant.
I think at the time I wrote: "I'll definitely pass every test!"
Maybe another little kid took it and used it as a good luck charm.
If that was the case, you wouldn't be Li Yubing, you'd be Koi Fish Bing. If I retweet, then will good luck come to you?
(T/N: Koi Fish is a homophone for Li Yu)
Stand up.
How did you know I was going to search your body?
I said there isn't.
Stop looking. What did you write?
My wish is that
every time Li Yubing takes a test, he'll get a big fat zero.
Tang Xue, you're so mean to me.
That's because you always got good grades back then.
My deskmate is called Li Yubing. He's a very annoying guy.
Why am I annoyed by him?
Because Grandpa promised me, if I could get first in the class for the exam,
he'd take me to Disneyland. I really want to go to Disneyland.
But I'm not first in the class. Li Yubing is.
Teacher praised Li Yubing at the parent-teacher conference. Dad said to me,
"Look at Li Yubing, then look at yourself."
I hope Teacher will stop praising Li Yubing,
because he's too annoying.
Okay, stop reading.
Do you know why teacher asked you to come to the office?
Classmates should be united and friendly,
helping each other and improving together.
Look at Li Yubing's essay.
It's all kind words about you.
He said he likes a deskmate like you.
But then look at your essay. What did you say about him?
Teacher knows you want to get first place. That's a good thing.
But we have to depend on our own hard work and improvement.
We can't hope for other students to deteriorate.
If you have a little improvement, Teacher will also praise you.
See! There weren't any incorrect characters in your essay this time.
This is a type of improvement. It's really worth praising.
Li Yubing helped to correct this for me.
Then next time, I'll let him correct it again.
Tell your parents to come tomorrow.
So, were you able to go to Disneyland?
Thanks to you, I have still never visited there.
If I knew you had this wish,
I would've pretended to be sick and not taken the test.
Hepatitis, gastritis, appendicitis.
I'd say anything for your wish to come true.
Actually,
I should thank you.
I was happy in those years because I had you.
Sorry, Tang Xue.
I didn't keep our promise.
It's been a long time since then. Let's not mention unhappy memories.
But I promise you.
From now on, we won't ever be separated.
Promise?
Promise.
It shouldn't be.
Open your mouth.
Tongue.
Down.
Right.
Li Yubing.
You're such a great guy. During these years, why haven't you dated anyone?
I have someone I like.
Who?
You want to know?
I'm not telling you.
So what if you have one, I have one, too.
Who?
Do you want to know?
It's definitely not you.
Go home!
Tang Xue.
Dummy.
The girl I like is you.
[Crystal Sugar stewed with Snow Pear]
[Dummy. The girl I like is you.]
So what if you have one, I have one, too.
I have someone I like.
Who?
I'm not telling you.
Xiao Xia, I miss you.
Listen. This city is really empty.
[Li Yubing]
Hey, Ice God. It's late, what's going on?
It's something urgent.
Xiao Liao,
today, Tang Xue told me that
she has someone she likes. Do you think it's me?
Say, do you think Master Tang might like Yu Yan?
See.
He's a champion, he's gentle, and he's handsome, too.
Who wouldn't like this kind of Little Sheep, right?
I doubt it. I don't think Tang Xue is into the underage type.
Besides, Yu Yan left already.
That's true.
Then it must be Bian Cheng.
Top student, mature, like a melancholy prince.
Also, he was the first boy Master Tang ever liked.
Impossible.
She wouldn't go back to the past.
(T/N: idiom: a good horse doesn't go back to the same pasture)
I don't think Tang Xue feels that way.
That's what you think.
Li Yubing, I have a small immature suggestion.
The early bird gets a worm and the late bird suffers.
Such a great girl is
like a Chinese New Year train ticket.
When you check on the computer, there are lots of tickets,
but in reality, each ticket is hard to get.
I'll leave it at that.
Think about it on your own.
Ponder it for a while. I'm hanging up. Bye-bye.
Hey–
Listen, how heavy is this brow?
Listen. How intense is this longing?
[Master Tang]
Master Tang, what is it this time?
Little Yuzi, there's something I need you to think about for me.
Li Yubing told me he has someone he likes today.
You're close with him, tell me who it is.
Master Tang, why are you asking about this?
Could it be... you like Li Yubing?
I—
What? I can't hear you. Speak up!
What'd you say?
I like Li Yubing.
Do you have a death wish? Hurry up. Analyze it for me.
Say, do you think Li Yubing might like Zhang Yuewei?
See. She's a champion, she's cool and mysterious.
This kind of girl can make a lot of guys want to fight for her.
Plus, the two of them hang out a lot.
I don't think so. They're like brothers.
Then it must be Zhou Ran.
Zhou Ran is the prettiest girl in school,
she has good grades, and such long legs, too.
She has everything that guys look for in a girl.
I don't think that's possible either.
If they were going to get together it would have happened already, why would he wait until now?
It's not too late now either, Master Tang.
I have a small immature suggestion.
Men are like the food in our cafeteria.
It doesn't taste good, but if you go late, there won't be any left.
Especially a specialty dish like Li Yubing, a lot of people will definitely fight for him.
I'll leave it at that.
Let's keep it simple. Master Tang, you think about it on your own.
I'm hanging up. Bye-bye.
If longing could be heard,
mine would be deafening.
Little Xia, it's so late, you haven't slept yet?
I miss you. What are you doing?
I miss you, too.
You're lying. Why didn't you call me?
It's not that. I was writing you a—
Write?
Hold on,
someone's calling me. I'll call you back in a bit.
Explain what you were saying first. What were you writing?
Ice God, what's up? Hurry up, I'm busy.
I've thought it through. I need to take action.
I've decided to be proactive.
Do you have any ideas? What do you think I should do?
You're an Ice God, and you still need to ask other people about this kind of thing?
Let me think.
For this kind of thing, there are three steps.
The first step is to carefully pick a location.
Second, create a romantic atmosphere.
Third, hug her. That's it.
Why does it sound so easy when you say it?
Yeah! It is that easy. What's so hard about this?
Bing, I have to go. I'm hanging up.
Wait. What location should I pick?
Since you're confessing, choose a place that has a ceremonial feel to it. Okay?
This idea is good.
Brother Bing, I really have to go. If I don't go now, I'll be dead.
Bye-bye, I'm really done. Hanging up now.
[hammer to head emoticons]
[knife emoticons]
I'm dead.
I was too focused on them.
Huan-huan, I was writing you a test message.
I don't think I can send this message tonight.
Let's do this. I'll just read it out to you. Okay?
Listen. This city is so empty.
Listen. This longing is so intense.
This road has all this heavy traffic.
(T/N: idiom: road with an endless stream of horses and carriages)
Who can I share it with?
Alone. Alone.
- Hello?
- Hello? It's so late, why aren't you here yet?
Traffic. Relax, I've already arranged everything for you.
I promise it's going to be a great surprise.
Hurry up, I'm panicking. This is such an important matter.
Plus, this moment is going to determine my life. Nothing can go wrong.
I'm reliable, don't worry.
I promise you'll have everything you need, and everything you don't need, too.
Just stop worrying, okay?
Everything I don't need? What does that mean?
Stop asking, stop asking. You'll find out soon.
I'm hanging up.
Hello? Hello?
What are you looking at?
You're here?
Look at this cathedral. It's so pretty. So pretty.
It's been here for so long, you just found out it was pretty?
That's true. I didn't really notice it before.
How can Liao Zhenyu be late at the most important time?
- Bro, what are you doing?
- For the last six years, all I thought about was you.
Nothing else, only you!
Everything I need, and everything I don't need, too.
Why would you be with this kind of lousy scum?
Come here, bro, come here. Listen to me.
Let's just do a classic "Hero rescues damsel in distress."
Don't worry, I'll be gentle.
Are you drunk?
- Didn't Liao Zhenyu send you?
- Are you crazy?
He's drunk. Li Yubing, let's go.
- Tang Xue.
- You can't leave.
When she was little, she said she liked romantic cathedrals.
I thought our reunion was fate.
But when I confessed to her here, why did she reject me?
Are all girls this ruthless?
You guys were apart for so long.
Right? You both changed over the years. Maybe she's not ruthless, she's just grown up.
Some emotions that you hold in your heart are precious memories.
If you say them out loud, it just ruins that feeling.
Loving someone shouldn't be like this.
If you keep treating her like this, she will definitely think she was right to reject you. Right?
I shouldn't have confessed today.
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
only you can understand ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ I had the kind of luck as if I plucked a star ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise and take
you traveling ♫
♫ In this big world, I’ll hold gently onto the secrets
you are protecting ♫
♫ I’m lucky to receive the surprise that came like a shock,
it’s a promise you’re giving me ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫
♫ The first time I saw your smile, my heart fell for you,
it must be destiny ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand and travel to the rainbow
to pluck a star ♫
♫ Secretly listening to your feelings and let the stars
fulfill each of your dreams ♫
♫ I want to collect every expression of yours, they are
the four seasons that belong to me ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise and take
you traveling ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like the sweet sea breeze ♫
♫ It is the signal you are giving me ♫
♫ This moment when your smile is like the sun ♫
♫ As if I’m nibbling a juicy peach, a beautiful love blossoms ♫
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
(only you can understand) ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫