♫ Anticipating tomorrow, surpassing the limit
because you are by my side ♫
♫ Our beliefs overcame the difficulties, not giving up
to advance bravely ♫
♫ The youngster is running with determined eyes
even in the face of a difficult challenge ♫
♫ Youth is persevering until the end, fearless and
never ceasing ♫
♫ Passion ignites and enthusiasm unchanging ♫
♫ Believe in tomorrow and shout it out ♫
♫ Continuously embrace every new starting point ♫
♫ Continuously pursue perfection in this moment ♫
♫ The dawn of victory, oh~ fluttering its wings ♫
♫ Flying with no fear of the storm oh~ ♫
♫ Pointing towards the direction of my heart ♫
♫ The dawn of hope, oh~ shining boundlessly ♫
♫ Taking off with no fear of the surging waves oh~ ♫
♫ Running towards and pursuing ♫
♫ The brightest place in my heart ♫
[Skate into Love]
[Episode 18]
Can I write a letter to the principal asking to get rid of the Glorious Youth Festival?
Why would we get rid of it? It's a great festival. Old Ye, what do you think?
Battle of the mountain cave.
A person's ability to accept other people's ideas determines their accomplishments.
Old Ye, you're so accomplished.
Did you spend the whole day studying in the dorm again?
What else? I'm not like you guys. One has a boyfriend who supports her dreams,
the other has a high school classmate who came to surprise her.
I have books. Books are my teachers and friends.
Books are the stairs humans climb to greatness, they are the fruit of human intelligence.
- Huan-huan.
- Yes?
What did Liao Zhenyu do today?
Today, since there were so many people out celebrating the Glorious Youth Festival, he raised over ¥10,000 for our Home for Homeless Babies.
How nice.
Why is that for me, the Glorious Youth Festival is just a day of hardship?
When I think about the final exam, my days seem hopeless. I almost want to die.
There's no point in complaining. Shortcuts...
What?
Do not exist.
Francis Bacon said, "Life is like a road,
the closest shortcut is usually the worst."
Old Ye, can you give some constructive suggestions?
I already set the alarm. Tomorrow morning, we'll get up early
and study together.
What?
Good luck.
Time doesn't wait for us, young people. Let's get moving.
- I still have to shower.
- I still have to wash my face.
Good luck.
Here, I've outlined it for you. Just review these topics.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't study anymore.
If I spend every day like this, I won't last until the exam.
Master Tang, do you want to try my psychological suggestions?
- "Blindly Guessing Happy"!
- Exactly!
(T/N: homophone of her name)
You give yourself a small psychological suggestion and it can give you awesome energy!
This is what Xiao Liao taught me.
You're already so good with your field of study, yet you still need to blindly guess. Should I even take the test anymore?
I'm not that good at it.
You can try, too. What is your name's homophone?
[Dripping Blood]
(T/N: homophone of her name)
I suggest that you go with another approach.
Stop worrying so much. I already outlined all the topics for you.
The topics I outlined for you are very likely to be on the exam.
[World's Top Test-taker]
As long as you are familiar with those topics, you can get whatever score I can get. I promise.
I didn't know studying with a top student would make me feel so secure.
I'm pretty useful, right?
But what about my competition?
Are you okay?
When doing anything, if you want to improve in a short time, the best method is to
have an expert lead you.
I think you should find an expert in your field to help you out.
An expert in my field?
[World's Top Baking King]
(T/N: test-taking and baking are homophones in chinese)
Li Yubing!
That one will do.
Morning.
Why did you throw rocks at my window?
Do you think it was because I wanted to? I called you but you didn't pick up.
I wanted to sleep in so I turned my phone off. What's going on?
By the way, why'd you run off during the Glorious Youth Festival?
It was... an impulse.
I heard your high school classmate gave you a grand confession.
If the rumors continue like this, are they going to start saying I'm marrying him soon?
Why?
Were you also going to confess to me that day?
Also, you were the one who told me not to date in the first place.
I said that because—
If Coach Chu actually kicks me out of the team, everything I've done will have been for nothing.
Enough of that, I have something serious to discuss.
In a few days, Coach Chu wants me to compete in the Tengxiang Cup.
But I feel like my training has reached a bottleneck recently.
My performance just won't improve.
So?
I want an expert in the field to lead me.
Lead you? Do you think we're playing video games? ¥50 an hour?
(about $7.05)
Old Ye said, if I want to improve in a short time, the best way is to
have an expert lead me. This method is tried and true.
I am an expert, but...
Okay, I'll think about it.
Last time, someone lied to me about having a fever,
what should I do about it?
Okay, I'll guide your training.
Then, let's call it even with what happened that day.
It's settled.
297, 298, 299, 300.
Get up.
Wasn't that the last set?
After you workout, you have to stretch. Get up.
I can't live like this. I have to train so much every day,
and I have to pass the final exam, too. And our professor
really doesn't like me. Should I just transfer to the sports college?
Seems like that would solve everything.
You're not studying to be a vet anymore?
I have to admit it.
I just don't have the talent for it.
I could spend 10 years studying and learn less than Huan-huan does in a month.
The professor was right.
People should do what they are good at and are passionate about.
If it's not something you're passionate about, there's no point.
It's like...
It's like if someone forced you to date a girl you don't like.
Are you being serious?
I'll think about it after I get through the final exam.
Huan-huan can take care of my major classes, but what about advanced math?
For advanced math, you can find someone to tutor you.
Old Ye and Huan-huan are busy with their own studies, how can I ask them to help even more?
What if... I'm be kind enough and tutor you?
You?
What? You don't think I'm qualified?
That's right. You've always been a high-level top student!
Then I'll officially entrust myself in your care.
(T/N: a phrase parents will say when their child is getting married)
It sounds like you're marrying yourself off to me.
It's not that, I–
You dare to tease Master Tang?
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your smile is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise and take
you traveling ♫
The library is going to be pretty packed, so come early tomorrow morning. Put on your shoes; let's go.
Let's go!
Tang Xue, do you really not care if I leave?
You're about to leave for Canada, aren't you going to pack?
I'll go pack now.
If you don't want to go,
I won't force you.
I can make my own decision?
Of course.
You're an adult now. You can make your own decisions.
But I have one point to say.
Mom is not trying to break you and Tang Xue apart.
I'm making you go to Canada because I want you to become better.
Because I know Tang Xue is a speed skater.
One day, she'll become a world champion.
What qualifications will you have to stand next to her?
Silly child.
Mom can't be by your side forever.
You can decide who you like and who to be with
when you grow up, isn't that right?
But before you become a world champion,
Mom is afraid you'll make a mistake every step you take.
Yan-yan,
all the efforts I put on you doesn't matter to me.
But you can't, you're my son.
I can't let my son's effort go down the drain.
I won't be able to endure that.
Mom,
I'll go.
Here.
You're so early.
My thirst for knowledge is bursting.
Here, here, here.
Can you help with this problem? I already tried to do it many times.
Let me see.
Let me look at this problem's reasoning.
Which formula?
No, no. This formula.
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing became erratic ♫
♫ I had the kind of luck as if I plucked a star ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
Why are you staring at me?
Did someone take your rank?
Are you even a top student? You can't even do the first question.
Let me think about it. Sit properly.
Sit properly.
♫ This moment when your smile is the same ♫
♫ As if I’m nibbling a juicy peach, a beautiful love blossoms ♫
♫ In this big world, I’ll hold gently onto the secrets
you are protecting ♫
My god! How did I fall for you?
I must have an issue.
♫ Loving with no reason until I met you ♫
You got me. You asked me to come help tutor you, but
you slept for forty minutes.
Are you blaming me?
Who was explaining the problems
so in-depth and hard to understand? We only got through three problems this whole morning.
How could I stay awake?
Fine! It's my fault. I'll repay you next time.
Okay.
It hurts.
What happened?
I accidentally twisted my ankle.
I'll send you back.
Then, we'll send you back?
No need. Your bike can only fit one person in the back.
I'm in a rush to get back. They're calling me. I'll leave first.
Tang Xue!
Senior Yubing, sorry to bother you.
Old Deng!
Do you know where the girl's dormitory for the broadcasting department is?
I know.
She twisted her ankle, send her back.
No need! I can go back on my own.
Don't. Didn't you twist your ankle?
- Fatty, she's all yours.
- Sure.
Bye-bye.
Li Yubing, even if you don't like me,
you can't like Tang Xue.
Let's go, Junior.
Senior, there's no need. I can go back slowly on my own.
- Let's go.
- I can walk slowly.
My ankle... My ankle is actually twisted this time.
Don't worry. I will complete the task my brother assigned me no matter what.
Let's go!
How is it?
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Let me know if you're injured.
- I'm fine.
What's wrong with you? Do you not look where you're going?
- Are the eyes below your eyebrows not working?
- You again.
Are you kidding me?
It was you who was only looking at the pretty girl and didn't see me and hit me.
I'm the victim.
Are your words the truth? Do you have evidence?
What a coincidence! Our school has security cameras everywhere.
Let's go to the control room right now.
We're all fellow students. Don't make this a bigger problem.
My Goddess has spoken.
Tell me! What should we do?
I'm afraid I might have internal injuries, send me to the clinic.
You–
You should help send this student, I'm fine. I can walk myself.
Let me send you.
No problem. I can walk myself.
- Goddess, walk slowly.
- Okay.
- Be careful on the road.
My heart is with you.
Let me tell you, I ride my bike fast. Hold on tight.
Men and women should not touch. Please don't touch my skin.
Why are you grabbing my collar? How can I watch the road?
Don't you like seeing with your belly button? Just use your belly button to watch the road.
Let go. Let go!
Next week is Tengxiang Cup. This is your number.
Stay in good condition these days and don't over practice.
Thanks, Coach.
They all call me the Iron Hammer behind my back.
But I don't need to push you because you're tough enough on yourself.
If all the team members were like you and Zhang Yuewei, then I wouldn't worry so much.
It was you who gave me an opportunity to join the short track speed skating team.
If it wasn't for you, I wouldn't even have an opportunity to work hard.
I'll let Li Yubing tell her himself.
Do well in your competition.
Is balancing school work and training at the same time tough?
I want to switch my major.
You thought it through? Did you discuss it with your parents?
About how I got injured in the past...
I don't even need to think and I know their response.
So I want to transfer first and then see what happens.
You need to think it through clearly.
If you transfer, there's no way out.
I don't want to give myself a way out. This way I can fight to win or die.
Good.
Whatever it is, I'll always support you.
Comeback Battle. Come watch if you have time.
Wow!
Master Tang, what are you saying?
Huan-huan and I will definitely be at your comeback battle to give you morale!
It happens that I'm free that day, so I'll grudgingly come and watch.
Tang Xue, I can't come to your competition.
The day before the competition is the day I leave for Canada.
You're leaving so soon?
You're going to Canada?
That means we have two happy events.
Yu Yan is going abroad for training, and I'm returning to the ice track.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
Tang Xue, do you really think I should go?
Why wouldn't you go?
You're not disappointed from the Glorious Youth Festival incident, are you?
You'll only be disappointed if you don't expect it.
Since I'd already expected it, how would I be disappointed?
Sometimes I feel like you're a bit scary.
How am I scary?
Scary that you're so mature. We're all just college students,
but you're trying to be even deeper than my grandpa is.
You live with such clear distinctions. Does your life even have any fun in it?
Are you saying that a chaotic life would have fun in it?
If a person lived without a goal,
things would be unclear and they wouldn't know how to achieve their goal.
They'd be living their entire life accomplishing nothing.
You're also someone with clear goals, right?
That's why we work together well.
Oh right!
This is a ticket to Tang Xue's Tengxiang Cup competition.
The competition is right at LUU. Are you coming?
I'll come. I'll also write a news report
that allows Tang Xue to re-emerge in the world of short track speed skating.
How do you know she'll definitely win?
Even if she loses, it can work. News reports have a lot of different aspects.
Whoever is your enemy will definitely die very tragically.
You should say, whoever is my friend
will definitely be very fortunate.
I hope so.
Come in.
Professor Zhou, are you free?
[Office]
You don't need to beg. You have to score 80 points to pass.
I'm not going to lower it for you.
I didn't come to ask you to lower the requirement.
I...
would like to...transfer majors next semester.
Transfer?
I want to transfer to the sports college and focus on training short track speed skating.
Then, why didn't you go to the Sports College from the start?
I was injured at the time and was forced to give up.
I thought I'd never be able to be an athlete again in my lifetime.
The first day of your class, you mentioned passion.
At that time, my head was full of speed skating.
I think that maybe the idea of speed skating was just in hibernation for a long time.
Now that the weather has warmed up, it's time for it to wake up.
It was difficult to get an opportunity for me to start again.
I'd like to try it.
You young people...
If you want to transfer today, would you transfer back tomorrow?
But it's great to be young.
When I was young, our teacher
made us write an essay called "my ideal dream."
Truthfully, what kind of dream did I even have at that time?
In the blink of an eye, I'd entered the middle-aged stage of life.
In this stage of life, if you tell people you've got a dream,
people would definitely laugh and say you're just dreaming.
So, regarding dreams,
it seems it's only suitable for those few years of your youth.
Tang Xue, I think that in this time of your life
you should do what you're passionate about.
You're approving it?
Approving is one thing,
but you must serve well on your last duty.
I'm telling you! If you don't pass the final exam,
I definitely won't sign your transfer application.
I promise! I'll definitely pass!
Professor, what's your dream?
My dream?
Zoologist.
Hibernating in the heart.
Little Yu Yan, please keep close to the tour guide.
Starting our one-day childhood tour.
You're the only guest today.
I'm your tour guide for today's day trip. I'm Xiao Tang.
This is your birthday present.
You need to be like him in the future.
Smile more.
But... I don't have many friends.
Now you do.
Everybody calls me Master Tang. From now on, if you have any troubles then look for me.
Say, a person like you, with good looks, a good name,
and good skills,
should only exist in comics books.
Which ones of these do you want?
I just want this one.
This one?
I just feel like... it's a little bit like you.
Tang Xue, I'm leaving.
Don't send me off. I'm afraid I will be too sad.
I'm even more afraid that if I see you, I won't be able to stop myself from staying.
I want to tell you, I like you.
I want to see you every single day.
I want to tell you, each time you appear in my mind,
I realize I'm always smiling.
I'm just like a sunflower. Wherever you are,
I grow in that direction.
Tang Xue, can you wait for me?
Please don't be so quick to like other people.
Yan-yan!
Did you pack everything up?
Get in the car.
Yan-yan, get in the car.
Coach Jin is waiting at the airport.
Yu Yan! In the future, I won't be able to look after you!
Make sure you look after yourself well!
♫ You left, your shadows accompanied by snowflakes ♫
Yu Yan!
In the future, I won't be able to take care of you anymore!
Take care of yourself!
- Stop the car! Stop the car!
- Keep driving.
- Yu Yan!
- Stop the car!
Take care of yourself!
- Keep driving, step on it.
♫ In the blink of an eye, the fireworks from the past
cross my mind ♫
♫ I couldn’t believe in that split second, she who
believed you or I shed tears ♫
♫ Lying to myself and not daring to ask if I can still
say that sentence ♫
Yan-yan, don't blame me.
I don't want you to waver.
If she likes you, she will wait for you.
If she doesn't like you, there's no need to be this upset. Right?
♫ The snow in my heart, please don’t fall ♫
♫ I’m waiting, waiting for someone’s response ♫
♫ Are you listening? ♫
♫ Yearning to meet, I want to tell you the sentence
that represents my sincerity ♫
Tang Xue, I'm leaving.
Don't send me off. I'm afraid I will be too sad.
How sad would it be if no friends came to see him off?
Good thing I made it.
♫ Looking at the unfinished puzzle, I smiled ♫
♫ If you remember the me who is waiting for you ♫
You went to see Yu Yan off?
Yeah, he left.
What did he say?
- He didn't say anything.
- He didn't say anything?
What are you trying to say?
I...
Tang Xue!
Team, tomorrow is the Tengxiang Cup.
Even though it's a new competition, everyone who entered is highly skilled.
The competition is hosted by LUU this year. We are the home field.
I want everyone to perform at their best. Can you do it?
Yes.
Did you guys forget to eat? Can you do it?
Yes!
Start practicing.
Yuewei! Tang Xue.
Yuewei, based on your performance during training,
you can easily get first place. The XDragons are counting on you to do well.
Tang Xue, you've only been training for three months. Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
I don't have high expectations for you. If you can make it to the semifinals, that's enough.
But Coach, I have high expectations for myself.
- Okay.
- Everyone who is competing wants to get first place.
If you don't believe me, ask anyone here. See if they don't want to get first place.
In any case, I don't believe you can do it.
The person who doesn't get first place has to bark like a dog.
Sure, little snail.
That's enough. Is our team a zoo?
Snails and dogs. Go practice.
Okay.
[Tengxiang Cup Short Track Speed Skating]
Our Master Tang is amazing.
She got first place in her heat and made it to the finals.
She's the biggest dark horse of this competition.
I predicted all this would happen.
Sure you did.
Tomorrow's the finals, what can we do to support her that will be more creative?
Your hair.
More creative?
What if we get a huge banner
so that Master Tang can easily spot us in the audience?
- It's pretty good.
- Right?
How's this?
[Autumn]
It's good.
A good horse needs a good saddle, and a good banner needs good words. It's creative.
In today's competition, I hope you two can perform to the best of your ability.
Show everyone the results of all our hard work up til now. Do you believe you can do it?
- Yes.
Tang Xue, this is your first official competition since joining the team.
I was truly surprised by your performance in the heat and semifinals.
Do your best. Don't be nervous.
Coach, don't worry. I'm not nervous.
I'm not just asking this of Tang Xue, I expect this from you, too.
During a competition, we have to make sure we have the right mindset.
Use your performance to demonstrate
the spirit of the LUU XDragons Short Track Speed Skating Team.
Let's go.
[Tengxiang Cup Short Track Speed Skating Competition]
[X-Dragons must win!]
[Master Tang, you're the best.]
- Master Tang!
Master Tang! I love you!
You're the best!
You're the best, Master Tang!
Good luck!
I didn't think Tang Xue would be able to make it to the finals.
Looks like you were right about her. Let's see how she does today.
You came prepared.
Of course. Opportunity comes to those who are prepared.
We are about to begin the women's 500-meter final competition.
Next, we'll introduce the athletes. In first position,
from Lincheng Union University, number 101 Zhang Yuewei.
In second position, from the North Heren Sports Center,
number 303 Xu Moyuan.
In third position, from Deqing City Athletic University,
number 407 Lin Yue.
In fourth position, from Qingcheng Skating Athletic Club,
number 703 Li Shuo.
In fifth position, from Lincheng Union University,
number 106 Tang Xue.
- Master Tang, good luck!
Good luck!
Go to the start.
Ready.
[101 Zhang Yuewei, 303 Xu Moyuan, 407 Lin Yue, 703 Li Shuo]
[106 Tang Xue]
Good luck! Good luck!
[3rd - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 6th - 106 Tang Xue]
[2nd - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 6th - 106 Tang Xue]
[Zhang Yuewei - 2nd, Tang Xue - 5th]
[1st - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 5th - 106 Tang Xue]
[1st - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 4th - 106 Tang Xue]
[1st - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 3rd - 106 Tang Xue]
♫ Anticipating tomorrow, surpassing the limit
because you are by my side ♫
♫ Our beliefs overcame the difficulties, not giving up
to advance bravely ♫
♫ The youngster is running with determined eyes
even in the face of a difficult challenge ♫
♫ Youth is persevering until the end, fearless and
never ceasing ♫
♫ Passion ignites and enthusiasm unchanging ♫
♫ Believe in tomorrow and shout it out ♫
[1st - 101 Zhang Yuewei; 5th - 106 Tang Xue]
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
only you can understand ♫
♫ Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ I had the kind of luck as if I plucked a star ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise and take
you traveling ♫
♫ In this big world, I’ll hold gently onto the secrets
you are protecting ♫
♫ I’m lucky to receive the surprise that came like a shock,
it’s a promise you’re giving me ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫
♫ The first time I saw your smile, my heart fell for you,
it must be destiny ♫
♫ I want to hold your hand and travel to the rainbow
to pluck a star ♫
♫ Secretly listening to your feelings and let the stars
fulfill each of your dreams ♫
♫ I want to collect every expression of yours, they are
the four seasons that belong to me ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like honey, it is the signal
you are giving me ♫
♫ Your embrace is like an island engulfed by a warm breeze ♫
♫ The first time I was certain of your feelings,
I couldn’t believe it and tears came to my eyes ♫
♫ I want to accompany you for every sunrise and take
you traveling ♫
♫ This moment has a scent like the sweet sea breeze ♫
♫ It is the signal you are giving me ♫
♫ This moment when your smile is like the sun ♫
♫ As if I’m nibbling a juicy peach, a beautiful love blossoms ♫
♫ This moment when my heart beats as in my dream,
(only you can understand) ♫
Your eyes like stars are twinkling in my night sky ♫
♫ The first time I held your hand, my breathing
became erratic and I was so mesmerized ♫
♫ The courage to hold you tight and never be apart again ♫
♫ Loving with no reason when I met you ♫