You're the one who thinks
highly of you. Don't seduce me.
Nervous,
no matter how hard the argument is today, there's no way to end it.
Come and have a drink with me.
What did
Meen say?
I...
I miss you,
It's not over yet.
Jerk!
Stop it. Songkhram,
the head of Dormitory 2,
I'm going to challenge you more than basketball.
Senior Tum, your TUM coins have gone up a lot recently,
making a profit of more than 100, 000 yuan last month.
Hundreds of thousands?
That's too much.
I started from scratch with 400 thousand.
Now I have my own digital currency.
What do you think?
You're awesome.
I want to buy your TUM coins, too. What about you?
But it keeps rising recently.
I don't even know when it's better to buy it.
Next week,
what do you mean by that?
I'll push down the price.
Then the tray.
We plan to raise 10 million yuan.
Gosh,
what a pity.
I'm still trapped.
Do you want to borrow my money?
Is that okay, Senior?
This little money is nothing,
we are seniors and younger brothers who have known each other for so long,
How much do you want to borrow?
Well,
if you throw a 400 thousand,
How much profit can I make?
How is your injury?
See for yourself.
Bad luck.
I was hit by a car and hit.
You deserve it.
Are you out of your mind?
Who are you messing with?
That's Songkhram.
Ai, I'm drunk.
This is another problem.
You even drove when you were drunk.
Are you tired of living?
Maybe it's better if I die.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing. I'm just kidding.
Are you kidding me?
It's better if you die.
Don't take it seriously.
Is there something bothering you?
You can tell me,
no matter what, we are all seniors and younger brothers.
Is it a family matter again?
It doesn't matter if you don't want to tell me.
Ai
You.
Can you lend me 400 houses?
What did you say?
I'm really in trouble this time.
What did you do to use 400 thousand?
Did you do something bad?
No
You have to tell Uncle Eak about such a big thing.
I'm sure your dad will help you.
You know I can't tell my dad.
If you don't tell me,
I don't know how to help you.
I... I
used the money to buy bitcoin.
If you borrow 400 houses to buy bitcoin,
that's 400 houses.
Are you out of your mind?
How much interest do you want?
Why don't you think about the consequences when you're doing things?
Do you want to borrow it or not?
I don't have that much money.
I do have a little savings,
tens of thousands,
Or you can find a way to sell something.
Watches, bags, clothes,
or cars,
The car won't work. I bought it under my dad's name.
Ai
Please save me.
If you don't help me, I'm dead,
okay?
Let me take a shot.
I can't do it.
I'll throw it in again.
Again,
again. Hold the ball like this. Your feet are flush with your shoulders.
Relax.
How about this?
Yeah, and throw it.
Wait here. I'll pick it up for you.
That's all for today.
Get some rest and eat something.
Yes. -Let's go.
What do you think?
I can't believe he wants to compete with Songkhram in basketball.
Asking for trouble.
[ I just recovered. Don't fight too hard. None of us will say anything about you. ]
What's wrong?
There's nothing of mine.
Let's go eat.
I'm starving.
It's your treat.
Okay.
A bunch of brats want to help with the basketball game.
I love them so much.
The smoothies in Sister Er Yo's shop are delicious.
Three Bright came to teach me how to play basketball and he rubbed his head,
and four Songkhram secretly stuffed mineral water into my bag.
A narcissist,
a pain in the ass.
Hey.
What's wrong?
About the other day,
I... I'm going to take a shower. See you later.
Thank you for helping me today.
You're welcome, Senior Ai.
Just give us some water,
Just open the back door of the dorm after 11 PM.
You brat.
We love you.
Okay, I love you, too.
Come on,
Do you want to fight for Dorm 3?
Fight
Shall we fight it or not,
Fight,
-Do you want to fight? -Fight.
Come here, everyone.
This game is a friendly match.
Just have fun.
Make yourself at home. Don't take it too seriously.
But we've never had a casual competition with anyone.
Yes,
you said you must be serious and win the competition.
I didn't say you don't have to win,
I said be casual,
Make yourself at home.
Just have fun.
The most important thing is that you don't get hurt.
You have an important competition?
For the sake of your future,
it's not worth it to get hurt like this.
And be careful not to let them get hurt.
Come on, everyone.
Come on, Dorm 2.
Okay.
Tell your team to be careful.
Don't get too close.
They're a fierce fighter,
Thank you.
Tell your men to stay away from us. Pass the ball.
Don't get too close to us. Or you'll get hurt.
Are you threatening me?
I'm not threatening you.
Senior Ai, go for it.
Cheer up and cheer for senior.
Dorm 3, come on, Ai,
get better soon, bro.
I'm sorry. Um,
have a safe trip, bro.
How did you get in?
She walked in.
Let's change the question.
What are you doing here?
Here you are.
Why did you give it to me?
You really don't know how to take care of yourself.
Don't you feel pain with such a big bruise?
No need.
I applied it myself.
You can go now.
I'm afraid the seniors will see it.
You can leave now.
Hurry up.
Why are you still here?
What's wrong? Can't I be here?
Aren't you going back to take care of the people in your dorm?
No one is here. Everyone in
Dorm 2 and Dorm 3 has gone back to the dorm.
You're the only one in the room. What took you so long?
Are you waiting for me?
I just.
=
Ohm = Hello.
What?
You trust others so easily.
I don't think it's a big deal.
He just asked me to have a talk.
Let me be honest with you,
if I happen to be away,
Are you going alone like this?
Promise me,
if something like this happens again,
You have to tell me,
every time,
Promise me.
If you don't promise me, I won't let you off the bus.
Yes, I promise you!
Let go of me!
Ai Ai
Ohm
Senior Tum,
What's going on?
Are Dorm 2 and Dorm 3 related now?
Let go of me now!
What do you need?
That's the point.
You should know.
Ohm lent me money but didn't want to pay it back.
So I took some interest from him.
Then why did you call Ai here?
He's just an ordinary student.
He's not the kind of person who can help his friend pay his debts.
I don't want money.
If I want money,
I can ask his dad for it.
You can tell me if you need anything.
That's why I can take Ohm to the hospital.
Ai, do you have a date?
No.
As long as you're my boyfriend,
I don't need him to pay off 400 houses of debt.
Jerk!
-Calm down, bro. -Let go. -Calm
down.
-Calm down. -Ai, he's
looking down on you.
I'm just making a suggestion,
so that Ai can save Ohm's life.
Help!
Ohm owes me a debt,
so you have to pay it back.
If you don't pay back the money, you have to pay it back with something else.
Like I said, I'm not short of money,
but it's illegal.
It's just a dog's life.
I can keep it from breaking the law.
-If I decide... -No, Ai. You
can't let someone do this because of him.
Oh my god.
I'll pay him back.
If you think you can do it, just come.
400 thousand pay it off before 10 o'clock this evening.
You don't have money to pay me back.
Wait and see.
What should I do?
Ai, help me.
-I'll come back to save you later. -Ai, don't
hurt Ohm.
Ai, Ai, Ai, don't go yet. Ai,
do you think your friends can help you?
Let go of me!
You're such a jerk!
Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Let go of me!
Where should we find the money?
400 thousand
is 400 thousand, not 4 baht.
You shouldn't have said yes to him.
This is not a joke.
I've never taken your matter as a child's play.
Do you have 400 thousand?
No.
Well,
if I'm willing to...
Shut up, Ai,
How can you be the object of that kind of person so easily?
He's looking down on your dignity.
I do have dignity,
but it can be Ohm's life.
Even if he has a bad personality,
he's still my friend no matter what.
Look at me and answer me.
Who are you?
I'm Ai.
Yes,
you are the head of the dormitory building of Ai 3,
He's kind and considerate.
And she's good at studying,
and she's the baby of my mom and the members of Dorm 3?
Yes.
Answer me now.
Who am I?
Song, the jerk from Dorm 2.
Jerk!
Yeah, okay.
I'm a jerk in Dorm 2.
A hillbilly is impatient and aggressive.
He only gets emotional.
You said it yourself this time,
so,
You have to trust me.
Sure,
but why did you grab my hand?
Where are we going?
Go find 400 thousand.
I can't change it myself.
Are you taking me to rob a bank?
You really are,
Ai
Let's go.
This should be the only way to pay interest.
But later, I will increase the hospitalization benefits.
So we should be able to adjust it a little bit.
Do you think it's okay if that's the case?
-I'll update it for you anyway... -You can't go in there.
OK OK It's okay It's okay,
I'll get back to you later Oh It's urgent.
I'm really sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Is it really urgent today?
Friends?
Yes, this is AiAi
and this is my dad,
-Hello. -Hello.
Tell me what urgent matter you have.
Lend me 400 thousand.
Borrowing 400 houses and taking 400 houses for what?
The people in the dorm caused some trouble,
and many of them got hurt.
So I have to pay the hospitalization fee.
There are a lot of injured people, so I have to charge a fee for the letter.
It's not real at all.
Say it again.
You know I don't want to talk about it.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have to make up a story.
But I promise it's not illegal. It has nothing to do with pornography.
And I won't let anyone get into trouble.
Okay? 400thousand
is in a hurry until today,
If you're really in such a hurry, why didn't you come since last month?
Dad,
400 thousand won't let anyone get into trouble.
Here it is. Those who get into trouble are here.
400 thousand.
Dad.
400 thousand OK,
today is your lucky day.
400 thousand.
Dad, this is,
yeah, if you want 400 thousand,
Help me deal with these.
I made three packages,
200thousand 400thousand 600thous. if you can get rid of any of them,
you can take the money.
What if I deal with less than 400 houses?
Then it's not my problem.
Can I go to them now?
That's your business. You can go tomorrow.
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
Let's go.
Goodbye, uncle.
Do you know
Amberly?
Is there anyone in UIT who doesn't know her?
Not to mention Amber, who set up the sand table recommendation,
there should be only one Amberly.
Businessman, Singapore, Thailand, mixed race,
has been successful since junior year and has his own company,
That's why UIT's sand table promotion was launched.
In Singapore, Taiwan, Korea and Thailand,
but the point is,
How can we win this person's heart?
Who are you calling?
Hello, Nucleus.
I have something to trouble you.
I promise I won't tell anyone.
I promise.
Thank you very much, Nucleus.
There's someone who can help us.
Songkhram Ai,
what can I do for you?
We need your help.
Even when you need my help,
I get goose bumps.
I don't know if it's a fear or an honor.
I'm serious.
Sakaojai Barkornyoskul
or the name in the passport is.
Scarlett Bottonli,
how do you know this?
So will you help us or not?
That depends on what you want me to do.
Help us win your mother's heart.
You like... -I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
not done yet.
Ai, give me the folder.
My dad asked us to talk about
insurance with your mom as representatives.
My dad has made a good offer.
We're just here to collect the bill.
Here you are
Just ask your dad to ask my mom out.
We're in a hurry.
We have to accept the bill tonight.
Tonight,
it's really urgent.
What if I don't help?
You probably don't want anyone to know.
You're Amberly's only daughter, right?
Because it will bring a lot of inconvenience to you and your mother.
Regarding the sand table recommendation,
Songkhram,
I'm begging you.
We really had no choice.
He...
This is really important to us.
If I help you,
what can I get?
I'll owe you one.
It's quite attractive.
OK, I promise you.
I happen to be having dinner with my mom at 7 p. m.,
so you should come with me.
I'll help you.
But... I can't guarantee the result.
It all depends on my mother's decision.
Hello,
please have a seat.
I can't believe Mr. Jim has such a handsome son.
How do you know?
Your dad called me and told me.
Mom, this is the head of Ai 3 Dormitory Building.
Hello,
Eat it.
All the dishes in this restaurant
are delicious. You're welcome,
Let's eat.
Are you busy lately?
Whether you are busy or not depends on who is asking this question.
A little bit busy,
but more bored.
Since there hasn't been a promising project for sand table promotion for a long time,
there's no need to be silent.
I'm used to it.
If I were to say it casually,
it should be air pollution.
PM2. 5
I remember the air quality used to be much better than this.
But now,
every time I go out,
I don't even feel like I'm getting enough oxygen.
I understand.
My mom complains a lot,
too. My mom is allergic.
Just like the bottle of water just now,
if more than 100 years ago,
no one would have thought that drinking water would cost money to buy.
Because the water in nature is clean,
and it's free.
Go on.
Okay,
If the air is still like this,
one day we may need to spend money to buy air for breathing.
Maybe there's bottled air and solid air
in the convenience store.
It's no different from bottled water now.
If that's the case,
where can we find fresh air for sale?
Maybe it's from nature that's still pure.
Mom, what do you think?
That's just a prospect.
Let's talk about your future plans.
That's the health insurance my dad proposed to you.
The cost of hospitalization is increasing,
although the hospital reimburses us for the medicine,
But there are expenses everywhere,
just like before my dad died,
My dad was sick,
and I still remember that the total cost was more than 300, 000 yuan.
My mom had to sell the store and the building.
Money at our disposal can make us happy.
Warm heart and peace of mind,
will not become a burden to our loved ones.
Don't be nervous.
I just appreciate your intention.
I don't know if you memorized it or if Mr. Jim taught you.
But I saw how hard you two worked.
But I invited my daughter to dinner today,
because I want to buy an insurance policy for her.
You understand it after hearing it, right?
How important is this?
[ Scarlett Bottonli = = 20-year insurance premium (no dividend) = How important is this?
[ Scarlett Bottonli = = 20-year insurance premium (no dividend) =
Hmm = Scarlett Bottonli = = 20-year insurance premium (no dividend) =.
= Scarlett Bottonli = = 20-year insurance premium (no dividend) =.
I plan to buy this insurance.
400 thousand.
But on one condition,
the two of you must be in the end of this year,
Give it to Sand Table to recommend an excellent development plan.
Okay. -Okay.
Songkhram Ai,
what's your dream?
My dream is to become a pilot.
I want to be an engineer that is beneficial to humanity and the environment.
What do you think?
Done.
Deal completed.
Really?
Awesome.
Do you want to come to work?
Let me find you a suitable position.
Congratulations.
How about this,
Take the money Ms. Aumber transferred in to do your business first.
But tomorrow, you have to bring me the documents
signed by Ms. Aumber and her daughter,
okay? I'll pay the money first.
Just give it back to me at any time.
OK
Thank you, Dad.
This is for you.
It means you have to pay it back.
Is it OK?
OK, I promise you.
As always,
you have to stand by my side,
Got it.
I'm a man. You don't have to protect me like that.
If something really happens to you,
will you be able to handle it?
Probably.
I might as well send you back to the dorm first.
I'll take care of the rest.
Of course not.
This is my family matter.
How can you handle it for me?
I can't thank you enough for helping me so much.
You've done so much for me,
no matter what happens to you in the future, I'll fight for you.
Let's fight together.
It sounds like we're getting married.
You're crazy.
What are you talking about?
Let's go.
Let go of me.
Ai
Ohm,
to be honest, I don't want you to pay me back.
Why are you paying me back?
I'm depressed, you know?
But forget it,
as much as I want Ai,
But what I said is hard to go back on my words.
Please don't break your promise, Senior Tum.
Don't waste your time.
It's 10 o'clock now.
Maybe Senior Tum wants to rest.
Oh dear, Ai, Bitcoin
is in the ascendancy these days,
If you want to start,
you can tell me,
I'll tutor you myself.
Ai, don't trust him.
Enough, Senior Tum.
Enough, Senior.
I'm begging you.
400 thousand.
Now that we're even, we'll leave first.
Ai, you can take Ohm away.
Songkhram, stay here and let's talk.
Can you do it?
Let's go.
If you like Ai,
who do you think Ai will date?
Do you think you two can be together?
Do you think you two can last long?
The people in dormitory building 2 and dormitory building 3,
it's impossible to be together.
Everyone will reject you.
It's really annoying.
When will I stop making trouble for you?
That's enough.
What did you talk to Senior Tum at the end of the day?
Who do you like?
What's your answer?
I said I don't know.
Tell him who you like
and who I like.
It's better if you have time to study hard, right?
I have to take care of my mom.
My mom worked so hard.
Now I'm focusing on learning and focusing on sand table recommendation,
Yes.
Go get some rest. It's been a long day.
Thank you so much for today.
From today on, I'll pay you back slowly.
If there's anything you need my help with,
just let me know as long as it's not beyond my ability.
I'm happy to help.
You have to be careful. Ai,
can you stop making promises to others?
But what I said is not beyond my ability,
I have already said my limitations.
In the meantime, I want to read your diary every day, okay?
What?
I want to read your diary.
Wait,
how do you know my diary?
Who am I? Songkhram?
So Songkhram is a gossip person?
Jerk!
Didn't you say there's anything you can do for me?
What can I do for you?
Just... to help me get to know you better.
Why do you want to read my diary?
That's my personal belongings.
I think we should keep a record of personal matters.
I read all these messy things by myself.
It's personal to be alone,
do you understand?
Yes, I see.
It's fine if it's okay.
Go to bed then.
The dorm door is closing?
Wait,
I'll help you with something else.
I know you have a crush on the people in our dorm.
I'll help you chase the man in dormitory building 3
to show my gratitude to you.
What do you mean?
I know you like Meen,
I was drunk that day and I vaguely heard you miss each other,
Do you think I like Meen?
Well, don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about this.
No one else will know about this.
Meen already knows.
Ah,
I like the person in Dormitory 3 Meen knew it,
and what did he say?
He didn't say anything.
Ai,
what are you doing there?
Go back to the dorm. It's late. It's closed at 11: 00. You're not allowed to come
in.
If the head of the dorm sleeps outside the dorm,
others will laugh their heads off.
Yes. Go to bed.
Wait, everyone is woken up.
Let me apologize to you for him.
Anyway, thank you again.
Yes.
Let's go.
Nano
Hey,
Ai told me he wanted to help me chase you.
What is it?
That day at the bar door, he wasn't jealous at all,
but he even chased you for me.
I've already told you.
Don't make it complicated.
I.
What?
Miss you
= Spoken English: What did you say =,
[ Oral:
No ] [ Oral: Let's see how he reacts when
he hears it
= = Oral: No = Are you done laughing?
So what? It's as you wish, isn't it?
It's been four years.
You don't have to remind me again, okay?
I'm sorry...
I didn't repeat the reminder.
What I'm saying is that you wouldn't listen to me.
I've been telling you a good way for years.
What if you don't care?
You just want to use this to make him jealous.
What should I do?
Stop using me as a shield.
Then just tell Ai,
you don't like me.
What if he gets angry and doesn't want to talk to me?
Just go and find him like everyone else.
What do you mean?
All right,
for this semester's mid-term assignment,
I want you to form a group
to help and illustrate how to improve the standard of living of human beings.
How many people are there in a group?
Why should I ask?
Dormitory 2 and Dormitory 3 will work together and form a team together.
Speaking of which, it's good.
It's the fourth grade.
Aren't you tired of the rules your senior set before?
Team up together in the same dorm for the rest of your life?
Do you want to change it?
Tell me,
Do you want us to form a team in the dorm this time?
Very good.
That's it. What world
is it now? What era is it?
Give me the list in the evening.
Let's be in the same team.
Jerk!
You asked in front of everyone.
If Ai doesn't agree, won't he become a petty person who bears grudges?
Yeah, okay,
Bright. You're with us. Two against two.
Just fine.
Then both of us will join in.
What did
Bright say?
Why are you chatting with Ai today?
How did you see it?
I like Ai.
I really like Ai.
Please help me.
No.
Why?
I like Ai, too.
I thought you liked Meen,
All I know is that Meen likes you.
Meen doesn't like me.
I wouldn't do that if I liked her.
Don't you ever think that he did that because of you?
Don't blame me.
I don't know, Bright.
No matter what, I won't give way to you.
Because I like Ai,
I don't care about any random rules. Next,
let's welcome Ai.
75，
54，
98，
40，
30，
All right,
this is another person who finished this year, Ai,
Since Dormitory 3 and Dormitory 5 have the same result,
now let Ai choose which dorm to stay in?
Dormitory 5,
I'd like to ask the heads of three dormitory buildings and five dormitory buildings.
Why should I be in your dorm?
I've been watching Ai's campaign,
and I can see your vision.
You're handsome and pretty. You're good at playing games.
If I come to Senior's dorm,
I will be the brightest star.
If Ai comes to Senior's dorm,
Senior will give you everything you want,
Although our three dormitory buildings
say that we are the school grass dormitory building,
We don't just have looks.
If Ai comes to our dorm,
You won't get everything one day.
During your four years in UIT,
you have to work hard on your own,
To get what you want.
We will support you and be your strong backing.
Okay, it's time for Ai to make a choice.
Which dorm do you want to stay in?
I'll choose three dormitory buildings.
I said I would help you chase Meen.
I've asked Meen out for you.
Ai chose me.
You don't have anything to tell me, do you?
Don't you have a lot of people talking to you?
Would you like to have dinner with me?
Where do you want me to sleep at this time?
Go sleep with me.