(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 33)
This one is silent too.
Silent again?
You open it.
Me?
Yes.
My brother hasn't eaten either.
You go ahead.
It's the password.
Eight?
It's the second or fourth digit password.
How did you know?
The time display is a four-digit number,
and the first and third digits can't both be eight.
Yes.
Opening the safe
is the most troublesome way to leave here.
Why?
Because the password may not be in one person's possession,
so when it's time to pass the door, whose note should be considered?
Forget it.
We opened two boxes, and nothing happened.
Let's go eat.
OK.
We can finally have a meal.
It's really not easy.
Xia, what should we do next?
I'm starving.
You have to be responsible for us.
We are all adults.
Why do you always want someone else to take responsibility for you?
That's not what you said before.
What if we can't pass the door?
Get lost!
They opened the box too.
It seems they couldn't resist either.
What did you all get?
We opened two empty boxes and a box contained the left hand of the Box Demon,
and got a digit of password
taking our chances.
(Left Hand, Tip: The left hand can manipulate players into opening boxes.)
We've all made our marks.
What's the use of the Box Demon's left hand?
It's a troublesome skill.
Both the left and right hands
can force a person
to open a designated box.
So, did you mean
she can specify who to kill?
But it might also be our chance.
In fact, both the Box Demon and the Box Slave
can be killed,
but it requires special props.
Just use them before opening the box.
It's not that simple.
So what did you find when opening boxes?
We found one digit of the password.
If you find other digits,
we can cooperate.
This is a password. How can we cooperate?
What about the note for the next door?
Whoever finds more digit passwords
gets the key.
If we find the same digits,
we'll decide by rock-paper-scissors.
It's fair anyway.
It's all about luck.
Luck will always be on our side.
The four of you only opened just two boxes.
It seems luck isn't on your side.
You...
Stop talking to her.
Let's leave after finishing eating.
The compass is spinning.
The Box Demon is about to act.
What's wrong with you?
Are you feeling unwell?
Zhu Meng.
Turn around.
Don't look at that box. Look at me.
There seems to be an important prop in that box.
Oh no! The Box Demon has used its skill!
It's left hand!
There must be something inside
that can kill the Box Demon.
As long as we open it,
we can go back
to the real world.
Zhu Meng, wake up.
Don't open the box, Zhu Meng.
Don't open the box!
Hang in there.
Don't open the box, Zhu Meng.
Zhu Meng!
Hey.
He still wants to open it.
Lingling.
No.
Hey.
Zhu Meng.
What happened to me?
You got hit.
You were almost dead.
Fortunately, Lingling had a prop.
He took a step ahead of you and killed the Box Slave.
Seeing you still got hit,
he opened the box.
Luckily nothing happened.
It scared me to death.
Even if I got hit,
you shouldn't have opened the box.
What if it didn't work?
I made sure the Box Slave was already dead
before opening it.
I'm fine now.
What were you sure of?
Did you take me as Mu Yu?
You insulted me.
I'm not stupid.
It's strange.
Sun Yuanzhou just opened a box that had the left hand of the Box Demon in it.
She couldn't wait to use the skill
as if it was specifically targeted.
Was she targeting us?
Could someone have found the eyes of the Box Demon?
The Box Demon's eyes
are used to find that red comb,
and the comb is used to block the its hair,
so the possibility of it being used against me is not very high.
Do you still remember the rules of the board game?
About whether players
choose to disclose information.
Oh,
you mean
our information is open
to the Box Demon.
Yes.
Now it seems that the rules outside the door
are almost the same as the ones inside the door.
I recall the rules of the board game.
When a player opens a certain prop,
he can choose to disclose the information
or keep it private.
Disclosing information has its benefits.
Everyone will know the situation of the prop,
and the Box Demon will also
be aware of it,
knowing what information the player has obtained.
If that's really the case,
it's not good.
The Box Demon
should be aware of our information all the time.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be in such a hurry to kill me.
It seems that
Xia is really smart.
She didn't hurry to reveal her strength,
which made her quite safe.
Because now, I am the only one
who knows the game rules.
If I am dead,
the Box Demon's next moves will be easily controlled.
Because no player knows
how to use the props and skills.
But the Box Demon's ears
haven't been found yet.
How did she know?
I guess
we have an informant among us who is working for the Box Demon.
When I was looking up information outside,
it was the first time I learned about the rules of the Box Demon Game.
Chen Fei introduced the rules to us.
According to this logic,
no matter what game we play,
there should be an introduction or explanation,
at least letting the players know how to play.
But so far, it seems that
no one knows how to play.
Yes, this informant
probably hid the game manual,
so now they want to kill me.
Yes.
Who is the informant?
Xia?
It's unlikely to be her.
Given our relationship outside the door,
if she were the informant,
she would have taken action against us a long time ago,
instead of waiting until now.
Zhu Meng.
Yu Lingling.
I'll go out and take a look.
I want to talk to him alone.
Before you say anything,
let me ask you a question.
Go ahead.
If I were in the same situation,
would you open the box before me?
Silence is an admission.
So, don't say much.
We both know
what the other will do.
I just wanted you to survive.
At least, don't die for me.
When facing the same situation again,
we would both make the same choice.
You can't protect others forever.
I remember you told me something
in the Snow Village:
you have to get used to others being kind to you.
There is something wrong.
Let's go.
What's up?
We obtained a prop.
What prop is it?
A lighter.
(Lighter) (Tips: Lighters can restrict the movement of Box Demon. Use it before opening)
I want to ask you how to use this.
A lighter can restrict the movement of Box Demon once.
A pair of scissors can interrupt the movement of Box Demon once.
What's the difference between restricting and interrupting?
Can you explain it clearly?
For example,
I was hit just now.
The Box Demon used her left hand to attack me.
What?
Didn't we just find her left hand skill?
Then why did you...
Did you find new props?
No.
It was broken by a prop brought from outside.
Go on.
The Box Demon used her left hand to attack me.
If I had scissors,
I could cut the Box Slave's hair
before I was dragged by
the Box Slave's hair
or hands into the box.
The Box Demon's skill will be interrupted.
In other words,
at least her skill is invalid in this round.
What about the restricting?
The lighter can kill the Box Slave,
but you have to use it before you open the box.
If the Box Demon uses her left hand skill
to force you to open a box.
But you used a lighter
before opening a box,
maybe the box is empty.
The Box Demon can use this method
to waste the props.
Right.
You can use scissors under any conditions,
but not the lighter.
At least it's a useful prop.
I want to ask you.
How many times can the Box Demon use her skills?
Only once.
For example, the left hand skill.
It will return to the box after using the skill.
She needs us to open another right box
before using it again.
It should be like this in the door.
By the way,
my friends
found a new prop.
But don't tell others.
What prop?
A red comb.
If we use it to comb the Box Demon's hair,
we can kill her.
But if the Box Demon finds out,
it'll be troublesome.
Why did you tell me?
Aren't you afraid that she'll hide in these boxes?
Didn't we confirm that
the Box Demon is in the bathroom?
Besides,
she won't be able to go anywhere
before the box with left or right foot is opened.
Anyway,
if you find the Box Demon's hair,
tell me ASAP.
Then we can go out early.
No problem.
Keep us
in touch.
Okay.
When did you find the comb?
I didn't find it.
Are you testing Sun Yuanzhou?
Unfortunately, Lingling's hearing
can only be used twice a day.
If Lingling's hearing skill is useful,
maybe my sense of smell can also be useful.
Right.
What if the prop has a smell?
Or the body part may have a smell.
Maybe the Box Demon's feet stink.
Let's go.
Let's find a place to try.
Here.
It's well-ventilated.
Try it.
Brother, come on.
How is it?
There's something.
It smells rusty.
It's iron.
Iron?
It should be a prop we can use.
(Scissors) (Tips: scissors can cut the Box Demon's hair and hands. Interrupting the Box Demon's Skill)
Scissors.
It's a pair of scissors!
It is such an amazing feeling.
I didn't have it when I needed it.
I just got out of danger, but I get it now.
The can opener was invented
10 years later than the can.
It's okay. It doesn't matter.
Take it.
Keep it.
It feels like you are taking care of the weakest person.
Brother, smell some more later.
Give Ruan one prop.
Then all of us can eat.
Brother, what do you smell?
Is it the Box Demon?
I can't smell anything.
But you just opened one box.
Why can't you smell anything?
It seems that Yixie's sense of smell skill
can only be used once a day.
Ruan, you...
I'm not hungry yet.
Now we can open three boxes every day.
We have three places to eat.
One person will take turns to starve.
I can hold on.
Look.
Why are there so many boxes?
What are you doing?
Don't open the box recklessly.
We're so unlucky.
We found an eye first.
Xia,
can you control your people?
Will you be happy
if we all die?
Are you kidding me?
We have props. How can we die?
You're the ones who should die.
Say that again!
You...
Don't.
Are you going to hit a woman?
Calm down.
Don't let her provoke you.
Coward!
Die in this door!
Say that again!
You...
What's wrong?
Why are you so emotional?
Her people opened the box recklessly
and found an eye.
Organs again.
Looks like the Box Demon is going to use her skill again.
The eyes of the Box Demon can let her see
her favorite red comb.
Whoever has a red comb will be the unlucky one.
Have a good rest.
I'll figure something out.
Zhu Meng.
Well.
T-Take care.
Let's go.
Do you think this person is reliable?
It'd be a bit of a coincidence.
We just said we got the comb,
and then they found an eye.
Let's see whether
the Box Demon will use her skill on me.
The Box Demon has used her skill today.
But we'll know after midnight.
Let's sleep.
I don't have the comb anyway.
The Box Demon will only waste her one skill.
Zhu Meng, I won't sleep tonight.
I'll stay with you.
They slept so well.
Stop coughing.
I heard it.
I'll hang on a little longer.
I can eat tomorrow morning.
You have chocolate.
Why didn't you eat it?
I wanted to give you one last night,
and leave one for you tonight.
I didn't expect you to open the box.
But I already ate today.
You don't eat even though you're so starving.
What if you starve next time?
I'll leave it to you.
Thank you.
I said
I'll protect you forever.
Whether it's your life
or mine.
A lifetime is too long.
I hope you can eat it now.
It's morning.
The Box Demon hasn't taken action yet.
So Sun Yuanzhou is clear?
I think so.
But we need to do something to give the
informant a chance to make contributions.
And let him know we noticed him.
Right.
Wake them up.
Let's open boxes.
Starving me today.
You should eat more.
Okay.
I've found the comb.
The prop to kill the Box Demon.
As long as you find the head of the Box Demon
and comb her hair with it,
we can go out.
But this comb is very dangerous.
I'm wondering if I should put it back.
Don't.
What if the box demon destroys it?
You can give it to me if you don't want it.
I'm not afraid.
If you're not afraid, how could I be?
That's it.
I'll keep the comb.
Let's find the head earlier
and get out of here.
Zhu Meng.
May I have a word with you?
Go ahead.
Am I clear now?
You're indeed a master.
You should be the strongest opponent here.
If we don't rule you out first,
we'll all be doomed.
We're not enemies,
and then we're friends.
Have you figured out who the informant is?
I'm not sure.
But he will take action soon.
He will give himself away.
The Box Demon has activated her skill.
Looks like he's done for this time.
Lingling, what are you worried about?
He didn't...
He's fine.
Where's the comb?
How come?
Zhu Meng, didn't you say you have the comb?
The Box Demon activated her skill,
but nothing happened.
What?
You really want the Box Demon's skill to work?
Impossible.
You can't resist the Box Demon's skill.
Why not?
Maybe, I don't have the comb at all.
Or maybe I lied to you.
If I didn't lie to you,
how could the Box Demon use her skill
and waste a chance?
W-What do you mean?
It means there's an informant among us.
Today until now,
the Box Demon hasn't used her skill.
But when I said I had the comb,
the compass moved.
He didn't want to wait for a moment.
Someone here tipped off the Box Demon.
How is that possible?
What's in it for him?
There are too many benefits.
He chose to work with the Box Demon.
When he killed us,
he could go out as he wanted.
He should be the first one to get here.
He hid the game manual.
If I had played this game,
we would just have waited to die.
So who came first?
Who is the first?
I think what he said makes sense.
But
there is a huge hole in it.
The premise of all this
is that the information he provided is correct.
But if the things about the red comb
and the so-called body skills
were made up by him,
then all this doesn't exist.
You're still so meticulous.
It's just a reasonable doubt.
Like you said,
you can lie to everyone
to achieve your purpose of leaving here alone.
Since we came here,
you've been
providing us with information.
You're the only one
who has played such an obscure game?
Yes, that makes sense.
So if someone
hid the game manual,
I think that person is you.
Eighty percent of the truth
plus twenty percent of lies
can deceive everyone,
right?
Is it enough?
So you have a note.
Sorry.
I like you.
You admitted your mistakes.
If you had taken this out earlier,
we would have...
But can't this so-called note
be forged?
The texture of the note is special.
Even if it's forged, it must be done outside the door.
But how did you know
what would happen in the door at that time?
I-I'm just asking.
Do you have any questions?
Since there's no problem.
How about this?
First, take good care of yourselves.
After all, there is
an informant of the Box Demon.
If you have any problem,
you can come to me in private.
Don't worry. No one else will know.
Are we going to share new information?
If it's about leaving here,
you can discuss it in private.
If it's about props
or the way to kill the Box Demon,
we can share it publicly.
But we don't know who the suspect is.
How can we discuss things?
Let's go.
We have opened a lot of boxes.
If the informant of the Box Demon
opens the box of her body,
it's not good for us.
Shall we continue opening?
No.
We've opened boxes today.
Starving me.
It's okay. I have eaten things these days.
What props do we have now?
Sun Yuanzhou has a lighter.
Ji has a stethoscope.
We have scissors.
We opened a box of number three this morning.
Now we have two numbers.
Three and eight.
We opened more skill boxes than prop boxes.
We're in a bad spot.
Opening the box is just about luck.
It's too hard.
I just told everyone that
there's an informant among us.
What would you do if you were the informant?
If I were the informant,
I would hide my identity if I had the advantage.
I won't expose myself.
If I were the informant,
I would find the Box Demon to get some props.
I'm afraid he'll stay clamer than us.
Then we'll be screwed.
Is there a better way?
It sounds like
we have no initiative.
(Opened, empty)
Let's go to find Sun Yuanzhou first.
I think he's prepared.
Sun,
there isn't an echo from the box.
Does it mean it's empty?
You're not picking a watermelon here.
Am I gonna open it or not?
It's a gamble about luck anyway.
The decision is yours.
Then...
I'll open it.
I'm really gonna open it.
(Torso Tips: The torso can destroy everyone in the same room as the Box Demon)
The torso?
What's the secret about the torso?
The torso is the scariest one
among all the body parts of the Box Demon.
Once its function is activated,
all the people in the same room
as the Box Demon will be killed.
I-It...
Sorry. I didn't know that.
No worries. We couldn't avoid it anyway.
How are we gonna deal with the torso?
When the Box Demon performs a function,
the body part representing it will automatically disappear,
and go back to a box.
We don't need to do anything about this.
Sun, do you think we'll be able to leave this place?
We'll have to roll the dice.
I've got this one covered.
This number takes either the second or the fourth place.
In the past,
(Opened, part of the combination)
I never counted on my luck for anything.
It has never occurred to me that I'd be taking such grave risks in this door challenge.
I'm afraid that when I'm out of this place,
I'll become much bolder.
Now we've got three numbers of the four-digit combination.
When we get the last one,
we can try opening the safe in the study.
Don't we need to insert the numbers in the right order?
We sure do. But that part depends on our luck.
We have to rely on our luck to find out the correct order.
But the last number has to be certain, right?
I've got a number.
You're alone? Where's Xia?
We aren't always together.
We're just fellow players. I'm not very close with her.
The last number is in my hands.
Are you gonna give it to us?
We all aim to solve this door challenge anyway.
I wouldn't mind giving it to you.
What do you want in return?
What can I possibly ask for?
I'm just being nice and doing a good deed.
Are you fraternizing with us behind Xia's back?
Having a friend is better than having a foe.
Don't overthink it.
Plus, there isn't a feud between us, right?
Drop the act.
Just say it. What do you want?
Please don't feel pressured. I...
I have only one number. It's not much helpful to me.
I might as well share it with you.
After all, we see each other quite often.
I'd like to reduce the tension between us.
That's a lot of talking. Why not show us the number?
Give it to us, will you?
Fine.
She and you are separate individuals.
We won't be hostile to you.
Don't worry. It's authentic.
The props in the door challenges can't be forged.
It's just too difficult.
But a friend of ours can make that happen.
It's a shame that he's killed by the X organization.
That's why we won't stop going after Xia.
Xia and I are just collaborating.
I'm not a member of her organization.
Let's go. Time to crack the combination.
What are you doing here?
They seem to have found the four numbers,
so they're now heading to open the safe.
Before they can figure out the correct order of the four numbers?
I arrived here not long ago, so I only caught the last few words they said.
Shall we go take a look?
Why would we tag along with them?
Let's find the props first. I've got a plan.
Is he up to this?
He surely is.
The safe and the floor standing clock are an item.
The clock isn't working now.
It means the combination
is related to the time shown on the clock.
Now we have all the four numbers.
Eight, three, seven, one.
If the combination reflects the time on the clock,
then 7 and 8
can't take the second or the fourth place.
3 can't be the first digit.
So 1 must take the first place.
He's good.
Then the order should be 1, 3, 7, 8.
You're even sillier than me.
13:78
is actually 14:18, isn't it?
If the first digit is 1,
then the third place can't be taken by 7 or 8.
There are only two possibilities left.
It's either 1, 7, 3, 8,
or 1, 8, 3, 7.
That's right. It's getting close.
As I said, he's surely up to this.
What is this about?
If that's the wrong combination,
wouldn't he have been dragged away by the Box Demon?
Is that the correct combination or not?
The whole thing's still about luck.
Lingling never relies on luck for anything.
You should keep your mouth shut.