(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 10)
What are you doing?
There seems to be something inside.
I didn't expect it to be these things.
Is it that scary?
Shouldn't I be scared?
There are bones inside.
You're right.
Where is the drumstick?
Go up
and play the drum.
What?
What if I want to kill myself
like Lingling after I play the drum?
Don't worry.
You don't have unpleasant memories.
Just say I'm silly.
The bones are moving.
L-Let's go back.
Why?
Let's go up.
Let's go.
I'm not going.
I don't want to go.
What?
This notebook
looks like the one we got before.
Open it.
There's a portrait here.
It was torn off.
Is this the page that was torn off
in that diary?
Lingling,
isn't this you?
What?
Does she
have a crush on you?
It's Xu Jin.
This man does look like me.
But it's definitely not me.
So,
the old lady's riddle
should be a story about jealousy out of love
and hatred out of jealousy.
Maybe
the younger sister got jealous
when she saw her elder sister's
happy life with her husband.
And she tore it off
when she saw this portrait.
So, that diary we found before belongs to the elder sister.
Now you keep up.
Of course.
I envy my sister and brother-in-law too.
But I'm not jealous.
Who's your sister?
Who's your brother-in-law?
Meng Yu.
I'll brick you up alive here.
When did she tear this page off?
I don't know.
But she didn't go up with us.
Lingling,
can I wait for you here?
Hui.
Hui, you're alive.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Xu Jin.
You seem afraid of the drumbeats.
It sounds scary.
So...
I think I understand now.
Let's follow her.
Keep it.
Where are your followers?
No followers are needed
at this critical moment.
Someone gave me this key.
I'll do you a favor
and give it to you.
You rule the game now.
Brother-in-law.
I look forward to a happy cooperation.
So do I.
He gave you the key so easily?
Have you found anything?
No.
Everyone, this is all about our tour today.
You can go back to your encampment.
I lost the key.
Don't panic.
The key is fake.
Meng Yu is a fraud.
Who stole it?
What would happen if it were used?
Meng Yu gave me the fake key
to test my ability.
I took this chance to disguise myself.
I didn't expect someone really stole my key.
Meng Yu is easy to deal with.
But the thief is hiding in the dark.
That's why I'm worried.
Let me do it. Let's lure him out.
Bad news.
Zhu Meng lost the key.
Please help him find it.
Why did you have the key?
You said you didn't find anything.
What?
You found the key?
Where did you find it?
At the observatory.
Is that important?
Now the key is lost.
We have to find it.
You lost it so quickly?
I worked so hard to find it.
You said you lost it?
Why did you give the key to this sick boy
after you found it?
Are you satisfied now that none of us can go out?
Lingling.
What should we do?
The key is lost.
We can't go back.
It's fine if we can't go back.
Let's stay here together.
Everyone.
It's getting dark.
It's dangerous outside.
Forget it.
The key won't disappear in the door.
Let's go back.
Why don't we follow Meng Yu?
He looks more experienced.
Oh.
Are we going to follow him?
Let's go.
I'm done. Enjoy your meal.
I'm going to the restroom.
If anything happened tonight
and I slept like a dog, please wake me up.
Okay.
Wake up.
Zhu Meng.
What's wrong?
It's Xu Jin.
Let's have a look there.
This... She...
What is she doing?
Is she taking a shower?
My goodness.
How did she become like this?
Go back.
It's almost done.
She is speaking
Don't be scared
Don't forget her
It's almost done.
When the moon rises
When the rain falls
She keeps silent
The silver hairpin
The pale face
Red flowers bloom on her body
It's so scary.
It's so frightening.
So frightening.
What happened to her?
It looks like a rite.
It seems
the powder in the bowl works.
It's an ancient medicine.
A tiny bit
can get rid of the fake and retain the genuine.
She is speaking
What should we do next?
Don't be scared
When it turns into a human again,
don't fight head-on.
Hurry up and find the key.
She's back.
The tours of the exhibition hall and the observatory
are over.
It's free time now.
Enjoy your stay here.
I hope when you came back tonight,
there would still be nine of you.
Thank you for your cooperation these days.
That's all for my service.
If you have any chance to come back tonight,
please give me a five-star review.
Hey. Hey.
What does she mean?
It seems
the countdown is going to start.
It's the last day.
If we still can't find the key,
the Door Ghost will be ready to kill us.
The game is speeding up.
It seems that me exposing Xu Jin
triggered the conditions.
What?
This game can be accelerated?
I think this game can be whatever it likes to be.
What should we do?
Let's find the Granny grinding the powder.
You
are responsible for dating.
Me?
Let's go.
Bye.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Let's go.
Hey.
Well,
I have something to ask you.
Thank you for the powder.
You're smart. You used it on the right person.
Can you tell us
why the younger sister killed her older sister?
Because of him.
You're good.
Life in the village was peaceful before.
That year, a young man called Hui
came here.
He looked exactly like him.
The younger sister fell in love with Hui.
Are you looking for me?
Here you are.
Sorry.
I can't accept your pouch.
I have someone I like.
I'm leaving.
But Hui liked the older sister.
In order to steal her lover from her sister,
the younger sister did everything she could.
But Hui still loved the older sister.
Later, the younger sister
heard a legend,
saying that a drum made with human skin
could go beyond time and space and realize one's wish.
After that,
the younger sister disappeared for three years.
When she came back,
she looked like a totally different person.
During those three years,
she learned how to make a drum with human skin.
She made a drum with her skin.
Besides, she cruelly peeled off her sister's skin
and put it on herself.
She broke her sister's leg bone and made them into drumsticks.
Then she played the drum with them.
She did everything she could to become her older sister
and be with Hui.
So the skin on Xu Jin belongs to her older sister.
And she made her skin into a drum.
It's the drum at the observatory.
What about Hui?
He's dead.
Even if the younger sister became her older sister,
Hui didn't love her.
Even if the older sister's skin was peeled off,
Hui still loved her.
This woman is really cruel.
She's inhumane.
You'll see the real effect
of the powder later.
You're quite cute.
Since you have any question to ask,
can I ask you a question?
Well, go ahead.
What do you think of me?
Pretty good.
I like the scene here.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I like you.
Do you like me?
Yes.
Really?
I mean
I like the view here.
Why don't we stay here together?
Isn't it good?
What are you talking about?
How's everything?
Let's go to the observatory.
Do you want to join us?
Keep an eye on her.
I find her strange too.
Although she's a beginner,
she never makes mistakes.
Hey.
You stay here.
Let's wait here.
They will be fine.
Hey.
What's wrong?
Xu Jin, your sister is looking for you.
Give your sister back her stuff.
Stop being stubborn.
Ling Jiushi, you stink.
You sleep in the dung pit every night.
Can such nonsense you wrote work?
Help me.
Don't leave me alone.
Ling Jiushi, you stink.
No.
Rewrite it.
We are the same,
being deprived and hurt.
Why aren't you on my side?
No.
I'm not like you.
She had gained the upper hand since we were young.
Everything belonged to her.
Whether it was love or attention,
she won it all.
I will only cherish what I have now,
instead of coveting what others have.
So we are different.
Lingling. Lingling.
Yu Lingling.
Jiushi.
Come back, Jiushi.
It's okay.
If you die,
you can stay here forever.
Stop!
If you dare touch him again,
I'll smash the drum right away.
Lingling.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Here. Let me help you.
Come on.
Xu Jin is missing.
What can you do?
What kind of boss are you?
I heard a piercing sound just now
that made me dizzy.
When I woke up, she was gone.
Feeling better?
What happened?
She was coming at us.
Okay. And then?
Then I reasoned with her.
She thought what I said made sense.
So she left you alone.
Feeling so happy after messing with me?
Happier than you thought.
As long as you're happy.
Where is Xu Jin?
We've already come to this point,
and you're still thinking about her?
She was busted and left.
Bro.
Can you stop playing that drum?
The material of this drum head is so delicate.
You must not fall asleep tonight.
The guide has left.
It means the Door Ghost
is going to go on a killing spree.
Skin. Skin.
I want your skin!
Zhu Meng!
I want your...
Are you hurt?
Why didn't you wake us up?
I... I did.
I called you many times, but neither of you woke up.
Did you hear him?
He called you many times, but you didn't wake up.
You didn't wake up either.
Looks like Xu Jin is very afraid of this drum.
It's broken.
I was so worried that I broke it.
So, the key is here.
I'll take the key.
Everyone knows I lost my key.
It's safer to keep it with me.
It's not the drum that Xu Jin is afraid of,
but rather that the drum might attract her sister here.
Now that it's broken.
If we meet her again,
I'm afraid it'll be harder to deal with her.
I thought Xu Jin treated you as her lover.
I didn't expect that she wanted to hurt you
and your skin.
So now we should find Xu Jin and give her to her sister,
then we can get out, right?
What should we do?
What should we do? Any clues?
No.
It's the last day.
- Yeah. - Let's look for her again.
- Hurry up. - Yes.
Zhu Meng.
I need to have a word with you.
Come with me.
Let's go.
How did you catch her?
Didn't I lose her?
I was worried.
I thought that I had to get her back.
After my detailed, clear-sighted,
and divine deduction,
I finally
got her.
Is she real or fake?
How could a human be fake?
Hey?
Say something.
Take her to the roof.
I wish your pain was shorter.
It's a pity that you're not Hui.
I can never become Hui,
just as you will never become your sister.
If I hadn't met you,
I would never have been exposed.
What should we do now?
Call her out.
I brought you the drum.
Your sister is here too.
It hurts so much.
My leg hurts.
It hurts.
You're finally here.
Did you come to him?
Do you want to go with him?
He's not Hui.
Hui is dead.
The human-skin drum that can make one's wishes come true
must be made with one's own skin.
After enduring the sharp pain
and peeling my skin to make the drum,
Hui still didn't love me.
So you peeled off your sister's skin
and wore it yourself.
It's his fault because he only had eyes for her!
But
why didn't Hui love me
even after I wore my sister's skin?
What did I do wrong?
Why should I have to suffer this?
It's not your fault.
It's your sister's fault.
Now that we've found your sister,
can you tell us where the door is?
Give me back the drumstick.
That's my bone!
The moon rises
Rain falls
She keeps silent
The silver hairpin
Delicate cheeks
Red flowers bloom on her wedding dress
Dong, Dong
She is speaking
Don't be afraid
Leave now.
Don't ever come back.
Don't forget her
Let's go.
You can't leave!
You stay here!
Don't come over!
Just give your skin to Hui.
Hui will come back to life.
The ceremony will be completed soon.
Look carefully.
He is Hui.
Are you going to hurt him?
Why don't you like me?
I've done so much for you.
Why do you still not like me?
Please stay.
Stay with me,
and I won't be afraid anymore.
I won't stay.
Do you know why both Hui and I
don't like you?
Because you're too selfish.
But I like you!
You don't like me.
You like my skin.
You're too superficial.
You'll never have love.
Am I wrong from the beginning?
Are you okay?
You should give my skin back to me.
Give it back to me.
No.
No!
Give it back to me!
No, sister!
No!
Give it back to me.
No.
Ah!
You stole the key?
You're such a good actor.
That's because you're stupid.
The key is fake.
Do you think I'd buy it?
The clue to the next door is mine.
Dong, Dong
She is speaking
Don't be afraid
Don't forget her
Let's go.
Hui.
You can't go.
Toast.
I'm finally back.
Are you okay?
Where is Ling Jiushi?
Hui, go!
If I can't have him,
you can't have him either!
She is speaking
Don't be scared
Don't forget her
What's wrong?
Chen Fei!