(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 15)
What do you have to talk with me about?
Didn't you claim to remember
whatever happened in the school?
We'd like to ask you about someone.
Who?
Sachiko.
I-I don't know about her.
Two years ago, outside the school,
a student had a car accident.
You know that, right?
It's been a long time.
Why are you bringing it up now?
You do know about this student,
don't you?
She was bullied by all of her classmates at school.
After she died, a number of students composed
a song based on her death to mock her.
Did she deserve all that suffering
simply because she had a poor family?
That girl was named Sachiko.
Not only did I know her,
I also knew her grandparents.
Her grandparents?
What about her parents?
They died.
A car accident happened on their way to deliver fish,
and killed them both.
Her parents had a car accident,
and so did she.
Poor thing.
Later on,
a reporter found out about this,
and thought it could make a good news.
So he went to her home and did an interview.
He took some photos too.
Do you have the news report and the photos?
Let me find them out.
Look.
(Victim of the accident, Sachiko)
She's a pretty little girl.
Why was she repelled by others?
Could it be that her classmates felt jealous of her?
Anyway,
she was isolated.
Look what the reporter wrote here.
So much gossip.
The whole piece is about
Sachiko's embarrassing stories at school.
The reporters in those times
would do anything to make money.
These photos reflect the road conditions when the accident happened.
It happened on a road in a remote place.
There shouldn't be too many cars.
Drivers would have a good view of the road.
Why didn't people further investigate
the cause of the accident?
Because it was hard, unimportant,
or just unworthy.
Sachiko's bedroom.
Judging from this photo,
her family was really poor.
But why would such a poor family
let their daughter
go to such a nice school?
Because they wanted to reshape their lives with knowledge.
Hold on.
(Sachiko's bedroom)
The bamboo basket in this photo
is identical to the one I saw yesterday.
I remember you telling me
that you first saw this basket
in the School Archive.
I didn't know it belonged to Sako.
Thank you.
No problem.
To be honest, you are the first people
to show so much care for Sachiko.
I hope you'll restore justice
for Sachiko.
Rest assured. We will.
Let's go.
It's still here.
It's adorable.
In my childhood, when I was upset,
I would also draw smiling faces on my toys,
just to cheer myself up.
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
Why are you always startled?
I heard a girl's laughter.
Where did it come from?
Now it's gone.
This basket must belong to Sachiko.
Her ghost goes everywhere with it.
The one you saw in the dormitory
must be hers too.
Let's go.
It looks like the key to the exit
is connected to Sachiko.
Now we've only figured out her ghost's motive to kill,
but we still don't know how to get the key.
Is destroying Sachiko's ghost the only way
to find the key?
Why would we do that?
Sachiko was the one being bullied.
What's up? Are you in a bad mood?
I just feel sorry for her.
What she was put through
might be more terrible than we think.
What on earth did you say?
I didn't say anything.
Is that Jiang Xinhong?
Why wouldn't you believe me?
I'm just a little scared.
Fear can't help you with anything now.
Just get through this period of time,
and you'll be fine once you start college.
Why are you so sure I'll be fine in college?
What if her ghost follows me to college?
You can go find her.
Let's see if she'll spare your life.
It's all your fault.
Don't you talk nonsense anymore!
Watch your mouth.
What are you doing here?
Spill it. What else do you know?
I've told you everything I know.
Did that classmate of yours ask you to keep a secret?
That's a private matter between him and me.
Let me venture a guess here.
You and he are related to Sachiko's death.
Sachiko's ghost kills in the school
with the purpose of finding you and him.
It's not like that.
Then what's the truth?
If you don't tell us what you know,
how are we supposed to help you?
Okay.
Sachiko was transferred to our class
in 10th grade.
All the classmates at that time
were from wealthy families.
No one expected
that a child of fish sellers could afford school.
Plus, in our class,
Sachiko performed quite well academically.
Out of jealousy, many other students
gave her the cold shoulder.
Have you smelled it?
There's a gross fish smell on her!
Maybe it's because she has to sell fish
on her way home after school!
Thank you.
Jiang Xinhong!
Why did you have to let her pick up the ball?
Now the ball has a gross fish smell.
How are we supposed to play with it?
Go and wash it now!
I don't wanna be stunk up by that smell!
Hurry up!
What were you thinking?
So stinky!
Everyone took pleasure in bullying her.
Sachiko wasn't angry about it.
So people started to escalate their acts.
There hasn't been much fun in recent days.
Yeah.
Aren't we going on a spring outing in two days?
Spring outings are boring.
We're tired of going to the park.
A spring outing?
I have an idea!
In the upcoming spring outing,
why don't we play a prank on that fish selling girl?
Sure!
No.
What kind of prank should we pull?
Let's huddle up and discuss it.
I knew that was wrong.
But I was afraid that if I helped her,
I would be isolated by the others.
That's why I never had the guts to tell her about it.
Then on the day of the spring outing...
Everyone, gather around!
Let's take a group photo, okay?
Okay!
Come on. Come here.
Let's take a photo.
Hurry!
Grab a seat and sit down.
Don't come over here!
I don't want to sit next to you.
There's a bad smell on you.
It stinks.
Is she gonna join us? Then I don't wanna be in this photo.
Nor do I.
We don't wanna be in the photo either.
Mr. Liu, do something!
How are we supposed to take a group photo with her around?
Her stink is making me woozy!
Go away!
Hurry up!
Guys, come back here for the group photo.
Come back now!
Let's have fun after taking this photo!
Okay.
Look at me!
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Everyone's free to move.
Be careful
of danger.
Okay.
Did she go that way?
Let's go.
Sachiko, let's play a game, alright?
Don't leave in such a hurry.
Look what this is.
Why are you holding my diary?
Give it to me!
Stop trying to grab it.
- Stand still! - Let go of me!
That's mine!
Let me read it to you. What do you think?
Sounds fine to me!
On February 3, it was a sunny day.
Although it was already a late winter,
it was still a little cold.
It was still a little cold.
I was on my way to...
To deliver the fish.
I felt like my hand was cracked.
Cracked.
Why do I have to live like this?
It's well written.
Let go of me!
Give it back to me!
Get lost!
You deserve it.
You're just a fish seller, but you acted all hoity-toity.
I'll make you show who you really are.
Do it.
Let me give you a shower!
It's pleasant to see you like this now.
Sachiko, I'm warning you.
Acting all hoity-toity, huh? Who do you think you are?
Let's go.
The next day,
everyone knew that Sachiko died in a car accident.
But no one cared.
It was as if a totally unrelated person had died.
They even made up a song to laugh at her.
Since that day,
some of her classmates died mysteriously.
Everyone was so scared.
My class was separated
and divided into different classes.
But death kept happening.
Did Sachiko ever come to you?
You all laughed at her,
but why did you survive?
Maybe I'm the only one in the class
who didn't read her diary.
I've never sung the song
made up to laugh at her.
He hasn't triggered the taboo conditions yet.
This group photo was taken that day?
I've said everything.
Can I leave now?
Who is he that just talked to you?
Is he your classmate?
His name is Mou Kai.
He has transferred to another school
and is going abroad.
Can I go now?
Yes.
If there's anything else,
we'll find you again.
A teenager girl
died at her best age
just because of the vicious joke of the young people.
They
should be responsible for that.
If what he said is true,
Sachiko
aims to take revenge on those students who mocked her.
But those students are dead,
why doesn't she give up her revenge?
Not all of them are dead.
Wasn't the guy who survived chatting with us?
Jiang Xinhong?
He said he never laughed at her.
Do you believe him?
I don't, anyway.
And Mou Kai.
They must have been classmates.
Why do you look so weird today?
It's not like you at all.
I'm just defending her against an injustice!
I just can't stand them
bullying a girl!
Don't you always bully me?
She's right.
We need to verify the authenticity
of what Jiang Xinhong said.
We need to go ask Mr. Liu again.
Lingling, you are so smart.
It's you again.
You keep coming to me,
which has seriously affected my work.
Jiang Xinhong is your student, right?
What kind of person is he?
He comes from a good family.
He studies very hard.
We're not asking you about this.
We're asking about his character.
He's quite stable in school.
He's popular.
What about Sachiko?
She got many awards, right?
Yes.
She made every effort to participate in many activities at school.
She thought as long as she won awards,
she could bring honor to the class
and everyone could accept her.
She was really a hardworking girl.
What a pity.
Is Mou Kai your student?
I didn't teach him.
So, all the awards in the dorm
belong to Sachiko.
Ripping the awards
means triggering the taboo conditions.
At least, where the awards were stuck
is like a protective umbrella.
(Annual Board of Directors of Ying Cai High School)
Why do you keep looking at these photos?
Did you find something?
Not yet.
But it's very strange.
The school is sponsored by businessmen.
Isn't it normal
for them to put their photos here to feel honored?
(Tian Weiguo)
(Mou Tangqing)
Excuse me.
Do you know him?
He was the director of our school.
He has resigned as director.
Thank you.
His last name is also Mou.
What a coincidence.
Would he have something to do with Mou Kai?
Let's go and have a look.
Let's go.
Zhu Meng and I will be enough.
Take Xia Rubei to the canteen and wait for us.
The boss of White Deer is surely vigilant,
afraid that we won't inform you
if we find any clues.
How could?
How could I be that kind of person?
Brother-in-law,
I just want to impress you
with my performance.
Let's go.
Are you still thinking about Sachiko?
Actually, my family was as poor as hers
in my childhood.
That's why I was always bullied.
I was really angry when I heard about her experience.
I heard something about you.
I think you're hardworking
and amazing.
Actually, I was always bullied
in my childhood as well.
You were bullied when you were little?
When I was ten years old,
the company my dad worked for was not doing well.
He was laid off.
Later, my family went through a difficult time.
To support my family,
my dad found a job as a worker in a septic tank
on the street.
Ling Jiushi stinks,
who sleeps in the cesspool every night.
Coward! Coward! Coward!
Look what I bought
for you.
What's wrong?
Who bullied my son?
Dad, do I stink?
Who said that?
You're very clean.
You don't stink at all.
Dad, why do you have to do the work?
Son,
if I don't do the job,
everyone's home
will become stinky.
So,
they should thank you.
Come on.
Look at this toy.
Is it fun?
Yes.
Why are there so many shapes?
These beautiful patterns
consist of insignificant, small fragments.
You should lead a beautiful life
just like these small fragments do.
Okay.
Give it to me.
Stop grabbing it!
Let go!
We want to play with it!
My dad bought this for me!
Let go!
Stop!
Hurry up!
Let go!
Don't bully him!
So the person who protected you,
I guess, is Zhu Meng?
No.
Thanks to my friend,
I didn't end up like Sako.
Aren't the weak always bullied
in this world?
But there are still many righteous people.
Unfortunately, Sachiko didn't get to meet one of them.
But I'm very lucky.
At the most difficult time of my life,
I met Meng.
You admire him?
Of course.
I mean,
he is the boss of White Deer.
Of course, I admire him.
There are many troubles in this world.
But there will be someone who will show you
that there are still many good things in this world.
To me, Meng is the one.
So, as long as someone harms him,
I will do whatever I can to protect him.
What's wrong?
If I were to tell you that in this world,
there's no such person as Ruan Baijie,
what would you do?
But that photo...
No way.
I see.
No wonder I can't find Baijie.
You won't tell Meng Yu right away, will you?
No.
As long as Meng likes it.
To me,
as long as he's happy, I'll be very happy.
I believe that one day,
he can see the people around him.
Yeah,
they are all real ones.
(Cateen)
Jiang Xinhong did lie to us.
He and Mou Kai were classmates.
After the accident, Mou Kai disappeared.
They were close.
They played volleyball on the school team.
Another one also lied.
Mr. Liu.
So, we have to find Mr. Liu again.
I'm annoyed if he isn't.
Let's go.
Why are you here again?
You won't stop coming to me, will you?
Mou Kai is the son of the school director, right?
How...
How did you know?
Why
did you lie for him?
You know
that all that happened in the school
are not accidents.
Why
are you reluctant to cooperate with us
to find a solution?
You can't solve the matter at all.
If you don't tell the truth,
we'll never find a solution to it.
Mou Kai
is indeed a relative of the school director.
He transferred to another school
after someone died in the school.
That's all I know.
I know nothing else.
Then help us
ask Mou Kai to come here.
How many times have I told you I don't want to go back to this damn place?
What do you want to ask me to come back?
All right. Everything will be fine soon.
What do you want?
- Come on. - Just a moment.
A moment!
Who are you?
Why are you looking for me?
We...
We are here to repair the teaching building in the school.
And ill-behaved students are included.
Are you kidding me?
If you don't want to be killed by Sachiko,
then listen to us.
I don't know Sachiko at all.
Jiang Xinhong told us everything.
How could you not know her?
Jiang Xinhong told you everything?
Yeah.
He said, you bullied Sachiko in those days,
so she took revenge on you.
Do you think you can survive after you've transferred to another school?
You are her next target.
Why am I the next target,
instead of Jiang Xinhong?
Because he's the only one who helped her
when you bullied her in those days!
Why are you sneering?
Go on.
Did Jiang Xinhong really tell you
that we bullied Sachiko
and he was the only one who helped her?
What do you want to say?
Damn it!
He is a liar.
He is a liar!
Calm down.
Take your time.
If I tell you,
can you guarantee that I'll be safe?
I don't know.
Anyway,
you don't have much time.
Well done.
Catch it.
She's weird but quite arrogant.
Why do you care?
Nobody cares about her.
I wonder
why she's so arrogant.
She's just pretending.
If she's in front of the one she likes,
she won't do that.
Why don't you give it a try?
I'm not interested.
You can't even handle her, can you?
Of course, I can handle her.
Just wait and see.
What if I win?
If you win,
I'll lend you the new car
my dad bought for me for a few days.
What if you lose?
Rest assured. I won't lose.
Come on.
Here.
What a bad luck.
Zhang Long.
Thank you.
Sako,
here's a letter for you.
I wrote it for you especially.
(To Sachiko)
(To Jiang Xinhong)
What is it?
A love letter!
Shameless!
Hey, when will you tell her the truth?
I can't wait.
Aren't we going on a spring outing in a few days?
Let's wait for the day of the spring outing
to make fun of her.
Don't come over here!
I don't want to sit next to you.
There's a bad smell on you.
It stinks.
Is she gonna join us? Then I don't wanna be in this photo.
Nor do I.
We don't wanna be in the photo either.
Mr. Liu, do something! Do you wanna take a photo of us or not?
How are we supposed to take a group photo with her around?
We all don't want to be next to you. Just go.
We can't take this photo with you around.
How disgusting!
Guys, come back here for the group photo.
Okay.
Look at me!
Three, two, one.
Okay. Go have fun, guys!
But don't go anywhere dangerous.
Mind your own safety.
Okay, sir.
Did she go that way?
Let's go.
Why don't we play a game?
(To Jiang Xinhong)
Sachiko wrote this love letter to me.
Give it back to me!
Jiang Xinhong!
Don't move!
Give it back to me!
Let go of me!
"Dear Xinhong,
when you read this letter, it's like we've met up again."
- Stop reading it! - "During this period of time at school..."
- Let go of me! - "I'm very pleased about our talks on literature."
I beg you!
"The first time I saw you,
I was already attracted to you."
Let me go!
"Every time I wrote..."
Screw you!
Acting all hoity-toity, huh?
Come on. Give me the water.
You stinky fish seller!
Bah!
Let's go!
The next day, we heard the news
about Sachiko dying in a car accident.
No one felt sad.
Instead, they found it quite interesting.
Jiang Xinhong even wrote a song in particular
to make fun of Sachiko.
None of us imagined that those who sang it would die two days later.
At first, we didn't take it seriously.
Some time later,
more deaths continued to happen to those who sang the song.
That's when we started to feel fear.
I then prepared to transfer to another school.
Now I'm about to leave the country.
When rich people are in trouble,
they make their way out in rich people's way.
Jiang Xinhong is a punk!
He deserves to die a hundred times!
How dare he pretend to be innocent in front of us?
I'm gonna kill him now!
Hey!
Why are all the classmates dead,
except for you and him?
The mastermind of that whole thing
was Jiang Xinhong!
He should've been the first one to die.
After Sachiko's death,
he and I felt odd about that matter,
so we've never sung that song.
What?
Are you happy now,
because he and you have escaped death?
I've told you everything I know.
How are you gonna help me, maintenance guys?
Are you gonna make Sachiko's ghost disappear?
Maintenance guys?
Don't worry.
Soon, everything will disappear.
(Ying Cai High School)
Don't rush into decisions!
We've gotta take some time to make plans for this matter!
My mind won't be at ease unless I kill Jiang Xinhong!
If you kill him, what am I gonna do?
I...
Meng,
what do you mean by that?
If you kill him,
what will become of the White Deer?
After I marry Baijie,
I'll work for the Obsidian with her.
The White Deer will have to rely on you.
Meng,
what's wrong with you?
Baijie is actually a...
What is it with Baijie?
Just stop quarreling. Stop it.
Our priority now is to find the key.
Judging from the current situation, finding the key
means calming the anger in Sako's heart, right?
That is to say, we still need to kill Jiang Xinhong.
Exactly what I want!
Excuse me.
Where is Jiang Xinhong?
He went home.
He went home?
When did he leave?
After he came back from outside at noon,
he packed his stuff and went home in a hurry.
Thank you.
Get your hands off me!
Now this is great.
The key figures are all away.
How are we supposed to find the key?
Shall we ask Mr. Liu to tell them to come back?
Do you think they will show up again?
If not, they'll just be waiting for their deaths at home.
Anyway, Sachiko
is looking for them, not us.
The time left for us
is becoming less and less.
These kids...
What lousy children!
Why must they hurt a little girl like that?
Isn't it just what all wealthy and spoiled kids do?
How boring!
I wish Baijie were here.
She must be a kindhearted person.
How is she doing now?
Even if Baijie is in this door challenge,
she won't talk to you at all.
By the way, now,
she's working along well with Lingling.
They help each other in the door challenges.
They even share one bed at night.
What did you say?
Are you sleeping in the same bed with her?
No. No.
We sleep in separate rooms.
Really?
But Baijie has told me
that the bed is so small
that she and you have to cuddle together when you sleep.
You look like an upright gentleman.
I've never imagined you're actually a brute in disguise!
Xia Rubei,
let's go.
Meng Yu...
Please explain it to him!
Now I'm finding this
very interesting.
Xia Rubei!
Coming!
Why did you have to provoke him?
He said he was bored,
so I spiced things up for him.
Oh, right,
did you say something to Xia Rubei?
Why would she make a funny face at you?
I accidentally
told her the truth.
When did that happen?
When you and Meng Yu went to look for Jiang Xinhong,
she and I both recalled
some troubling issues from childhood.
As we got deeper into our talk,
that secret just slipped out.
Troubling issues in childhood?
Why did you share those with her instead of me?
Well, one thing led to another...
It just felt natural to spill them out.
Okay.
Hey!
Are you upset that I didn't tell you?
I-I still have tons of stories.
I can tell you two more.
Meng Yu,
it's really not what you think it is.
I don't have any ties with Baijie whatsoever.
Zhu Meng,
are you still up?
Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little.
That's hilarious.