(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 16)
Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little.
That's hilarious.
She likes bananas very much,
but each time she'd only eat half of one banana.
What a poor thing!
Sako has gone far away.
She'll forget me, won't she?
So lonely, Sako.
Why would she come here for me again?
Can you hear it?
What do you want me to hear?
Some sort of singing?
Crying.
She cried in agony.
Why did no one hear her?
Who was crying?
Was it you?
She did nothing wrong.
Why would they treat her like that?
Jiang Xinhong!
Help me!
Don't leave.
Jiang Xinhong.
Jiang Xinhong, don't go!
She's beyond help, Jiang Xinhong!
Go!
Let's go! She's beyond help!
It's Mou Kai.
I beg you...
Don't go!
Don't go away!
- It hurts! - Do you hear it?
It hurts!
She's in enormous pain.
I beg you!
Don't go!
Don't go away!
You...
How do you want me to help you?
Do you want me to bring those guys to you,
so that they can be at your disposal?
You're a good person.
I want you to have this.
What is this?
Why are you giving it to me?
Because you like kaleidoscopes too.
Isn't it what I saw last time in...
So you didn't get any sleep last night?
I don't care if she did or did not stop by.
She...
What was she here for?
To give me this.
These two photos are different.
The new one has Sachiko, while the old one doesn't.
The number of people is different too.
It seems that
when a member of the class dies,
there will be one more person in the photo.
Let me see.
So the two spots in the middle
are reserved for Mou Kai and Jiang Xinhong, right?
Anyway,
we'd better find them first.
Plus, it's possible
that only when they both show up in the photo
will the key appear.
It looks like Sachiko really wants them dead.
You phony!
But they are not in the school.
What can we do to find them?
We'll go talk to Mr. Liu again.
By the way, Lingling,
did Sachiko's ghost just give you that kaleidoscope?
Why is every female Door Ghost
attracted to you?
Is that a problem?
No.
Hello.
I'm Mr. Liu, a teacher at Ying Cai High School.
Mr. Liu, hello.
Hello.
Listen, I have a question.
Is Mou Kai home?
Mou Kai...
He went to school early in the morning.
What?
He came here early in the morning?
Who asked him to come?
I don't know.
He left in a hurry.
Okay. I got it.
Mou Kai's family said
he had set out for school early in the morning.
Who asked him to come?
His family said they didn't know.
They just said he had come here early in the morning,
and that he left home in a hurry.
Take care of your injuries.
You've done a good job.
You won't come here again, will you?
Jiang Xinhong, come out!
Didn't you say you had found a way to deal with Sachiko's ghost?
Jiang Xinhong!
It wasn't me.
It really wasn't me.
It was Jiang Xinhong!
Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little.
- That's hilarious. - It really wasn't me.
She likes bananas very much,
but each time she'd only eat half of one banana.
What a poor thing!
Sako has gone far away.
She'll forget me, won't she?
So lonely, Sako.
Who saw the snowflakes drifting?
Who was abandoned in the middle of the road?
What's the last line?
I don't know.
Didn't you guys write this song?
How could you not know the last line?
I really don't know that.
I really don't!
I've lost my legs.
Would you give me yours?
I don't know!
I really don't know!
Stop it! I don't know!
Sachiko, I really don't know that.
I don't know...
I really don't know...
I really don't know!
I don't know!
Stop it, Sachiko!
Stop it! I don't know a thing!
I really have no idea!
I don't know!
I really don't know! Stop it, Sachiko!
I don't know.
I really don't know!
I don't know!
Stop it!
I've lost my legs.
Would you give me yours?
There's only one spot left.
We must find Jiang Xinhong as soon as possible.
I've got a call from Jiang Xinhong's family,
who said he came to school early in the morning too!
I've asked his classmates,
but no one has seen him.
Has he been killed by Sachiko's ghost?
No.
The spot for him in the photo is still vacant.
I know where he is.
Mou Kai is dead.
I'll be the next one.
Are you gonna hide here forever?
When you bullied Sako,
didn't it occur to you that she'd feel scared,
and hopeless?
When did I bully her?
I never bullied her.
I never ever bullied her.
Who said that to you?
Who said I bullied her?
Was it Mou Kai?
Was it him?
Ridiculous!
Has he gone crazy?
This is ridiculous!
He's the culprit.
How could he shift all the blame to me?
You'd better make it clear now.
Will you still believe
what I'm gonna say?
We'll decide whether to believe you or not.
You'll decide whether to tell the truth or not.
Sachiko and I
knew each other when we were little.
Back then,
every few days,
her family would bring fresh fish to my house.
Later, as we grew up,
I was sent to a noble school,
while she
went to an ordinary high school in the city.
But we'd still meet on weekends.
Thank you, Xinhong.
Afterwards,
one day, Sachiko's parents
had an accident when delivering fish to the customers.
They were hit by a car
and didn't survive.
The one who hit Sachiko's parents was Mou Kai,
who had just learned how to drive.
His family settled the matter with money
and promised to arrange
the best school for Sachiko.
Sachiko's grandparents had no choice
but to reluctantly agree.
What I didn't expect was
that Sachiko actually became our classmate.
Of course, I was very happy about it,
but Mou Kai wasn't.
He was afraid that Sachiko would take revenge on him,
so he started spreading rumors about her
among our classmates.
Gradually,
Mou Kai started to doubt my relationship with Sachiko.
He brought a lot of people to question me.
Mou Kai had a lot of influence in school.
I was afraid to offend him.
I was also afraid of being isolated.
So I told them
that I also hated that girl.
Since you also hate her,
do you
dare to play a game with us?
What game?
I have a letter here.
Give it to the fishmonger girl.
(To Sachiko)
Why are you doing this?
We've been bored these days.
Let's have some fun.
This is too...
Hey,
are you reluctant to do it?
Yeah.
I'll do it.
I was really afraid to offend him.
So I had to do as he said.
Actually, many times,
I really wanted to tell Sachiko the truth.
But every time...
I would run into Mou Kai.
Jiang Xinhong.
I'll leave first.
Okay.
Jiang Xinhong.
Where are you going?
I...
There are guests coming to my house today.
I wanted to order two fish from her.
Fine.
If you dare to tell her about our plan,
I'll make you regret it.
I... Bastard!
You bastard!
My parents
also worked under Mou Kai's parents.
I didn't dare to offend him.
Until the picnic day...
If you don't leave now, we won't be able to take photos today.
Don't you realize that you smell bad?
Get lost!
Everyone, look at the camera.
Cheer up.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
It's free time now.
Don't go to dangerous places.
Be careful.
I couldn't imagine how Sachiko would react
if I had told her the truth.
Sachiko,
how about we play a game?
You stinky fishmonger.
Stop pretending to be aloof.
Don't think we don't know
what kind of person you are in private.
I have a letter here.
Let me read it to everyone.
Do you want to hear it?
Yes.
Mr. Xinhong.
Give it back!
Seeing your words is like seeing you in person.
Give it back to me.
During the time in school,
our literary exchanges
brought me great joy.
Let go!
Stop reading.
Do you remember the first time I saw you when we were kids?
At that time,
I felt inferior because I was from a fish-selling family,
but it was your smile that gave me confidence.
How did Xinhong smile?
Get off me.
You smell so bad. How can you go to school?
Give me the water bucket.
Acting aloof, huh?
Dare you pretend to be aloof with me again?
Sako.
Jiang Xinhong.
Why did you do that?
I...
Why did you give the letter to Mou Kai?
Say something. Why?
Hey!
Are you waiting for your boyfriend here?
Did he force you to say it?
Say something.
Did he force you to do this?
Tell her.
Did I force you,
or did you do it willingly?
I did it myself.
Did you hear that?
Let's go.
Jiang Xinhong.
So annoying.
Jiang Xinhong, I don't believe it.
Are you done?
Jiang Xinhong!
Jiang Xinhong, don't leave!
Leave her alone, Jiang Xinhong.
You can't help her.
Help me!
Don't go, Jiang Xinhong!
How can you save her like that? Jiang Xinhong.
Let's go, Jiang Xinhong!
Jiang Xinhong!
Go!
Don't leave.
You all know
what happened later.
You wrote that ironic song about Sako, right?
I didn't write that song to mock her originally.
I wanted to remember her.
But the lyrics were changed by Mou Kai later.
She didn't even know about it at all.
(Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little. She's an independent girl.)
(She taught me a lot. Now I want to write a song for her.)
Don't you want to see her?
What's the meaning of seeing her?
So you just want to hide here for the rest of your life?
Don't you have friends whom
you want to see but are afraid to see?
I really don't have the courage.
After Sako died,
she'd been carrying this with her.
Now,
I'll give it back to you.
But you, Jiang Xinhong,
don't deserve to be remembered by her.
Let's go.
Wait.
I'll go with you.
(Class 2, Grade 1)
Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little.
That's hilarious.
She likes bananas very much,
but each time she'd only eat half of one banana.
What a poor thing!
Sako has gone far away.
She'll forget me, won't she?
So lonely, Sako.
You wrote
this song, right?
It's beautiful.
No.
It wasn't like this originally.
I don't believe it.
Sachiko has called herself Sako since she was little.
She's an independent girl.
She taught me a lot.
Now I want to write a song for her.
She likes bananas very much,
but she always leaves half of it for her parents.
She has a hard life,
but she always smiles at it.
One day, Sako will go far away.
Will she forget about me then?
Maybe she'll feel lonely and lost,
just like every time I think of her.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have done that. It was my fault.
I wish I had more courage.
Do you know what the last line of
the lyrics says?
I know.
You would ask me,
"I've lost my legs.
Would you give me yours?"
I, Jiang Xinhong, now
will tell you without hesitation.
Yes.
Okay.
I know.
It'll be too late to forget you
In this desolate world
You won't be there
No one can escape the destined game of separation
This ridiculous fate
Only you are willing to
Wait for a snow with me
Wait for the stars to fill the sky
Let this moment
Be worth 10,000 light years
This Sachiko
was quite an honest person.
Person?
Well, an honest ghost.
Jiang Xinhong.
I wish you
all the best.
I will carry the memory of Sako
and move forward.
Until the night and day blur
You will be
Behind me
I know
From afar
Looking me
In the eye
Will we
Meet again
In some other time and space
To have you in my arms
I won't give up
It seems
that we shouldn't joke about love,
nor play pranks on people.
Otherwise,
it can be taken seriously.
I think he's right.
I think he's right too.
What about the other door-passing shepherds?
Should we tell them where the door is?
Don't worry.
They will definitely find the door to go out.
Besides,
there are no strange things
guarding the doors in this world.
Zhuang.
Go and open the door.
Let's go.
By the way,
Meng Yu,
I have something to tell you.
Actually, Baijie...
It's me.
Ruan Lanzhu!
I'm going to kill you!
Let's go and eat.
You're back.
I made night snacks.
Have some before they are cold.
Coming.
Here.
Be careful.
Okay.
Just take one bowl.
Are you still thinking about Sachiko?
Didn't you say
not to tell Li Dongyuan about Baijie?
Why did you change your mind and tell him?
I pitied him.
What did your childhood friends look like?
I forgot.
How could someone forget their childhood?
Maybe I was so happy
that I forgot,
or maybe I was so miserable
that I forgot.
You have a bad memory.
Weird.
In the future,
you will find that I am weirder than you think.
Fortunately,
you have had friends since young.
Otherwise,
you might become another Sachiko.
Do you believe that?
It was my good friend
who made me
a laughing stock.
I believe that.
When I find him,
I'll avenge you.
Forget it. It's all in the past.
Where are your good friends now?
They are with me now.
I passed the door of Sako with them just now.
The Spring Festival is around the corner.
I'm not lonely
if I can celebrate the festival with you all.
(Li Dongyuan)
Ruan Lanzhu, you bastard!
I'll teach you a lesson!
Get prepared
and meet someone with me.
So early?
Ruan. Lingling.
Have a seat.
Where is he?
He'll be here soon.
Ruan.
He is arrogant
and straightforward.
Please don't be mad at him.
I will persuade him.
Have a seat.
I didn't expect
that he would play this game.
He just told me
he thought it was a dream.
So, Ruan,
can you take this job?
We'll talk about it after meeting him.
Hello?
Mr. Zhang.
I see.
Okay, go ahead.
Could it be him?
Who?
A very unique young director.
Zhang Yiqing.
He has directed many art films and has won many awards.
Let me tell you.
Capital is capital. Creation is creation.
Don't interfere with my creation.
Bye.
Sorry.
Director Zhang.
This is Ruan Lanzhu.
Ling Jiushi.
I told you before.
They led me
to pass the door before.
They are very reliable in the circle.
It's hard to meet them.
Zaozao.
I've thought
about this.
I need to
think about it twice.
Nice tea.
No, Director Zhang.
Your next door is about to open.
Now, if you...
You are good-looking young men.
You can contact me
if you want to be an actor.
To be honest,
other organizations have contacted me.
White Deer.
Oh?
Let's go.
You've known that.
Ruan.
Lingling.
Are we leaving like this?
Or what?
Do you want an autograph or a photo?
Li Dongyuan did it?
Who else could it be?
He did it to take revenge on you
for Baijie.
Anyway, it is quite difficult to deal with him.
It would be troublesome if we screwed up.
Leave it to him.
Perfect.
You're right.
He's quite arrogant.
Did you leave the clue to him on purpose?
You really did that?
Why?
Li Dongyuan called me last night.
So I told him
as compensation for him.
Besides, I don't want to be a bad guy like Mou Kai.
You're right.
But why should we come here so early?
We didn't sleep well.
This long journey was costly.
After all, he's a friend of Tan Zaozao.
I have to respect her.
But since he didn't choose Obsidian,
it has nothing to do with me.
I have money for gasoline.
How did White Deer persuade Zhang Yiqing?
Think about Li Dongyuan.
Think about his skills to persuade.
It makes sense.