(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 6)
Someone's here.
It's you!
Why are you sleeping here?
Keep your egg safe.
- Thank you. - Sleep?
Luckily, you're smart.
The triplets gave me the key.
Are they asking me to save you?
You met the triplets?
You tell them apart?
O-Of course.
Alright. No.
I knew it.
Not being able to tell the triplets apart
is not a taboo condition.
Then why are they so persistent in
wanting us to tell them apart?
Let's go back first.
Let's go.
Who is it?
It's me, Zhu.
I have to come and share a room with you.
No, the bed is too small.
I can sleep on the floor.
Hey.
It's too depressing to share a room with Tian Yan.
I'm afraid I'll expose myself if I say something wrong.
I won't go out, no matter what you say today.
Drag me out if you dare.
You're so darn heavy.
Who can drag you?
Who are you talking about?
You.
Aren't you named Xu Xiaochen?
That's Cheng, not Chen.
Forget it. I'll sleep on the floor.
No.
It's improper for men and women to sleep in the same room.
Let her do it.
She saved us.
It's good to be alive inside the door.
We can't care too much.
Turn off the lights.
Time to go to bed.
Love you, Lingling!
I'm kind enough to let you in. You'd better not be a chatterbox.
Do you think
someone will die tonight?
I'm afraid that we'll lose another person
before we know it.
Thank you, the organizing committee of the Oscars.
I'd also like to thank the director
and the producer.
What kind of beautiful dream is she having?
It's not a beautiful dream.
Xu Xiaocheng!
Don't wake her up.
Or she might ask you to give her Oscar statue back to her.
Why are you still up?
I'm having a dream too.
Who is it?
Someone who can save your life.
You?
It is debatable whether you can protect yourself or not.
You haven't heard me out yet.
How can you tell
if what I'm saying makes sense?
What's wrong?
Someone's outside the wall.
I nearly died.
The sound has disappeared.
It has happened again.
He really left this time, right?
What's the matter?
I saw a red eye.
- A red eye? - What happened?
Let's go check it out.
Gosh!
It's so big.
Fortunately, I sat up.
Otherwise, my head would've been cracked open.
I wasn't in breach of any taboo conditions.
Why would he try to kill me?
Whose egg is broken?
Mine.
When did it happen?
When we were on the seventh floor.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You didn't sleep because you knew he'd attempt to kill you, right?
It was meaningless to tell you that.
Now your egg is broken.
He'll keep trying to hunt you down.
We've gotta knock him down first!
Like what Zhang Xinghuo did?
The Wizard can't be killed.
There must be a solution.
Yo.
You care that much about my life?
God knows why you're still in the mood for jokes.
Since that man is the Wizard,
the triplets must have been kidnapped and brought here,
like what happens in the tale of Fitcher's Bird.
They don't look like father and daughters at all.
That is to say, this place isn't the triplets' home.
This is not our home.
We wanna go home.
It's easy.
We can just ask the triplets.
How are we supposed to find those elusive children?
How could you ask me to play with a ball here in the middle of the night?
Don't you find it amusing?
Shouldn't you say "crazy" instead?
Don't you think you're saying too much crap?
Fine.
I'll play with the ball.
Xiaocheng, can't you look happier?
I...
How am I supposed to feel happy about it?
Can we play with you?
Sure.
But if we play here,
people will be disturbed.
Why don't we go somewhere else?
Are we really gonna treat the kids this way?
There's no room for mercy.
Step aside. Let me handle it.
Are we gonna play here?
Isn't it nice?
If it's really nice, why did you shut the door?
If I hadn't shut it, you might have run away, right?
Kids, don't be afraid.
We are good people.
We just wanna ask you a few questions.
You were captured and brought to this place, right?
We can't tell you about that.
If you don't tell us, how can we have fun together?
You still don't wanna say it?
Tell the truth now,
or I'll smash the eggs in your hands.
Will you let us go if we tell you the truth?
Yes.
We were caught and brought here by him.
Do you know him?
No.
But he said he knew us.
He is kind to us,
but he wouldn't let us leave this place.
He has asked us to play a game about protecting eggs.
He hasn't locked you up.
Why don't you make your own escape?
No one can go anywhere in the thick fog.
Why would he ask you to hold eggs in your mouths?
I don't know. He trains us every day,
emphasizing that someone will die if an egg breaks.
He was kidnapped by a bad guy when he was ten.
That bad guy forced him and his mother to hold eggs in their mouths.
The one who broke their egg would be killed.
Then, his mom's egg broke,
so the bad guy killed his mother.
He cried his heart out when he said this.
What we saw on the seventh floor
must be the Wizard's story.
Hmm.
Do you happen to know where the door is?
At first,
I meant for us to team up.
If you tell us where the door is,
we'll help you get rid of him
and take you out of this place.
But now it seems...
We know where it is!
The door is right over there.
You mean that storeroom?
Yes!
Can you let us go now?
He forbids us from being away for too long.
Thank you. See you next time.
You're so good at picking locks.
I have more skills than you think.
You stay put. It's dangerous inside.
They didn't lie to us. The door is right here.
Should we tell them?
Tian Yan, Zhong Chengjian, come in.
How did you know we were outside?
If I were you, I would do the same.
The taboo conditions are clear now.
When an egg breaks,
the Wizard will kill.
Protecting our eggs is the most important thing.
Now that we've found the door,
we can leave when we get the key to it.
It won't be easy to get the key.
The Wizard can't be killed.
Why can't he?
He is clearly a human,
not a ghost or a demon.
Ordinary approaches will surely fail.
If ordinary approaches won't work,
then what will?
Are we gonna let ourselves die here?
This is my very first door challenge,
and I'm already having such bad luck!
It's creepy as hell!
Calm down.
What if your egg breaks?
So, that's your new partner?
Let's go.
Go.
I'm feeling dozy.
Don't sleep tonight.
The Wizard will try to kill Zhu Meng again.
How about this?
We'll take turns to keep watch at night.
I'll sleep first.
I'll keep watch.
Such a careless young man.
Go to sleep, Xiaocheng.
Thank you, Lingling.
(One day)
(Before the Birthday Party)
Don't just sit there.
Dig in.
Who put a needle in my bowl?
Was it you?
Are you...
Are you out of your mind?
Haven't you been allies for a long time?
If you wanna act stupid, just harm yourself,
not me!
The porridge had been placed in the bowls before we came in.
We each chose a random seat.
Who would've known you'd sit there?
Then who did this?
You were late.
So what if I was late?
Because you were late,
we all assumed that the seat should be yours.
Whoever did that must have targeted you.
Fine. Then come at me! Come at me!
Did you put that needle in my bowl?
What did you say?
I was asking if you had put that needle in my bowl!
- Sit down. - No way!
You all fear death, don't you?
Don't make rash decisions!
I'll stab you to death!
I'm really gonna stab you to death!
What?
He can't kill until an egg is broken, can he?
My egg isn't broken yet.
It doesn't mean
I can't break your egg
before killing you, right?
I'm only 26 years old.
I haven't gotten a girlfriend yet.
Can you spare my life?
What did you say?
I asked if you could spare my life.
Haven't I told you not to break your eggs?
I don't want to play anymore. I want to go home.
Neither do I. I wanna go home too.
You're not going anywhere!
Take it.
Take it!
Time's up.
Go back to your room.
A-Am I safe now?
You're safe for now.
But given your recklessness,
it's only a matter of time before you die.
The Wizard seems to have a different attitude
towards the triplets.
J-Just like our fingers, which vary in length,
it is common for people to treat others with different attitudes.
Have we missed
the key clue in the tale of Fitcher's Bird?
Though knives and guns can't hurt him,
I just noticed
a new burn scar on his hand.
I guess his hand was burned as he was cooking.
Maybe he's afraid of fire.
That's right!
The book says that the Wizard was burned to death in the end.
That's a lead!
At least, it proves
he's not a man without weaknesses.
The birthday party will be held tomorrow.
Let's give it a try at that time.
Okay.
Try... it out with our lives?
You should be glad that you're alive now.
This door challenge is quite odd, isn't it?
It seems simple.
We managed to figure out the Wizard's story
on the seventh floor quickly,
and correctly deduced
that breaking our eggs is a taboo condition.
But now, with all these clues,
this door doesn't seem simple at all.
Are you wondering
why the triplets always ask us to tell them apart?
Yeah.
According to the tale of Fitcher's Bird,
we know for sure that the Wizard has the key
to the door that we've found.
What on earth is wrong with the triplets?
Even the information about the door
was provided by the triplets.
Many things
can be explained by common sense,
but sometimes our thinking is also limited by it.
I know.
I'm just afraid
that the idea that fire can kill the Wizard
is a sort of common sense that limits our thinking.
What if fire can't hurt the Wizard?
Anyway, many tales end
with monsters being burned to death by fire.
Common sense...
Are we gonna believe our common sense or not?
Stop with all that thinking.
Let's get some sleep first.
Why are you sleeping here?
Keep your egg safe.
Thank you.
Where is your egg?
Why do you ask?
This isn't my egg.
There should be a dark spot on my egg.
There you are.
Why are you sleeping here?
Keep your egg safe.
Thank you.
So,
the person he has been trying to kill is me.
I thought switching our eggs
would make him come after me instead.
I didn't expect that he'd still target you.
This is so nerve-racking.
Take your egg back.
What are you doing?
It slipped.
Are you crazy?
This could have been eaten.
What a waste.
Actually, I've been wanting to ask you.
Are you taking care of me
just to get me to join Obsidian?
I think you're talented,
and I want to be your friend.
Not everyone gets to be my friend.
So, you entered the door just to help me, right?
Don't flatter yourself.
I did it for Xu Xiaocheng,
and you don't need to burden yourself
with so many moral constraints.
As the head of the door-passing organizations,
the spokesperson, an outstanding leader,
and a legendary figure,
I also have a responsibility to figure out
why the Fitcher's Bird,
despite being a low-level door, could kill so many people.
Have you found the answer?
Not yet.
So, aren't you feeling wronged
by being trapped here?
No.
I believe you
can lead everyone to find the door and the key
because I see a light in you
that others don't have.
Alright,
we will definitely get out of here.
I'll bring Chestnut
to find you at Obsidian later.
Agreed.
Today, as the best actress,
I have something to say.
(On the Day)
(Of the Birthday Party)
(Hotel)
Ruan, you're really bold.
I can't sleep at all.
I didn't sleep either.
So, do you think
my sleeping posture looks good,
or does Xu Xiaocheng's look better?
Both look good.
Let's go. Time's up.
Wait a minute.
Actress, why are you still putting on makeup at this hour?
Just in case I die, I want to be the most beautiful one.
Wait for me!
(Happy Birthday)
Wasn't it supposed to be the triplets' birthday?
Why is there only one person wearing a birthday hat?
Can't he even buy more birthday hats?
Thank you all for coming to their birthday party.
Please have a seat.
Happy birthday to you.
Do you not find his voice eerie,
as if he's at a funeral?
Let me sing too
and drown out his voice.
Happy birthday to you.
Make a wish.
Then
let's blow out the candles.
Next,
let's cut the cake.
Have a piece.
OK.
Is this red velvet cake?
I don't know.
I'll eat.
Have some cake.
I don't want to eat.
Pour it on.
Have some cake.
I don't want to eat.
Why won't you eat?
It's gonna take some time for me to tell you.
Is this the bones of Zeng Ruguo
and Zhang Xinghuo?
What do you mean?
Sorry, slick hand.
Drop my cake. You all need to die.
None of you can escape.
Did we make it?
Where is the key?
He can actually survive this.
He is really amazing.
Today,
all of you will die.
W-W-What should we do?
Everyone, run in different directions.
Where do we run to?
Go downstairs.
Wait, wait.
He's gone.
He's not chasing us anymore. Something's not right.
Dare we go check out Room 720?
Let's go.
What is this?
Does he kill people when the egg breaks?
This is the Wizard's past.
That little boy is the Wizard.
2010.
This is 2010.
If this is 2010,
then the Wizard is 10 years old...
I'm only 40 years old.
It's not quite appropriate for you to call me "Old Bro," right?
It was 1985 on the 14th floor.
The Wizard said he was 40.
What's going on?
The timelines don't match up.
Could it be that the little boy is not him?
It should be him.
That face
has distinctive features at both 10 and 40.
What's going on?
I feel itchy as soon as I come in.
Lingling,
it seems that you've aged a few years.
Aged?
Yes.
The 14th floor is in the year 1985.
This is 2010.
We'll definitely age rapidly when we reach the seventh floor.
So, it seems like this building has 2 timelines.
No.
No, if there are only 2,
the Wizard couldn't be 40.
There must be a third one.
Let's go.
Time in this building is a mess.
Go to the first floor. The old lady's house.
Let's go.
Granny.
I've told you everything I know.
Granny, please don't play dumb.
I want to know if there was a murder
in Room 720 of this building.
Come in and talk.
Why is this in the year 2040?
Granny, there must be a mistake.
It's 2040 now.
This is the third timeline.
Granny, in which year did the murder happen?
2010.
Wait a moment.
(Egg Murder)
It's him.
But he was not born in 1985.
Granny.
How is the man doing now?
He's not doing well.
He lives next door to me,
but I haven't seen him for a long time.
He's 40 now.
That's right.
Men will still act like children.
even though
they are middle-aged.
He's always playing with knives and stuff at home.
His knife skills should be quite good
now,
but unfortunately, he's living alone.
Are you single?
Granny.
Well, how long has it been since you last saw him?
It's been quite a while.
If you don't go out
before 12:35 p.m.,
the apartment door will open,
and dense fog will engulf everything here.
The murder occurred at 12:35.
No wonder Granny mentioned this specific time.
It's almost 12 o'clock.
Only half an hour left.
It's 2040 now,
which means the Wizard returned to 1985 from here.
He doesn't belong to that timeline,
so no matter what, we can't kill him.
Yes.
I suddenly have a bold idea
that can explain everything here.
You mean the time machine.
Yes.
Are you talking about the crazy man from 404?
Why are you here again?
Bro, I want to go back to the past
and start over.
I thought you didn't believe in it.
I believe it now.
I'm living a terrible life.
Please help me.
Now?
I don't have that concept.
Time means nothing to me.
Can we go inside and take a look?
Let me broaden your horizons.
This is in the year 2040.
Where's the time machine?
Come in.
Don't mess around anywhere.
Is the time machine
in bad shape?
I have been repairing it for six months. What do you think?
The man on the fourteenth floor
used it, right?
How did you know?
Have you seen him?
Where is he?
It all started
about six months ago.