(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 38)
Since his friend designed this game
and he even left the important clue to him,
then the key or the door
must be related to him.
He used to rent a house
with a boy named Wu Qi.
That fast?
Are we the White Snake?
How can we arrive here so fast?
This game is guiding us.
It means I'm right.
The key should be here.
The key?
The Moon in the mirror.
Find the mirror first.
It's like fishing a needle out of the sea.
We're at a loss for what to do
and can't do anything.
Qianli,
I wanted to ask you just now.
Now you like idioms so much?
You've found it?
Do you feel like I've become
more mature and reliable?
Yes.
Yes my ass.
You're just a kid.
Don't pretend to be an adult.
Is it so easy
to use a few idioms
for the responsibilities in the adult world?
I don't want to grow up.
I
used to make you worry outside.
I think if there's a chance to see you again,
at least I won't trouble you, right?
If it weren't for Qianli,
we would have been dead.
Don't be too judgmental.
Just relax in this world.
This game
will disappear soon.
It won't be like this anymore.
That's great.
If the game disappears,
won't you also disappear?
Not only him,
but you will also be gone.
It doesn't matter if I exist or not.
I can't go back anyway.
Ruan can get out.
What if
he can't get out?
It's okay.
Don't worry about me.
I had no intention of going out
from the beginning.
Such a stupid game.
It's really harmful.
We just jump into the pit one after another.
Lingling,
can you design another game
without any taboo conditions,
violence, or death?
We can just get together happily
and help each other in times of poverty.
That'll be great.
Don't use idioms recklessly anymore.
Okay.
Who do you want to live with?
You, him, my brother,
Chen Fei, and Xue.
It's fine if Yi Manman is there.
Oh.
And Zaozao.
She is a superstar after all.
It's better not to have them.
If there is a chance,
I will definitely fulfill your wish.
During this time,
I've been thinking about the relationship between reality and virtuality.
People who disappear in reality
can exist in the virtual world.
And the emotions in the virtual world
are more real than in the real world.
Reality and virtuality seem to be opposite
and complementary.
If we can pass the Spi Realm,
I will do everything I can
to let you exist.
Thank you.
Now that you mention it,
I feel quite good.
It's true.
You know me so well
because you have my big data, right?
If I have more of your data,
I can create you.
It's not difficult to do it
with the current technology level.
Ruan,
you're scared too.
I'm much better than you.
I've checked all the mirrors,
but it seems like they can't reflect the moon.
The clue is so important,
so it can't be so silly, right?
Rest enough,
let's go.
What time is it?
Oh no.
It's about three o'clock at night.
How did you know?
Before I came in, I took a look at the moon.
Time has been chaotic since we got here,
so I rely on the moon's phase.
You can tell time from the moon?
Yes, indeed.
The moon turns perfectly round on the day after mid-autumn day.
On the 17th of the 8th lunar month, the moon is before Geng, on the 18th, the moon is after Geng.
On the 19th and 20th of the 8th lunar month, the moon rises at 9 p.m.
On the 21st, 22nd, and 23rd of the 8th lunar month the moon rises
at midnight.
On the 24th, 25th, and 26th of the 8th lunar month, the moon appears
for the cattle.
On the 27th, 28th, and 29th of the 8th lunar month,
the moon follows the sun.
Cheng Qianli.
If you keep talking nonsense,
I'll teach you a lesson for your brother.
Well, ancient people used lunar phases
to determine dates.
But it's more complicated to determine time through lunar phases.
Qianli,
are you suggesting that the moon can represent time?
Yes.
I see.
Since the moon represents time,
the Moon in the mirror is the clock.
I've been ignoring this all along.
The watch in my house ran backward.
Gao Dawei has been designing games abroad,
and he must miss home very much.
The time abroad
is reversed compared to ours,
so the Moon in the mirror he left behind
has the time reversed.
That backward-running watch is meant to remind me
that it's the Moon in the mirror,
symbolizing both time
and his longing.
Let's go.
Let's go, Qianli.
Lingling,
I'm now
the NPC inside this door.
I can't fight with you anymore.
We will definitely meet.
Keep going.
The key,
why are there two?
(Illusion of Life) (Reality of Death)
Life?
Death?
The words seem to be about reality and illusion,
not life and death.
(Illusion of Life) (Reality of Death)
Reality and illusion are just adjectives;
life and death are the key.
So many people
can't kill you guys.
They have already been killed by us.
You found the key?
Yes.
The Moon in the mirror is not exactly the moon in the mirror,
it's the time in the mirror.
Ling Jiushi,
you didn't expect it, did you?
In the game designed for you,
I am the ultimate winner.
If you were the one holding the key and opening the door,
then there would be no winner in this game.
Nonsense.
You've been against me all along.
Now the keys are in my hands.
If I'm not the winner,
then who is?
You've failed.
You've lost.
You seem to be going crazy.
Don't waste time talking to him,
snatch the keys back.
Come over...
If you come closer, I'll swallow the keys.
I could just kill you first
and then dig it out of your belly.
Hold on for a moment.
We haven't found the door yet.
There's only one door to exit,
but we have two keys.
Let's find the door first,
then discuss the keys.
What do you think?
You got it wrong.
I'm not here to compete with you past the door.
I'm determined to pass it.
I agree.
Why?
All along,
I never had a choice.
From entering the door with you
to witnessing your death,
I can only accept and understand.
But this time, Yan Balang will make the choice for me.
If he chooses correctly,
I'll stay here with you.
If he chooses wrongly,
then I'll send you to purify the game.
But if you don't purify the game,
more people will die.
I don't know those people.
I only know you.
I will only save you.
Since entering the first door,
there's been this question:
save someone I know
or save a group of strangers?
While you all chose to sacrifice the one you know.
I know I should choose this way.
So, I handed over the choice.
This way, whether it's for you
or for other players,
it's relatively fair.
I don't have that much ability.
I just want to save the people I care about.
Save all the people I care about.
So altogether,
I'll save many people.
You said
you would protect me for a lifetime,
whether it's your lifetime
or mine.
Well, I feel the same way.
Thank you.
Now,
I just hope this way
can be a little longer.
(Amazing Supermarket)
Let's go.
(Amazing Internet Cafe)
Don't let them come over.
Your choice will create a sequence.
The choice should be simultaneous.
Opening the door and inserting the key simultaneously.
The one who chooses correctly lives,
while the one who chooses wrong dies.
(Reality of Death)
(Illusion of Life)
How did you know?
The clue to this door
is, Two leave, one returns."
Isn't that the current situation?
This door's clue isn't unsolvable.
It's not like an applied problem,
so how could it be unsolvable?
Don't you know?
At this time,
what's the point of saying these things?
How could it be meaningless?
Is the purpose of me staying by your side
just to come in and die for you?
Did I painstakingly accompany you until the end
just for money?
I...
You clearly knew the clue to this door,
yet you didn't tell me.
Are you trying to drag me in to be your scapegoat?
What am I to you in your heart?
Isn't the answer obvious?
If you two go in, only he will survive.
He wanted to use your life
to achieve his own success.
This man
is really bad.
If you two can't decide,
just give us the keys.
No.
(Illusion of Life)
Honey.
I'm sorry.
Please help me.
Ah.
I...
I'm so close,
I've put all my efforts into this.
Just this one step, that's all I need.
If I can't replicate this game,
I'll lose everything.
I've already lost everything.
I...
I swear
I didn't mean to hurt you.
But
there's no other way.
Honey.
You know
I can't die now.
I promised those people.
I... I can't die.
I can't die.
Honey! Honey!
Please.
Please help me.
Please, I can't die.
Help me, honey.
Please help me.
I can't die.
If this is your choice,
I'll help you achieve it.
Whether successful or not,
we won't see each other again.
Let's pretend we never met.
(Illusion of Life)(Reality of Death)
If it were me,
I wouldn't choose it.
Reality and illusion are just adjectives.
Life and death
are the doors of destiny.
(Illusion of Life)(Reality of Death)
Ah!
The Reality of Death
is the way out.
But if I open it,
you'll stay here forever.
If you open it,
you won't be able to purify this game.
But this is a fair choice.
You choose first.
This is definitely not the original design of this game.
Gao Dawei
wouldn't have led you to a dead end.
You said
that this is the original design.
The game may have been heavily modified to the point of
distorting the initial setup,
but the choice is fair enough.
I can accept it.
Life, death.
(Reality of Death)
Life and death have consequences,
so we need to choose between illusion and reality.
Actually, the boundaries aren't that distinct.
I can't choose.
This is a real deadlock.
There's a solution to every applied problem.
What solution?
Even though I joined the X organization for money,
I fell in love with him.
I also know
he's not worth loving,
but I can't help it.
I've decided not to leave.
I want to stay with him.
Since we have to open two doors at once,
I'll open the door of the Illusion of Life.
You go
and do what you want.
All this time,
we've been at odds, fighting to the death.
I'm sorry.
You're the best opponent I've ever encountered.
(Illusion of Life)(Reality of Death)
Why are all the other doors gone?
There wasn't a chance
to finish the design for the 12th door challenge.
In fact, when players get through 11 door challenges,
they've already finished the game.
So the settings for my character
say that I'm a skilled player who's done 10 door challenges.
Only when I get to this place
can the content of the game be corrected.
What will happen then?
It's hard to explain.
To put it simply,
the rest of this matter
only concerns me.
I don't have a problem understanding all this.
It's just that you aren't making things clear enough.
I'm not stupid.
12 doors.
12 Sufferings?
Can that many sufferings befall one's life?
Birth, old age, illness, and death.
The pain of parting with a loved one.
The bitterness of not getting what one desires.
The resentment for unpleasant happenings.
Sometimes people are confused and their minds are clouded.
Worries, sorrow, sadness, and anger.
I see it now.
It's what Gao Dawei first had in mind when he designed this game.
12 doors.
12 Chinese zodiac animal signs.
12 months.
12 two-hour periods of a day.
12...
It's a number representing the endless circle of life.
12 Sufferings
correspond to 12 negative emotions.
Players do door challenges that stand for different emotions.
When they solve all 12 challenges,
it means
they've overcome 12 negative emotions.
Then
they'll feel like they've been reborn.
The term "reborn" here
doesn't refer to biological changes.
It's only about a person's state of mind.
It seems like you've suddenly become talkative.
I'm busted.
I was thinking
that if our chat continued,
you could stay longer. Right?
However,
there's an end to every conversation.
Parting is inevitable.
The days we've spent together
have brought me so much joy.
I'm grateful.
♫It'll be too late to forget you♫
♫In this desolate world♫
♫You won't be there♫
♫No one can escape the destined game of separation♫
♫This ridiculous fate♫
♫Only you are willing to♫
♫Wait for a snow with me♫
♫Wait for the stars to fill the sky♫
♫Let this moment♫
♫Be worth 10,000 light years♫
♫You're on the other side♫
♫About to disappear♫
♫Please stop counting down the time♫
♫I'm afraid I'll do anything♫
♫I won't give up♫
I hope you'll stay safe
and happy forever.
♫You will always be in my eyes♫
♫Until the night and day blur♫
♫You're on the other side♫
♫About to disappear♫
♫Please stop counting down the time♫
♫I'm afraid I'll do anything♫
♫I won't give up♫
♫Want to return to the end of the world♫
♫You will be♫
♫Behind me♫
♫I know♫
♫From afar♫
♫Looking me♫
♫In the eye♫
♫Will we♫
♫Meet again♫
♫In some other time and space♫
♫To have you in my arms♫
He's moving!
He seems to be awake now.
He went across the road when the red light for pedestrians was still on.
I was driving as normal.
Xiong Qi?
Did you just knock an acquaintance down with your car?
Who do you mean? Do we know each other?
I don't know him at all!
Don't you try to blackmail me!
Xiong Qi...
Please let us get through.
Excuse me.
Bring the stretcher here.
You finally woke up.
I was worried sick.
Doctor! Doctor! He is awake.
Look at this.
Everything's fine.
Thanks to your good physical condition,
you're recovering quickly.
Chen Fei,
why are you working in this hospital?
Do you know me?
Dr. Chen has been working here all the time.
Aren't you
a vet?
Dr. Chen, have you been a vet?
Contact the department of neurology.
Arrange a consultation in the afternoon.
Okay.
Have a good rest.
I'll lift your bed up, alright?
Is it okay?
You just woke up from a five-day coma.
Are you feeling alright?
Are you hungry?
Shall I buy you some food?
The Spi Realm...
How is this game now?
How did you get to know about this newly launched game
called the Spi Realm?
Has the car accident turned you into a psychic?
The game has gained much popularity.
Let me show you.
No.
Don't get it started.
It's too dangerous.
What's dangerous about it?
Look.
(Click to start)
(Friends on an adventure)
It's a great stress reliever.
No. This is not what I'm saying.
I mean a game about door challenges
that combines virtual reality and real life.
Well, players open a door and take a challenge.
Has that car accident done something to your brain?
I've never heard of such a game.
No. I've helped you solve a door challenge,
where Li Dongyuan died.
Do you remember?
Who is Li Dongyuan?
What are you talking about?
Previously,
I received a hard disk,
in which this game was found.
Then I moved to a new house
and joined an organization called Obsidian.
You've been to that house several times to visit me.
The leader of the organization
is named Ruan Lanzhu.
Did you have a ridiculous dream
when you were in a coma?
Jiushi,
you had a car accident,
and have been unconscious until today.
What's all that "obsidian" stuff about?
A car accident?
Are you saying
that I went out on that day and had a car accident?
Yes.
See for yourself.
It's only been five days since the accident, right?
It's impossible.
This is impossible!
Calm down.
You've been severely injured.
It can be a cause of
memory disorders.
I'll talk to the doctor,
and see if he can move up the consultation.
I'll be right back.
It can't be true.
It just can't be true!
Move slowly.
Here, your cellphone.
It was broken in the accident.
Then I fixed it for you
and restored the data.
(Contacts)
Where is Zaozao?
Who?
That actress named Tan Zaozao.
What kind of actress
would have such a terrible name?
My girlfriend knows about tons of celebrities,
but she's never talked about someone called Zaozao.
The number you dialed does not exist.
Please check it before you dial again.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'd like to go out for a walk.
Then give me a moment so I can ask for a leave from work.
Let me keep you company, alright?
No need.
Just take care of Chestnut for me.
Who are you looking for?
Is there an organization called Obsidian?
Obsidian?
I've been living here for a long time,
yet I've never heard of this organization.
You came to the wrong place.
Well,
I have one more question.
Is there a man named Ruan Lanzhu?
Ruan Lanzhu?
It doesn't ring a bell with me.
Why's everything so familiar?
Am I in the game or out of it?
Hello!
What's up?
How's it going with the Spi Realm?
The Spi Realm?
Is that a game?
What else can it be?
How come I don't remember it?
I played it here not long ago.
I'm talking about the game
whose beta version starts
with a fight against huge wolves.
Oh, that one!
People often offer
to install free beta games on my computers here
in order to collect feedback from players.
The game you're talking about is so cheesy.
The reviews about it aren't very good.
Even the game designer has given up on it.
Is the designer's surname Gao?
No.
He's a college student in America.
He hasn't graduated yet.
The game is supposed to be his graduation project.
But I doubt if it's a wise choice.
Sir, do you have new games here?
I want something exciting.
I've got tons of new games.
Pick whichever one you want.
Can't you stop playing games like this?
It's so scary that I cried last time.
Why don't you play puzzle games instead?
Yixie? Qianli?
What are the odds of seeing you here?
Don't talk nonsense.
I'm trying to win this round here.
Don't disturb me.
We...
I've been looking for you for a long time.
Do we know each other?
Of course, we do!
Didn't we used to be members of Obsidian,
and fellow door challengers?
Obsidian...
What is he talking about?
I don't know. I have no idea.
You don't know me?
Well, don't get
too obsessed with computer games.
He seems like a young man.
How come he's such a nag?
He actually looks a bit familiar to me.
Do you know him or not?
No.
Zhang Mingyu?
It's really you!
I spotted you from a distance.
Did you
go abroad?
Ah!
How did you know that?
I've just returned.
Have you got any news about Gao Dawei?
He's in Europe now.
Recently, he's been working on a big project.
I don't think he'll come back soon.
Do you know
that he's been developing a game lately?
A game?
He studied economics abroad.
Why would he develop games?
Economics?
Maybe
I'm mistaken.
Honey, what are you doing?
I'm starving.
Come back now!
Sure. Sure.
I need to go. Talk to you later!
Bye!
Let me think about what day it is, alright?
I'm gonna...
Thank you so much for the "hot balloon" tip!
You guys are the best!
I'm on the list of the top ten streamers now!
Ms. Nannan, long time no see!
Guys, today you're amazing!
Okay. I'll take these two.
Maybe I'll pick a few more.
This one looks good too.
Does it also cost 10 bucks?
Hello, Mr. Wang.
I'm not in the office now.
Do you need my help with something?
Can I hand in that file tomorrow?
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Sir, want a new cellphone screen protector?
Put one on my cellphone first.
I'm in a hurry. I need to go to work.
Alright. Chill out. I'll do it now.
Be quick!
What are you doing here?
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Why wouldn't you go home?
I'm thinking about moving out.
You should live there with your girlfriend.
Why?
I want my own place.
You're trying to bury your head in the sand again, aren't you?
You always complain about not being discovered, even though you're talented.
What you're doing now will only make you feel more isolated.
Do not bury your head in the sand.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm on a quest.
A quest for what?
The combination of virtual reality and real life.
What is that now?
The Spi Realm.
(50 years later)
Why are you still a rookie?
Do you have any problems?
If you have, let's have another round.
What problem?
Look at you. You're old.
And you're sitting in a wheelchair.
Take care of yourself.
Rookie.
Digital Technology
is more advanced than humans think.
It has been iterated so many times
since 5G was created 30 years ago.
But for me,
what I want is still the Spi Realm,
which is virtual reality technology.
Someone called it, the virtual reality,
metaverse 30 years ago.
But actually,
Qian Xuesen explained the principle
of virtual reality technology 60 years ago.
And he called this technology and research
the Spi Realm.
Wu Qi.
I finally made it.
Do you want to take a look?
Well.
No. What should I look at?
I'm taking care of my grandson.
I believe in virtual reality technology.
And I believe that there will be a world of the Spi Realm.
Everything inside
is virtual, based on reality.
And the reality can be virtualized again.
As long as we have enough data
to simulate and generate this system,
maybe it will have its own consciousness
and form a different worldview.
Including
the 12th door.
Coming.
Lingling.
Come in.
Manman, Lingling is back.
You are back.
Not funny.
What do you want to eat?
Jiushi.
Stay for dinner.
I'll cook your favorite dishes.
Hurry up. You can't catch up with me.
You should hurry up.
Why are you so bad at this?
You rookie.
Who is the rookie?
You.
I'm dying.
Lingling,
you're finally back.
I feel like
I had a long dream.
Well.
Playing a game is like
having a dream.
Long time no see.
Not long.
I'm glad you're back.
Welcome to
the world of the Spi Realm.
♫Thinking of the first time we met♫
♫We were still young♫
♫Too many memories are like movies♫
♫It makes me sink into the night breeze♫
♫If I could go back to that day♫
♫I don't want to have any change♫
♫I don't want you to laugh at me for being too serious♫
♫I don't know what to do in the story♫
♫If fate had no plan♫
♫I didn't enter this door♫
♫This story will be wonderful♫
♫And disappear from the world♫
♫One accident and another accident♫
♫Connect us♫
♫I can find another one if I miss you♫
♫I'll just be one person lost in the crowd♫
♫Sincerity is all I have♫
♫Just out of nowhere♫
♫We've been passing the seasons♫
♫One accident and another accident♫
♫Connect us♫
♫Hold on to it tightly♫
♫This fate♫
♫If I could go back to that day♫
♫I don't want to have any change♫
♫I don't want you to laugh at me for being too serious♫
♫I don't know what to do in the story♫
♫If fate had no plan♫
♫I didn't enter this door♫
♫This story will be wonderful♫
♫And disappear from the world♫
♫Hold on to it tightly♫
♫My love♫