(THE SPIREALM)
(Episode 32)
Why are you still in the mood for playing?
Don't worry.
I've memorized all the rules.
Take it.
For self-defense.
Isn't this Yan Shihe's knife?
Yes.
He carried it with him all the time.
It must be useful.
It's about time.
The tenth door is dangerous.
I'll go in first to check the situation.
You pack up your things
and bring those two kids in.
Okay.
Get up, stop playing.
Where's your bag?
I forgot my bag.
I'm leaving first, Yixie.
Hurry up and come over.
Lingling.
We don't need to introduce ourselves now?
This is the tenth door.
Surely, none of us came here on our own.
So there's no need for self-introductions.
Okay.
Got it.
Hello.
What took you so long?
Waiting for him.
What's going on?
There are quite a few people here.
It seems like there are many rookies.
Using rookies as cannon fodder
might work in other doors,
but in this one,
it will backfire.
There are actually 18 people.
That woman looks quite familiar.
Xia?
It's her.
You know her?
The last time I passed the tenth door,
it was very challenging.
In the end,
only a woman and I came out,
and that woman was her.
Looks like we've encountered
a rival this time.
I heard a woman crying.
It has begun.
Is it the Box Demon?
Probably.
Her voice
is on this floor.
Let's go to the second floor and take a look.
Let's go.
I didn't expect to see you inside the door.
Last time when I was passing the door,
how come I didn't know
you were the boss of the Obsidian?
There are a lot of things
that you haven't noticed.
Young man, calm down.
I know you blame us for the death
of the boss of the White Deer.
Anyway, now we're inside the same door.
I'm ready
for whatever you want.
You're in such a hurry to come here and make a fuss
before finding the door and the key?
Both of them will be ours anyway.
The person who lost to me last time seems quite confident this time.
We'll see.
I'll be watching you.
The next door for that woman
is the 11th one.
She's back here now
for the clues to it.
Ruan.
She seems quite formidable.
She is.
Don't be afraid.
Opening the first box
requires luck.
So, we're all on the same starting line,
right?
I remember this.
The Box Demon can only use skills once a day.
Before using the skill,
the compass will rotate,
like winding up a spring,
right?
Not bad.
You remembered everything.
Of course, I can remember such important things.
Lingling, don't forget to keep listening.
Let's go.
Don't touch it.
I was not opening a box.
This is more important than the boxes.
This must be the safe.
The key must be inside.
Someone is screaming.
Looks like these rookies are opening the boxes blindly.
Should we remind them?
Let's go. Let's play it by ear.
(Stethoscope. Note: The stethoscope can pick up the sound of the Box Demon or a Box Slave)
You're quite lucky.
You unpacked a prop the first time you tried it.
Really?
What is this prop for?
I told you not to say too much.
Who was screaming just now?
It was me.
My name is Tian Guxue.
I just saw him opening this box,
and I didn't know what was inside.
I got scared
and screamed.
Are you a newcomer?
I brought her in.
I'm Sun Yuanzhou.
This is my tenth door.
They're all my friends.
While some are indeed newcomers,
don't worry,
they are not cannon fodder.
Why are you looking at me?
Everyone I brought in is my friend.
Don't open the boxes casually.
These boxes are everywhere.
They must serve special functions.
It's risky to open them recklessly.
What could go wrong?
I'm perfectly fine, aren't I?
Can you control
the people you brought in?
He just got here today
and is not familiar with the situation.
Ji,
don't open boxes casually anymore.
If something goes wrong,
it'll be too late.
The higher the risk,
the bigger the benefit.
How dare he open another box?
What is this?
If I'm not mistaken,
this should be the mouth of the Box Demon.
Oh.
Inside this door,
it should be a board game
called "Box Demon."
Don't open boxes like this anymore.
You might unpack terrible things.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
My mouth
wasn't as fast as your hands.
In other words, inside this door
is a live-action board game.
Have you ever played this game?
At first, I wasn't sure,
so I went upstairs to check.
Now I'm sure.
Inside these boxes in front of us,
there are props and the Box Demon.
If you get a prop,
you can use it against the Box Demon.
If you get a Box Demon...
more precisely,
one of the ten parts of the Box Demon:
the eyes, ears, mouth, nose, head,
left hand, right hand, left foot, right foot,
and torso.
If you get one of her organs,
it will trigger a certain ability of hers.
If you get her hair,
you will die immediately, turn into a Box Slave,
and become an accomplice of the Box Demon.
If we get her entire body,
we will all die.
Well...
according to you,
if we don't open the boxes,
nothing will happen to us.
Then we'll be rejecting the game.
What I just mentioned
are the rules of the board game outside the door.
As for the rules of the game inside the door,
there must be some changes.
However, I still don't know
what these changes are.
But you've unpacked
the mouth,
so now the Box Demon can lie.
Lie?
The Box Demon can speak?
In the board game outside the door, the Box Demon was played by a person.
Of course, it can speak.
As for inside the door...
I guess it can also speak.
Did you notice
the strange howling
when we just entered the door?
Please, do not open any more boxes, okay?
I didn't know that.
How many boxes
are there in this room?
Let's count them together, shall we?
My name is Yin Xinyi.
I'm passing the door on my own.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Zhu Meng.
You may look young, but you appear to be meticulous
and quite experienced.
I was forced into this state by this stupid game.
Now that everyone knows this is a board game,
let's not randomly touch these boxes anymore.
It's late today.
Everyone, go and have a rest.
What about this mouth?
Since no one wants it,
I'll take it.
(A lying)
(Mouth)
I've checked this villa just now.
The first floor has a hall and a restroom,
and the second floor has a dining room and bedrooms.
You can assign them yourselves.
It's better not to sleep alone
so that you can take care of each other in case something happens.
Sun,
can I have a room to myself?
I'm a bit of a neat freak.
You want to live alone?
Aren't you afraid?
I am.
That's why I won't sleep tonight.
I need to clean the room thoroughly tonight.
Then be careful on your own.
Okay.
Oh my. There are boxes everywhere.
I have to resist the urge
to touch them.
There are over two hundred boxes in total.
If none of us opens them,
what will happen?
There must be restrictions inside the door.
It won't allow us to exploit such a basic loophole.
And, uh...
what's the use of
that stethoscope earlier?
Outside the door, we've played many times.
Why can't you remember the rules?
If the Box Demon is in the box we're about to open,
the stethoscope can help us hear its sound.
Oh.
It's quite useful.
If only we had it in our hands.
Can we take it and use it?
I don't think so.
In the board game,
only the one who unpacked it can use it.
It really is a luck-based game.
But there's one thing very strange.
If this is a game,
there should be a rulebook.
But so far,
no one has mentioned it.
I don't know
if it truly doesn't exist
or if someone has hidden it.
I think
someone has hidden it.
This person doesn't want us to know the rules of the game.
Fortunately, we had the note before coming.
Otherwise, we would still know nothing.
The key is in the floor clock.
We must find out the password as soon as possible.
As for the door,
it should be inside one of the boxes.
We have to open more boxes to find it.
Don't be afraid.
We are lucky.
Ji has already started well for us.
Something happened.
Let's go out and take a look.
Get up. Something happened.
Get up.
No one would think they've lived too long
and open the box secretly, right?
Newcomers can be troublesome
because of their uncertainty.
No one knows
what they'll do.
It's locked!
I'll go find the tools.
Let me do it.
Help me!
I don't want to die!
The upper bunk is clean,
and the lower bunk is messy.
It means two people lived there.
They were gone.
They got hair.
Your people lived here, right?
Yes.
I told you to take care of your men.
They are adults.
No one can stop them from opening the box.
You just want the newcomers to be the cannon fodder.
Now there are two more box slaves.
It's harder to open the box.
Can you guarantee
that no one will die if we don't open the box?
You won't take advantage of this game.
Some people know the rules,
but they don't tell us.
Sooner or later,
you'll be others' cannon fodder.
It's true that showing off your strength will attract attention.
Go back.
We'll talk about it tomorrow.
Let's go.
We told them
not to open the box,
why didn't they listen?
That woman did it on purpose.
She just wanted them to try and make mistakes.
Now you know the consequences of opening the box indiscriminately.
Brother, don't worry.
Without your permission,
I will never open the box.
I want to go to the lavatory.
I'll go with you.
Lingling.
What's wrong, Zhu Meng?
Didn't you bring tissues?
Help me, Lingling.
What's wrong?
I'm locked in the box.
Lingling.
Help me!
Zhu Meng.
Lingling.
Help me!
Help me.
What's wrong?
What's wrong, Zhu Meng?
Wait for me.
Lingling, hurry up.
I can't hold on any longer.
Help me, Lingling.
Lingling.
Zhu Meng!
What are you doing?
The mouth.
Do you still have the Box Demon's mouth?
No.
Something happened?
Yes.
The skill of Box Demon's mouth
is not to lie,
but to use your voice.
He just called for help from inside the box
to lure me to open the box.
You mean
you heard me calling for help inside the box?
Yes.
Where did you hear me calling just now?
Over there.
The second room.
There is indeed a box.
She is most likely inside.
Well,
let's confirm her location with Ji.
If it's confirmed,
it'll be safer
to open the other boxes.
Okay.
You mean the Box Demon used the skill of mouth to you?
That means
the mouth will disappear after being used.
And the Box Demon can only use its skills once a day.
At least tonight,
no one will be killed.
And according to your deduction,
the stethoscope can determine
whether there is a box monster in the box.
Since the stethoscope is so useful,
just listen to the boxes one by one.
There are limits to using props.
Maybe it's a limit on the number of uses.
Maybe it's a time limit.
You can find a box and have a try.
It has sound.
It really works.
I knew it.
Only the person who got the prop
can use it.
There's no sound in this box.
But
I'm a little scared.
Why don't you open it?
Okay,
but who owns the prop?
Of course, it belongs to us.
The stethoscope is not free.
There's no such good thing.
I take the risk,
and you get the benefits.
I'll do it.
The box is empty.
Come with me to the lavatory.
I'm afraid it's inappropriate.
If we miss this chance,
it'll be hard to know where the Box Demon is.
We'll go too.
This is it.
Try using the stethoscope.
There's a child crying.
Let me use it.
Did you hear anything?
The Box Demon is inside.
She can't move
until her feet are opened.
If you open the key prop,
you can try it on her.
Ji,
your stethoscope
can be used at least three times a day.
If there is a chance,
try if it can be used for the fourth time.
I'm just lucky.
Ji is always lucky.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have taken him to pass the door.
But
it seems that you're not that lucky.
And we won't let you
use our stethoscope.
Ji, let's go.
Don't let them steal the stethoscope.
They can't use it even if they steal it.
Even if they can't use it,
we will throw it away or destroy it.
You're so thoughtful, Xia.
It's not that I'm thoughtful,
but I know them too well.
Let's go somewhere else.
I don't know
if the stethoscope has any special function.
If it simply amplifies the sound,
then we have
a better one here, right?
There should be other restrictions.
Otherwise, if I can hear everything,
why do we need props?
Shall we try?
There really is a little girl crying.
Ah?
You can really hear it.
Oh my god.
So we can hear the sounds
in all the boxes?
You wish!
Lingling's hearing must also be limited.
How?
Let me try again.
How is it?
There's no sound in this box.
Then it's empty.
What did I say?
Oh.
You told me not to open the box casually.
Let me do it.
It's really empty.
Let me try again.
Stop trying.
I'm afraid you will be in danger.
It's okay.
You won't know until you try.
What's wrong?
Lingling, what's wrong?
I'm fine.
I didn't hear anything.
I just feel like
my eardrums are going to burst.
This...
It seems that
cheating also has a limit on the number of times
just like the stethoscope.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
It's open!
What?
The door is open.
Oh.
Someone is really here.
What are they doing?
The time of the floor clock
is the password for the safe.
They're guessing the time and trying the password.
Is it going to work?
If they insist on trying,
they can succeed.
It's a four-digit number.
There were originally 10,000 possibilities.
But it's a watch password,
so there are only 720 combinations.
If they try once for five seconds,
they will use 3,600 seconds.
They will spend an hour
trying out the password.
And it is the most unlucky situation.
Normally, it will be faster.
No one will try all the numbers
from the beginning to the end,
unless they are really unlucky.
So difficult?
Well,
it's useless for us to get the digital password.
Be quiet.
Hey.
Stop trying.
There won't be such a big loophole in the door.
Don't talk nonsense.
Who are you trying to scare?
It's normal
to try the password for the safe.
Are you jealous?
This is the benefit of having more people.
There is strength in numbers.
What's wrong?
Don't go.
I feel something is wrong.
It's open.
Ah?
It's open?
Didn't you say they would spend an hour?
Besides, how could they cheat?
Oh my god.
If the password is wrong,
the safe is also a box,
and it will swallow people?
Three more Box Slaves
on the first day.
They had no sense of respect
and thought they were the protagonists.
In fact, they are just someone else's cannon fodder.
(Password box) (Hint: The key is in the box.)
Wow.
The treatment is so good this time.
The midnight snacks are so abundant.
Why don't you eat?
I can't.
What?
It really can't be eaten.
I'm not hungry.
You have to eat.
Why are you all looking at me like that?
The food is poisonous.
If we can't eat it,
can we share the food?
Ji, feed him.
What?
We can't eat it,
and only you can touch the food.
We're testing this right now.
Hurry up, feed me.
See if you can share it with me.
Can I feed someone else?
Why are you so nosy?
Feed me. Hurry up.
Hurry up.
I can't pass it.
I can't reach it either.
If we want to eat, we have to open the box.
I told you there must be a time limit.
The taboo condition for this door is to open the box.
This is to avoid the possibility that
if we don't proactively open the box,
the box demon will not be able to take action against us.
Now it seems that this road is blocked.
If we don't open the boxes, we'll starve to death.
I'm not hungry, but I have to eat something.
Help yourselves.
I'll just starve.
At this time,
you should know
that this is a team game.
We must work together,
otherwise, we'll all die inside the door.
How can we cooperate?
By sharing the information.
Of course, we won't force you to open the box.
You can starve to death if you like to.
But you have to put stickers on the boxes you've opened
to avoid repeated opening
and write what's in the boxes on the stickers.
What?
What's the use of stickers?
Every night after midnight,
everything in the box will be reset.
The stickers are useless.
The things will be reset.
But no props will show up
in the empty boxes that have been opened.
And the hair of the Box Demon
and the Box Slaves transformed by the Box Demon
will randomly show up
in all empty boxes.
So opening an empty box that has been opened once again
only carries risks and no profits.
So the later we open the boxes,
the more dangerous it is.
So we need to
open all the boxes as soon as possible
and find a tool to subdue the Box Demon.
But what if someone deliberately hides it?
Then kick him out of this alliance.
The Box Demon is already troublesome enough.
We can't engage in infighting anymore.
It is dangerous to open the box.
The more people die,
the more box slaves there will be.
But there are profits in risks.
We can't get out of this door
unless we open the box and get the tool to kill the Box Demon
or the password for the safe.
Zhu Meng, you've played this game.
I want to know if the Box Demon can enter the box
that has been opened.
Of course.
She will be able to move
as long as the box with her feet is opened.
She can go anywhere.
Did you hear that?
When we open the box later,
at least two people should work together.
If anything happens,
we can record it.
Any questions?
All the content was told to us by him.
So if he wants to deceive us,
we don't know.
You don't have to believe me.
I don't mind.
If you have any other information,
I don't mind either.
So, we can check the situation
at any time, right?
Yes.
But equally, we also need to check
the box you opened.
Okay, we can cooperate.
But I reserve the right to stop it at any time.
Whatever.
We might be the ones to end cooperation first.
I'll share the stickers with you.
If you find any important props
or the Box Demon's skills,
make sure to speak up. Don't keep it a secret.
From now on, let's exchange information
here every day at noon.
We won't eat today.
We'll wait until Lingling finishes listening to and opening the box tomorrow
before having a meal.
It's okay to starve for one day.
If the box is opened incorrectly,
our lives might be at risk.
Hang in there.
This door is really unfriendly to newbies.
Indeed.
Hopefully, the newbies
won't impulsively open the box.
Otherwise, it will be even more challenging.
Xia will definitely take action.
Let's be careful.
At this point,
does she still have a way not to open the box?
I'm just hungry.
I can endure it.
I'm fine too.
I can endure hunger.
Hang in there. We'll eat tomorrow morning.
I might even eat the plate by tomorrow morning.
Bro, go to sleep.
If you don't sleep now, hunger might keep you awake.
Go to sleep.
In your dreams, you can dream about anything.
Take it. You get one, I get one.
Just one piece?
Yes, so we'll have to let them go hungry.
Thank you.
Is it sweet?
Yes.
What about you?
I also think it's sweet.
Xia, I want to go out.
I don't want to open the box.
I want to leave. I want to live.
It's useless. You can't get out.
But you clearly said you would protect us past the door.
Must I fulfill every promise I make?
I've made too many.
You'll have to wait in line.
You'd better calm down.
Are you trying to use us as cannon fodder?
Not you all, just you.
I've brought many people through the door.
Surely there will be classifications.
You just play your role as cannon fodder.
After passing the door,
I can arrange a decent farewell ceremony for you.
Xia, why did you bring me to the study?
It's past midnight,
the stethoscope can be used.
I need to find a box.
Wait, I...
I just heard you arguing,
and saw you meeting a mysterious man.
You must have some plans,
and I want to know.
I don't want to be cannon fodder.
You're indeed smarter than I thought.
Let me tell you,
I have the note for this door,
and I know the rules for all the games.
If you want to live, do as I say.
Then why did you listen to Zhu Meng?
Pushing him to the front, so that I can shift everyone's attention.
It's easier for me to do things in the shadows.
There's no movement here.
Really.
If you don't open it, I'll open it.
After I open it, don't come looking for me.
Can the stethoscope hear if there are any props?
The stethoscope can only detect whether there is sound or not,
avoiding the Box Demon.
What are you looking for?
A comb that can kill the Box Demon.
If we find it,
we'll be invincible.
What are you doing?
Lingling, let's open the box.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
Zhu Meng didn't allow me to wake you up.
Let's go.
Okay.
This one is silent.
This one is empty.
(Opened, empty)