Lingfeng,
I can give you
the power
and wealth of the world.
But why do you
go against me?
Are you like your brother,
being enchanted by a woman,
and forgetting your last name?
Is that so?
Father,
brother,
do you really think I don't know
what happened eight years ago?
I didn't expect
the misunderstanding between us
to be so deep.
Fine,
it's time to tell you the truth.
You
are not an adopted child.
You are the flesh and blood
of me and the Queen Mother.
Back then,
I was a horse washer
at the royal stables.
He,
Xie Zhicang,
was just a military officer.
I gave my heart to him,
and we pledged our lives to each other.
But he,
when he learned the late Emperor
took notice of me because
I resembled the late Empress,
for the sake of power,
he offered me to the late Emperor.
And at that time,
I was already pregnant.
Not long after she gave birth to you,
relying on
her resemblance to the late Empress,
[while I was away at the border,]
[she seduced the late Emperor.]
[To avoid future troubles,]
[she cruelly ordered the nanny]
[to dispose of you.]
[I had intended]
[to secretly give you away,]
[hoping you]
[could grow up in the civilian world.]
[But years later,]
[Xie Zhicang]
threatened me
with this painting
and the news of his son
to pave his way to power.
Fortunately, the nanny was kind-hearted
and placed you in a monastery.
Eight years ago,
the Queen Mother learned of this.
Fearful of exposure,
she sent assassins
to silence you and the monks.
I arrived in time
to save you from the assassins
and brought you back to the Xie family,
raising you with all my care.
What about those 300 soldiers?
And the monks in the temple?
They were innocent.
It was their misfortune
to have encountered
the assassins sent by the Queen Mother.
I couldn't risk
leak this information.
Otherwise,
if the late Emperor finds out,
how could my son
survive in this world?
But I was wrong.
The late Emperor
entrusted me to assist the young Emperor
and protect the empire.
But Xie Zhicang harbors treacherous ambitions
and seeks to overthrow the empire.
Over the years,
I've endured and retreated,
hoping
to bring about a moment of peace
and stability to the empire.
However,
this constant retreat
has not only fueled his power,
but also sown the seeds of disaster.
Now,
with the young emperor weak and the court depleted,
It's the time to change the emperor.
Lingfeng,
you are
the royal blood,
and you have the ambition to rule the country.
I'm willing to clear the way for you,
and put you on the throne,
on the top of all the people.
What do you think?
Your Highness,
everything is ready.
Tomorrow is your brother's big day.
I will give him a grand
and proper farewell.
After his burial,
we'll have a heart-to-heart talk.
Until then,
stay here.
Think everything
through.
Your Majesty,
Xie Zhicang is using the orphan of a loyalist
using the last of the loyalists as bait.
I implore Your Majesty to intervene
and save them.
And also save
the precarious state of the empire.
But...
I...
I am powerless to help.
Your Majesty,
you are the mother of the empire.
How can you just stand by
and watch the loyal and righteous die,
while the treacherous run rampant?
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your wisdom.
You sent the message in time.
Your Majesty,
my son thought of you until his last breath.
His journey to the underworld
must be lonely.
It's just right
for you to perform the ghost wedding,
and be buried with him.
Take her!
Yes!
Your Majesty!
- Let me go! - Go!
Your Majesty,
please save them!
I've decided to
Huaiyun should be given a grand burial
with the honors due to a prince.
At that time,
Your Majesty and Your Highness
should preside over it in person
to show the grace of heaven.
[The blood flowing in your veins]
[is indeed royal blood.]
[Little slave,]
[do you miss me?]
[I'll make you the emperor,]
[standing above all.]
[From now on,]
[I'm the master,]
[and you're the slave.]
[Your life is mine,]
[not the God's.]
[An Rao was captured.]
She'll be sacrificed in a ghost marriage.
[Xie Huaiyun, son of the late Prince of Lin'an,]
[a member of the royal family,]
[a descendant of the imperial clan.]
[I sympathize with the Prince of Lin'an's loss of his son,]
[and posthumously grant you the title of Duke,]
[with a royal tomb.]
[In recognition of your youth and talent,]
[and in mourning for your lonely spirit,]
[I specially select a virtuous girl]
[to be your ghost bride.]
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Please, father of the bride, drink the wedding wine
to celebrate this perfect union.
My son,
I won't let any of those who harmed you
get away with it.
Since this girl meets your approval,
let her join you in the afterlife
and serve as your slave.
Let her atone for all eternity.
The time has come.
I'll personally see you off.
[Qi turbulence,]
[meridian entanglement.]
[How could this be?]
It's you!
You poisoned my wine!
Protect the Queen!
Quick, protect the Queen!
You...
Are you human or ghost?
Human,
but a ghost that will take your life.
I urge you to purge the court,
and bring peace to the nation.
Do you think I haven't considered it?
But Xie Zhicang
is deeply rooted.
One move could shake the whole.
I must consider the Emperor
and the nation.
If so,
I'll have to
try another approach.
What do you want?
To convince you.
Anrao would beg you,
but I won't.
You have two choices:
either
cooperate with me to kill Xie Zhicang,
or
die.
This painting is so brilliant.
If it spreads among the people,
the Queen Mother can only
choose death as an apology.
Even if I agree,
it must be planned carefully.
He is a powerful official.
He can't be killed at will.
If Xie Zhicang is found guilty,
the entire Xie family will be in danger,
including Xie Lingfeng.
It's precisely because his martial arts
and power are so formidable
ordinary methods can't deal with him.
Fortunately,
I'm a madman who doesn't care about his life.
That's why
the Queen Mother can get rid of him.
I just need you to do one thing.
At the funeral,
hand him a cup of wine for me.
I'll take responsibility
for all the blood debts.
Xie Zhicang,
today is your day of death!
Do you remember Su Heng,
who served you loyally eight years ago?
When you ordered his death,
did you ever imagine
that you would meet the same fate?
Su Heng?
He was nothing but an ant!
I, Xie Zhicang,
never remember the names of the dead!
Mu Qing,
take the sword.
Today,
you'll pay with your life.
Go and
kowtow to the ghosts
you wronged.
Luo Yao,
if you hurt me,
the Xie Family Army
will tear you apart.
Lingfeng,
kill her!
Turn your head,
don't look!
You traitor!
My great cause...
Prince of Lin'an is dead.
Brother,
soldiers,
did you see that?
I finally killed my enemy
and avenged you all!
The Jiu Yao Faction
assassinated the Prince of Lin'an.
They will be immediately arrested
and executed on a later date
to demonstrate the divine authority!