[Extremely Perilous Love]
[Episode 22]
[Don't Dream Of Marrying Her]
Stop struggling.
The Soft Bone Powder
is extremely powerful,
and not easily cured
by ordinary antidotes.
Gu Shengming.
All of this today
was planned by you.
It's like the story of the
snipe and the clam competing,
while the fisherman benefits.
Blame yourself
for always looking down on me.
What exactly do you want?
As long as you spare Yin,
I can fulfill any of your desires.
I will obtain whatever I want on my own.
Let me personally take my bride away.
I don't want to trouble you, Shenghan.
Save your strength for later.
You still have to officiate our wedding.
♪Two swallows build nests on the beam♪
♪Carrying fresh mud in their beaks♪
♪Gazing into the distance,
the path is filled with thriving grass♪
♪The beautiful scene
feels undeserved by you♪
♪The night wind suddenly rises♪
♪Ruffling the rippling pool water♪
♪The full moon is what I fear the most♪
♪Similar smiles♪
♪Conceal varying degrees of familiarity♪
♪Emotions overflow deeply;
how much do you know♪
[General's Manor]
♪May you never leave♪
[Happy Wedding]
♪How easily we part, unbeknownst to us♪
Gu Shenghan.
Gu Shengming.
Don't even dream of marry her.
You've always been so domineering.
You won't spare even my bride.
But today,
I'm afraid you won't
have a say in the matter.
Shenghan!
You better cooperate with me
and complete the wedding.
He will naturally feel better afterward.
Gu Shengming.
Is this all you've got?
♪Our paths crossed, but we
misread the profound meaning of destiny♪
♪Hand in hand, we've weathered
storms, fortunate to have each other♪
Don't!
♪I offer you a branch of jasmine♪
I will marry.
♪How easily we part, unbeknownst to us♪
♪When we meet, there is
no predetermined time to return♪
♪ I see you, why aren't you happy♪
I will marry.
I will marry you.
Yin.
No, Yin.
I just hope that
you can take over the role
of our ailing grandmother
and officiate the wedding.
You'll witness
the ceremony in that state.
Shengming.
How could you treat
your own brother like this?
You are simply
disrespectful to your elders.
You are committing a grave offense.
A grave offense?
I have committed a grave offense?
Why is it that he
can be forgiven for any misdeeds
he had done from childhood to adulthood,
while I have to endure
and tolerate everything?
It's all because he is
the esteemed legitimate son,
and I am just a poor illegitimate child.
This is unfair.
How did you end up like this?
It's all because of your pressure.
I don't want to compromise
under the shadow of Gu Shenghan.
I want to have all of him.
How could there be
such a beast in our family?
I spare you because you are an elder.
You won't witness a bloody scene.
Now, go and rest.
You.
Take Old Madam down.
And take good care of her.
The wedding will continue.
[Harmonious Climate]
I'm going to kill you
and avenge my father.
You've been acting all along.
I married you
just for this moment.
You...
Luckily, I was prepared early on.
Want to kill me?
It's not that simple.
If you don't behave,
he will be the one suffering.
I...
I promise you.
As long as you don't kill him,
I'll do anything you want.
♪Once merely a speck of cosmic dust♪
♪Ensnared in folly's fervent lust♪
My wife.
♪If life's illusions♪
We've paid our
respects to the ancestors.
We've exchanged wedding cups.
What should we do next?
♪The withered grass leaves no trace♪
Let's do something exciting.
♪The unresolved hatred♪
♪Carved another inch into the bone♪
♪If there were never deep feelings♪
[Harmonious Climate]
♪Missed in a fleeting glance♪
♪The original person♪
♪Thoughts of you entered my dreams♪
This is our wedding night.
Why not have idle onlookers leave?
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪
How could Gu Shenghan
be considered as an idle onlooker?
He's the witness of our love.
Gu Shengming.
You better kill me.
How could I let you off so easily?
I want you to
witness with your own eyes.
Your woman,
your power,
your dignity.
Everything of yours belongs to me.
♪Let me be soaked
in snow for a hundred years♪
Gu Shengming.
I didn't expect you to be so insane.
This is just the beginning.
Remember.
No matter who among you dies,
I will make sure the other one
suffers a fate worse than death.
What's wrong, Shenghan?
How does the poison that
I specially prepared for you?
This poison acts up every other hour.
It feels like
the sensation of hundreds of insects
crawling and scratching your body.
You'll be begging for death
but you are unable to die.
Do you want to save him?
Please me with your body.
Take it off.
Alright.
I will satisfy you.
No way!
Come at me!
Yin is innocent.
I like her so much, but she likes you.
How could she be innocent?
What do I need to do
so you can spare her?
You want me to let her go?
♪If life's illusions♪
Beg me.
♪Were encased
within the circles of time♪
♪Lingering desires awaken anew♪
♪With a fervent kiss♪
♪The withered grass leaves no trace♪
♪Buried a lifetime♪
Alright.
I beg you.
Please.
♪Carved another inch into the bone♪
I beg you to let go of her.
♪If there were never deep feelings♪
Let go of her.
♪Missed in a fleeting glance♪
♪The original person♪
Is that how you beg?
♪Thoughts of you entered my dreams♪
♪No one to share the same pillow♪
♪Forgetting everything♪
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪
♪Let me be soaked
in snow for a hundred years♪
Kneel.
♪Turning away,
rushing towards the next life♪
♪If fortunate enough
to grow old with you♪
♪How long is destiny
going to keep this promise♪
♪Missing and calling out for you♪
♪No one to share the same pillow♪
♪Forgetting everything♪
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪
I, an inferior person,
is willing to bow down and surrender.
I only ask for you
to show mercy, young master.
Spare her.
♪If fortunate enough
to grow old with you♪
♪How long is destiny
going to keep this promise♪
Starting from today,
I, Gu Shenghan, appoint
Gu Shengming as the Northern General.
All staff on the viewing platform
will listen to
Gu Shengming's arrangements.
No one shall disobey the orders.
Shenghan.
Look at my handwriting.
Doesn't it look the same as yours?
Finally.
You have to bow down and surrender to me.
Release Gu Shenghan.
I'll help you find the tiger token.
♪Fine rain infiltrates
the deep night, awakening the jasmine♪
♪Two swallows build nests on the beam♪
♪Carrying fresh mud in their beaks♪
♪Gazing into the distance,
the path is filled with thriving grass♪
♪The beautiful scene
feels undeserved by you♪
♪The night wind suddenly rises♪
♪Ruffling the rippling pool water♪
♪The full moon is what I fear the most♪
♪Similar smiles♪
♪Conceal varying degrees of familiarity♪
♪Emotions overflow
deeply; how much do you know♪
♪I offer you a branch of jasmine♪
♪May you never leave;
we rely on each other from dawn to dusk♪
♪How easily we part, unbeknownst to us♪
♪When we meet, there is
no predetermined time to return♪