[Extremely Perilous Love]
[Episode 12]
[The Deadly Scheme]
The key is hidden so discreetly.
It must unlock something important.
She took the key to the token.
But if I had the key
and stole the token,
could it harm Gu Shenghan?
Why do I still sympathize with him?
Shenghan.
You lost.
According to our childhood rules,
the loser has to fulfill a request.
What do you want?
The Northern General's Manor is yours.
Power and wealth mean nothing to me.
All I want
is Xu Yin.
So you know her identity.
I underestimated you.
I was just suspicious before,
but now I'm sure.
You're nothing
but her father's murderer.
If you're to keep
someone who wants to kill you
by your side，
why not leave her to me?
I can offer her
the love you can't give.
Shut up!
You're beyond measure.
Stop it!
Are you alright?
Qingqing, I'm fine.
Shenghan didn't mean it.
Gu Shenghan.
Why are you so heartless
to your own brother?
I may be cruel,
but it's better than
the deceitful love of a spouse.
You're hopeless.
I'll help you back to check.
Don't think I don't know what you did.
You must be thrilled now.
I did what I had to do.
You're so naive.
You're being manipulated repeatedly
but remain completely unaware.
♪Once merely a speck of cosmic dust♪
Qingqing.
Stay with Shenghan.
Don't make him angry again.
♪If life's illusions♪
♪Were encased
within the circles of time♪
♪Lingering desires awaken anew♪
Your brother is too precious for me
to take care of him.
Let's go.
Madam.
The Old Madam requests your presence
in the front hall.
Grandmother wants to see me?
Can I treat Shengming's wound
before going there?
There's someone to attend
to the Second Young Master's injury.
No need for Madam to do it personally.
Please go ahead.
I'll accompany you.
♪Knocking on the door of my heart♪
♪Missed in a fleeting glance♪
♪The original person♪
♪Thoughts of you entered my dreams♪
♪No one to share the same pillow♪
♪Forgetting everything♪
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪
♪Let me be soaked
in snow for a hundred years♪
♪Turning away,
rushing towards the next life♪
Greetings, Grandmother.
Since you're injured,
you should rest in your room.
I am feeling better now.
Why did you summon me, Grandmother?
Now that you've married
into the General's Manor,
you must abide by the rules
of the Gu family,
regardless of your past conduct.
If not, you'll face
the same consequences as before.
Punishment awaits.
Last time, you accused me
of plotting against the General
and the family rules
were employed recklessly.
What have I done this time
to violate the family rules?
Exceeding
the boundaries with brother-in-law
is sufficient grounds for punishment.
What...
Grandmother.
Qingqing is not
well-versed in family rules
and has not learned
proper female virtues.
I am willing to go to
the ancestral hall to transcribe
as a way to apologize.
Please forgive me.
Since you sincerely want to amend,
kowtow before the ancestral tablets,
making thousands of bows,
and pray earnestly
for their blessings.
Grandmother, you...
Silence!
There's nothing between me and Qingqing.
We just share common interests.
Silence!
If you genuinely
want to protect her, then do nothing.
She belongs to your brother.
I'll arrange a marriage for you soon.
Settle down and behave.
Why does everything
favor Gu Shenghan?
Yet I have to endure
and accept all the arrangements.
She belongs to you,
and so does the tiger token.
No.
I can't accept that.
Madam.
When you finish kowtowing 1,000 times,
you can leave.
So, this is the ancestral hall
of the Northern General's Manor.
There's a faint scent
of incense on the key.
Year-round, only the ancestral
hall has continuous incense burning
and is located in a remote area.
The token may be hidden here.
Shengming, what brings you here?
Grandmother is resting.
I brought you some food.
There's only this left in the kitchen.
Please bear with it for now.
I'll get you some good dishes tomorrow.
This is good enough.
Thank you.
You never have to
be polite to me.
I was too presumptuous.
I was often reprimanded by Grandmother
and locked in this ancestral hall.
Perhaps
this is the trouble
of being born into a prominent family,
often restricted
by rules and traditions.
So, the days in
the thatched hut three years ago
were the most carefree days
I've ever had.
Are you thinking of the thatched hut?
Yin.
I've never forgotten this name.
The girl I deeply loved
in the thatched hut.
I have more important things
to take care of now.
Let's treat
what happened three years ago
as beautiful memories.
You've always kept her in your thoughts.
Yin is truly fortunate.
Why doesn't this trick work on her?
Did she discover my pretense?
General.
Second Young Master
just left food for Madam.
This woman.
She can't behave
even in the ancestral hall.
I fear she has ulterior motives
for visiting the ancestral hall.
How could I not know her little schemes?
[Viewing Platform]
Pass token for the viewing platform.
Finally, I found it.
General, what brings you here?
The ancestral hall is so quiet.
I thought you
would be hungry and cold here.
I worried too much.
Shengming sent these snacks over.
Don't forget that you ended up here
because of him.
It seems that family rules
can't make you learn your lesson.
I came to
the ancestral hall voluntarily.
It's peaceful here,
much better than
the chaotic surrounding outside.
It looks like someone isn't sincere,
falsely claiming
to be copying scriptures
but meddling with things they shouldn't.
You will believe me
if I risk my life to save you.
I'll be your hero.
I thought this old incense burner
might need some tidying up.
General, why do you care
so much about this incense burner?
Is there anything special?
There's nothing special about it.
No matter
how much effort you put into it,
it won't make any difference.
Don't worry, Yin.
This is just a bit of smoke.
I'll save you soon.
It's on fire!
The door is locked.
How did it suddenly catch fire?
Qingqing.
Are you inside?
Shengming, I'm inside.
And...
You hold on.
I'll come to rescue you now.
It's on fire!
Servants must be outside
trying to extinguish the fire.
Push me out later.
Remember,
you must keep the fact
that my leg is not lame a secret.
General, you are indeed cautious.
Even in such a dangerous situation,
you are still skilled in scheming.
♪Drowning in a whispered tale♪
♪Disturbing a dream♪
Water is here!
♪Once merely a speck of cosmic dust♪
This way!
Hurry, there's no water left!
Step aside!
♪If life's illusions♪
Yin!
Hurry!
Quickly!
Get more people to come!
Hurry!
♪The withered grass leaves no trace♪
♪Buried a lifetime♪
♪The unresolved hatred♪
♪Carved another inch into the bone♪
♪If there were never deep feelings♪
♪Knocking on the door of my heart♪
♪Missed in a fleeting glance♪
♪The original person♪
♪Thoughts of you entered my dreams♪
♪No one to share the same pillow♪
♪Forgetting everything♪
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪
♪Let me be soaked
in snow for a hundred years♪
♪Turning away,
rushing towards the next life♪
♪If fortunate enough
to grow old with you♪
♪How long is destiny
going to keep this promise♪
♪The withered grass leaves no trace♪
♪Buried a lifetime♪
♪The unresolved hatred♪
♪Carved another inch into the bone♪
♪If there were never deep feelings♪
♪Knocking on the door of my heart♪
♪Missed in a fleeting glance♪
♪The original person♪
♪Thoughts of you entered my dreams♪
♪No one to share the same pillow♪
♪Forgetting everything♪
♪Cruel are the mottled years of time♪