Father! Father!
Episode 25
Father. Pull yourself together! I said pull yourself together!
Do Chan.
I get to call my son's name before I die.
What are you talking about? Who's dying? Get up!
You brat. Your heart beats fast as it always has.
A scammer's heart should beat slowly.
The biggest con in the world is to
win one person's heart completely.
Please, just like that,
live a normal life while having a fun with a girl.
Son.
I'm sorry.
Father. Father.
Father!
Father.
Sa Do Chan. What? Do you come here for, revenge?
You devil bastard!
So? Are you going to kill me?
I was getting along with your father at first
as an ambitious detective and a splendid scammer.
We conned here and there to achieve everything we wanted.
But he began to block my path at some point and started to bother me.
So I got rid of him.
Why? Do I need to explain more?
I won't forgive you forever.
I will return you your father's fake hand.
Why?
Your heart can't beat slowly anymore?
That's what your father Sa Ma Cheon used to say all the time.
"A scammer's heart beats slowly."
Do you want to kill me?
Does your heart feel like exploding out of anger?
Do you want to get revenge on me for your father?
Sa, Sa Do Chan.
You...
CEO.
Sa Do Chan.  Stop there. Run slowly.
Sa Do Chan.
Switch
Anger makes your heart beat faster.
Give out all the information on the case to reporters.
Saying that Victor Jang and Sa Ma Cheon beat each other to death after their scams were revealed.
And scammer Sa Do Chan misunderstood me and assaulted me last night.
He tried to kill me but ran away.
It's an attempted murder.
You must tell the reporters to write the article.
Okay. Understood.
Two male bodies which were discovered at the warehouse by the port yesterday afternoon
turned out to be fraud suspects.
They were scamming by means of a Turkistan natural gas project.
They are assumed to have killed each other while fighting over profit division.
Breaking News: Two bodies from the warehouse at the port were identified.
Especially, one of the scammers fled after their scam was exposed
and raided Feel Gallery CEO Geum last night.
Scammer Mr. Sa assaulted Feel Gallery CEO Geum, even pretended to be a prosecutor
The victim is currently beleived to be in a serious condition.
Did Sa Do Chan really do this?
I heard that they even obtained Sa Do Chan's fingerprints at the scene.
This is driving me crazy.
Hey, how about Geum Tae Woong? How is he?
I heard that he is still in a coma. He seems to be in a serious condition because he lost a lot of blood.
Police are chasing after Scammer Mr. Sa as a prime suspect.
Given that Mr. Sa approached the investors, taking advantage of his resemblance to Prosecutor Baek,
he is charged with impersonation of a public official. Police are diligently attempting to apprehend him.
He's so gutsy. How dare he pretend to be a prosecutor?
Wait. Now that I look carefully, he really looks like him.
All right. I won't date. Satisfied?
Did I say not to date anyone? I said not to see Prosecutor Baek.
With that con artist?
By chance, did she mean it when she said con artist?
Wow, they do really look alike.
There's no way he came all the way into the prosecutors' office and scammed us. Could he have?
Geez, no way, unless he tried to win women at a nightclub acting like a prosecutor.
How could he come all the way to the prosecutors' office on his own?
Never mind other people. He can never fool my eyes.
I guess. There's no way a con artist would come up with investigative knowledge so fast.
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
You saw the news, right? The murder incident at Incheon port.
Yes. I heard CEO Geum almost fell for a con.
The problem is the con artist who attacked CEO Geum and ran away.
He pretended to be a prosecutor.
Isn't this Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo?
The Baek Joon Soo you've been seeing all this time could've been him.
Sa Do Chan.
Prosecutors Yang Ji Seung and Oh Ha Ra. From what point, were they deceived?
Were they perhaps accomplices? Find out all that in detail.
Okay. I'll look into it thoroughly.
Prosecutor Oh. This is war.
For now, stand your ground. That's the only way we can have a chance to fight.
You and I. No... At the least, you didn't know anything. Got it?
Now that the things have come to this far, I don't know if that would work.
If Sa Do Chan was a con artist, did she know about it?
No way. Could a prosecutor have been playing around with a con artist?
See? She goes around as if nothing's happened.
So brazen.
Hey, Oh Ha Ra. You really didn't know? Didn't you pretend not to know while you were plotting with the con artist?
Even an elite like you, Sunbae, whenever there are new cases,
there are so many things you don't know, right?
For someone who's not a prosecutor, he writes out an indictment right away without help from his superior, arresting drug smugglers.
Do you think that makes sense?
I've been working with Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo all this time.
Fine. Let's say what you say is correct.
Then, where is the real Baek Joon Soo right now?
Did you know there was a con artist pretending to be you?
Could you say one word about how you feel?
One word please!
Your valve stenosis is serious! You can't move!
Whether it's morphine or defibrillation, I don't care.
Please help me to work once more for this case.
How much did you know, Prosecutor Baek? Did you possibly know he came all the way to the prosecutors' office?
I have never...
I've never left the prosecutors' office.
This guy, Sa Do Chan, I guess he knew he looks like me, so he must've been going around pretending to be me.
Since he's suspected of attempted murder, I'll make sure I catch him myself.
For my reputation.
Sunbae, what are you going to do? Are you really going to arrest him?
If he gets arrested for impersonating a public official and for attempted murder, he'll receive a heavy punishment.
So, he shouldn't have made the mistake. Now, we're all at risk.
Sunbae, must you be so cold in a situation like this?
Sa Do Chan. His father died right in front of his eyes.
Geum Tae Woong killed his father right in front of his eyes, yet he couldn't do anything.
That's why I came out. I want to clean up what Sa Do Chan did.
If I don't stop this now, we won't be able to handle it later.
I'm also worried that Sa Do Chan will slip up more.
I have to try to stop him from going over the edge, but I can't contact him.
Sa Do Chan, he'll be in danger if we leave him alone this way.
Suspect for Murder Wanted
Bounty Maximum Ten Million Won
Sa Do Chan
Until I say, "I can't find you, where are you?"
Be sure you hide well. You can't come out, okay?
- Even though my hand looks like this, I have a big hand.
- A big hand?
Yes, of course. I can catch Brown Bear with this hand.
With this one hand, I can protect you, Prosecutor.
Son...
I'm sorry.
Oh, okay. Thanks.
Geum Tae Woong is conscious. Aigoo, I'm so glad he didn't die. Aigoo.
I'm from the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
You look healthier than I thought.
Should I reveal your shoulder or something? There's no way Sa Do Chan is in front of my eyes, is there?
He's already on the Wanted List. I'll catch Sa Do Chan with my own hands.
Of course, you should.
First, catch Sa Do Chan and bring him to me.
Sa Do Chan, Oh Ha Ra, Prosecutor Baek.
For the crime of mocking me, Geum Tae Woong, the three of you together.
I'll pay you back according to your part.
When I catch Sa Do Chan, I'll ask you for the weight of your crime as well.
I'll be sure to stand you at trial.
Go ahead.
You will meet a  miserable end.
You can imagine to your heart's content.
Oh, yeah. You should put a bodyguard around Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra.
I feel nervous that a woman would walk home alone at night.
Geum Tae Woong.
Are you saying you're going to hurt Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra or something?
I'm showing my concern for her.
Where will you use this?
This is the method often used by con artists.
Sa Do Chan will come by the gallery soon.
Move out all the security guards and let me come in.
Are you saying you're setting a trap?
It's a method I used to use a lot while I was a detective,
when a person is put on the spot.
If you use it especially when one is in a state of rage, it works well.
Are you going to get revenge on me for your father?
Geum Tae Woong is fine? Are you saying he put on an act?
It's a relief. It means Sa Do Chan didn't make a huge mistake.
What's different though?
Sa Do Chan is on the run as a murder suspect. The warrant for his arrest is out already.
Geum Tae Woong is the one who killed Sa Ma Cheon. That's the fact.
I have to arrest Geum Tae Woong.
With what evidence? You don't even have a warrant.
I also want to arrest him right this minute. But we don't have evidence.
Calm down and obtain evidence according to the law. Arrest him solidly.
So, we're supposed to leave him alone?
I can't do that.
Geum Tae Woong, you're perfectly well.
Prosecutor Baek was here earlier.
I'm Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra.
From now on, don't come unless you have a search warrant or an arrest warrant when you come to see me.
When I see you, I get very sick to my stomach, Prosecutor Oh.
Geum Tae Woong, you're under immediate arrest for the murder of Sa Ma Cheon.
Immediate arrest?
You can hire an attorney and file a petition for your release if your arrest is illegal.
If you have something to say, please do so.
Let's go. I can go with you.
But if you can't provide real evidence, I'll make sure you regret this.
What is the reason he was placed under immediate arrest?
- CEO Kim, do you have anything to say?
- Please say something!
You act exactly like those slippery loaches (which avoid legal punishment by all means).
Geum Tae Woong is a victim. What is the reason for bringing in the victim?
- One word please!
- Say something!
CEO Geum, are you going in without saying anything?
How can you arrest the victim all of a sudden? You think an immediate arrest is a cure-all?
It's highly probable that he's connected to Sa Ma Cheon and Victor's case.
He was actually at the crime scene. He must be interrogated at least once.
Don't you know it's humiliating for the prosecutors' office if you can't indict him within 48 hours? Will you be responsible for that?
For now, please trust Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra. We'll do our best.
Feel Gallery CEO Geum who was known to be a victim of Turkistan natural gas case was summoned to the prosecutors' office today.
Even though his life won't be threatened, this is still drawing attention as to why he had to be arrested without a warrant.
Geum Tae Woong is alive?
We'll have to use a weaker explosive.
I almost died.
Geum Tae Woong set me up? He faked his own death, huh?
I'm grateful that he's alive.
That's a relief. Hey, Geum Tae Woong isn't dead.
Right, our Oppa Do Chan ...
There's no way he would've killed a man out of anger.
At a glance, you can tell this is a victim cosplay.
I thought Do Chan was becoming a murderer. I was so shocked.
Hyung, don't you think this was Geum Tae Woong's setting?
Then, he's extraordinary. He's smart and evil.
That bastard got Do Chan twice.
The contract we found at the crime scene.
Your name. You see that, right?
This is your car that was photographed at that time near the location.
And you say you're not connected?
Geum Tae Woong.
My legal team will be here soon.
Talk with them please.
As you can see, I have no strength to testify. I've been seriously injured.
Bringing in a critical patient to conduct a coercive investigation. How can you do this?
This is proof that Victor Jang and Sa Ma Cheon entered the country illegally with fake IDs.
The con artists fought and killed each other at the crime scene when the scam didn't pan out as planned.
Mr. Geum Tae Woong's signature isn't there on the line.
Geum Tae Woong left the meeting when he found out the contract was a fraud.
No, you had no intention of signing the contract to begin with.
We carefully monitored your cash flow through the FIU.
FIU: Financial Intelligence Unit
You actually sold your real estate including your buildings and stocks in order to deceive the con artists.
But you didn't convert  the proceeds into bearer bonds.
You had transferred all that money you gathered into a secret account in Liechtenstein.
The account holder is Simon Jo.
You went there without an intent to sign the contract. That means you had another goal.
To get rid of the con artists.
Chief Prosecutor, Prosecutor Oh is cornering him too much.
No, she's not. I'm sure he's connected.
You have evidence? Both of the con artists died.
We don't have a case. So wrap it up and release Geum Tae Woong.
Yes, ma'am.
Chief Prosecutor, please—
Leave quietly.
Okay.
Geum Tae Woong, you can leave.
Sunbae Gil.
It's Chief Prosecutor's order. What are you doing without any evidence?
Let's go.
Geum Tae Woong.
I'll bring you back here someday.
As you wish.
I'm glad you came out without a huge issue.
I was dragged to the prosecutors' office and you say you're glad?
Prosecutor Oh, I can't leave her alone.
What should I do?
First of all, we have to catch Sa Do Chan.
Then, the fact that they were part of the con will be revealed.
For both of them, their careers as prosecutors are over.
Then...
Keep an eye on Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra's surroundings.
I'm sure she'll go near that Sa Do Chan. Bring her to me then.
I understand.
Unni, you're not connected to this incident, right?
Let's talk later.
Unni, you said that Prosecutor Baek was undercover when he was pretending to be a doctor that time.
By chance, was that doctor a con artist?
I guess this is what people mean when they say the world is a small place.
When you asked me to find Sa Do Chan who resembles Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo, I had no idea it would become this big.
The popcorn man— I mean, how long did Sa Ma Cheon know about Sa Do Chan's whereabouts?
I've known Sa Ma Cheon for a long time.
I told him about him when Sa Do Chan started going into the prosecutors' office.
And the people who rescued Sa Do Chan when he was in trouble while digging into the  Hongdae drug incident...
He and I were the ones.
That's what happened.
I was always curious about that.
People's relationship links are so mysterious.
I'll pour you a glass.
As for Sa Ma Cheon,
why couldn't he show himself to Sa Do Chan when he knew he was his son?
He said he was ashamed.
That he was too ashamed to show himself to his son.
That Terracotta Warrior incident, Elder Sa Ma Cheon planned that to catch Geum Tae Woong.
It was ruined because of Chief Prosecutor Jeong Do Yeong.
Sa Do Chan had to give up on taking the bar because of that incident.
Sa Do Chan was preparing to take the bar?
You didn't know?
If it wasn't for that incident, Sa Do Chan would've become a prosecutor by now.
Elder blamed himself a lot for this.
He said he's a father who ruined his son's life. He said he'd be able to face his son better if he took his revenge on Geum Tae Woong.
I will work hard, including Sa Do Chan's portion. I will destroy Geum Tae Woong for sure.
Sunbae!
I need this man for sure.
I'm truly grateful.
What about?
I'm saying I'm grateful that you got prettier while I haven't seen you.
Sunbae...
♫  Close your eyes and in your warmth wait and sleep on  ♫
Prosecutor Oh.
I told you not to look at me so longingly.
I'm warning you. Don't try to get to know me too much.
Father!
♫  Raise me up stay there for me  ♫
♫  Raise me up though far away  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫
♫  At my side  ♫
Frivolous
The customer is not answering the phone. After the beep...
♫  I will embrace all your hurts  ♫
♫  I will remember you always  ♫
♫  Raise me up stay there for me  ♫
♫  Raise me up though far away  ♫
♫  Stay with me  ♫