I finally got rid of the ghost from 20 years ago.
20 years ago
Everything was all planned out from the beginning, huh?
Meeting at the concert and rescuing me from the thugs.
You say when coincidences keep happening, it's meant to be?
You say you didn't know that I'm a daughter of an assemblyman?
You didn't need me, but my dad's power!
That's a misunderstanding. It's not like that.
What do you mean it's not?
You even have a woman
and a child you're hiding.
I'm done with you. I'll tell  Dad everything!
Mi Rae, listen to me.
I didn't know either. I just found out that I have a child!
Don't touch me, you fraud!
- What did you just say?
- Am I wrong?
Everything about you including the breaths you take was all a lie.
You're despicable, you scamming a**hole.
What? Scamming a**hole? Hey, hey, hey!
What did you just say? Say it again!
Mi Rae! Mi Rae!
Hi Hyungnim, I want to introduce you to a job.
How is it? Do you like it?
- Dad, did you pull another scam?
- Huh?
I quit doing that!
Starting today, I'm going to manage this vacation home and we're going to live here.  What do you think?
- Really?
- Of course.
Let's go.
You're early.
I wasn't ready to receive you, Hyungnim.
What exactly did you do?
You saw. Geez.
Now that it's come to this, let me ask you for a favor.
Please lend me your fingerprints.
You a**hole...
It can't be helped if you refuse a deal.
You killed my wife and
committed suicide.
Don't do this.
Brown Bear... please...
Hey!
You bastard. Die. Die. Die!
CEO Geum who was attacked during the involvement in an unexpected fraud...
Geum Tae Woong, you punk.
Even Sa Ma Cheon died.
He snuck out all by himself like a rat, huh?
Victim Mr. Geum of "Feel Gallery attacks • natural gas fraud incident"... discharged from hospital today
I brought Jo Seong Do.
Tell him to come in.
Governor, it's my honor to meet you this way.
Sit down.
But, what is the reason you want to meet me?
You.
Do you know who your parents are?
My mother died and I don't know my father.
This is definitely me and my mom.
That person is your father.
He's your biological father.
No way, Governor.
Your joke is too much.
Is it really true?
Geum Tae Woong.
That scum of the earth. He left your sick mother and you.
He became my son-in-law,
deceiving me and my daughter!
No way.
You get it now? Then, go now and be good to your father.
I'd never forgive a father like that, though.
That boy.
He's going to become Geum Tae Woong's time bomb.
Who are you?
I'm her sunbae from her hometown.
I heard about her out of the blue.
What are you going to do now?
- I'll have to cover it up.
- Cover it up?
Are you going to pretend not to know?
Right.
I'll pretend I don't know.
Pretend to work hard for him.
Pretend to be grateful.
Until I kill that bastard.
Sa Do Chan!
Sa Do Chan! Are you okay?
Why did you come all the way here? It's dangerous.
Geum Tae Woong... He's eagerly trying to catch you now.
I know. I was so shaken up that day that I was fooled by him.
Sa Do Chan.
Who's Sa Do Chan?
Who are you? Why did you run away?
You came running after me. That's why I ran away.
I ate not too long ago.
Now that it's come to this, I'll have to become a real attempted murderer.
No way. Never. I'll make sure to catch Geum Tae Woong. I'll clear your name, too.
- No matter what happens, you have to abide by the law.
- Prosecutor Oh.
I decide the rules of this game.
The law to me is to punish that bastard, Geum Tae Woong.
- I know how you feel now, but—
- By chance,
do you remember what I told you last time?
I said try not to get to know me too much.
Was it the villa?
Oppa Do Chan, do you think he's going around eating his meals?
You know Do Chan. I'm sure he's fine.
- The entire country is out to catch Do Chan. There's no way he's been caught already, right?
Hey! Don't even say that.
Get caught? Who do you mean?
Oppa!
Do Chan!
Why didn't you call us? Do you know how worried I was?
Sit, sit. I'm glad you're fine.
You're okay, right?
What's with your mood, everyone? Why so down?
You must be struggling so much (with your loss). We were so worried.
Why worry?
You heard, right? Geum Tae Woong is still alive.
Because he was called Brown Bear, I thought he was like a (dull) bear.
He's a (clever) fox. He even deceived you.
What are you going to do?
What else? I'll pay him back the as much as he hurt me.
Are we going to set him up?
Now, our genius hacker. Should we take a look at what you can do?
Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo
Prosecutor Baek, are you all right?
You don't look too good.
Hey, is it possible  just because I complimented that Sa Do Chan,
you're not upset inside, stressing out, are you?
Deputy Prosecutor, Sa Do Chan has to die if we have to get Geum Tae Woong legally.
What are you saying now?
Why must he die?
When I heard his story, aigoo...
Joon Soo, you must be thinking all kinds of things because you're not feeling well.
Brown Bear. Sa Do Chan is an obstacle for catching Geum Tae Woong.
Me, Prosecutor Oh, and you, too... We were also accomplices at one point.
So, Sa Do Chan has to disappear and Prosecutor Baek alone must remain.
And when that happens, please lead the investigation properly, Deputy Prosecutor.
Spooky?
Hey, Jack, long time no see.
Man, I haven't heard from you in ages.
When you fell off the grid, I just assumed the FBI had caught you or something.
I've been busy with business.
Do you still have that program you used to hack into the FSB server?
If so, can you give it to me?
That program.
It's hard to come by and it's super expensive.
But because it's you, sure, why not.
I'm sending it now.
Thanks.
Download
If everything goes according to our plan, can you really steal it?
Of course. You can say that's all up to our In Tae.
What do you take me for? Just trust me.
Do you trust him?
- Yes, I believe in you!
- I believe!
We believe!
If you knock, it will be open for you.
Download
920,000 Swiss Francs have been withdrawn. (Worth $920,000 US)
920,000 franc... 1 billion won?
Your money has been withdrawn.
What's this?
Director Kim!
- The money is coming out of my secret account.
- What?
- Find out what's going on right away.
- Okay.
Download
Done
How much is it? One, ten, hundred, thousand, ten thousand...
Good job! Good job!
You did good!
A Korean hacker is attacking them.
A Korean hacker?
They must be able to trace them to find out where doing this!
They're tracing the IP.
Go and get him right away! Now!
All right.
Governor Choi Jeong Pil
It's me.
What's this about? I believe there's no need for me to be talking to you.
Two-hundred billion won.
How did you know...
That was my money originally. I'll be putting it to good use.
You're going overboard. Think of your age.
Do you want to get that money back?
Then, bring that ledger to me.
Bring it to that location in an hour.
This old man!
Old man, I'll have to finish you off.
I think it's over there.
There's nothing here.
What's this?
Bees!
Run fast!
Too bad. It would've been daebak if we stole it away.
We can live without ever worrying about money.
This is where our plan ends.
I know.
Our genius hacker. You did well.
Prosecutor, we're ready to dispatch.
Great. Let's go.
But where are we going?
I'll tell you on our way.
Governor.
I'm here. Geum Tae Woong.
Sa Do Chan.
I did as you told me to.
Thank you, Governor.
My 200 billion won. You were behind this.
How about the ledger?
You thought I'd fall for such a trick?
Did you think that account over there would be hacked by such child's play?
I came here to send the old man off to the world beyond, but you get to go unexpectedly.
To your father's side.
Right. Since we started here,
let's finish here, Brown Bear.
Start?
Twenty years ago,
you tried to put the blame for killing your wife on my father.
How did you know that?
Because I was there when it happened.
Die. Die!
So you're saying you were up there.
I lost my father twice.
To the same guy.
Thanks for being alive and well. Let's see the end of it today.
Don't make a mistake, Sa Do Chan.
Because I didn't come to pretend to be dead this time. I came to kill you.
You!
Murderer!
I'll prove your sins no matter what it takes.
I can't forgive you!
If you can kill me, kill me. You probably can't kill me.
Your father was dumb too.
If he wanted to get revenge, he shouldn't have scammed me. He should have killed me.
You resemble your father. You can't kill a person.
Why?! Because you're a dumb scammer.
You judged me wrong. I'm different than my father.
Sa Do Chan... spare my life.
Why? Why don't you act like you're not scared, huh?
Please... please...
Sa Do Chan, stop it!
Don't let him go. He's the guy that killed my father.
He's the guy who killed my father!
No!
Arrest him.
Scammer Sa Do Chan who was on the run for the attempted murder of Feel Gallery Geum Tae Woong
has been arrested by Oh Ha Ra's team from Seoul Central Prosecutor's Office.
While Sa Do Chan was assaulting Chairman Geum again he was arrested at the scene.
Why did you pretend to be a prosecutor? Were you really thinking of killing CEO Geum?
Did you really plan to kill him?
Was there a reason for this?
Was there a personal motive?
Please tell us.
Were you thinking of killing him?
- Please tell us!
What was the reason?
Was that a penthouse?
I'm going to call him there and kill him.
You can't become a murderer.
There... you come and arrest me.
Crime scene. You know it right? I'm getting arrested because I will be trying to kill Geum Tae Woong.
During the interrogation, I will testify that you, Prosecutor Baek and Deputy Prosecutor Yang have nothing to do with me pretending to be a prosecutor.
That's how I'm going to testify.
Perhaps, to protect us?
You and Prosecutor Baek have to stay in the prosecutors' office to catch CEO Geum.
And then indict me with severe punishment so that people will believe that you didn't plot with me.
What are you thinking? You'll be in jail for at least 10 years.
I have an idea about that too. So don't worry.
You just match the timing and come to the penthouse.
Beware, Prosecutor Oh. Even if you're a little late,
I will truly kill Geum Tae Woong.
- True Name?
- Baek Joon Soo
Occupation?
Prosecutor. Seoul Central Prosecutor's Office Crime Division 6.
Are you joking right now?
I will ask you again. Name?
So annoying.
Sa Do Chan.
Occupation?
A scammer who impersonated a prosecutor.
Scammer.
Sa Do Chan, did you ever impersonate a prosecutor?
Not one person noticed that I was posing as a prosecutor.
Are you saying no one in the prosecutor's office conspired with you?
This is why prosecutors are the problem.
They think they're the smartest people in the world because they are good at Korean, English and math.
They were all fooled.
No co-conspirators.
Did you ever approach Feel Gallery CEO Geum with the intention of harming him?
Mr. Prosecutor. Let's not lead this into a homicide. That sounds too horrible.
It was just a fist fight between two men. Let's just wrap it up as an assault case.
It'd be even nicer if I got to meet with Geum Tae Woong and settle this with a fine.
Answer: No, I want a settlement.
Impersonating a public official is subject to prison time up to three years and assault is subject to prison time up to seven years.
But this is my conviction and my motivation of crime can be extenuated and I can confess during the trial to beg for a pardon.
Well, if I look a little regretful in front of the judge then
I think I'll be sentenced to maybe 2 years?
Sa Do Chan. Is this who you are?
A guy with a cold heart like you won't understand.
Cold heart?
Could you leave us for a moment?
Yes.
I'm pausing the recording for a moment.
What's he doing?
Deputy Prosecutor Yang.
Yes, Chief Prosecutor.
What is Prosecutor Baek doing right now? What is going on?
Whatever happens, don't you know he can't assault him?
Yes, I will go in and check.
Baek Joon Soo, what's going on?
Open the door.
Sa Do Chan, I heard from Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra.
In order to protect us, I heard you staged this murder attempt and got arrested on purpose.
I really wanted to hit him a couple more times but Prosecutor Oh came faster than I thought she would.
You irritate me, Sa Do Chan.
If only one, Baek Joon Soo or Sa Do Chan could live, Baek Joon Soo has to live.
So I will kill you, Sa Do Chan.
Why are those two men so serious?
Crazy, different world.
Crazy, a decision like a fate
♫  It became natural to approve it  ♫
♫  Crazy, never ending  ♫
♫ Crazy  ♫
♫  The penetrating gaze.  ♫
Arrest Sa Do Chan.
Aren't Prosecutor Baek and Prosecutor Oh a little too much?
Why are they ignoring him after using him so much?
There is 2 billion won under your name.
T-Two- billion won somewhere?
That's Geum Tae Woong's hidden son.
He's really bothering me. Get rid of him quietly.
I will die as Scammer Sa Do Chan.
Please live as Prosecutor Baek.
Why do I have to live as someone else?
Do Chan collapsed?
Did he do that to kill Do Chan?!
Sa Do Chan has escaped  while he was transferred to a hospital.
Sa Do Chan?
This is a good chance to get rid of him. If you lose him again
I can't forgive you.
♫  Was it changed?  ♫
Remember that time.