I heard from Prosecutor Oh Ha Ra.
In order to protect me and Prosecutor Oh,
I heard you came in for the attempted murder of Geum Tae Woong on purpose.
I wanted to beat him up more,
but Prosecutor Oh arrived faster than I thought she would.
You irritate me, Sa Do Chan.
Baek Joon Soo and Sa Do Chan. If one of us should survive,
Baek Joon Soo has to live.
So, I will kill you, Sa Do Chan.
Why are those two people so serious?
Kill me? What are you talking about?
Sa Do Chan, you're now a suspect for attempted murder.
That means you have to be behind bars for at least a year or two
which means the game with Brown Bear has no possibility of being won.
I will die as the con artist Sa Do Chan.
Look, Prosecutor Baek.
Please live as Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo.
Why should I live as you?
Even if I go to jail, I can run away. Don't worry about me.
I refuse your suggestion.
I don't want to live as Baek Joon Soo. Why should I live someone else's life?
I'll stop persuading you here. I'll move forward with my plan.
Deputy Prosecutor.
Prosecutors' Office
Unlocked
What's going on? What did you two talk about?
What's with the mood?
Sunbae. What did you tell him?
What did you guys talk about?
What's with you two?
Place Sa Do Chan under arrest.
Timing and
Please prepare the indictment against Sa Do Chan.
How should I prepare it?
Geum Tae Woong has claimed a homicide attempt.
Just write that down on the indictment.
Okay, I got it.
I did as you asked me to about Sa Do Chan, but I'm really sorry.
I'm sure we'll hire a lawyer for him and get him out as soon as we can.
But going to jail isn't easy for anyone.
Sunbae. Why aren't you saying anything?
You weren't sad that all of this time I only called out "pretty Mi Ran," were you?
I won't get to see you for a while, pretty Ha Ra.
Switch
Between hot and cold
What's going to happen to our oppa? How many years do you think he's going to get?
I'm not sure. Attempted murder and fraud.
About ten years?
On top of that it was against Geum Tae Woong.
I can't see Oppa Do Chan for ten years?
No! I want to go with him!
No! Oppa!
Take me with you!
You can't see Hyung Do Chan even if you go to jail.
Do Chan, that punk.
He took it all on himself. I really don't know what he's thinking.
I feel so sorry for Oppa Do Chan.
For hitting the enemy who killed his dad, how could he get attempted murder?
Isn't this too much from Prosecutors Baek and Oh?
They used him all they wanted to. How could they ignore him now?
I know. I told him not to trust prosecutors.
What happened to Sa Do Chan?
He's been transferred to a detention center.
Impersonation of a public official, assault, and attempted murder.
He'll be there for at least a year or two or he'll be sentenced to the maximum of ten years.
To avoid the fact that they worked with a con artist, I'm sure they'll give him a hefty sentence.
Is that something that can be hidden?
Even though I know about it.
I won't let those two, Prosecutors Baek and Oh, off the hook.
Sa Do Chan, this bastard,  really tried to kill me.
I can't let him live no matter what.
Two-hundred billion won. Sa Do Chan noticed it and the Prosecutors' Office sensed it, too.
I have to start with that. Tell the lawyers to come.
All right.
I indicted Sa Do Chan for impersonation of a public official and attempted murder.
Good job.
Geum Tae Woong. Please let me investigate him for laundering illegal funds.
Geum Tae Woong? Why?
He got rid of his assets which were under borrowed names for the Turkistan natural gas project.
He siphoned that money away overseas.
Liechtenstein. It's a famous country for tax evasion.
Are you sure? Do you have evidence?
FinCEN confirmed it for us.
FinCEN: Financial Crimes Enforcement Network
Are you sure it belongs to CEO Geum Tae Woong?
It's a secret account. There's no way he would've used his own name.
The account owner is Simon Jo.
Who's Simon Jo?
That's what we have to find out.
Leichtenstein. I heard it's a safe place and that's why I sent it there.
If the prosecutors' office requests cooperation from FinCEN, your account can be frozen.
But who is the account owner Simon Jo?
You don't have to know that. Just tell me what you propose.
You should launder your funds and bring them back into the country as soon as possible.
That's your best bet.
I'd need a reason if I want to bring in the money.
Why don't you open up a trading company?
A trading company?
Foreign imported vehicles that are old aren't that expensive.
Buy them at several million won and sell them again overseas.
Set up a paper company overseas first.
Sell the used cars to that company at high cost.
Do that and bring in 200 billion won back?
Yes. But you'll need an international lawyer who knows a lot about that area.
Director Kim, look into getting a lawyer in that field.
Okay, will do.
And I don't need to set up a separate trading company.
Among my employees, I have someone who already runs a trading company.
- Next, let's hear the process in detail.
- Okay.
Have a look, please.
VK Trading Company
CEO, hello.
What were you doing?
I was reading a book.
Reading?
Do you have something you want me to do?
Let's sit.
Do you know who your parents are?
That person is your father. He's your biological father.
If you get it now, go and be good to your father.
I'd never be able to forgive a father like that, though.
I have something to tell you.
Do you still gamble?
No, no. I quit.
The history of a gamble is the history of a human betting his fate on an uncertainty.
Gambling is fun, but you know,
gambling legally is more fun.
What? Gambling legally?
I'm about to teach you real gambling starting now.
Since you have a sign that says you're a trading company, run the business properly.
Buy used foreign vehicles,
and sell them to the foreign collectors.
I'll work hard.
Establish law and rule: Detention Center
Hey, 408. You pretended to be a prosecutor, right?
How dare you pretend to be a government official?
Guys like you who scam pretending to be professionals are the most despicable.
Geez, so disappointing. Professional? I'm a real prosecutor.
Because there is some misunderstanding between me and the judiciary,
I am getting fed by the judiciary (in their custody).
Once I get out of here,
- I'll go directly to the prosecutors' office...
- A**hole, you sure are a con man.
Hey, 828, you worked at city hall?
We shouldn't do this to each other as we're both government officials.
Both the same government officials?
You came in for accepting a bribe, right?
Five years in jail. Did you receive around 100 million won?
Fifty-million won!
Fifty-million... Geez, what a waste.
If you had gotten ten-million won less, you could have gotten probation.
R-Really?
Go ask the briber to testify like this in front of a judge.
"On your way over, you bought a drink that cost 1,000 won because I was so thirsty."
Then, the money you received becomes under 50 million won.
Then, you can have probation.
Hyungnim, I mean, Prosecutor, thank you!
Thank you! Bow!
Prosecutor, it's so unfair for me, too. Please hear me out.
Okay. One at a time.
That's not it.
Something's wrong with your sentence.
It was a crime of impulse. That's the problem.
Prisoner entrance/exit
Oppa! Are you okay? Your face is so gaunt!
You're fine. You're still so handsome.
My soul is having its heyday for the first time in a long time.
I'm eating and resting well, so don't worry.
Right. Even on a desert island, our Do Chan will
scam seagulls and have them deliver fish to him.
Did you find out what their moves are?
Big Bear has been having meetings with lawyers for days.
Bang-Bang is suddenly purchasing used cars.
Used cars?
Foreign vintage cars, you know. The ones collectors like.
I see the big picture.
The 200 billion won that's overseas. He's trying to bring that back into the country.
In Tae got him a bit upset with the fake hacking job.
Big Bear got scared, so he's trying to get all that back.
If that's the case, he'll try to open up a trading company.
He'll need an international lawyer who will work in the middle.
Okay. Shall we set it up?
A setting?
This plan is called Big Store Plan.
You borrow the authority which an actual attorney's firm gives for a little bit.
Roy &amp; Royce Law Firm
I am Law Partner Park Hyeok.
In Tae will be the inside man
in the attorney's office that CEO Kim wants to approach.
Attorney Park Hyeok
- Let's go have lunch.
- Yes.
Director Bong is the Big Store manager.
Big Store Manager: A person that takes care of the big store and knows what's going on.
Eun Ji is the Tailor. You have to make sure that the attorney is 30 minutes late to the meeting.
Oh yes.
Yes, yes.
Roy &amp; Royce Law Firm
He can't be coming out already.
It's a new beer. Please drink some and fill out a survey.
I quit drinking.
I didn't know that.
This is soda. Not beer.
Roy &amp; Royce Law Firm
Where is Attorney Park Hyeok's office?
It's the one on the right at the end of the hall.
Yes. Yes, please do that.
I'm Kim Hyeon Wook. I called you earlier. I'm here five minutes earlier than our appointed time.
I am the partner lawyer Park Hyeok from Roy &amp; Royce law firm.
I'm fine.
I'm working so hard trying to earn my tuition, yet you won't even treat me like a human being?
You won't even taste test just because you quit drinking?
It's not that. I don't drink.
I said it's a soda.
Geez!
This is beer!
It's soda.
Oh, is it soda that tastes like beer?
Move.
Please fill out this survey since you drank.
In Tae, quote a really high price. Hike it up to 20 percent.
Twenty percent?
As you know, it's all about know-how in this field.
Because I'm a sure thing, I'm a bit expensive.
Thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
The door...
Forget it.
Han River Detention Center
Rules for visitors
This is Attorney Jeong Choon Gi, your attorney.
Please have a talk first. I'll step outside.
What? I'm sure you didn't come by because you wanted to hear me say "pretty Ha Ra."
How did you know? I've been so sad all this time.
Don't you remember? I told you that you were pretty from the first time I met you.
I'm genuinely grateful.
About what?
Grateful that you got pretty while I didn't get to see you.
I feel so bad toward you...
for making you sacrifice in such a big way.
Don't worry about me. Don't skip your meals and do a good job.
Don't walk alone when you're going home.
Okay.
Listen to me carefully.
My father left me an inheritance.
An inheritance?
- 200 billion won.
- 200 billion won?
He told me who the owner of the 200 billion won is before he died.
It's Simon Jo.
I did find that out when I traced the account, but I haven't found out who Simon Jo is yet.
But how did you...
I told you. It's my father's legacy to me.
My father wanted to catch Brown Bear Geum Tae Woong all his life.
Don't you think he looked into such a thing?
Simon Jo is Jo Seong Doo.
Jo Seong Doo?
Jo Seong Doo is a lot more despicable and scary than you think.
It's good to be careful.
Why would Geum Tae Woong give that money to Jo Seong Doo?
Because Jo Seong Doo is his son.
Don't you think this is a great legacy from my father? Geum Tae Woong's weakness.
Why is that Geum Tae Woong's weakness?
Jo Seong Doo is not just a son, but a hidden son. The son CEO Geum abandoned.
In order to marry Governor Choi Jeong Pil's daughter, he cruelly abandoned Jo Seong Doo.
Geum Tae Woong will never reveal to him that he is his father
for the sake of his pride.
Prosecutor Oh, get Jo Seong Doo.
Get him and tell him that he has 200 billion won in his name in an international account.
Then there will be a breakdown within Geum Tae Woong's organization.
This. This, this one.
- How much is this one?
- This one?
- 10.9 million won.
- 10.9 million won?
It sells for 10 million won on the internet. What are you talking about?
Then, what do you think about this one?
- How much is this one?
- This is under 10 million won. It's cheap.
This looks good, huh? Show me this one.
- Here, this way. It's over there.
- Let's go.
-  Let's take a look.
- Okay, okay.
Why does CEO order us to buy the used cars under ten million won when they don't even run properly?
Who'd know what he's thinking?
Since he's asking me to do this, I'll have to just do it and cover it up.
Cover.
Hello, we're from the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
You're CEO Jo Seong Doo of the WK Trading Company, right?
Yes. We met last time. What? Is there something else now?
That must be why we're here, right?
You must be shopping for a car, huh?
Why did they bring me in? I don't think I did anything wrong.
Am I going to jail again?
Your international account has been detected by the financial investigations.
You have to reveal where you got that money from.
I have an international account?
I-I only have a bank account with a negative balance.
There's 200 billion won under your name and you say you don't know about it?
Two... Two... Two-hundred billion won?
Whoa.
This doesn't make sense at all.
Simon Jo
What? The Prosecutors' Office took in Seong Doo? For what crime?
Well, I heard they came and got him all of a sudden while shopping for the used car.
I don't know why they did that all of a sudden.
Call up Chief Prosecutor Jin right away.
Okay.
Mr. Jo.
Director Kim.
You came for me?
Why did they get you? For what crime?
I don't know. They keep asking me if I have slush funds overseas.
It's so strange. They say it's under the name Simon Jo.
Simon Jo?
You didn't know? They're saying I'm that Simon Jo.
They said I have 200 billion won.
What's going on?
How is it going looking for the money laundering expert?
I met with several international law attorneys. One of them who seems very capable asked for too much money.
I'm thinking about it.
You think that's important right now?
It's better to be safe when you bring in billions.
Hurry up and acquire him before Baek Joon Soo digs further into this and proceed with it.
Okay.
There are batteries for all these, right?
In Tae, didn't you ask for too much? Why isn't he biting the bait?
I did as Do Chan told me to do.
Director Kim
Hurry, hurry.
Yes, this is Attorney Park Hyeok.
This is Director Kim Hyeon Wook from last time. I'd like to meet with you again.
Yes, sure.
Welcome, Prosecutor Baek.
You don't look too good.
Are you that sad that a con artist who used to move around like your avatar is sitting in jail?
You're amazing.
The prosecutors' office is being played in the palm of your hand.
That's nothing. All these things can't happen for free.
It costs a lot.
That cost, I'll reveal it.
I'll investigate how you laundry slush funds.
If you stop me from doing that, I will investigate your attempting murder and smuggling drugs.
Everything. I'll investigate everything.
I'll take that as a declaration of war.
If you start a war, I'll have to fight back.
I feel more comfortable with this.
Trying to figure out if you're Baek Joon Soo or Sa Do Chan. Trying to figure out if you're my friend or foe.
It's much easier to fight the enemy once I can identify him.
When this war is over, I've told you this before.
I'll punish you for the sin of you working with the con artist.
Then, you'll never be able to work as a prosecutor again.
I'm saying this will be the last time you'll be standing in front of me with your head held high just because you're a prosecutor.
Do you perhaps know this?
The car accident that I was involved on my way up from Sokcho to Seoul.
You ordered Director Kim to do that.
You had reported that plan to Governor Choi Jeong Pil.
Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo is coming back to Seoul.
I think he found a video clip of me smuggling drugs.
How did he get that?
If that comes out to the world, you're finished since you were recorded on the spot.
I can't let him be. I gave my order to Director Kim.
I told him to push him off the road on his way up from Sokcho.
Prosecutor Baek Joon Soo... He'll become fish food.
And Governor Choi recorded that conversation.
And Sa Do Chan currently has that voice recording.
I still don't know where that voice file is.
There's no way he would've taken that with him to jail.