What if Fou4Mod happens to like you for real, what will you do?
Wait, when you said, "In case you'd like to have your nails done..."
you meant, you, yourself, are doing nails for them?
Well, no, there's still no definition to what we both are yet.
Be careful you might get hurt.
Hello.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm gonna go see my friends.
I'll have some of this.
Hey, can I ask you something?
Our home is only 10 minutes away from the school.
Why do you have to go to school so early every morning?
I have to help my friends do their homework.
I used to send a file for them to copy but the teacher caught us so no iPads are allowed.
- Oh oh
- See you.
- Have a good day at school.
- Bye-bye, dear.
Bye-bye.
To BTS Mo Chit, please.
Please hurry, I don't want them to see me.
Thank you.
Fou4Mod.
Where exactly are you right now?
The first carriage, it's least-crowded.
Period.
Are you gonna copy my homework?
No, I did it myself.
Chian did the lotus for me, it's gorgeous!
You know what, you can have my phone, if you're gonna stare like that.
So nosey.
Fou4Mod.
He's graduating, when is he gonna ask you out?
Hey!
I cut him off.
Huh?
Why's that, Coach?
Although I like girls, I still think he's hot.
I got sick and tired of him. He's boring.
It was annoying. That's it.
Look at you!
You're so charming, so charming...
He's so so confident, your friend.
Fou4Mod.
He couldn't hear you.
So what are we doing?
I don't know. Just take some rest.
We're too stuffed.
Need to sit down to digest.
Hey, hey!
Move!
You actually didn't cut Wichianmas off. I can tell...
he cut you off, didn't he?
Excuse me.
How did you know?
Take a look at yourself.
Shit.
I think he just ghosted me.
How are you feeling?
You can tell me. I won't tell anyone.
Shit, there must be something wrong.
You know, he hasn't replied to my DM on Instagram for a month now.
Does that mean he doesn't like me?
But you know, he used to tell me...
that he was put on hold by Bua.
You know what he told me?
He said he was done, he had enough...
he didn't wanna get hurt anymore.
Shit!
It's like him giving me a sign that he's free.
Is that all?
Yes, that's all.
For real?
Yes, for real. Really.
Alright, go on.
Why did he do that to me?
And you know, the other day...
I saw his Story, he's back doing nails for Bua.
Here's the thing, do you have his Line ID yet?
You guys don't even talk on Line.
Would he be serious with you?
How are you feeling?
You can tell me. I won't tell anyone.
So...I think he's keeping on a hook.
Do you remember when you said you two didn't have a status?
Well, I'll give you the definition.
Something like, he's a breadcrumber.
I'm like...
I keep going on a loop thinking if Chian likes me or not.
You know, I wake up and see his Instagram everyday. Boohoo.
You seem to like him a lot. LoLLLLL!
Desprately.
Just get over him already, really.
My cards turned out really bad.
If yours are good, you must be the one purchasing the concert tickets.
Alright.
Enjoy! This is the first time you're gonna meet Lisa.
After you spend time at the concert, you'll get over the heartbreak.
Your cards are really good.
Let him purchase the tickets. 5,800 baht on the 27th. You'll get them.
Lisa won't be smiling at me, looking from the cards.
How about my friend?
Pick three cards.
Your love is really good on the concert day.
Prepare to celebrate. Lisa will be smiling at you.
You try on your phone and I'll try on mine, okay?
Okay, okay.
And the fortuneteller says that zone E2L is really good.
E2L, E2L!
Do you get it?
Alright, I got it, E2L.
Whomever gets it first, okay?
Alright, okay.
Shit, I'm so nervous.
- C'mon, it's about time.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
On a count of five.
Five, four, three, two, one...press it.
Shit, my screen froze.
Fuck, please help me, God.
Please, they need to be confirmed.
Namo tassa bhagavato arahato samma sambuddhassa.
- Namo tassa bhagavato arahato samma sambuddhassa.
- Shit, it's going through. It's going through.
Namo tassa bhagavato arahato samma sambuddhassa.
- Fuck, it's here, confirm!
- Confirm it, comfirm it!
Okay, okay.
Fuck, I finally get to meet Lisa!
Man, which pink is Blackpink's?
I'm dizzy. There's a lot o f them.
This one.
Do you want a hoodie like mine?
No. Never the same design.
Wow, this is pretty.
Wait, I haven't finished wearing it.
Okay.
It's good.
Thank you.
This is nice, I bet Lisa will be able to see me for sure.
Ooh, there's a design at the back as well.
Are you alright?
I miss him again.
I wanna try on a shirt with him again.
Hey.
Why don't you do it with me instead, what you wanna do with Wichianmas?
It might help you forget him.
Are you crazy?
I'm for real.
No, I wanna hold his hand.
Fuck it!
Damn you.
Well, do you want it?
You know, that day, I was holding his arm like this.
But actually, I wanted to do this so much.
Can I lean on you a bit?
What the hell? What the fuck are you doing?
Well, I'm playing Wichianmas.
There's no Oscar for you. Just a little bit is good enough.
Well, you told me to be Chian.
Ah, try being Wichianmas.
Dear Fou4Mod, would you like to have your nails done?
- Haha, that's not like him at all.
- Would he say that?
Dearest Fou4Mod, how are you doing? Lol.
Just chillin' but I miss you a lot, Chian.
So does your face look like this when you put away the shades?
Fuck you!
You're funny.
I like that.
LoLLLllLllLLLLLLLLLL
What's so fucking funny?
I'm a funny person. LolLLLllLLLLLllllL
You know,
today is the first day I haven't looked at his Instagram.
I'm 10% on forgetting him.
Period.
Let's go get some smoothies.
Why did you kick me?
C'mon, get up.
Right.
Hey!
What?
Let's take a selfie.
What about me?
How was that?
I'm more handsome than you.
That's not true.
What the heck?
Wanna get our nails done?
Let's go.
Wanna try this?
Don't look.
Chian is here.
Damn you, I told you not to look.
Let's go get our nails done.
Man, should I say hi to him?
Don't even think about it.
C'mon, let's go.
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing here?
I'm here to buy new uni uniform.
And thinking about going shopping.
Finding something to wear at the welcoming orientation.
Oh.
You've disappeared.
Are you here to get your nails done?
Where are you going next?
Actually, I walked Baa here to get his nails done.
After that, I'm going on a walk.
Right, has the person you're having a date got here yet?
Is he here yet?
He's getting off a Tuk-tuk in front of MBK.
Oh.
Why don't you go with Chian?
When my date is here, we're gonna go for a walk too.
So shall we?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Alright, see you. I'm off.
Chian.
If there's nothing that you like, why don't you find it on an app?
I'm not sure about the size, I'm afraid it won't fit me.
Hey.
I'll help you look.
C'mon.
Shit, my battery is running out. Only 10% left.
You can't buy it if you don't have enough battery.
C'mon, choose the design.
Could you do that for me?
How about grey?
Size...large.
When you said you wanted me to do your nails...
that time...
Do you still want me to do them?
Seven, eight...so eight yellow sticks.
Four red sticks.
What's up? I'm working. Speak quickly.
Alright, I'll be fast.
I'm not going to Blackpink's concert anymore.
Chian wants to do my nails.
Excuse me, one moment.
Do them another day.
You told me you wanted to go to Blackpink's concert with me.
Well, the fortune teller told me that my love's gonna be good.
If I confess how I feel and he says no, I'll be able to move on.
Okay?
Then do it another day. You're in a good luck already anyway.
Man, why wouldn't you want your friend to have a scene?
If I confess to him and he's okay, then period!
So I don't have to be annoying around you, isn't that a good thing?
If you see me happy, are you not gonna be okay with that?
You're always like this.
You can sell my ticket. I'll give you a share.
Okay, deal. Bye.
Chian.
Baa-bin?
Yeah?
I like Fou4Mod.
I like Fou4Mod. Will you stop messing with him?
@Buawaterlily : Blackpink's concert on the 27th's ticket needed, no markup.
Bua.
Hey, thanks for the discount.
Is your friend really not coming?
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
When are you and Chian going to be a couple?
Why are you asking?
Then I'm gonna be straightforward.
Would you stop keeping Chian on a hook?
You're fucking nosey.
What the fuck are you doing? Take this goddamn ticket back.
No, you take it.
No! You take it back now.
Let's go.
Bua.
Bua. Bua.
Bua, take the ticket!
But please, end up with Chian.
So my friend can cut him off.
I like Fou4Mod.
"Looking to buy a concert ticket."
You like Lisa the most?
Just cover the ticket price.
Give me your hand.
Don't be stiff.
I'm not.
Yes, you are.
I'm not, do you know how to do it?
Of course.
Stay still!
After my nails are done, I'm gonna make a love confession.
After your nails are done, let me know.
I'll be rooting for you.
Hey, I really am not interested in Chian.
I think I'm being very clear about that.
We can only be friends.
Imagine being more than friends, it won't work out.
You're frowning.
So tell me, does Chian really like your friend?
They're doing nails right now.
After my friend's got his nails done, he'll confess to Chian.
They'll end up together for sure.
So you're gonna be heartbroken, huh?
Have you ever told your friend that you like him?
And you're gonna let him go, just like that?
I don't know.
I think this is your last shot.
If I were you, I would say something already.
Like, I like you. Like, right now.
At least, if you tell him and he doesn't like you...
or doesn't wanna be with you...
you won't have any doubt.
Really.
I don't know. Maybe there are too many people here causing internet problem.
I'll tell him after the concert.
Come on, man.
Listen, this has nothing to do with the goddamn internet.
You're doing it to yourself. No one is keeping you on hold.
You're keeping yourself on hold.
I bet...
with the next concert's ticket...
If you're still like this...
you two will never end up together.
Please, I mean well.
Let's listen to some music.
Hey, I got something to tell you.
Are you done with your nails?
Hello?
Excuse me, excuse me. I'm sorry.
So sorry. Excuse me.
Where have you been?
If Lisa turns around, please give her a smile. I'm off.
Excuse me, excuse me. I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
Don't tell Chian that you love him just yet.
I'm on my way to you.
Hurry up, please!
Thank you.
Can I take a pic?
Yeah.
So which one do you like, customer?
Okay.
That's cool.
Fou4Mod, I like you.
I've liked you since the day you texted me to copy my homework,
and you told me I had nice handwriting.
It made me feel really good. You know, I screenshotted that conversation.
Actually, I've screenshotted many of our conversations and made them in to an album.
I lied about living around Mo Chit,
because when you get on a BTS, you'll pass Mo Chit, right?
So I could have at least ten more minutes with you. That makes me happy.
Seriously, do you have any feelings for me?
You asked me to do nails with you...
you tied my shoes with beads...
and you created a playlist with me...
you don't seem to do these kinda things with other people...
You doing all that makes me like you more and more.
Or is it only in my imagination?
Sometimes, I feel like you don't like me at all.
Like, you're not that interested in me.
I don't wanna ask a fortune teller about you every day anymore.
Can you choose me? Don't choose him, please.
Is it cute?
Yes.
Here we are Fou4Mod. Ants printing.
So sweet. Do you like it?
Thank you.
This ant is a big one.
What about these ants?
There are so many ants already.
I'll take a pic of it, okay?
Alright.
What message have you unsent?
I sent the wrong one.
I just pocket-dialed.
I like it.
Chian.
I have something to tell you.
Yes?
- Are you still there?
- Huh?
What's wrong?
There's a new photo booth.
Let's check it out.
- Sure
- Ok.
- That's it?
- Um.
Well, I want to take a photo of my nails.
Sure thing.
I thought that what's any big deal.
I just messed you up. There's nothing.
- Ok.
- Will you get your nails done?
Can I have one sec.
Sure.
Let me choose the color first.
Ouch so tired.
What's the matter? Are you old?
You took it so long.
Oh I'm sorry.
I'm not going to confess him.
I think I already know the answer.
Please don't tell him.
Can you scan this one too?
My LINE ID.
For chitchat.
Siamese cat.
The ants.
Fou4Mods.
I probably won't be able to come and help film your Tik Tok often.
How's you and P'Fou4Mod?
Didn't you see it in his story? He posted things of Fou4Mod until it was spots.
One more shot.