[English subtitles are available]
[My Sassy Princess]
[Episod 10]
[Duke Dingbei's Mansion]
You bastard!
Father! Father!
Don't be upset.
I know I was wrong.
I know I was wrong!
Now you know
you were wrong.
You let a dangerous person into our home
without telling me.
You want to bully
Ling and I?
Right?
Tell me.
What did Family Lu
promise you
that makes you
worship them like a dog?
What's your family name?
I've already
sent Yue Ling off.
Sent her off?
Now you know to send her off.
Too late!
There's nothing I can do.
It's already happened.
Even if you beat me to death,
it won't make any difference.
You brat.
How dare you talk back to me?
Listen.
If anything happens
to Ling,
you will bear the brunt!
Father,
don't you worry about her.
She is having a great time
somewhere now.
Having a great time?
What do you mean?
Those are not my words.
I heard it from a servant.
He said when things got serious,
a tall man
on a horse came
and took her away.
Who was he?
He...
He looked like
the commander of one of the fourteen armies,
Shen Yan.
Shen Yan?
Again?
This is the cloth
you made for Shen Oink.
It loves the cloth very much
and wears it every day.
Oink was in my arms this noon.
Now that it's gone,
you should learn to let go.
Lord Shen,
you said you'd give me
something better.
What is it?
Were you talking about
the stars in the sky?
Take a guess.
I just did.
Since you came back to Yejing,
you’ve become
more and more secretive.
Shen Yan,
did you know?
I didn't mean to
make things difficult for those beggars.
I didn't despise their life
and that child's life.
I know.
Yue Ling
is very similar to Madam Lu.
She pretended to be
gentle and kind.
Her miscarriage
and the death of Oink
were her calculated moves.
I know that, too.
You know everything.
Do you know
what's on my mind?
You think
I left you at Duke Dingbei’s Mansion
for nothing but my reputation.
You've suffered a lot
and feel being wronged.
What else?
Also,
you want me to make it up to you.
With what?
It should be on the way here.
Almost here.
In the midnight, in the middle of nowhere,
it's fine if you are half-hearted.
But at least try to find
a better excuse.
Look.
That's your compensation.
What a beautiful meteor!
Do you like it?
Yes.
But
I like it too much to
feel regrets already.
What do you mean?
Look.
The meteor burned its life
to shine with
such bright light.
But it's fleeting.
Don't you think such beauty
is too short?
I think
many things
become more beautiful
precisely because of its fleeting life.
I hope you can
cherish the beauty
in your heart forever.
Let go of all the
frustration
and anxiety.
Blossoming flowers wither within a day.
All the beautiful things
vanish eventually.
Lord Shen,
will your affection for me
disappear just like that?
Don't be silly.
Greetings, Lord Lu.
Has the war fund been prepared
as requested by His Royal Highness?
Last month, I just gave him
hundreds of thousands of taels of silver.
He used up
all of it already?
My son-in-law
thinks I'm
a cash cow?
Forging fire arrow machine
is a costly cause.
His Royal Highness budgeted carefully,
considering you as his father-in-law.
His Royal Highness also said that
people were asking questions about the cold Jiangzhou case.
It will break out eventually.
Having the machine in place as soon as possible
can prepare us for the worst
and give us an option.
Fine.
Go to the treasurer.
Daddy, don't be upset.
Once His Royal Highness and you
carry out your plan,
the money you spend now
will seem like nothing.
You are back.
Come here.
Join me for a drink.
Any update on the
investigation?
My younger brother,
I'm drinking alone here,
while waiting for you for half a night.
When we meet,
you didn't even greet me,
just cut to the chase.
I'm your older brother,
not your servant.
Tonight is a starry night.
Tomorrow will be a sunny day.
Stop.
That's enough.
My men are still
trying to find the clues
of the hade's pattern.
The carving technique
is very good.
It won't be easy
to investigate.
What we know now is
that the piece
is not from the Central Plain.
Its origin
may be in the north.
Please
be patient
and wait longer.
Then why are you here?
I admire you
for saving the beauty
in front of Duke Dingbei's Mansion.
I came here
to pass on advice from mother.
You know what she's thinking about,
"Princess Changle
takes life easily.
She's not a virtuous lady.
Your brother has gone too far.
He's misbehaving."
Hey!
What?
Are you upset again?
I heard
you want to go against Family Lu.
That's right.
What's your plan?
The Lu family killed Yun Yi.
They thought there was no evidence.
But I think
their temporary relief
will result in disaster.
When I was in the capital,
I filed secret reports to His Majesty
and asked for permission
to make moves on Family Lu
and teach them a lesson.
Only when Duke Lu is cornered,
can his weaknesses
be revealed.
Judging by your face,
has the crown prince approved of it?
[Shen nodded] I finally got the answer
after several days.
They got the
Kun jade.
I must get it back as soon as possible.
The crown prince considers you as a deadly weapon.
But the Lu family
has many contacts in the central government.
If you offend them,
I'm afraid
they will bring you
more trouble.
Be careful.
I know what to do.
Okay.
I've drunk and we've talked.
I should go.
By the way,
come home and comfort mom sometimes.
It's enough to have
one trouble-maker already.
You need to behave.
Young Master, welcome.
Please come in.
See you again.
Mr. Shen is here.
This way, please.
Okay.
Keep playing.
Keep playing!
Go on.
Mr. Shen, this way please.
Shan,
don't blame me for being cruel.
You are a baseborn.
If you marry a lowly maid.
People will laugh at you.
You are right, aunt.
You are a man.
Sooner or later, you'll take over the family business.
A person who does great things
shouldn't have
any weaknesses or scandals.
You can't let these things
obstruct your path upward.
Today,
your grandfather
asked you to kill her
to help you remember.
Do you understand?
Yue Ling.
Young Master.
Get lost
Get lost!
Go away!
I understand.
Someone jumped into the river!
Miss Yue
lost her life
at such a young age.
The people at the riverside said
she...
She had a miscarriage
because of the princess. So she...
Although her fingers were stiff,
they were pointing downward.
There's no mud in her nails.
It means she didn't
struggle much in the water.
I gently pressed the her abdomen
and found that
no fluid was discharged from her nose.
It means it wasn't a suicide.
She was suffocated to death
before being dumped into the river.
How did you know
she must have been suffocated to death?
She looks pale
with unnoticeable blood spots.
It is a sign of suffocation.
There are no obvious wounds
on her body
and no bruises on her neck.
The only explanation is suffocation.
My lord, you're amazing!
Number Seven.
Yes.
Get everyone on the list
and come here.
Yes.
The body has just been delivered.
You've already drafted
a list of suspects?
I meant to give a lesson to Family Lu.
Now there's a murder.
It's time for them
to pay their debts.
[Lu Mansion]
-Go away. -You...
What do you want?
Jinlin Guard.
We are here for a case.
[Administration of Beidian]
Let's go, Mr. Lu.
From the last nightfall
to this early morning,
did you go out?
I'm the butler of Family Lu.
I have to deal with
hundreds of issues
in the mansion every day.
Of course I went out.
Hundreds of issues?
What are they?
Tell me one by one.
If you miss anything,
you'll be guilty of deceiving us.
Do you know it's a crime?
How inappropriate!
Mr. Lu,
please.
You can question me here.
Where did you go last night?
Luo Xiaoqi.
Why ask when you know the answer.
Where did you go last night?
Flower Pavilion.
Do you have any witness?
You.
Duke Lu.
Grandfather.
I...
Duke Lu.
Please.
Lord Shen.
So many guards here!
It's how I investigate a case.
Investigate a case?
Forgive me for being ignorant.
Lord Shen,
What is this major case about?
Is it so important that
you have the whole Lu family
and officials in contact with us
here at the administration of Beidian?
It is
Miss Yue’s case.
Princess Changle
lost her beloved pet last night.
So she assaulted Yue in public,
causing Yue's miscarriage.
The farce in front of Duke Dingbei’s Mansion
is heatedly discussed in the capital.
Everyone in the city knew that
Yue committed suicide
by jumping into the river because she's heartbroken.
If you are investigating Yue's case,
then, where is Liu Ling?
Mr. Lu
stayed at the Flower Pavilion all night.
But you are
very well-informed
about what happened outside.
Shen Yan.
I know
you and Princess Changle
fell in love.
the princess is sad,
so you are unhappy.
You want to revenge for her,
You can take it out
on me.
But you can't do this.
Using public office for private gain,
framing the innocent.
That's right.
How could he
get us involved?
It's not good.
Jinlin Guard never
follows orders
from you.
Who told you to stop?
Continue!
-Yes. -Yes.
Why do you ask?
Again?
Are you done?
They are causing delays.
[Duke Dingbei's Mansion]
Why is she not here already?
Father.
I'm hungry.
I'll eat first.
I can't stay here anymore.
She's just a junior.
How can she
keep the elderly waiting for her to eat?
Enough, stop talking.
What's wrong with that?
Ling.
-Grandpa. -Come here.
Sit down and eat.
Ling,
I heard
you went out last night
with Shen Yan?
Yesterday,
I was in trouble.
Lord Shen saved me,
Did you hear that?
You were ridiculous!
Yes.
I was ridiculous.
I wronged Ling.
Ling,
I will reward Shen Yan
for helping you.
But there is one thing.
From now on,
you should
stay away from him.
Okay?
Grandpa,
you don’t like Shen Yan?
Marriage is a major issue.
It's totally different from
liking someone.
-Grandpa, I... -Enough.
I can let you do anything else you want.
But you have to listen to me
on this one.
I'm not feeling well.
I'll go back to my room.
Ling.
All you care about is eating. Enough!
Uh...
Now,
There's a lot of gossip
about Ling and Shen Yan
in the capital.
Tell me,
what should we do?
Why do we need to do anything?
This is a good thing, father.
Who is Shen Yan?
The commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard!
He is favored by His Majesty
and His Grace.
If they get married,
our Duke Dingbei’s family
will have a close relation
with the administration of Beidian.
Nonsense!
All you think about is marrying into power.
You don't care about Ling at all.
Royal family issues
are complicated.
Ling and her father became enemies.
I'm the only one
holding them together.
I'm old now.
What would Ling do
when I'm gone one day?
Didn’t she fall in love with Shen Yan?
With Shen Yan there,
who dares to offend her?
Shen Yan is one of the Jinlin Guard.
What's his job like?
It looks glamorous.
But actually,
it is an extremely dangerous job
with too many uncertainties.
If Ling marries him,
she will be considered as
a widow-to-be.
You are her uncle.
Why aren't you worried at all?
Yes.
Father.
You are right.
This marriage brings nothing
but harm.
She cannot
be with Shen Yan!
Father,
if you
break them apart,
aren’t you afraid that Ling will hate you?
Of course I'm afraid she'll hate me.
She's my treasure.
How can I not be afraid?
Then, what should we do?
You go.
You!
I...
My lord.
Everyone,
let's call it a day.
This homicide case involves many people.
In the next few days,
I'll have to bother you with it.
Luo Fan.
Yes.
See them out.
This is ridiculous!
I think
you're acting like you are impartial.
But in fact, he's using his power for personal gains
and personal revenge.
-Isn't he? -He is!
How could you do that?
Your Excellencies.
-What's with all this! -Please.
The Duke is
so unrighteous.
He has been
spoiling Ling.
Now he has a plan that will upset Ling.
He hides up
and pushed me out to be the bad guy.
Be gentle.
Legs.
You're right.
Your father
doesn't like you
for a long time.
Today,
he asked you to break them up
and then let Ling deal with you.
Making others take the hit for him.
Killing two birds with one stone.
Young Duke, Madam.
Lady-in-waiting Xu is here.
Let her in.
Yes.
Greetings, young master.
Greetings, Madam.
-Rise. -Rise.
Please have a seat.
Your Ladyship
called me here in a hurry.
Is there anything urgent?
Yes.
You and Ling are close friends.
Do you know anything about
her and Shen Yan?
A little.
The members of the Jinlin Guard
deals with officials
and criminals
They can easily cause hatred.
His Lordship cares for Ling.
It's reasonable if he
wants to break up
Ling and Shen Yan.
What reasonable?
The Duke
wants to break Ling and Shen up,
but he doesn't want to upset Ling.
So he dumped the responsibility on me.
I...
You are Ling's uncle.
Of course
you wish her well.
Yes.
It's just that
Ling has never showed respect to us.
If we go and talk to her,
I'm afraid
she won't listen to us.
Right.
Lady-in-waiting Xu, you are
the best fit for this job.
In that case,
I'll give it a try.
Great.
Very good.
I'll take Ling out
for a walk later.
Young Master,
please go to
the administration of Beidian later
and ask Lord Shen to come here.
Please tell him
Ling has something important to tell him.
When he arrives at Ling's door,
just cough a little.
Okay.
I'll go get Ling.
What an interesting family！
He's afraid of offending the princess
so he wanted you to take the blame.
Why did you help them
and get involved in this mess?
I'm not helping them.
I'm helping Ling.
Will Madam Shen
go to Hong Luo Temple today?
Yes.
I've asked around
for you.
She will leave around eight to pray for
happy marriages for her two sons.
Got it.
[All Wishes Will Be Granted]
Jin!
Why did you bring me here?
Ling, did you know
Hong Luo Temple is famous for
praying for marriage?
Really?
You can try it
to see if it works.
Why don't you try it?
Go now.
"Amorous is also heartless.
What's left is
sadness with wine."
Jin,
it's an unlucky draw.
It doesn't matter.
Let's burn it
in the incense burner,
then it won't work.
-Really? -Yes.
Let's go.
Madam Shen.
It’s God’s will.
Why are you so stubborn?
You just did
a sinful thing.
How dare you come to the Buddha to make a wish?
I didn't know
about her pregnancy.
Pregnancy?
Did you know
Yue Ling
is dead?
Madam, you are a wise lady.
Although people in the capital
said Yue Ling jumped into the lake
because she had a miscarriage.
In my opinion,
there's something fishy about this.
I'm afraid from the beginning,
someone plotted it against Her Highness.
Madam Shen,
do you think
I killed someone
because of jealousy?
What I think
doesn't matter.
But Yue died
because of your
flashy personality.
We dare not to have someone like you
marry into our family.
Please have some mercy
and let go of Yan.
Let’s go.
Ling.
He is just a commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard.
How dare he act
so arrogantly?
He's relying on the Crown Prince.
I think he's determined to
act against your family
and us,
the veteran officials.
Lord Liu,
don't worry.
Even His Majesty can't do it.
The Crown Prince
can't do anything about it.
Without his right-hand men,
he won't be able to
make any trouble.
You mean...
What funny things
did you hear?
A nobody
has
great expectations.
What follows will be
more amusing.
Take a seat.
You are making me dizzy.
Jin,
did you plan my meeting
with Mrs. Shen?
You'll have to face it
sooner or later.
You can't avoid it.
What should I do now?
Mrs. Shen and grandpa
won't allow me to be with Shen Yan.
When we had breakfast today,
grandpa
forbade me to talk to Shen Yan.
Since I came back to Yejing,
troubles followed me
wherever I went.
It feels like there's no end.
That's how life is.
Especially with love,
things are more complicated.
You've only been back a few days.
Your relationship
has been obstructed by many.
It must be hard for you.
Jin,
you don't support us
being together as well?
I do.
Shen Yan is a good man.
When you are with him,
you look different.
Ling, did you know
when you were with him,
you had the brightest smile
that I haven't seen
for many years.
But...
But what?
But
I’ve been wondering.
The mistakes your parents made
when you were little
traumatized you.
All these years,
you haven't
fallen in love with any man,
right?
Then why is Shen Yan
an exception?
Shen Yan
is different!
Please.
Ling,
if you are not sure about your heart,
listen to my advice,
break up with him for good.
Stop falling for him.
Why do you say that?
Do you know
what you have to overcome
for your relationship?
Mrs. Shen?
Grandpa?
And Family Lu?
No.
You have to face your mother's death
and solve your own issue.
Let’s leave other things for now.
Ling,
tell me with certainty
right now that
you love Shen Yan
with all your heart.
And you believe
you and he
will love each other for life
and grow old together.
You have no doubts about that.
I do love him
whole-heartedly.
But
I'm not sure about
loving each other for life
and growing old together.
As you said,
my mother's death
and my own issues
scare me.
So,
I don't know and don't dare to
think about the future.
I...
I don't know
what will happen in a lifetime.
Shen Yan!
Shen Yan, I...
If you are uncertain,
what's the use of going after him?
Did you
do it on purpose?
You may think
I'm trying to break you up.
But Ling,
I hope
you can listen to me on this.
Although Shen Yan is
a member of the Jinlin Guard,
his family is not as powerful
as the Liu and Lu families.
Your Mr. Shen
can’t stand
the schemes and changes in Yejing.
If you are uncertain,
you might as well stop right now.
Otherwise,
if Shen Yan
risks his life for you in the future,
I'm worried about you.
I'm afraid you'll regret it.
You're here.
How is the investigation going
about the jade?
This is the only place
to find clues about the jade?
Even with your skills,
you can't
walk freely there?
Fine.
It looks like
I need to do it myself.
"You love Shen Yan
with all your heart.
And you believe
you and he will love each other for life
and grow old together.
You have no doubts about that."
"I do love him
whole-heartedly.
But
I'm not sure about
loving each other for life
and growing old together.
As you said,
my mother's death
and my own issues
all scare me.
I don't know and don't dare to
think about the future.
I don't know
what will happen in a lifetime."
Your Highness.
I just came here
and saw the light on in your room.
Why are you still up?
I can't sleep.
Let me chat with you.
If a woman
really falls in love with someone,
there should be signs?
Signs?
Your Highness,
I remember.
I served a lady
at Duke Dingbei’s Mansion.
She said there are thousands of bitterness in the world.
Living as a human is the most painful thing.
She also said
she fell in love with a man.
But when she wanted to see him
but couldn't,
she cried very often.
She cried very often?
You have a point.
I know.
From tomorrow onwards,
I won't see Lord Shen.
If I can cry
because I miss him,
it means
I really love him.
That way,
I can stand in front of him
to express my feelings.
[Administration of Beidian]
-Lord. -Lord Shen.
You're awake.
My lord,
it's just seven in the morning,
why are you here?
Wake up the brothers.
Get up and work on the case.
Work on the case?
Why are you in such a hurry?
We're not in a hurry.
We need to let some people feel anxious.
Yes.
[Lu Mansion]
Open the door!
My lord.
Look how scared someone is.
Open the door.
When you go in,
search the place
Open the door!
I still don't understand
what we are searching for.
Open the door!
It doesn't matter if you don't understand.
Mr. Lu understands.
Okay.
We'll search it
thoroughly.
Open the door!
Search it!
Yes.
Jinlin Guard.
Search it!
Shen Yan.
You keep saying
you wanted to investigate Yue's death.
You let someone break into
my grandfather's study.
What do you want?
Search for evidence.
You know
what we are searching for.
Search for evidence.
Okay.
I'll let you search today.
But if you can't find anything,
how will you explain it?
If we can't find it this time,
we'll find it the next time.
Why don't we make a bet
and see how long
you can hide it.