[English subtitles are available]
My Sassy Princess
Episode 7
-Lord Shen! -Your Highness!
-Your Highness! -Lord Shen!
Your Highness!
Lord Shen!
Why are you laughing?
I laugh
because in the world
there is indeed a man so courageous,
and this man belongs to me.
What a bargain!
I feel happy
so I laugh.
Indecent.
Decency?
Leave it to other women.
As for me,
Lord Shen!
I don't need it.
Your Highness!
Lord Shen!
It's my lord!
My lord!
How come they came so quickly.
My Lord,
we found you at last!
Are you okay?
I'm good.
How are the brothers?
Don't worry, my lord.
We are hard to kill.
The fact that you two haven't returned for days
worried us to death.
Exactly.
We went to the mountain every day
to look for you and princess.
We've searched almost the whole mountain
and found you at last.
Yes, my lord!
[Courier Station]
My Lord,
we've investigated.
These killers are clean and quick.
Because of their deadly efficiency,
not a single trace
is left for us.
Did you notice anything unusual
during the fight?
My lord,
these people seemed to have done it on purpose.
Their skills were very sophisticated.
But in the heat of the fight,
I noticed that some skills are similar to
those of the family Lu's in Yejing.
It's the Lus.
You Highness,
since you had a hard time coming back,
why don't you go to the room and rest?
Why do you come here for the case?
I'm not here for the case.
I
come to see Lord Shen.
What is it?
Amazing, my lord.
How do you know that
inside Yun Yi's mouth
lies the mystery?
What a deadly crime!
If so,
I don't want you to win.
Wait till I am dead.
I'll do you a favor.
I reached an agreement with Yun Yi.
Despite his mortal sin,
before he died,
he saw sense.
Take it.
After we return to the capital,
check the jade
and Lu Lianshan.
Yes.
Isn't the princess
a little weird today?
Since you said so,
she is indeed.
Your Highness,
did anything happen
in the last few days at the foot of the mountain?
When she was with us in the past,
-It's never so quiet. -What happened?
Now,
Why are you here?
it looks like...
We...
down the mountain...
Go away.
The princess is tired, and she needs to rest.
Why so sudden?
They are holding hands!
What's going on?
They're holding hands.
Shen Yan,
you dragged me out in such a hurry.
Are you afraid...
Afraid of what?
afraid that others will know our relationship.
Right?
You and me,
what relationship?
Nothing.
Since you refused
to marry me down the mountain,
of course, there is nothing.
Now, as I recall that
you were eager to return to the capital,
I'm afraid from the beginning
you never thought of
being with me forever.
Your kisses and hugs
were misinterpreted by me.
On the cliff,
you saved me when falling off the cliff
to fulfill your duty.
And...
when we were on the iron chains
and a thousand birds flew by,
what you said
was not true at all?
Since Lord Shen doesn't want to answer,
I won't force you.
Men are heartless,
which is no news.
I'll take those days
as a dream.
Why
are you angry?
Shen Yan,
you are bullying me.
Bullying you?
If you dare
to talk nonsense in the public,
believe it or not,
I'll prove it to them right away.
I don't believe it.
What will you do?
You don't believe me?
It's up to you.
You.
Be a good girl.
Lord... Lord Shen.
Your...
Your Highness,
are you alright?
Yes.
I'm good.
Attention!
-Lord! -Lord!
Early in the morning tomorrow,
we'll return to the capital.
-Yes. -Yes.
Come in if you have something to say.
My Lord,
although the fish we're going to catch
is off the hook,
you manged
to get the information
from Yun Yi.
We can continue investigating the case.
If the crown prince hold us accountable,
will we
be beheaded?
Having said so,
my Lord, your face
shows that
something difficult happened.
Do you know the case
of the late Princess of Guangping?
My Lord,
you asked the right person.
The official announcement writes that
Princess Guangping fell into the pond by accident
and drowned.
However,
according to my research,
it was because Prince Guangping's
infidelity.
Princess of Guangping
jumped into the lake because she was heart-broken.
Ok.
I have a question for you.
Who is Prince Guangping's new wife?
Everyone knows who she is.
She is from Family Lu...
Family Lu!
Family Lu again?
You sensed it's weird as well.
My Lord, do you have any discovery?
As far as I know,
the Family Xu of Yejing
and the Family Zhang of Dingbei Mansion
have been friends for generations.
The eldest son of the Family Xu
and Zhang Yun, late Princess of Guangping,
are sworn siblings.
According to the princess,
after the case in Jiangzhou happened
where the Xu couple died,
the late princess and Prince Guangping
had an argument.
Shortly after that,
the princess drowned in the pond.
It was just at that moment,
Family Lu connected themselves with
the Family of Prince Guangping by marriage.
What a coincidence,
yet could it be
just a coincidence?
I have worked under your supervision, my Lord,
for only a few years,
but I know that
there must be a demon if something goes wrong.
Coincidences
happen very often
in the tales of storytellers,
but in the real world
they rarely happen.
Poor princess.
If you're right,
I'm afraid, in the end, the Jiangzhou case
will cause more pain to
Her Highness
who lost her mother at a young age.
[Yejing]
Princess Changle, Liu Ling
I pay respect to Your Grace.
I
have something to report.
I hope Your Grace will give me a chance.
My cousin,
you haven't shown up for years.
When you do,
you have things to report.
Interesting.
Tell me.
The criminal Yun Yi's death
is not the Jinlin Guard's fault.
It was due to me who was so unruly
and delayed the important matter of His Majesty and Your Grace.
Good.
I've never blamed you,
yet you're trying to silence me.
You are still
as discerning as ever.
Forget it.
I don't need you
to mind the state affairs.
I heard you have
officially engaged with Lu.
Engaged?
That's Prince Guangping's
wishful-thinking.
It has nothing to do with me.
If my memory serves me right,
Lu Mingshan
is the son of a concubine.
You are a princess.
Marrying him
is below your status.
However,
The Lus have few heirs.
He'll inherit the title from Duke Lu
in the future.
Compared to Shen Yan,
Lu Mingshan and you are a good match.
How come a human and a beast
belong together?
Beast!
My cousin,
you're still full of witty words.
I also hope
you can find your Mr. Right.
But
in this world,
people who can do whatever they like
are few.
For those who are born into royal families,
it's even harder.
I hope your expectation
will be neither an illusion
nor a pipe dream.
All right.
The lychees of tribute
were brought to the palace yesterday.
Today,
I'm to hold a banquet in the court
and invite the officials
to enjoy.
Since you just came back to the capital,
come and join us.
I have something important to discuss with Shen Yan.
You can go back now.
"In this world,
people who can do whatever they like
are few."
Your Highness!
Be careful.
"I hope your expectation
will be neither an illusion
nor a pipe dream."
Shen Yan.
Your Highness.
The commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard, Shen Tan, arrives.
Let him in.
The commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard, Shen Tan.
I pay respect to Your Highness.
My dear Shen,
you're finally back.
I, your humble subject,
failed to fulfill my duty
and didn't live up to Your Grace's expectation.
Please punish me, Your Grace.
Father and I
have high hopes
for you.
Do you know
in order to have you
in charge of the case
I have drawn
many controversies in the court.
I have defended you,
but in the end what I got
was you apologizing
for failure
and incompetence.
I
deserve to die thousands of times.
The news of the Jinlin Guard
escorting the princess back to the capital
was released by Shen Yu on your order, isn't it?
Your Grace is wise.
You want to
use the news that the princess has returned to the capital
to lure the criminals out.
But in my opinion.
you are spinning your own web.
In the court,
Duke Lu repeatedly
complained to me
that you didn't make a distinction between private and public interests.
It has affected the state affairs.
The princess came back,
but Yun Yi died.
Shen Yan,
I want to ask you.
How do I
explain it to other officials
and how should I punish you?
I, the commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard, Shen Yan
failed to handle the case properly
and let His Majesty down,
but Your Grace is fair in giving out rewards and punishments.
Considering that I have protected the princess,
I hope to be exempted from death penalty and
be held on suspension.
Your Grace will see whether I will have bettered myself.
Rise.
Thank you for your mercy.
Why do you
give this to me?
The jade
was kept in Yun Yi's mouth by himself
before he died.
If I'm right,
this jade
is not only one of a pair
but also closely connected with
the treasury that was stolen in Jiangzhou.
Through mere one word "qian",
what connection you can see?
Your Grace has sharp eyes.
The word "qian" on the jade
is one,
while the other
is Yun Yi.
This man
is cunning
and stingy.
Both the Jinlin Guard and the prime culprit of the Jiangzhou case
wanted to find the treasury silver,
both were his enemies.
He knew
he won't be able to escape.
As a result,
He placed them
at two places,
so that each side gets one
and fight endlessly
to the advantage of neither party.
That's how it goes his way.
The bait fell,
but the fishing line
is still there.
Your Grace,
my suspension
on the one hand can stop the gossip
and let the chief criminal lower his vigilance,
on the other hand
it enables me
to have more convenience
and make amends for my negligence.
Based on what you said,
this time
you worked hard.
Shen,
why don't you greet your older brother?
You are getting older every day,
yet you have no manners.
Did you give them back to your parents?
My Lords, you haven't seen each other for a long time.
I'd better not to disturb you.
See you.
You look like a philanderer.
If the palace servants noticed it and spread the word,
how indecent it would be!
Just like
you and Princess Changle.
Your love affair,
despite the long distance,
is known by everyone.
Irresistible love and passion.
It is indeed indecent.
You're making up stories and adding fuel to the fire.
I haven't got even with you
for what you did.
You brat,
taking your undeserved gains for granted.
You walk so fast
to meet your princess?
Your Highness, this way.
Your Highness,
this way.
Lady-in-waiting Xu.
-Ling. -Jin.
You can go.
Let's sit down.
Ling,
It’s been years since we parted.
Have you read the letter
I wrote to you?
Which one?
The one in which I told you
your betrothed Lu Mingshan
had an affair
with his maid Yue Ling,
and before marriage
he'll take her as a concubine.
Lady-in-waiting Xu is amazing!
You are
straight to the point.
Compared with Princess Changle,
I feel inadequate.
Although Lu Mingshan is indiscreet,
you are no better than him.
In just a few days,
you had an affair with
the commander of one of the fourteen armies of the Jinlin Guard.
Otherwise I'd be like you
being single all along.
Ling is still the old Ling.
You haven’t changed at all.
Seeing you come back safe and sound,
I'm very happy.
However, seeing you
makes me feel bad.
It turns out
that you don't want to see me?
Yes, I want to,
but I dare not to.
Everyone in Yejing
knows Lady-in-waiting Xu
as being astute
and tough.
Everyone says
that you are trusted by the crown prince and
has a bright future.
But I'm the only one who thinks
you have changed.
Jin!
Was I wrong
to help you enter the palace?
As the saying goes,
taking people as a mirror helps one understand gains and losses.
Do you know
you are my mirror?
Give it back!
No. What can you do?
He is robbing her!
Give it to me!
Why are you grabbing me?
Are you the national traitor?
Who kicked me?
You.
You are Xu Shijin?
That's right. Let's go.
Wait and see.
I'll go home and ask my father to punish you.
You...
My name is Liu Ling.
Duke Dingbei is my grandfather and
Zhang Yun is my mother.
What else do you want to ask?
Why did you help me just now?
They were bullying you,
so I helped.
My grandpa said
my mother and your father were sworn siblings
by burning yellow paper
in front of gods.
Then you and I
are sisters.
Your parents died
and so did my mother.
Since we are sisters,
we should rely on each other, right?
That's right!
Jin, don't be afraid.
If anyone dares to bully you again,
I will help you
fight back.
Happy or sad,
right or wrong,
it seems that the pain I don't want to see
and the past I don't want to recall
have no place to hide
in front of you.
This old thing
is still kept by you?
It's priceless.
How could I throw it away?
Without you
and the protection from the Duke,
I’m afraid I wouldn't be here today.
At that time in Yejing
only you believed me.
Only you.
My parents didn't betray the country.
They were set up to die.
Do you remember
I asked you
whether you believed what I said?
How did you answer me?
You are my sister.
Of course I believe
what you said.
Since you call me sister,
I have to ask you about
you and Lu Mingshan,
what's your plan?
There is no plan
other than making him back off.
That's easy for you to say.
How many royal women
can marry
out of free will?
I think
the Family Lu is determined
to cling to your family.
Making him back off
will not be as easy as you said, I'm afraid.
If he insists,
I'll give him some trouble.
Ever since I came back to Yejing,
I've been upset.
Lady-in-waiting Xu,
the palace banquet is ready.
It's time for you
to join them at the Eastern Palace.
Okay.
Please, Your Highness.
The lychees,
precious as they are,
are unable to
fill the stomach.
My ministers and officials,
it's rare for you to come here.
If I
let you go home
hungry,
I'm afraid you would call me name
after leaving the palace.
My yard often receives
people who are
the younger generations of Wei,
so relax today and
speak your mind freely.
Today's banquet
coincides with
Princess Changle's return to the capital.
Here,
let's make a toast to the princess
as a welcome.
Here we go.
The bitch got lucky,
but she caused a lot of trouble for me.
This Princess Changle.
How interesting she is!
She's been staring at you
as if she wants the whole world
to know about your affair.
Shen Yan,
tell me the truth.
How far did you get with her?
Ling,
I’m so happy
to see you back.
Ling,
are you still angry with me?
I know
your way back to the capital was full of danger.
I couldn't stay by your side.
I feel guilty.
Ling,
I'll have a drink as a punishment.
I apologize.
The princess is...
Look at Her Highness...
What brings Your Highness
to see me?
Someone boring
was around me.
Come on,
On my way to the capital,
thanks to Lord Shen's company
day and night,
I am safe and sound.
This is
for Lord Shen.
It's my duty and
I dare not to take the credit.
Lord Shen, you're too modest.
Thank to your escorting my betrothed,
she is here
safe and sound.
I heard that
you failed on an important matter for the sake of princess;
as a result,
you are punished
by the crown prince.
I
feel unease.
This
on the behalf of the princess and I
is for you.
Now that Ling is back,
our wedding
is around the corner.
I'd like to invite Lord Shen
to come to our wedding
along with all officials here.
All of you
will bring joys to our big day.
What do you think?
That's a good suggestion.
Lord Shen,
please.
Mr. Lu is being funny.
You talked about you getting married
in the public for a while.
Why didn’t you ask
if I would like to marry you?
Today's wine is strong.
Your Highness must be drunk.
If you say I'm drunk,
then I'm drunk.
The wine of the palace banquet
I will drink no more.
I'm not happy here
so I'm leaving.
Shen Yan,
you owe me
a drink.
Your sweetheart is gone,
why are you still sitting here?
If you don't go after her,
I wonder what trouble
will this wild girl cause.
Jin.
Jin!
As soon as Ling is back,
the capital
will be eventful again.
Have you had enough fun?
I told you not to come back,
but you insisted.
You see, I've only been back for half a day,
yet I've caused so much trouble.
Then tell me, Lord Shen,
when are you going to marry me?
I have a plan.
You just need
to behave yourself.
When will it be?
Today?
Tomorrow?
I am not sure about
what you said.
How can I...
♫We two love each other forever♫
♫Arrows stop time♫
♫Life is short ♫
♫Attachment hidden in every tear♫
♫We two love each other forever♫
Are you sure now?
♫It is shown through our eyes and knitted eyebrows ♫
Forget it.
♫No matter how long our reunion would be♫
It's cold here.
You just drank wine.
♫Our hearts are forever together ♫
Go home and have an early rest.
I’ll deal with
Lu Mingshan.
But Shen Yan,
be efficient.
Don't let me wait too long.
I know.