[English subtitles are available]
[My Sassy Princess]
[Episode 3]
But Lord Shen.
We were having such a good time
a moment ago.
Why did you become so cold,
right after Mr. Lu came?
Could it be...
that you're jealous?
Let's go, Ling Bi.
Your Highness.
What did Lord Shen mean by that?
He's brushing me off.
But I
wouldn't brush him off.
He's my beloved one.
He deserves to be treated carefully.
Yang Ye.
Yes.
Let's go.
Well...
Why did she leave suddenly?
I have no idea.
Where do you think
her Highness is going?
Lord Shen.
Lu Mingshan, son of Lord Lu.
Did you know him?
What would happen if I do?
What if...
I don't know him?
He's here.
In my opinion,
this person is up to no good.
What do you think?
I have no contact with Family Lu.
Him being here
has nothing to do with me.
It better be.
Otherwise,
you won’t be able to get to Yejing alive.
Princess,
what are we doing?
Waiting for someone.
Waiting for someone?
For whom?
Look, your Highness.
Is it him?
He looks like
he's been starving for days.
It's not him.
Give him some silver.
Here.
This is from our Princess.
Thank you. Thank you.
Your Highness.
Is it him?
He's like a cow chewing peony.
He can't tell good food
from bad for sure.
Not him.
My lady.
Is this the place?
Yes.
It's him.
When will you bring me to try it?
How about tomorrow?
I've been waiting for you.
W-Waiting for me.
How dare you?
How dare you lie to me and cheat on me?
I just wanted to ask him something.
Where is the best restaurant
around here?
Restaurant?
My lady.
The Xichun House is the best.
Xichun House?
Chef.
I want all
the best dishes you've got.
If the food tastes good,
the Princess will reward you.
She won't be disappointed.
Tofu Skin Spinach Rolls.
It can increase your appetite
and help digestion.
Reward him.
Mianyang Steam.
Fresh, tender and soft.
Fat but not greasy.
I like this one.
Reward him again.
Fried cabbage.
It can strengthen your bones
and soothe your organs.
-So many food. -Awesome.
Reward him again.
Great.
That's a lot.
So much food.
So much...
I've never had
something like this.
I've never seen...
Look at all the dishes.
His lordship said he wanted to have dinner.
The Princess then
invited the best chef in town.
You are right.
Everyone will envy him.
Guys,
that's some benefits we got
following Lord Shen.
Hear, hear.
Luo.
Look at this one.
It looks so delicious.
Yes.
It looks so good.
And so green.
Speaking of green,
who is as green as that Mr. Green?
Why are you all standing?
Have a seat and eat with me.
-Thank you, Your Highness. -Thank you so much.
Ling Bi.
Go ask Lord Shen to join us.
Yes.
This seat is saved for Lord Shen.
-Move. -Move.
Mr. Lu has sharp eyes.
When Lord Shen comes,
he won't be able to eat under your watchful eyes.
Luo Fan.
Block it.
Go.
Go. Go.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Your Highness.
I've got wind of
people talking in Yejing.
They said that Yun Yi, the prime culprit
behind Jiangzhou Treasury Silver Robbery
has been captured by Jinlin Guard
sent by your Highness.
Is that true?
Shen Yan did mention this capture
in the letter he sent to me.
Your Highness is very decisive and effective.
It's a blessing for the people of Wei.
[Lord Xu]
I'd like to propose a toast
to your Highness.
I wish your Highness every success!
You are all indispensable
to the Wei.
Please feel at home tonight.
Father appreciated your hard work.
You and I
will hold this banquet here in the Eastern Palace.
Let's not talk about national affairs tonight.
I want all of you to drink as much as you want.
And enjoy the night.
Cheers!
Thank you, Your Highness.
Did you hear that?
His Highness just mentioned
the name of the second son of Family Shen.
Seems like Lord Shen has a young successor.
You will not have to worry about your future.
[Lord Shen]
Lord Lu,
we are no match to him now.
Back then,
my son made a grave mistake
in the old Jiangzhou Case.
Our Xu Family also suffered because of this.
His Majesty is kind and generous.
He spared the lives
-of my family. -Your Highness.
For so many years,
I've been feeling uneasy.
I wonder...
His Highness ordered
to re-investigate this case.
Could there be more
than we saw of this case?
The only thing His Highness cares about
is the Treasury Silver
that went missing.
If there's indeed something more behind this case
that could clear the name of Family Xu.
That would be great.
But I'm afraid
that after investigating,
they didn't find anything.
Instead, after being solved
for so many years,
this case managed to get noticed by His Majesty.
By then,
I don't know
if it's a blessing or a curse for you, Lord Xu.
What do you think, Lord Shen?
As far as I'm concerned,
a blessing, a curse,
what will happen will happen.
Why are the three of us sitting here
speculating others for no reason?
I suggest
that we drink
as much as we can.
Come on. Bottoms up!
Cheers.
You're so thoughtful, Lord Lu.
But Yun Yi
was arrested
by the second son of the Family Shen.
The rumor
has been widely spread in Yejing.
A blessing, or a curse.
I'm afraid we'll find out soon.
Why are you so worried, Lord Xu?
If I remembered correctly,
the Xu and Shen Family
almost became in-laws.
Why is this marriage
dropped afterwards?
I guess Miss Xu
must feel proud and superior.
Anyway,
although she didn't marry the young Lord Shen,
since she entered the Royal Palace,
she has made her way up to the Prince's side.
Remarkable skills.
From now on, the Crown Prince will support Family Xu.
Even if something bad happens,
Family Xu will be able to avoid bad luck,
and get a blessing instead of a curse.
She's just a court lady.
She can't be that lucky.
Speaking of which,
why didn't I see
your youngest son come to the banquet today?
He's just a son of a concubine.
I wouldn't count on him to be successful.
Well,
I heard that his betrothed,
Princess Changle is on her way to the Capital City.
He was ready early in the morning
and went outside of the city to wait for her.
Shen Yu,
what a thankless role you played.
These old foxes
fight against each other.
Now you are caught in the crossfire, too.
Such good liquor.
Now I have no appetite.
-Why isn't he here yet? -Is he coming?
Where is Lord Shen?
He said he's not hungry.
He's not eating tonight.
Come on, let's eat.
Stop.
Eat.
Go get me a lunch box.
This one.
And that one.
Come on...
Hurry up.
That one.
Your Highness.
-I don't want to hear it. -The lord doesn't...
What should we do?
Should we eat first
or watch the drama first?
Are you stupid?
Of course we're eating while watching.
Come on.
You should have told me earlier.
Lord Shen.
Would you like to try the food?
They cooked so many delicious dishes.
You really don't want to try?
It smells so nice.
Do you want to try it?
It's mouthwatering.
Ling Bi, check the door.
Is the door locked?
Lord Shen.
I brought you some tasty
Eight Treasure Duck Gizzards,
Phoenix Tail Shark Fin,
Dried Scallops Balls,
Buddhist Hand Pork Rolls.
You scared me.
Your Highness,
you don't know yet, do you?
Lord Shen is different from us.
Different how?
Tell me.
Our Lord Shen
doesn't eat meat.
He's vegetarian.
Vegetarian?
He's a grown man.
Why is he picky about food like a child?
You're right.
Vegetarian.
All the chicken, duck and fish.
Seems like we have to eat for Lord Shen.
Luo Fan,
you knew that
Lord Shen doesn't eat meat.
You deliberately
lied to our Princess, didn't you?
I...
Your Highness,
why do you bother so much
to please our lord?
You are already betrothed to a man.
Even if you go out alone,
you don't need to make it so wildly known.
Besides,
your future...
Mr. Green,
no,
Mr. Lu
is watching over there.
It's none of your business.
Ling.
Come with me. We need to talk.
Come.
-Let go. -Your Highness.
The young couple are talking.
Why are you interrupting?
No, you...
You are senseless.
Stop eating!
I...
Let go of me!
Come here.
Liu Ling.
Stop playing
and put an end to this farce!
You're not a kid anymore.
You should know
what our marriage means.
I don't.
I don't want to know either.
It doesn't matter if you don't want to know.
But let me tell you this,
this is not
just about the two of us.
This is about the House of Prince Guangping
and Family Lu. It's huge.
I respect you in front of everybody
because I like you,
and because I respect
Prince Guangping.
But if you keep
behaving like this,
the Lu family
will not treat you like before.
I won't be able to save you then.
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing at you.
You keep talking about marriage
and something huge.
It's like you already have it all.
But in the end,
you don't even
know the woman you will marry.
It's okay.
Let me tell you this.
The favorite thing
Princess Changle likes to do
is to embarrass
those hypocrites
in front of everybody.
Liu Ling!
You really think you are so popular, don't you?
Well then you're wrong.
Other women at your age
are already married.
It's just my friendly advice.
If you miss this marriage
to Family Lu.
Even if you have this
Princess title,
you'll never ever get married.
So what?
The misfortune of women in the world
is mostly caused by marriage.
If I, Liu Ling,
can't find someone
I truly love,
I'd rather stay single forever.
Your Highness.
Sorry that I'm not feeling so well.
Please excuse me.
In that case,
Lord Lu,
you should leave and rest early.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
I think I caught a cold
and have a headache.
I think I'll take a leave from Your Highness.
I shall take my leave.
Jin.
If you really want to leave,
you can go back and rest.
But don't worry.
I will ask Lord Xu
to pay you a visit later.
Thank you for your understanding, Your Highness.
Court Lady Xu.
Go get His Highness' cloak.
The night is cold, and the wine is strong.
Don't let His Highness catch a cold.
Yes.
Also,
after getting the cloak,
prepare the Tai Qing Red Cloud Wine.
After a while,
His Highness will want to treat the lords
with something light.
Jin.
You are being so considerate of me.
How can I
let you go?
If that's the case,
I’m afraid I’ll let you down.
I'll take my leave.
Eunuch Li.
Send Lord Xu to the Eastern Palace.
Yes.
It's a small world, isn't it?
Did something bother you, Court Lady Xu?
That's why you're leaving.
Isn’t it the same for you, Lord Shen?
The wine in the Palace is good,
but drinking it,
can't make me happy.
Lord Shen is a simple person.
You need to be at ease while drinking.
The Palace makes one feel restrained.
No matter how good the wine is,
I'm afraid you can't taste it.
What an interpretation.
No wonder Court Lady Xu
can win over the Prince
and became so successful in the Eastern Palace.
It's just a small trick.
It's nothing impressive for Lord Shen.
I dare not disturb your good mood.
I shall take my leave.
It's hard to walk at night.
Court Lady Xu,
be careful.
Please don't let me bother you.
I'm already used to it,
walking in the dark in the Palace.
My lord.
Lord Shen.
You've been busy all day.
Have something to eat.
My lord.
Does the fish we're catching
really have something to do with the Family Lu?
I wasn't sure before.
After this whole Princess business,
I’m sure of it.
What do you mean?
Lu Mingshan is arrogant.
If he really came here
as the the future husband
of Princess,
after being humiliated by the Princess,
even he didn't dare cancel the engagement,
he should at least have left.
But now?
In order to stay in Liaison Office,
he doesn't care about his reputation.
So, my Lord.
you purposely didn't come out of your room today
to provoke Princess Changle?
Shen Yan.
Shen Yan, come out!
You...
Are you really not willing to see me?
My lord,
why don't you...
You really gonna ignore me?
Fine.
[Toilet]
Your Highness.
Fine.
I can't do it anymore.
Your Highness.
Luo.
I can't hold it anymore.
Please go and beg her.
Why is it always me?
-I... -You're the most experienced with her.
Luo, please. I beg you.
Besides...
-We can't walk. -Go!
She...
Princess! Princess!
Please, Your Highness.
-What? -Please have mercy.
Please let us through.
I beg you.
What did I do?
What do you want?
Just one joss stick's time.
Just one joss stick, Your Highness.
After that,
I'll ask them to come out in time.
Yes.
We'll do whatever you want us to do.
I beg you, Your Highness.
You want to use the toilet?
One joss stick's time, two joss sticks' time.
I won't stop you
even if you sleep in there.
Fine.
But you need
to let me see Lord Shen first.
My goodness.
Princess, please don't whistle.
Stop whistling.
I can't hold it anymore.
Come in.
My lord.
My lord, my good lord.
I beg you.
We really have no choice.
We can't stand it anymore.
Ignore her.
Just go to the toilet as usual.
How can we ignore her, my lord?
When we are in the toilet,
thinking that the Princess is outside...
W-Who can ignore her?
Then go outside.
Outside?
There hasn't been scented.
Those poisonous insects in the wild...
are d-
dangerous for a reason,
my lord.
Please, my good lord.
Please help us.
I can't...
Hurry up, my lord.
-Right here. -He's here.
My lord!
My lord! My lord! Help!
My lord.
Lord Shen is here.
Finally wanna see me?
Make way, Your Highness.
Don't make things difficult for us.
No.
We haven't talked yet.
I can't leave.
You mean it?
Yes.
Then sorry in advance.
Your Highness.
I'll go first.
Don't push. I'll go first.
Stop fighting!
I'm so close...
Stop!
It's late at night.
Now you locked me
in your room, Lord Shen.
For what?
For protecting others from your harassment,
I'm here
because I want to tell you
in person.
My engagement with Lu Mingshan
was made by Prince Guangping alone.
I don’t like him.
Nor will I marry him.
So,
are you relieved now?
Yes.
Whether you marry him or not is your business.
It has nothing to do with me.
Why should I not be relieved?
Shen Yan, you...
You don't trust me?
You know what?
If the princess doesn't leave,
we won't have one good day.
You're right.
Alright, Princess.
Go back.
Save all your tricks
for Yejing
and use them to your Mr. Lu.
My tricks
can’t be saved for Yejing.
Guards!
Let me out!
Lord Shen!
What are you doing, Lord Shen?
What?
-Let me out! -Lord Shen!
Y-You dare assault our princess!
I'm a Princess.
How could you lock me
in your room?
-Your Highness! -Lord Shen!
Lord Shen.
Why did you blow out the candles?
Help!
Guard Yang.
Don't shout.
What's going on?
Y-Your lord
assaulted our Princess!
Nonsense.
-Don't talk nonsense. -Yeah.
I'm telling the truth!
What are you talking about?
-Our lord is not that kind of person. -Stop, Lord Shen!
How do you know what kind of person he is?
You're bullying me!
Lord Shen,
why did you
lock me up in here?
Lord Shen.
Don't come over!
Lord Shen!
Liu Ling.
Are you out of your mind?
You don't believe me.
Of course I have to prove it to you.
People will talk.
Before I'm in Yejing,
you will be mine.
Are you threatening me?
What if I am?
Help!
Is anyone here?
Shen Yan.
Why did you stop yelling, Princess?
I will yell.
Since you are determined
to get involved with me,
I’ll make it clear.
We are not the same kind of people.
Right now,
maybe you want to make things difficult for me,
or
maybe you just want to have fun.
But I’m not an easy person.
Once I think you're The One,
I will be yours
forever.
By then,
even if you are annoyed
and tired of me,
and had your fun,
I will follow you wherever you go.
You can’t get rid of me.
I suggest you think about it.
Are you ready for this?
Liu Ling.
Listen carefully.
I'm not someone you can mess with.
Put on your clothes
And get lost.
Your Highness.
Why did she stop yelling?
Princess, what's wrong?
Princess, are you alright?
What's wrong?
Your Highness.
Is she crying?
Not just crying.
Yes.
She's crying with her clothes mussed up
and ran out of
the lord's room.
-Luo. -Luo.
Did something went wrong?
Something happened?
Is that true, Luo?
Wait here. I'll go check it out.
Go ahead.
Go.
-Go! -Go!
My lord.
The princess was...
What?
S-She went back to her room.
It's windy outside.
I...
I'll close the door for you.
Court Lady Xu.
Lord Xu is here with the imperial doctor.
Come in.
Girl.
I heard that His Highness said
you didn't feel well during the banquet.
I've brought an imperial doctor
to take care of you.
It's okay, grandpa.
I'll be fine after some rest.
Court Lady Xu is all well in general.
She's just over-thinking
and has some disorder in heart and spleen.
Besides,
she might have caught a cold at night,
which explains her headache.
She will be fine after taking medicine.
I'll go prepare the medicine for the Court Lady.
I've brought
the person you asked.
Come in.
His name is Ghost-face.
He's a mute.
He won't show his face
because his face was injured.
He is a bit strange,
but he's loyal
and skilled in martial arts.
You can rest assured.
The news of Yun Yi's arrest
has spread so fast in Yejing.
It’s beyond my expectation.
After today's banquet,
the Family Lu
will be restless.
Ghost-face.
In the following days,
you will keep an close eye
on Family Lu.
Once they take action,
you must report to me immediately.
[Lu Mansion]
Greetings, my lord.
Is Shan there now?
Don't worry, my lord.
Young Master sent a letter today.
He's made his way
into the Liaison Office
as the Princess' betrothed.
What about the Tiger Wings Camp?
Are they ready?
Before Master Lu left,
he had made sure everything is ready.
Tiger Wings Camp will join him
in three days.
We can't wait any longer.
The day after tomorrow.
No.
You will set out tomorrow.
Tell Shan for me
to do it as soon as possible
in case there will be more troubles.
Yes.
Right now,
maybe you want to make things difficult for me,
or maybe you just
want to have fun with me.
But I
am not an easy person.
Once I think you're The One,
I will be yours
forever.
Listen carefully.
I'm not someone you can mess with.
Put on your clothes
And get lost!
Come in.
My lord,
this is the latest pigeon mail.
Please have a look.
I'll take my leave.
Greetings, Shen Yan.
The trap is set.
Be careful.
The prey is cunning and suspicious.
Be careful not to fall into the water if you fail to catch,
and suffer a double loss.
Your Highness, the water is here.
Your Highness.
Lord Shen.
Our princess is missing.
I've searched everywhere
and she's not here.
[I will get lost.]
I will get lost.
The enemy is in front of us.
And the Princess went out alone.
I will find her myself.
But...
Come here.
C-Can I do it?
Don't worry.
Tomorrow morning,
just do as I say.
I’ll take care
of the Princess' safety.
Lord Shen,
you must bring
our Princess back.
Let's set out.
Come in.
How is it?
Hu Xiao.
Have you seen him clearly?
Even bandits like Hu Xiao
were under his command.
The Family Lu is truly outrageous.
Now they dare to do
something so bold as
to kill someone.
Ghost-face.
Meet up with Shen Yan as soon as possible
and help the Jinlin Guard protect the camp.
I'm safe here in the Palace.
But Ling is not.
Take care of her for me.
If things went south,
just make sure Ling is alive.
Anything else
is irrelevant.
Ling, Ling.
Of all the places you could be,
why did you have to go there?
What should I do
if something happens to you?