[English subtitles are available]
[My Sassy Princess]
[Episode 14]
Kill!
Lianshan did ask someone
to hand over the box of the Kun jade
to me.
In the box
there was a handwriting letter of him.
In the letter,
he said
he risked his life
to steal money from the Jiangzhou treasury.
If he came back alive,
it meant he got rid of
those spies.
By then,
both of us
could take the money
and change our names
and live a carefree and wealthy life.
If he couldn't come back,
I can
make myself a Qian and Kun jade
to open the box
and get the money alone.
Lianshan
did such evil things,
but he never wants me to
get involved in the conflicts
between the government and Family Lu.
He kept reminding me
not to
revenge.
But you just said
Lianshan asked you to come to me
for the
box of Qian and Kun jade
in order to avenge him.
This is not
what Lianshan would do.
That's right.
The box you want
is indeed
in my hands.
But unfortunately,
there's only one box.
If any of you can survive to the end,
I will
give it to him.
I'm just a warrior.
I'm not
as graceful as you.
For you,
you can refuse to give the box of Qian and Kun jade
to the the Jinlin Guard
or Family Lu,
but if
Lady-in-waiting Xu outside
asks it from you,
you definitely can't refuse her.
My lord,
what do you mean?
In your eyes,
Lu Lianshan is your beloved disciple.
You treats him like your own son.
But in Lady-in-waiting Xu's eyes,
Lu Lianshan
is a villain who
worships money
and killed her parents.
The Lady-in-waiting's surname is Xu.
Could it be...
Yes.
In the Jiangzhou case,
the Xu couple who believed in Lu Lianshan
and was framed as the main culprit,
and ended up with death with unjust
are her parents.
Mr. Lu He.
The tea
is cold.
Mr. Lu He.
Don't break your promise!
The game is over.
You should keep your promise
and hand over the box of Qian and Kun jade.
You said
you lost your son,
and couldn't let it go.
But Lady-in-waiting Xu
lost her parents at an young age
just because of your son.
Don't you think
you should apologize to
Lady-in-waiting Xu?
Sir,
I've been planning for years.
I'm here today
to bring the real criminal
of the Jiangzhou Case into justice
and clear my parents' name.
Please give me the box
to help me express my filial devotion to my parents.
Please rise.
I feel unworthy of
your courtesy.
The innocence of the Xu family
was owed by Lianshan.
The box of Qian and Kun jade...
Just
take it.
The crime committed by my disciple
hurt your family so much.
I
cannot deny it.
I feel guilty.
I hope
the thing in this box
can fulfill your wish
of clearing Family Xu's name.
Thank you, sir.
[Duke Dingbei's Mansion]
Is this your house?
Isn't it big?
Look.
There is a backyard.
Princess.
Ning?
Brother Hong?
Yuan Zhelin!
I've been wandering around for three years.
I've been looking for you for three years.
Since you're still alive,
why didn't you send a message
to me?
Ning.
Listen to me.
-I... -Shut up!
I'll kill you!
Ning.
So,
Yang Ye
is her Brother Hong.
It was Yang Ye who offended you.
Why are you fighting with this bottle?
He's not Yang Ye.
He's Yuan Zhelin.
Is he really
your Brother Hong,
or Yuan Zhelin?
It's a long story.
Three years ago,
Yuan promised to
retire
and live with me.
But he was
the leader of the best assassin gang
of the martial world.
It was not that easy
to escape safely.
As a leader,
he can't decide where to go.
Yuan Zhelin was planning
to retire.
The elders of the gang
knew they couldn't keep him.
After discussion,
they decided to make him
do something big for the gang.
That is to challenge
the masters of
the Four Righteous Sects
in the martial world.
Only Yuan and the four masters
knew the place
of the battle that day.
Nobody had the chance to watch it.
I was waiting for news at home.
I heard
he defeated the four masters.
I was very happy.
I thought as long as he came back,
I could be with him forever.
We could live a carefree life
together.
But I waited for him day after day,
and he never came back.
Now it seems
he must have been
severely injured
in that fierce battle.
After that, he ended up in Jiangzhou,
and was accidentally rescued
by you.
I thought
he was a hero.
I didn't expect
his background is so complicated.
You saved his life.
I have nothing to say if he wants to repay you.
But it's been three years.
Over 1,000 days and nights,
I was looking for him everywhere.
I was afraid he would be killed by his enemies.
I couldn't sleep tight.
But what about him?
He didn't even send a message
to me.
Maybe
he
did
send you a message.
In the past three years,
you've been traveling around
to look for him.
If he wrote to you,
you may fail to receive.
That's just an excuse.
If he wanted to tell me,
he will find me.
I, Qin Ning,
swear to revenge!
Still want to revenge?
When you were fighting just now,
he was obviously giving ground.
Even if you want him to die now,
he will give his life to you.
Heroine Qin,
do you really want to kill him
to solve the problem?
Qin Ning.
Life is short.
It's a pity for you
to waste three years.
The top priority now is not
how to take revenge.
You should think about
how to stop him from repaying me
so that you can leave
and live together.
To repay you?
Yes.
Why didn’t I think of it?
Ling,
you enlightened me!
You are really my lucky star.
Yuan Zhelin
wanted to repay you for saving his life.
But for three years,
he hasn't found the opportunity.
If I can
repay you
before he does,
does that mean
he owes me
another big favor?
Then,
he has to think about
how to repay me.
He will rack his brains.
Then my revenge plan
will finish.
No.
That's not what I meant.
Calm down.
Let me think about
how to repay your kindness.
I'll discuss with you later.
How can I
repay your kindness?
You go on.
I'm going to bed.
If he can...
Today, the crown prince
summoned you to the palace.
What are you talking about?
What was he up to?
He began with some gossip,
and then we tried to sound out.
Maybe
he has noticed
what you and I planned?
Under such a circumstance,
how can you still laugh?
The father hid behind
and just sent his little son
to talk with me.
Isn't it funny?
Father, don't worry.
As long as what I'm doing in the camp
goes well,
we will succeed.
Then not to mention Liu Wang,
even His Majesty won't be a threat.
But as for the military expenses,
you need to work harder.
Tell me, how much more do you need?
Five million taels.
Liu Lishan,
do you want to
impoverish me?
What if I say yes?
Father,
you forced me
to marry your daughter
into our House of Guangping Prince
with the money of Jiangzhou
as a bargaining chip.
Weren't you planning for
the current situation?
Don't hesitate.
If I can succeed,
your family will be royal family.
If not,
the crime of treason
will cause execution.
Five million taels is not a small amount.
It will take some time.
Father,
be quick.
Your Highness,
even you know
Yigu State came to pay tribute.
It's such an honor to the state.
The situation is turbulent.
I heard that the emperor of Yigu
exhausted all resources to build up the military power.
I'm afraid he has been disloyal for a long time.
This time,
they came when the crown prince is in charge of supervising the state.
We should be careful.
In your opinion,
besides the tribute,
do they
have other plans?
I don't care.
As long as the request is not too much,
I believe
His Highness
will give them what they want.
Lord Li.
Summon Tuoba Lie.
Summon the Crown Prince of Yigu, Tuoba Lie.
[The Crown Prince of Yigu State, Tuoba Lie]
The Crown Prince of Yigu, Tuoba Lie,
is here to greet you, Your Highness.
You don't have to be so polite.
Please rise.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I heard that the Emperor of Wei
is sick.
My father couldn't sleep or eat well.
He ordered me to
bring some
rare herbs from Yigu to His Majesty
to show our sincerity.
I hope
the Emperor of Wei
can get well soon.
[List of tributes]
The Tuoba family is so thoughtful.
My father
is fine.
He was just busy with the court affairs.
So he was a little upset.
He
is resting in the palace.
Look at me.
I've been busy talking
with you.
I forgot to ask you
about an important matter.
I heard that at this time last year,
your father went hunting
and fell off the horse,
and was badly injured.
I wonder
whether he has recovered?
Thank you for your concern.
My father has recovered now.
It's just a minor injury.
No need to worry.
That's great.
Brother Tuoba,
you've been traveling
for a long time.
I've ordered someone to prepare a room for you.
You
can take a rest.
Later,
I'll hold a banquet
in the Eastern Palace
to welcome you.
Your Highness.
We didn't come here
just to pay tribute.
There is one more thing.
I hope Your Majesty and Your Highness could kindly permit.
Please go ahead.
Although I'm the Crown Prince of Yigu,
I haven't got a wife.
Following
my father's order,
I come here to
beg your permission
to allow me to marry a princess of Wei.
I hope Your Majesty and Your Highness
could help me
fulfill my wish.
The marriage will be a bond between our two countries
and a symbol of peace.
I already know
your request.
By the way,
I heard
you
and Lu Mingshan
got along well with each other.
I'll let him
accompany you to travel around the capital
for a few days.
As for the marriage,
let me
think about it.
I will surely give you
a satisfying answer.
Good.
I'll
wait for the good news.
How dare a barbarian
ask permission to
marry the Princess of Wei?
A symbol
of peace?
His disloyal heart
is already obvious.
Lord Li,
ask Lord Xu and Lord Shen
to the Eastern Palace for a meeting.
As for the rest,
let them go.
I don't want to see those losers.
You saw
what happened in the palace just now.
Tell me what you think.
Your Highness.
I think
Tuoba Lie
took the opportunity
of paying tribute
to propose marriage.
It's obviously a test.
Last year,
they sent us a thousand boxes of pearls and jade.
But this year only a hundred.
Last years they sent us a hundred steeds.
This years only cows and sheep.
In your opinion,
should I approve of
the marriage
or not?
Your Highness.
You shouldn't
approve
or
disapprove.
What do you mean?
If Your Highness doesn't allow the marriage,
it will hurt the Tuoba family's reputation.
After he goes back,
he will use this as an excuse
to lead troops into the border.
If it's approved,
even if it solves the urgent matter,
but
they will find that
we are unwilling to start a war.
In the future,
they'll push us step by step.
The Tuoba family
only occupies a tiny piece of land.
In terms of wealth and military power,
how can it compare with Wei?
Instead of waiting for Yigu to attack us,
it's better for Wei
to deploy troops now
and strike first.
Your Highness,
I don't think it's appropriate.
If the war starts,
the people will suffer.
This is not
what you want to see.
In my opinion,
if Tuoba Lie
brings this up
again,
you may agree first
and choose a suitable candidate
to marry him.
That will
delay their plans.
And in this way,
you prioritize the welfare of the people
over the dignity of the royal family.
There is a saying that
a man who is not content is like a snake which tries to swallow an elephant.
When Tuoba Lie
gets carried away
or offends the dignity of Wei,
you can discuss with His Majesty
how to deploy troops.
Trying fair means before resorting to force.
What a brilliant idea, Lord Xu.
We will have room for manoeuvre.
Very good.
Lord Xu.
if it weren't for
the Jiangzhou case,
I think
you could have
enjoyed a higher rank
in Wei.
You flatter me, Your Highness.
After crossing the mountain ahead,
and then walking a few miles,
we will arrive at Yejing
within three days.
We've been on the go for days.
If you
feel tired,
I will go first,
and you can
walk slowly
with Ghost-face.
Let your feet have a rest.
It's fine.
Come to think of it,
I have been away from the capital
for a month.
I miss Ling
just like you do.
I want to go back as soon as possible.
Cheers, Brother Tuoba.
Crown Prince Tuoba,
you came all the way to the capital.
You must be exhausted.
Shan and I reserved
the Flower Pavilion
to entertain you.
I wonder whether the dance today
satisfies you.
The dance is not bad.
But...
When I proposed in the palace that day,
your crown prince
promised me that
he would give me
a satisfying answer.
But so many days have passed.
I haven't heard from him.
It seems
he looks down on
the Yigu State,
a small place near the border.
You worry too much.
Although Wei
is a large state,
but it's actually
outwardly strong but inwardly weak.
But Yigu is totally different.
With heroes like you
and the king of Yigu,
the Yigu State
will be
thriving and flourishing.
Bravo!
Brother Tuoba,
if you like the girl who is dancing,
after she finishes this song,
I'll order someone
to send her to your room,
and you can have an intimate talk.
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Young Master.
I heard that
Tiger Shou failed in Xuanwu Town.
He was killed by Shen Yan.
Where is the thing?
If the information is correct,
the thing
has fallen into Shen Yan's hands.
OK, I see.
You may leave.
OK.
Brother Lu,
the princess who
your crown prince will allow to marry me
should be
no less beautiful than
these girls.
Otherwise,
I won't accept it.
Brother Tuoba,
the Yigu State
is quite powerful now.
I think
instead of waiting for the approval,
you can choose a lady
you like
from the royal families.
Then you may ask permission from the crown prince.
If you just wait here,
I'm afraid you'll miss
an exceedingly beautiful noble lady.
Among the noble families of Wei,
is there an exceedingly beautiful lady?
If you don't believe me,
come with me
to see her.
Add wine and light up to have another feast.
Ling Bi.
I don't know what's wrong with me today.
I feel very nervous.
I quit.
Why is it so hard
to embroider Shen Yan's name?
So complicated!
I won't finish
before he comes back.
Don't be angry, Your Highness.
If you
think it's too complicated,
you can just embroider
two vertical bars
to represent the two characters.
That will save us a lot of trouble.
How dare you make fun of me?
I’ll beat you!
Ling.
Hurry.
I know
how to repay
your kindness as soon as possible.
Come with me.
Hurry up.
Where are we going?
Qin Ning.
Does your way to repay my kindness
has anything to do with the well?
It has something to do with the well.
I'll ask the Ling Bi
to bring Yuan Zhelin here.
When he comes,
you pretend to
accidentally fall into this well.
Then I will throw this bucket
down.
You just need to hold this bucket.
And then I'll
pull it up...
This...
This way doesn't work.
It's more effective to hang yourself from a beam.
You just need to stand on the chair.
When you kick the chair,
I will throw out my dagger.
Forget it.
I think you should
listen to me.
Just forget it.
Actually, I know
my methods
are against justice.
But
if I can end this matter,
I wouldn't have
made things difficult for you.
I know Yuan so well.
If he doesn't repay your kindness,
he won't leave with me.
Do you
really want to repay?
As soon as possible.
Alright.
You helped me
in front of Mrs. Shen.
I should help you this time.
Ling.
Are you serious?
Yes.
But we have a deal.
You have to follow my advice.
I'll listen to you.
[Duke Dingbei's Mansion]
My lord, you're here.
The Crown Prince of Tuoba condescends to
Duke Dingbei's Mansion.
We're honored to have you here.
Please.
Is Duke Dingbei here?
He has been waiting for a long time.
Please.
Father.
He's here.
I'm Lu Mingshan.
Greetings, My lord.
My lord.
This is the Crown Prince of Yigu,
Tuoba Lie.
Why don't you salute me
when you see me?
Well, you
confused me.
You are
the Crown Prince of Yigu.
I'm a minister of Wei.
We have nothing to do
with each other.
Salute?
Why should I salute you?
I could have refused to see you
since you came without informing me beforehand.
But considering
your father was a hero,
I give you some respect.
Tell me.
What brings you here
out of a sudden?
Good.
Straightforward.
I like it.
I came to the capital of Wei
to
marry a noble lady of Wei
to be
my Crown Princess.
I heard Princess Changle
is exceedingly beautiful.
So,
please ask her
to come here.
Let me
take a good look.
Crown Prince Tuoba,
if you're here for this,
I'll have to disappoint you.
Ling is not feeling well.
She can't come out.
Please go back.
Damn old man.
Calm down, Brother Tuoba.
Duke Dingbei has always been like this.
Don't take it seriously.
Let's go.
I heard Princess Wuyou
instigated Princess Changle to jump into the river.
I think we should forget it.
Ling.
Don’t be afraid.
Just close your eyes
and jump down.
I promise
nothing will happen.
You...
That's easy for you to say.
You're not repaying my kindness for Yang Ye.
You're obviously seeking revenge!
I'm repaying you.
Of course.
My dear Ling.
As long as you
fulfill my wish today,
I, Qin Ning,
will remember your kindness forever.
All right.
Over there.
Shen Yan,
for all these years, I've worked so hard,
but you ruined all of my efforts.
I should
repay you today.
You...
Who are you?
Shameless!
Gather your sweet rosebuds while you may.
Since you like
Princess Changle,
why don't you go to the palace
and ask the crown prince for permission?
Duke Dingbei is so tough.
What if the crown prince
doesn't approve?
Now the army of Yigu is strong.
Yigu is so powerful now.
And the Emperor of Wei
wants to avoid war.
If he doesn't agree,
why don't you
threaten him with the war?
Don't worry.
What you want is just a marriage.
Compared to the safety of the Wei people,
which is more important?
Are you still afraid
you can't get what you want?
[Duke Dingbei's Mansion]
The emperor issued this imperial edict:
Princess Changle, Liu Ling,
is noble, virtuous and polite.
Knowledgeable and intelligent.
elegant and prudent.
She has served the palace for a long time.
She has been a comfort to me.
I'm conferring the title of Princess Peace to her.
I allow her to marry Tuobo Lie.
By the emperor himself.
Princess Peace,
accept the edict.
What are you waiting for?
Go comfort her.
Go.
Look.
Virtuous and polite.
Knowledgeable and intelligent.
Such a compliment!
Ling,
since you are conferred Princess Peace by His Majesty,
from now on,
you are a member of the royal family.
Ling,
congratulations!
What?
What are you talking about?
Our Ling
has been
a member of the royal family.
In addition to being conferred,
she will marry the Crown Prince of Yigu.
Now she is the Crown Princess.
In the future,
she will be the Empress of Yigu.
She will be above everyone.
What a blessing!
But I
don't want such a blessing.
Do you like it?
If you like it,
write a divorce letter,
and divorce my uncle.
I can ask His Majesty
to make you
become the distinguished empress.
You...
If the imperial edict was about me,
I would be so willing to marry him.
This...
How dare you!
Yang Ye,
get the carriage ready.
Move.
-You can't go. -You can't go.
If you break into the palace arbitrarily,
His Majesty will be angry.
Our family will be in trouble.
If she should go against His Majesty's will,
I'm afraid all of us in Duke Dingbei's Mansion
would be in great trouble!
Father,
you can't indulge her anymore.
Father, please discipline her.
Discipline her.
Ling.
Grandpa.
Are you going to stop me, too?
It's not easy to ask His Majesty
to retract the order.
I
have to go with you.
Let's go.
Father, you can't go! Father!
Move!
No, you really can't go, Father.
Father!
Father, you can't go!
This...
Oh no.
Our House of Duke Dingbei
is so miserable!
[Jinghe Palace]
What did His Majesty say?
Still the same.
Refuse to meet anyone.
Duke,
His Majesty is recuperating in the palace.
He won't see anyone without an edict.
You and princess broke into the palace like this.
It's against the heaven's will.
You should take the princess
to go back.
-Grandpa. -Duke Dingbei
and Princess Peace
are here to meet you, Your Majesty.
Please allow us, Your Majesty.
My dear duke,
you...
Why are you doing this?
Your request
really puts His Majesty in a difficult position.
His Majesty won't see you.
If you insist on it,
and it irritates His Majesty,
I am afraid that
something bad will happen.
Lord,
I understand
what you said.
But
I only have
one granddaughter.
She has suffered
a lot.
Well...
Grandpa.
Don't kneel anymore.
Since His Majesty wants me to marry him,
I should kneel myself.
This matter
has nothing to do with the House of Duke Dingbei.
Go back now.
Silly girl.
you can't
handle it
on your own.
It’s OK.
My body is not
as weak as you think.
Don’t worry.
Grandpa.