Quick, keep up
After them!
Catch them!
Looks like a dead end
Search carefully
Leave no one alive
Yes!
Ye Li
I'm scared
Don't be afraid
I'm here
Zhao Yun, look
Let me help you up
This is a dense forest
Let's go
Ye Li, I can't walk anymore
Why don't...
...we stay here together?
Here?
What's wrong?
Could it be...
...you want to be apart from me?
No
Something's wrong
It's an illusion from the Miasma
Ye Li
Do you want to leave me?
After the wedding bows...
...we will be a family
First bow to Heaven and Earth
Second bow to the high hall
Husband and wife bow to each other
Ye Li
There are no ghosts or gods in this world
Only inner demons
You must walk out of it
Ye Li
You're awake
Where is this?
You were affected by the Miasma
Let's go
We must leave here immediately
Zhao Yun
We're saved
What is going on?
Ye Li
I take Poison-Warding Pills year-round
My blood has medicinal power
Ye Li
Hold on a little longer
We're almost out
Why are you so foolish?
Zhao Yun
Hold on a bit longer
The Crown Prince and the others are here
We can go home
Ye Li
I'm not going
I'm tired
Ye Li
Don't be trapped in the past
Look to the road ahead
I don't want to
Zhao Yun
No!