Isn’t that Ma’am Luna?
- Ma'am Luna, please get down there!
- Ma'am Luna!
Get down from there!
Please don't jump, Ma'am!
Oh, no!
Ma’am, I’m done with the test.
Hi, Babe!
Hey, Babe. What’s that?
- I brought pizza. It’s still warm.
- Pizza.
Sir, please don’t fire me.
My wife is ill.
That’s your problem.
Had you been working hard,
I wouldn’t have fired you.
But, no. It’s been three days
and you haven’t finished the job yet.
But, Sir, the deliveries are delayed.
And we haven’t paid the suppliers yet.
Take care of him.
Yes, Sir. Let’s go!
Sir, please. I beg you, Sir.
- Don’t fire me, Sir.
- Go!
I beg you.
Boss!
You’re early.
My plans with Auntie got postponed.
Let’s eat.
Always better when it’s warm.
It's so good.
Do you know what tastes better?
You.
Wasn’t that Caloy?
Oh.
​Isn't he hardworking?
Don't meddle in my business.
Just prepare our dinner.
Let me take this, Ma’am.
No, it’s fine. I’ll help you
prepare dinner.
Where do you think you’re going.
You’re mine. I won’t stop.
​Enough. Please stop.
Babe, does the shampoo model
always have to be a sexy girl?
The consumers are just
ordinary girls, anyway.
So, why not use an ordinary woman?
Like Ms. Bebang?
Because, Babe, we’re selling a fantasy.
What the buyer could be.
Not what she is.
And why do you always
need to show the cleavage?
I can’t see the connection
between "boobs" and "shampoo."
Unless we’re supposed to shampoo our boobs.
Come on, Babe. Don’t be naïve.
We’re selling the whole package.
From the head to the…
Now I'm the naïve one?
I have work to do.
My deadline is in two weeks.
Us first.
The script can wait.
Make the script really sexy,
like you.
Fuck. It's so good.
Abe, stop. Does it
have to be every night?
You smell like medicinal oil.
Fool! You'll like it anyway!
​You’re so good, Arnold.
You’re better.
No. You’re better.
Do you really need to mind that?
I want to leave him, Auntie.
I can’t take it anymore.
I signed an agreement, Luna.
You’re up to your eyeballs in debt.
He’s not going to let you go.
Every time I go out of the house,
I feel like running away.
Just be patient.
I really don’t understand
why you still choose to work.
It’s the only time
I can escape from him.
He doesn’t treat his workers well, Auntie.
He treats them like slaves.
​That’s none of your business.
So, it’s also about control?
Not about who has
the say in the relationship?
Love should not be
equal to subservience.
Yes, from household chores
up to their sexual activities,
​including which brand
of toothpaste to buy,
or whose turn is it
to do the dishes,
it’s a question of who is in control.
I don’t agree.
Lines get blurred
when two people are in love.
It doesn’t matter
who has control.
Love is love.
So, what do you think?
Love should not be equal to subservience.
I personally don't mind doing
what my boyfriend wants me to do.
I don’t feel diminished
when I give him what he wants.
I love him.
Love is love.
I want him to be happy.
Love should not be equal to subservience.
Love is love.
Love should not be
equal to subservience.
- Love is love.
- Love should not be equal to subservience.
Love is love.
Roger!
​Stop or I’ll kill her!
Don’t come closer.
I'm not kidding!
Hand me the keys!
​I'm on my way home.
Just hand me the keys! Hurry!
I’ll shoot you. Hurry!
Run!
What are you doing?
My glasses.
Hurry!
I'm not going to hurt you.
I just need to get away.
I beg you. Please let me go.
Fuck! Shut up!
Get out! Hurry up!
Listen to me!
Come on! Someone might see us here.
Listen! Hurry!
- Where are you going?
- ​You don’t need me anymore.
Why don’t you just run away?
I’m sorry, but I need you
until I am sure I wasn’t followed.
Get in! Go. Get inside.
They're going for the both of us.
Stop fidgeting! Be grateful
I'm holding a gun.
Are you seriously about to piss yourself?
Let’s look for a bathroom upstairs. Relax!
You're going to get us both hurt!
Where are you going?
Don’t you dare!
Roger!
Damn this life!
Fuck! Where are you going? Sit down!
Just do what I say
if you don’t want to get hurt.
Sit!
Hey!
Where are you going?
Let go of me!
Shut up!
Don’t tie me up.
I won’t try to get away.
- Please don’t tie me up.
- Not gonna happen. Sit down!
Where's your phone?
You’re such a pain in the ass!
Please, I beg you.
Untie me.
Tomorrow, once I’m sure
we weren’t followed,
I’ll set you free.
Wouldn’t it be easier for you
if you don’t drag me along?
Didn’t you hear what I said?
I’ll let you go tomorrow.
It was so wrong
for you to take me.
You shouldn’t have involved me.
Will you shut up?
What if they saw the cab?
What if they find us?
You should have just ran away.
I said, shut up!
I have to go to the bathroom.
I need to pee.
And attempt to run away again?
Would you like me to take a leak here?
I won't run away. Promise.
Can you untie these?
"Don’t use the bathroom. It's out of order.
Use the bathroom outside."
What are you waiting for? Get in.
Wait.
Can’t you read?
The toilet’s clogged.
Clogged...
I’ll just pee outside.
No. You can’t go out.
Untie me, please.
Remove it yourself. Pee quickly. Come on.
Chief, it's been hours and you still
haven't found my wife.
You don't have any leads.
She's my wife.
Calm down, Abe.
Sir, what’s happening here?
Why are you not giving us any update?
We’ve been waiting for hours.
Thank you very much, Mr. Dizon.
This is a big deal for me and Bela.
As long as this will profit like we agreed.
We’ll do our best. For sure.
We’ll do our best.
- You have to make it sexy.
- Sexy.
- People want to see sex.
- Okay...
Bela’s already working on it.
Mr. Dizon, may I add...
your concepts are brilliant.
How do you even come up with them?
- Really?
- Yes.
I’ve got more where those came from.
My wife even said
that I should be a writer.
- See? A writer.
- I told her
a businessman is like a writer.
Both sell their products.
They're salesmen.
Am I right, Bela? Bela, right?
Yes, Sir.
But no, Sir.
I don’t think I got you right.
It depends on what’s being sold.
But we are not “salesmen.”
Although, I think that “salesperson”
is more appropriate.
It seems like you’ve been writing
a very good script, Arnold.
- For sure, it is, Mr. Dizon.
- This Bela seems good.
I like women who have ideas.
They’re fun to converse with.
So, when can I read the script?
Very soon, Sir.
I need time, Sir.
I would like to read
whatever you’ve finished.
I’m leaving for Belgium next week.
I can’t let you read it
until it’s done, Sir.
Because any changes to the last part
will affect the first part.
I don’t mind. Just don’t remove
the parts that I want.
Yup. We won’t.
I need you to be proactive.
- Proactive.
- More than breast exposure,
there should be some action.
Fondling or… whatever.
You know what I mean.
Friday, Sir.
Good!
The budget’s too small
for his expectations.
Let it go, Babe. We’re lucky
to have found a producer.
We should have just entered Cinemalaya
to make the film we really wanted to make.
We would still need a producer.
And besides, Mr. Dizon doesn’t want
to join Cinemalaya.
What if we propose a new material?
Babe...
Not as sexual as he wants.
Babe... that’s his material.
Changing it would offend him.
Why does everybody think
they can be writers?
Just because they come up with a concept
doesn’t mean they can write a screenplay.
That’s just a concept.
I agree. I understand you, okay?
But, please. Do this for me.
Why don’t you write it yourself, Babe?
You can do it.
You just need more confidence.
But, Babe.
- Why?
- I’m not a writer. You know that.
Sometimes I ask myself if
I’m really ready to direct, or…
maybe I’m just rushing.
You can do it. Whenever
you have doubts,
flashback!
Five years ago, do you remember
when we were at the UP lagoon?
We were lying down on
the grass, under the stars,
and we were dreaming
of our future.
You know what I remember from the lagoon?
What?
We had perfect sex.
Oh, you! Well…
It was good sex.
But it was more than that.
Of course.
We made a promise that you will become
a director and I, a scriptwriter.
You achieved yours. Three of your scripts
have been made into films.
You can do it, too. Your dream.
Our dream.
We’re lucky to find food here
and you’re not even eating.
Eat a little.
I’m sorry about
what happened to your friend.
I’m Luna.
How about you? What’s your name?
I know you’re not a criminal.
And...
I know why you don’t want to let me go.
You’re afraid to be alone.
You have no idea what to do
now that your buddy is gone.
I can help you.
If you surrender, I’ll tell them
you’ve been nice to me.
My husband might know someone.
He’s got connections.
He’ll help you.
Get off my back!
I’m sorry about the things I said.
I was blabbering because I was nervous.
I’m sorry if I aimed my gun at you.
I’m not a bad person.
I know.
We are not bad people.
The money we stole, it was ours.
Money that was being robbed from us,
workers, by Sir Louie.
And then he would
fire people just like that.
But your buddy is gone.
You’re alone now.
Instead of hiding,
you can turn yourself in.
You’ll have a chance to change.
But it’s too late.
It’s never too late when
doing the right thing.
Earlier at the bathroom,
I noticed that...
you can not read.
There’s nothing to be ashamed of.
Maybe, you weren’t given
a chance to study.
If you won't turn yourself in,
what is your plan?
I have no idea.
Uncle Roger, my buddy, planned
everything, where we should go,
what to do with the money...
But now that he’s gone,
I feel lost. Uncle Roger
was like a father to me.
He took me out of the streets.
You know what? Life hasn’t been
that good to me either.
My mom, she needed to undergo surgery.
But hospitals wouldn’t accept us
because we can’t afford it.
Our medical bills reached a million.
So I married Abe.
He took care of the bills.
Now I'm stuck with him.
How’s your mother now?
She died two weeks after the surgery.
Thank you.
I only reached second grade.
So I didn’t learn how to read.
Where were your parents?
I don’t know.
I was essentially an orphan
until Uncle Roger took me in.
I married his daughter, Nelia.
But she died giving birth.
What was your job at the factory?
They hired you despite
being unable to read?
I worked different jobs at the factory
given my limitation.
It was Uncle Roger who brought me in, too.
But that factory treated us like slaves.
It must be a struggle
not knowing how to read.
I don't need to know how.
I read the things around me
but not through letters of the alphabet.
What do you mean?
Every object has a written name, right?
Instead of reading their names,
I observe them.
A chair, a piece of steel,
a wall, a pillow...
Everything is alive to me.
I can hear them. All I need
to do is close my eyes,
and listen to their heartbeat.
I don’t need to learn
how to write their names
because I’ve always
known who they are.
All you need to do is touch them,
close your eyes,
and try to feel their heartbeat.
How’s it going?
I can’t do it.
Why, Babe? Is there a problem?
They’ll have sex just like that?
The woman will give in
on their first night?
Why not? That can happen.
Luna is sexy.
She doesn’t love her husband.
Diego is a man.
It’s wrong.
Well then, you can change it
if you want.
I think it’s actually better if
Luna resists then Diego rapes her.
No. What I mean is why does
everything have to lead to sex?
That’s one of Mr. Dizon’s suggestions.
Sex while the girl is tied up. Remember?
So I don’t understand
why you untied her.
No…
I don’t want the girl to seem subjugated.
She shouldn’t be tied up.
But is that not the theme of your story?
That she has no freedom,
and this will be her liberation.
She is a hostage not just at the house,
but in her marriage as well.
And the guy is her savior?
Why not? Isn’t that
the story's direction?
Does a girl have no purpose other than sex?
Can we just let him have this?
Let’s just give Mr. Dizon what he wants.
I swear it won’t look gratuitous
when I mount the sex scene.
What if we reverse their roles?
Luna becomes the abductor.
No! Please!
Or Diego is a ghost.
He was shot and killed
along with his buddy.
Sex with a ghost? That isn’t sexy.
Babe, let’s not make this difficult for us.
Let’s just give Mr. Dizon
what he wants so he won’t back out.
Alright, fine. You write it
how you want it, okay?
But please meet the deadline. Okay?
We might just convince Mr. Dizon.
Just please finish it.
I have an idea! This is what I’ll do.
It will be a sex scene,
but it’s not physical.
They will make love through words.
She teaches him how to write the names
of the parts of the body.
She spells the words..
S...
And he spells them back.
- U...
- S...
- O...
Breast...
Breast.
- H...
- I...
- T...
- A...
- Thigh.
- L...
- A...
B...
- I...
- Lips.
Lips, thigh, breast.
It will be pure sexual tension
as they gaze at each other.
They had sex through spelling?
Yes.
Not even kissing? Didn’t we agree
on having a bed scene?
That’s the bed scene.
It’s more poetic that way.
What do I care about poetry?
Don’t you want to see some action?
When there is sex, there should
be a climax, right?
No. Not this time.
But other investors might not agree.
Why does everything need
to have a sex scene?
Because everything revolves around it.
If not for sex, would there
be people in this world?
Maybe Bela has gone too far? She held back.
We can easily revise.
No. I don’t want to revise.
It’s the story that
I will give a climax to.
Not Diego and Luna.
Arnold.
Bela, what are you doing?
Baby, please. What's up?
Hey, do you not love me anymore?
Why do you always emotionally blackmail me?
What blackmail?
I’m just asking for your help.
So why do you always bend
to that delusional friend of yours?
That misogynistic, egoistic, macho guy.
- Gardy...
- Gardy?
Hello, Bela.
Arnold and I are
in the middle of a quarrel.
Gardy, can you please
convince your friend
- to stop being stubborn.
- Again?
Gardy, please. Don’t meddle.
- I’ll talk to you later.
- Gardy, please.
Get in.
Thank you.
Remember, Babe? You first
had me in the rain.
It was our first date then it rained hard.
The thunder and lightning scared you.
I’m not scared of thunder anymore.
Really?
I remember when you told me that
it reminded you of your father.
You embraced me as if
you never wanted to let go.
- I love you, Babe.
- I love you more.
Let’s give Mr. Dizon what
he wants. Do it for me.
So that’s it? You gave in because of sex?
It’s not that. Don’t simplify.
Anyway, when is your deadline?
Are you going to make it?
I’m not even halfway through.
But you, you have to submit yours,
the one you told me about before.
Cinemalaya will always be there.
Arnold needs me now.
So you keep postponing your dreams for him.
May you get struck by lightning
to wake you up from your stupor.
He’s not like you
who can write and direct.
It’s not about being able to.
It’s about trying to.
I work hard for it. Just like you.
So can you please tell your boyfriend
to find you a project
with a decent talent fee?
I bet you’re not even getting paid.
Oh, shit.
Seriously, I don’t know how you manage
to stay in that relationship.
If I were to rate your relationship,
it would be three!
What? It's an eight.
Eight? I don’t see it as an eight.
Well, at least, our sex life is a ten.
So it’s okay for him to be an asshole
just because the sex is good?
People who love assholes
are much bigger assholes!
- You’re an asshole. You're crazy!
- I know.
But seriously. He visits my father.
- What?
- My monster dad.
The famous writer who thinks
he’s entitled to terrorize our family
just because he’s good novelist.
He hurt me and my mom.
Well, nothing lasts.
He’s now in a nursing home.
He has Alzheimer’s.
But he’s too young to have that.
Isn’t he just in his 60’s?
Arnold consistently visits him,
once a month.
While I always find an excuse
not to visit him.
I just can’t forgive him.
Arnold doesn’t tell me
what they talk about
or even what he looks like now.
Because he knows that
I don’t want to hear anything.
So my asshole boyfriend
is actually a very sensitive person.
And I know that he will be
a good director someday.
So I’m here to help him realize that.
Oh, well...
Why don’t these fathers and boyfriends
just act like fathers and boyfriends?
I’ll give Mr. Dizon what he wants.
I’ll make the script very sexy.
L-A-B-I.
Lips.
L-E-E-G.
Neck.
S-U-S-O.
Breast.
I knew it, Babe.
I knew you had it in you.
Mr. Dizon will be pleased.
I cringe at what I wrote.
Babe, it’s okay. It’s really good.
- Really?
- Yes. I just have a suggestion though.
I’m thinking of adding a little detail
to the bed scene.
I want Diego and Luna to orgasm
at the same time.
What?
What? Just like the two of us.
That’s too much.
Why is it too much?
You want it to be realistic, right?
- Yes.
- More realistic?
- Then that’s it.
You know what, I have an idea.
I have a friend. She’s a girl.
She’s open for a threesome.
- No.
- Let’s just try it.
I don’t want to.
- Just once?
- Disgusting.
Don’t tell me you’re going to enjoy that.
Of course. And you’re going
to enjoy it too, Babe.
Don’t you want us to explore?
- Then what about a threesome with a guy?
- Fuck no, Babe.
Why not?
Babe. I’d get jealous.
But it’s okay if it’s with a girl?
You’re so unfair!
I’m a man, Babe.
I’ve got nothing to lose.
And you know that
I’m the jealous type, right?
Yes, you get jealous towards everyone.
Even Gardy, who’s gay!
Babe, that guy still has a dick.
Whatever! I don’t want
to talk about it anymore.
I’ll just continue writing.
Babe.
Come on.
Uncle Roger was like a father to me.
If I knew my real father,
I feel that Uncle Roger
would still be more of a father to me.
Me...
I don’t even know
if my father is kind or not.
I saw him only thrice in my whole life.
I was sneaking peeks
in their huge house.
I was just a kid.
I would always think
of him as my hero,
even though I am an illegitimate child
and he never really knew me.
You know how heroes are in stories, right?
They’re noble, larger-than-life,
unattainable, but you still
look up to them.
One day, I went back to their house.
He was gone.
They migrated abroad.
The father I thought of
as my hero was gone.
I haven’t seen him since.
He was always there.
I always see him.
Growing up, even if he wasn’t around,
His presence.
This monster.
This famous writer in our house
who was a god-like figure of rage.
He would type on his manual
typewriter the whole day
while drinking beer.
Each hit to the typewriter key
was like a punch to my chest,
because if my mother and I
did anything to disturb his writing,
or if we weren’t quick enough
to get him another bottle of beer,
he would hurt us.
Wherever I go...
long after my mother passed away
and I started living on my own…
even now that he’s in a nursing home
and doesn’t remember who I am…
I can still feel his presence.
I can still see him.
Dad.
I brought you something that you’d like.
Ordinarily, beers are not allowed in here,
but we give him an exemption
because beer helps with his tantrums.
What about you?
Don’t worry about me.
I can handle this.
I don’t want to go back to Abe.
Take me with you.
I can’t. It’s dangerous.
I don’t want to put you at risk.
Where are you going?
You don’t have to know. Don’t look for me.
But don’t worry, I’ll find you.
We’ll see each other again.
Can I really not go with you?
L...
A...
B...
I...
Lips.
Diego. My name is Diego.
Something happened between you two.
Did you like it when he fucked you?
Answer me!
Why won’t you answer me?
You were together the whole day,
and you’re telling me he never touched you?
Was he better than me?
I can’t take this anymore!
What now?
This feels better, doesn’t it?
Diego...
Candy, please.
Wow, babe. You’re so good.
Round two later?
- Round three, four?
- Four?
- Five.
- Five, six.
- Seven, eight, nine.
- Oh, Babe.
Is it true that you’re together?
Babe. Let me explain. Okay?
I’m asking if it’s true.
Yes.
Finish your damn script yourself!
Babe.
You betrayed me again.
This is the second time.
I was just horny the first time.
It was just one night.
Babe.
This one, who is she?
- Babe...
- I said, who is she?
She’s Mr. Dizon’s sister.
It’s nothing serious.
You couldn’t even mention her name
because you’re just using her.
Because all you want is Mr. Dizon’s money.
You’re a whore!
Get out!
I said, get out of my house!
Pack your things and go!
Rot in hell with your nameless woman.
He’s reckless because he knows
that you’ll always take him back.
Your relationship has always
been like this, on repeat!
How do I get rid
of these feelings?
You never learn. What was his reason
the first time he cheated?
He said he needed to explore...
- for his art.
- And you believed him?
I’m so stupid.
Tell him that if he wants to experiment,
he shouldn’t be in a relationship
so he and his birdie can be set free.
Not like this! He’s taking advantage
of your illiterate heart.
I know. Anyway, I thought you
needed my help with your script?
You have two days to finish it, right?
Yes. But I didn’t want
to bother you anymore.
You’re going through a lot right now.
I can handle this. And besides,
I’m writing a love story.
A subject you’re not adept at.
- You’re crazy!
- You’re crazy, too!
Good luck to all the writers
slaving away at their laptops,
trying to keep up with deadlines,
draining their minds,
hearts, and souls dry.
Good luck to all the lovers
who never learn,
who make fools of themselves,
- who drive themselves insane,
- who act like hopeless martyrs!
You know, if I weren’t gay, you and I
would be the perfect match!
Look at us, we get each other!
Don’t be silly.
Right, that will never happen.
- Cheers!
Hey.
Promise me that if your asshole boyfriend
wants to get back with you,
you won’t take him back.
No matter how often he calls or
no matter how much he begs, don’t cave.
But how about the script?
Drop it.
What?
Let’s just do a toast.
That script be damned.
- I’ll just drink to that.
- Yes, that’s right!
I’m having doubts on whether to continue.
Why?
I feel that I’m writing
about myself, not about you.
Listen to your heart.
Sometimes I feel like I don’t know
what’s in my heart anymore.
Sometimes, you have to write something down
in order to reveal its truth.
Hello?
Luna.
Yes, Diego. Where are you?
I’ve been wanting to talk to you.
Where are you?
Am I going to see you?
Look at me. Let's come together.
Get some sleep.
I don’t want to sleep.
I just want to feel you all night.
I thought you’ve come
to take me with you.
This money is more than enough
for you to pay off your husband.
Don’t worry, I didn’t steal this
from the workers.
I took it from Sir Louie.
Uncle Roger and I have been
targeting him for a while.
You need this more than I do.
I already got some for myself.
Don’t worry about me.
Use this money to fix your life.
Wherever I may end up,
I won’t stop worrying
unless I’m certain that you’re okay.
I want to be with you.
If you come with me,
where will this relationship lead us?
Our lives will always be in danger.
Let me sort out my life first.
Who knows, I might just muster
up the courage to turn myself in.
I already talked to someone in Bicol.
I’ll stay there for a while.
We’ll see each other again.
You need to leave now.
I need to go. You take care.
Drop your weapon!
Diego, it’s time to surrender!
Diego! Stop it!
Stop shooting! Diego!
I’ve finished the script.
I’m done with mine, too.
Submit yours. They might like it.
But the concept isn’t mine.
I just wanted to finish it.
So you’re just going to give it
to your producer?
How are you?
I'm good. And you?
I’ve finished the script.
But I deleted it.
Why did you delete it?
What a waste.
It wasn’t a waste, because I finished it.
I’m sorry though
that Mr. Dizon backed out.
It’s not your fault. I’m not blaming you.
There are other opportunities out there.
I’m sorry I fucked up.
Friends?
Friends.