[Episode 5]
[Officer Choi Moo-gak]
Hello?
It's me.
Where are you?
Why?
Come out.
I'm in your neighborhood.
Do you know where I am now?
What makes you think that I'm home?
Right now, you're eating ramen at home.
I can hear the TV sound, too.
Come out now.
Is your place far from here?
Did you have to cross
rivers and climb mountains?
What's wrong with you?
I stopped eating ramen and
came right away because of you!
Why are you looking at me like that?
How could you be wasting time like that?
What?
What don't you like now?
Aren't we practicing your skit?
Didn't you say this is your last chance?
So you're here to practice?
Why? You don't want to do it?
I can go if you're busy.
It's not that...
Since you came all the way here,
we should practice at least.
Where should we practice?
There?
Or there?
Didn't you say you had been
eating ramen? Follow me.
He always walks away first.
Wait for me!
So what brings you to Seoul?
I brought $20,000 to live in Seoul
like you do!
I want to get a place with a
lot of sunlight with this $20,000!
I will live in Seoul!
Now don't be shocked when I tell you this.
With $20,000, you can only get
places that are dark inside!
You must be lying!
Everyone here knows that except you!
How will you be able
to live in Seoul like that?
I will live in Seoul... no matter what!
Ring me up, please.
Someone has already paid for your bill.
Pardon?
He wanted me to tell you it's okay to live in
the countryside and to keep your head up.
I sincerely apologize for being
a burden on the team.
I'll pay for my sins.
I thank you for your kindness and
generosity during my time here.
I'm really sorry!
Detective Choi, thanks for
catching me so quickly.
I might have committed
more crimes if you hadn't.
I'm sorry.
Our time together wasn't long,
but I liked spending time with you.
I liked our time, too.
May I shake your hand?
[Police Identification] [Tak Jae-suk]
- Clean up everything.
- Okay.
The personal trainer
murder case is now closed.
It was a copycat crime of
the barcode chain murders
that caused a great deal of
confusion in our investigation.
We shall resume the investigation
of the barcode chain murders.
Please focus on gathering
evidence for the Joo Ma-ri case.
Let's get moving.
This may sound trite, but if you prick her,
not even a drop of blood will come out.
I really want to quit right now...
but I have to survive until my retirement.
Let's move!
You got a new car today. Didn't you say
that you'll treat us to lunch?
Hey. Even my Elena Vashilivashivanova
hasn't been in it yet.
Let's move then.
You're on the white line.
I think you should go more to the right.
Just like that. Straight.
Stop!
Okay!
Is it okay?
Yes.
Should I go more to the left?
What if others dent my car?
This is brand new!
Let's be honest. This isn't brand new.
You just bought a car
that has 60,000 miles on it.
Shall we?
Wait!
Let me go more to the left.
That's enough, Detective Ki!
I heard you!
Hey! Don't open the door!
Only open it once I turn off the engine!
What is this?
The roof!
There's a man on the roof!
Cordon off this area, Detective Yeh!
[10 minutes ago]
Thank you for coming. Thank you, come in.
Thanks for your invitation, Chef.
Welcome. Did you find the place easily?
Of course, thanks to your directions.
I was as fast as the wind!
What is it, Chef?
As fast as the wind...
Please come in.
Yes.
It's probably going to be so delicious!
You can sit here.
We don't have much time.
Why isn't our food coming yet?
Please wait here, Cho-rim.
I need to check on the kitchen.
Sure.
What are you doing? The guests are waiting.
Why aren't the dishes going out?
I haven't received confirmation.
Where's your boss? Where is
Chef Hong right now?
He went to the rooftop to get some spices,
but he hasn't come back yet.
This isn't my restaurant, but since you're
busy, there's no choice.
Redo these dishes, and these are
fine to go out to the guests.
Yes, Chef.
Is Chef Hong out of his mind?
Chef Hong!
What are you doing here?
Well... This is...
No one else is here.
You've been caught red-handed.
You're under arrest.
W-wait. Listen to me.
That's not how it happened.
This area is closed off.
No one gets in or out.
This is a murder case. We ask
for your cooperation.
Please clear the way! Please!
Chef Kwon!
Let's go.
Excuse me!
The area is closed off.
I'm sorry.
- It's fine.
- Thank you for your cooperation.
Do you know him?
Yes. He used to work for me.
He just left my restaurant
and opened his own.
Why did you kill him?
There are marks on his neck.
Did you suffocate him and
then push him off the roof?
I refuse to answer.
I need my lawyer.
Okay.
You can call your lawyer
from the police station.
Detective Choi.
Yes.
I'm so sad.
Chef Kwon didn't have
any scent on his hands.
So he couldn't have suffocated the victim.
It's okay.
That's the same scent!
He's the murderer!
Kwon Jae-hee is indeed rich!
He told his lawyer to bring
him a change of clothes.
I really like his style!
I should ask him where he got his
jacket during the interrogation.
Do you think they'll issue
an arrest warrant for him?
Of course they will.
He was alone on the rooftop from
which a suffocated corpse fell.
A search warrant will be
issued tomorrow morning.
I need to see you, Officer Choi.
I was just on the rooftop, Officer Choi.
The spices the victim grew
didn't have that scent.
And that scent wasn't on
Chef Kwon's hands either.
The scent on the victim's neck
was something very strong.
And I saw the man who had
that scent on his hands!
I saw him, too.
I clearly saw Chef Kwon's face
staring down on the fallen corpse.
This is frustrating!
I'm telling you that
Chef Kwon didn't kill him!
Chef Kwon's hands
didn't have any scent! None!
He was the only one on the
rooftop when the corpse fell.
The evidence is very clear.
He really didn't kill him!
It's impossible!
Just think about it.
There was only Chef Kwon
and the victim on the rooftop.
As they were arguing, Chef Kwon pushed the
victim toward the edge while choking him.
And as the victim lost strength
from being choked,
he couldn't help but fall from the building.
That's not it, Officer Choi.
Anyway, Chef Kwon is clearly the murderer.
So say nothing more about this case.
Seriously.
I won't tell you more anyway even
if you come back begging!
Another interrogation?
Drink it. It's from Oh Cho-rim.
From Cho-rim?
She told me to take good care of
you since she knows you're innocent.
If we don't find anything during the search
of your house tomorrow morning...
they won't issue a warrant for your arrest.
Please let me know if
there's anything you need.
Sure. Thank you, Officer Choi.
Right.
Oh Cho-rim was worried about your dog.
She's worried about it being alone at home.
Ah, Moongchi...
Hey, Moongchi!
Long time no see. How have you been?
Do you want to come home with me?
This scent is...
The scent of Joo Ma-ri's perfume...
Right, she was Chef Kwon's girlfriend.
I guess it's her souvenirs.
Let's go, Moongchi.
Let's go, Moongchi!
Oh, my!
I'm sorry, Cho-rim. Did I startle you?
No, it's okay.
Are you here for Chef Kwon?
Yes, I heard you're taking Moongchi.
Yes...
Please take good care of Moongchi.
I think I'll be here for a while.
I see. Good night then.
Dr. Chun...
This is very embarrassing, but I
don't have any other choice.
It's okay. Tell me whatever you need.
I went a bit overboard while
expanding my business.
There are financial statements in my home
that will damage me once the cops see them.
Please do me a favor keep them with you.
There are three wine boxes next to the sofa.
The middle one has the financial reports.
Joo Ma-ri's diary.
According to her friends, she used this
company's notebooks to write her diary.
Please note this as
you search for the diaries.
Before her death, Ms. Joo swallowed
the key to the box that had her diaries.
That means she wrote down
the killer's name in her diary.
I think we'll find her diaries if
we search Dr. Chun's place.
I don't understand why we
can't get the search warrant.
Because there's no evidence against him.
We must find something first.
When Joo Ma-ri's diaries went missing...
people automatically thought
the murderer took them.
Detective, we have the search
warrant for Kwon Jae-hee.
Okay. You can leave it here.
So the person who took the
diaries must be the murderer.
We should leave now.
There's a designated timeframe.
I get it, dude! Now...
Let's comb through everything
in Kwon Jae-hee's house.
Let's go.
The scent was something like mugwort.
But this isn't it either.
Hot, hot, hot!
Would you please add more mugwort?
Hello, ma'am.
Hello.
That mugwort has a great scent!
Geez...it's so heavy.
I've been to every
place that has mugwort,
but I can't find that guy.
My whole body is aching!
That man...
That man!
Who are you?
Save me, Officer Choi.
I'm being chased by a murderer.
Why are you following me around?
Do you want to die?
Oh Cho-rim! Where are you?
It's Officer Choi!
Oh Cho-rim!
Are you okay? You're not hurt?
Let's get out of here.
It's okay.
What are you so proud of?
This is a job done by trained
policemen and detectives!
Do you know how dangerous
it is to chase a suspect?
Are you really out of your mind?
According to you, he's a murderer.
But you just chased him alone?
Are you out of your mind?
He's the murderer!
That's why it was even more
dangerous! He killed a man!
Chef Kwon is under arrest for
a crime he didn't commit.
So it was urgent for
me to catch the culprit!
Shouldn't the innocent be
freed as soon as possible?
We're still conducting the investigation.
He'll be free once his innocence is proven.
No, thanks. I just ate.
It's mugwort rice cake.
I know what mugwort rice cake is!
But I'm full.
The neck of the victim, Chef Hong,
had the scent of mugwort.
This scent?
It was a scent 20 times
stronger than that right now.
The criminal's hands also had the same scent.
So you were following
around the mugwort scent?
Don't even get me started.
I was at stores that sell
mugwort rice cakes...
Clinics that do mugwort moxibustion...
Mugwort steam baths...
Health stores that sell mugworts...
I went to every place that has
some kind of mugwort.
But nowhere had a scent that strong.
Okay, enough about mugworts. You can't
just chase after anyone from now on.
Why is he just anyone?
He's the culprit!
I need to go back to the station.
Goodbye.
What? We're in the middle of a conversation.
How can you just leave like that?
Don't be too meddling.
What? Meddling?
Dang it! This is infuriating!
Why am I doing this anyway?
For what glory?
Wait a minute.
Rose, lily, freesia, baby's
breath, chrysanthemum...
Why are there so many
flower scents on this?
Flower shops don't sell mugwort...
What? He left already?
Oh Cho-rim!
Look.
Here, here, here, and here.
It's all flower scents.
What are you talking about?
When the criminal held me,
these scents got on my jacket.
They were of all kinds of flowers, too.
Got it.
Here.
Shouldn't you see a
doctor for your wound?
Well... It's not that serious.
I think some ointment will suffice.
You think so? That's a relief.
Oh Cho-rim.
Listen carefully.
Don't go after police cases from now on.
It's all my fault for asking
you to help with cases.
I'll continue to be your skit partner.
But you don't have to
be my investigative partner.
It's too dangerous.
I'm sorry, but I'm running
late for my meeting.
Make sure you disinfect before putting
the bandage on, okay?
Goodbye.
Focus on Kwon Jae-hee's relationship
with the victim when looking for clues.
- Yes.
- Detective Yeh. Go upstairs.
When will I ever get to
live in a place like this?
Look at all these trees!
I've never searched a place that's
as nice and impeccable as this!
I guess he makes a lot of money!
This may sound cliché, but
he sure does live in a palace!
He's the owner of a restaurant chain,
so of course he's rich.
Anyway, we combed through
everything, but didn't find much.
Let's go.
Right.
This is an important case, too. But
what happened with Dr. Chun's alibi?
Dr. Chun Baek-gyung has no family.
He got married 4 years ago, but his wife died
2 1/2 years ago from heart disease.
Are you certain of that?
We've confirmed she always had a heart
problem since she was young.
It seems their marriage was pretty strong.
They even moved to Jeju Island so his wife
could live in a good environment.
Did you say that he lived in Jeju before?
Chun Baek-gyung quit his job at
one of the best hospitals in Korea.
And moved to Jeju Baekrok
Hospital for his wife.
Jeju Baekrok Hospital?
Why are you acting like that?
Jeju Island, Jeju Baekrok Hospital...
Are you suspicious of something because
Dr. Chun's alibi is in Jeju right now?
Perhaps he went to Jeju to
reminisce about his past?
When did Chun Baek-gyung work in Jeju?
Chun Baek-gyung... Oh, right here.
He lived in Jeju for one year from
September 2011 to September 2012
when his wife died.
Look. It coincides with the time the diver
couple was killed in February 2012.
Detective Choi, go to Jeju Island right
now and trace back what Dr. Chun
did during his stay while
Joo Ma-ri went missing.
There must be some
sort of hole in his alibi.
Yes, ma'am.
That's right, Detective Ki.
It's a bikeable distance from the restaurant
where the murder occurred. Yes.
Then please find the home with the highest
electricity bill within a 1.8 miles radius.
Yes, thank you.
Welcome!
Look at this. "Hello,
I'm a merchant. Thanks!"
"Hello, I'm a merchant. Thanks!"
Moo-gak, I'm starving.
What's good in Seoul?
Let me see.
Choi Eun-seol is stupid.
What is this?
[Ms. Choi Eun-seol ]
Hey, why do you look for
meat noodles in Seoul?
Don't be a such country bumpkin.
Seoul people eat pork cutlets!
There are pork cutlets in Jeju, too!
And it even tastes better there!
Let's go get meat noodles.
You can have it every day
once you go home tomorrow.
Please...
Pork cutlet!
Meat... Pork cutlet!
Seriously!
You're so mean!
So mean?
Yes.
You're pretty.
[Jeju Baekrok Hospital]
Did you say Dr. Chun Baek-gyung?
He did come here.
When was it already?
Wasn't it either February 9th or 10th?
That's right, detective.
It was February 10th.
He wanted to check some medical records.
Whose?
Give me a second. Let me check.
It was Choi Eun-seol.
Choi Eun-seol?
Chun Baek-gyung looked for
Choi Eun-seol's medical records?
Yes, he browsed through her ICU records,
X-ray photos, and surgery records.
ICU, X-ray, surgery...
My Eun-seol was murdered as soon
as she got to the emergency room.
What do you mean by ICU and surgery?
My Eun-seol doesn't even
have a medical record.
Pardon?
I'm afraid I don't understand.
Let me see Choi Eun-seol's medical records.
I said let me see her medical records.
[Emergency Room Medical Records]
Choi Eun-seol... Born on May 11th, 1994...
My Eun-seol was born in March of 1995.
[Next day]
This household pays
$1,500 in electricity per month.
They have a sick family member,
so they're operating an air purifier
and other medical devices.
This household paid $1,600
in electricity per month.
It turned out to be an illegal gambling
house, so we've arrested them.
How about this place?
They paid $1,900 in electricity last month...
Is it a flower shop?
The murderer is related to a flower shop.
That is indeed... a flower shop.
[Flowers]
We'll barge in on my count 3.
One, two, three!
You're surrounded!
Freeze!
What if Choi Moo-gak dies?
Let's go collect evidence.
Okay!
Is anyone here?
We're coming in!
Jackpot...
He was right.
It's marijuana, just like
Choi Moo-gak predicted.
Of course the electricity bills would
be high to cultivate marijuana.
This does smell like mugwort.
This is a lot stronger.
Hey!
Now that they've confessed, put them
in jail for cultivating illegal substances.
Yes, sir.
Also...
Yang Suk-jin, you are under arrest for
murdering Chef Hong Chul-soo.
No, what are you talking about?
I didn't kill anyone.
On the opening day of the restaurant,
you called Hong Chul-soo up to the roof...
as he no longer allowed his restaurant to
be a rendezvous point for drug dealers.
And then you threatened him to
keep dealing marijuana.
But because Hong Chul-soo didn't comply,
you threatened to choke him to death.
But he really died and you
didn't know what to do.
So you wanted to disguise his death
as if he had jumped on his own.
But then you heard someone
walking up to the rooftop.
So you quickly hid yourself.
The man who came to the rooftop
was Chef Kwon Jae-hee.
And that is what my boss thinks.
Arrest them immediately.
Officer Choi. No... Detective Choi, what are
you doing instead of releasing Chef Kwon?
Yes, sir.
Thank you for your work, Mr. Shin.
Sure, get some rest.
I will.
Please come in.
Isn't it a relief, Chef?
It is. Please come in.
What a relief, Moongchi!
The medical records?
So his sole purpose of going to Jeju was
because of the medical records, right?
Yes, he browsed the Choi Eun-seol's
medical records at his former workplace.
Did you just say Choi Eun-seol?
Yes, ma'am.
She's the daughter of the diver couple,
the second victims of the serial killer.
Born on May 11th, 1994.
The daughter of the diver couple?
The suspect in Joo Ma-ri's
murder case was looking for
the medical records of
the divers' daughter...
That murder occurred three years ago.
So why was he looking at the
daughter's medical records now?
Choi Eun-seol came up as deceased
when I ran a search with her ID number.
Then why is he looking at
her medical records now?
I think we're one piece of
evidence away from arresting Dr. Chun.
I thought we wouldn't be able to eat this
because I've been at the police station...
But it still looks pretty fresh.
You're right!
Cho-rim?
Yes?
Are you okay with steak?
Of course! I love steak!
I bought these directly from the farm.
I'll cook you some incredible steaks.
Okay.
I heard you believed I was innocent
and worked hard for my release.
Don't mention it.
I didn't do much.
Do you need help with this?
No, it's okay.
I can do it.
You can sit down.
I wish Officer Choi could join us.
I guess he's out of luck.
I'll take my steak rare.
You want them rare. Okay.
[Jeju Baekrok Hospital Murder Case]
Why is it the same name?
Why?
Detective Choi, please put that
case on the big screen.
This is my personal file.
Please put it up.
Killed from a slit to her throat...
Jeju Island...
Her name is Choi Eun-seol,
the same name.
Who is she?
She's my younger sister.
I'm sorry. I should've told you earlier.
There's something I haven't told you.
Choi Eun-seol, the daughter of
the diver couple,
is the only surviving
witness of the serial killer.
I'm so full! I can't eat anymore.
Look at it!
I've brought some desserts.
Are you really full?
I'm ashamed of saying this, but women
have a separate stomach for sweets!
Thank you!
Let me see.
This is so delicious! Just my style!
How's your work in the troupe going?
Is it fun?
Of course. I can't do it if it's not fun.
It's tiring, but it's not like
I make a lot of money.
I guess you have a second job then?
Normally I should, but my hours at the troupe
change so often that it's hard to schedule.
No employer would be kind
enough to understand.
Would you like to work at my restaurant then?
I'll try to be that nice employer
who's kind enough to understand.
Really?
Yes.
But if you don't work hard,
I'll yell at you.
You'll no longer be just a guest.
Thank you, boss!
So the daughter witnessed the murderer
kidnapping her parents.
The murderer chased after
the girl who ran away...
and she got into a car accident.
After the murderer found out her name
from her belongings back at home,
he went to the emergency
room where the girl was.
And there, he saw the name Choi Eun-seol...
and cruelly slit her throat.
So the murderer mistook
your sister as the witness...
Chun Baek-gyung...
Detective Choi!
You killed my sister because you
thought she was the witness!
Take a good look at my sister
whom you killed, you creep!
She isn't the witness!
She isn't!
Stop it, Detective Choi!
I'm sorry, Lieutenant.
The rule that prohibits detectives from
working on cases involving their families...
You're the one who mentioned it first.
I really want to solve this case.
So I don't want anything to happen that'll
cause me to lose investigative authority.
I've never heard your sister's story before.
That's Officer Choi's scent.
Why are you hanging out so late?
It's not that late.
I was at Chef Kwon's house.
Why?
I brought his dog back,
so he cooked dinner for me.
He also gave me a job.
You've met your Santa Claus!
He is Santa Claus, except he's not that old.
Do you how popular he is
among women these days?
Is this the time to be talking about that?
Why? Are you here to practice at this hour?
You said you quit drinking after
causing all that trouble before, right?
That's right. I quit drinking.
Why?
If you quit, that's fine.
I guess it's bad for your health anyway.
Why? Do you want to drink?
Something bad happened, right?
Your complexion sucks.
My complexion sucks?
You should learn how to speak properly.
This was a buy-one-get-one-free item.
They just gave me one
more when I got one.
Here.
Wow! How cute!
I'll have to pay for this doll with drinks.
Let's go.
I'll pay for drinks.
But will you be okay?
Why are you talking so much today?
Stop worrying! Let's just go drink.
We'll drink...
Soju.
Sounds good.
Let's go!
I've been craving soju, too!
But did something bad really happen?
You drank a lot already, but you want more?
How did the soup get to the top of your head?
One more soju, please!
Okay!
I'm stepping out for a bit.
What is it?
Ae-ri, this is the story
of my friend's friend.
A man and a woman are just acquaintances.
They only shared meals 4 times such as pork
ribs, sushi, fried chicken, and potato stew.
Quite the variety.
And?
And then the man gave
the woman a doll as a gift.
It's apparently a talking doll.
She said it's pretty cute.
Is this a green light?
So Officer Choi bought you a doll?
You little brat.
Officer Choi...
I have something to tell you.
Can't I go with you on
your next investigation?
Officer Choi?
Officer Choi...
I couldn't sleep for days
because of the pain and agony.
Then, I suddenly fainted.
Hello, Eun-seol. It's your brother.
How's everything?
I don't know why I'm reminded of this...
We should've had those meat
noodles when you were in Seoul.
I had a younger sister.
Not anymore, though.
Excuse me, but he can't sleep here.
I'm sorry. We'll get going.