Hello
Is this Miss Sandy?
to have a close call
I thought Qin Luo Luo was crazy enough.
I didn't expect that there's no normal person around Lin Zeyan.
What's your relationship with Ze Yan?
Can't you see that?
You shameless woman.
You did it for money.
You're wrong.
I see your public relations press release is very happy to admit it.
The same to you
We still have feelings.
If Zeyan hadn't been too busy,
It's your turn.
But as far as I know,
Your rumors can be published as a tutorial.
Hello, Li.
You got it?
The clothes are 2,680.
It's 580 yuan.
For mental injury.
Two thousand six hundred.
It's 5,000 yuan.
You have one minute to think about it.
Can't cure Lin Zeyan.
I can't cure you.
Who are you?
It's me.
I'm your fan.
Did you really shoot it just now?
You believe the trick of lying to a fool.
It's interesting.
How can Lin Zeyan tolerate your mouth?
There's no other way.
It's Dad.
Wait
Do you know Lin Zeyan?
Isn't it stupid?
Hey, Wildcat.
What's your name?
I'm in a hurry.
Thanks for the coat.
Give me the contact information.
I'll pay you back next time.
Hey, wait a second.
If I have a part-time job next time,
I miss you first.
no problem
I'll give you 20% off.
Zeyan, Luo Luo told me everything.
She's also your fiancee.
You chose her.
I didn't choose it.
She saved you back then.
I don't want to see those messy reports.
So you asked someone to watch me.
That's what I want.
But also to take care of you.
I have a meeting to attend.
If there's nothing else,
I'll hang up.
I'm just taking care of the patient.
To the top search for no reason.
And was splashed with coffee by his ex-girlfriend.
Why are you so unlucky?
Why don't you change your job?
This is not a long-term solution.
I signed the contract of selling my body.
If you break the contract, you have to pay ten times the salary.
if
You don't want to.
and
I found a way to make money.
The wool of capitalism.
Hey, wait a second.
Let me record it first.
I'm going to write a grand drama.
Let that Midnight have a look.
What is art?
By the way, Yoyo.
Don't be angry.
I'll take you there tonight.
go
Young Master Lin,
The taste has changed, right?
I heard you have a wild cat at home.
You've learned to hide a lady in a golden roof.
When are you going to let me meet your little girl?
Well
Hold on. I have something to deal with.
Ha-ha
Are you all right?
Nothing.
Are you a person
My friend and I
I just went to the bathroom.
Hey, where's my friend?
Xiayu
Xia You, where are you?
Why does the name sound so familiar?
This is not a cafe war.
An old artist with an ex-girlfriend?
The Earth is really round.
This is your best friend?
I know him.
She's a wonderful woman.
Since we are so fated,
Let me buy you a drink. Let's go.
Mr. Lin, this is the first half of the company's business.
There are some documents for you to sign.
To summarize the market trend in recent months.
And analyze the trend of the second half.
To work out the next step.
Alright, President Lin.
The cup is in the right place.
Although this woman is arrogant and greedy,
And your brain is not sharp.
But at least it has some advantages.
At least until now.
En
Well
Mr. Lin, we received a message.
President Shang wants to hold a small birthday party for her little girlfriend.
This is the best time to get on the line.
Look.
Yes, I know.