(Ciro's Club)
Zekai,
why are you here?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Nothing.
You've gotten stronger lately.
Don't you have
a social engagement today?
It ended earlier than expected,
so I came to pick you up.
You've always avoided coming here
to avoid suspicion.
Why now?
Has there been any unusual personnel changes
at Ciro's Club lately?
Why?
(Ciro's Club)
Get me all the records
on everyone here.
=Found & Lost=
=Episode 9=
(Danger!)
I'm Zhang Mingrui,
a reporter from Shanghai News.
The paper sent me here to Puyu Hall
for a feature report.
This way, Mr. Zhang.
The Vice President
has already instructed us.
We'd appreciate it if you could
give us a favorable write-up.
Of course.
Please, this way.
(Encrypted codes, codebook)
Nanluo Bay No. 34.
Falcon 32.
Snow Wolf 12.
Viper 9.
Beijiao Lane No. 5.
Red Fox 27.
Jinming Temple, Falcon 67.
Sparrow 34, Snow Eagle 25.
These animal code names
and numbers warrant scrutiny.
I've got some here too.
Huage Road No. 128.
Falcon 5, Snow Wolf 4, White Tiger 2,
Red Fox 2, Sparrow 1.
(Falcon 5, Snow Wolf 4,
White Tiger 2, Red Fox 2, Sparrow 1)
If I'm not mistaken,
this records
the Chen family case.
(Huage Road No. 128, Falcon 5, Snow Wolf 4,
White Tiger 2, Red Fox 2)
Huage Road No. 128
is Chen Garden's address.
There were 13 people in my family.
The date at the bottom also matches.
So
these animals
must be the codenames of the operatives.
What do the numbers represent?
(Huage Road No. 128, Falcon 5, Snow Wolf 4)
And who do these animals refer to?
Falcon?
Yang Ziqin?
(Files)
No.
It's unlikely it's him.
This "1"
should refer to my father.
I caught a glimpse of a page about him
in the archives.
He joined the Haitang Society
less than five years ago.
That's not enough time
to carry out these missions.
So this "Falcon" executed
both my father's assassination
and the Chen family massacre.
What's your problem?
I'm running late.
I have to work overtime
at the paper tonight.
I've got to go.
I'm leaving now.
Just as well.
Mr. Kun needs to ask me
about some herbs.
Wait…
You'll be in charge
of securing the opium shipment.
I heard you made a big splash
at the banquet over a woman.
Didn't expect that from you.
Let's get to business.
Of course.
If you want to play
the knight in shining armor,
that's your choice.
However,
the higher-ups asked me to remind you
not to forget who you are.
One wrong move
and the whole game is lost.
After all,
you know better than anyone
the cost of recklessness.
(Yongchun Medical Hall)
Why did you lie to me?
- Happy birthday!
You guys…
I almost gave it away just now
with my terrible acting.
I went out of my way to ask Mr. Zhang
for your favorite dishes and recipes.
I made some myself. Hope you like it.
Thank you, Mr. Kun.
Here's my gift.
It's modest
compared to Mr. Yang's,
but it's from the heart.
Not bad.
Forget fancy jewelry.
This suits you better.
Wait.
I'm not taking your gifts anymore.
It cost me a month's salary.
Can't return it now.
Why?
Do you have something for me too?
Can't I?
This is hand-embroidered
by the Young Lady herself.
Mr. Kun.
Spare the unnecessary details.
I noticed you always carry one with you.
Don't you like it?
I do.
Very much.
Come.
Let's all eat
before the food gets cold.
Let's dig in.
Wait a second.
We can't let a moment like this go
without a photo!
Then what are you waiting for? Go!
Mr. Kun, get in there.
Come on.
Get ready.
Here we go. Three, two, one.
- Happy birthday!
Inform everyone.
The hunt is set for this Saturday.
Come, Mr. Gu.
Have a seat.
Very well.
Vice President,
your brilliance is unmatched.
Coming up with such a clever plan.
Puyu Hall doesn't have many people.
Taking care of it won't be hard.
Leave the dirty work to me.
As for fundraising,
I'll leave that to you, Mr. Gu.
Rest assured, Vice President.
The funds will be in your account
within a week.
Good.
It's been a while
since I've stretched my muscles.
I'm ready for some action.
♪As dusk approaches, dreams unfold♪
♪Laughter drifts with the wind,
hard to hold♪
♪Entwined within the mortal world♪
♪Watching fates intertwine, unfurled♪
♪Like moths chasing flames,
to blaze they're drawn♪
♪We brave the darkness,
spiraling into cocoons♪
♪Chasing a single, unwavering dream♪
♪But life's endless twists and turns
can't be undone♪
♪As fleeting splendor fades
without regret♪
♪We cross the smoke and ashes,
torn by goodbyes♪
♪In every moment♪
♪Stained by the verses of dawn's light♪
♪Love spreads like wildfire,
boundless and bright♪