=Love Behind the Mask=
=Episode 1=
Her Royal Highness is here.
Make way.
Disperse!
Why is she making such a big show?
What does she want now?
The Princess Royal is debauched.
She likes handsome men.
Her mansion is full of toyboys.
I guess
she took a fancy
to Princess Liangyin's ghost husband.
I heard that the ghost husband
has unparalleled beauty.
The whole capital has heard about it.
(I am the ghost husband
they are talking about.)
(Mu Han)
(I'm Mu Han.)
(But I have another identity
that must be deeply hidden:)
(Lord of Zishang's Son, Si Yichen)
(Lord of Zishang's son,)
(Si Yichen.)
(Three months ago, Zishang State)
(Three months ago,)
(on the night of my wedding,)
(fearing the power
of Zishang State, the emperor)
(sent Princess Royal Wen Yanshu)
(to annihilate
my entire family overnight.)
(Lord of Zishang)
Hide my son in the secret passage now.
(Lady of Zishang)
(To protect the Si family's bloodline,)
(my father had my master
seal my acupoints)
(and hid me in the secret passage.)
(Hang Zhan, Si Yichen's Master)
(I survived the massacre)
(but also witnessed my dearest ones)
(being brutally killed one by one
before my eyes.)
Execute the entire families
of Hang Zhan, General Zhenbei,
and Lord of Zishang!
(Lord of Zishang's Memorial Tablet)
(That night,)
(the joyful red curtains
were stained black by the massacre.)
(The mansion of Lord of Zishang,
who killed countless enemies)
(and defended the borders
for the country for decades,)
(was covered with corpses and blood.)
(Then, the feet that trampled
on my parents' blood)
(appeared in front of me.)
(She was attracted by the smell
of blood like a hungry wolf,)
(playing recklessly
with my parents' blood.)
(She looked both intoxicated)
(and insane.)
(It made me remember that face)
(of the person
I have a vendetta against,)
(Princess Royal Wen Yanshu)
(Princess Royal Wen Yanshu.)
It's snowing.
Greetings, Your Royal Highness.
(Coming from Zishang State
to the capital)
(and becoming the ghost husband
of a prematurely deceased princess...)
I want
the man in this sedan.
(It's the quickest way for me
to get close to my enemy.)
Your Royal Highness,
that's improper.
The man in this sedan chair
is Princess Liangyin's ghost husband.
Get lost.
(Wen Yanshu is debauched)
(and addicted to men.)
(She's obsessed
with collecting toyboys everywhere.)
(As expected, she came.)
(Tonight)
(is the best chance
for me to kill my enemy.)
It's very inauspicious.
Princess!
What's your name?
Mu Han.
You are mine now.
Your Royal Highness, you mustn't...
A ghost's sedan chair
is not as comfortable as my sedan chair.
(Wen Yanshu,)
(you'll soon regret tonight's decision.)
(Princess Royal's Mansion)
Kneel.
Swallow it.
Take them off.
Go on.
Princess Liangyin's ghost husband
is indeed handsome,
as the rumors say.
An exotic man
does have a different charm.
Come.
Undress me.
(Wen Yanshu,)
(you killed my parents)
(and eliminated my family.)
(I will definitely make you)
(pay with blood.)
(No. I can't move at all.)
(What...)
Kneel.
Bring it up.
(Why can't I control my body?)
(Bright and Virtuous)
If it weren't for me,
you would have been buried
with that dead princess.
And now you want to kill me?
You are debauched.
Everyone would want to kill you.
What I just fed you
is poison of the Corpse Bellflower.
Whenever I ring
my Dream-Shattering Bone Chain,
you'll have to obey me.
If I die,
no one else in this world
can relieve the poison.
Then, it won't be long
before the poison spreads
throughout your body.
If you want to kill me,
just do it.
There's no need to bother.
Well,
I like it.
(The power of the Evil Bone)
(is the most powerful in the world.)
(Whoever gains this power
will rule the world.)
(To obtain this power,)
(one needs to inject)
(Myriad Threads into it and nourish it
with love, hate, and fall)
(to make it bloom into)
(the Flower of Three Lives.)
(For some reason,)
(he hates me so much
that he wanted to kill me.)
(But it suits my purpose perfectly.)
(The flower of hatred
grows from hatred.)
(His hatred grants a great opportunity
to nourish this flower.)
Hate me
all you want.
I like to see you
hate me to the bone.
Why don't you show me
how intense your hatred can get?
(All men in the world
are ashamed to be a toyboy.)
(If I use this to humiliate him,)
(it'll definitely intensify his hatred.)
I like to tame uncontrollable people.
I will tame you well.
Enjoy it.
Come here.
Stay here
and make no sound.
(He Chuan, Marquis Cheng'en)
Shu,
I've heard you took
Princess Liangyin's ghost husband.
Brother, you are really well-informed.
You know I don't like
you calling me that.
But we are nominally siblings,
and this will never change.
Shu, your scent
is enough to destroy all my willpower.
Do you smell it?
What is it?
Did you forget?
This is what we frequently use.
Hypnotic Incense.
What?
Shu,
you have never treated me this way.
Is it because
of the person on the bed?
No.
I have my period these days.
It's just inconvenient.
Why did it come early?
Do you need an imperial physician?
No need.
A few days of rest will suffice.
You should leave now.
In case someone finds out about us.
Your Royal Highness, didn't you say
you want to tame the uncontrollable?
You...
Marquis Cheng'en,
you should leave.
Take me to the medicated bath.
(Only she can cure
the poison within me.)
(So I can't kill her yet.)
(But I can gain her trust first)
(to get close and kill that tyrant.)
(To counteract the aphrodisiac incense,
a mere medicated bath is not enough.)
(There is only one way.)
(She doesn't seem to want
to have intimate contact with me.)
(No.)
(If I can detoxify her today,)
(it would be a perfect opportunity
to gain her trust.)
(What I am doing is not what I wish.)
(But compared to the vendetta,)
(it's really not a big deal.)
(The Princess Royal is known
for her ruthlessness.)
(Why did she suddenly
become compassionate today?)
Your blood...
The less you know,
the longer you live.
(Her blood can cause visions.)
(What secret is she hiding?)
Your Royal Highness, bad news!
Princess Jiyao has stormed
into our mansion with her people.
♪In the deserted world♪
♪There are countless thoughts♪
♪How many of them come true♪
♪I've asked a thousand times♪
♪Who is writing♪
♪Our mutual wishes♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪