=Love Behind the Mask=
=Episode 15=
It was snatched from your hand.
What brings you here?
Yanshu,
I'm here to check
if General Mu needs any help
when establishing his mansion.
Please don't take offense.
No need.
Without my permission,
he can forget about leaving my sight.
Yanshu, aren't you
too overbearing like this?
So what?
Is the person in your heart
Mu Han?
You may guess.
The answer is all over your face.
In my opinion,
you should be bold,
pin him onto the bed,
and ask him,
"Do you like me?"
What if he says
he doesn't?
It's not up to him.
Just tie him up.
Truss him up.
Tie him up.
Truss him up?
It's a great idea.
In that case,
he will have to like me
no matter what.
That's the spirit!
I'll help you.
I don't need your help.
I'll do it myself.
♪Is it♪
♪A destined♪
Why are you here?
♪Trap♪
♪I can't get over it♪
♪No matter how much time has passed♪
Who is this handsome young man?
He's so good-looking.
How much did you drink?
Not your business.
♪So ridiculous♪
You're drunk.
Leave.
I won't.
If I leave,
you'll run away with some bad woman.
I'm not stupid.
Look closely
at who I am.
I know.
You are
a goosie.
♪Why do I still need♪
♪To pretend not to see you♪
What are you so focused on?
♪Why do we♪
(Three Lives Without Sorrow)
Three Lives Without Sorrow?
What kind of magic book is this
that you cherish so much?
(Three Lives Without Sorrow)
It's much better than magic books.
♪Forget you again♪
(It's a story about)
(Shang You from the Holy Spirit clan)
(and Si Yuan, the King of Hell.)
(At the time,)
(to revive her clan, Shang You)
(disguised herself as a deer demon)
(and approached Si Yuan,
who destroyed her clan,)
(to lure him to fall for her)
(so that she could get his Amber Heart.)
(After Shang You took his heart,)
(Si Yuan did not die)
(because his true identity)
(was the Heartless War God,)
(while Shang You
was actually an ancient demon.)
(Their bond)
(started thousands of years ago)
(in the God-Demon War.)
They went through
three lifetimes of stories
and had only each other in their hearts
(Three Lives Without Sorrow)
with no room for anyone else.
So
in the end,
who won the God-Demon War?
Was it Si Yuan or Shang You?
(You're indeed a goosie.)
(I won't tell you.)
♪It turns out nothing has changed♪
♪Just pretend the story is replaying♪
Say that again.
What am I?
♪How should I choose♪
♪You are♪
A goosie.
♪Why do I still need♪
♪To pretend not to see you♪
♪Why do we♪
♪Dare not continue to write♪
♪At the same time♪
♪Do I have to♪
♪Forget you again♪
What are you doing here?
That's my question for you.
After drinking last night,
you left me alone in the yard,
and you slept soundly.
Never mind.
It matters not.
Come with me.
Where to?
And what for?
To set you up with General Mu.
You said you have feelings
for General Mu last night.
Have you forgotten?
(If he has feelings for me,)
(the flower of love can be stimulated.)
Stay here.
Why did you bring me here?
I meticulously prepared this for you
and General Mu.
Take full advantage of it.
I'll leave first.
Stay here.
You two stay put
and enjoy some time alone.
I also prepared a big surprise for you.
You had Yuan Jiyao bring me here.
How will you torture me?
If I say it was not me,
do you believe me?
♪I'm imprisoned in the endless abyss♪
♪In an instant♪
♪The night becomes sleepless♪
♪I'm left behind in the world alone♪
♪Through all the love♪
♪And hatred♪
♪I can't escape destiny's scheme♪
♪With one glance♪
♪The bond resolves♪
♪It's just waiting
another ten thousand years♪
♪We are fated, yet not deeply enough♪
♪We own each other nothing♪
♪It's just one heart♪
♪That was sundered into halves♪
♪When love cannot reconnect♪
♪No redemption lies in this life♪
♪How to achieve three lifetimes
with no regrets♪
♪Or missing♪
(Will it be too cruel to him
to deceive his feelings)
(to get the flower of love?)
My lord,
when burning the camp,
we found this person sneaking in,
so we captured him.
I remember him.
The late Lord of Zishang's general,
Bai Ling.
You know my identity.
Then who are you?
Who am I?
I am the one
who will take your life.
What grudges do you have
against the late Lord of Zishang?
Even if the Lord of Zishang
you respected
were cut into a thousand pieces,
his sins could not be atoned for.
His filthy and disgusting mansion
deserves to be trampled
and destroyed.
My lord,
don't torture him to death yet.
I remember when burning the camp,
there were only people from Xuanhuang
and Mu Han in the camp.
I see.
The person you are loyal to
is Mu Han.
Both of you
are remnants of Zishang.
Aren't you?
You won't tell?
Then I'll wait for Mu Han to come.
And you two can die together.
Keep an eye on him.
No mishaps are allowed.
Understood.
Your Highness,
my brother acted on his own
to deliver a message to Xuanwu
and hasn't returned yet.
Not even his body has been found.
(To save Bai Ling, come to the dungeon
before dusk tomorrow.)
Bai Ling was captured by He Chuan.
Bring me my sword.
Your Highness,
you can't go.
This is clearly a trap.
It's all because of my indecision
that Bai Ling is now in peril.
I can't let him
bear all the consequences for me.
My lord.
Princess Royal.
Did you take me here at night
to watch you torture a prisoner?
Do you know
the General Mu that you care for
is plotting
together with him?
What does that have to do with me?
You'll find out soon.
Speak.
Who are you exactly?
Who are you?
Speak.
Speak now.
Marquis Cheng'en,
why do you want me here?
General Mu.
Do you know who he is?
I don't know him.
You don't?
Alright.
Your actions
are so cruel.
Don't you fear retribution?
Mind your own business.
Brother!
♪In the deserted world♪
♪There are countless thoughts♪
♪How many of them come true♪
♪I've asked a thousand times♪
♪Who is writing♪
♪Our mutual wishes♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪