=Love Behind the Mask=
=Episode 31=
I'm sorry
for not fulfilling
my duties of marriage.
I've been in love with someone.
I will repay you
what I owe you.
My lord,
concerning Miss Wangyou...
Without my orders,
she is not allowed to step out.
Yes.
Let me out.
Miss Wangyou,
without permission,
you are not allowed to leave.
You...
I want to see him.
My lord,
Miss Wangyou wants to see you.
No.
No?
Miss Wangyou,
you haven't eaten anything for a day.
If this continues,
your body won't hold up.
Tell Mu Han.
If he doesn't show up,
I will continue my hunger strike.
My lord,
Miss Wangyou says if you don't show up,
she'll refuse to eat.
How about
seeing her?
No.
Why are you doing so?
You clearly care so much.
Why torture each other?
I don't dare to see her.
I'm afraid of losing control
and hurting her
when I see her.
(Princess Royal's Mansion)
He won't show up.
Why torture yourself here?
Let me help you leave.
You will help me?
How will you help me?
Here is some medicine.
After taking it,
you will lose breath overnight.
But it won't be deadly.
If you really want to leave,
take this medicine
and fake your death
to escape from the palace.
Why should I trust you?
What if it is poisonous?
If I truly wanted to harm you,
I wouldn't need to go through this.
I'll leave it here.
It's up to you whether you take it.
By the way,
if you don't want to leave,
that's fine too.
You can stay here.
Some days later,
welcome to join our wedding.
Miss Wangyou.
Summon the imperial physician!
Shu.
What happened?
Although her face is pale,
her breathing's steady.
It's obvious she's faking it.
Everyone, step back.
Yes.
She...
Stop pretending.
Get up.
I...
Why are you pretending
to be ill and fainting?
Do you want to leave me that badly?
What's wrong?
Why do you imprison me?
I told you,
whether you remember it or not,
you are Wen Yanshu.
Why? I'm not her.
Because I look like that woman?
Besides, you have a fiancée.
Why can't you let me go?
She is dead.
Fine.
You don't remember?
Let me help you.
Let go of me.
Look.
These are all what you loved most.
Do you remember anything?
Do you remember?
Even if you make me wear her clothes
and put on her hairpin,
it can't help.
I said I am not her.
She is dead.
And she will never come back!
Shut up!
I don't want you
to say it a second time!
Otherwise,
tomorrow, Linzhao's army
will overwhelm Zhuyan.
If you don't want to see Yan Shi'an die,
follow my instructions obediently.
You...
Don't hurt Shi'an.
It's not his fault.
I'll wear it.
I'll do as you say.
Good.
Sit down.
♪Dreams are shattered, and snow spreads♪
I just want
to keep you by my side.
I don't want to lose you again.
♪The heart eventually broke♪
But I'm not her after all.
Even if you keep me
by your side every day,
it can't help.
As long as I believe you are Wen Yanshu,
that's all that matters.
Nothing else
matters.
My lord.
Prince of Zhuyan arrives.
Behave
well.
Stay here.
I will be back soon.
♪Like a snowstorm♪
♪That shrouds the moon♪
♪If we rewrite the story♪
♪And cover the flaws♪
Where is Wangyou?
Set her free at once,
or I'll find it myself by force.
This is Linzhao.
I have
the final say.
I'm here.
Shu.
Wangyou.
Did he bully you?
I will take you back.
Let's go.
Wait!
Whether to stay or leave,
let her decide.
Wangyou,
if you agree,
I'll take you back to Zhuyan now.
Even if you don't want to be my wife,
I can still give you everything.
No one will restrict your freedom.
You can go anywhere.
Think it through before you answer.
Stop!
You both want to keep me by your side.
But have you ever thought about me?
Shu.
Wangyou.
You've heard it all, right?
Get out now.
Wherever she is,
I will be there.
Your Highness.
You've already found her.
But why haven't you
brought her back yet?
Lord of Zishang guards her closely.
I personally instigated.
But they became even more entangled.
Besides,
she seems to have fallen for him.
I'm taking her away tonight.
Coordinate me well
and take her out.
Let's meet at the backyard
of the teahouse.
Yes.
Go.
(Princess Royal's Mansion)
Shu,
calm down.
Lotus soup is good for calming mind.
Try it.
No.
Shu,
haven't we made a deal?
You would stay by my side.
Why do you have to force her?
Wangyou,
these are your favorite pastries
from Zhuyan.
Try it.
The imperial physician advised
her
not eat too many sweets.
Wangyou has always liked eating sweets.
You may not know it.
She just had lotus soup.
Can't you understand me?
Unlike you,
I don't talk the talk of doing good,
while pushing her
to do things she dislikes.
You...
Stop arguing!
Sit down.
Shu.
Wangyou.
Shi'an.
I'll take you away.
I'll promise you anything
if you go with me.
Sorry,
I don't want to be your wife
or anyone's substitute.
I just want to be myself.
Trust me.
I won't trap you anymore.
Come back with me.
What's up?
I came here just to tell you
why Yan Shi'an cares about you.
He only sees you as Wen Yanshu.
So from the beginning to the end,
in your eyes,
I am always a substitute for her.
Am I right?
No,
you are not a substitute.
♪In the deserted world♪
♪There are countless thoughts♪
♪How many of them come true♪
♪I've asked a thousand times♪
♪Who is writing♪
♪Our mutual wishes♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪