=Love Behind the Mask=
=Episode 12=
(Ancestral Hall)
Killing Lord of Zishang
equals treason.
Tonight,
I will let you
go with him.
Shu.
I made him do it.
Lord of Zishang secretly offered
sacrifices to rebel spirits.
Shouldn't we kill him?
Shu.
Killing Lord of Zishang
deserves death.
Even if I don't kill him,
His Majesty won't spare him.
Shu,
are you trying to cover for him?
Brother,
I'm not covering for him,
just killing someone for you.
That night,
you wanted to
kill Lord of Zishang, right?
Can we go now?
Stand down!
(Ancestral Hall)
(Father.)
(Lord of Zishang, secretly
enshrined rebel spirits)
(with intent to rebel,)
(has been eliminated by me.)
(I stationed here)
(to stabilize it.)
(Zishang)
(will be under control soon.)
How did you sleep last night?
Not bad.
How about you?
Thank you
for helping me kill Si Sheng.
You're welcome, Your Highness.
This is
what I should do.
The weather is nice today.
Do you like sunny days
or rainy days?
Neither.
People's mood
is subject to changes.
You should
go outside more often.
Okay.
Why hasn't Wen Yanshu
come back yet?
She is not Wen Yanshu.
When you arrive at Zhuyan State,
we will settle these grudges.
Last night,
a handsome young man entered my dream.
But unfortunately,
it was just a fleeting moment.
Upon arriving in another country,
put away your lovesick expression.
Hurry up and pack your things to leave.
(Garden with Splendor)
♪My excitement like strong wine
sliding down the throat♪
He
is the person in my dream.
(Shi'an.)
Wait for me.
Here's a person.
Wake up.
Who are you?
♪Filled with desolation♪
This way, the wound is gone.
Much better.
Is it good-looking?
Not long ago, I learned
Linzhao's envoy is coming
to visit Zhuyan.
My father is very happy.
But recently, he has been ill,
unable to meet with you all.
So I will entertain you all.
♪The world is so absurd♪
I am the Crown Prince of Zhuyan State,
Yan Shi'an.
♪Every word and sentence is staggering♪
♪Stories of the world have ended♪
Please.
On this visit,
we brought rare treasures from Linzhao
for you.
We do not lack these things.
You might have heard
Linzhao and Xuanhuang
are in constant
conflict.
This is a national crisis.
Zhuyan's help is needed.
If Zhuyan has any requests,
we will
help with all our strength.
Our Zhuyan is full of gold.
Helping you in this urgent matter
is a trivial thing.
But today, I wonder if you are willing
to give me what I want.
Your Highness,
please.
I want Princess Royal
to dance a piece for me.
Show me your sincerity.
What do you think?
Let me tell you, Your Highness.
Princess Royal
looks extraordinarily beautiful.
Her dance
is also excellent.
Your Highness,
Princess Royal
is the dignity of Linzhao.
This might be inappropriate.
Is this your attitude
towards peace talks?
The soldiers are fighting to the death
but are not receiving relief.
Now Princess Royal
is merely dancing a piece,
but you find it so difficult.
How ridiculous!
Your Highness's sincerity,
how much is it worth?
I am willing to spend a fortune.
Your Highness, what do you think?
I hope
you will act as promised.
Shu.
How about dancing barefoot?
If you fall,
I will consider you
lack of sincerity.
♪At dusk♪
♪The bright moon and gentle breeze♪
Well done.
(When did Shu learn this dance?)
♪I want to pick up the brush♪
♪Write down poetic lines♪
♪Obscure expressions
show full of sorrow♪
♪With every stroke♪
♪The word "love" is easy to write♪
♪Trapped me for a lifetime♪
♪Completion always brings hopes♪
Bravo.
♪Mountains are always♪
♪Separated♪
♪People are always♪
♪Regretting the separation♪
♪Silver frost paints the night,
and I sigh my dreams♪
♪Feeling all over chilling♪
♪In the fate, we♪
♪Having thousands of entanglements♪
♪Yet the song ends and we disperse♪
♪We missed each other♪
♪The sound of light rain
falling on the eaves♪
♪Can't express all the sorrow♪
♪Heartless ink marks♪
♪Leaving a few articles♪
♪Heaven doesn't fulfill people's wishes♪
♪In the deserted world♪
♪There are countless thoughts♪
♪How many of them come true♪
♪I've asked a thousand times♪
♪Who is writing♪
♪Our mutual wishes♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪