=Love Behind the Mask=
=Episode 16=
Mind your own business.
Brother!
Let me do it.
My lord,
he's dead.
Sorry.
I just wanted
to torture him a bit.
I didn't expect him to die so quickly.
Then throw him into the mass grave
and bury him.
General,
we haven't found Bai Ling's body.
You may leave.
Your Majesty.
Please spare me.
Your Majesty...
Maybe the blood spirit
can only be continued
by Shu's bloodline.
Your Majesty,
is it bad news from the border?
To avenge his son,
King of Xuanhuang
deployed all his forces.
Our border
has already fallen.
Forgive my bluntness.
If we agree to the marriage alliance,
Zhuyan will definitely
send reinforcements immediately.
Shu cannot marry far away.
But the Crown Prince of Zhuyan
specifically requested her.
She can't be replaced.
Your Majesty,
Zhuyan's Crown Prince's letter.
(Yan Shi'an)
(If Your Majesty doesn't marry
the Princess Royal to me,)
(we)
(will then fully support Xuanhuang.)
Please calm your anger.
Did the Crown Prince of Zhuyan
say something in the letter?
The top priority now
is to quickly arrange
Shu's dowry.
Once she marries into Zhuyan
and gets pregnant,
there will be ways
to summon her back.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Father
won't have me marry away
in place of Wen Yanshu, will he?
I'm afraid that's his intention.
Don't worry.
I will finalize your marriage soon.
Okay.
Fuyu,
do you have someone you like?
Of course, I do.
I've already had someone in my mind.
(Taiji Hall)
I've drafted the decree
for the marriage alliance.
Father!
Hurry up and accept the decree.
The Crown Prince of Zhuyan
is very fond of you.
You will grow old together in happiness.
Your Majesty,
since Shu's marriage has been settled,
why not finalize Fuyu's marriage
as well?
Okay.
Fuyu.
♪Holding tightly to the obsession♪
General Mu
is a young talent.
Fuyu has long admired him.
It's truly a match made in heaven
and another delightful event.
Mu Han,
are you willing to marry me?
Wen Yanshu will leave
for the marriage alliance
and never return.
If you are willing to marry me,
you will not only be a general.
But in the future,
I'll get you to a position
below none but one.
At that time,
if you want the throne...
I'm not getting married.
Shu.
Everyone, leave.
Leave.
Shu,
do you remember
the consequence of defying me
last time?
Father, please calm down.
I'm just sad about the thought
of leaving you
and my country.
That's why...
Your marriage
is settled.
(If I refuse,)
(the people of Linzhao
will be plunged into misery.)
(If I accept it,)
(the worst result)
(is to tell Shi'an the truth,)
(and I'll still have a way out.)
I accept it.
It's just that I want
to choose the entourage for myself.
I know
your little schemes.
Shu,
don't overdo it.
I understand.
(Princess Royal's Mansion)
Is Shu going to marry for alliance?
Why are you so angry?
Have a cup of tea
and calm down.
In 24 hours,
I'm sending her to marry for alliance.
Aren't you preparing anything?
Do you believe
I will kill you right now?
Even if you kill me,
it will not change the fact
of the marriage alliance.
Her Royal Highness is helpless now.
The only one who can save her
is you.
Do you think I don't know
this is the trap you set,
waiting for me
to step into it obediently?
She has been kind to me.
I don't want her to live in misery
in a foreign land.
If you are willing to save her,
I can pretend not to see anything.
Why do you think
I will believe what you say?
Do you have another choice?
Will you watch the person
you care about the most
marry someone else far away
and have children
so that you will never
see her again?
Think about it.
My lord,
are you really snatching the bride?
This mission is very important.
Be sure to find a few skilled people
and act cautiously
so as to alert no one.
Understood.
(Princess Royal's Mansion)
(Prosperity Court)
The journey ahead is long.
I will ensure
Your Royal Highness's safety.
Capture the rebel attempting
to sabotage the marriage alliance.
♪In the deserted world♪
♪There are countless thoughts♪
♪How many of them come true♪
♪I've asked a thousand times♪
♪Who is writing♪
♪Our mutual wishes♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪
♪When I open my eyes♪
♪I see your smiling face♪
♪Years pass by like fleeting water♪
♪And the world keeps changing♪
♪I wish to be with you
for the rest of my life♪
♪No fear of winds far away♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Time is exchanged for moments♪
♪If wishes can come true♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Eternity is the end point♪
♪Facing the abyss♪
♪Between you and me♪
♪Why fear this nightmare♪
♪Ultimately one day♪
♪The world changes no more♪
♪Allowing me to gaze again♪
♪At your smile♪