[Unenlightened to love]
♫ Presenting you with scenery you never come across ♫
♫ I love it ♫
♫ All the sounds you have ever heard ♫
♫ Lost track of time, searching for the perfect
night sky on the pale blue wind ♫
♫ We ride with ease, locating the heavy rain ♫
♫ The way you lose control is amusing ♫
♫ It's fantastic ♫
♫ The plan was salvaged through a hail of bullets ♫
♫ Including the next second ♫
♫ I can't find the evidence of being defeated by you ♫
♫ Lost track of time, searching for the perfect
night sky on the pale blue wind ♫
♫ We ride with ease, locating the heavy rain ♫
♫ The way you lose control is amusing ♫
♫ Looking for new topics ♫
♫ Leaving them to expectations ♫
♫ Whether it's windy or rainy tomorrow ♫
♫ I will be there ♫
♫ Back to the starting point, I come to understand ♫
♫ I'm still by your side ♫
[Why Women Love]
Delivery. Delivery. Delivery.
Coming.
Delivery!
Miss Zhao, here.
Please sign for your package.
Package?
Cover your skin.
It's covered.
What is this?
Since I'm teaching you how to fall in love,
we'll have our first lesson tomorrow.
We look for feelings of first love.
Please date me.
You?
No special meanings.
You... You haven't dated anyone for too long.
You've lost your love nerves.
I... just... going to help you activate your muscle memory.
We'll also have some fun in passing, outside of work.
I'll show you what a nice date means.
Dating a nice person is a nice date.
But with you? That's just more work.
Right. Work it is. I arranged everything.
Just follow my lead tomorrow.
Isn't this my high school uniform?
Where did you get it?
It cost me a whole set of game skin to get it.
Just for the date tomorrow.
Remember to bring your alumni card.
Don't say no. Good night.
[Episode 4]
[My heart flutters, but I'm not in love]
How we are dressed is so embarrassing.
People will laugh at us.
- No, I'm going upstairs to get changed.
- No, wait.
The atmosphere is important.
Can't you just cooperate?
I cooperated enough.
It was silly of me following your plans.
I should've stayed at the company and worked. Not playing "house" with you.
Do you know what the most important thing is when it comes to dating?
The most important thing is not where we go,
what we do, or who we're with.
It's enjoying the present,
feeling your own heartbeat,
and looking forward to love.
Come on.
♫ Presenting you with scenery you never come across ♫
♫ I love it ♫
♫ All the sounds you have ever heard ♫
♫ Lost track of time, searching for the perfect
night sky on the pale blue wind ♫
♫ We ride with ease, locating the heavy rain ♫
♫ The way you lose control is amusing ♫
♫ Presenting you with scenery you never come across ♫
♫ I love it ♫
♫ All the sounds you have ever heard ♫
♫ Lost track of time, searching for the perfect
night sky on the pale blue wind ♫
♫ We ride with ease, locating the heavy rain ♫
♫ The way you lose control is amusing ♫
[Sujiang]
I told you to slow down.
You had to ride so fast.
I'd have thrown up if you had driven any faster.
No way.
I was slow today.
I'm glad I haven't eaten.
So? Did your heart beat faster?
It almost jumped out of my chest.
Exactly. Speed can excite you and make you nervous.
Then adrenaline will rise sharply
and the heart beats faster.
Many people mistakenly think the feeling of the heartbeat means you're in love.
What's your point?
Teacher Gu is teaching you.
Ask the boy you like out. Choose activities that can boost your adrenaline.
Such as watching horror films, room escaping,
and riding roller coasters.
It will increase the probability of the other person falling for you.
Calculating.
[Sujiang First High School]
It's been so long.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay. Let's go.
Take out your alumni card, or they won't let us in.
This place used to be a shop.
Why is it a toilet now?
We used to buy snacks here.
Was it delicious?
Yeah.
Wow!
I miss that.
You must've been a good student.
Of course.
Are you on there?
Of course not. It's been so many years.
Let's take a look.
Which year?
I'm not telling you.
There is me.
[Outstanding Graduate]
Is that you?
Stop. Don't.
You look prettier now.
I never relied on my face all these years.
I relied on this.
Your hair?
Talent.
Right.
Look how you were dressed.
I can tell you never had puppy love.
Who said I didn't?
I guessed.
There are so many regrets in your journey of love.
[Bulletin Board]
Don't forget about our theme today.
- We look for feelings of first love. Follow me.
- To where?
The place where campus couples like to go the most.
I'll let you have your youth back.
We are at the playground.
What for?
Playground at night.
The place where countless teenage love sprouts.
Guess which pairs of students are couples.
Over there.
Aren't they afraid of being caught by teachers?
That's the thing about campus love.
Most things are not allowed.
Hold my hand.
Do we have to go into such details?
Give it a try.
How about now?
- Do you feel anything?
- No.
Then, why did you peek at me?
- I...
- You...
keep pretending.
The rostrum. Let's go.
Where?
Why are we here?
Just follow me.
[Fun Games]
I heard that this place
is where campus couples secretly go to make wishes.
Here.
- Look. Look.
- I didn't know about this place.
This is vandalism.
[Story needed. Already restored. Do not imitate]
Can't you have some fun?
Look at the darkness.
[Story needed. Already restored. Do not imitate]
What a good time to date.
Xue Dabao "lives for" Zhao Jiangyue.
[Story needed. Already restored. Do not imitate]
Who is Xue Dabao?
Xue Dabao?
Is this the one who always had a runny nose?
Seems like it wasn't a romantic memory.
I recall. He wrote love letters to me.
And he always wrote "lives for" instead of "love."
The way he pursued girls. It was never going to work.
Also, back at school, I wouldn't date.
It's bad for studying.
You haven't changed a bit.
My goal was clear.
Schools were for study.
I would graduate with the best grades and work at the best company.
I had no time for dating.
In his case,
then when was your first love?
Don't tell me it's after you started working?
Why do you have so many questions?
Information check?
Was it with Mr. Xu?
Don't spout nonsense.
Are you nervous?
Your eye contact was different that day.
It's not what you think.
When I had my first job after I graduated,
Mr. Xu was my supervisor.
He was kind to me.
I respect him a lot.
Then, why did you quit?
He looks more like a good leader than my mom does.
Later, he was sent abroad by the company.
And I went to work at another company as well.
It was natural.
Do you know why I like racing?
Because it reminds me to live in the present.
Let bygones be bygones.
Why did you write down your name?
[Gu Jiaxin ❤️ Zhao Jiangyue]
It's worse than Xue Dabao.
Why am I worse than Xue Dabao?
You are too hard to move.
One final trick left. Come with me.
[Gu Jiaxin ❤️ Zhao Jiangyue]
♫ Get on an unknown train ♫
♫ Love will decide where the destination is ♫
♫ Expectation brings more fear of being hurt ♫
Zhao Jiangyue, I like you!
♫ Fearing that I still have to leave someday ♫
♫ Now the world, it is upside down ♫
♫ And we were floating in the sky ♫
What are you doing? Stop.
Zhao Jiangyue, I like you!
- Stop.
- The student there!
- Zhao...
- Stop! Student there. Which class are you in?
Stand right there. Don't move!
- Stand right there.
- We run?
We run.
♫ Now the world, it is upside down ♫
♫ 'Cause I'm so loving you and you loved me too ♫
[Run! Juveniles]
♫ Now the world, it is upside down ♫
♫ And we were floating in the sky ♫
Where are they?
Maybe ahead. Come on.
Do you feel anything?
Feel what?
Feelings of first love.
When we were running,
I was a little frantic.
Right. That's right.
Let's go.
My friend,
fancy underwear.
In the back.
I didn't show my best self today.
Let's continue next time.
No need.
I've felt it.
Thank you.
Huh? For what?
You made me feel the confidence and happiness I had in school.
I could focus on my studies back then and date no one.
I can still focus on my work now and date no one.
That's not right. Stop.
I can be so excellent because I worked hard back then.
Then I should work even harder now so that I could be more excellent.
This is the logic, right?
It's a big problem.
Returning to school today has made me feel energized.
I feel so much more energetic.
I can work an extra 24 hours without feeling tired.
Oh god, come on.
You're style is so messed up.
This is not what I wanted.
It's what I want.
So, thank you. My good assistant.
Hold on to your Calabash Brothers. Let's go back.
Hey!
Now I know who forever single people look like.
[7 SEVEN!!! CUCURBNBOY]
[Lived together for three years before knowing he was a scum]
[Having a secret crush is painful. What should I do?]
[Gaslighting is terrible]
[Long-distance relationship, I recently found out that he might be cheating on me]
Why do people date?
I shouldn't have set the goal.
One wrong promise may cause lifelong regret.
[Influencer Qian Jingjing's husband secretly dated a hot girl in the pub]
[Qian Jingjing avoided interviews]
[No response yet to the rumor that her husband, Zhang Hao, might be cheating]
[Does this mean the rumor is true?]
Here she comes.
The news that Mr. Zhang Hao secretly dated a girl in a pub.
Did you see it? Did you know about his affair with a young model?
Miss Qian, please make a statement.
Did you know that Zhang Hao had an affair with a young model?
Please respond, Miss Qian.
Mr. Zhang Hao cheated.
Even Zhang Hao could cheat.
I don't believe in love anymore.
The mistress is prettier than Qian Jingjing.
Isn't it men's nature to chase new things?
Divorce. Scum will die painfully.
Oh my god.
[Superluminal Entertainment]
What is this?
[Jingjing]
Jingjing,
are you all right?
- Where are you now?
- I'm home.
Can I come to you?
- The news about Zhang Hao...
- You don't need to come. I'm fine.
The news is fake.
Are you with him now?
How did he explain to you?
It was a misunderstanding.
Zhang Hao is on his way back.
He said he'll explain after he comes back.
Don't worry, I won't let this thing affect the launch of your application.
Don't worry about the company.
You just take care of yourself.
And if you need anything, you have to tell me.
Okay, don't worry. We're fine.
Okay. Time to hang up. Zhang Hao is back.
He is here to apologize.
The punishment is ready.
Okay.
[Link Technology]
[Sorry, we made everyone worry. Fake news. Please don't worry.]
Now speak. Otherwise, my fans will be pissed.
Hi, everyone. I'm Zhang Hao.
I'd like to talk about the picture of the trending topic.
It was made out of thin air.
I was at a party with friends.
And the angle of the shooting
was purposely chosen by intentional people,
which made me very angry.
But as a husband, I got my wife, Qian Jingjing,
in such big trouble.
Here, to Jingjing and everyone who cares about her, I sincerely apologize.
Meanwhile, I want to inform the accounts
who are posting aggressive messages online
that I've prepared a demand letter.
You should be prepared, too.
Jingjing, from now on, I won't let anyone hurt you again.
Let's check the comments.
- Next page.
- Jiaxin.
The next page.
[Only the wearer knows where the shoe pinches. Why are some so jealous of others' happiness?]
Let's look at the comments. Pretty Positive.
[Only the wearer knows where the shoe pinches.
Why are some so jealous of others' happiness?]
PR Department. Buy more trending topics while the public opinion has reversed.
Don't let this topic go unnoticed.
Combine Qian Jingjing being cheated with "Love Note."
Different topics can be forwarded together.
Okay, I'll go get ready.
Such a good chance for free promotion.
We can't miss it.
All departments need to speed up.
- Start the internal test in advance.
- Okay.
That's all.
Come with me.
I have a question.
Was that statement credible to you?
What do you mean?
Jingjing is not just the poster of our company,
she is also my best friend.
I worry about her.
About Jingjing...
Anything to eat?
Sweets.
Firstly, no matter if Zhang Hao cheated or not,
people believed Qian Jingjing's words.
And "Love Note" got attention because of it.
I consider that a good thing.
As for the truth, whether they are okay,
you can ask her directly.
Don't worry.
Jingjing is beautiful and feminine.
I believe in her charm.
Right. She'll come for filming next week.
If you worry about her, you can ask her then.
[Link Technology New APP "Love Note" will be launched as scheduled]
Tips for communication in relationships.
Talk like you're pulling pranks.
In other words, when you talk with a guy, tease him.
For example,
"Oh, you have something on your face."
"Just kidding."
Oh, you have something on your face.
- Just kidding.
- All the VIPs of "Love Note," did you master it?
Pulling pranks sometimes can deepen your connection and affection.
Miss Li, your coffee is ready.
Two cups.
Look into an application for me.
It's called "Love Note." From Link Technology.
Yes. Link Technology.
Okay.
Mister, you have good taste.
Link Technology. It's my boyfriend's company.
Your boyfriend?
This is my boyfriend. Here.
Isn't he handsome?
Don't we make a good couple?
Your boyfriend is the owner of Link Technology?
His mother is the chairman of the company.
So the company will be his sooner or later.
I'm leaving now.
He will be off work soon. I'm going to surprise him.
Mister, remember to download the application.
Jiaxin!
Surprise.
Li Yanran? Weren't you abroad?
It's been a long time. Did you miss me?
I bought you coffee.
Your place is big.
Nice bed. I like it.
Wait. You are a girl in anothers' place.
Do not lie down.
Stand up.
When did you get back?
I just arrived today.
I came to see you before I started suffering from jet lag.
I'm super nice to you, right?
Be honest.
How did you know where I live?
Isn't it easy for me to know where you live?
You cannot escape from me.
Wait! Why are you back?
I came back to have fun with you. It was boring without you.
I don't have time for you. I'm busy.
I know.
Ms. Jin told me that you are working hard at the company.
Working super hard.
That's great.
I won't... won't disturb you.
Oh, right.
Why did you want to live alone?
This place doesn't seem to be convenient.
And you can't keep Ms. Jin company.
Adults need to learn to leave home and live alone.
It's close to the company.
I like it here.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Then I do, too.
Should I move here to live with you?
No way.
You are a girl. It's not safe for you.
You can protect me.
Quit being naughty.
I said no.
In order to see you,
I didn't have time to eat anything.
I'm so hungry now.
What do you want to eat? I'll order it for you.
Okay.
I'll send you home afterward.
Don't even think about sleeping here.
Then I'll eat slower.
Let's go out to eat then.
I want pizza.
It's closed.
Then I'll have this. This.
- Roast duck?
- It's not good. It's not good.
Have you ever tried it before?
Ms. Zhao, the equipment is ready.
Once Jingjing arrives, we'll be able to start.
- Send me a copy of the script.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you? Being so down?
Are you ill?
Bad luck. These days.
Young lad, don't be superstitious.
Pull yourself together and go to work.
Everybody, we are about to go live streaming.
Jingjing, are you ready?
[Home-field Advantage]
Jingjing? Ready?
[Qian Jingjing's Love School]
- Good.
- Okay. Three, two, one.
Go.
Today, we'll talk about home-field advantage.
Once some ladies fall in love,
they let the other person take control
and forget that they should have the initiative.
Home-field advantage is about dating
in your own field.
Only then can women shine bright.
Did something really happento Jingjing and her husband?
No one can be a superwoman forever.
No matter how bright she smiles,
the sadness always stays in her eyes.
So we have to find our own home-field advantages in relationships.
You seem a bit tired today.
Are things really okay between you and Zhang Hao?
Yes. We are doing fine.
That's good to hear.
How did he explain to you that day?
Did he kneel all night?
Certainly.
His knees were swollen.
He dared to make it so public.
Of course, I couldn't forgive him easily.
What...
[Divorce Certificate]
Didn't you two work it out?
Jiangyue...
I...
I'm divorced.
I just went to the Civil Affairs Bureau.
I knew that things weren't so simple.
Men always lie.
Zhang Hao, what a bastard. I will make him pay.
But... how could you agree to it so easily?
Isn't it too easy for them?
I didn't want to, either.
But I had no other choice.
I know what you want to say.
It's all for business. I get it.
But even if you apologize genuinely, I wouldn't forgive you so easily.
The news was real.
What did you say?
I indeed cheated on you.
Nonsense!
I know you. You won't do such things.
I said, the news was real.
If I have to be blunt about it...
Jingjing, I don't love you anymore.
Let me go.
I don't believe your feelings have changed.
How long have you known her?
Three months.
How long have we known each other?
Five years and six days.
Three months could beat our relationship of five years?
Did you forget what you promised me?
You said you'd love me forever.
Jingjing.
Let's divorce.
I know this is cruel to you.
So, I'll take full responsibility for my doing.
[Divorce Agreement]
You can take all the real estate and property.
I'll take nothing.
Think about it.
I don't want to divorce. I refuse to do so.
It's not going to work.
Do you think that if you don't sign the paper,
we won't be able to divorce?
Zhang Hao, have you ever loved me?
Qian Jingjing, have you ever loved me?
Can you tell me you love "me"
or the fake character online,
the perfect husband, Zhang Hao?
Fine.
Divorce it is.
But I have a condition.
Name it.
I just started endorsing Jiangyue's application.
Our divorce cannot go public.
You need to keep playing the good couple with me.
No problem.
Of course, no problem.
I'll see you tomorrow at the Civil Affairs Bureau.
You know what?
At that moment,
I knew he was serious.
He really doesn't love me anymore.
A sugarcane man.
He tastes sweet
but leaves nothing but scum.
Don't worry, Jiangyue.
Although I got divorced,
I won't let my mess have any bad influence on you.
I looked into it.
If I don't announce the divorce within six months,
it won't count as a breach of being the poster of "Love Note."
Instead of that,
I'm more concerned about you.
What will you do?
Don't you believe me?
I'm the Queen of Love.
Divorce is no big deal.
Don't worry.
I'll make sure Zhang Hao gets what he deserves.
We can't expose him yet.
After all,
we need to keep playing the sweet couple.
Otherwise, it'll have a bad influence on your company.
It'll ruin you, Jiangyue.
No, it won't.
Hail to being single.
Countless scum,
but only one bestie.
Don't cry.
- Don't cry.
- I'm leaving. Go back to work.
I'll walk you out.
Wait.
Okay. Let's go.
[7 SEVEN!!! CUCURBNBOY]
[Love Note: The theory of 60% destiny]
Under many circumstances, we'll consider someone is not really bad.
We feel that they are nice and think that he or she might be a good partner.
But when it comes to pursuing, you don't really feel like it.
When we set terminating singlehood as the final goal,
and the requirements for the other half become not so strict,
then our type will no longer be one person.
It will be a group of persons, instead.
This is the so-called transient "The theory of 60% destiny."
In this case, when we lack the motivation to pursue someone proactively,
what we need to do is turn the 60% into 100%.
Increase the chance of the other person making a move first.
Firstly, do your skincare, enhance self-confidence.
Be aware that no matter how we look,
confidence is the reason that a person shines.
Secondly, do your time management.
Manage your time.
Make some room for your potential dates.
Thirdly, no more fantasy.
Accept the other person's imperfection.
Agree to disagree. Learn how to get along.
The 60% fate can gain 100% love.
I'm your Love Bestie, Zhao Jiangyue.
Run into problems of love? Remember that "Love Note" can help.
[Love Note]
Please let me help you as I'm helping myself.
♫ Love me, love me ♫
♫ Say you love me now ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Love me, love me ♫
♫ The right person... Oh, my true love ♫
♫ Don't rush into defining love ♫
♫ Orderliness is not a problem ♫
♫ Being harmonious is the key ♫
♫ If facing difficulty in inhabiting a role due to apathy ♫
♫ Don't dwell on your astonishment ♫
♫  Keep me in consideration ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Tips on improving compatibility ♫
♫ I'm telling you now ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Say you love me now ♫
♫ I will always love you ♫
♫ Love is true love ♫
♫ It's my love ♫
♫ It's true love ♫
♫ Now I need you, give me your love ♫
♫ The love is true ♫
♫ It's true love ♫
♫ Please let me know when you have fallen for me ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Love me, love me ♫
♫ Say you love me now ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Love me, love me ♫
♫ The right person... Oh, my true love ♫
♫ Don't rush into defining love ♫
♫ Orderliness is not a problem ♫
♫ Being harmonious is the key ♫
♫ If facing difficulty in inhabiting a role due to apathy ♫
♫ Don't dwell on your astonishment ♫
♫ Keep me in consideration ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Tips on improving compatibility ♫
♫ I'm telling you now ♫
♫ Say you love me ♫
♫ Say you love me now ♫
♫ I will always love you ♫
♫ Love is true love ♫
♫ It's my love ♫
♫ It's true love ♫
♫ Now I need you, give me your love ♫
♫ The love is true ♫
♫ It's true love ♫
♫ Nothing can stop true love ♫