[English subtitles are available]
[2004]
Will you write it or not?
I will.
I will!
Write.
It's taken care of.
Here.
What is this?
Luck is coming.
It's a good omen.
Do you know the address?
Send it over.
Understood.
[Shangshu Building]
Boss.
It's done.
Okay.
[TELL NO ONE]
[Episode 12: The Truth]
Chief Li.
Child.
It's okay, Uncle Li.
Let me see my dad.
I can handle it.
Jiadong.
This was the first bullet
I shot after I became a police officer.
I saved it for a long time.
I know you have
wanted it for a long time too.
Today,
I'll give it to you as a gift.
Congratulations on getting into college.
No.
This is such an important thing.
Dad,
you're giving it to Jiadong,
but even I don't have one yet.
This kid.
Give it to me.
Let go.
Uncle Zheng gave it to me.
Thank you, Uncle Zheng.
Jiadong,
this bullet
is very special,
because to me,
it represents justice.
I hope you can
become a just and brave person
and become a real man.
Then I'll put it on.
Dad,
you always say in my dreams
that it feels wet and cold.
There are bugs too.
Yes.
It must be so cold lying here.
Sorry, Dad.
I came late.
I'll take you home tomorrow.
You won't feel cold again.
Uncle Li.
Gao...
Gao... Gao Hu?
You're a cop?
Chen Jiadong.
From now on,
I'll be in charge of
your interrogation.
Gao Hu,
tell them.
I...
How could I...
How could I be a murderer?
My father
just passed away.
My sister is still at home.
How could I?
Do you think
that your plan is perfect
and meticulous?
All the insiders are dead
and they can't testify now.
You think we can't do anything about you, right?
If you want to know anything,
just ask me.
I'll tell you everything.
Do you recognize this?
This was a gift from Zheng Ying to you.
Why did your personal belonging
appear now
in Zheng Ying's hand?
Also,
why was Zheng Ying's body
buried in your backyard?
I want to see my sister.
[Linjiang City Psychiatric Hospital]
♫Bright stars follow♫
♫The bugs fly♫
♫Who are you missing?♫
♫The stars in the sky hang low♫
Xueying.
♫The roses♫
Go.
♫On the ground wither♫
I gave the recording to Lei Naiwu.
I wanted him to kill Gao Hu,
but this loser
was useless.
However, he was already supposed to die,
because he'd crossed my limit.
He dared to hurt my sister.
Anyone who dares to hurt my sister must die.
Lei Naiwu and Chen Jingming
had to pay the price.
Without them,
my mother wouldn't have died.
And your father, Gao Hu.
You must have seen
my video gift.
You lost your father that day,
while I saw the recording.
Chen Jingming was usually
a submissive coward. I didn't expect
he would do such a thing.
I was angry,
but I decided to help keep it a secret.
If I died...
But the next day,
my mom still found out.
She wanted to take Chen Jingming to turn himself in.
Go away!
I couldn't allow Chen Jingming to be arrested.
If he was arrested,
our whole family would have to go back to the countryside.
Go away, Jiadong.
We'd worked so hard
to get out of that quagmire.
Go home.
But things went out of control.
Xue!
I accidentally killed my mother.
Since then,
I hated Chen Jingming so much.
If it weren't for him,
my mom wouldn't have died
and my sister wouldn't have gotten sick.
Countless times before,
I stood by his bed
and thought of countless ways
to kill him.
But I suddenly figured it out.
I wanted to keep him.
I wanted him to live.
I wanted him to wish he was dead.
The death of Gao Jialing on June 11th
was Pandora's box.
They killed Gao Jialing
and my mother.
No one who participated in these sins
could escape,
including Liu Qing.
I went to Industrial University
and majored in chemistry.
My research direction
was the ink printing of banknotes.
I finally got the chance I was waiting for.
You still haven't figured out
the ink formula?
Jiadong,
you bastard!
That night,
I gave Chen Jingming
a big slap.
From now on,
you need me.
I can help you succeed.
Brat,
you can even hit your father.
That was the first time
I felt a thrill in my life.
Chen Jingming had to listen to me.
Liu Qing had to listen to me too.
They were just my puppets.
They were worthless.
They were just
one part of my plan,
all just objects to be buried with my mother.
I wanted to put
everyone inside.
Have some tea.
The explosives are buried.
Is it enough?
Don't worry.
After tomorrow,
there won't be any evidence
and the necessary people would be gone too.
You have to wash your clothes when they're dirty.
If there's lice...
You have to burn it.
Jiadong,
I realized
you're the one who will do great things.
You're much stronger than your father.
Boss Liu,
I'm just worried
you'll fail in your old age
after being successful your entire life.
Do you really think so?
Of course.
Jiadong,
I like it.
[Jin Min]
By the way,
I'm afraid Chen Jingming will make trouble.
Don't let him go.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Drink.
Naiwu.
Think of a way
to stop him
from walking around these days.
Why did you push me?
You're too slow.
I considered everything,
but I didn't expect
that the Lu Sheng doing the deal with us
would be Zheng Ying.
Since Zheng Ying is here,
it means this deal
is completely
under the police's control.
I must tell Liu Qing as soon as possible
that this plan
has completely failed.
Unfortunately, Zheng Ying...
Saw me too.
Jiadong.
Jiadong,
why are you here?
How do you know Liu Qing's group?
Go back with me now.
Let's tell the truth
and apply for clemency.
I'll accompany you.
Let's go back.
Get up.
Don't be afraid.
I'll take you back.
Let's go.
Go!
I shot him just like that.
But when I was about to
add a second shot,
I suddenly hesitated.
I thought about it.
I couldn't give him another shot.
I wanted to take him back.
I wanted to kill Chen Jingming's good friend
in front of him.
Jiadong.
What happened?
Jiadong!
This...
Who is this?
You know him too.
Zheng?
Isn't this...
Isn't this your Uncle Zheng?
He's also Lu Sheng.
Lu Sheng?
How...
How did he get shot?
I shot him.
Quickly send him to the hospital.
Quickly send him to the hospital!
Hurry.
Send him to the hospital.
Jiadong.
He saw me today.
Either he dies or I die.
Kill him.
What did you say?
I said kill him.
Jiadong, are you crazy?
This is your Uncle Zheng.
When Lei Naiwu tells you to kill someone,
you do it.
But when I tell you to kill someone,
you won't listen to me?
Jiadong.
Back then,
I had no choice.
I did it for you,
for Xueying,
for our family...
I had no choice.
No matter if he was...
Something Jialing,
Gao Jialing or something,
I didn't know him, after all.
But this is...
This is your Uncle Zheng.
He's my good friend.
Jiadong,
take him to the hospital.
Chen Jingming.
He's your good friend.
The one who died
because of that recording back then
was my mom.
It was your wife.
I know.
So...
So I
regret it too.
I don't want you
to do anything you regret again.
Chen Jingming.
Do you know
that I've wanted to kill you all these years?
But why didn't I kill you?
Do you know?
Because I want to see you
wish you were dead instead.
Jiadong.
Kill him.
I told you to kill him.
Jiadong.
Can't do it?
Then watch from the side.
I'm sorry.
Chen Jingming was such a coward.
To be honest,
when I suffocated Zheng Ying,
Chen Jingming didn't even
dare to breathe.
[Control Room 2]
I'll be there on the day
you get executed.
Behave yourself.
Take him away.
Go.
Let's go.
Zheng,
[Mother Hu Wanying, Father Zheng Ying]
I have something
to talk to you about.
The night before the deal,
you and Gao Yang
disappeared for 46 minutes.
Where did you go?
I've asked Gao Yang.
He kept hiding it from me.
He wouldn't tell me the truth.
I'll say it.
You all listen
and see if I'm right.
Royal Flush!
Coming.
Have some supper.
Hu is here.
Hu.
How is he?
He's inside. He's fine.
You always lose, but you still play.
Don't drink too much.
Okay.
There's work tomorrow.
Go work, Hu.
Are you hungry, Mr. Lu?
Where are we going?
What happened?
Mom is dying.
Go back.
Look at the situation now.
Go back now.
Blame it on me if anything happens.
What are you talking about?
Honey,
I didn't take good care of you.
How are you?
I'm here.
Tomorrow,
I'll take you out of the hospital.
Honey,
I won't leave you.
I won't walk a single step away.
Stay safe.
♫Can't bear to miss you too much♫
♫I'm afraid the memory will fade♫
♫In my dream, you're by my side♫
♫If I reach out, I can touch your face♫
♫After so many years♫
♫Loneliness is more obvious♫
♫The you from before seems to be by my side♫
♫I returned to the yesterday♫
♫I want to stay by your side, no matter how many years♫
♫Freely and safely let time flow♫
♫Experience the hardships and sweetness together with you♫
♫Forge on even without a poetic future♫
♫I want to keep your footsteps and soften your time♫
♫Let the world spin with strength and persistence♫
♫Looking for the hardships and sweetness with you♫
♫Even without a poetic future, it's still a place with love♫
♫Can't bear to miss you too much♫
♫I'm afraid the memory will fade♫
♫In my dream, you're by my side♫
♫If I reach out, I can touch your face♫
♫After so many years♫
♫Loneliness is more obvious♫
♫The you from before seems to be by my side♫
♫I returned to the yesterday♫
Doctor.
♫I want to stay by your side, no matter how many years♫
Your mom has passed away.
We did our best.
♫Freely and safely let time flow♫
Mom.
Mom!
♫Experience the hardships and sweetness together with you♫
♫Forge on even without a poetic future♫
Zheng,
♫I want to keep your footsteps and soften your time♫
Sister-in-law,
it's been six years.
♫Let the world spin with strength and persistence♫
Now, you can be together
without worry.
♫Looking for the hardships and sweetness with you♫
A toast to you.
♫Even without a poetic future, it's still a place with love♫
♫I want to stay by your side♫
Hu?
Hu.
What's the commotion for?
Hu,
Boss called.
He said it's a long journey, so leave at daybreak.
Mr. Lu,
we'll leave at daybreak.