[English subtitles are available]
[Low Frequency]
[Previously]
What will happen
if I don't return to my body?
If that's the case,
Grandma and Sister Bua
will be heartbroken.
But if you have to take the risk
to wake me up,
I can't accept it either.
But if I'm safe alone
while you stay unconscious,
I’ll be sad too.
Let go of me!
-What's wrong with you, Thames?
-Excuse me, please.
Patient! Patient!
-What's wrong?
-The patient has no pulse, start CPR.
Thames.
Brother Mon.
Why are you hugging me?
You...
What can you remember?
I
went to the wrap-up party.
Then I had an accident.
And then?
Then
my soul went out of my body,
and I appeared in your house.
You scared me. You think that’s funny?
Don't leave me again.
Okay, I won't.
Thames.
-Thames -Thames!
Grandma.
Sister Bua.
Let's check out the big news
that has been making the rounds lately.
Around 12 a.m. yesterday,
the police received an important clue
regarding the scandalous drama producer
and celebrity manager, Thanit.
He is suspected to be directly involved with the accident
that happened to the famous young actor,
Thames Thinnaphat.
He might also be related to human trafficking
and the online drug-dealing network.
An anonymous report was made to the police
that he planned to flee the country.
That's why they helped arrest Thanit
and handed him over to the police.
He deserves it.
Karma is real.
I hope he rots in prison.
Calm down, grandma.
Otherwise, your blood pressure will rise again.
How can I calm down?
He's lucky that I wasn’t there.
If I were there, he would have suffered.
That’s right. If my grandma were there,
he would have been gone!
He would have died long ago.
It makes me sick.
How did he survive until now?
Amitabha.
I hope the Karma goes harsh on him.
He deserves it.
Are you sure this is enough for him?
But it's strange.
He was arrested right after you woke up.
The retribution came just in time.
That's right, Grandma.
Yeah.
But I think it’s a bit late.
He should be punished sooner.
If I catch him, I'll devour him.
How dare he lay his hand on my grandson?
-Eat up, kid. Eat up. -Alright.
-Eat a lot. -Okay, Grandma.
Look how skinny you are.
Hey, Mon. Let's go shopping.
-Okay. -We'll be right back.
We’ll come back later.
I can't trust people these days.
Let me feed you.
-It's okay, Grandma. -Let me feed you.
You've lost too much weight.
When you were sick,
-Okay. -I couldn't eat or sleep.
Eat up.
Look how skinny you are, my baby.
-Look. There are only bones left. Goodness.
-Yes.
I can't sleep and eat.
-But you’re still so handsome. -Right.
My grandson is always so good-looking.
-Grandma, you always tell the truth.
-Eat up.
What’s up with Thames?
Uh...
Explain it to me.
Well,
it's what you understand.
Thames and I,
we’re dating.
I knew it.
Actually, I have no problem with Thames
dating anyone he wants.
But I'm more worried about you.
Worried about me?
Why?
Is Thames a playboy?
No, it’s about his fans.
But
he said
his fans will accept it.
But no matter what, there are people who can accept it
and people who can't.
Be careful.
Okay, Sister Bua.
That's all I can remind you.
The rest is between you two.
Please love each other nicely.
If Thames doesn't treat you well,
tell me right away.
I'll take care of him myself.
Copy that, Ms. Manager.
Good.
I'll tell you right away.
Actually,
Guy had always been here.
Yeah.
He asked me
to tell you to stop blaming yourself.
I'm quite disappointed
that I can't see
Mr. House Spirit when I’m home now.
Yeah.
I did a merit
for the uncle next door last night.
-The uncle next door? -Yes.
I made it for you.
I did a good deed for you, uncle.
Please sweep the floor carefully, okay?
Will he kick me?
Let's go home.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
Why are you standing there?
Waiting for you.
Waiting for my permission to come in?
No, I'm waiting for you to pack up.
Pack up? For what?
-Pack up your clothes. -Why?
-Pack up my clothes? -Yes.
Where are we going?
Well,
to the place we promised.
It's delicious.
Didn't Sister Bua tell you
to control your diet?
Yeah.
I don't care about abs.
I have to make up for what I’ve been missing
when I get the chance.
-Wow, it's so delicious.
-Can you finish all that?
Can I have the menu, please?
Thank you.
I want this, this, and this.
-Thank you.
-Hey.
That's enough. You already have a lot here,
and you still want to order more?
Oh, brother. I almost had no chance
to eat ice cream again in this life.
Of course I’m going to eat as much as I can.
What?
If you keep eating like this, I promise
-that it won't take long.
-It won't take long for what?
That you won't be eating ice cream
for the rest of your life.
So,
it means I can still eat it today.
It's delicious.
Delicious.
No!
Brother Mon, I got dirty!
That's enough.
Ah.
Mon, oh Mon!
If you come back, I won't ask you
to buy me pork skewers anymore.
Okay.
Wow.
Ever since I was born, I've never seen
anyone eat so much ice cream.
It’s not that much.
Are we going home?
Wait, brother.
I didn't ask you to pack up for ice cream.
Then
where are we going?
Chiang Mai.
Chiang Mai?
Yes, we made a promise, remember?
If I can return to my body,
we’ll go there again together.
Well, I remember that promise.
But why are you in such a hurry?
Because I won't be free later.
What about my job?
If I sneak out like this, I’ll be in trouble.
There must be a lot of problems.
Don't worry. I’ve settled it for you.
What's wrong?
What?
Are you okay?
I told you not to eat too much.
And you insisted to order more.
-Stop it. -Goodness.
The lemon sorbet is so green.
Are you good?
Are you feeling better?
Brother Mon!
-I'll sing with you. -Sure.
Sing it.
Let's sing that song together.
Leave it to me.
-I'll start first. -Okay.
Here we go.
♫You turn every gloomy day
into a bright day♫
♫Your voice
is like a song echoing in my heart♫
Is it awkward?
Not bad.
♫My heart melts every time I see you♫
These lyrics are mine.
♫It seems to melt in your eyes ♫
♫It's like I'm bound by magic♫
♫I give my heart to you♫
♫I just want you to know
that you make me feel like sunshine♫
♫You make the whole world smile♫
♫You are the magic in my life♫
♫I want to get close to you, darling♫
♫Just a few seconds of your smile♫
♫Made me have a good dream all night♫
♫I don't know how to control my heart♫
♫Like I’m controlled by magic♫
♫Baby, being with you
makes my whole day meaningful♫
♫I don’t want a sunrise,
I just want to see your eyes♫
♫My heart melts every time I see you♫
♫It seems to melt in your eyes ♫
♫It's like I'm bound by magic♫
♫I give my heart to you♫
♫I just want you to know
that you make me feel like sunshine♫
♫You make the whole world smile♫
♫You are the magic in my life♫
♫I want to get close to you, darling♫
♫Just a few seconds of your smile♫
♫Made me have a good dream all night♫
♫I don't know how to control my heart♫
♫Like I’m controlled by magic♫
What?
It's nice.
Of course.
It’s because you’re singing with me.
Do you want to know my plan?
This...
-What is this? -Take a look.
First,
eat ice cream until I’m satisfied.
Second,
drive Brother Mon to Chiang Mai.
Third,
sing with Mon while he plays his guitar.
If that's the case,
I'll add the fourth plan.
What is the fourth plan?
I'll tell you tomorrow.
What's taking you so long?
Just wait.
Okay, fine.
You'll know tomorrow.
I want to know right now.
Just wait.
But there must be a fourth plan.
So this is your plan?
Yes.
You can go back if you can't do it.
No. I won’t go back no matter what.
You're already part of my family.
And I want to be a part of your family too.
Your body is a slave to your mind.
If you're scared, grab my hand.
Brother Sing, don't scare Thames.
I didn't do anything.
So what's going on?
It's our promise, remember?
I brought my boyfriend to make it public.
This is my boyfriend.
Are you Mon's boyfriend?
Uh...
Yes, I'm Brother Mon's boyfriend.
Brother Sing.
If you keep scaring Thames,
I'll get mad.
I’m just playing around, and you already get angry?
Did you learn that from mom?
Then how is my boyfriend, Brother Sing?
Did he pass the test?
I met him before.
I’ll let him pass. He's handsome.
But isn't a celebrity like him a playboy?
Brother Sing, I can swear whatever you want.
I’ll only have Brother Mon.
No need to swear.
I'll ask Bua to keep an eye on you 24/7.
No problem.
Trust me, brother.
I chose the right person.
This is the first time
I've heard you say that.
And it should be the last time.
Let's eat.
Don’t be shy. Make yourself at home.
But why were you so mean
to him in the first place?
I didn't know if he's good or not.
-Alright. -Let's eat.
I'll scoop it for you.
Thank you.
For what?
Is it
about me helping you return to your body?
That too...
But...
I thought about it.
I want to thank you for everything.
Well...
You always find a chance to tease me.
I'm telling the truth.
Before I met you,
all my life was work, work, and work,
then I went home to sleep.
But after I met you,
I started thinking
that I want to do something like this
and live like this.
Also,
I want to be this happy.
You’re in the honeymoon period.
I guess so.
Well,
when will it end?
When
you cancel it.
Come on, otherwise you'll get sick.
When I look at these stars,
it's like seeing some sample houses.
What do you mean?
Have you heard of it?
I heard that when people die,
they become these stars.
When I look at them, I wonder
where I should go when I die.
I think...
I want to be there.
There are many shining stars around.
What about you?
Me?
I want to be somewhere with you.
In that case,
you don't have
to wait until you become a star.
Because
you already have me by your side.
You’re right.
It's nice.
Yeah.
It’s too good.
What’s wrong with that?
Well,
what will happen if things aren’t that great
one day?
Don't think too much.
It's because you work
in the entertainment industry.
If you get tired of me,
and cheat on me,
what should I do?
I promise you, that won't happen.
I'm sick of my boyfriend.
But you already have a boyfriend.
Will it be better if we talk
after you break up?
I'll be single in a few days.
Why should I waste my time?
Cut.
Good take.
Let's call it a day.
-We’re done. Pack your stuff and let’s go home.
-Thank you.
-Thank you. -Bye.
-It's finally over. -You're amazing.
What do you think? You’re finally
playing the lead together.
Are you satisfied?
Playing the lead together? I don't think so.
A lead is a lead.
Thames, where are you going later?
Why? Are you buying me a drink?
Yes.
I'm busy. Sorry.
You should drink less.
Your liver is so stiff that it’s about to break into pieces.
-Alright. -I’m leaving with Ai.
-Okay, see you. -Bye.
I'll go change and get my bag.
-Bye. -Bye.
Good job. Especially the highlight.
I'm good at every scene, right?
Yes. Actually, today's work is over.
Why did you tell Mark that you're busy?
I want them to spend some time alone.
-Let's go home. Go change your clothes.
-Let's go. I'm so tired today.
Let's go.
That was so well acted.
Thank you.
You're not like this
when you're with me, though.
Are you jealous?
No.
I'm not that unreasonable.
Are you jealous of me or Thames?
You’re jealous of Thames, I guess.
You punk.
Do you want something
stronger than that tonight?
You’re so dirty.
Let's go. Hurry up.
-Hello. -Goodness.
You scared me.
You're back early.
I'm afraid someone will miss me.
Well...
If you don't tease me,
you won't be able to sleep, right?
Hey.
What are you watching?
It's the drama you played with Mark.
It's the first episode today.
Don't you remember?
I forgot.
Come on, let's watch it together.
I'll be single in a few days.
Why should I waste my time?
Why did you turn it off?
I'm shy.
Why would you? Give me the remote control.
I want to keep watching.
Give it to me.
You know that, right?
I have no right to refuse.
What are you doing?
You don't have
to play a live performance for me.
Brother, I won't sleep here tonight.
Why?
I have an important job tomorrow.
What about our date tonight?
I'll pick you up.
I won't forget our Valentine's Day dinner.
Okay, that will work.
I thought we could sleep together tonight.
Oh, don't be mad.
I'll pick you up on time.
-Don't be mad. -Okay.
You can continue watching.
Brother Mon.
Yes?
This is your second life,
and also my second life.
I don't know if the world
will give us a third life.
So...
I don't want to wait anymore.
Is your heart racing?
Mine too.
I like it so much
when we can feel each other's heart.
Brother Mon.
Yes?
Can you stay and listen to my heart
until it stops beating?
Yes.
-It’s so pretty. -Yeah.
-Let's go. -Let's go.
Are you tired after driving for so long?
No, it was easy.
By the way,
it's quite cold today.
Are you cold?
Give me your hand.
Look. Rub it like this.
Do you feel better?
-I feel much better. Come with me. -Wait.
Oh, it really warms up.
Keep rubbing.
♫You turn every gloomy day
into a bright day♫
♫Your voice
is like a song echoing in my heart♫
♫My heart melts every time I see you,
it seems to melt in your eyes♫
♫It's like I'm bound by magic,
I give my heart to you♫
♫I just want you to know
that you make me feel like sunshine♫
♫You make the whole world smile♫
♫You are the magic in my life♫
♫I want to get close to you, darling,
just a few seconds of your smile♫
♫Made me have a good dream all night♫
♫I don't know how to control my heart♫
♫Like I’m controlled by magic♫
♫Baby, being with you
makes my whole day meaningful♫
♫I don’t want a sunrise,
I just want to see your eyes♫
♫My heart melts every time I see you,
it seems to melt in your eyes♫
♫It's like I'm bound by magic,
I give my heart to you♫
♫I just want you to know
that you make me feel like sunshine♫
♫You make the whole world smile♫
♫You are the magic in my life♫
♫I want to get close to you, darling,
just a few seconds of your smile♫
A soul is a low-frequency wave.
It's so low
that it's invisible to humans eyes.
I, Mon Manayu Woraphat,
can sense low-frequency waves, and see souls.
This also allows me
to be attracted and to meet with
a low-frequency wave
called Thames Tinnaphat Thanatikarn.
I should thank the low-frequency waves
that I never wanted
to see.
It allows us
to own each other, like we do today.
And even though we lost our ability
to sense low-frequency waves,
along with our heartbeats that are beating
at the same pace,
a promise is ringing.
The words of love
are dancing, full of emotions.
I might not be able to see it
with my naked eyes.
It's like a low-frequency wave.
We can only find it
through scientific equipment.
But
when it comes to love,
we should use
the device called "heart",
and feel it in person.
[Low Frequency]