[English subtitles are available]
I'm going to confess...
To Da-eun.
I'm sorry.
I like Da-eun.
No.
Don't!
[Episode 2]
Darn it.
That was horrific.
[Yeji]
[Yeji, are you asleep?]
[Are you really asleep?????]
[Moon Yeji!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]
Yeji.
[Yeji...]
[What exactly is love?]
What exactly is love?
[Yeji...]
[What exactly is love?]
[Nothing goes my way. Really.]
[Sobbing]
Nothing goes my way.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
I don't understand.
Why are you staring at it?
It's dazzling.
Why are you still the same?
Because today's weather is really nice.
It's pissing me off.
Da-eun.
Oh.
Yeji, hi.
What are you going to do after school today?
Me?
Well...
Shall we meet after school?
At the cafe in front of the school.
No.
I'm the only one who's the same.
Saena, did you buy new headphones?
The color is pretty.
Hey.
Did you call me?
Yeah.
These headphones' noise-cancelling function is awesome.
I couldn't hear anything outside.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Always?
It's really light.
It's great for practice.
I'll make an exception and let you use it.
How is it?
Ah. Ah. You couldn't hear me, right?
[Seon Joohyuk, where are you?]
[Hurry up over here after you register your attendance. Set off now]
[Stop it, you guys]
[Joohyuk, take your time]
Seon Joohyuk, where are you?
Hurry up over here after you register your attendance.
Set off now.
Stop it, you guys.
Joohyuk,
take your time.
Yeji.
What do you think
love is?
I don't know.
What is it?
Love...
is like fire.
Whenever I see Saena,
it sets a fire in my heart.
Me too.
You too?
But...
why?
I see. So that's your preference.
Guys.
Breaking news!
-What is it?
I heard Dongkyu signed with an agency.
Dongkyu?
He must have really signed with an agency.
-You even applied mousse on your hair.
-Where did you sign with?
What's going on?
Hey, Dongkyu.
Are you really going to debut?
Debut!
Don't tell me it's one of the big three agencies?
One of the big three agencies?
That would be insane.
It's a new agency.
They were looking for artists who look like me.
They found me through Moon Yeji's account.
They gave me a spot in a team that's about to debut.
I'm also going to debut soon.
Moon Yeji's influence is really something.
This is amazing.
-Can't you post my photo too?
-Me too. Me too.
Please put me on your social media account.
-Just once.
-Post mine first.
Post mine first.
Just once.
I asked first. Just once.
Please post just one photo of me.
Me too.
Everyone.
Go back to your seats.
Come on.
-I only want to have practical classes.
-I don't want to have class.
I don't want to have class.
Why did I
assume it was me?
I'm...
going to confess.
To Da-eun.
What?
Who?
So,
I need your help.
Post it on your social media account.
Post what?
A photo of Da-eun and me.
Say that we're officially a couple starting today.
Darn it.
I have to go.
And...
I don't accept such requests.
Yes, "adapt," right?
Yes.
This part
is "approach"
and "process and accept the change."
Through this...
Oh?
Da-eun.
Oh.
It's smudged here.
Yeji.
Thank you.
Wow, I've so many followers.
Moon Yeji's influence is amazing.
Gosh... he's at it again.
Can you go to school?
People will think you'd dropped out as soon as you transferred.
Seonjae.
I'm completely upgraded.
TenH's rookie development team contacted me!
What?
What-What's wrong?
What's wrong?
Gosh, him and his temper.
Oh, Yeji.
What are you doing here?
Oh.
I have an appointment.
With whom?
Oh.
I was too clueless.
You two, have a cozy time together.
-It's not me.
-Huh?
Let's go.
Oh?
Hello.
What's going on?
I thought you said you had to leave.
Oh.
I asked her out.
You?
Why?
Well...
What's there to ask?
Let's go.
We're leaving.
We're preparing for the arts festival together.
The arts festival?
You've agreed to participate as a team?
Yes.
Gosh. I actually thought...
something's going on between you two.
Da-eun.
Why are you flustered?
I...
I'm working really hard
so that I can have all kinds of experiences with the person I like.
I'll get going.
Hey, Yeji.
Yeji.
Are you okay?
Can you wait for a while?
I'll be done soon.
Cha Soobin.
Act consistently.
Soobin.
Are you leaving?
No, let's go back in.
Yeji, be on your way.
It's over.
Cha Soobin let go of...
my hand.
See you tomorrow.
Did you know?
I heard that Korea Institute of the Arts' campus is really beautiful.
They're close now?
Yeji, let's go eat tteokbokki.
You go first.
Hey, Yeji.
I'm not done yet.
Why isn't it me?
It's all...
my choice.
Your choice?
I'll show you that it should've been me.
[CEO Kim Changyong]
This is the CEO. Greet him.
Hello, sir!
You don't mind, right?
You all smoke anyway, right?
Yes.
It smells good.
As long as you choose me, I'm confident I can
give my all.
Wow, this year's players are interesting.
Fine.
We need someone like him too.
Gosh, please.
Ah!
Nice. Wow.
Nice.
Hey.
What?
Why isn't Lee Dongkyu here?
Dongkyu went to TenH to sign his contract.
Wow, but it really takes just one opportunity to transform one's life.
Who would've thought Lee Dongkyu would be the first to become famous?
If Moon Yeji posts my photo just once...
What?
Wow, Joo Seonjae!
You've gone too far.
I didn't know you were like that.
This.
[Joo Seonjae]
Isn't this you?
Wanted. Dead or alive.
[#Wanted #DeadOrAlive #AcceptingTips #FindJooSeonjae]
Accepting tips.
Find Joo Seonjae.
[TenH]
[Hello. This is TenH's rookie development team.
You have the image we're looking for.
Please contact us. Thank you.]
Hello.
This is TenH's rookie development team.
You have the image we're looking for.
Please contact us. Thank you.
-What should we do?
-What's wrong?
I think Dongkyu is done for.
-Dongkyu?
Didn't he say he's going to debut?
-What's going on? Spit it out.
-Spit it out.
I heard you went to the studio last time too.
Goodness.
It suits you.
Piggy.
You pig.
You were bragging about becoming a trainee.
So, why do you look so down?
So,
when will you debut?
Hey.
You were so excited because Moon Yeji made you popular, right?
Do you want me to explain it to you?
Your level
is right here.
The ground that everyone steps on.
No matter how much you try to climb up,
you'll still be here.
Understand?
What's wrong? What happened?
He thought he was casted by a rookie development team,
but he was actually casted to be a bar host to entertain drinkers.
The news has spread all over the school.
Joo Seonjae?
Delete it.
What?
My photo.
Oh.
I don't want to.
What a piece of trash.
What did you say?
I said you're a piece of trash who makes money by selling out your friends.
Look at the outcome of sending a kid to a lion's den.
Let's go.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
I chose to do it.
I went there on my own accord because I wanted to.
What?
Yeji, thank you for everything.
It was brief, but I...
I was really happy.
I've always only been ignored, but for the first time...
I thought I was valuable for the first time.
When they asked me to work with them, it felt really good.
Darn it.
I even almost made the cut.
I'll work really hard from now on.
I'll lose weight
and do everything I can
to be a person they'd want to invite to their agency.
Hey!
What's going on?
Joo Seonjae.
It was impossible to see you at school.
And you're causing trouble as soon as you appeared.
Especially because of that incident...
If you're going to be like this,
why did you bother spending so much money to transfer here?
I can't help you if you keep doing this.
Either you drop out or show up.
Or you can't graduate.
You know that, right?
As for you, Miss Moon Yeji.
I've told you that you should
prepare for your college applications or something useful,
haven't I?
You're short of time even if you work around the clock from now on.
Sir.
I want to participate
in the arts festival.
Hey.
I won't delete your photo.
You know who I am, right?
I watched your videos.
Do me a favor.
I heard you'll be suspended if you miss any more classes.
Hey!
Devoting all your energy to something
seemed tacky,
but I realized that requires courage too.
I'm going to cheer myself on as I become petty and corny
devoting all my energy to something.
So please help me.
And why don't you take this opportunity to
cheer yourself on, too?
Do you have main character syndrome?
Gosh. It doesn't work with you.
Then...
If you agree to participate in the arts festival with me,
I'll delete your photo.
What do you think?
-Please.
-Hey.
Are you crazy?
You must have your reasons for transferring here.
Let's encourage each other
as partners.
Partners?
I don't trust anyone.
Neither do I.
I only believe in your ability.
[Snap and Spark]
Wow, thanks.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
Next week, ask your dad to come over.
-Okay.
-Bye.
Huh?
Why?
Do you know him?
No.
He's a student from Korea Institute of the Arts.
He's really decent.
He's so desirable.
Korea Institute of the Arts?
Yeah.