[Episode 13]
Chairman.
- Why are you being so nice to me?
- Pardon?
Because you are so nice to me,
my heart feels like it will explode.
What did you say?
I think...
I like you, Chairman.
Whenever I see you,
my heart beats like crazy.
Chairman, what if I get heart disease from this?
Will you take responsibility if I get heart disease?
Ms. Park.
But don't worry.
I will not ask you to take responsibility for my heart.
It's not your fault
that my heart beats like this.
I think you're pretty drunk.
Let's go home now.
Chairman.
This is an absolute top secret.
The truth is,
you are...
my first love.
I think that's why
my heart acts like this.
What?
When I was young,
you gave me a ride on your bike.
At that time, I said go this way,
go that way,
and gave you a hard time.
But you did everything I asked you to do.
The way you were like a fool
was so cute to me.
- Was I?
- Yes.
You seemed foolish
and cute and nice.
On top of that, you're very handsome.
That's why I totally fell for you that day.
And I wished to see you again.
But who knew
that I would not recognize you when I saw you again?
How's that possible?
Ms. Park.
I think we need to go inside now.
Chairman, why did I not recognize you when you were the first love that I wanted to see again so badly?
Try to guess it.
Number one, because you were not wearing the military uniform.
Two, because your hair style had changed.
Three, because you became
so spectacularly handsome?
The correct answer is!
Number three.
It's because you became so handsome.
Chairman, come catch me!
It's crazy, crazy, crazy!
Hey, Park Dan Dan, what did you do?
What do I do now!
How do I face Chairman now?
Should I run away right now?
No, then what about Jenny, Se Chan, and Se Jong?
Should I say I'm sick and stay in bed?
No, no. How long could I do that?
Right.
I don't remember anything from yesterday because I was too drunk.
I have no memory of yesterday.
I was blacked out. Blacked out!
I must have lost my mind!
What should I do?
Chairman doesn't come out at this hour.
Let's quickly get some water and go back upstairs.
Chairman, good morning.
Are you going to work already?
Yes, I have a breakfast meeting today.
Chairman, I came home very late yesterday.
I don't know what time exactly I came home.
I took the last bus and got off at the stop.
I remember until then.
But I don't remember anything after that.
I think I was blacked out.
I can't remember anything at all.
Is that so?
Yes. We found our long-lost aunt.
I got too excited that the whole family gathered in a while.
So I think I overly drank a bit.
I hope I didn't do something wrong to you, did I?
You said you don't remember anything because you were blacked out,
but I guess you do remember seeing me last night.
No! No, I don't.
I don't remember a thing.
Did I run into you last night?
If you don't remember, that's okay.
It sounds like you were blacked out last night.
Chairman, have a good day.
Have a good day as well, Ms. Park.
I hope he believes that I don't remember anything.
So she was blacked out.
Chairman, why did I not recognize you when you were the first love that I wanted to see again so badly?
It's because you became so handsome.
Please eat some for yourself, Noona.
I'm very full.
Kyung Hoon, I mean Soo Chul.
I get full just watching you eat.
Excuse me, can we have some cold buckwheat noodles?
I really can't eat anymore. I'm full.
But they say there is a separate stomach for cold noodles.
You can eat it.
Are you going to fatten me up?
Yes, I am.
I am going to give you everything I wanted to feed you until now.
Even if you get fat, it doesn't matter.
Oh, Noona.
I forgot about this.
I asked to see you because I wanted to show you this.
What is it?
Take a look.
It's a photo of our mom and dad.
Are they my mom and father?
Yes.
They're our mom and dad.
Who brought you into this world.
Noona,
can I keep this photo?
Yes. Of course, you can.
Father...
Kyung Hoon...
I'm so sorry.
Kyung Hoon!
Kyung Hoon... Kyung Hoon...
I'm sorry, Kyung Hoon.
If I didn't lose you that time...
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kyung Hoon.
Don't cry, I'm sorry.
What is this?
Mom! Mom?
Mom, mom!
What is it? I'm busy working!
The balcony here is connected to the neighbor's house!
Why is the balcony connected?
Oh, according to the Madam, no, she's my in-law's now.
She said they visit each other with the neighbor anytime.
I think they're very close to each other.
With the neighbor?
But how friendly can they be to share a balcony?
It's as if it's one house.
Mom, when can we live in a house like this?
Mom, I think sister-in-law's home.
- Welcome home!
- Hello, I came together this time.
Lady-in-law and sister-in-law,
what brings you here?
Were you working here?
You're our family now! We need to work harder, then.
No, that's impossible!
When I didn't know is one thing, but how can I ask my in-law to work for me?
And it's good that you're here.
I was going to call you, sister-in-law!
Since you're with lady-in-law, let's all go together.
Lady-in-law, let's go.
Go where?
How do I look, Mom?
[Fantom]
It's so pretty and elegant!
We're trying these on because she told us to,
but should we be buying these?
Look at the price tag!
These are very expensive.
She's not going to give these out for free. What should we do?
Right, what kind of money do we have to buy these? We barely have enough to feed ourselves.
Mom, let's tell her we had something come up and leave.
Right, I think that's the right thing to do. Go take that off--
Oh, sister-in-law!
Wow! You picked the right ones!
They suit you very well.
You too, Lady-in-law, it looks great on you.
Did you pick some clothes for Soo Chul, Dan Dan, and Dae Beom as well?
And why don't you pick some more for your son as well?
No, how can we choose more clothes?
I'm getting these as a gift for you.
So please feel free and choose anything.
A-A gift?
Of course!
You're the one who found my lost brother.
What couldn't I do for you?
But still, these are so expensive, how can we take them all for free?
And our son-in-law Park will say something when he finds out!
Why would he?
We're not strangers anymore.
If Soo Chul says something, call me.
I'll talk to him well.
But still, how can we have this all for free...
Thank you so much.
Thank you, sister-in-law! I'll wear them well!
Choose some more! Come, choose more.
- Go pick more clothes.
- Shall we?
- Next month?
- Yes!
The children decided to get married. There's no reason to delay.
If we let this year pass, they will only age one more year.
Oh, yes.
That sounds right.
If it feels rushed, should we do it next year?
We don't mind,
but I thought it might not be okay for the bride to age another year.
No, next month sounds fine!
Since it's an unprecedented situation, let's have a small ceremony.
Of course! Who holds such grandiose ceremonies these days?
What's going on with Se Ryun?
She didn't tell me a single word about this.
Is she doing this because she really wants to get married?
It seems like they're meant to be together.
Our Kyung Seok insisted on dying single,
but he fell in love at first sight with Se Ryun!
I know!
Se Ryun, are you sure about getting married?
Are you really going to do it?
Mom, you said it's your wish to get me married.
Wasn't it? Should I not marry him?
Who said you shouldn't?
I'm just asking whether you're certain.
Are you really doing it because of me?
Because I said it's my wish?
No. I'm doing it because I want to.
Are you happy now?
Then I'm going to arrange your wedding day, okay?
Don't say something else later on!
Mom, can you give me your credit card?
- Why do you need my card?
- Why else?
I filled out the limit on my credit card.
My goodness... Fine.
Here.
Just use it as you wish.
As long as you get married, we can get the shares your father left to you.
Then we don't need to use credit cards with limits,
and we don't need to ask your brother for more money.
Mom. I have a plan, so I'll get going first.
- Don't forget to lock the door.
- Hey!
I'm going to tell your brother about setting a wedding day for you.
Do what you want to do. I'm leaving!
Why does she look like that when she says she's going to get married?
Is she going to say something else later on?
No, it's better to make her get married at least like this.
Rather than being with that playboy from that parasite household, this is better.
That's how we can get the shares.
- Thank you!
- Here's your Padak Padak, sweet and salty one!
- Enjoy!
- Thank you!
- Padak! Padak!
- Money! Money! Thank you!
Thank you!
Why is this not working?
Hey, hey.
It looks delicious!
We're meeting again here.
- Let's go somewhere else.
- Why, Oppa?
I want to eat that chicken skewer!
Why do you want to eat such a thing?
Eating things like this is the reason why you get stomachaches and diarrhea.
If you go over there, there's a delicious high-end handcrafted burger place.
Let's go eat high-end handcrafted burgers instead.
Oppa, wait for me!
He looks like an ostrich egg.
Hey, he's the guy who drove terribly last time, isn't he?
He's with a different woman already.
Wait. Is he two-timing right now?
How can a man do two-timing?
Dae Beom. If he's two-timing, what about Ms. Se Ryun?
I don't think he's two-timing.
He probably didn't go well with Ms. Se Ryun after the arranged date.
Padak Padak! Padak! Padak! Chicken skewers!
It's Hot Young Men! Welcome!
Oh, my eardrum hurts.
Oh, that looks good on you!
- It suits you perfectly.
- I think it's too expensive.
Today, I'll buy it for you.
Oh, we should get two or three more!
Baby!
Baby, try this on too, this too!
Baby, your body is like the sculpture in Greece.
In Park Dae Beom's life,
Se Ryun is the only woman!
What? Did you find your brother?
- The brother you lost when you were little?
- Yes.
We were living under the same sky of Seoul.
Wow. How did you find him?
So the grandma who is working for my house
saw the pictures of my brother on my dresser
and ran a DNA test.
She did it because the pictures were so similar to her son-in-law's childhood photos,
so she was surprised.
Then the results came out,
and the kid in the picture was my real brother.
Wow. How can you meet that way?
It felt like my mom and dad from heaven
sent that grandma to my house
to find my brother Kyung Hoon.
I still feel like I'm dreaming!
Hey, but it seems like your brother's family is struggling financially.
By seeing his mother-in-law is still working for other people at her age.
They were living in a run-down house.
He was supporting six family members, including his in-laws.
I got so upset just looking at it all.
But what can you do?
I hear there's a lot of people who regret reuniting with their families
because their lifestyle gap is significant.
Even if there's a huge gap in lifestyle, he's my only brother!
How can I regret it! That doesn't make any sense.
Besides, he's my only younger brother.
What can I not do for him?
Oh my god, is she going to ask me to move out of my house?
So that she can let her brother's family stay?
Oh?
It's from Mrs. Wang! Your friend, Gye-Ran.
Why would Gye-Ran call you?
Congratulations!
Mrs. Wang, I truly congratulate you on your daughter's wedding!
Oh, it's all thanks to you, Mrs. Jang!
Although we don't have a definite date down,
I can finally sleep in peace now!
Mi Sook, you really did a great job!
Dae Ran! When your daughter gets married, don't forget about us!
You need to buy us a meal, okay?
Of course, of course!
Gi Ja. Every time you call Madam Wang
by her name, I can't get used to it!
How can you call Mrs. Wang "Dae Ran?"
Dae Ran and I are friends! How else should I call her?
Well then,
Mrs. Jang, you can be friends with us! We're all the same age, after all.
If you're Gi Ja's friend, we're all friends!
How can I do that?
Just call her Dae Ran.
I guess you don't want to be friends with me. But I want to.
Let's be friends slowly.
- Oh? It's Chief Jo.
- Sarah?
- Yes, Chief Jo?
- Madam, when are you returning home?
I think you need to come back now.
The Chairman asked about the dementia test over the phone.
I told him the results will come out later for now.
- But what should I do?
- What?
Really?
Okay, I'll come home soon.
What's going on?
It's nothing! Let's do cheers again!
Cheers!
You are doing very well, Se Jong. Jump like this.
Why don't you put that on your back?
- Noona.
- What is it?
About Ms. Park.
Do you think she has a boyfriend or not?
I don't know. We've never asked her. Maybe she doesn't have one?
She's always home every day.
That's right.
Should I ask her if she has a boyfriend?
But you are only a baby.
I am curious too!
Children, I brought you refreshment.
Yes!
Let's go.
Ms. Park, let's play truth or dare while drinking this!
Truth or dare?
- Yes.
Okay, let's do it. It sounds fun.
Nice!
Then, what should we do about the penalty?
Write your name with your butt.
Okay, sounds good!
If you don't play, you lose! Rock, scissors, paper!
Yes!
I am the captain, so I will ask you a question, Ms. Park.
To me?
Okay, ask me anything.
Ms. Park, do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don't.
Really?
I really don't have a boyfriend.
Ms. Park, let's do another round.
If you don't play, you lose! Rock, scissors, paper!
Okay!
I have a question for you too, Ms. Park.
Okay, fine.
Do you have someone you like?
If you don't answer, you have to write your name with your butt.
We will count to one, two, and three!
Okay.
One, two, three!
I have one!
Oh, my goodness!
Who is it?
Where did you meet him?
Is he more handsome than me?
Oh? Dad!
Children, I...have to go in.
Ms. Park! Where are you going?
Who's the person she likes?
How long was the Chairman standing there?
Did he hear everything I said?
Does everyone now know that I have feelings for the Chairman?
What do I do?
Chairman will be home soon. What should we do?
What do we tell him if he asks about the result of the dementia test?
Do we tell him you have dementia or not?
I know.
Should I say I am, or I'm not?
Who is it?
Chairman is home and looking for Chief Jo.
Okay, I'll be there shortly.
Should I say you have dementia?
But I don't have dementia.
But if we say you don't have it, then you framed Ms. Park for stealing.
I don't think Chairman will let that go.
Seriously!
Just tell him that I have it a little bit.
Just a very beginning stage.
It's a very early stage.
Yes.
Is she in the early stages of dementia?
That's what I expected. That's why she treated Ms. Park like that.
What prescription did the hospital give her?
But it's at the very beginning stage.
If she takes the medication diligently, she won't get any worse.
She will be able to live a normal life like now.
That's fortunate.
Thank you, Chief Jo.
You're welcome.
What should I do?
What are you going to do now, Park Dan Dan?
How will you face Chairman, living in the same house?
Who is that?
Yes?
Ms. Park, Chairman is looking for you.
Is Chairman looking for me? Why?
What's wrong? Did you do something wrong to him?
No, I didn't. It's not that.
Madam went to the hospital, and it turned out that she does have dementia.
He wants to talk about it to all of us.
Does Madam really have dementia?
Grandma received a diagnosis that she has an early stage of dementia.
Dementia?
Is that really true, Dad?
Yes.
Dad, what is dementia?
It's a disease that makes you lose memory little by little.
It can make you act strangely and not remember people later on.
I didn't know that. Is Grandma sick more because I gave her a shock?
That's not why, Se Chan.
Fortunately, she's at the early stage, so she will be fine as long as she takes her medication.
Don't worry.
Really?
Yes.
But Grandma may say something or act weirdly sometimes.
But please understand it's because of her illness.
And if something happens, tell the adults immediately, okay?
Okay.
What do we do? Things are getting out of my hands.
It's affecting the children.
- Chief Jo.
- Yes.
Please pay more attention to their Grandmother.
Report to me on any hospital visits she may have.
Yes.
Mrs. Yeoju, it might be more work for you, but please take good care of her.
Yes, don't worry, Chairman.
Ms. Park.
Yes, Chairman.
If something like what happened to you happens again, please tell me directly.
Yes, I will.
♫ I was leaving home after my breakfast ♫
♫ I feel the shimmering sun rays enveloping me ♫
♫  I feel the attention towards me  ♫
♫  I was walking arrogantly  ♫
♫ When I was leaving my house after breakfast ♫
♫ I love the new pair of shoes I bought  ♫
♫ I feel like I can fly ♫
What are we doing here, Chief Jo?
What do I do? Am I supposed to live as a dementia patient from now on?
♫ I was leaving my house after breakfast ♫
Just hang in there for a bit. We can just tell them you got better naturally later.
What if the rumor spreads that I have dementia? My daughter has to get married soon.
I can't say I'm not sick at this point.
This is driving me crazy!
♫  This little kitten is staring at me  ♫
♫ I can't lose the staring battle because I'm a fighter ♫
♫  So I'm glaring  ♫
- Are you home now, CEO Anna?
- Yes.
Have you had your dinner?
Yes, I have. It's late.
You came home late today.
I had to check on the samples that arrived from the U.S.
What's going on? Did something good happen?
You were right, Noona. She has dementia.
So children are performing to make her feel better.
Oh, no. I was wondering about it, but it turned out to be true.
But she's at the early stage, so it's possible to have a regular life as long as she takes the medication.
We should be careful with each other.
♫  Especially today, my back is not in pain at all  ♫
♫ I open up my chest, and I feel ten years younger ♫
♫ I walk in big, big, big steps ♫
She did that crazy thing when she was only at the early stage?
I am home.
Welcome home!
What are all these clothes?
Honey, take a look at this one.
Please sit.
Sister-in-law gave clothes for you, Dae Beom, Dan Dan,
and all of us.
She gave us all these expensive clothes for free.
Honey, please try this on.
My sister just gave these to us?
How could you bring all these without paying?
I offered to pay, but she said these were gifts.
She's said I was a savior for finding her brother. She bought us everything.
She kept thanking me.
Ah, yes.
Now that I look, we are missing one for Mi Rim.
I have lots of clothes. It's okay.
This is for Dan Dan, but you should try it on.
You and Dan Dan wear the same sizes, don't you?
No, it's okay, Aunt. I have to go to work.
I'm late. I'll get going!
- Okay.
- See you!
Why didn't you get one for Mi Rim?
I couldn't think of it because I was too busy picking clothes for Dan Dan and Dae Beom.
I thought you would get one for Mi Rim while picking it for Dan Dan.
How did I not think of Mi Rim?
Mom, Noona. My oldest sister in heaven must be crying now.
Please don't forget Mi Rim next time.
Okay, okay.
Honey, please try this one.
Here, try it on.
Now that I look, we are missing one for Mi Rim.
We didn't get one for Mi Rim.
♫  My heart beats louder. Suddenly love feels so easy  ♫
♫  So I fall deeper and deeper for you  ♫
♫ That's what you do to me ♫
♫  I am alcohol-free, but I get drunk  ♫
♫  Although I did not drink at all  ♫
♫  It happens whenever I'm with you  ♫
♪ Like this, oh yeah! ♪
You startled me.
What are you doing here?
Why did you come here?
I came to buy ramyun.
What's with that guy? Why is he everywhere I go?
He was at the hairdressing school as well.
How did he know that I worked here?
Did you come here because you know I'm working here?
No, I didn't. I live in the neighborhood.
It's a coincidence that I see you here.
It's ridiculous. He's lying.
I've never seen him before, even once.
Excuse me, I'm saying it just in case.
If you came here because of me, be careful.
I have an athletic cousin and two strong uncles.
If you get caught, you may not be able to save your bones.
Don't think anything strange.
Got it?
You really have princess syndrome.
Why are you so confident?
I forgot to bring water.
What if I run into the Chairman downstairs?
I should try not to run into him for a while.
And,
when I erase my feeling for him in my heart,
everything will be okay.
Isn't that the Chairman?
Ms. Park. I'm leaving now, so you can come out.
What am I going to do?
Park Dan Dan, why do you keep acting foolishly?
Chairman knows how you feel now.
All of it.
Chairman, may I see you outside for a minute?
I have something to tell you.
Chairman, thank you for coming out.
And I'm sorry for asking you to come out.
It's okay. It's nice to feel the fresh air.
So what is it about?
I have something I must tell you.
But just in case someone hears at home,
they might misunderstand it.
Okay, please tell me what you have in mind.
Chairman, earlier today,
when the children and I were playing truth or dare,
did you hear everything...
Did you hear everything I was saying?
Yes, I heard everything.
I was wondering about it, and I was right.
That's why I wanted to see you.
Because I thought you would misunderstand.
What kind of misunderstanding?
So yesterday,
when I said you were my first love,
it meant I liked you when I was young,
not that I still have feelings for you.
In other words, please don't misunderstand
because of what I told the children while we were playing truth or dare.
I didn't mean that I still like you.
So what I'm saying is,
from now on,
please don't avoid me.
I never tried to avoid you.
That's what I'm saying. I won't try to avoid you from now on.
And let's not be uncomfortable with each other. That's why I asked you to gather tonight.
I will try my best to look after the children
and teach them well.
I will just concentrate on work from now on.
- Okay.
- Yes!
I'm sorry for calling you out here at this late hour.
Then, I will go in first.
- Ms. Park.
- Yes?
Baby.
Ms. Park.
Why was she in my dream?
Have a good day, everyone.
Chairman.
Aren't you going to have breakfast?
I have to go out now because of work.
Have a great day.
I guess he doesn't even want to see me anymore.
I understand how uncomfortable he must be.
So stupid of me!
Chairman didn't even look at her today.
And he only looked at me.
Was I being too sensitive about nothing?
Yes.
Chairman, here is the fashion editorial for the new products to be unveiled next month.
Thank you.
Chief Jo, what brings you here?
You came to work without eating breakfast.
So while I was out to buy some clothes for Se Jong and Se Chan,
I brought your favorite mushroom soup and fruit.
Please have them when you feel hungry.
Thank you, Ms. Park.
I'm sorry, Chief Jo.
I will get going now.
What's wrong with me today?
How much space does Ms. Park occupy in his brain?
He even called me by her name.
How could he call me Ms. Park? How?
Chief Jo.
What do you mean you are not going to work for our house anymore?
I do not have any more hope.
Or the desire to try harder.
I cannot do it anymore.
You can't leave, Chief Jo.
How can I live without you?
I rely on you even more than I do my Se Ryun.
I guess Chairman only has Ms. Park in his head
for him to call me Ms. Park.
Why are you overreacting by he called you with the wrong name once?
I do that sometimes too.
I mean to call Mrs. Yeoju but call Chief Jo, sometimes.
How is that the same as this?
I've worked for Chairman for more than five years.
But how can he call me by the name of a girl who's worked there not even for five months?
How can he do that to me?
Has Young Gook gone mad?
Ms. Park is so young and has nothing to see from her.
Young Gook has lost his mind.
Because of you, Madam,
If it weren't for you,
I would've not endured it until now.
But I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it any longer...
Give me your hands.
I will take care of it.
My daughter-in-law.
I have to act like this to get rid of Ms. Park.
That's the only way I can protect my Se Jong.
Yes, yes.
Get home now.
When my Se Ryun gets married,
and Chief Jo becomes my daughter-in-law, everything will be perfect.
But how could that young girl make such a mess of things?
Driver Park, let's go.
Yes, ma'am.
What?
Chairman Lee called Sarah by Ms. Park's name?
Did Chairman Lee lose his mind to that girl?
Otherwise, how can Sarah say she's leaving
when she's committed to staying there forever?
Don't get overheated and come up with some idea!
How can we kick Ms. Park out of the house?
Right, if they become a couple, everything will be ruined.
Let's think of some good ideas.
There is no need to come up with ideas to fire someone.
You just have to let her go.
Why not just ask her to leave?
It's because that hasn't worked.
Chairman Lee, the children, Mrs. Yeoju, and even the guest, CEO Anna,
all of them are on that woman's side!
You said she was a young lady.
She must be extremely capable.
How did she manage to capture all of their heart?
That's why she's not an ordinary girl.
She came in with a plan to hook the Chairman from the beginning.
That's how she won over the children's hearts right away.
She sounds very scary.
She's going after him with all her might because he's rich.
What has the world come to?
That's what I'm saying.
Are there no good ideas?
I accused Ms. Park of stealing to kick her out of the house
and ended up acting like a dementia patient.
If I were a real dementia patient,
I could do something ridiculous and kick her out.
Yes, that's right.
- That's it.
You startled me.
Does it make sense for her to ask me to go all the way to Damyang to buy grilled short rib patties at this time of the day?
She must have dementia.
Driver Kang could go on his own. Why do I have to go too?
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. Madam wanted to eat short rib patties all of a sudden and asked me to go to Damyang.
I have a lot to do and what will we do for supper?
Sarah is at home.
And I could help too.
So don't worry and think of it as a nice drive.
♫ Endlessly ♫
What's going on? Does Chief Jo think this is her house?
But something feels not right for some reason.
I have to go now. Will I be back by the end of the day?
Mrs. Yeoju is gone. All we have to do is to hunt the rabbit.
Did you call me, Chief Jo?
Oh, you are here.
Mrs. Yeoju is not here, can you help us?
Yes.
Can you bring this to Madam?
I have to prepare snacks.
Okay.
Dae Ran, why am I shaking this much?
You really have to pull this off.
Make her want to leave the house at once.
I got it. I will make her hate this house.
Don't worry.
Madam, I've brought your juice.
You horrible, despicable wench!
Madam!
Dae Ran, what's going on with you?
You wench, you put poison in this, to kill me. I know that!
Get out of my house. Now!
Madam, this is just juice.
Also, it's me, Ms. Park.
Yes, Dae Ran! It's just juice.
What's going on with you? Get yourself together.
You're not Ms. Park. You're Yang Kyung Sook.
You're that woman who seduced my husband! Get out!
Get out of my house, now!
Madam, please calm down!
Chief Jo. Chief Jo!
Chief Jo, nonsense. Get out now!
Get out!
Get out, you wench!
- I said, get out!
- Dae Ran!
Who brought her into my house! A man seducer!
Madam.
Please get yourself together, Madam.
You, get out of my house, right now!
Get out, you wench!
Madam! What the heck are you doing right now!
CEO Anna...
Ms. Park, get up. Are you okay?
What's going on?
I'm okay, CEO Anna.
But I think Madam is ill again.
What do we do?
- Dae Ran.
- CEO.
Madam is a little...
Chief Jo, what are you doing?
Get rid of that wench, Kyung Sook!
Hey, Dae Ran...
What are you all doing here?
Look at her.
Ms. Park. What happened to your clothes and face?
What's going on?
It's nothing.
I'm okay.
Madam, please don't.
Kyung Sook! Kyung Sook, you wench!
Kyung Sook, you wench!
Please go inside.
Ms. Park, is it--
That's right! Madam did something unspeakable to Ms. Park again.
What is this? Let's talk later.
Ms. Park is not in a good state. Let's go upstairs.
Are you okay?
I thought we only had to get rid of Mrs. Yeoju, but what's this?
Who would have thought the Chairman would be home early? And that woman, Anna too!
What am I going to do now?
Mom, I think it'd be best for you to go home.
Right, I will.
- Let me go with you.
- No, Madam!
You have to pretend to be sick and sleep.
Since things have come to this, I'll go and confront it with the Chairman right now.
- Mom, I told you to go.
- Okay.
Dae Ran, you got this, okay?
Madam, please lie down.
What do you mean by confronting it with the Chairman?
Whenever Madam sees Ms. Park, her symptoms get worse.
Then Ms. Park should quit. Don't you think so?
Yes. Yes.
Of course.
Your clothes and everything is a mess right now.
What kind of craziness is this?
Clothes can be washed. It's okay.
What do you mean by it's okay! You got attacked vulnerably.
How can you say it's okay?
It's because Madam is sick.
Ms. Park.
Are you working here even enduring all these things because you have nowhere else to go?
I told you.
You can work with me, so--
That's not the only reason.
I have a place to go now.
I can go home. And I have saved some money too.
It's just because...
I like working here and it gives me joy.
It makes me happy and grateful that someone needs me.
That's why I want to stay here.
My sweet Dan Dan, if staying here makes her happy, then she should stay.
Next to me like this.
I know that Madam is not acting like that on purpose,
and it's all because of her illness, but it still upsets me.
And it makes me worry that she might get worse because of me.
So should I leave here?
I don't know what to do.
Ms. Park, don't worry.
We will find the right solutions.
And now that Chairman knows everything, he won't let this happen again.
So let's get changed, Ms. Park.
And rest comfortably, okay?
Yes. Thank you.
It will be okay.
Madam's behavioral symptoms are not for early stages.
She can't act like this if she's at an early stage.
What do you mean Ms. Park should resign, Chief Jo?
Madam seems to act quite normal when Ms. Park is not around,
but whenever she sees her, whether because of hallucinations or unhappy memories,
her condition gets worse.
Even still, Ms. Park is working hard and doing well.
How about if we send her on a long vacation, so she doesn't appear in front of Madam?
Until Madam gets settled, perhaps.
I think it'd be better for Madam to go to a nursing home for a while.
A nursing home? That doesn't make any sense.
She's still at an early stage.
From what I see, she's not at the early stage but a severe stage.
You saw how Ms. Park was covered in tomato juice.
Madam did that, didn't she?
That is...
And she was telling her to get out and pushing her to the floor.
A good thing the children weren't there. What if they saw it?
They would have been in a big shock.
Did she really do that to Ms. Park?
If she's at the early stage of dementia, that couldn't happen.
There must have been a mistake in diagnosis.
Chief Jo, did she get a proper dementia examination?
I know you didn't go to Dr. Kim. Where did you go for the test?
Madam didn't want to go there because she was too embarrassed.
So we went to a different, small hospital.
Young Gook. What if she gets this violent toward the children? I get the chill just imagining it.
Putting everything aside, it's in the best interest of Madam for her
to get help from specialists.
I heard there are many good nursing homes nowadays.
Yes, I agree.
I will go talk to her.
How long do I have to lie here like this?
If you feel okay, can you sit up?
Ah, yes.
Oh, my head.
Why does my head hurt so much?
Do you recognize me?
Chairman Lee! I'm at the early stage of dementia.
I am okay.
Then do you remember what you did to Ms. Park?
Ms. Park? What did I do to her?
You don't remember?
I guess I did something to her again.
Yang Kyung Sook and such.
Yes.
Oh, what am I going to do?
So please go to Dr. Kim and get a thorough examination tomorrow.
And why don't you get treatment in a good nursing home for a while?
A nursing home?
What nursing home?
I think you are in serious condition.
We've never had anyone named Yang Kyung Sook work in our house.
Even so, you treat Ms. Park in a hostile manner.
I don't want my children to see such violent behavior.
The truth is, Chairman Lee...
For our children, please go to the nursing home.
I will make sure you get the best treatment possible.
No, that's not it! What treatment do I need in a nursing home?
I'm not going to a nursing home. I'm not going there!
Please do so. I won't give you a hard time.
Chairman Lee!
Young Gook. I don't have dementia.
It was fake dementia.
I don't have dementia.
What?
I never went to the hospital.
Nor did I get diagnosed with dementia.
I was just acting a show. I just acted like I was crazy!
What are you saying right now?
- What kind of nonsense!
- No, no.
Young Gook, Young Gook.
Because you seem to have feelings for Ms. Park.
You shouldn't do that!
What kind of household are we?
What kind of company our FT Group is?
If a strange rumor spreads about you and Ms. Park, it's a big problem!
That's why I did it.
I wanted to kick Ms. Park out quietly.
For that reason,
that's why you pretended to have dementia?
Chairman Lee, I'd lost my mind.
At that time, I'd lost my mind--
Get out of my house now!
Chairman Lee, Chairman Lee.
You lied in front of my children and accused an innocent person of stealing!
And then you pretended to have dementia. How can you humanly do that?
Chairman Lee, Chairman Lee. I did wrong.
I'm sorry, Chairman Lee. I was out of my mind!
I can't live with you anymore, no matter what you say.
So please leave. Get out right now!
Okay, I get it.
I will go.
But not until my daughter Se Ryun gets married.
Can I please stay until then?
I know you hate me, but Se Ryun is your only sister.
We can't let Se Ryun pay for my mistake.
Chairman Lee, I'm begging you like this!
I'm begging you, Chairman Lee.
I'm sorry, Chairman Lee.
Chairman Lee.
Chief Jo!
Yes, Chairman.
Come to my study, now.
Chief Jo. That she didn't go to the hospital nor get examined,
is that all true?
Yes.
Are you saying you reported lies to me?
I'm sorry, Chairman.
I had no choice since Madam asked me to do so.
Are you giving me that as an excuse?
I'm sorry.
I am seriously disappointed with you, Chief Jo.
Chairman, but this is my first time.
I've never lied to you before. I swear!
That's enough. Please leave.
Why were you shouting at Chief Jo?
It's nothing.
What did Madam say?
Did you talk to her about the nursing home?
She will not do anything like that from now on.
Just leave it at that , Noona.
What are you saying? If you leave it, she will do that again to Ms. Park.
No, she won't do anything like that again.
Let's leave it at that.
I will take care of this myself.
Okay, that's good then.
Is Ms. Park okay?
She says she's okay, but I think it was very hard on her.
She even thought about quitting here.
Is that really true?
Of course. Why wouldn't she think about it when that kind of thing happened to her?
Get some rest. I'm going to my room.
Ms. Park, please come out to the front of the house for a minute.
Ms. Park, please get in.
Pardon?
Please get in first.
And put your seatbelt on.
Chairman, where are we going?
Hurry up and put on the seatbelt.
Let's go now.
Please drink.
Why don't you have a sip?
How is it? Does it make you feel better?
You told me once that your mood gets better when you drink this.
Did you remember all that?
I have a very good memory.
Ms. Park, what should we do now?
Yes, you like playing the whack-a-mole.
Let's go catch some moles.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Come on, whack them.
How was I? I even caught your moles too.
I did better than the last time. Didn't I improve a lot?
Are you still upset, Ms. Park?
I guess it'd be hard to feel totally better with this.
Since we couldn't do it with whack-a-mole, how about a bike ride?
It's breezy out, perfect for bike riding.
Should we ride about thirty rounds today?
Chairman.
Why do you act like this to me?
Do you also have feelings for me?
That's it, isn't it?
♫ Why do you run away, love. Like a shy child ♫
♫ In case I lose it. I hold it tight ♫
♫ But love always runs away, chased by longing ♫
♫ It would be nice to take a break ♫
♫ I have to abandon the longing and the grieves ♫
♫ What am I looking for on this road wandering ♫
♫  Why am I here for what  ♫
[Young Lady and Gentleman]
It's my friend's story.
- A woman with quite a bit of age gap likes him.
- Good luck!
It's not me, I told you.
Please take this necklace.
Why are you giving this to me?
It's because I'm so sorry.
Does it make sense I can't get rid of that country bumpkin even with Madam's help?
There is no one without a flaw. You will find something if you shake them.
There will be a way to kick her out.
We've set the wedding date. It's the second Saturday next month.
That's good.
Are you really going to marry that guy? It doesn't matter for me who you marry.
But he's not okay!
Why do you care?
What does it matter to you!
If you like me too, please hang the handkerchief on this tree by tomorrow.
What should I do?
I am back.
What are you? Who are you?
Are you really Driver Park's daughter?