Stop right there!
[Episode 2]
Young lady!
You shouldn't go in there!
- Young lady!
- Please, somebody save me!
It is dangerous!
You crazy man!
Save me!
Excuse me?
Hello?
Is he... dead?
What is this?
Did I just...
killed a person?
Did I?
Is this 112?
[T/N: 112 is the number to call the police in Korea.]
Yes this is 112, please speak.
Hello? Please tell me what's going on!
Please hurry up and come here.
Hurry!
Careful!
I really didn't do it on purpose.
That crazy perverted man was coming after me.
Without me knowing,
with this tumbler, I once,
not even twice, hit him.
Where is it? Are you sure it was here?
Yes. I think so. This way is right.
If only that perverted crazy man didn't follow me,
something like this would've not happened. Trust me!
Please believe me.
That person isn't dead.
He didn't die.
God, thank you!
It is that person. He didn't die.
He didn't die.
Who are you?
It is this person! This person!
He is a perverted guy who followed me.
What? Perverted?
Are you talking to me right now?
You were calling me 'Young lady' and followed me and tried to harass me earlier!
It's so absurd that I can't speak.
Is that this person is saying true?
It's not true.
Who are you to say that?
I was trying to help you in danger.
After this attack, you don't even apologize, and
you say that I did what?
Excuse me. What do you mean dangerous situation?
This lady did not see the Forbidden, Danger Zone sign.
It's a cliff there, so there was a fatal accident that happened recently as well.
So I was trying to help her not to get into an accident.
Then suddenly she hit me with something.
Danger zone? Forbidden Area? I can't believe this.
How are you saying such obvious lies?
This man is lying!
Danger Zone, and Forbidden signs weren't there!
Then we can go and check.
Then we can see who is lying right away.
Sure! Let's go right now!
You are about to be caught!
[Do Not Enter: This section is restricted from entering.]
How did this happen?
This sign was really not here.
Why did I not see it?
Why?
Are you going to say that I installed it?
No, that's not it.
It is such a big sign,
but the fact that I didn't see it is astonishing.
Officer, there is alcohol in here.
Excuse me.
Did you drink alcohol in the mountain?
That is...Something bad happened today.
I just had one sip. Just one sip.
My goodness, this Young lady.
Don't you know that you cannot have alcohol in the mountains?
I am sorry.
I am a bit weak with alcohol.
So,
is it true that this man did something bad to you?
I'm sorry?
Hey, there!
You can't go in there!
[Danger: Do Not Enter]
- Why is he coming this way? What is wrong with him?
- Excuse me, Young lady!
Young lady!
No, I think he was just calling out to me.
You just think so?
No, he didn't do anything bad.
He said it was dangerous, and don't go.
I am so sorry. So sorry.
Lawyer Koh, it's me...
You will have to come here right now. I will call again later.
I'll sue her for detriment, defamation, and false accusation of an innocent person.
Let's do with by the law.
I can't let this pass.
You will have to come to the police station with me.
Let's go, come on.
What do I do?
What's that?
A special assault crime with the use of a weapon?
You hit someone with a tumbler.
Since your lawyer came, you can leave now.
Please take good care of this.
I am so sorry. I will repay!
Please forgive this once. Please!
Please don't do this here.
I really did something wrong.
You were trying to help me in a dangerous situation but I didn't even know that.
I really thought you were a crazy psychopath.
This lady still have not come back to her senses.
Please make sure you include defamation.
That's not it! You are so handsome!
In a mystery thriller or drama,
the psychopathic murderers are usually so handsome.
You are just so handsome.
On top of that, you are wearing a great suit.
Where there's no one in the forest, you were coming toward me, calling me Young lady,
so without me knowing, I thought I was part of this scary movie,
so that is why I did that!
I am so sorry!
Please have mercy on me.
Please.
That lady must have been really shocked after doing that to you with the tumbler.
She confessed that she killed a person. I feel bad for her.
Young Gook.
What should we do? Just take care of it that way?
Here you go.
Thank you! Thank you!
You don't need to thank me, and from now on,
don't drink alcohol in the mountains.
Yes! I will promise that.
Take care.
Lawyer, please send me your account number.
I want to send him the hospital expense.
He probably won't take that.
I will send him your thoughts though.
Take care.
Thank you for your hard work.
It can't be like this.
I would feel better if I at least gave him the money for the hospital.
My goodness, could there be something prettier than this block of gold?
My cute little baby!
One, two, three, four!
Smell of money is better than the smell of perfume.
My cute babies.
Hey, you old geezer.
Are you looking at this right now?
Do you see the ring that you were searching for until your death?
Hey, if you think it is unfair that I am wearing this ring,
then try to steal it by coming back from the after life.
You bad man. Do you see this ring?
Madam! There's a big problem!
What is it? I almost had a heart attack!
Is there a fire somewhere?
Madam... The thing is...
something must have happened to the Chairman outside.
His clothes are a mess and he also hurt his forehead.
What?!
I'm sorry!
I was just in a hurry that I forgot to knock.
What is it?
What do you mean? I was worried that you got hurt.
Did you go to the mountain today as well while you were at work and got hurt there?
That was right! I knew it.
You have to think of your children and put yourself together! How long will you be like this?
What is the point of thinking of someone who is dead?
- A dead person is a dead person.
- Can you please leave?
I need to change my clothes.
Oh...okay. You can change your clothes.
I can't believe he even locked the door! Does he think I'm going to attack him?
If not me, who would even worry about him?
Oh, Chief Jo!
Why did he get hurt? Did you hear something?
I just talked to Lawyer Koh on the phone.
He went to the mountain, and he got hit by a strange woman.
Oh my goodness, what crazy woman?!
Oh my...
So did they put that crazy woman in jail?
No. Looks like he just let it slide.
What?! He shouldn't let this slide.
He's too understanding, just like his Father. He's only harsh with me.
But shouldn't he need to go to the hospital?
He went to Professor Kim's hospital.
Professor Kim said there was nothing wrong according to the tests,
and that there is nothing to worry.
That's great.
That's really a relief.
But ma'am...
That ring is something I haven't seen. It is very pretty!
How come you didn't wear something this pretty?
Hey, this isn't anything special.
He is probably the driver who was scheduled to have an interview today.
Open the door for him.
Please come in.
You've worked as a manager at the supermarket for quite some time...
Why did you quit?
Due to the company's situation, 6 months ago,
I resigned voluntarily.
Then, is it first time for you to work as a personal driver?
I never worked as a driver before,
but I was a driver soldier in the army,
and it has been over 30 years that I had no accident while driving.
Ah, really?
You probably heard about the condition that you have to move into this house.
Sometimes there are company works, but mostly, it's the household work.
There is a lot of mundane works.
If you just give me the opportunity to work, I will do my best.
Wait...
Did Young Gook see that I was wearing this ring earlier?
He wouldn't have stayed still if he had seen it.
He would have lost his temper and kicked me out.
That was really close.
Yes?
Madam, this is the new Driver Park Soo Chul.
He will be working starting today.
Hello. Glad to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Can I just comfortably call you Driver Park?
Yes, of course.
I was so uncomfortable lately.
I feel great now that Driver Park is here.
Oh, Mrs. Yeoju!
Please guide Driver Park to where he will be staying.
Take care of him to make sure he is comfortable.
Yes, Ma'am. Please follow me.
He looks like a good person.
I think you made a good choice.
He has a good impression and seems calm.
But, he does not look like he would be a driver to somebody.
Maybe his business went bankrupt?
Do you have to move into that house today?
Yes.
They told me to move in today and start working tomorrow.
Did you see the people at that house?
They're not people who abuse their power and disrespect others?
No, they seem like great people.
But are you really going to do that work?
I don't want you to that work.
What are you talking about it? Of course, I have to do it.
We need to make more money to live.
And also, the salary is almost the same as my last company's.
Really? They give you that much?
I have to be grateful and work.
It is hard to find a job like this these days.
Okay.
I guess there is no choice.
If you are like this, how can I leave?
Is it because of the moving?
I already took care of it with the moving company and Mr. Jang.
You just have to take care of your small belongings.
That's not it.
You are not the person to do that kind of job.
Because of me and my family, you have to do these kinds of work,
so I am heartbroken.
I said I'm fine!
I was just worried about how you will move on your own.
Dae Beom isn't picking up the phone either.
He turned off his phone. There is no signal.
Honey.
Do you think something happened to Dae Beom?
What something? You are saying nonsense.
No news is good news.
Let's just wait a bit.
Okay.
Also...
you didn't hear from Dan Dan too, right?
Yeah.
You know...
Until we find a new place, Mr. Jang agreed to keep our stuff in his storage.
I'm sorry, but why don't you stay over at your friend Hee Sook's place for now?
There is nothing to be sorry about to Hee Sook.
When she was debating whether to divorce or not,
she lived with us for almost a year.
But still, you should say thank you and sorry to Hee Sook.
Honey.
It is going to be hard until we get settled,
but let's endure through it.
Yes, I get it.
This is so pretty. Give us this too.
This, too.
Why don't you try these on?
Ah, okay.
Dae Beom, baby, you'll look great in any of these clothes.
But still, try it on.
I want to see how you look.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Your boyfriend is so handsome.
Is he?
Is he handsome?
This is so cute.
Baby, baby!
Try this on too! This too!
Baby, your body is like the sculpture in Greece.
It is like an art.
What are you doing? I am embarrassed.
What if someone hears?
Baby.
What do we do?
You are so handsome!
I can't help it. Come here!
What is it? So crazy!
Oh, my goodness! What is going on?
Yes?
Chairman, please have your medicine.
Thank you, Chief Jo.
Are you going somewhere?
Chief Jo, please take care of Se Jong and the children today.
I have some work.
Don't worry about the children.
It is something I should do.
But Chairman, isn't it better for you to take medicine and have some rest today?
You went through big trouble today.
I am okay now.
Chief Jo, please take care of the children.
It does not seem to be the company work. I wonder what he is up to.
What? Were you really treated as a psychopath pervert in the mountain? Young Gook, you?
That really happened.
Okay, stop now, Lawyer Koh.
But that lady was really funny.
Or should I say she was cute?
She said in movies and dramas, the psychopath serial killers are all handsome.
Because Young Gook was so handsome, she mistook him as a criminal.
That is the honorable scar.
Really?
I shouldn't laugh, but I can't help it.
I'm sorry, Young Gook.
Lee Young Gook, you still got it.
You are over 40 years old with three kids, yet you still hear that you are handsome from a young lady in her 20s.
I am jealous. Very jealous.
You won't say that once you get hit by a tumbler, too.
Young Gook was pretty good-looking when we were in college.
Whenever the theater club had a performance, Young Gook would always be the main character.
Gook Hee, you were great back then too.
You also played a lot of the leading female characters.
That's true.
How did we somehow become over 40 years old now?
Thank you for coming today.
Congratulations, Author Hong Chun Sik!
Congratulations.
Should we do cheers?
Yes!
A toast to wish Young Lady and Gentleman's big success! Fighting!
To big success! Fighting!
Cheers!
To big success! To big success!
To big success!
We'll take the pictures now.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Let me take a picture! In three, two...
Get more closely, one, two...
Amazing!
Please smile! One, two!
Let's just go simple!
Is it Reggae music?
That's correct!
Jenny.
Awesome! That's crazy.
He prepared it a lot! Wow!
No, really...
Lee Jenny?
If you listen to Reggae music...
What are you doing right now?
Why are you coming into my room without knocking?
I did knock. I guess you didn't hear it because you had your earbuds on.
What is it?
Jenny, it has been more than five years since I came into this house.
I want to have a good relationship with you, like friends.
I am busy. Please leave.
Okay. We can talk another time.
Don't go to bed too late.
What is wrong with her? She's so overreacting.
Se Chan?
Chief Jo, I was about to do my homework.
That's okay. At your age, you should like these things.
You can study later on.
Chief Jo is the best!
The best! Do more!
Jenny and Se Chan are so tiring.
I am going to make sure those two get sent to America to study abroad.
One, two, three. Awesome!
We arrived, Jang Gook Hee.
Okay, okay...
I am okay!
- I am not drunk!
- Hey, hey!
You are going to fall.
I am okay.
I said I'm fine.
If I fall, I can just get back up again. What is the problem?
You should get back in the car. Go! Bye!
Oh, my goodness! Who is this?
Unni!
Oh, my goodness!
How long has it been, Chairman Lee!
What happened to your forehead?
Hello, Noona. Please talk comfortably to me like before.
Should I, Young Gook?
Why are you standing here like this? Come in for a second.
No, I was going to drop Gook Hee off and leave.
Unni! I am not drunk.
I am not drunk at all, but he insisted he would drive me home.
You, really!
Then I really cannot have you just leave.
Young Gook, please come in even for a little bit.
Just a little bit.
You, follow me!
Let's go in.
- How long as it been?
- You.... You should go--
How have you been?
- Let's see each other faces more often!
- Yes.
It's so good! Oh, my, you!
Take care of our Gook Hee, Young Gook.
Walk straight!
Let me go!
Be careful of the stairs.
The thing he needed to do was to see Gook Hee?
Young Gook, have this snail noodle dish.
Looking at this reminds me of the past.
During college, you made this a lot for us.
Do you remember that?
When you and your friends all came to our place together,
I'd make this spicy snail noodle in a big bowl, and you all loved it!
That's right! We did that!
We all ate as if we starved for days.
We would fight each other to eat more. Do you remember that?
That feels like yesterday, but you somehow are now over 40.
Unni, let's not talk about age.
That is annoying.
Also, we are only 41 years old.
That's true. Who would think you guys are in your 40s?
You're still a bachelor and bachelorette, right?
Unni... did you say, "bachelor"? What kind of bachelor has three kids?
I am a bachelorette though.
This girl doesn't know how to match the mood.
Would it hurt her to act more lady-like?
- Mi Sook!
- Yes?
Gi Ja, what is that?
I-It is a side dish.
I brought some as I was making mine.
What side dish?
Ah! You know Sarah's mom.
Yes.
Is it stir-fried anchovies again?
Next time, make me seasoned dried pollack.
I still have the anchovies from last time left over.
O-Okay.
But, thank you! I will eat them well.
Hey, you can go now.
Thank you, Unni.
Young Gook, please have a seat!
Why don't we gather!
Here, everyone!
Bottom's up!
Let's all do bottom's up!
Bottom's up! Cheers!
Hurry up and drink.
- Seriously.
- Aren't you drinking too much today?
Sarah is working hard at his place, but he is having fun here.
Darn it!
Let's drink up!
♫ Love trapped us in a windowless room (Love) ♫
♫ What can we say? ♫
♫ Long for love even though it hurts every time (Love) ♫
What is it?
Did you go dancing again?
Do you know who's at Mi Sook's house right now?
It's Chairman Lee Young Gook!
Chairman Lee Young Gook, the one you're secretly head over heels with!
He's being treated as a son-in-law at Mi Sook's house right now!
Don't you have any pride?
♫ It's as if we've been waiting for this agony ♫
♫ Maybe it's all just for a moment ♫
Let's go and dance!
I'm down!
Hey! Darn it!
♫ We are the lovеsick girls ♫
♫ You can't just end this love on your own ♫
- Jump! Jump!
Let's go!
♫ I'm nothing without this pain ♫
♫ But we were born to be alone ♫
♫ Yeah, we were born to be alone ♫
♫ Yeah, we-- ♫
You crazy man!
I think I killed someone!
What? A pervert?
You were calling me 'young lady' and followed me and tried to harass me earlier!
I am so sorry!
Please have mercy on me.
Why did I do such a thing today?
Am I crazy?
But I should've somehow given him the money for the hospital.
What if he changes his mind later and sues me?
Dan Dan, are you really not going to go home?
Would you want to go?
The stepmom and her family
ruined our home not once, but twice.
But Dad only takes the stepmom's side.
I'm just going to think that I was an orphan in the first place.
Dan Dan...
I am okay.
I can live well on my own.
I am sleepy.
I am going to sleep.
[My daughter Dan Dan]
Jenny, is everything okay in school?
Yes.
Eating like this is quite simple and nice.
This blueberry compote was well made without it being too sweet.
Se Jong, you like bread more than rice and soup, right?
Yes.
Se Chan, I told you not to use your phone during meal time.
Give me your phone. You can't use it anymore.
Dad, I'm sorry.
I won't do it again, please!
Give it here.
Se Jong, you have to eat carrots as well.
Lee Se Jong, you don't have to eat things you don't want to eat. Don't force yourself!
Lee Jenny!
Dad, do you know that?
You're like a boomer dictator!
Excuse me first.
That girl's temper! I wonder who she got that from!
Excuse me first as well.
I have a meeting.
Mrs. Yeoju, I'll have my meals separately from tomorrow. If I kept eating like this, I think I would get indigestion.
Oh, Se Jong, you are eating well today.
Chew it well and eat slowly.
You're eating so well!
What is that on your lips?
Who said a student can put that on your lips?
Dad, do you know that?
You're like a boomer dictator!
[Gift for middle school girl]
[Perfume for women, Make up palettes]
- Driver Kim.
- Yes, sir.
- Please stop the car in front of a make-up store.
Look at this. The color is pretty, right?
Is this the color you're wearing it?
It looks a bit different, but it's the same one.
This color is also very pretty. Look at this one.
- It looks good, right?
- Yes.
But I will just get the one that you are wearing.
Okay, you picked well.
What about you?
Ajusshi.
Oh... Why are you here?
Look around for a second.
What brings you here?
Are you here to see me?
No.
Why would I?
That's not the reason I'm here.
Anyway, it's good to see you again.
I wanted to see you so much.
Me?
Why is that?
Is your forehead okay?
I was so sorry.
I should have given you money for the hospital, but I missed the chance.
I was so worried and sorry that I couldn't sleep.
It is all a done deal, so forget about it.
To those students who should be studying,
is it okay for you to be selling lipsticks to them?
What?
Ah, forget about it. I'll get going.
Wait a moment!
Ahjussi!
Please take this.
What is this?
You decided not to press charges against me.
I think I will feel better when I give you money for the hospital.
As you can see, I'm just working in a part-time job, so it is not a lot.
But it will be enough for the treatment.
I don't need that money.
I definitely gave you the money for the hospital!
That is for your treatment and settlement money.
So please don't sue me next time!
Did you get it?
Excuse me! Young lady!
- Goodbye.
- Enjoy the lipsticks!
Unni!
Why? Do you want to exchange it?
No, that's not it. But this.
The gentleman who was just here asked me to give this to you.
What? Oh, no.
Why doesn't he take this money? It makes me feel unsettling.
He still had a bandaid on his forehead.
I hope it doesn't become a problem later.
Thank you!
I got a phone call from Mr. Jang. You moved well, right?
Why is this so heavy?
Why did you bring so much? You should have just brought whatever.
It is all something you need. There is some of my things too.
But is this the house you're working from now on?
Yes, this is the back door. The main entrance is around over there.
The house must be very big.
Oh, I should not have let the taxi go. You have to ride to go to Hee Sook's place.
What are you talking about it? I came all the way here, so I should see where you would be staying.
No, you can't.
Why can't I?
I'll just see the room for a second and go.
I am curious. Please?
Just for a bit! Please?
This is really good, honey.
The home owner must be really rich.
The driver's room is this good?
Separate door, and a separate room? This is a truly separate house.
It is so good. So quiet and cozy.
There is even a bed.
The bed is also a good one.
But it would've been nicer if they put a double bed.
Honey...
I'm just saying. Can't I even talk?
Now that you saw it, you should go.
Can I rest here a bit more?
I was standing the whole day today moving,
so my entire body hurts as if someone beat me up.
Honey, shh!
Yes, Mrs. Yeoju.
Yes, yes, I got it.
You should really go.
They said Madam is going out, so I have to go.
How can you tell me to leave as soon as I arrived?
I am really tired right now.
I really can't move because I am so tired.
You really...
It's true.
Honey, then you better stay here quietly until I come back.
If they know you are here, I will be in trouble.
Okay. Do you think I'm stupid?
I won't even breathe and stay quiet as if I am dead.
Is this good?
Ah, it's so nice!
[Father]
[My Love, Yeon Sil]
You have one unheard voice message.
It's me, your dad.
Please call your mom.
Your mom is very worried.
Don't worry about us and eat well.
Father...
It's me, your son.
Hey, you! Why did you turn off your phone?
I was so worried!
If you didn't call today, I was going to report that you were missing!
Mom, why do you worry about a grown son?
When you left like that, how could I not worry?
What about food? Did you eat anything?
I sent you ₩200,000. Did you receive it?
Mom! Why did you send me money when you don't have any?
Why do you think I sent it? Because you left without any money, so I thought you might starve to death.
How dare you give me attitude when you're wrong?
I'm staying really well! Actually, I'm staying unnecessarily fine!
Really? Where are you now?
I am at my friend's house, so don't worry about me.
I am glad that you have a good friend.
Your dad and I moved out of the old place and finding a new house right now.
When we move to a new place, I will call you.
Okay.
Mom, I will go see you once I become successful.
So don't send me money and you just use it, okay?
Okay. I got it.
Baby!
What's wrong?
What is going on?
Se Ryun, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
What's going on with your face?
Why are you suddenly so scary and serious?
I think we won't be able to see each other for a while.
Why?
Actually, I need to make money because my family went bankrupt, so I'm not in a position to have a relationship.
Once I settle, I will call you.
Are you saying it's because of money?
You can't see me because you have to make money?
Right, until I am settled.
My money is your money, so why are you worrying about that?
Baby, you don't have to make money.
I have a lot of money.
What?
We are lovers.
Everything that is mine is yours.
Se Ryun...
So don't say that you can't see me because you have to make money!
I will punish you!
Se Ryun, you...
I thought you had another girl besides me.
Another girl?
In my life dictionary, there is no 'another girl.'
In Park Dae Beom's life, Se Ryun is the only woman.
- Really?
- Really.
- For reals, right?
- Yes.
- You can't take that back.
- Sure.
I'm so happy!
Oh, Madam!
I guess you're coming back from a workout.
I was thinking of calling you soon.
To me? Why?
Are you going to have your friend continue to live at your place?
Probably for another two years. Her situation is a bit rough.
Just now, another customer came by again.
[Real-estate agency]
Madam. Do you know that you can charge over two million won in rent for that place?
Really?
Yes! I'm saying this because it's such a waste!
Madam, tell me the truth.
Did you even get one hundred million won as a deposit?
Don't ask me.
Oh, my gosh. You didn't even get one hundred million!
The best location house in Seoul! My goodness!
I can't believe it. You give it almost for free!
Such a waste.
She's nothing but a daughter of a widow...
A Chairman of a large company is way out of her league.
She's wasting her time reaching for something impossible.
Who's going to want her--
I won't be able to marry her off to anyone.
Yes, there is no time to be like this.
Seriously though, does Gi Ja have no conscience?
Living in this expensive place, she should at least pay a bit of rent,
or at least pay more deposit fee.
The mom and daughter wear good clothes.
Right, Gi Ja is a very good friend of mine.
Let's just have her stay there for another two years.
- What is a good friend for?
- Mi Sook!
Mi Sook!
Yes. What is that?
These are apple mangos.
You like these. It tasted so good, so I brought it thinking of you.
Do you buy these expensive fruits for yourself?
Huh? This is imported.
Gi Ja, don't be offended. I'm saying this because you are my friend.
You have to leave this house after two years.
Do you know how much housing and rent fees have risen?
Of course, I know.
That is why I will never forget your kindness.
So what I am saying is that, nowadays, people live up to 100 years.
So we might live until 100 years old. We should make more money when we are young and able.
Young Ja is even working at a grocery store as a cashier.
So you shouldn't just play around and do something.
This girl has no idea what I'm going through.
I wish I could punch her little mouth!
Okay, I got it. Don't worry! As long as we're alive, we won't starve!
Hey, do you remember that civil servant guy who has a 25-pyeong apartment that you mentioned?
Is it still possible to arrange a blind date with Sarah?
Of course! They actually called me again a few days ago.
I don't know where their son saw your daughter, but he seems to like her a lot.
But I thought Sarah wasn't interested.
That's not true!
Mi Sook, can you set up the blind date as soon as possible, like today?
Really?
Did I drink too much yesterday?
I'm okay!
- Aigo! I said I'm not drunk!
- Hey, hey!
You're going to fall.
Yes. I'll have to drive a wedge in.
So, she'll stop eyeing the Chairman.
I'll be out for a bit. Call me if anything happens.
Oh, Sarah! What brings you here?
I have something to talk about with you.
Something to talk about it?
What is it?
We could've talked about it at home later. Is it something important?
Unni...
The Chairman almost got really hurt at the mountain...
But did you have to call him out at night,
and go drinking?
I didn't call Young Gook out.
Young Gook came voluntarily.
But even if I had called Young Gook out for drinking,
why would that bother you?
Unni... I think I have the right to be bothered.
I have been working at the Chairman's house for more than five years, including the time before his wife passed away.
I took care of everything at the Chairman's home during that time.
I'm especially doing my best so that he doesn't feel his wife's absence.
Out of all those things, the Chairman's health is my number one priority.
Jo Sarah... You're overreacting quite a bit, do you know that?
You're acting as if you're someone special to Young Gook.
Of course... I'm someone special to him.
I'm the chief manager of the Chairman's household.
So, please don't do that anymore from now on.
I'm busy, so I'll get going now. I'll let you get back to work, Unni.
What's up with her?
Does she have feelings for Young Gook?
What is it, Mom?
Now?
What is it?
People may think you're the one going on a blind date.
I'm not the one going on the blind date, but why am I so nervous?
Your daughter's here. Sarah!
You're here too, Mrs. Jang!
What's going on, Mom?
You look so pretty today, Sarah.
You seem to look a little younger too.
- I'm getting a good feeling! I think it's going to work out well.
- Hey!
Sit down. Sit down.
What is it, Mom?
He's here!
- It's here...
- Ah!
Nice meeting you.
Let's go, Gi Ja.
I hope she doesn't just leave...
Wait, you're saying you came without knowing?
Yes. I'm sorry.
I never even thought of meeting or getting married in this manner ever.
My apologies. I hope you meet someone nice.
Hey, excuse me! Sarah!
My goodness... Sarah! Hey!
My goodness...
How embarrassing.
Ms. Sarah!
Gi Ja.
Did you see that guy's face? He was smiling from ear to ear.
I think he liked Sarah.
It was love at first sight!
It's all thanks to you.
If things work out today, I'll treat you grandly!
All right. Please, do that!
You should get to live with your head up high, thanks to your daughter and your future son-in-law.
Don't forget about me then, okay?
Of course, not!
How can I forget your kindness?
I'll carry you around on my back!
- You mean it, right?
- Yes, I mean it!
If it weren't for you... How could I have lived like this.
Even my dead husband wasn't able to give me a life like this.
Thank you... Really.
You don't have to say that.
My husband died from a heart attack at his prime...
If it weren't for you... I...
I think I would've gotten depressed.
Mi Sook...
Let's stick close to each other like now,
and depend on each other as we grow old.
Let's do that.
It's Madam Song.
Yes, Madam Song.
What did you say?
R-Really?
Oh, my... I'm so sorry, Madam Song.
Yes, I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Mi Sook? Did she do something wrong?
Gi Ja... Sarah didn't like that man...
So she ended the blind date without even having a cup of coffee!
Oh, my..!
What kind of behavior is this?
She should've at least had a cup of coffee for my sake!
Is Sarah in her right mind?
He's a government employee, has a decent sized apartment in Seoul, tall, and he's even the same age!
Shouldn't she be grateful for a man like that?
No matter how wrong she was... How could you say something like that?
Am I wrong? She's already 36 years old!
How does she not know her place even at that age?
Okay! I'm sorry that she doesn't know her place!
I'm sorry!
Him balding a little bit.... that...
That's the only one flaw he has!
I was going to pay for his hair implants!
As a wedding present! I was going to!
Oh, my gosh!
Mom! Are you out of your mind?
Why did you do that without even asking me? I didn't ask for that!
Hey! For someone like you...
You should be grateful for a man who's a government employee and has an apartment in Seoul!
If you like him so much, you marry him!
You know... You'll turn 40 before you even know it!
You're getting blind date offers now because at least you're young and pretty.
Jo Sarah!
Nothing's going to happen with Chairman Lee Young Gook. Don't even dream about it.
Even though he has three kids, he's still a chaebol.
Do you think he'll even notice a poor widow's daughter?
Everyone may be calling you, "Chief Jo, Chief Jo!" now.
But, you're just a maid at that household!
Mom!
Out of all people... How could you say something like that to me, Mom?
Because I'm your mom!
That's why I'm telling you the truth!
Call the man you met at the blind date now.
Tell him you're sorry and that you'll meet him again. Here you go.
Mom! I'd rather not get married and live alone.
I'm not going to get married unless it's with Chairman Lee Young Gook. So don't ever do something like this again!
Or else I'm not going to see you either.
Until when are you going to just reach for the stars!
Oh, my!
Can you touch or eat stars?
I'm doing this because I'm worried you're going to get old and die alone!
Yes, I'll help with your oder--ah!
- Welcome!
- Hello.
Cafe latte and mango smoothie, right?
Yes, just a moment please!
♫  When I walk this road, it makes me cry  ♫
♫  It reminds me of that person's touch  ♫
♫  I couldn't hold her and just trembled my heart  ♫
♫  My unforgettable love  ♫
Park Dan Dan, you did well today too!
♫  Like a shy child  ♫
♫  In case I lose it, I hold it tight  ♫
I can't continue to work off part-times and living day by day.
Let's get a full-time job.
Park Dan Dan. You can do it!
♫  It would be nice to take a break  ♫
How long is your friend going to stay here?
I said, I can't help it for a while--
No, no! You choose. Is it your friend or me?
What kind of question is that?
Let's talk later. Dan Dan's going to be here any moment.
Just go!
Dan Dan.
Eun Ju.
Dan Dan, it is--
Eun Ju, I got a room.
What?
There's a good place near my part-time workplace.
So I came here to get my stuff.
Are you doing this because we were fighting?
No! This place is far away from the cafe I'm working at.
That's why I got it.
I'm really grateful for everything you've done for me, Eun Ju.
I'll be right out once I get my stuff.
Park Dan Dan... Why did you come here?
Everyone's living so well without me.
Is she the daughter of the people who lived here before?
Their father asked me to tell his daughter they moved if she ever visits.
Honey!
Honey.
Honey?
I've got some medicine.
There's no fever.
Honey. Dae Beom's mom.
It's hard to get employed these days. The ones still in school are having trouble, too.
Professor. I still had high grades, and...
Anyway, fill out the paper before you leave.
I'll contact you if a position opens up.
Park Dan Dan!
Professor!
Why did you come to school?
Ah...that's...
This isn't like you. Why are you so down?
Actually, I visited the employment counseling center to see if I could find a job.
What? You got employed already!
I still remember seeing your document.
Something happened, so I had to quit.
Professor. Is there a place where I can get employed?
Never mind. I'm whining at you, Professor.
Oh, it's time for my part-time job! I'll get going, Professor.
Dan Dan.
Yes?
Are you interested in being a live-in private tutor?
Live-in tutor?
Yes, but there are three children.
Oh, Professor! I can do it, even if there are three, four, or ten kids!
Please let me do it!
Yes, Gook Hee?
Really? Is there a good person?
I have a meeting outside, so I'm heading out.
I'll tell Chief Jo, so send her to my house.
If it's a live-in tutor, it can resolve the housing and food all at once.
On top of that, it's my Professor's recommendation, so it'll be a trustable place!
I guess there's always a way to live!
Park Dan Dan. You need to get this job!
I need to look as modest as possible.
Se Jong! I think it's dangerous, so let me carry the ball.
It's okay. I can carry it.
It's dangerous!
Oh, no!
No!
Se Jong!
Se Jong, are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay...
Oh, are you okay? Oh, no!
Kid. You need to be careful of cars from now on. Got it?
Yes...
Thank you so much.
Won't you have to go to the hospital? It's bleeding...
No! It's okay.
I have somewhere to go!
Se Jong... You almost got into really big trouble!
Se Jong, if something goes wrong with you, I can't live anymore!
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful...
Who is it?
Hello!
I'm Park Dan Dan, here to take the interview for a private tutor.
Wow... The trees are amazing.
It's like a house straight out of movies!
Are you a candidate to be our private tutor?
Yes, Mother! I'm Park Dan Dan.
Did you think I'm the mom?
Do I look that young?
Teacher! You've passed no matter what!
Come this way. The Chairman is waiting for you.
Oh, yes, you should head in!
Is she not the mother?
Hello! Nice to meet you!
I'm Park Dan Dan!
Ajussi!
♫  A smile runs to me in every step  ♫
♫  It's a shiny day because of you  ♫
♫  Strangely, I'm drawn to you  ♫
♫  Nobody will understand me, you're the one that I was looking for ♫
[Young Lady and Gentleman]
I think a person like her is much more needed for Se Jong, Se Chan, and Jenny.
Park Dan Dan. Is she really your student?
You got employed as our in-house tutor!
Me? Really?
I thought I wouldn't get it.
D-Did he hire a new private tutor?
You fired the previous one because she was flirting with the Chairman!
She's just a hillbilly girl!
What if some other girl takes Young Gook away again!
Did he notice my feelings..?
Isn't this a man's underwear?
Dae Beom! Run away!
How dare you bring a man from a club into the house!
Isn't that our Dae Beom?
Didn't you hear Dan Dan's voice just now?
Dad?
Miss Park. Did something happen?