[Episode 22]
Dan Dan!
Sunbaenim.
- Did you get your homework done?
- No.
- I thought so.
- Of course.
What's going on?
Does Ms. Park Noona have a boyfriend?
She said she was going to study.
Is that why she wanted to go to an English academy?
So she can date?
Because you left right after class yesterday,
I didn't get a chance to talk or ask for your number.
How have you been?
I've been like everyone else, working every day.
Did you get a job? What kind of work are you doing?
- I work as a live-in tutor.
- A live-in tutor?
It must be hard teaching the kids while living there.
How many kids are you teaching?
- Three kids.
- Three?
Wow, that must be really tough.
It's not. The kids are nice and adorable.
And they listen to me well, so it's not hard at all.
Rather, I get energized by looking at them.
That's Park Dan Dan. You haven't changed at all.
You've always been positive and brave.
How have you been?
I'm getting ready to go to law school.
That seems pretty hard.
I'm trying to enjoy it.
- By the way, do you have time this Friday?
- Why?
Ji Hae is getting married next month.
So we decided to throw a congratulation party.
People from your year will be there too.
Really? I should go.
If Ji Hae Sunbae is getting married, I have to go.
I should go and see people I haven't seen in a while.
Yes. When we set a place and time, I'll let you know.
Can you give me your number?
It's annoying.
What is this? Is it not a soft drink?
Excuse me, sir! You have to pay first.
I'm sorry.
How much is it?
It's 5,000 won.
What drink is 5,000 won?
It's a drink for hangovers.
Ah, that's why.
Where's my wallet?
Did I not bring my wallet?
I'm sorry, but I'll be back soon from my house with my wallet.
Okay, but you have to leave your phone here.
My phone?
I think I left my phone too.
Seriously. Ajussi, you shouldn't be doing this.
You look like a normal person. What are you trying to do?
I'm not that kind of person!
I'll pay for it. He seems like he really forgot his wallet.
I'll pay for it together.
I said, give me your number.
I'll pay back the 5,000 won.
It's fine.
Things like that happen in life.
You drank the wrong drink earlier. It seems there's something on your mind.
Drink this.
Hyung.
Are you calling me?
Yes, Hyung. Thank you for helping me today.
Thank you for the water!
Sure. You're welcome.
Why does he seem familiar?
[FT Group]
Hello.
I'm Cha Geon, reporting for the first day as a driver.
I will do my best.
Hello.
Follow me. I'll take you to the Drivers' office.
The weather and the air are good today.
I came out for work, but it's nice.
Yes, it is nice.
Mr. Park, let's have some udon before we leave.
No, I'm okay.
Why don't you go and eat without me?
I can't leave you here and eat by myself.
Let's go together, Mr. Park.
Let's go.
Oppa, we can't miss the bus. Let's eat faster.
You'll get indigestion. You have to chew it well.
We can't miss the bus.
Oppa, what should we do? The bus is leaving!
Ajussi! Wait!
Wait a minute!
What do we do?
The bus left.
I'm sorry.
It's all because I said let's eat udon.
How can we not eat udon when we're at the rest stop?
Ji Young, since it ended up like this, let's finish eating.
We can just take the next bus.
Sure!
♫  The path that's given to me  ♫
♫  I hope I can find it  ♫
♫  Please open a way for me  ♫
It's strange, but udon at a rest stop is always delicious.
Yes, I think so, too.
I like rest stop udon a lot, so one time I missed a bus while eating udon at a rest stop.
Really?
I did that once too.
It looks like you and I
have a similar memory.
♫  Please open a way for me  ♫
Eating rest stop udon makes me reminded of old times.
I see.
♫  The hidden road of mine  ♫
It's the boat! Run, run!
Here! Here!
Right, I can't help it.
I will have to adapt to the 22 years old Chairman.
I have to try my best to fit in with him and get close to him first.
These documents from Executive Director Han, I can't understand any of it, no matter how hard I try.
You look like you lost more weight!
No, I didn't.
What is their relationship?
Is he really her boyfriend?
If you hadn't grabbed onto my waist when you fell,
there would have been no reason for our lips to collide!
I can't believe this was my first kiss at the age of 22.
It's so unfair!
What about me?
It was my first time too!
She said it was her first kiss.
Then did they start dating recently?
Boyfriend or not, it's none of my business.
I don't understand, nor can I focus on any of these.
What am I doing? I'm so distracted.
It's driving me crazy.
Please come in.
Chairman. What are you doing?
I'm reviewing the documents Executive Director Han gave me.
But I have no idea what they are about.
Don't worry too much.
Executive Director Han, Lawyer Koh, and senior management are taking good care of everything.
You can take your time.
Also, I will meet up with Executive Director Han and get an update regularly.
Will you do that for me? That will be very helpful.
Chairman. Do you want to play games to decompress?
Games?
Do you play games?
Yes. I want to play games.
Please teach me how to play.
Sure. I was stressed out.
Playing games will help.
Follow! Follow! Now! Now!
If you don't go now, we will die!
But how? I tried to shoot them, but they hid.
They are out again. Shoot them, shoot them now!
Shoot? Okay!
Seriously. How many times have you done that?
It's no fun if I'm the only one who survives all the time.
I'm sorry. Let's try it again.
I don't want to. How come you can't play when I explained it over and over?
- I will try harder and practice.
- No, please don't.
I understand you are trying hard to get close to me.
But you have to play games because you want to, not because you're trying to.
Don't force yourself if you can't.
I will go to the PC room and cool down.
I'm stressed out about something else already.
I got even more stressed playing the games.
Ah, really. I can't do it!
Why is it so hard? It's annoying!
What do I do now?
Seriously!
So pronouns are going to be really, really important.
Please memorize them as soon as you can.
Now, if you take this example, it is going to be 'I am,' right?
The next one is 'you are.'
This isn't the time to be playing games.
I think I have to confirm it with my own eyes.
This is for the sake of my kids.
If the teacher is focused on something else, she will lack attention to the children.
It's not something I can let go of as their father.
[YNB Language Academy]
It's time for her to get off, but where is she?
Did she leave already?
- See you tomorrow.
- Yes, see you.
What?
Is he not her boyfriend?
If he was, they should be holding hands or going for something to eat.
Maybe there is nothing between them.
Of course, Ms. Park Noona is not someone who would do something like that when she has children to look after.
Ms. Park Noona?
Chairman.
What brings you here again?
What a coincidence!
I was meeting up with Lawyer Koh nearby,
and we were talking about serious company issues and about to go home.
How could we run into each other like this?
Since we did, let's go home together.
Chairman, why don't you go home first? I have somewhere to go.
Where do you have to go?
I have to buy picture books for Se Jong and workbooks for Jenny.
Then, let's go together.
No, I prefer to go by myself.
Please go home first, Chairman.
I cannot do that.
Buying books for my children is an important matter. I must go with you.
Let's go together.
Ms. Park Noona, how about these books?
At Se Jong's age, it's important to encourage creativity and imagination.
Yes, it's good.
See? You can pick the book faster with me.
Yes.
Ah, I suddenly feel hungry.
Did I spend too much energy choosing the books?
Aren't you hungry too, Ms. Park Noona?
I am okay. I can eat when I get home.
It'll be a while before we get home.
There is a very popular pork cutlet place nearby. Why don't we eat out there?
Why don't you go and eat? I can't go home late.
Why is she so strict?
Aren't we all living to eat?
Ms. Park Noona, let's take a taxi. I will pay for it.
Why don't you take a cab?
I feel more comfortable taking the bus.
If I take a cab alone when we are going to the same place, that would be a waste.
My goodness.
Seriously, why is he acting like this?
I bought this for Se Jong, but let's have one each.
It's bubble gum.
No, thank you--
Do you want to make a bet on who blows bigger bubbles?
I'm not good at making bubbles.
No way, everyone knows how to do that. It's very easy.
I will show you how to do it.
Seriously, what's wrong with him?
I lost the air.
CEO Anna, thank you for coming all the way here.
No problem. If you have any difficulties, please feel free to contact me anytime.
It's great that feedbacks are good.
Thank you, have a great day!
Are you done for the day, CEO Anna?
Yes, this was my last one.
We can go back to Seoul now.
Yes, I will get us going.
CEO Anna, your face doesn't look good. Are you okay?
Do you want me to stop the car?
No.
I can rest when I get home.
Please, just keep driving.
Yes.
CEO Anna, we are here.
Are you okay, CEO Anna?
Yes, I'm sorry.
CEO Anna, are you okay?
Should I pat on your back?
No. I am okay.
Here.
Thank you.
Driver Park, I am sorry,
but can you help me go inside?
Yes, let's go in.
I don't think you're okay.
How about going to a hospital? I'll go with you.
No, it's okay. I think I have indigestion from what I ate at the event.
I'll be okay once I rest.
Then, I will go and buy the medicine for you.
Yes. Thank you, Driver Park.
Not at all. Wait a few minutes.
I didn't want to be like this in front of him.
Wonder what's going on with me.
CEO Anna, please take this medicine.
Here.
Thank you, Driver Park.
I'm really sorry that you have to see me like this.
I've made it too hard for you today.
Not at all.
CEO Anna, you need to get better soon.
Yes, since I took medicine, I will be okay.
Please go to the hospital tomorrow.
Yes, thank you. I will do that.
I will get going now.
Driver Park, please wait a minute.
Here.
I almost forgot to give you this when you worked so hard for me.
No, I can do this for you.
You've been so good to my Dan Dan all this time.
No. Please accept it.
If you don't, I will feel terrible.
Please don't.
Then, have some rest.
If you have any other issues, please call me.
I wanted to go on a drive with him
and eat something nice.
I wanted to have a good time with him.
That's strange.
Wonder where she's sick.
She was like that when she first came back to Korea as well.
Yes, it's me.
Where are you, Honey?
Let's have a party tonight.
Sister-in-law and everyone else is coming.
Are you not done with work yet?
No, I'm done. I'm on my way.
What about Dan Dan?
She's on her way.
Okay, I will be home soon.
Dan Dan and your niece are here.
But where is the eldest son of the family?
Pardon?
I'm talking about Dae Beom. Our family's eldest son.
He's been busy with work lately.
So he took time off and went on a vacation.
You have to travel a lot when you are young to broaden your worldview.
Ask him to come by my store when he comes back.
Yes, I will.
I'm home!
- Welcome home.
- Dad!
Congratulations on getting a business!
Thank you, my daughter.
- Congratulations, Uncle!
- Thank you, Mi Rim.
I'm sorry for being late.
It's okay. Please sit.
We've all been waiting for you.
Son-in-law Park, your sister brought this expensive beef for you! So we were about to have a grill party.
Now that the main star is here let's eat.
Please sit, Honey.
- Please help yourself.
- Yes, it's good. The stew is good too.
Mi Rim, you're good at grilling!
- It looks good.
- It tastes good.
Eat as much as you want.
But Noona, Noona, hold on a second.
Shouldn't we stop to celebrate my Brother-in-law's big day?
That's right. We should.
I was too busy eating.
Here. Ta-da! Everyone!
Please look at this.
This is our store lease contract.
And look at this as well.
The leaseholder, Park Soo Chul!
It feels real now.
Boss Park Soo Chul, please say a word.
You're making me embarrassed. I didn't open the store yet.
Thank you for gathering here to congratulate me.
For my sister, who trusted me and helped,
I will work hard and make sure to be successful.
Boss! Boss!
Yes, Soo Chul. You can do it!
Yes.
Thank you, Aunt.
Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Why are you all saying that?
It's nothing.
Honey...
Please, have some more.
Okay, everyone!
To wish my brother-in-law big success,
let's all cheer shouting "Family Chicken Daebak."
Did you all get your glass?
One, two, three.
Family Chicken Daebak!
Have a good night.
Please stay healthy.
Thank you.
Come to my house sometime, Dan Dan.
Yes, Aunt.
Mi Rim, please come to my house with Dan Dan.
Yes, thank you.
- Good night.
- I will walk you to the car.
Have a goodnight. Goodbye.
Good night.
Yes, please do not come out.
Really? Did you get a job, Uncle?
Yes, he did. He's a big company's driver now.
Congratulations, Uncle.
I should've talked about this when our in-law was here.
I forgot all about it.
My mom can't stop bragging about Geon.
You really are awesome, Uncle.
- Uncle, which company is it?
- What?
It's Dan Dan's Chairman's company. The FT Group.
What? The FT Group?
I didn't know until I got the job.
I only knew it after your father told me.
Dan Dan, would that make you uncomfortable?
No, there's no reason for me to be uncomfortable.
You're working at the office.
It's fine with me, so don't worry.
Thank you, Dan Dan.
It's late already.
Are you not staying here tonight?
I have to go.
Dad, I will get going now.
Right, hurry up and go. You'll be late.
Dad, please take this.
I'm sure you spent a lot of money to open the restaurant.
I hope this helps a bit.
I'm so proud of you!
Dan Dan is the only one who thinks of us.
How much is this?
It's ten million won.
Ten million won?
Give it to me.
Why? Dan Dan gave it to you in the thought of you.
Just give it to me.
What money do you have?
Take it back and spend it for yourself.
Dad, I have no need for money.
- So please--
- No, just take it back.
Let's go. I will walk you to the bus stop.
Bye, Dan Dan.
How could he embarrass me like that?
Seriously, it's ridiculous.
Honey, how can you humiliate me like that in front of the family?
Did I ask Dan Dan for money?
I took what she wanted to give us. But how can you take that away like that?
Did I take something I shouldn't have?
Why do you make me a bad person?
Okay, I'm sorry about that.
But how could we take that money?
You borrowed money from your sister, who you reunited with fifty years.
Why can't you take money from Dan Dan?
It's the reward for raising her.
What? A reward for raising her?
Listen to yourself.
That's hard-earned money from looking after three kids in a stranger's house.
How can a parent accept that money from their child?
Why can't you?
Dan Dan is not a stranger.
Besides, she's giving it to you as a good daughter, so why not?
Do we become bad parents for accepting it?
We could pay it back if we succeed later.
We could pay it back when she gets married!
Where are you going at this hour?
What did I do wrong?
It's past midnight.
Why is Ms. Park Noona not home yet?
It's dangerous to go around this late at night.
What if she runs into a scum on her way home?
I'm worried.
I've no choice. I will have to set a curfew from now on.
Are you coming home now, Ms. Park Noona?
Yes, I'm sorry I'm late.
Don't be.
You are a bit late, but it's okay.
Did you have a good time at home?
Was everything good?
Yes.
Then go upstairs and go to sleep.
Yes. Good night.
I can go to sleep now.
I'm tired.
- I'm going to work, Mom.
- Sarah!
Drink this first.
What is it?
Don't ask about it and just drink it.
It's good for you.
Still, I should know what it is.
It's called medicine for keeping your youth.
If you drink it consistently, you will have rejuvenated skin.
Really?
Didn't you say you wanted to look younger? I searched everywhere for it.
Hurry up and drink it. It's expensive, so don't leave a drop.
Okay.
Get younger! Get younger!
Mom, what's wrong with the taste?
It's a bit fishy and makes me nauseous.
What's wrong with that?
Hold your nose and just swallow it.
Get it all down.
There you go.
There you go, Sarah.
That's right!
That's right.
Don't leave any drop.
Yes, Driver Kang.
Chief Jo, I injured my arm during the vacation, so I couldn't come to work.
I'm sorry.
Is your arm okay?
The doctor said it'll take two weeks to get treated.
What should I do?
Two weeks? I get it.
I will ask for a driver from the office.
Don't worry and receive your treatment well.
Yes.
He should have been careful.
Madam will not be happy about this.
What's wrong with my stomach?
Is it because I forcefully drank that earlier?
It doesn't feel okay.
You stay like this, and when you hear the starting gun,
you sprint out like this.
Then you will get first place in running for sure. Did you get it?
Dad, that's not the pose.
We do it this way to start.
Ah, is that so?
I guess they do an easier start pose for kindergartners.
The important thing is, the start is crucial for a race.
The moment you hear the bang, you have to sprint. Got it?
Yes.
Chairman.
Why, Chief Jo Noona?
Driver Kang took two weeks of sick leave due to an injury.
So we will have a temporary driver from the company.
Is that so? I get it.
Dad, let's go to the yard and practice running.
I want to get first place.
Yes, just trust me. Let's try it.
Get ready. Bang!
Chief Jo.
Madam.
Please call Driver Kang. I have to go to the department store.
Driver Kang took two weeks off due to an injury.
Sick leave? What do I do then? I'm meeting the lady of Sunny Department store for lunch today.
I can't miss it.
Right. You can drive me there.
Madam, today I have to go to Se Jong's athletic competition.
That's in the afternoon. It won't take long.
Besides, Ms. Park will be there, so no need to worry. I'll be late, let's go!
Yes.
It's a fantastic sunny day today.
It's a day you want to travel.
Before it gets too cold, maybe I should visit Se Ryun in New York.
It's no good if it gets too cold in New York.
Oh my, what are you doing?
Chief Jo, how can you drive like that?
I'm sorry, Madam.
My stomach hurt so much.
Madam, I think I'm going to die.
What's wrong, Chief Jo?
Chief Jo? What's going on?
Oh, my! What should I do?
Sarah, what happened?
- You're here.
- Dae Ran, what happened to my daughter?
What happened to her?
I don't know. Her face suddenly got pale while driving.
She said her stomach was aching so much, so we got an ambulance, and they said she had food poisoning.
Food poisoning? Sarah!
It's not even the middle of summer. What did she eat this morning?
This morning?
She didn't eat anything unusual.
Mom. That stuff this morning.
What was that?
That stuff I drank.
That's something good! It's medicine.
I'm asking what was in the medicine! You must know.
Yes. It has frogs,
- slugs, snakes,
- Slugs...
and also...
It has centipedes and black goats.
Did I put in too many things?
Hey, all of that is good for your body!
Chairman.
Are you going somewhere?
What do you mean? I'm going to Se Jong's Athletic competition.
- Are you coming too?
- Of course!
It's my Se Jong's event. I should go.
There will be games for fathers, and there is a game to play with the father and child together.
Of course, I should go.
But Chief Jo said I should go alone.
Since other people don't know about your memory loss,
just in case you make a mistake.
I won't make a mistake. Don't worry about that.
Let's go.
Still, what if something happens?
Especially when Chief Jo can't come with us.
Ms. Park Noona. Please don't worry about things like that.
I have a good sense now.
If I don't go to things like this, Se Jong will be discouraged.
Then, Chairman, you must be very careful.
My goodness! Ms. Park Noona.
Do you think I'm stupid? Let's go!
Our Se Jong's waiting.
What do I do? Would it be okay?
Se Jong, don't worry. I'll win it all for you. Do you trust me?
Dad, fighting!
Yes, fighting!
Ms. Park Noona, watch what I do.
I have a strong arm strength than I look.
Fighting!
Okay, The blue team!
Please come in!
Fighting!
The red team, please come in!
Okay. Fathers, please get ready.
Play it fair and square.
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Ready, set, go!
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
It's okay, Se Jong.
Se Jong.
Don't cry. I will win it for you.
- Really?
- Of course.
Don't worry.
[Family Chicken]
Mom, it's here. Here.
The neighborhood looks so clean. The business will do well.
Mom, let's go in.
Mi Rim, let's go in.
My goodness! Hey!
We will be getting customers shortly.
What are you looking at instead of getting ready?
Hyung. That new Boss Park from the Family Chicken restaurant.
It looks like he has a large family.
I'm envious.
There's no need to be jealous.
Imagine how hard he has to work to feed all those families?
You have a better life. Come inside and chop the meat.
Hurry.
Oh my. Did you make all these?
Yes.
When did you learn to do this?
I learned a bit when I worked at the market.
I'm learning everything from Sergeant Heo at the moment.
Mi Rim, try it. Please have some, Mother-in-law.
- Yes.
- Mom, here you go.
Uncle, it's delicious.
Maybe because you made this, it tastes great!
- It's delicious.
- Really?
Does it really taste okay?
Yes, it's okay.
The store is nice and neat, too.
Where is the owner? I wanted to thank him.
He's gone to the bank. He will be back soon.
It wouldn't need a lot of renovations either.
It looks like they took good care of it.
I think we just need to change the utensils to new ones.
Why don't you work part-time here when we open, Mi Rim?
I will think about it if you pay me more than other places.
Mi Rim, you are not giving an inch.
Of course, you should. You have to make sure of those to become successful.
By the way, I have something to tell you.
What is it?
I am moving in with a friend.
Are you moving out?
Which friend?
My friend from the academy. We will pay half and half.
Still, you should live with me.
Otherwise, you won't eat well.
I should get the certificate soon and get a job.
And I wanted to live with a friend too.
Sure. If you're living with a friend,
you can share information, and it can be a bit of good competition.
Sure. Okay.
Since you will be eating poorly from now on, eat some more.
Yes, Grandma.
Mom, you should eat too. Here's a big one.
It's really good.
It's really good. You're amazing!
Boo!
Ta-da!
What is all this?
I couldn't just let our first day go by.
I bought the cake and flowers and brought the other stuff from home.
What? I'm touched.
Really? I succeed then.
Have a seat.
I didn't bring anything but my clothes. Thank you.
The cake is really pretty. It's nice.
Let's take photos to mark our first day.
Sure.
It's so pretty.
Friend, how do you feel on our first day of living together?
I'm not sure, but I think it will be fun.
I hope we have a happy relationship.
It's your turn.
Okay.
Okay, Mi Rim, how do you feel about our first day together?
I'm excited.
And I think a lot of good things will happen.
Let's have a good relationship for a long time.
Get ready.
Play it fair and square.
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Go, Park Dan Dan!
Ready, set, go!
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Yes!
Fighting!
Fighting! Park Dan Dan!
Ready! Set!
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Park Dan Dan! Park Dan Dan!
Didn't I do good?
This is the last round.
Both competitors, please come out.
Ms. Park, if you beat her, we win.
The thing about arm wrestling,
it's not about strength but strategy.
You have to overpower them with your gaze.
Keep your eye on her, and don't lose confidence.
Good luck.
Go, Ms. Park...
Oh, no. We're going to lose to that family again.
Se Jong, don't worry. I will be sure to win.
- Good luck!
Get ready!
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Play it fair and square.
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Ready, set, go!
- Go, blue team!
- Go, red team!
Park Dan Dan!
- Go, Ms. Park!
- Yes!
- Go, Park Dan Dan!
- Go, Ms. Park!
- Stay strong! You can do it.
You did it!
♫ A smile blooms in every step ♫
Dad, Ms. Park, let's win the cookie-eating contest, too.
- Yes.
♫ Strangely, I'm drawn to you ♫
Get ready!
Start!
♫ You're the only one that I was looking for ♫
♫ Woo, it's a happy day like a dream, yeah ♫
♫ Woo, you are always my love ♫
♫ I feel love, only you ♫
♫ It is definitely love ♫
It's okay, Dad and Ms. Park.
We can win the next one.
Mugunghwa flowers bloomed!
♫ You're mysterious like deep ocean ♫
♫ You come to me like a child sometimes ♫
Mugunghwa flowers bloomed!
♫ Woo, it's a happy day like a dream, yeah ♫
I got you.
- Go, blue team!
- Fighting!
♫ always my love ♫
♫ I feel love, only you. It is definitely love ♫
♫ It is breezy wind ♫
♫ Woo, you are my love ♫
Ready! Go!
♫ Woo, it's a happy day like a dream, yeah ♫
Hurry, hurry.
♫ Woo, you are always my love ♫
♫ I feel love, only you ♫
♫ It is definitely love ♫
♫ It is breezy wind ♫
♫ Woo, you are my love ♫
- Chairman!
- Dad!
Chairman, your nose is bleeding.
You have a nosebleed.
You're bleeding! What should I do?
Did you do well today, Se Jong?
Yes. It was so much fun.
Ms. Park won the arm wrestle contest.
But she's now a stone head Ms. Park.
Stone-head Ms. Park? What is that?
While Ms. Park and Dad were in the cookie-eating race,
she bumped my dad's nose with her head
and made his nosebleed.
So my dad called her head is a stone head.
What?
Are you going to tease me too?
I'm sorry, but it's too funny.
What about the Chairman? Why isn't he coming in?
Did he go to the hospital for a nose bleed?
He's going to get ice cream.
His nose bleeding was minor.
Se Jong, let's go upstairs and wash up.
Yes.
Se Jong must have had a great time. He's so excited!
You scammer thief!
You parasite bastard!
You!
You come here!
Mom, Mom, Mom!
How dare you grab my son's head!
Mom. Mom!
Grandma!
The company sent me, so I'm here. But what should I do?
Am I getting fired on the first day of work?
The world is filled with landmines.
Nothing is simple.
It's driving me crazy!
Okay, even if I get fired,
let's face it.
Hyung!
It's you from the convenience store.
Yes, right. But what are you doing here?
What are you doing at my house?
Did you come to see me?
Your house?
What are you all doing!
Stop right now!
I thought he looked familiar, but he's the Chairman.
That is... Sir.
I've been sent here by the office.
I'm here as a temporary driver.
Temporary driver?
- Yes, I've heard about it. Was it you?
- Yes, sir.
Then we should go inside.
It's just great that it's you.
What do you mean?
You are Park Dan Dan, our Ms. Park Noona's uncle?
Yes.
What sort of a fate is this? It's crazy!
I've heard he lost memory. He does seem strange.
It's like he's missing a screw.
That must be why he doesn't recognize me.
But still, why is he calling Dan Dan, Ms. Park Noona?
Uncle.
Yes, Dan Dan.
Ms. Park Noona. I heard he's your uncle.
Yes.
But what brought you here, Uncle?
He's been temporarily posted here while Driver Kang is on sick leave.
Is that true, Uncle?
Yes. That's how it turned out.
What? Who's doing our driver?
Hey! How dare you come here?
Get out, now!
How dare you come back here, you parasite dirtbag!
Ajumma, what are you doing to the person I've hired?
Who do you think you are, Ajumma?
Young Gook, it's not like that.
Get into your room, now.
You need to hear me, Young Gook!
Get into your room, now!
It'd be better if his memory came back.
Even if I'm a mistress, I'm his sister's mother.
How can he humiliate me like that in front of a stranger? I can't live like this.
Rather than getting a ride in a car driven by that bastard,
I'd ride a bike.
I can't live like this.
This is really getting on my nerves.
I can't do this.
I can't live like this.
Hyung, please come in.
Yes, sir.
Hyung, I'm the owner of this house.
So don't worry about that Ajumma earlier.
- While you are here, make yourself at home.
- Yes, sir.
I was already happy that it was you.
And knowing that you are Ms. Park Noona's uncle makes me trust you even more.
Hyung, let's get along well from now on.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Park Noona. Since Chief Jo Noona is not here,
please explain the stuff around our house to him.
Yes, Chairman.
Then, I will leave it to you two.
Yes.
Dan Dan.
I was told by the secretary to keep his memory loss a secret.
But he's acting much more strange.
He's calling me Hyung even though he's much older than me. What's going on?
Chairman thinks he is 22 years old.
He's lost all the memory after that age.
What? How did that happen?
Actually, this is something only the family and immediate people know.
So you should be careful too.
Okay, I got it.
I can't quit when I'm already here.
I only need to be here for two weeks. So I will keep my head down until I go back to the office.
So don't worry too much, Dan Dan.
Yes, Uncle.
Don't worry about me.
But wasn't that Madam too much?
She knows Dae Beom wasn't mooching off, and how can she still act like that?
You look good in anything you put on.
It feels great to try different clothes on you.
I do have a good body.
And you're cute as a puppy, too.
You are cute and handsome.
You are everything.
Now that you said all that, I can't stop myself.
It's nice.
Hey! You're mine. Don't forget!
Okay, okay. I will tattoo "Se Ryun's" right here if you want.
What are you saying? Will you do that for real?
For real, of course. I'm not joking.
Right, right. Look at this.
This is yours.
What is it?
It goes so well with your clothes right now.
Try it on.
A watch?
This can do that, too.
Look. If I press it here.
Look at here.
It shows the same thing with the phone!
Wow!
I will be back.
Wait a second. Don't forget to take this with you.
Have a good visit.
Thank you, Se Ryun.
Call me when you are coming back.
I will be back.
He's so handsome.
He's so cute!
What's this?
Why there's such a nice car in front of our house?
What's all this?
Oh, my goodness.
These are all expensive luxury brands goods. Who brought it here?
Mom.
Dae Beom. What's going on? When did you come?
A few minutes ago.
What are all these? Did you bring these?
Yes, these are gifts for you and Dad.
And those are for Grandma, Mi Rim, Uncle, and Dan Dan.
How did you buy all these? Where did you get the money?
Mom, I'm back together with Se Ryun.
What? Who?
Do you mean that house's daughter?
Are you crazy? No way.
It doesn't matter even if you oppose. I've made up my mind.
Wake up, you fool! Not with that woman.
She's much older than you and once married.
She didn't get married, and we are not having an affair.
There are no legal problems for me to date her. So don't worry.
Dae Beom, you can't date that family's daughter.
You know how that family treated us.
Why don't you work at Dad's new chicken place?
What? Chicken place?
Yes. Your dad is starting a chicken business. So forget about Se Ryun.
Let's run the chicken place together, okay?
Mom, I don't want to do stuff like that anymore.
- What?
- I don't want to live like that anymore.
How much money can you make with that?
I didn't take a day off selling chicken skewers and made no money.
I don't want to live a pathetic life anymore.
I will live next to Se Ryun, in the same class of life as her.
Dae Beom.
Why? Am I not allowed to do so?
Why can't I have a lot of money, spend it freely and drive a nice car?
I'm going to live like that, so accept it.
Hey, Park Dae Beom. Get yourself together.
Please use this money to buy things you need and for the store.
And please, do not call me.
Nor text me.
I'll live my life on my own.
Dae Beom. Dae Beom.
Park Dae Beom!
Dae Beom, Dae Beom!
She must have bought him that car too.
What should I do with him now?
How many one million won checks are these?
What are you doing?
What are all these?
What are those checks?
I'm asking you what those are!
Honey.
Actually, Dae Beom came by.
What? Dae Beom?
You did it!
Chairman! Your nose is bleeding.
What should I do?
Ms. Park Noona really has a stone head.
I've never seen a woman with such a hard head.
Hyun Bin Sunbae.
That hotel? Yes, I know that place.
Are we meeting there? Sounds good.
Yes.
It's my first time, so I'm very excited.
- It's been a while.
- What?
Hotel?
Is Ms. Park Noona going to a hotel with that guy?
[YNB Language Academy]
Sunbae, shouldn't we get a bottle of wine?
Or maybe some flowers.
It's all spent by the club fees.
Let's go in.
But still.
It's okay, I said.
I wondered about it, but how can she do this to me?
How can Ms. Park Noona do this to me?
- Sunbaenim!
- Dan Dan!
It's Dan Dan.
Congratulations on your wedding, Sunbaenim.
Thank you.
But is everyone leaving already? I don't think it's started.
Her brother rented a big club room. Let's go there.
I see. It sounds good.
Let's go.
Have you been well?
I have to save my naive Ms. Park Noona.
He definitely forced her in when she didn't want to go.
Chairman..?
♫ Woo, it's a happy day like a dream, yeah ♫
♫ A smile blooms in every step ♫
[Young Lady and Gentleman]
Let's focus and try to like Chief Jo Noona. That could help me get the memory back quickly too.
Sure, I'm leaving this house.
I can't stand living in this house anymore.
- Open that safe now.
- What did you say?
Give my gold bars and money back!
This Ajumma!
Why are you acting like this? This is not you.
- What have you done for me?
- Dae Beom.
I'm not your real son anyway!
Yes, please come in.
- Ajussi!
- Sokcho Night Beach.
Did you dig on my back? Are you crazy?
- Please quit this job.
- What?
Why do you care if Ms. Park Noona is single or not?
What is he doing to our naive Ms. Park Noona?
What are you doing?
I didn't know you were there.
This is not something that's within my power.
I will have to ask her to quit.
Do you have something to tell me?