[Episode 28]
Seeing the ocean sitting here like this,
I realized what a fool I was.
For what did I live struggling so much?
This is all there was.
One step forward, and everything could end.
Why did I cause such pain and suffering?
Am I getting punished for that?
The ocean wind is cold.
Let's go. I will take you home.
♫ It's hard to find even if I look around ♫
I am so scared.
What if I don't wake up from the surgery?
I still have things left to do.
I don't want to die. I want to live.
I have something to do still while living.
CEO Anna.
I'll be by your side.
I will be next to you.
I'll be here.
So don't become weak.
It's okay. You can do it.
You can do it.
Nothing will happen.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry...
♫ Please be my strength ♫
♫ The hidden road of mine ♫
What's going on?
Has Soo Chul still not come home yet?
Wait.
It's 5 AM.
Did something happen?
- Honey!
- Yes.
Where were you until now?
You said you were going to the hospital to visit a patient. Have you been there until now?
Yes.
Does that person not have any family?
Why do you have to stay overnight at the hospital?
She doesn't have any family.
Right, today you and Dae Beom will have to look after the store.
I have to go when she takes surgery to help with her hospitalization process.
What? Are you going there to do the hospitalization process?
Who on earth is this person that you care so much about them?
When I was in tough times, that person did me many favors.
It's because I want to help her.
Today, I'll just do the hospitalization process and come right back, so you don't have to worry.
I mean, does that person not have anyone but you?
Imagine how hard it would be to have a major surgery by yourself.
If it were you, and you were all alone,
how scared would you be to have cancer surgery by yourself?
Does that person have cancer?
Yes. That's why at least I want to be there to help out.
But they can just hire a caretaker.
How many favors did you receive to do all that?
Aigoo, you're too compassionate.
You're too soft-hearted, and that's a problem.
Chief Jo, I thought about it all night.
The situation between you and me, and the fact that I have no recollection of it now, leaves me very confused.
That being said,
I would like it if we went back to dealing with one another as we used to.
So, what you're saying is that you'd like to treat me, not as your fiancée,
but as a butler who works here?
For the time being, I think that would be best.
Sarah, come eat breakfast.
I'm not hungry. Eat by yourself.
Why are you going back into bed while getting ready to go to work?
I'm not going to work and just rest today.
Just quit that house at this time.
I get that you're holding on to him because of Se Jong,
but this can never work.
No matter how much you glue a broken bowl together, you can't even use it as a dog bowl.
I'll take care of it myself.
What? You take care of it yourself?
Hey, what if the Chairman's memory after his accident when he was 22 comes back?
Ultimately, it's over anyway.
Inevitably that bomb is going to blow, so why are you holding onto that bomb?
If that bomb goes off, you're dead, you brat.
If I die, so what? Life leads to death anyway!
You brat. Is that something you should say in front of your mother?
If you can't let go of Se Jong,
then let's bring him here.
I'll pay the lawsuit fees.
What money do you have?
Get out. I want to rest in peace today.
Se Jong, today, let's go with Dad and Ms. Park
to watch a movie all together. How does that sound?
Sure, I like it!
Last time when we met at the bookstore
and ate pizza and walked while holding hands was good, right?
Yes. It was a very happy moment!
Then let's do a good job today, too, okay?
- Yes!
- Fighting!
It's so cold. Why is it so freezing today?
When are Dae Beom and everyone else coming?
It's so cold today.
Grandmother, Mother!
Why did you come so early?
Se Ryun, it's so cold. How long have you been waiting?
Not that long.
Since I'm going to work, I wanted to come early to clean.
What do you mean you didn't wait that long? You're all frozen.
What a desperate love story.
You might as well just shoot a movie.
Mom, what are you doing? Go unlock the door.
My Se Ryun is about to freeze to death.
Alright.
Let's go.
- Se Ryun first.
- My goodness!
My goodness! Mom!
I thought the line, "it's no use raising a son," was other people's story.
Did you see him pushing me like this?
It's not like he's someone else's child, but how could Dae Beom treat me like this?
Do you think it's different with daughters?
Look at me. Look at what you've put me through.
You were always thinking about Soo Chul. Is he the only person that exists?
You didn't even care if your mother was alive or not.
But Mom, does she think she's at a fashion show or something?
She's coming to work at a chicken place, and what's with her clothes?
It's so cold, but her legs are completely exposed.
Oh, look who's talking.
When you were her age, you wore skirts even shorter than that.
Everyone could see your butt.
Why are you here?
Weren't you going to the hospital today?
I just wanted to help with the food prep and go.
Really?
Aigoo.
Honey, I'll be back.
Go help with the hospitalization process and come back.
Mother-in-law, I'll be right back.
See you later!
I don't understand why he's helping that person so much.
It's someone who has no family.
It's good karma for him, and it'll return as blessings.
We can handle everything on our own over here, so don't bring it up anymore.
I'm not saying anything.
Look, Ms. Se Ryun! Mop over there, every nook and cranny.
Yes, Mother!
Oh, my! Are you okay? Did you hurt anywhere?
Yes, I am okay, but...
My goodness! What are we going to do with all this?
Well, since you're not hurt, that's a relief,
but what a loss! We just washed and sanitized all these.
What bad luck right before opening up the restaurant for the day!
Why weren't you more careful?
I told you to clean the floor, not to break the cups!
What should we do about these cups?
I am sorry.
I'll go buy better cups than these.
Buying cups isn't the issue.
What did we say?
This type of work isn't for everybody.
That's why Dae Beom's dad and I tried to stop you.
You can't even work, so why are you trying to help?
I don't think this will work out. Just hurry up and go.
Don't interrupt our business.
We're going to have customers any minute, and we can't put out paper cups. What do we do?
I am sorry.
Why? What's going on?
What do you mean by that? Look at all this!
Look at the mess your Se Ryun made.
My goodness...
Oh, why did I do that? I'm crazy, crazy, seriously.
Se Ryun.
Dae Beom, what should I do?
I made a mess.
Your grandmother and mother seem very angry.
Se Ryun, don't come here again. You do not belong here.
Why are you saying that, too?
Se Ryun,
this job looks easy to you, but actually, it's not easy.
No. I'm going to do whatever it takes
to be accepted by Grandmother and Mother.
Hey, Lee Se Ryun!!
- Why?
- You really love me so much, don't you?
I do.
That's why I'm doing this. Why else?
Come here.
Why are you so adorable?
You're my forever Beautiful Bambi Baby.
Got it?
Beautiful Bambi Baby...
It's a good time. I'm jealous.
If I were 20 years, no, 10 years younger--
Hey, you punk.
Why are you peeking at other people dating?
It's creepy, you punk.
Let go of this! It hurts!
- When did you get over here while straining jokbal, you punk?
- Ow, Hyung!
Se Jong, did you want to see this movie that bad?
Yes.
Then I'll go get the tickets.
Ms. Park, wait just a minute.
Why? Do you want to watch a different movie?
That's not it... Hyung will come here.
Se Chan is coming?
Dad! Hyung!
Se Jong, were you waiting long?
No, I only waited a little bit.
Ms. Park, you're here as well.
Ah, yes.
Se Jong said that he wanted to watch a movie.
Dad, Se Jong told me he wanted to see this movie,
so I got Se Jong's, mine, Ms. Park's, and your tickets.
Did you?
Then Dad, let's get popcorn and drinks.
Okay, let's do that.
Se Jong, let's go.
It looks like here.
I'm going to go sit first!
Then I'm going to sit next to Se Jong!
♫ Even now, I remember your memories ♫
♫  Your name in my memory comes back to me in a smile,  ♫
♫ and comes back to me in pain sometimes  ♫
♫  If I get to see you once again  ♫
♫  You, the one I put in my heart  ♫
♫ I want to take you out on this cozy day ♫
♫ It gets deeper at the end of the day ♫
♫ I think of you a lot more ♫
♫ All night long, in my heart that has you in it,  ♫
♫ I want to call your name ♫
♫ Our time that was filled with excitements ♫
♫ The memory that's shining like you ♫
♫ The world seems to have stopped for a moment  ♫
♫ I'll always be by your side ♫
I said I was too sick to come to work.
Then Chairman should know, too.
But how can he not even send a text to see if I'm okay?
How can he do this to me?
If I'm going to be ignored like this,
should I just quit like what my mom says?
Se Jong.
Chief Jo Ajumma?
No way, how can I live without Se Jong?
That's right. I can't just crumble like this. At least, for Se Jong, I can't.
- That was fun, huh?
- I told you.
- Let's get inside.
- Dad, did you enjoy it, too?
- I thought it was great!
- Me, too!
I'm his fiancée,
but why is he going around with a different woman with the kids?
Driver Park.
CEO, everything will be all right.
Don't worry about a thing. All you have to do is get some deep sleep and wake up.
I'll be here waiting until your surgery is over.
So don't worry about a thing.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry...
CEO, why do you keep saying that?
This whole time,
I've been very grateful.
CEO, words like that,
say them when you come out from the surgery.
CEO...
I'll be here.
Okay.
[Operating Room]
Oh, what's up with you, Jenny?
You used to eat breakfast like a little bird,
and now you're eating this well?
I did jump rope in the garden for my morning workout, so I have so much appetite.
Oh, that's the reason!
If it weren't winter, I'd like to work out as well.
I don't like winter. It's too cold.
Chairman Lee, don't you think Chief Jo should eat with us from now?
I mean, she is your fiancée.
For the time being, Chief Jo and I are going back to the way things were before.
Like before?
Now Se Jong's eating vegetables well. Eat a lot.
Yes, Dad.
What a cold-hearted bastard.
Just because he doesn't remember getting engaged,
is he drawing a line to Chief Jo?
What should I do with this?
Does he have to say that he'll treat me as a butler like before, not as his fiancée,
in front of other people and the kids?
That's right. No matter what anyone says,
I'm the Chairman's fiancée.
I'm his fiancée.
I'm the fiancée.
An article? What kind of article is it?
It's about your engagement, Chairman.
Excuse me?
Who released this article?
Was it from the Public Relations Department?
No, it was not.
The Public Relations Department knows the best that your engagement was an unofficial matter.
But still, I checked to see if it was released by mistake,
and they said they never released an article.
Secretary Yoon, please contact the PR department now
and find out who released this article.
Yes, sir.
An article about the engagement?
Yes! Look here. My friend sent this to me.
Oh my. There's even a picture of the engagement.
But they covered Chief Jo's face.
Mrs. Yeoju, make me some tea. I want an aromatic herbal tea.
Madam, Madam, you came just in time.
Look at this. The Chairman and Chief Jo's engagement article came out.
An engagement article?
Oh, my! It's true!
[FT Group's Chairman Lee Young Gook got engaged after two years he became a widower! Who is the fiancée?]
But do they know about this?
Chief Jo! Chief Jo!
Yes, Madam, what is it?
Look, Chief Jo. Your engagement came out as an article. Did you see this?
Oh, really?
Look at it! But why did they blur out our Chief Jo's pretty face?
Anyway, congratulations again, Chief Jo, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Did Young Gook release this?
Yes, I wonder.
[FT Group's Chairman Lee Young Gook got engaged after two years he became a widower! Who is the fiancée?]
Yes, come in.
- Did you find out?
- Yes. The person who released your engagement article today
was the woman you engaged, Chief Jo Sarah.
- Are you certain?
- Yes, it is certain.
Okay. You may leave.
Honestly, I was so surprised this morning because of Young Gook.
How hard is it to include someone in a meal?
How can he say like that in front of the kids and Mrs. Yeoju?
He's such a cold-hearted jerk, a rude bastard.
You don't know how much I was cursing him in my head.
You must be so upset, aren't you?
Yes.
I guess he felt bad about how he treated you
since he released that engagement article.
Anyway, it's a good thing. When it comes to responsibility, no one has more than Young Gook.
Him telling the world: "I got engaged"
means that the wedding is definitely on. There's no chance of him backing out now.
Actually, I released that article.
I called the newspaper.
What?
Chief Jo, did you do this on your own without telling Young Gook?
Yes.
But you know Young Gook's temper, but how could you make such a huge mistake?
I don't want to just sit and take everything.
If it were you, could you stay silent?
Chief Jo, the Chairman is here, and he's looking for you.
But he looks very upset.
Does he?
Oh, my.
Excuse me, Madam.
Oh, my god. That little dummy made another huge mistake.
Knowing Young Gook's temper, he'll never let that slide.
Oh, what a dummy.
Chief Jo is a dummy.
Today's engagement article... Is it true that you released it?
Yes. I asked them to release it.
Chief Jo, I asked you to put this off until I regain my memory.
I said, when my memory returns, let's discuss this again.
But how could you release such an article first?
Without even consulting me. What the hell were you thinking?
If I had asked you, would you have given me permission?
What?
I had no choice. I had no choice but to release that article!
Chief Jo.
Chairman, I am your fiancée.
I'm your fiancée who only trusted your love and promised to live my life forever with you.
But now you don't want me to be your fiancée,
and you just want me to be someone who works for you, so what am I supposed to do?
Just because you don't remember,
does that mean that our engagement goes away?
Our love, our memories, do all those go away as well?
Just because I work here,
am I a toy you can play with and then throw away?
You're too harsh.
Chairman, you're being very harsh to me!
Oh, this is trouble!
Oh, I don't know anymore!
Wait, what is going on?
[An* Kim is in surgery.]
[The guardian should wait in the waiting room.]
They said it would be done in four hours.
Why is this surgery taking so long?
It's already past five hours.
Why haven't they finished yet?
I hope nothing bad happened.
[An* Kim's surgery is now complete, and the patient is now in the Recovery Room.]
[The guardian should come to the entrance of the Recovery Room.]
How is the patient, Anna Kim? Has her surgery gone well?
Are you her guardian?
Yes, I'm her guardian.
The surgery went well, and she is currently in recovery.
The results will be explained later by her doctor.
She's in the recovery room resting, so you can go in to see her.
Thank you very much.
CEO, it's me.
It's me, Driver Park.
Are you regaining consciousness?
Can you see me?
Soo Chul.
Yes.
It's me, Park Soo Chul.
I'm right here, CEO.
You really did stay here.
I told you I'd be here.
I told you nothing would go wrong.
They said the surgery went well.
CEO,
you don't have to worry about anything anymore.
Listening to what you said earlier, I see there's something I did wrong.
I only thought of my situation without regarding yours.
I'm sorry, Chief Jo.
Chairman.
I get it.
I'll also acknowledge...
our engagement.
Chairman, please...
Please regain your memory back soon.
You loved me so much,
but every time you treated me like a stranger now,
I felt like I could die.
Ms. Park. Ms. Park, while you went to your class,
there was a big incident.
Why? What happened?
That engagement article.
Chief Jo sent it to the media without the Chairman's knowledge.
He got angry with her for not talking to him in advance.
- He's not the one who did it?
- No.
It sounded like he wanted to cancel the engagement.
She figured that out and published their engagement.
Really?
Yes. Chief Jo was like when Chairman was a 22-year-old, he wanted to get engaged to her,
but why is he flipping it now and cried out loudly.
- Chief Jo did that?
- Yes.
Chairman then said, okay.
That he would acknowledge the engagement.
It looks like he doesn't even like Chief Jo.
But he is forcefully dragged into the engagement.
But isn't it strange?
Didn't she say they were in a relationship before? That's why they got engaged.
But now that his memory is back, why is he acting like that?
Were they not in a relationship?
Oh my, that renowned Jinsa Group second son had feelings for my Se Ryun?
Yes. In fact, while he was studying in the US saw your daughter a couple of times.
The madam of Jinsa Group found out about it
and went to the US and stopped him from dating her.
Why?
It's because...
Was it because of me?
Because I'm the mistress?
It's ridiculous!
It's hot.
So why are you telling me this now? Are you trying to make me angry?
That's not it. I sent them information about your daughter without knowing anything,
but their second son still has feelings for your daughter and hasn't gotten over her.
So they said if your daughter approves, they want them to arrange to see each other.
They ignored her because she's the mistress daughter. Why did they change their mind?
Didn't you hear about their son's broken marriage a few months ago?
Was he married?
Is he a divorcé?
They got into a fight during a honeymoon and broke up.
They never registered their marriage.
That's similar to what happened to us.
But their son often talks about how his mother stopped him from dating Se Ryun before
and resented his mother for that.
So the parents are regretting now that they should've not stopped him.
And, they are very sorry.
If Se Ryun is willing, they would like their son to see her.
Really? Did they really say that?
Yes.
But are you okay with him with that shortcoming?
Why is that a flaw? Se Ryun is fallen into this crazy gigolo right now.
Compared to that gigolo, he sounds a thousand times better.
So I told them about your daughter, honestly.
That she is caught by this weird family and tricked by them.
I thought it was only right to tell them about that.
Just in case it turns into a big problem if they find out about it later.
That was not wrong of me, was it?
Of course, not. You did it right. They should know about it.
But even though you told them all that,
they are still interested in meeting her?
Yes. If it's okay with Se Ryun,
they want to meet her immediately.
Oh my, how did that happen?
Oh my, what kind of fortune is this?
If it works out this time,
I will never forget your good work.
Oh, my. How could this be?
My goodness, you don't have to say that.
But will her daughter Se Ryun
agree to meet him when she's blind by love?
We have to persuade her somehow and make it work this time.
Oh, my.
That looks like my Joon Oh.
What's he doing here at this hour?
Joon Oh! Hey!
Joon Oh.
- Yes, Mom.
- Where are you now?
Me?
Where would I be? I'm at school, of course.
School?
Hey, Bong Joon Oh. You are not at school.
Why are you lying?
I'm looking at you right now. Why are you lying to me!
What?
Mom.
What? Did you take time off from school?
A leave of absence?
How could you do that without discussing it with me at all?
Also, you should've told me if you took time off from school.
Why didn't you tell me? Why did you lie to me?
It's because you would be shocked like this.
Also, I told you before that I want to take some time off, and what did you say?
You told me to endure that medical school is difficult for everyone.
Even so, how can you lie to me?
I'm sorry for lying.
But, Mom. I don't think I'm suited for medical school.
So I wanted to find out what I wanted to do before telling you.
I wasn't trying to lie and deceive you on purpose.
You should have told me and consulted with me first.
It really hurts me.
After your father passed away when we were young,
I only had you in my life.
How could you do that without saying a word to me?
Are you living alone?
Are you an orphan?
What am I to you?
Mom, I'm sorry.
Making you a great doctor
and setting up a nice hospital for you was my purpose and dream.
How could you disappoint me overnight?
When you got accepted to medical school,
I felt like I owned the world.
I was so happy and proud.
Joon Oh. Since you've taken a leave of absence,
just take a break for a year and go back to school.
Okay, Joon Oh?
Mom. I can't.
Every time I do an anatomy practice, I get sick. I throw up and can't eat for days.
I even fainted once.
What?
I feel nauseous just being near the anatomy practice room.
The important thing is I have no fun doing it.
How can I spend my life doing something that I don't feel compatible with?
Who studies because it's fun?
Even if it's not suitable, you adjust and work on it.
Also, it guarantees your future.
And it gives you social respect. That's why you should do it.
Why would you quit something that guarantees a bright future?
Mom. I've lived my life you've wanted until now.
I've never gone against your wish.
When you told me to come 1st, I studied hard to get there. I got into medical school even though I didn't want to!
I've lived the way you wanted until now!
So from now, I want to live the way I want to.
So please, Mom. Trust your son.
And just watch me.
I beg you, Mom.
Oh, my goodness...
Is that really my son?
How could he do that to me?
How? How?
That makes no sense, Sister-in-law.
Why would he quit medical school when other people want to get in there so bad?
He didn't quit it yet, but just took a leave of absence.
It's probably for a short time.
Everyone gets sidetracked once.
He will probably return once he's had a break.
Right?
Of course, he will.
Did Soo Chul and Dae Beom not come home?
Is the restaurant not closed yet?
Dae Beom will come home once he's finished at the restaurant.
Someone who helped Soo Chul had to go in for surgery,
and they had no one to take care of, so he's helping them.
But he hasn't come home yet.
Is that so?
How much and what help did he receive?
I know.
I am home.
Mi Rim, you are home.
Yes, Grandma.
Hello.
It's good that you are here. What are you doing these days?
Do you still go to the beauty academy?
Yes.
Would you be interested in working in my store?
Our part-time staff is quitting.
I will pay you more than in other places.
Yes, I'll take it.
But I have to take time off three times a week for the academy.
Of course, you can take time off for that.
When can you start?
I can quit the convenience store job in two weeks.
Then, I will make it work until then.
Can you start working in two weeks from now?
Yes, thank you!
Thank you.
Welcome!
Can we have one more soju here?
Ajussi, you look cute and nice like a teddy bear.
Be careful.
It's the teddy bear Ajussi! When did you get here?
Can I have a bowl of noodles and soju?
Okay.
That's refreshing.
What more is there in life? Have a drink like this and forget it all.
It looks like the Chairman wanted to cancel the engagement with Chief Jo.
Chief Jo was like when Chairman was a 22-year-old, he wanted to get engaged to her,
but why is he flipping it now and cried out loudly.
It looks like he doesn't even like Chief Jo. But he is forcefully dragged into the engagement.
But isn't it strange?
Didn't she say they were in a relationship before?
That's why they got engaged.
But now that his memory is back, why is he acting like that?
Were they not in a relationship?
Chairman did not get engaged to Chief Jo because he liked her.
I know that better than anyone.
The one who made him suffer like that is me.
Should I reveal everything now?
That the one the Chairman liked was me.
Go see Chief Jo
and say, "you are lying."
Like that.
Park Dan Dan.
But Chairman isn't saying anything. How can I say something?
Just have some drink.
And then forget it all.
In three months, you just leave without looking back.
It's cold.
Cheers!
Why does it taste so sweet?
Is it a low alcohol beer?
♫  When I walk this road, it makes me cry  ♫
Ms. Park looked a lot drunk.
♫ It reminds me of that person's touch  ♫
♫ I couldn't hold her and just trembled my heart  ♫
♫ My beautiful love ♫
♫ It seems like love is bitter  ♫
♫ The more I try to grasp it, the further it gets  ♫
It's all because of you.
Park Dan Dan, you're an idiot.
Let's just forget about it.
I should've left when the Chairman said so.
I can't even forget about him.
I'm such an idiot.
I'm an idiot. Park Dan Dan, you're an idiot.
♫ But love always runs away, chased by longing  ♫
I can't even forget about Chairman.
♫  It would be nice to take a break  ♫
Se Jong, try this oyster pancake.
I can use chopsticks very well.
You too, Se Chan.
Please stop doing this.
Please give me the right to choose the side dish I wish to eat.
Me, too. I don't like someone passing food with chopsticks they were using it.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Se Chan is so witty.
He said he wants the right to choose the side dish he wants?
You must be popular in school, Se Chan.
Yes, I think so, too.
I'm sure.
Go ahead and eat what you want.
I'm here.
Hello, Boss.
Maybe it's because you've had lots of part-time job experiences.
You are really meticulous.
It looks clean outside and brighter inside.
I feel relieved having you work here.
Thank you.
Please leave that down for a minute.
Okay.
Miss In-law.
Try this on.
What is it?
It's an accessory I used to wear when I was young. You should try it on.
It looks like gold.
Yes, it is. It's not pure, but an 18k gold necklace.
I want to thank you for doing such a great job.
You don't need to give me something like this.
I'm giving it to you because I appreciate you.
Please wear it. It's my appreciation.
Thank you.
I have to go out because I have a plan. You'll be okay by yourself, right?
- Of course.
- Work hard.
- I will be back.
- Have a nice day.
- Bye!
- Yes!
It's pretty.
It smells good. It smells nutty.
It's a pine nut porridge.
It will be so good.
What am I going to do now, Soo Chul?
What about it?
Now I'm looking forward to the porridge you make every day.
All of it tasted good.
I don't think I can eat any other porridge now besides yours.
What do I do now?
My goodness, CEO.
You made me nervous because I thought something had happened.
I will have to learn how to make porridge from you.
So I can make it for myself when I am alone.
You can't be here all the time when you are busy.
Yes, I will tell you later.
It's all done. Please sit down.
Yes.
Maybe because I walk with you every day, I'm digesting well.
And I feel like I'm gaining muscles in my legs. Walking is the best exercise.
Thanks to you, I've gained a good habit.
It's nothing.
You should walk outside often even if I'm not around.
Yes. I will.
Here.
You shouldn't get a cold.
You have to keep your neck warm.
Thank you.
It's a bit colder than yesterday.
It's so warm.
Because it has your warmth, it feels warmer.
♫ The road wrapped in the mist  ♫
♫ It's about to catch it, getting farther away ♫
♫ The road like a rainbow  ♫
♫ Where is it waiting for me?  ♫
♫  It's hard to find even if I look around  ♫
I almost fell.
If it weren't for you, I might have had another visit to the hospital with a sprained ankle.
Thank you, Soo Chul.
Let's go.
Yes, let's go.
I'll make Soo Chul my man, no matter what it takes.
Like before.
Have a nice date!
Yes.
Chairman, it's beautiful here. The steak tastes great too.
Is it? I'm glad you like it.
But the chicken you grilled at the vacation home was way more delicious.
Did I do that?
Yes. You and I were there alone.
You cooked the delicious chicken at night.
It deliciously melted in the mouth.
Is that right?
Yes.
Eating steak and wine right now reminded me of that time.
We roasted sweet potatoes in the bonfire. It was very romantic.
Don't you remember?
No, I don't.
We took a selfie while walking in the park.
Do you want to see it?
Here.
You look a bit different from now, don't you?
You really were like a 22-year-old.
You were cute and sweet.
I see.
Thank you, Chairman.
It was really fun tonight.
You're welcome. I'm glad it was fun.
Chairman.
Are you alright?
Who's this? Isn't it you, Ms. Park?
Yes, it's me. Ms. Park.
Chairman, have you been drinking?
Yes. I had some drinks.
I have some very difficult and depressing issues, so I drank.
It's because of you.
Because of me?
Yes, because of you, Ms. Park.
What did I do? Was there something I did wrong?
In my heart... you're the only one filling it to the brim.
I don't know why I made the mistake of getting engaged to another woman.
I want to know the reason so bad, but because I don't know,
I'm incredibly frustrated.
I want to open my head.
If I did, would I be able to know?
I can't forgive myself.
Why did I do such a stupid thing when I lost my memory?
You should have stopped me, Ms. Park.
This is all your fault.
You should have told me that we liked each other and stopped me.
Because of that, I got so upset with you,
that's why I drank.
Chairman...
I...
I really don't know what to do.
Should I just be the bad guy?
Should I just...
Should I just love you?
Ms. Park, will you be responsible for me?
Chairman...
I don't know how the day went by so fast.
It went by like a breeze.
Today was also a very fun day.
Since you had such a fun time, I'm relieved.
You said that I need to spend more time having fun.
Yes. That's how you can recover quicker and not relapse.
There's porridge in the fridge so just heat that up in the morning for breakfast.
I'll come back tomorrow after work.
Okay.
Then, get some rest. I'll get going.
Can you stay the night with me?
Stay with me.
♫  You're inside of fantasy that I can't reach  ♫
♫  Show you to me  ♫
♫  Even if I get a little bit closer, you go farther  ♫
♫  My love, my dream  ♫
Soo Chul?
♫  Don't say I'm making myself to fit you  ♫
♫  I'm inviting you to me  ♫
♫  The mysterious way you are is love to me  ♫
CEO, always take good care of your body and be healthy.
Thank you for everything until now.
"Thank you for everything until now?"
♫  The mysterious way you are is love to me  ♫
♫  You in the time that's stopping little by little  ♫
♫  Like a light in the darkness,  ♫
♫ My love ♫
You should've stopped me, Ms. Park.
You should have told me that we liked each other and stopped me.
I really...
don't know what to do.
Should I just be the bad guy?
Should I just...
Should I just love you?
What have I done?
Yes, who is it?
Ms. Park, what brought you here this early?
Chairman, I thought a lot about what you said to me last night.
What did I talk about last night?
Excuse me?
I drank a lot last night. I must have made a mistake to you, Ms. Park.
Since it was all drunk talk, don't worry about it.
I have a morning meeting.
Then, have a good day today as well.
He doesn't remember anything he said to me last night?
That it was a mistake?
I apologize for contacting you again when I know you're busy.
I have something very important to discuss with you.
What is it?
I don't want to beat around the bush, so I'll be upfront.
Soo Chul, stay by my side.
Being with you brought me so much strength and joy.
Now, to me, you are an incredibly important person.
- CEO...
- Soo Chul.
Come with me to America. With Ms. Park.
♫ Why do you run away, love? Like a shy child ♫
♫ In case I lose it
, I hold it tight ♫
♫ But love always runs away, chased by longing ♫
♫ It would be nice to take a break ♫
♫ I have to abandon the longing and the grieves ♫
♫ What am I looking for on this road wandering ♫
♫ Why am I here for what ♫
♫ Why do you run away, love
?
Like a shy child ♫
[Young Lady and Gentleman]
- I scouted Ms. Park to come with me, but I wondered if Park Soo Chul could also come with us.
- Pardon?
Chairman, it's me. There's something important I need to tell you.
Do you still not remember?
- I don't remember.
- Then I'll tell you everything.
I'm going to have some courage.
- Chairman!
- Ah, you startled me!
Listen to what Chief Jo says. In no time, she's going to become your mother.
Seriously, you're pissing me off.
I thought it might be awkward for you, so I asked to meet you outside.
You're just a mere live-in tutor--
You need to watch your words.
Hey, I'm not done talking!
Did you get money from my sister?
I had no other choice than to take that money!
- What?
- You should go to America and bring us more money!
You also have feelings for me, don't you?