♪You are the best thing on my mind♪
♪A total sugar rush♪
♪Oh you make me blush♪
♪'Cause now it's more than a crush♪
♪The way you caught my eye♪
♪It's like we're synchronized♪
♪Guess I'm all yours now♪
♪I guess♪
♪You make me wanna fly to the moon♪
♪You make me wanna dance right here♪
♪You make me feel like I should cry♪
♪'Cause I'm the happiest, that's true♪
♪You make me wanna kiss the stars♪
♪You make me wanna dream 'bout you♪
♪You make me feel like I should weep♪
♪'Cause I'm the happiest, that's true♪
♪Just for you♪
=Smile Code=
(Adapted from Douban Read's work
"Smile Code" by Zhu Yue)
=Episode 3=
♪I only wish to be your sun♪
♪Deep within your heart♪
♪No matter how far the destination is♪
♪Don't be afraid. I'm here for you♪
♪I only wish to be your sun♪
You are my sun!
Your sun
is...
Woohoo!
♪A drop of tear falling silently♪
You are my sun!
I wish to be your sun!
Deep within your heart!
♪All those joyful young ladies♪
♪They seem jealous♪
♪What else do I need to find?♪
(Housemate, Liu Qingchun)
Is this Gu Yi's unit?
You must be Gu Yi's friend.
Just hand her to me. Thank you.
What are you doing?
Are you two sharing a unit?
We're just like a family.
Don't worry. Just leave her to me.
What?
Is this your unit?
What are you looking at?
♪I can give up on my life♪
You should leave her here
before leaving!
♪For love♪
Woohoo!
♪I only wish to be your sun♪
♪Your sun♪
♪Deep within your heart♪
♪No matter how far the destination is♪
♪Don't be afraid. I'm here for you♪
♪I only wish to be your sun♪
♪Deep within your heart♪
♪Even if I can't stay by your side♪
♪I'll try to shine for your sake♪
Why are you back?
She mentioned in her jokes
that her housemate was shady.
I verified it myself.
Tell her to move when she's awake.
You...
Wait, she...
You're something else.
You probed along the edges of morality.
In the end, you escaped unscathed, huh?
What a waste of my effort.
Why am I sleeping here?
Mr. Yu.
You're awake.
How did I end up
spending the night here?
Don't tell me you blacked out?
I didn't.
You, I, and Mr. Lu
were drinking over there.
You even won 800 yuan
through a lottery ticket, right?
That's right.
You do remember things clearly
when they're related to money, huh?
If so, do you still remember
the incident with your housemates?
I do.
I drove two of them crazy.
As for the other one,
it's a long story.
It's no wonder
Liang Daiwen sent you back here
after sending you back home.
What are you saying? Stop joking.
You...
Don't tell me you blacked out for real?
What do you mean by that?
You know what I mean.
Yesterday, the three of us
were drinking over there.
When we left the door after drinking,
we encountered
Liang Daiwen doing his night jog.
You said nothing
and threw yourself at his feet.
After that,
Liang Daiwen
asked me for your address.
He sent you home.
After that, he sent you back here.
He said you should move out.
Don't tell me you forgot about it?
My goodness.
Are you the living Liang Daiwen?
Have you seen
a dead Liang Daiwen before?
Since fate has led us to each other,
I'll join you for your night jog!
I'm done for!
What do you mean?
It's not that back.
I do think
that he's interested in you.
He was already kind enough
to give you a ride home.
After that, he reminded you
that your housemate was problematic.
He's concerned about you,
don't you think? That's great.
Yu Dule,
can you let me be dignified for once?
Just once is enough.
He already thought
that my jokes weren't funny.
Now,
I'm utterly embarrassed.
It's not that bad,
So,
we should get to work first.
Gu Yi.
What's wrong?
Are you sick?
Morning, Director.
We have a meeting at 6 P.M.
Would it be convenient for me to discuss
this topic with you in advance?
I'm new here. I'm not familiar
with the procedures yet.
Why don't you ask Ms. Zhang directly?
Ms. Zhang has a client to meet today.
Gu Yi, you should join us.
Gu Yi still has revisions to make
on the trend color draft.
She has to send it to our client
before 3 P.M.
3 P.M.?
Wasn't it 5 P.M.?
The automatic office system
updated the time.
What?
So, you have time to do a talk show,
but you don't have time
to amend the draft?
How did you find out as well?
Yi,
you actually do talk shows after work?
Can you please don't bring this up
in the office?
There's no one else here.
Everyone in the world
knows about it now.
I'll stop, then.
Fine.
If you wish to come,
I'll reserve two tickets for you.
Miss.
Why should you employ me?
And now, my rate is
much higher than before.
You also know that Nextmonday
has been trying online integration
for the past few years.
Currently, magazines
can't feature anything
other than ads and promotions.
As for print media,
the purity is too high.
When there's a new trend,
it'll jeopardize our progress.
I agree.
But you haven't answered
my question yet.
Haven't music variety shows been popular
for the past few years?
I wish to create a column
for music.
Readership numbers don't matter.
What matters is
the synergy of omni-media channels
in the future.
Understood.
That means I'll be the key
to your views.
You should consider it.
Actually, the terms are free
and easy for contributing writers such as you.
You don't need to come up with scripts.
The content department will help you out with that.
But you have to attend all events.
The content department?
Last time, there was a person
who interviewed me.
That's Gu Yi.
Gu Yi, huh?
That's right. That's her.
Rest assured about
the quality of the script.
She's doing multiple jobs
at the same time, huh?
She'll perish under such pressure,
you know?
You don't understand her at all.
Look at her.
Does she look like
she's perishing under pressure?
You see, a female housemate of mine
likes to put sand in her room.
She said she wanted to take a sand bath
plus perform hot yoga at home.
(Liang Daiwen)
(Home Design, To Feel Good Than Look Good
Interviewer: Gu Yi)
Gu Yi,
how did you come up
with such exciting jokes?
You're
so intelligent!
Why didn't you go home?
Did Yu Dule tell you to move out?
He did.
He even told me
that you sent me home
and sent me back to Ounce again.
It was a risk transfer.
I...
I didn't do anything strange to you,
right?
You suddenly jumped onto my back
and recite your jokes
when I was sending you home.
Was it that embarrassing
for me to send you home after you got drunk?
That's not it.
It's not too bad.
I'm glad to hear that.
I came here to collect materials.
What are you doing here?
You mentioned this garden in your jokes.
I came here to take a look.
I didn't expect
to encounter you again.
Sounds like you don't like
to encounter me.
You can leave, then.
Goodbye.
Sorry about that.
Pat the head,
no more dread.
♪Twilight overtakes the sky
at the horizon♪
♪The stars arrive slightly late♪
♪Despite my hesitation,
I won't back off♪
♪How I wish for one more page
in our story♪
You're expressionless even when
a basketball hits you on the head, huh?
Now, I believe
that you cannot laugh.
Are you No-Face?
♪Soothing all the worries♪
It's my issue for
not being able to laugh.
Your talk show is very influential.
Your jokes are full of expressions.
I can tell
that you truly like it.
If my presence does affect
your performance,
I'll stop attending them in the future.
That won't do.
Huh?
It's fine that you're not laughing.
However, you have
to come and hear my jokes.
I have an infinite number of them.
Do you need me to send you home?
You don't?
I mean, I do.
Where did you learn
how to be hot and cold?
From
TV dramas.
Let's go.
Actually,
you didn't need to send me home.
He just likes to trash-talk.
He won't do anything to me.
I think the lamp is broken.
Why aren't you singing?
Singing? What do you mean?
Woohoo!
How did you know about that?
You sang it before.
There's one more song.
So, I've arrived home.
I'll head upstairs first.
Door unlocked.
You still know
that this is your home, huh?
This is none of your business.
How is this none of my business?
That guy who carried you
back home last night, who is he to you?
If I must say,
we should confirm our relationship
as soon as possible.
This way, those scoundrels
wouldn't dare to harass you.
Am I right?
Mind your actions.
It's you again?
What? Are you not done
taking advantage of her?
You carried her back again, huh?
What? Are you her mount?
We have evidence of
the person taking advantage of her now.
She won't be living here in the future.
If you keep this up,
I'll call the cops on you.
What are you saying?
We're a family.
Tell him. Aren't we a family?
Hey, you...
Go away.
What do you mean by that?
Why are you bringing him inside?
This is our home, you know? You...
Open the door!
You shouldn't bring outsiders
to our home!
Operation failed.
You...
Liang Daiwen.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
Your house is messier than I thought.
The customs
should've confiscated your mouth
when they were checking you.
You dare to say
that he was trash-talking?
You announced
that I would be moving out.
What did you mean by that?
Which part of me made you think
I've got enough money
to move?
I...
I can tell that you can't.
Did you see that hospital?
If you do infuriate me to death,
remember to call 120
so that they can collect my body.
Your cactus is actually dying.
Can't you tell that I'm dying as well?
Did you see this?
This was supposed to be the perfect day
for me to get promoted and move.
But now, my promotion is jeopardized.
A salary increase
is out of the question as well.
How can I move when I'm penniless?
Do you think I'm willing
to stay in such a crappy unit?
Sorry.
Maybe I'm being nosy over here.
But if you continue to stay here,
you'll only expose yourself
to more danger.
So, you're concerned about me, huh?
Maybe.
I'm not forcing you to make a choice.
However, your housemates
are pretty weird.
Avoiding them alone
won't resolve your issues.
Getting a promotion
and a salary increase
aren't as important
as your personal safety.
I also know that avoiding them alone
won't resolve my issues.
But now, I'm in too much debt.
Moving to another place
is as tough as taking on
a Level Nine Fire Phoenix.
I understand.
A fallen phoenix
is worse than a chicken, right?
There's a whetstone in the kitchen.
I should use it to shut you up.
Is it a burden?
Burden?
Is that the only thing you know?
I don't have that much burden.
You think it's a burden to me.
But I'm the one suffering here.
How can I still
live in this unit after this?
(Say goodbye to shared rental)
What if Liu Qingchun comes back?
This is so infuriating.
Just let me die.
This is so annoying!
You need a place to stay, huh?
You don't say?
Why don't you stay at my house?
You...
Are you serious?
You said the best thing to give a friend
should be simple and straightforward.
You need a place to stay, right?
My house will do.
Of course, this is just a suggestion.
If you don't need my help...
Open the door!
Don't take outsiders home!
I need it.
I need it urgently.
♪You are the best thing on my mind♪
♪A total sugar rush♪
(It doesn't mean
that your hand is aching.)
(It means that someone has invaded
the blind spot of your mind.)
♪Now, it's more than a crush♪
♪The way you caught my eye♪
♪It's like we're synchronized♪
♪I guess I'm all yours now♪
♪I guess♪
♪You make me want to fly to the moon♪
♪You make me want to dance right here♪
♪Just for you♪
(Jacqueline: Send me
next week's roster period)
(All right. I'll send it immediately.)
We're almost done here.
Should I call for a cab?
Do it on my behalf.
I'll transfer the money to you later.
Call for a large one.
I can't fit all of them in a small car.
Where's my PC?
You just sealed it in the box.
Is this the "cab" you called?
Yeah, a huge one.
Miss.
Is that all you have?
Isn't this truck too big for you?
Please fetch me as well.
(Huohuo Renjia, Your Goods Deliverer)
(I'm on my way to Liang Daiwen's house.)
(We're going to live together.)
(That's cool. Stop being a jokester
when you're there. That's not sexy at all.)
(You need to show him your sexy side.)
(He already saw everything about me.
How can I still be sexy to him?)
(Yu Dule: It's fine.
You can get a rebound after this.)
(What's with the basketball reference?)
Are you discussing what to do
when you reach my house?
That's not it.
I'm typing jokes
in my notepad.
Your notepad is pretty unique, huh?
It can actually reply to you.
Did you take a peek?
Your glasses were reflecting
your screen.
Don't worry.
You can stay in my house.
I'll stay in my office.
Both of us will be safe.
Mr. Liang.
Can I ask you something?
Why are you helping me out?
I analyzed your situation.
I realize
that you need help at this moment.
Is that all?
That is all.
I only analyze reality.
I never act with emotions.
Mr. Liang,
is your brain made out of chips?
You wouldn't want to know
what my brain was made of.
1402.
The password is 001402.
Head upstairs and unlock the door first.
You want me to head upstairs first?
You want to move them all by yourself?
That'd be too embarrassing for me.
I'm not telling you
to head upstairs empty-handed.
Take your stuff while you're at it.
Now, I have new materials
for my jokes after moving here.
Remember to tell me the jokes.
Mr. Liang,
are you interested in stand-up comedy?
Or are you merely interested
in my jokes?
I'm interested in the slogan
of the comedy club,
"The human soul only weighs one ounce."
I think I have an ounce of soul as well.
I need to find it myself.
Door unlocked.
♪Twilight overtakes the sky
at the horizon♪
♪The stars arrive slightly late♪
♪Despite my hesitation♪
What are you doing?
Why are you blushing?
I'm radiating with vigor.
(Why are you trying to be funny now?)
(Female comedians
don't deserve love at all.)
Is that a burden to you?
Sorry about that.
It was a conditioned reflex.
Your hobbies
are quite unique.
My friend said that keeping pets
helps with mental health
and can also cultivate one's character.
By pets, I think your friend
was referring to them.
Were you the one who launched
a sneak attack at me?
I thought of keeping
a South American spider.
But I gave up when I knew
I had to feed it with cockroaches.
They were wandering nearby.
That's why I brought them back.
Just like how you brought me back.
I was joking.
Do they have names?
Daju.
Erju.
Sanju.
Siju.
Wuju.
There's only one orange cat.
Why is the name orange
in all of their names?
I reared a dog before this.
It had orange in its name too.
But it got depressed.
Someone else adopted it.
We're kindred spirits.
The cactus I kept
was barely surviving.
Daju, Eeju, Sanju, Siju,
Wuju,
nice to meet you guys.
I'm a part of the family now.
Let's get along in the future.
Mr. Liang,
do you have OCD when it comes
to arranging the cat bowls?
Red, orange, yellow,
green, blue, indigo, violet.
The first five colors of the rainbow
is easy to remember.
If so, I need an indigo bowl.
That's another burden.
The company rented this unit for me.
I've already paid the deposit.
No dismantling,
smashing, or modifications.
I rarely cook usually.
There's nothing in the refrigerator.
You can order for food delivery
or get your takeaways.
Just dispose of the rubbish on time.
Both the washing machine
and dryer are inside the bathroom.
I've cleaned up the room for you.
The new bedding set is in the wardrobe.
The housekeeper will
clean them periodically.
I can just sleep on the sofa.
Your cats are sleeping on the sofa too.
The study room is also my workshop.
I'm used to locking it up.
Don't mind it.
I've set the air conditioner
to a constant temperature. Don't adjust it.
Okay.
Don't worry.
I'll thrive wildly while
following the regulations.
Leave the kittens to me as well.
Make yourself at home.
I'll make a move first.
This design
doesn't make sense at all.
I wonder if the robot can sleep well
after moving to another charging port?
Erju.
A stray cat like me has a home now!
(Nextmonday)
What clients are featured
in next week's headline?
The domestic beauty brand
Radiance Series,
a smart desk lamp brand,
and a reading APP.
They'll be featured between
Tuesday and Friday.
On Monday, there will be a post
related to youth.
It'll serve to attract
potential customers.
What is the theme of the post?
The initial draft is...
The new consumption mindset
of current youths.
That's lame.
It's not memorable at all.
There are plenty of magazines in the company
that bypass the "wall" every month.
You guys are also allowed
to gather materials outside.
How come you guys are still
only capable of coming up
with topics
that only outline the basics?
I have nothing to say to you.
The main thing here is the ability
to deliver news with passion.
Stay there and don't move.
What do the readers desire?
What do our clients desire?
That's the true goal we're after.
Sorry about this.
I need to head out for a second.
Go ahead.
Let's continue.
Welcome.
I was talking about my divorce with her.
I just didn't expect to see you here.
Listen to me.
I'll call the cops on you
if you keep this up!
Baby, it's my fault.
I'm begging you.
I always wanted to tell you about her.
We got married
after going on a blind date.
We have no children.
We don't love each other.
I truly have feelings for you.
Chen Yijin,
can you be a decent human for once?
Although you have no shame,
I still have my dignity.
We've been together for a long time.
Must you break up with me?
I've already broken up with you.
I kept your dignity intact
because I felt sorry for your wife.
If you have the time to find me, why don't you
ead back and console her instead?
Don't tell me you think
that you're a victim?
You must've lost your mind!
Guan Xingxin, you better cherish
the respect I'm showing you here.
Let me put it this way.
If news of
our relationship gets out,
do you think any of us
can escape unscathed?
Are you crazy?
I'll show you crazy
if you dare to come here again!
That crazy woman.
Why did you press the doorbell
before coming inside?
Did you forget your password
after going out?
I came back to take some clothes.
I was worried
that the timing might be inappropriate.
Liang Daiwen!
It's fine.
I often roll off the sofa as well.
Why don't you...
You should
move back
and live here together with me.
You don't mind
living together with me?
I don't.
I've been to your office before.
Your sofa was quite small.
The size is too small for you.
Good friends have to be understanding
with each other.
Don't let me presence
affect your daily life.
Alright.
I'll go and get changed first.
(We're living together!)
(Layla, the mistress)
(Layla is actually a mistress)
(The actress, Layla,
is actually a mistress?)
(Layla, the cheating mistress.)
(Layla got to her position by
having an affair. Shameless woman.)
(I didn't expect her to be like this.
Shameless woman. Let's expose her deed.)
(Women like her have
to ruin other people's families.)
(The all-evil mistress.)
(I'm Chen Yijin's wife.
I know that I'm not perfect.)
(I'm past my prime, and I've lost
both my husband and child.)
(My goodness. She harmed
other people's child as a mistress.)
(She's so evil.)
♪My palm lines are learning to imitate♪
♪My eyes shine with thrilling starlight♪
♪As I step into the whirlwind
of this brand-new world♪
♪A touch to this face
makes my heart flutter♪
♪How can I escape♪
♪From these sparks of destined love?♪
♪The mist looms over the streets♪
♪Many mysteries are hidden♪
♪The stars will guide me♪
♪Deep within the noisy crowd♪
♪There is a light♪
♪Illuminating me in the darkness♪
♪It should be you♪
♪Nobody else but you♪
♪A bond formed when we first met♪
♪Will lead us into a new journey♪
♪You should be my star♪
♪The moment you cross the sky♪
♪A colorful story is lit♪
♪The wind carries my wish across,
under the gaze of starry skies♪
♪With the clues in the script of destiny♪
♪We explore the path toward happiness♪
♪In courage and perseverance♪
♪All emotions will eventually♪
♪Find the right colors♪
♪'Cause I'll always be with you♪
♪The mist looms over the streets♪
♪Many mysteries are hidden♪
♪The stars will guide me♪
♪Deep within the noisy crowd♪
♪There is a light♪
♪Illuminating me in the darkness♪
♪It should be you♪
♪Nobody else but you♪
♪A bond formed when we first met♪
♪Will lead us into a new journey♪
♪You should be my star♪
♪The moment you cross the sky♪
♪A colorful story is lit♪
♪The wind carries my wish across,
under the gaze of starry skies♪