♪You are the best thing on my mind♪
♪A total sugar rush♪
♪Oh you make me blush♪
♪'Cause now it's more than a crush♪
♪The way you caught my eye♪
♪It's like we're synchronized♪
♪Guess I'm all yours now♪
♪I guess♪
♪You make me wanna fly to the moon♪
♪You make me wanna dance right here♪
♪You make me feel like I should cry♪
♪'Cause I'm the happiest, that's true♪
♪You make me wanna kiss the stars♪
♪You make me wanna dream 'bout you♪
♪You make me feel like I should weep♪
♪'Cause I'm the happiest, that's true♪
♪Just for you♪
=Smile Code=
(Adapted from Douban Read's work
"Smile Code" by Zu Yue)
=Episode 24=
Well,
you look honest,
but you acted otherwise
when you were drunk.
I'm sorry, Mdm. Wang.
I just want to pursue Gu Yi,
but
I don't know what to do.
Well,
that's exactly what I'm waiting to hear.
Tell me
what Gu Yi said to you.
She said
she doesn't mind my alexithymia issue,
only my attitude.
She said I treat her like a trash cat.
And
she wants me to live well
and stop seeing her.
What should I do?
That's tricky.
She's lost trust in you.
Is there any way
to fix it?
Forget about that for now.
Tell me about your alexithymia
in detail.
My therapist says
it's a kind of personality trait
or a psychological symptom.
The main issue is
my lack of ability to feel,
identify,
and express feelings.
I have a poor imagination,
I'm overly objective,
and I can't interpret
feelings correctly.
I get it.
It means
you're still a kid.
That's not a big deal.
Gu Yi was the same when she was young.
Some kids are different.
They have done nothing wrong.
What's the problem with that?
The world is so complicated
and full of deceit.
Isn't it good
to live like a kid?
Just live in a comfortable way
for yourself.
You're not hurting anyone,
right?
Liang,
you can't take away
my daughter so easily.
Let's have a drink.
Let me tell you
Gu Yi's childhood story.
Kids always write essays like...
Here. Over here.
Jacqueline,
lie down.
Who is this?
She looks like the Consort Jing.
[*A character in a harem series.]
My superior,
the wicked Medusa.
Music!
What kind of music does she like?
You don't know her at all.
Are you trying to get me into trouble?
Zhang Junjie!
Wake up.
Wake up!
What are you doing?
Gu Yi.
Wake up.
Zhang Junjie,
give me the right
to create independently!
Give me an opportunity!
Give me a promotion!
Give me a raise!
You all call me Demoness.
I know.
And I don't care.
Let me tell you this.
I'm a machine.
I'm heartless.
Rules of the jungle.
Only the strong survives.
Don't you know that?
Look at you.
You're an honest fool.
You can't even handle someone
like Penny.
Listen up.
If it weren't for me, you would've...
Don't throw up yet. No!
I just cleaned the place.
Bathroom.
Help me out.
Should I call your friend over?
No need.
I don't have friends.
Zhang Junjie.
You never changed.
Get up.
Let's have another drink.
Come on.
Get up.
Up.
Stand properly.
Walk slowly.
Mr. Huang,
I don't have the strength
to send her home.
But let me remind you.
Don't take advantage of her.
Little girl,
when I was taking advantage of others,
you were still in kindergarten.
Be careful.
I warn you, don't throw up on me.
Careful.
Little girl?
How old is he?
Who knows?
Come. I'll give you a ride home.
Let's go.
♪No matter how far the destination is♪
♪Don't be afraid. I'm here for you♪
♪I only wish to be your sun♪
♪Be your sun♪
♪Deep within your heart♪
♪I'm by your side♪
Mom.
Mom!
♪Still, we say goodbye♪
What are you two doing?
Gu Yi.
She's my daughter, Gu Yi.
A stand-up comedian.
She's really good at it.
Gu Yi.
I...
I've watched your show before.
Your jokes are funny.
How about she perform for us?
Come on.
Quiet.
My neighbor will call the police on you.
Come on.
Perform for us.
I love you, Daiwen.
My dear mother.
Gu Yi,
I love you.
I love you, too, Mom.
Sleep tight.
Be good.
Okay.
Let me tuck you in.
I love you.
Gu Yi.
Quiet.
Your mom is really cute.
She doesn't treat me as a robot.
She treats me as a kid.
Thank you
for treating me like family.
(Wet floor)
You're awake?
Here.
Drink this.
You'll feel better.
Get off.
Here.
You haven't changed one bit.
You always throw up the next day
after drinking a lot.
What?
Why am I at your place?
You ask me why?
You were drunk,
and I helped you.
Get off.
You're a lunatic.
I'm a lunatic?
If it weren't for me taking you in,
you would've been on the news
this morning,
you know?
I'd rather be on the news.
I'll pay
for the room charge.
Also,
from now on,
don't ever get close to me.
You never speak nicely
as you always have.
Hangover tea.
It's the brand you always drink.
It's clean.
Drink it.
Well,
I went to visit your aunt
a couple of days ago.
She's in good health.
Do you know she was hospitalized
before Chinese New Year?
You don't have to tell me this.
I pay her
without a dime less.
You're cold-blooded.
Huang Wenda,
don't think I don't know
why you went back.
You just want to know
if I gave birth to the child
and handed it over to her.
Give up already.
Let me make this clear again.
No!
Zhang Junjie.
What are you doing?
That's also my child.
How desperate you are for your career
is equal to how desperate I was
to keep the child.
You know what I truly want is
to have a child with my loved one,
but you aborted the baby.
You threw the baby away.
How ruthless you are.
Don't you have nightmares?
I don't.
I'm glad I didn't give birth
to the baby.
Because
you don't deserve it.
I don't deserve it?
I'm the baby's father!
I just want to know if
it's a boy or a girl.
Is that too much to ask?
Do you remember what you replied to me?
(Zhang Junjie: It)
Just one word.
You used "it".
Are you an animal?
I still keep the message on my phone.
Let me be honest with you.
Every time I can't fall asleep
thinking about you,
I read the message
to warn myself.
Mr. Huang,
we can argue about this until we're 80.
Haven't you gotten sick of it yet?
By the way,
here's a kind reminder.
Marry a young woman and have a child
as soon as possible.
The kids won't be as good
when you get older.
Stop following me.
You're awake?
Morning.
Morning?
You're a habitual drunk, aren't you?
Do you have anything to tell me?
Will you be my girlfriend?
You...
You were drinking a lot
with my mom
last night, and this is the first thing
you say when you wake up?
If so,
what should I do
to make you my girlfriend?
Forget it.
We'll talk when you're sober.
What's wrong with you? Let go of me.
I won't if you don't say yes.
If you want to leave the door single,
kill me
and step over my dead body.
Liang Daiwen,
what's wrong with you?
Can you please consider my feelings
before you say something this gross?
I like you, and you like me.
Why can't we be together?
Let go of me first.
My mom will wake up soon.
I'm already up.
Mom, I'm off to work.
Gu Yi.
Xin.
Dad.
You're up early.
Aren't you sleeping in today?
Xin.
Are you going out?
I bought you a new dress.
Do you not like it?
It's not that.
Put that on.
It doesn't look good
wearing this.
Xin,
you look prettier in a dress.
Listen to your mom. Go put it on.
Come.
Dear,
that's enough.
She's already of age to get married,
not your doll.
What were you doing?
Get married?
Who is she marrying?
That jobless guy?
That's impossible.
Keep it down.
What is this?
Xin's parcel.
What are you doing?
Hey.
(Virtual Idol Performer Contract)
(Agency: Nextmonday,
Artist: Guan Xingxin)
Mom.
(Oncology Department, Clinic 2)
(Pancreatic space-occupying lesion.)
(The cancer in your abdomen
has metastasized.)
(Doctor,)
(I heard that cancer in its final stage
can be very painful. Is that true?)
(The prognosis for pancreatic cancer
is very poor,)
(and surgery for the final stage
is delicate.)
(The effects of immunotherapy
and targeted therapy)
(are not favorable,)
(and they can easily trigger metastasis.)
(Once the tumor spreads
and compresses the nerves,)
(some parts of your body
may become paralyzed,)
(and the pain)
(Radiology MRI Results Report)
(will intensify.)
(How long will I live
if I start treatment?)
(With adequate financial support
and good body condition,)
(continuous treatment
could extend your life)
(for around half a year on average.)
What if I give up?
Cheer up.
Don't worry. It's not that bad.
You can still be treated. Really.
Don't think about it too much.
We'll go to the hospital
tomorrow.
Don't worry about money.
I want bubble tea.
Okay.
Wait here. I'll get it for you.
Nice?
Yes.
You look pretty just when you were
in the opera troupe.
He,
I want to bring Gu Yi home.
Okay.
That's funny.
Isn't Guan Xingxin Nextmonday's artist?
Why does she need Roger's consent
to attend events?
Her parents are irrationally anxious.
They called Roger
to have Guan Xingxin replaced.
Do I have a reason to reject them?
Then what was the point
of all the preparation?
Guan Xingxin's homewrecker scandal
is exposed
through Nextmonday.
It's understandable
that her parents don't trust us.
Roger has to do them this favor.
We just follow the orders.
The exhibition is important,
but it's also normal to replace artists.
No more questions.
I can keep quiet,
but Guan Xingxin will ask questions.
How should I explain to her?
Continue working on the contract.
Then, find an excuse to cancel it
when she signs.
Don't make things difficult
for her parents.
Don't tell Gu Yi about this.
Roger
doesn't like her.
Leave Guan Xingxin's matter
to Huang Wenda.
Why haven't you left yet?
Deputy Director took on a promotion
project for an aesthetic clinic.
I'm thinking of creating a comic
for both Nextmonday and the bypass.
This is the manuscript.
Have you had
a cosmetic treatment before?
No.
There aren't always heart-shaped faces.
You need to experience
to create a comic about it.
Here's a clinic membership card.
Don't need to pay me back.
Thank you.
Get off work after eating.
Well,
would you like to eat together?
Ms. Zhang,
you and
Mr. Huang...
Are you all right?
Keep quiet if you have nothing to say.
If that happens again,
don't call him.
Why do I get the feeling
you really dislike him?
Are you asking,
if I dislike him so much,
why was I with him in the first place?
Huang Wenda is very smart.
Many people notice
opportunities in the industry,
but only a few
can truly reap the benefits.
He's gifted.
He's born to be an opportunist.
When I first came to this city,
I didn't know anything.
He taught me step-by-step
how to build a client base
and expand networking resources.
Because of his guidance,
I avoided many missteps.
However,
an overly smart person
tends to control everything.
I didn't want him to decide on my life,
so I joined his competitor
and took away
all his clients and resources.
To put it nicely,
it was a competition between a couple.
But to put it bluntly,
we turned against each other.
So
you broke up
because of competition?
If two people can't meet
each other's expectations,
they end up pursuing self-interest.
Why?
Is something wrong
between you and Liang Daiwen?
It's hard to say.
Do you have to stay up late
writing scripts
as a public account editor?
You suddenly become so dedicated
because of a breakup.
I heard about Liang Daiwen's reputation.
He's unsociable, stubborn, and aloof,
but a true talent.
Everyone knows
he didn't commit plagiarism,
but no one will stand up
for him.
Because they all know
Zhang Qingya and he
each have their own motives.
Breaking a contract is like a breakup.
Either you end things nicely,
or
both sides suffer.
Do you think
the allegorical long comic
really supported him?
If they fall out,
it'll also be tough for Liang Daiwen.
After all,
Zhang Qingya led him into the industry.
What are you talking about?
Stop pretending.
The long comic
is your creation.
However,
it's a shame you did it for a man.
The bypass is a suitable platform.
Play to your strengths.
You were shouting at me
and demanding the right
to do independent content.
Weren't you drunk?
Did you hear everything?
I was drunk,
not deaf.
I'm surprised
by your drive.
I'm also glad to see it.
Go ahead and do it.
But remember,
finding a partner who matches you
is like hitting the jackpot.
Having
your own muscle
gives you true strength.
Since you brought it up,
please reimburse me
for the taxi fare from that day.
What did I just tell you?
Muscle.
Build my own muscle.
I remember your advice.
(61.9km, 419 yuan)
I'll transfer you the money.
Take the trash out later.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to pick you up.
Liang Daiwen,
did you forget what I told you
at Fuzzy?
No, I remember.
You said we shouldn't meet again.
Then what are you doing here?
I remember what you said,
but that doesn't mean I agree.
It's hard to get a cab on a rainy day.
I only have one umbrella.
Do you want to share it with me?
Tactile paving.
It may not be common
to meet people with disabilities
in real life,
but we need to respect their space.
How's your studio
coming along?
It just started.
Li Ai is developing an application
that amplifies sound
for people with hearing issues.
It's like
a cochlear implant on a phone.
Isn't that
a hearing aid?
Sort of.
But hearing aids
have strict medical standards
and are pricey.
Compared to hearing aids,
everyone has a phone now.
A phone application
could achieve wider accessibility.
Subtitles were initially designed
for the hearing impaired.
Why are there
apps to aid
hearing and sight
but not smell?
Both hearing and sight
facilitate communication.
However, smell
can't be digitized.
Also,
it doesn't affect our daily lives much.
Why not?
The sense of smell is very important.
If you can't smell,
you won't know how fragrant the food is.
You can't also smell
perfume, fragrances,
or body wash.
Right.
And also pheromone.
It's said
everyone carries
a unique scent.
It helps us
identify our loved ones.
Why are you avoiding me?
Did you think I wanted to kiss you?
What are you sniffing for?
Are you a dog?
Don't worry.
I promised your mom
I'd behave.
Regardless of the type of disability,
disabled people
can never fully enjoy the world.
This is the purpose of my job.
I went to Italy before.
In Naples,
there's Braille on the railing.
It says,
"You're facing the ocean.
There are houses around you.
On the road,
flowers are in full bloom."
It helps blind people know
the scene they are visiting.
What a romantic place.
Did you go there with Zhang Qingya?
Are you jealous?
It was a business trip.
Nothing happened between us.
Nothing happened?
Then why didn't you file a lawsuit
when she slandered you?
I notice
you hold grudges more than I do.
Zhang Qingya
is my senior.
She helped me a lot
and guided me into this industry
when I was in college.
She went with me to every competition
and looked after me like a big sister.
I'm not a cooperative person,
so she was always torn
between me and the clients.
However, I never expected things
to turn out this way,
and I don't want to argue over it.
It's seven figures we're talking about.
You let it go that easily.
You're too soft-hearted.
No wonder she bullies you.
It's fine that they bully me,
but they can't bully you.
Boya is your client.
You have a lot of flaws
when dealing with people,
careless,
and easily riled up.
That's why it's easy
for her to target you.
Who has a lot of flaws?
I do.
You asked me that question
back at your place.
I wasn't sober enough
to react.
Now I want to answer you properly...
Wait.
Don't you say something tacky.
I don't want to hear it.
I want to tell you
I love you.
The door is unlocked.
I'm home, Mom.
You're back.
You look tired.
Come here.
Why haven't you slept yet?
What are you writing?
I'm waiting for you
and doing bookkeeping.
There's no need to jot down
your grocery expenses.
I got promoted.
I can pay for anything
you buy from now on.
Really?
You're such a nice girl.
I have something to tell you.
Sure.
If you're not busy with your work,
take a few days off.
Let's go back to our hometown.
Why?
I want to sign the house over to you,
so I won't have any worries.
What do you mean?
Why do you want to transfer
the house to me
all of a sudden?
You've grown up.
Aren't you worried?
Liang Daiwen is back now.
If I sign the house over to you,
it's considered
your premarital property.
Owning a house
gives you confidence
and courage.
You'll have nothing to worry about
even if anything happens to you.
I never said I wanted
to get married, Mom.
Don't try to brush me off with that.
Hurry up and tell me. What's it?
You're getting sharper now.
You can see through me.
If you don't tell me the truth,
I won't go back with you.
All right.
Well,
I'm getting married to Mr. He.
What?
Seriously?
Yes.
After I sign the house over to you,
I'll be on my own.
Anything wrong with that?
I knew something had happened.
You're so anxious to transfer the house
so it won't delay your wedding.
So, do you agree?
Of course I do. I couldn't agree more.
Mr. He is a good man.
I'll take leave tomorrow.
Very good.
Yes!
Now go wash up.
All right.
That's wonderful.
I think I'm pretty
and I usually
dress up a lot.
People around me
gave me a nickname.
It's called
"Gorgeous-Wicked Lady".
I really liked it.
Only then
(My Request)
(Jacqueline approved)
did I realize that...
Yes!
Why are you so happy?
You should be sitting in the audience.
What are you doing here?
I can't be far away from you.
I get anxious.
Too bad,
I just got my leave approved.
I'm taking my mom back
to the northeast tomorrow.
Enjoy the anxiety yourself.
Take me with you.
We're back for some serious business.
Why should I take you?
I can
help you out.
We can manage.
Honestly,
I went to a boarding school in Donghai
when I was in junior high.
It's been many years
since I last went back to the northeast.
My hometown...
Liang Daiwen,
drop your act.
You just went back from Dalian.
Don't call my mom.
No.
Very well.
You'd better keep your word.
Are you there, Mdm. Wang?
What are you doing?
Who's calling me?
Mdm. Wang,
I'm Liang.
Gu Yi said you're going back
to your hometown tomorrow.
Can I tag along?
Sure.
Mom.
It's fine.
If she doesn't want to take you, I will.
See you tomorrow, Mdm. Wang.
All right.
We've arrived.
Come.
Nephew-in-law!
Here you go.
Aunt,
what is this?
You look like a fan girl at the airport.
Look at him.
Tall and handsome.
Perfect for my nephew-in-law.
Who said he's your nephew-in-law?
I did.
Why? Is he not good enough for you?
I am.
Shut up.
You shut up, too.
Let's take a photo.
Look at me.
Wait.
What's wrong with you?
My bad.
Are you guys ready?
One, two, three.
Cheese.
Come.
♪My palm lines are learning to imitate♪
♪My eyes shine with thrilling starlight♪
♪As I step into the whirlwind
of this brand-new world♪
♪A touch to this face
makes my heart flutter♪
♪How can I escape♪
♪From these sparks of destined love?♪
♪The mist looms over the streets♪
♪Many mysteries are hidden♪
♪The stars will guide me♪
♪Deep within the noisy crowd♪
♪There is a light♪
♪Illuminating me in the darkness♪
♪It should be you♪
♪Nobody else but you♪
♪A bond formed when we first met♪
♪Will lead us into a new journey♪
♪You should be my star♪
♪The moment you cross the sky♪
♪A colorful story is lit♪
♪The wind carries my wish across,
under the gaze of starry skies♪
♪With the clues in the script of destiny♪
♪We explore the path toward happiness♪
♪In courage and perseverance♪
♪All emotions will eventually♪
♪Find the right colors♪
♪'Cause I'll always be with you♪
♪The mist looms over the streets♪
♪Many mysteries are hidden♪
♪The stars will guide me♪
♪Deep within the noisy crowd♪
♪There is a light♪
♪Illuminating me in the darkness♪
♪It should be you♪
♪Nobody else but you♪
♪A bond formed when we first met♪
♪Will lead us into a new journey♪
♪You should be my star♪
♪The moment you cross the sky♪
♪A colorful story is lit♪
♪The wind carries my wish across,
under the gaze of starry skies♪