TONGYEONG OFFICIALS
SPONSORING HOUSE OF LOVE
Do twins really have telepathy?
The more items we share,
the more frequently
I ask myself that in the mirror.
"Eun-bi, what are you wearing today?
What kind of music are you listening to?"
SONG MI-GYEONG
TO: EUN-BI
"I was at the department store
shopping for my daughter
and thought of you,
and bought one for you, too.
From Song Mi-gyeong."
-What do you think?
-It's pretty.
I had the same dream again...
about the day
I first met Mom when I was five.
12 YEARS AGO
SOMANG ORPHANAGE
It was the third day
after returning to the orphanage.
I was hurt from having
my adoption dissolved.
It was then that an angelic lady
came and spoke to me.
Hi.
Don't you remember me?
You were in House of Love in Tongyeong.
I saw you a few times there.
You have gotten prettier.
What?
Her adoption was dissolved?
Yes.
Eun-byeol came back three days ago,
and hasn't said a word since.
Poor thing.
Eun-byeol.
Do you want to go home with me?
Her embrace was so warm
that I couldn't tell her that
the child she met
at the House of Love in Tongyeong
wasn't me.
It was my twin sister, Eun-bi.
I couldn't tell her that I was never
at House of Love.
I didn't want to tell her.
If I had known then that
I had a twin sister
and that it was her that Mom had first met
Eun-byeol...
Would I have been able to be honest?
She forgot her phone again.
5 MISSED CALLS
CHA SONG-JU
FROM LEE EUN-BI
Please forgive me for leaving a letter
instead of telling you in person.
I am...
Lee Eun-bi, and I grew up
in House of Love in Tongyeong.
There must have been a mistake
when I was rescued
because we look alike.
Thank you for all
the warm memories, and...
I'm sorry.
HOSPITAL
I was admitted here about a month ago.
Can you check if someone else
came in on the same day?
What is the person's name?
Ko...
I mean, Lee Eun-bi.
LEE EUN-BI
There was no one by that name.
I see.
Yes, that's correct.
Was someone else rescued along with me?
No one was saved,
but a body was found
at the same place a few days ago.
A body?
THE LATE LEE EUN-BI
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Sir.
Do you know
that Tae-gwang's birthday is coming up?
What should we do?
Tell him to pick a gift he wants.
Should I prepare a birthday dinner?
I'll let you know
after I check my schedule.
Eun-byeol isn't here yet?
Did anyone hear from her?
I-an.
Did you not get a call from her?
No.
How far did we get last time?
HOUSE OF LOVE
Hello.
I'm Song Mi-gyeong from Seoul.
I see, but what brings you
all the way from...
Song Mi-gyeong...
Oh, my.
You came to see Eun-bi, didn't you?
How did you know?
Eun-bi was so happy
every time you sent her a package.
How could I not know?
Packages?
This is all she left behind.
I kept telling myself
I need to get rid of them,
but I could never get myself to do it,
so I kept them.
Leave things behind?
What do you mean by that?
Oh, my.
Didn't you come
because you heard that Eun-bi died?
What?
That poor thing was bullied...
by the kids at school.
And then she was framed...
and was expelled.
It must have been too much to bear.
I'm to blame.
I'm supposed to be her substitute mom...
but I knew nothing until
after she decided to take her life.
May I look inside?
Yes, of course.
LEE EUN-BI
SONG MI-GYEONG
TO: EUN-BI
Where...
Where is she now?
THE LATE LEE EUN-BI
Eun-byeol.
Where were you?
I looked all over for you.
You are...
You are Eun-byeol, right?
This.
I tied this around your neck
when you left for the trip.
Try to remember.
You had it with you at the hospital.
Please.
Please try to remember.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what happened.
But I think my sister saved me, and...
I'm sorry.
Stop teasing your mom.
That's not true, Eun-byeol.
It's not true, right?
Eun-byeol.
It isn't true.
I'm sorry.
You brat.
Why are you upsetting me so much?
You're making me go crazy.
It isn't true! Why are you doing this?
No.
My Eun-byeol is alive.
My Eun-byeol didn't die.
She didn't die.
No.
My Eun-byeol...
My Eun-byeol is alive.
-Yes.
-Hello.
I had to spend some money recently.
I get paid in a few days.
Give me a call then.
I haven't been in an accident
over the past 12 years.
I won't get into an accident. Okay.
My precious 1.2 million won...
No one knows what will happen.
No one knows they will be in an accident.
Do you want me to lend you some money?
That smell.
You've been smoking...
Tae-gwang.
Don't worry.
"Maintain a safe distance" is my motto.
This not only goes for the distance
between cars,
but also between teacher and student.
Okay?
What is he saying?
Take your math notebook.
My mom wants you to take a level test.
What? Well...
What's wrong?
You've been waiting for a while.
My parents said the tuition
was burdensome.
Never mind. I'll be there.
Are many kids being tested?
I think it's just you and Si-jin.
"Lee Si-jin?"
What about me?
Your mom didn't tell you?
I heard you wanted to join
our study group.
I guess the cut-off
isn't that high after all.
There isn't much to prepare.
Mom, I can't believe you!
They know I'm going to fail.
They're only trying to look generous.
Why else?
Because you've been bribing them!
You and Min-jun's mom being close
won't make me turn into Min-jun.
Being with them
won't make my grades go up.
Forget it.
I'm going to hang up.
Why are you so down this morning?
My mom is hanging out
with some bad friends.
The top star Song Hui-yeong
has announced that
she will be getting married a third time.
Her fiancé is a businessman
who is six years younger.
They plan to keep the wedding private
since her fiancé is not a public figure.
We wish them a happy marriage.
Oh...
Did you just get here?
Do you want to eat anything
special tomorrow?
No. Everything you make tastes good.
Wow. Balloons.
Wow.
You're so lucky.
You get to have a birthday party
and see Mommy too.
Yes.
That must be your mommy.
-Excuse me.
-Yes?
Don't tell her that I'm here, okay?
I want to surprise Mommy,
so it's a secret.
Okay, it's a secret.
Did the shoot go well?
You know already.
Did you think I wouldn't know
that you had people tailing me all month?
These are divorce papers.
Send them to me after you sign them.
What are you doing?
You didn't marry me for love anyway.
How we met each other,
how that led to our marriage,
and Tae-gwang being born
were all mistakes, weren't they?
That's why I'm accepting...
my punishment.
Tae-gwang and I are a punishment to you?
Tae-gwang.
You poor thing.
Eating all alone even on your birthday...
I don't care about that.
What's wrong?
Have some while it's still warm.
I don't really like it.
Sure.
Seaweed soup isn't
for the person celebrating his birthday.
It's actually meant for the mom
who gave birth that day...
The director was upset
that he couldn't eat with you.
He said to pick out a really nice gift.
Sure. I will.
Thank you.
Stop!
What is it? Is it okay now?
The girl over there.
Isn't she really pretty?
Shit.
Ouch, that hurt!
Hey, Tae-gwang.
Are you okay?
No.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim.
It's not like you to rear-end people.
You need to always maintain
a safe distance
with the cars in front and behind you.
Between teacher and student as well.
You should know better.
Oh, my.
That will be pretty expensive.
I'll have to call the insurance company.
Sir, your car insurance
expired as of May 3.
You!
You'll call the insurance company, right?
I guess so.
HOUSE OF LOVE
I heard you worked multiple part-time jobs
to support the other kids.
It was okay.
It's what I wanted to do.
The things they did to you
even when you were doing your best
to be strong without parents were...
Those wicked things.
You had no one on your side.
Life must have been so hard
for you to bear.
Enough for you to decide on
doing something so horrible.
Call me at any time
if you ever need anything.
I will.
Thank you for everything.
And...
it wasn't intentional.
But I'm sorry.
Because of me...
Goodbye.
I guess
I was a happy kid.
Hi, Mom.
Mom.
I don't want to sleep alone.
I like your scent, Mom.
I still feel like I'm dreaming.
Thank you for coming back to me,
my precious daughter.
Mom.
Yes.
Mom...
Why do I still feel like
you're my daughter?
It's so hard to believe what is happening.
Maybe it's because I'm in denial.
But to me,
you're still like my Eun-byeol.
Do you want to erase
all your memories of this place
and live with me again?
If I let you go too,
I don't know how I'll go on.
I don't think I can do it.
Can't you just...
live as Eun-byeol for me?
That's crazy.
How...
How could I?
Just like when we didn't know anything,
let's just...
Let's just live together, you and me,
and be there for each other.
The May competition applications
are due tomorrow.
It's the national team in Seoul,
so you know how important it is.
You know only two
can compete per category, right?
-Yes, Sir.
-And...
Han I-an is doing
the 100, 200, and 400m freestyle,
so the rest of you
choose three categories each.
-Yes, Sir.
What was that?
Hey!
You better prepare yourselves, got it?
-Yes, Sir.
That's all.
-Thank you.
Hey.
They give you the best
and tell us to pick the leftovers.
Don't be like that.
It's because it comes to him easily that
he keeps fooling around at competitions.
What? Do you want to fight again?
I'm sorry.
It will never happen again.
That's cold.
Wake up.
Are you taking after Eun-byeol?
I want to show you something.
Ta-da.
They're picking a school uniform model.
I'm going to apply.
If I make it,
I'll take you out to celebrate.
I hope I catch someone's eye
and make my debut.
SCHOOL UNIFORM MODEL APPLICATION
You want to become a celebrity that badly?
Yes.
I'm jealous.
Really?
I have another application. Want it?
Not that.
You're lucky you have something
you want to do.
It's only good if I make it.
That you can worry about later.
Why do I have millions of things
I don't want to do,
but not a single thing that I want to do?
I don't know what I live for.
Gosh.
MEN'S LOCKER ROOM
-You're leaving already?
-Yes.
No, don't. Stop it.
-Why not? Give it to me.
-You punk.
Your body is your biggest asset.
Don't waste energy doing this.
This is all exercise too.
You'll hurt your shoulder.
-I'm fine.
-Geez.
-Dad.
-What?
It's tough, isn't it?
Hang in there. I'll try hard--
Nonsense.
You think I would live off of my kid
and live in luxury?
You know that's not what I meant.
Look at this.
Oil stains don't come off easily.
Being in the water is what you're best at,
so focus on that only.
You know what keeps me going, don't you?
Yes.
Good. I'll see you later.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Don't skip your meals.
I won't. The same goes for you.
Go on.
I'll go in after I park.
What are you doing when you should be
getting ready for school?
I'll go tomorrow.
What are you talking about?
Get ready.
You don't seem well, ma'am.
Why are you speaking so formally?
Nothing has changed.
Just be how you have been.
-Please eat.
-Leave it.
I'll eat after I drop you off.
After I see you eat,
I'll take the bus, ma'am.
Again.
"I'll take the bus, Mom."
Okay.
Mom.
Good.
Shall I give it a taste, then?
It looks good.
My daughter is a good cook.
Will you be okay to take the bus?
You aren't familiar with this place yet.
I have taken it with my friends
here and there.
So, I'll be fine,
Mom.
Okay then.
I'm going to be late.
KO EUN-BYEOL
Eun-byeol.
May I really live as Ko Eun-byeol?
I'll always believe that you're with me.
I'll always work hard
not to disgrace your name.
Thank you.
You were absent. Were you sick?
No!
Then? You skipped school?
Yes!
Are you really Ko Eun-byeol?
Eun-byeol.
Aren't you going to reply?
Well?
No?
Lend me your world history notes.
I wondered why you were absent.
Thanks.
Eun-byeol, lend me your scissors.
Oh, wow.
Does your handwriting change
if you have amnesia?
-Really?
-Yes, look.
-It's different, right?
-That's amazing.
What's so strange about it?
Wait.
Look at this.
This is a letter that you wrote me before.
It's totally different, right?
Isn't it amazing?
Yes.
You're right.
In the movies,
even if they lose their memory,
the body still remembers things.
For example, doing sports,
and playing musical instruments.
You're right.
Hey, I-an.
If you got amnesia, do you think
you'll forget how to swim? No, right?
Well, who knows if I'll forget
how to swim?
I'll do this later.
Where are you going?
I'm going to get some medicine
from the nurse's office.
I have a headache.
Tae-gwang, the bell rang. Get to class.
Please.
I was just in a car accident.
Then you should go to the hospital.
It isn't that bad.
I'll be fine in...
two hours.
Goodness.
I'm going to the administration office,
so stay quiet.
Okay.
THE TOP STAR, SONG HUI-YEONG,
ANNOUNCES HER THIRD WEDDING
Tae-gwang.
I heard you were in an accident.
Did you get hurt?
Don't talk to me. It's bad.
You said before that...
I didn't treat you like a human being
and that we barely spoke.
So, you must not know much about me.
I know one thing.
What?
You have amnesia.
Yes, you're right.
I don't know you and you don't know me.
It's fair.
That's nice.
You like having amnesia?
Want me to tell you a secret too?
Don't believe anything I say.
I'm a total liar.
More than I am?
You know,
my name is...
Ko Eun-byeol.
What the...
Like I expected.
I mean, who wouldn't go crazy
after studying their ass off like you?
I can't lose to you.
You know the top star, Song Hui-yeong?
She's my mom.
Did you call, Sir?
Jun-seok.
Yes, Sir.
I heard Tae-gwang
played a prank on you again.
-Don't worry about the accident.
-No.
I'll take care of it.
If you can't handle Tae-gwang--
I treat him like every other
student in my class.
I know you're very disappointed in me.
I'm not disappointed.
I have no right to feel that way.
Teaching is just like any other job.
When I think about it that way,
it's not so bad after all.
I'll get going now.
Hello.
AT LEAST KEEP THE GOOD MEMORIES, WILL YOU?
JEONG SU-IN
You came over often
when you were in grade school.
Don't you remember me?
I'm Su-in's mom.
"Jeong Su-in"?
What?
Nothing. I just got a strange text.
Mr. Kim,
is there a student named Jeong Su-in
in our school?
I don't know.
There are too many students
for me to know all their names.
Awesome.
Song Hui-yeong is our director's ex-wife?
Poor Director Kong.
He's still alone
but she's getting married a third time.
I'm sure he has a girlfriend too.
Someone super young.
You should date him, punk.
My mom said she heard from someone
that this woman is a pro
at marrying rich men
and collecting huge alimony.
I heard our gym shrank to half its size
to pay off Song Hui-yeong.
You're annoyingly loud.
What the heck?
No.
You asshole, I warned you.
Darn it.
You have lost your mind, haven't you?
Stop them! Tae-gwang is going to die!
If I try to stop them,
I'll be the dead one.
Hey, Tae-gwang. What's wrong with you?
I'll get a teacher.
Sir, you have to come quick.
Tae-gwang and Gi-tae are fighting.
What?
Those punks.
-Hey!
What's so funny?
Hey!
Tae-gwang...
-Tae-gwang, stop.
-Let go!
-Eun-byeol!
-Eun-byeol, are you okay?
-Stop!
-Move it!
-Did you get hurt?
-Are you okay?
-You might end up killing him!
-Just leave me.
Stop it, you punks!
Eun-byeol got hurt!
What's your problem?
What's going on here?
Kong Tae-gwang. Kwon Gi-tae.
Come with me.
Eun-byeol, are you okay?
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're lucky you didn't get hurt more.
I know. How could you step in
when they're fighting?
The old Eun-byeol would have
complained of the noise
and gone to the library.
Hey, Eun-byeol.
I was waiting to tell you
once you got your memory back
but you have been acting strange
since the school trip.
What did I do?
You fought with some guy
at the resort where we were staying,
and had a wound on your neck, too.
A wound?
The wound healed. It looked pretty bad.
Right, that was from the trip.
You wouldn't talk to us
and were troubled by something.
There were so many things.
But what guy are you talking about?
Who was it?
It was too dark, so I couldn't see.
He was very tall.
Was it I-an?
I-an wasn't there.
Really?
No one saw him?
No.
He was at a competition the entire time.
I spoke to him on the phone, too.
Hey, Eun-byeol.
Are you okay?
I am not hurt much.
Don't do that again, okay?
You said you stopped by
during the school trip, right?
Did you see me?
Right. You couldn't come on the trip
because of your competition.
How would you know?
I did go. Briefly, at night.
No one else knew that.
Of course not.
I went there quietly to only see
the person I wanted to see.
Did you see me or not?
I didn't.
Song-ju and Si-jin said
they saw me fighting
with some guy at the resort.
So bad that I had a wound on my neck.
Hey, that was--
Who was it?
Do you have any idea?
I don't know.
Quit school and prepare
to go abroad for your studies.
Why?
Sending me to a mental institute
for a month or two didn't suffice?
I think the best way is for us
not to see each other.
That's right.
Now you show your true colors.
Treatment, my ass.
All along, you just wanted to get me
out of your sight.
You know...
what day it is today, don't you?
I don't need a gift.
Why don't we have a family dinner?
It's been ten years.
We can congratulate Mom
on her third marriage too.
You're becoming more and more...
like your mom.
You can't express yourself
rationally or normally.
I wonder.
Do I take after her because I'm her son?
Or maybe everyone
who lives with you turns out that way?
Pathetic fool.
How long will you keep
throwing your tantrums?
If you can't handle it, just leave.
No.
You said you're being punished.
You said giving birth to me was your sin.
Then keep being punished!
If I die, that will fix it!
How dare you say that to your father?
Think about it.
For a child
to turn out like this,
think about the things
he must have seen or heard.
I'll regret it. I won't regret it.
I'll regret it.
HIGH SCHOOL, MALE 400M SWIMMING
I won't regret it.
I'll regret it.
Eun-byeol, I need to tell you something.
Come out for a bit.
HAN I-AN
What are you doing here?
What's it to you?
Hey.
Why did you have to butt in?
Is your arm okay?
I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
Are you indirectly implying that you're
not okay and want me to worry about it?
You said everything you say is a lie.
Think whatever you want.
Hey.
I really...
want to be alone today.
Did I say anything?
You're so dense!
Put your foot on it.
One, two, three.
-Like this?
-Okay, now go forward.
It's hard.
-I'm letting go.
-No.
-I'm letting go!
-Don't!
Hey...
HIGH SCHOOL, MALE 400M SWIMMING
Cha Song-ju! Massage my shoulders.
Quiet!
Everyone sit down!
We have a new transfer student.
Shut up.
Everything will be new to her,
so help her out until she adjusts well.
Come in.
Introduce yourself.
I came from Tongyeong's
Noori Girls' High School.
I'm Kang So-yeong.
-Tongyeong.
-We were there.
-The Tongyeong where Mt. Mireuksan is?
-We went there.
I hope we can get along.
It's nice to meet...