Are you really Yu?
I once told a girl
that I would make her the happiest person in the world.
Until this vow is fulfilled,
I cannot show her my true face.
This is for you.
What is this?
Dandian is my most precious thing.
I have been hiding it
so that the Gu family wouldn't find it.
Then why did you give it to me?
Because right now, you are the most precious to me.
What's wrong?
You seem preoccupied.
Yun, I, Gu Chengyu, swear to heaven
that one day you will become the happiest person in the world.
But you don't need to worry.
This vow will be fulfilled soon.
About those childhood memories,
only Ayu and I know.
If he really is Ayu,
why does he feel so unfamiliar to me?
This is a forbidden area.
Who let you in?
I let you go,
not to give you freedom.
If you dare approach this Yuyun tree again,
you will die.
Yuyun Tree.
How could he know about the Yuyun Tree?
I thought of a name for it.
Let's call it the Yuyun Tree.
Yu represents you, and Yun represents me.
The Yuyun Tree is a secret between Gu Chengyu and me.
How could Mo Yu know about it?
Could he be...
But Su Cheng has the jade pendant,
and knows about our childhood.
There can't possibly be two Gu Chengyus in this world.
There must be a conspiracy.
Mo Yu. Su Cheng.
The mysterious person.
What is the relationship between them?
I want revenge.
I want to kill Gu Licheng and his wife right now.
Didn't I tell you to wait?
Now is not the time.
I'm just informing you.
If you want the Minister of Revenue,
you only have one chance.
Whether you can seize it
is up to you.
Since you insist,
I'll help you once.
But this plan
requires using someone.
Why are you here?
A letter of divorce.
I know you don't want to marry me,
but I have a favor to ask now.
If you are willing to help me,
after it's done,
I will give you complete freedom.
What exactly do you want me to help you with?
To deal with Gu Licheng and his wife.
You mean you want them to compete fairly?
Exactly.
Although Gu Licheng and Su Cheng are both Vice Ministers of Revenue,
there is only one person in charge of the rock oil trade between our countries.
That is the Minister of Revenue.
Instead of letting the Emperor of Great Jin decide,
it's better for us to take the initiative.
But in a fair competition,
how can we have the initiative?
Think about it, Mother.
If we propose a candidate directly,
the Emperor of Great Jin will definitely refuse.
But if we suggest a fair competition,
the Emperor will have nothing to say.
No matter who wins between the two of them,
they will be grateful for your promotion, Mother.
In the future,
as long as we win them over,
we can hold more initiative in the trade.
Alright. I'll go talk to the Emperor of Great Jin now.
But my dear,
why are you suddenly so interested in state affairs?
Although I married into Great Jin,
I will always be the Princess of Beidi.
Naturally, I want to fight for more benefits for our country and for you, Mother.
I have summoned you here today
because His Majesty of Beidi and I have agreed
that you two will compete fairly
for the position of Minister of Revenue,
to be responsible for the trade between our two nations.
I obey your command.
However, I believe that
since you will be responsible for bilateral trade,
apart from having solid professional skills and being meticulous,
you also need to be tactful
to win the favor of both nations.
Therefore, by organizing the alliance banquet,
you two will compete fairly.
Whoever organizes it better
will become the Minister of Revenue.
Your Majesty of Northern Di, what do you think?
Very well. It is decided then.
Mo Yu,
I did what you asked me to do.
Even though I do not know what you want to do,
I also have my own backup plan.
I heard you still have not gained Mo Yu's trust.
Mo Yu is suspicious by nature,
temperamental,
and there are villains getting in the way.
No need to explain.
I only want results.
I still need his prestige to intimidate enemy countries.
He thinks he holds the power of both the military and finance.
But I placed the two of you by his side
just to monitor his every move.
If he has any intentions of rebellion,
we must strike first
and get rid of him.
Your Majesty is wise.
Step forward, my minister.
My minister,
this last chance,
it is truly for you
that I lowered its difficulty to the minimum.
If you cannot even organize a small banquet well,
then I will have to support Su Cheng and give up on you.
I will definitely do my best.
Bo Baorui
Zhong Xiaqiang
Peng Yin
Zijian Qiangqipin Peng Yin
Zijian Qiangqipin
Quan Xuhang
Quan Yulong
Licheng Lefei
Yunlong Yinyu Jiaguangjing
Luoxiao Conglin Xunbo