I'm not defending Xiao Man. I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
On the Dragon Boat Festival,
I went to deliver rice dumplings to Rumeng.
I heard a man talking through the door.
That man
was the one who killed Like A Dream.
What time did you go there?
At 9:15 p.m., I heard you were there. I heard you.
I heard someone inside.
I went back.
It matches the time of the crime.
Why didn't you tell me
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You know my relationship with Ru Meng.
I'm afraid I can't explain it and get myself into trouble.
I was hesitating for a while.
I was going to tell you
I didn't expect you to leave Mengzhou.
That man's voice
his voice?
It's been too long I can't remember
Anyway, he's a young man.
Xiao Man must be taking the blame for him.
Don't worry.
I will
to persuade Xiaoman to find out the truth.
Did they give you a hard time?
You were unhappy when you were young.
Once you eat this candy, you...
What are you doing here?
Man Man, why bother?
You're a murderer for a man.
What are you talking about?
I know you're not the murderer.
As long as you tell me who the murderer is,
I'll ask Xingyuan
to talk to Director Jiang.
Let you go.
Don't beg her. I'm the murderer. I'm the murderer. I'm the murderer.
I'm the murderer!
Let me out!
I'll kill her first.
You...
Your mother's death...
is my fault.
It has nothing to do with others.
You can't get into trouble.
Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out of here!
Don't worry.
Give me more time.
I can convince her.
By the way,
I'm here
to tell you.
I hope everyone is here because
a week before Master Fang passed away,
he made a will
and asked me to verify it.
This is it.
The will is as follows.
I'm willing to sell 40 stores under my name
20 properties
and all cash investments
to
to Lin Xingyuan.
How could it be Dr. Lin?
Don't you dote on him the most?
Why didn't you give it to him?
Young Master is his son.
He didn't give it to me.
Did Master and Dr. Lin
have an affair?
That's not right.
Didn't you say Dr. Lin
why my father
left all his inheritance to Lin Xingyuan?
Because she’s Mr. Fang’s daughter.
From now on,
you are the master of the Fang family.
the richest man in Rong City.
I don't care.
He abandoned me and my mother.
and made us suffer so much.
Do you think this can make up for it?
You misunderstood your father.
He never abandoned you and your daughter.
Everything
is fate.
Your father and your mother loved each other.
and engaged in private.
This is my first time drawing eyebrows.
I'm not good at it.
I'll practice hard from now on.
Your eyebrows
looks good.
Who knows?
the good scenery didn't last long.
The elders of the Fang family thought your mother was from a lowly background.
and arranged a marriage for your father.
It was Madam Fang.
Madam Fang is so obsessed with your father.
She even poisoned your father
with Fang Yilin.
Your father is a stubborn man.
He would rather die than marry your mother.
Who wants to marry you on the wedding night?
Madam Fang.
She switched the beam
to marry your mother.
Your mother was disheartened
and left Mengzhou.
I found you.
All these years,
your mother has been unwilling to tell your father.
She was in Mengzhou.
A month ago,
your father came here
Your father told your mother
Madam Fang died of illness many years ago.
Now there's no obstacle
between them.
Your father
wanted to make up for his regret.
and marry your mother.
I didn't agree.
But your mother didn't listen to me.
In the end,
No wonder he cried so sadly at my mother's funeral.
Then...
why didn't you tell me back then?
Your father was worried about you.
Dangerous?
I heard him mention it.
I don't know the details.
Dr. Lin, don't worry.
As long as I'm here, no one will bully you.
Master Fang.
I don't need your protection.
The last thing I said to him
was
I don't need him.
Your father won't care.
He just wants you to be fine.
He left all his inheritance to me.
And the murderer kept framing me.
and tried to kill me.
Obviously,
his goal is this inheritance.
And the beneficiary of the inheritance was...
So,
the murderer is Mr. Fang,
or Director Jiang.
What should we do next?
what are you going to do?
Roasted duck.
Here you go. Here you go.
Roast chicken.
These are all your favorite dishes.
Don't waste your energy.
In my heart,
you can only get three words.
Go to hell!
Do you think I won't know
if you don't tell me?
The murderer is in Fang Mansion.
and the beneficiary of his inheritance.
I found evidence of his murder.
For Uncle’s sake,
as long as you can testify against him,
I'll let you go.
You have no evidence.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have come to me.
Believe it or not, it's up to you.
I'll give you half a day.
Think about it.