[Adapted from Wanzhi's
"Perfect and Casual"]
[Perfect and Casual]
[Episode 22]
And then I said to Mr. Zhang
that I love him.
And then?
Then Mr. Zhang
said he loved me too.
And?
And...
And we went to sleep.
Mr. Zhang is really quiet inside.
I think
he doesn't bother to think about these.
There’re still errors in the calculation
in the mathematical samples.
This is really urgent.
Okay, okay, I got it.
I see.
Take a break.
Everybody, take a break
and drink coffee.
Thanks, Miss. Lin.
You're welcome.
Take a break
and have a cup of coffee.
Okay, thank you.
Why is Professor Zhang's coffee
different from ours?
Professor Zhang is picky
and has many requirements.
You know about his habit.
His coffee must be made specially.
Come on, enjoy coffee.
Thank you.
Okay.
It's hot.
All right.
Let's call it a day.
You should sort out all the files later
and send me.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work.
Okay. It's okay!
Remember to give it to me again
when finish calculating.
Okay.
Thank .
I'll go first.
Okay.
We're leaving first.
You should be tired, too.
Take a rest.
I'm leaving.
Si Nian.
I want to talk to you.
Grandpa.
Yun Shu.
It's alright.
When one gets old,
he'd always encounter many accidents.
Don't worry about it.
Dr. Zhang,
what's wrong with grandpa?
Is it serious?
No big deal.
Spend more time with him.
Okay, thanks for your hard work.
Grandpa.
Have a good rest.
I'll always be with you.
Where's Si Nian?
Si Nian went to retreat because of work.
Chu Chu.
I'm married now
and I have my wife.
So your questions
for Yun Shu
were quite offensive.
But you’re in a contractual relationship.
And you did this for grandpa...
But
we changed contractual relationship
to a real marriage.
And I really love her.
You used to
focus on data only.
You only believed data
and the future inferred by the data.
Then can you tell me
if you're sure enough
to always be happy with Yun Shu?
From what I know about you,
the gap between you two
will lead to a long running-in period
for your love and marriage.
You're aware of this, aren’t you?
But these factors
aren't what both of us
to prove.
Grandpa, wait a minute.
It's Si Nian.
Yun Shu, did you just call me?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Nothing important.
I was in the studio just now.
I'm a little busy.
I'm hanging up.
Grandpa.
Why don't you let me tell Si Nian?
No big deal.
Don't disturb Si Nian.
He needs to work.
And
it's enough for
you are here with grandpa.
Is it really okay?
Graduate defence season
is coming soon.
Why did he suddenly go to retreat?
Actually, I don't know either.
Si Nian said
the investigation time report of
Lin Chu Chu's company was advanced.
So
maybe they're
making every endeavour during retreat.
They just work.
Si Nian and Lin Chu Chu
are working together.
You're worried about that, right?
I believe him.
And
what is likely to happen between them
should have happened a long time ago.
Yun Shu, you're smart and generous.
In fact, you don't have to worry.
Because they're so much alike.
They're like two parallel lines
and never intersect with each other.
They're elites
with common interests
and they've known
each other for a long time,
but if they're together,
they can only
become like-minded friends.
Grandpa.
You’re really good at judging people.
Of course!
The first time I saw you,
I knew
Si Nian and you
were a perfect match.
Really?
When did Grandpa ever lie to you?
Yun Shu.
Lin Nuo.
You're off work?
Gao Zhi Yi told you to here?
Didn't she tell you
to come to complain?
You're overthinking.
I came to see grandpa today.
Grandpa, he is in hospital again?
Is he alright?
I hope so.
Lin Nuo.
You forgot your mobile phone.
I'm so dumb.
Thank you.
Bye.
Lin Nuo,
is there anything
or anybody
that distracted you?
Alright!
Yi Yi told you
I have a new love, didn't she?
Isn't it true?
Of course not.
My breakup with Yi Yi
is totally our own problem.
If you two are doing it because
of Gu Xiao,
you're overthinking.
Our breakup
has nothing to do with
anybody. You know that?
You know me.
I never thought of
breaking up with Yi Yi.
Then why do you two become like this?
I think,
in our relationship,
I was too meek.
She and I have never been reciprocal.
Reciprocal?
Lin Nuo, you know.
Yi Yi didn't mean that.
But Yun Shu, we've also known
each other for a long time.
You know
I wasn't like this before.
But since I met Gao Zhi Yi,
I'm completely different from myself.
You know?
When a boy and a girl are together,
they should change for each other,
right?
No, I don't think so.
I think a good romantic relationship
shouldn't be like this.
Even if you like somebody
and change for him,
it should be a happy and relaxing process.
But I'm not happy at all now.
All right,
I think there's
no use going like this for you two.
You should find a chance
to meet with her
and talk with her.
That won't be necessary.
We fight
as we see each other.
Lin Nuo,
can you drive?
I can.
Yun Shu,
didn't you ask me to come and help?
Why did you call him?
I don't know either.
I didn't know you'd come.
Yun Shu, did you do it on purpose?
Come on,
I really have something urgent today
and I need your help.
If they're together...
I don't talk to jerks.
This is weird.
Don't you only love jerks?
Yeah, I used to have "eye problems".
That's terrible. You need a cure then
or you'll be blind.
Okay! Would you please
find a handsome doctor
in your hospital for me
to cure my perennial illness?
No.
The doctors in our hospital
have noble medical ethics
and aren't qualified for you.
Stop.
Stop fighting!
Yun Shu, let me tell you something.
Someone
just likes to covet other
people's boyfriends.
This time
we must return home in triumph.
We must not let people like Lin Chu Chu
get any chance to
interrupt your relationship.
It's not that serious, is it?
Of course it is.
You can ask Lin Nuo.
He has the most say.
Darn.
Nuts.
What?
Yun Shu.
Is this the right way?
Check the navigation.
I've never been there either.
I'm so sorry.
We can't reveal the
privacy of our guests.
How can it be privacy?
I told you he's my husband.
I come here for my husband.
What's wrong with it?
You can call him
and let him pick you up.
If he answers my phone,
why do I bother to ask you for a favour?
I'm really sorry.
I have a photo with him.
Let me show you.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you like this?
I got married after
graduating from college.
I can do nothing but housework.
If my husband is taken away,
what can I live on?
I have to raise two children.
Yi Yi, let's forget about it.
Men nowadays are unreliable.
They hanker after women
or are chased by women.
They don't take the initiative
and don't take responsibility either.
My life is so miserable.
I can't tell them the room number.
They don't take the initiative
and don't take responsibility either.
Personally, I am very sympathetic
to what happened to you.
But the hotel has rules,
so there's nothing we can do.
Yun Shu, what should I do?
My husband is going to be taken away.
When we leave,
you can go to the first
floor of the East Building.
Thank you. That's very kind of you.
Coming.
Let it go.
If you're here to argue with me,
I don't think it's necessary.
Actually,
there're other things I want to ask you.
Yun Shu.
How about you call him again?
Is that Mr. Zhang?
Go! Go! Go!
Si Nian.
I really can't figure out
why you like Yun Shu.
Yun Shu.
Come here.
Come back.
Come here. Come here.
Come over here!
After I came back, I also counted
the times we get along with each other
since I met Yun Shu for the first time
to the building of our
contractual relationship
and to this business trip.
The number of times we get along
with each other during this period
is 821 times.
In the process of contact,
the percentage she showed happiness to me
is 83.33 percent.
12 percent of which
wasn't caused by me.
When she's with me,
she's generally
happy.
I also calculated
my feelings about Yun Shu.
Happiness and joy
account for
73.33 percent.
So the data of the two of
us get along with each other
is quite big
among general couples.
Sorry!
I used
the relevant data in the laboratory
without your permission.
Why are you suddenly so serious
about this kind of thing?
Didn't you tell me this afternoon
that my answer didn't seem to be
out of rigorous professor of mathematics?
I'm...
I'm really hard to imagine
why would you be with a girl
whose personality is
entirely different from you.
As you know,
the reason why I came back this time
was to cure my grandpa.
Grandpa's illness made me
feel so lost.
I've always
hoped everything
can be under control and planned well.
I don't want anything
to go out of control.
Until that day,
a person who had
diametrically opposite character
with me came into my life.
She reconciled
herself to her situation.
She was totally an "almost girl".
She changed me.
At the very beginning,
I didn't admit it.
Until recently I started studying
my relationship with her and I found
she gave me company.
Why did
you help me?
We were all alone at that time.
But I noticed that
you were very much like me.
We had the same life experience
and same character.
Even
the similar future life planning.
So Chu Chu.
I’ve always regarded
you as my best friend.
Am I not excellent or
good enough?
No.
Two people who are too similar
are just like two parallel lines.
It's hard to intersect.
So Chu Chu,
I really hope you can find a man
who complements you
with intersections.
Just like Yun Shu and I do.
Although we have
different starting points
and direction of life,
it's like climbing a mountain.
I’m willing to wait for her
halfway up the mountain.
Take her hand
and to be with her.
I’ve also learned a truth recently.
Enjoying scenery alone
is worse than doing the same
thing with someone you like.
So you never
liked me?
Maybe I didn't
know myself then.
It may be just like that
when I met Yun Shu.
Don't lie if you can't.
Alright,
I get it.
Can I
hug you?
Think of it as the last farewell.
I already have someone I want to hug.
Yun Shu.
Mr. Zhang.
We came with Yun Shu.
Mr. Zhang,
I didn't mean to eavesdrop on you two.
Actually, I was going to...
What else did you want to say just now?
I was just about to say
I went to the hospital this morning
to see grandpa.
What's wrong with grandpa?
Grandpa is in a good state.
That's good.
It's so late. How can we get back?
I...
I hailed a cab.
Don't you have anything to tell me?
Does it work if I say?
Lin Nuo.
You're strange.
It's not like you before.
Maybe
this is the real me.
What do you mean?
Here comes the cab.
Won't you go?
I go alone.
Mister driver,
please drive her to Zheng Ben University.
Okay, no problem.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Surprise!
I flew over when I finished working.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
Tell me about it.
What's going on?
Xi Xi came to see you?
I told her many times
not to tell you.
I can't believe
she didn't listen to me at all.
I'll go to her.
You can't escape.
You have to make it clear to me.
Honey.
Listen.
Don't be angry.
It's you!
What a coincidence!
What? What?
I’m warning you.
Stay away from Yun Lan in the future.
I won't let you go
if you scheme to harm her again.
Hear that?
Yes!
Don't punch me.
[Replay]
I didn't really hit him.
I just scared him.
You are a celebrity.
If it gets worse,
the impact on your career is fatal.
So now you're blaming me.
I'm not blaming you.
I'm worried about you.
It's not worthwhile
for your career to be affected
for such a man.
I
am willing do everything for you
I'll find Han Rong.
Stop!
You can't go to the scum.
Can you stop being wilful?
Yun Lan.
I'll handle this matter myself.
You just stay out of it.
Mr. Zhang.
Grandpa gets better today.
How about you go back first?
I can take care of
grandpa by myself.
Don't worry.
Mr. Kobayashi.
Is it really the Mr. Kobayashi?
Yeah.
He said your painting
style is unique and novel
and different from others.
I have a feeling that
my heart is going to jump out.
And now I think
my life is so glorious.
I never thought
my work would be
evaluated by my idol one day.
Don't get carried away.
I haven't finished speaking yet.
Could it be...
But...
Don't be nervous.
In fact,
Mr. Kobayashi's studio
is recruiting new assistants.
He sent you an invitation
by the publishing house.
He wants you to be his new assistant.
Me?
His new assistant?
I’m not free to joke with you.
I'm busy.
I don't want you to go yet.
Then
how long will it take?
A three-year contract period.
That's great.
What's there to hesitate about?
I have to give you a
celebration ceremony.
You have to
send me the serial of next week.
No problem.
Hello, Editor Gao.
Are you free next week?
What's up?
Yun Shu's work
has caught the attention of
the overseas god of cartoonists,
Mr. Kobayashi.
It's also our company's honour.
So
I'm going to hold a celebration for her.
Her work was once
blessed and supported by your talents.
So you must join us.
Okay, I'll definitely go.
May I ask
how long does it take Yun Shu
to go abroad this time?
Three years.
OK, then I'll see you next week.
Okay, thank you.
Lan,
do you think I should go or not?
The reason why you want to go is...
Mr. Kobayashi.
He’s my idol since I was a child.
If I can become his assistant,
I can realize my dream.
The reason why you don't want to go is...
The contract period is three years.
I can't bear to be separated
from Mr. Zhang for so long.
Dream
and love.
They form the most
difficult thing to decide
in life.
You have to figure it out for yourself.
Lan,
if it were you,
how would you choose?
Yun Shu.
My opinion
has no reference value
for you.
Hello, Dr. Zhang.
Academician Zhang's
treatment plan has come out.
Come over if you have time.
Dr. Zhang,
please just tell me the truth.
The cancer cells
have spread to the bones.
Your grandpa has also known about it.
I was going to tell you.
But he didn't agree.
He wants to be with you two.
Aren't there really
any other treatments?
With the current treatment method...
How long can
my grandpa live?
Two months.
Si Nian.
I'm here to see grandpa.
Thank you.
I contacted
Dr. Smith from overseas before.
He’s an authority in
the field of lymphoma.
Today, the overseas
clinic finally gave a reply.
Here's the information. Read it.
Chu Chu,
I would like to thank you
on behalf of grandpa.
It's alright.
But grandpa
needs to go overseas.
Can you do that?
Go... Go overseas?
Of course.
Why don't you discuss it?
I'll come back to see
grandpa in a couple of days.
Okay.
Then I'll go first.
Thank you.
Yun Shu,
I forgot to congratulate you.
I heard
you received
an invitation from Mr. Kobayashi's studio
to be his assistant.
You're going to Kobayashi's studio?