- Anything to report?
- Nothing unusual.
They're all staying put for now,
but we may see them
move in tomorrow.
And Agent Gray?
He's waiting nearby.
Just give me the key.
I'll drive you, sir.
I'm going alone. Keys.
But Chief...
I understand.
The company is expecting me
tomorrow at the earliest.
You've never seen me, alright?
I understand, sir.
(Jang Dong-gun)
(Kim Myung-min)
(Park Hee-soon)
(Lee Jong-suk)
(Directed by Park Hoon-jung)
How was your flight?
Yeah, I know. Economy sucks.
You know what? I tried very hard
to get you a business class,
but there's been cutbacks
in our budget.
Sorry.
You're not gonna order something?
I know this is a shitty
neighborhood, but this restaurant
they make pretty decent steak,
I gotta tell you.
So, where did you come from?
Erbil.
Erbil? Are we talking Iraq?
You know what? You always
struck me like a field guy.
I knew you would come.
You seem so free.
Got nothing to do?
You see, our friends in Beijing...
They agreed to step back
and look the other way,
and the target won't be able to
move until tomorrow.
Yeah, we don't need to rush.
If Beijing is stepping back,
why not just do it yourself?
You see,
the condition of the agreement was
that we would play this quietly.
But, this whole thing might
end up messy and bloody.
Thus, the call for help, again?
Jerk...
Come on. You're my friend.
Just do me this favor,
and I pay you back. I promise!
I always paid you back!
It's very simple.
All you got to do is to escort
the subject out of that building,
and gently put him in the car,
which is parked over there.
That's all.
This one's for you. A little gift.
It's a Tokarev.
No serial.
And here is the key
to that building.
There're 9 guards on the premise,
and we're gonna close down
the surveillance cameras
for 15 minutes.
So that's gotta be
enough time for you.
You try some. It's very good.
Now what the hell
did you do that for?
I wasn't finished!
Enjoy your meal.
Well, I gotta...
I gotta order another one.
(1. Prologue)
Shit...
He's the girl's father.
We think he was beaten to death
as soon as he opened the door.
Her brother.
A regional judo athlete.
Is that all?
Well, Unit Chief... Uh...
Gun...
Isn't this a gunshot wound?
The thing is...
Unit Chief!
You worthless piece of shit.
Report properly.
I'm sorry.
Goddamn bastard...
What did you just say?
You want to let that bastard go?
Director comrade...
Are you serious?
If not, what else can we do?
That's what you come up with,
after seeing the photos?
Oh, shut up.
Look here, Comrade Lee.
Why are you stirring things up
in my division?
What?
You should've stayed in Bureau 35,
or either make this a quiet visit.
Why come here to cause a stink?
What are you implying?
How is my background
relevant to this case?
And I'm causing a stink?
Forget it, here.
Your order.
You and your underlings are
now re-assigned
to a fertilizer plant in Daeryong.
What?
Consider yourself lucky.
Had you not served our country
or the Bureau 35 abandoned you,
it would've been
the concentration camp.
I want no more business with you,
so hand over your ID and gun,
and get out!
(Hurray for the Democratic
People's Republic of North Korea!)
Hey, smile for us.
Don't be so nervous, now.
Wow, good! Very good!
Take a photo of me, too.
Closer.
Please...
...don't kill me...
What did she say?
"Don't kill me."
Gonna talk about that
brother of yours again?
The judo athlete?
He's gonna mess us up, eh?
What could this be?
Give me that.
Your brother didn't put up
much of a fight.
Oh yeah, you got
a 5-year-old brother, right?
We tied him up to the window.
Any other family members
you're curious about?
No-one?
Hey, look.
Let me see.
How is it? Feels nice?
Tell us.
Hold her, hold her down.
(V.I.P.)
What's that by her legs?
Shit, this is not good...
Hold it up and make sure
there's no gap in between.
Yes, sir.
No, not over there!
Send more men here.
Boss, how much higher?
Not there, just send me more.
It's him, isn't it?
Yes.
At least from the way
the victim was tortured
then murdered.
Let's go, we'll be late.
What? You're leaving?
Is there more to see?
Rain's coming, let's hurry.
Dammit, come with me.
We're just going to leave?
Hey, it's raining!
Go get some plastic cover!
Come on! Hurry the hell up!
Watch your feet!
Another female victim of a
serial killing in Seoul.
A 30-year-old woman was found dead
with evidence of sexual violence.
On the victim's chest and stomach
were stabbing wounds...
The victim was strangled to death,
which led the police to conclude
that this case has relevance to
the Southern Seoul serial murders.
Meanwhile, Detective Jo Sung-oh,
Chief of the Task Force,
unable to bear the pressure
of this serial murder case...
Seoul Metro Police stated that
Detective Jo's body was found
in his car, stationed under a hill
just behind his home.
Burned charcoal was discovered
inside the vehicle,
but no will.
Jo's body was moved to a
nearby hospital
after 3 hours of
forensic analysis on site.
The bereaved family will hold
his funeral this afternoon,
and Jo will be rested at a
charnel house near Seoul...
(2. The Suspect)
Shit, the case can't be
any more twisted than this.
Jo, that bastard...
How could he drop everything
and kill himself now?
Damned coward...
You know what this means
for us, don't you?
We're close to being goners.
I think we already are.
You bastard...
Anyway,
I got no one else to replace him.
Even if there was a candidate,
it'll take time to fill him in.
Honestly,
you were the go-to man
on the field before Jo.
Why don't you get your boys
and wrap this up quickly?
I know how you feel about this.
I really do, shit...
It wasn't long ago that we played
dirty to kick you off the force.
Right?
What about my suspension, then?
Revoked?
Must you make me say it?
Of course.
Not gonna make excuses later?
Trust me for once!
You want it in writing?
Just solve the case,
and I'll make sure to
have your records restored
crystal-clear, like how it was
before the suspension.
Solve it by any means necessary?
Yes, but please... Go easy.
I know you go off the books.
If you go out of bounds,
it'll have consequences.
So take it easy, okay?
Then find the bastard that way.
You bastard...
Decide now,
or I'll be late for the funeral.
Yeah, do whatever you please.
Just solve the case.
Understood.
No bruises though, this time.
He's gotta be presentable
to the media!
Don't make him a cripple again
like the other guys!
Chae!
(Jo Sung-oh)
(Fight another day!)
(To: Detective Jo Sung-oh)
What's that?
Sir?
Oh, these are the
tip-offs we received.
Put them here.
We usually check each one, but...
After Det. Jo's suicide,
we didn't get a chance yet.
(Detective Jo Sung-oh)
We got a call from the lab.
The lab?
They got something?
Did we send them a sample?
I did.
A month ago before I got the boot.
Why? Got a problem?
- And?
- They think they found something.
- Come.
- Yes, sir.
Suit up!
This was inside the eggplant
found in the victim #7's vagina.
It was so small that
we overlooked it the first time.
But we found something,
just like you said we would.
Want to take a look?
They're the epithelial cells
under the fingernail,
and they don't match
the victim's DNA.
Okay, so this must be...
We had a match with the other
tissues samples we found on her,
so he's our suspect.
Our key suspect.
"Suspect"? Are you new to this?
It's the perp,
this bastard is the killer.
But not 100%.
- Take care.
- See you.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Match it with all our list
of suspects,
and the ex-cons who used the
same killing methods.
Obtain DNA from all suspects,
anything we can compare to.
- Find them, got it?
- Yes, sir!
You obtain DNA samples
from these guys.
Oh, this? Chief,
we received a few of them already.
When something happens,
we get bogus tips like these.
Our hands will be tied,
if we have to check all of them.
What I mean is...
The bastards at the hospital won't
cooperate since it's illegal...
And you must not know
about these pricks, but you see...
Det. Jo also had to...
So damn yappy.
Shut your hole
and stand up straight.
- At attention.
- Hurts...
You grew a tongue
while I was away.
- Did you forget how I work?
- No, sir.
Should I care
who these pricks are?
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't care who they are,
unless they're the killers.
Got a problem with that?
Of course not, sir.
Right, the hospital?
Of course they won't cooperate.
it's illegal.
But so what?
Will you halt the case
because of that?
No, sir.
Why don't you use
that goddamn excuse?
Say you can't catch the killer
for lack of cooperation.
I'm sorry, sir.
Stop being sorry.
Yes, sir.
You got that?
Yes, boss!
I know how you worked till now,
so take your badges off
if that's all you got.
The only thing that should be
in your head is the killer.
The process means shit.
Focus on catching that bastard
and putting cuffs on him.
Everything else...
...is totally irrelevant to you.
Got that?
Yes, sir.
Yes, boss!
Then move!
Bastards...
With no further
developments on the case,
many citizens are still fearful.
Unable to leave the house freely,
the citizens want the police...
That means shit for us. So?
Is the info solid?
You saw the report yourself.
The police got it right,
it's those dicks.
How old is the intel?
That damned Agent Gray
gave it to us an hour ago.
An hour ago?
That's bullshit.
Only top-ranking officers
can see this report.
Come on now,
this is Seoul.
It's like their home ground.
Good for them.
So what?
Get with it.
Do you even need to ask?
What a moron.
Look.
This can't happen.
These dicks...
...especially that big dick...
He can't be the killer.
When they were
brought here 2 years ago,
I planned it
and you carried it out.
And we both got cushy jobs
because of it.
It's been a month
since we got a new boss.
Promotion announcements
will be made soon.
We backed the wrong horse
and ended up in this shit.
So if we don't stop this,
both of us are out for good.
I told you to go easy
with playing politics.
I knew that old man
wouldn't last long.
Shut up, bastard.
This is a jungle.
Everything is politics.
The weak is torn apart,
if you won't lick ass.
And tell me, who watched
your back until now?
So what, then?
- Bury the whole thing?
- The Yankees won't stay put.
They went apeshit trying to
get those dicks out of the North.
The company will find out,
and there'll be backlash.
We'll settle that later.
Let's locate them first.
If they're desperate,
they'll give us something.
That's our only play right now.
What about their handlers?
Wasn't someone looking after them?
What have they been doing?
I know...
We received orders to
go easy on the dick, and...
From whom?
That bastard Gray?
But that's not all.
He messed up with my agents.
So it's all gone to hell, huh?
Your temper can wait.
Let's get a move on, though.
I sent some agents over there,
we gotta find a way out first.
If we're not careful,
it's a one-way to hell.
Yeah?
The police are on the move.
How?
I'm sure they haven't
got a warrant yet.
Emergency arrest, probably.
Where are you?
We're almost there.
What have you been doing?
What's taking so long?
Taking a trip somewhere?
I'm sorry, sir.
There's a bit of traffic...
Hurry, secure the target first.
You owe me one, okay?
Debt is there to be paid off.
Call me if you need anything,
I'll pay back big time.
Very good.
But this is no easy foe,
will you be okay?
A VIP from North Korea...
With a VIP this size,
the agency won't be too pleased.
We're not in a position to
take their feelings into account.
But my colleague burning charcoals
to death is my business.
if this doesn't work out,
my team'll be next.
But isn't that what
got you reinstated?
Life is full of ironies, no?
He got you
the disciplinary action,
but also gave you a lifeline.
Am I right?
Everything's a blessing
in disguise.
Yes?
Okay, got it.
- It's ready.
- Hold up.
I'll go see to him
and hand him over to you.
You know we're just around for
the show and cake.
Det. Chae.
Good luck!
We arrived here first,
but the police barged in.
So what?
Did you secure the target?
Well...
we haven't exactly
secured the target, but...
Make way!
Don't shove! Let's talk it out.
Out of the way!
Make way!
Kim Gwang-il.
You're under arrest for violating
the National Security Law.
What National Security Law?
Here are your rights.
You've the right to remain silent,
and to consult an attorney.
Anything you say may be...
That'll do.
We'll finish the rest.
How about an intro?
Intelligence? Nice.
He broke
the National Security Law.
He'll need to come with us.
National Security Law?
Right, that.
We're in a bind,
this complicates things.
He's a murder suspect,
serial killing, no less.
You heard of those recent
Southern Seoul killings?
They're his work.
You got evidence?
That should be discussed
with the lawyers.
No need to worry,
we got irrefutable evidence.
Anyway, we arrested him first,
we have the jurisdiction.
We'll aid
your investigation later.
Come on now.
That's not how this works.
See this?
It's a warrant, an arrest warrant.
A warrant issued by the
honorable district judge himself.
You got one too? No?
Then who has the jurisdiction?
Huh?
Why? Wanna bypass the court too?
Come on, boys! Take him away.
- Sure!
- Yes, sir!
Out of the way, make way.
Thank you and take care.
What's this? You said the warrant
was being taken care of!
My contacts at the court
bailed on me.
That's your excuse?
Fine, hold on,
I'm going to get the court to...
That ship has sailed.
The police aren't idiots.
They can reach out to
the media and have a feast.
Come on, this isn't a normal case.
It's a serial killing case.
If this blows up,
it's all game over.
Once Chae Yi-do goes on TV,
we're finished.
Do everything in your power
to stop that, at all cost.
Send a lawyer to Kim and
tell him to stall
the investigation.
And get the security cam feeds
around his home and office
before the cops do.
Right away.
What about Kim's minions?
Have you secured them?
Well, they must've...
...gone dark, because we can't
find them anywhere.
- Both of them?
- Yes, sir.
For some time, it looks like.
Damned idiots...
Is this how they managed them?
Find them at all cost.
The lawyer can't stall too long,
find them before then.
Get their corpses if you have to.
Yes, sir.
Let's move!
(3. Attack and Defense)
Please... Don't kill me...
I didn't do anything wrong,
please let me go...
As it's pointed out
in the fax I sent earlier,
my client was on a road trip
with his friends in the south
during the estimated time
of the murder,
when he supposedly left his
epithelial cells on the site.
And this is a list of his alibis.
Oh, we'll look into that
later for sure.
But how will you refute
the DNA evidence?
Why was your client's DNA
found on the victim?
Oh that...
Shit, so he can talk.
I thought you were a goddamn mute.
And you don't stare down
at cops here in the South.
That stupid smirk...
Alright, let me hear you.
How did your DNA come
out of the victim's vagina?
We started a weekend farm
as a hobby.
We got a small land near our home.
It's got some cucumber
and eggplants, too.
Here.
Quite a bit of eggplants.
They give away the harvest
to their friends and neighbors.
One eggplant is hardly
irrefutable evidence.
We'll look into this as well.
So you arrest first
and come up with evidence?
Get with the times, detective.
If you find more
solid evidence, call us.
But send him home for today.
The warrant was issued today.
We can still...
...hold him for another 42 hours.
Anyway, nice meeting you,
and see you again.
Oh yeah, Mr. Kim.
Guess you don't know me well yet.
Keep that smirk on
while you can.
Buddy.
I only said we got your DNA,
but nothing about an eggplant.
How did you know
it was off an eggplant?
And you even prepped
a photo of the farm too.
Open up.
They take me
for a goddamn fool?
Dig into his alibis' whereabouts.
Find everything and anything
you can about these pricks.
- Got that?
- Yes, sir.
- Anything from Kim's house?
- We ransacked it,
but nothing useful.
What about his minions?
I sent out APB for their arrest.
Find them fast, bastard,
they're accomplices.
Of course, sir.
-Find them, bastards!
-Sure.
Go to the info division
and dig into the lawyer.
Especially his bank account.
Should focus there.
Check his bank records
and see who paid his retainer.
How can we do that?
Stop asking me to shit...
...I mean, how will you
handle the backlash?
You jerk again...
You'll make me say it again?
Sorry, sir.
I'll take care of the shit,
so you just
bring me results, alright?
Or you still don't get it?
Yes, sir, I get it.
Get a move on,
why're your feet on the ground?
You two, track the alibis.
- Get a move on!
- Yes, sir!
Run, bastards!
Thought those bastards
could fool me?
(Cafeteria)
- Over here!
- Sorry about that.
- Took you long enough.
- Sorry.
- Are you new?
- Yes.
- It took so long.
- Lunch is here!
Sorry for being late.
It's gone all cold.
Easy on the wheels.
Hey, I asked for rice and noodles!
Come get lunch.
Good work, everyone.
Security cams near
Kim's home and work
were already taken
by the intelligence.
It's okay.
There are enough cams out there.
We got tons of dash cams.
Taking some of them won't hurt us.
Go through what we got.
Scour every minute
and every second.
- We'll get a hit.
- Yes, sir!
Let's split it up evenly.
Firewall is off.
Frequency tracking is complete.
Can we mirror
what they're watching?
Yes, if they are online.
Bringing it up on channel 1.
- That one as well.
- Coming online.
Those dumb bastards...
They're seriously going to
comb through everything?
Sitrep on Kim's boys.
Not yet, sir.
Cops will be all over them,
put more agents on it.
Yes, sir.
(Seoul Gaebong Police Station)
(Cafeteria)
Alright everyone, focus!
- Food is here.
- Why are you always late?
Let's eat, guys.
Chief, I think I got a hit!
Let's see.
Here! I got him too!
- Where?
- Seoul tollgate.
Chief! Here too!
Me too.
Over here.
Guess what this is.
Go on a road trip?
Is that your alibis?
You got a teleportation machine?
Why don't you check
the date and time.
We found you in Seoul,
here, here,
and here, too.
While your alibis were elsewhere
during that time.
Got anything else to say?
Anything at all?
You're finished, bastard.
Where's that smirk now, huh?
Yes.
I understand.
We'll move in right away.
Yes, sir.
We found him, Kim's minion.
Drink while it's warm.
It's Solomon's seal tea.
Without company approval,
what have you two been doing
with American spies?
I'm sorry, sir.
Paul Gray...
Of all the Yankees, you had to
side with the worst one.
Didn't something feel fishy
from the beginning?
Kim Gwang-il is
the only son of Kim Mo-sul,
the holder of Jang Sung-taek's
China account!
The CIA has never handed over
anyone like him before.
Those bastards...
...already knew who
Kim Gwang-il was.
And you two took the bait
without knowing anything.
Dumb bastards...
So?
Pardon?
So what will you do now?
The police debunked the alibis,
they're under pressure, too.
From the start, the alibis were
to buy us time.
Can you finish the job
without him?
Taking his head is enough.
I don't need yours too
Get the police off your back,
and wrap this up by
handing Kim over to the CIA.
If this ends well,
you'll see another day.
If the company reputation
is tainted,
you two will be our scapegoats
for all to see, got that?
Yes, sir,
I'll sort it out quietly.
Drink up, it's getting cold.
I couldn't reach you,
so I had to drop in like this.
If I'm not reachable,
that means something.
Are you thick?
Did you do okay in school?
I have something to tell you.
I know what you came to say,
and I already told your boss off.
You're in no position to
tell us to halt the case.
We're not doing this
over a parking ticket.
This a serial killing case,
with 7 confirmed victims!
If this doesn't get solved soon,
the media will have my neck.
So my apologies to you,
but I can't help you on this.
My hands are full already.
Let's deal with our
own business, alright?
And don't go looking for me
at a place like this,
it's embarrassing!
And it's rather awkward
for the both of us.
I'm not asking you to halt.
Continue the case.
However,
I'd like to give you something.
What?
Another freebie?
Let's help each other.
Get him ready.
What's going on?
Come with us.
Will he be okay?
He was raised by Kim's family
like their own pet.
He will die for Kim, if he has to.
Shit, what's this?
What did you just say?
Release Kim?
We got the offender,
so let him go.
No, he's not the one.
Kim's the real killer.
That bastard is just a pawn.
Take a look.
What is it?
It's from the lab.
The pawn's DNA was recovered
from victim #3, 5 and 7's
personal items.
Is that so?
How do evidence we
couldn't find suddenly surface?
And this.
You must have this, too.
This guy was captured
on the security cams
near where the bodies were found.
And we got a full confession.
So who else is the killer?
Where did you get all these?
Who gave them to you?
Detective, this is enough.
Let's wrap it up here.
We got the killer, so that's that.
They went this far
to make us look good,
why not return the favor?
"They"?
Hand Kim over.
Eyes forward when driving.
Sir? Sorry.
Finish Kim's report tomorrow
and hand him to the prosecution.
What? But that's...
Yes, sir.
Press conference in the morning,
so get the media ready.
Wait, drop me off at my place.
I need to change.
Okay.
I'll be right over once
I get changed,
so go finish up the report on Kim.
What? But Chief!
- Shut up and go.
- Yes, boss.
- Go on.
- Bye.
Who is it this time?
Thought you wouldn't be
home tonight again.
Who are you?
I don't think we're acquainted.
Maybe you got the wrong house?
I don't remember cuffing you.
That's you, isn't it?
So?
How's Gwang-il doing?
Who are you?
Your eyes say
you're a hunting dog.
We must be in
the same line of work.
Gangwon province?
Your accent is familiar.
Up north.
North? Northern Gangwon?
You got a case on Kim?
12 confirmed victims.
4 cases in which he wiped out
the victims' families.
You're being dramatic.
How does it look?
The killing methods are similar,
aren't they?
He toys with the victim...
...and kills her in the end.
I'm from the North.
To catch that
bloodthirsty bastard.
Lee Dae-beom,
Security Division from the North.
(Det. Kim)
- You're under arrest...
- Out of my way!
for violating
the National Security Law.
You have the right
to remain silent...
What the hell's going on?
Beat it, bastards.
That bastard's mine,
don't you dare step in!
Chief, you can't do this.
Enough of this bullshit
and get the hell out.
You got shit in your ears?
What do you think you're doing?
This matter has been settled.
Chief, calm down,
it's an order from the top!
Let go.
Let go of me. Let go!
Chief, please...
Sons of... Are you all nuts?
Chief, just this once.
You dare smirk?
Is that a smirk?
Why, you bastard...
Stop that!
Don't touch him!
I said, let go!
Did you just laugh? Is this funny?
But it's funny,
should I cry instead?
What? You bastard...
Have you ever heard that sound?
It's my favorite.
Do you know what sound people make
as they die?
Especially when
the young girls die.
The moan of pain.
Man, it's something.
Demented bastard...
By the way, how'd the funeral go
for the idiot who killed himself?
Shut your mouth.
You know what sound they make
when they suffocate?
Don't feel so embarrassed,
your predecessor wasn't the first.
You little bastard!
- Hold him back!
- This bastard...
Chief!
I'll kill him!
Got any more wisdom to spill?
Because I'll kill you!
Chief! Chief!
Kill me?
Pitiful bastards.
If you can, why don't you?
Why you...
- Chief! Chief!
- Let go of me!
Why you...
I said let go, bastards!
Stop the reporters! Stop them!
I said, let go!
You're photogenic.
You didn't know?
You could be an actor.
An action star.
But at least only this site
ran with your story.
Other sites focused on
closing the case, what a relief.
Hey, I was up all night calling in
for favors to pull that off.
You're suspended for a while.
From arresting and
assaulting wrong suspects,
your record is already
filled with assaults.
You should've been
fired for this,
but at least the case is closed.
We decided to wrap this up
with a short suspension.
Stay low for now, okay?
Holy cow!
Why that jerk...
South Korea can't touch him.
It's a soar eye
to your intelligence division.
Even if you wanted something done,
you got Yankees
for a puppet master.
So what, then?
You're saying you can?
So why didn't you?
Why let him go wild
and wait till the 12th victim?
At the time, his father Kim Mo-sul
was Jang's right-hand man.
In other words, he was
"royal family." Untouchable.
So we got hit instead.
It was a night ambush.
Two of my men were beheaded,
and I took a bullet and
fell into the Yalu River.
All the top brass knew
about it but it was covered up.
So what's changed?
What will you do?
Just before Kim defected
to the South 2 years ago,
Kim Mo-sul and his men were
charged for counter-revolution.
Which means
we can now get him, too.
Hand him over.
I guarantee you,
the South won't prosecute him.
(4. V.I.P. from the North)
- Tired?
- Nope.
I doubt that.
Is everything settled?
Yes, just the tidying-up now.
All docs are shredded.
Then check Kim Ji-won's
border-crossing route for me.
What's this?
It's you?
Yes, sir.
About 5 years ago,
in Peshawar, sir.
Oh, Peshawar.
So the Pakistani job was yours?
I see.
You field agents belong out there,
why bother with a desk job?
So stick with what you're good at.
When is the exchange?
We're in talks.
Gray won't just take him,
Kim's a handful.
But he won't give up on
what Kim knows.
We notified we won't babysit Kim,
so they'll be an answer soon.
Good.
Let's wrap it up nicely, alright?
I don't want any more trouble.
Gather up the remaining
loose-ends as well.
And move into this office.
By the way,
that blind doesn't fit,
change the color.
What is it?
Where the hell is he?
I'm sorry,
I went out for a smoke...
Are you insane?
I'm sorry, sir.
Kim Gwang-il,
you think we're easy?
Don't you fret,
I didn't do much with this girl.
I was simply...
Whoa. Hold up.
What? "This girl"?
Tell me again, what did you say?
"This girl"?
What do you mean?
You know,
the girl you gave me before.
What about their handlers?
I'm sure they had some,
what have they been doing?
Well, uh...
We received orders to
go easy on the dick.
But that's not all.
He messed up with my agents.
You didn't...
I just had some fun
with them, too.
I didn't kill them.
You bastard!
Buddy.
You psycho bastard,
you got a death wish?
Should I just end you here?
Is this really part of your job?
Shouldn't you be
protecting me till the end?
The Yankees won't be
too happy about this.
I've had it with you!
Boss, please calm down!
You'll kill him at this rate!
Please calm down.
Cuff his feet too.
Toss him in the corner
so he can't move.
Right away.
Get on the ground!
Hold him tight!
Who the hell are you?
Know when to quit.
Did it cross your mind,
that maybe I don't want to answer?
Have you considered my words?
What?
Oh, you're the Northern spy.
I was right, wasn't I?
Will you hand Kim over now?
Are you kidding me?
I've been stripped.
I can help you.
Help with what?
The bastard's gone.
Give it up.
The game is over, pal.
No.
It's not over.
At least I know how to
extend this game.
Prior to arriving in Seoul
two years ago,
Kim and his minions
stayed in Hong Kong
and left 2 open cases.
They tortured, killed the girls,
recorded the whole thing,
and sold the snuff film
to fund their escape.
Kim's face is on that video.
(Hong Kong Causeway Bay Case:
Murder of Cho Yu-na)
If it's Hong Kong...
One of the victims was
a Korean residing in Hong Kong.
Did you verify?
Yes, we did.
His face is visible.
Make enough copies
and gather everyone.
Even the off-duty!
District Attorney,
let me ask you another favor
while at it.
It's been a long, long time,
Mr. Kim.
Two years, right?
You look good,
it's gotta be the water in Seoul.
Now after what I heard, things are
not too going to well for you.
I'm sorry to hear that.
And you picked up some sick hobby.
Couldn't you have picked up
something a bit more refined? Huh?
Isn't that why you released me
in the first place?
So it would come to this.
You got a point.
So what now? Hmm?
Sounds like you are
in desperate need of help.
Please don't get me wrong.
I don't care what the hell
you were doing in Seoul.
Now what I am trying to
figure out is,
what value you hold and
if it's worth protecting.
Do I really need you?
Honestly, when I look back on
these last two years,
I'm not so sure.
What do you think?
Why did you guys relocate me from
Hong Kong in the first place?
I asked you a question.
You piece of shit.
You haven't changed at all, huh?
Now, the only reason
you were relocated
was because of the Chinese
bank account your father manages.
And we assumed that
he had given you
all the information to that
account when you left North Korea.
So?
So what?
I think you know
the answer to my question.
We couldn't find
any money, Mr. Kim.
Only some petty cash of yours.
Which leads me to wonder
if you knew anything at all.
You really think so?
What I think is not important.
It's up to you to prove I'm wrong.
Oh I forgot to tell you,
some Russians are looking for you.
Oh yeah, you didn't know,
now, but you see... Mr. Kim
spent some years in Russia. Yeah!
Studying, right?
Don't you think he pulled up
some sick shit over there, too?
You sick bastard. Is that why you
gave us this piece of shit?
Can you imagine?
If this bastard
started killing girls
in New York City instead of Seoul?
How do you think
we could handle it?
We can't just pull him out.
And you guys... You didn't suspect
one single thing, huh?
You got yourself
a serious problem there.
You had this guy for 2 years
and you came up with nothing.
You couldn't even
keep him on a short leash.
What the hell
are you guys good at?
Come on. Hey, stop it! Easy.
We're trying to make
a deal here, okay? Thank you.
Why is that Pyongyang
can't kill my father
even after they cleaned him out?
Everyone called my father a genius
when he was a child.
He is very smart up here.
But you see, I am smarter
than my father.
You guys want his
banking information?
It's all in here.
I will give them to you.
Okay, good.
Now we're talking.
And let's talk details later
on our side, not here.
How about we take these off
before we talk further?
The police are here.
The police? How did they find out?
Isn't it obvious?
We got wiretaps, too.
Where are you off to now?
A different warrant, this time.
You see this?
You're quite photogenic, you know
Could be an actor.
Perfect for a psycho role.
Yes, sir.
Out of the way!
You still want to continue
covering for him,
as a fellow human?
Gwang-il,
I'm so happy to see you again.
I was depressed because
I thought I'd never see you.
You bastard.
Where's that smirk now, huh?
Laugh and smirk
like you did before.
You bastard, seriously...
You're a tenacious one.
Have some respect
for your elders, you prick.
Oh yeah, Gwang-il.
By the way,
I figured it out.
The reason why you shove
weird things into vaginas.
You can't, right?
What?
This.
Jerk...
You wanna die?
So I was right.
I was spot on!
He can't, erectile dysfunction!
You bastard!
How dare you attack a cop?
You piece of shit.
Goddamn shit.
Buddy.
I told you,
this is not North Korea.
Did I tell you that or not?
Give it up, all of you.
If you try to intercept again,
I'll toss you in for
harboring a killer. Got that?
Take him.
Get the hell up.
Don't be a pussy.
Wow, that's Chae Yi-do?
He doesn't waste any time,
does he?
What's the matter with you?
You're not gonna go after him?
But do you know where Chae Yi-do
keeps getting
all this information from? Here.
And you guys, you
knew about it, huh?
Because the piece of shit that
you picked up... He ratted, right?
Oh yeah...
Well, Lee Dae-beom,
he used to work for...
Was it called
Foreign Operations Bureau 35?
Before he got transferred to
the Police Department
up in Northern Pyeongan.
Now, 3 years ago while Lee was
cracking down on Kim and his gang,
Lee got fired, he and his team got
kicked out from the police force,
and sent to a fertilizer
plant to work their asses off.
Now, Kim's gang followed,
they killed all of Lee's men.
You see, to Kim Gwang-il,
Lee Dae-beom is
the North Korean Chae Yi-do.
Come on, this isn't right.
Out of the way!
Shutting down the task force?
Without consulting me?
By whose orders?
The case is closed,
what's wrong with that?
It's far from over! Shit!
Alright, fine.
If this is how you want to play,
I'll take him to the HQ.
Get it together, you idiot.
You can't will
yourself through this.
Hand him over
before shit hits the fan.
What shit?
We got new evidence!
How could you say that
after watching it?
Have you all gone mad?
Goddammit...
Why're you going nuts
over a closed case?
Wasn't this a done deal?
The matter's been settled
with them, too!
If we continue, we'd be
backstabbing the Intelligence!
Yi-do, listen...
The serial killing case is over.
Cased closed!
We got the killer.
I mean, you did with your team.
There won't be any more victims.
Even the Hong Kong cops
swept it under the rug.
So why bring it out
and cause a stink?
What about Det. Jo?
For what did that idiot
kill himself then, huh?
You're the one who put
an incompetent idiot on spotlight.
You wanted the killer!
You told me
to bring in the killer,
by any means necessary!
Kim is the goddamn killer!
You know that, bastard!
You bastard...
Hand the key and phone in,
and head back with the boys.
What? Chief, what'll you do?
We'll come with you.
Shut the hell up,
you're all useless idiots.
Give me the key and phone,
and beat it.
- Come on, Chief.
- Now.
Chief...
Good job today, so be on your way!
Things aren't working out
as you had hoped?
Shut your goddamn hole.
You have to know your limits,
otherwise life gets tiring.
District Attorney,
it's Chae Yi-do.
Are you filled in?
I'll head over now, then.
What?
You see, I was given an order
not to get tangled up.
You know my situation,
we're just a third-party.
It'll look like we interfered
a done deal, right?
So,
drop us from this case.
I heard you're suspended,
you should take it easy.
This is no small business.
You can't do this alone.
It could be the end for you.
So what?
Arrest me for violating
the National Security Law?
Go on, then.
No.
I don't really feel like it.
Besides, Lee's status is
defector anyway.
He defected after
the incident 3 years ago.
He's been hunting down that
psycho all along.
I guess he wanted to
return to post with Kim.
The agency had a hand
in Kim's defection.
He couldn't move in while Kim
was under our protection.
So instead, Lee tipped
various agencies,
just enough to corner Kim.
He's a former spy,
that's his specialty.
And? So?
What will you do with him?
I know for a fact, he won't stop
until he drops dead.
He'll keep killing.
If I let the bastard go,
I'm going to regret it.
That's enough.
It's out of our hands now.
The Americans will
take him away, somewhere.
What, people don't live there?
It's their problem now.
So that
North Korean spy was right.
I need to take that out, too.
Hey, Chae Yi-do!
Stop the bleeding
and call an ambulance!
What the hell is wrong with you?
What the hell are you laughing at?
Jerk...
Goddamnit!
You bastard!
It's been a while, Kim Gwang-il.
Lee Dae-beom!
You didn't close down the piers.
Well, I guess it'll do no favor
to us to have him back.
Good job, let them take him.
Yes, sir.
In any case, it's over.
We clearly handed him
over to the CIA,
and they blew it while
he was under their custody.
They can't say shit to us.
So... He's Lee Dae-beom,
from Bureau 35, is he?
Too bad for him.
Finally on his way home, after a
ghost life to catch Kim, but...
...the supreme leader is dead.
Now, Kim Gwang-il's cohorts
are in control of the country.
They wiped out Bureau 35
and Jang Sung-taek is in charge.
Kim Mo-sul has been
reinstated, of course.
(5. Epilogue)
Very good.
Agent Park, it's been a while.
So, is South Korea handling
my case again?
Tell the Yankees,
I'm different this time.
Sure, I bet.
Your father Kim Mo-sul was
executed with Jang Sung-taek,
and you'll be, too,
if you're sent back.
You're in no position to
play with us both again.
I know that.
So what?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll spill the beans.
I'll tell them everything I know.
The Pyongyang account in China.
Does it hurt?
Listen, Agent Park!
What are you doing?
It's your duty to serve me!
I asked you a question,
does it hurt?
Park, you damned bastard...
Why are you doing this?
You can't do this to me.
Why not?
Agent Park, have you gone mad?
You... You...
Do you know what you just did?
I told you, I'll give you
everything I know!
I don't need your shit.
You cockroach, how dare you...
...Paul Gray.
Bring me Agent Gray.
I'm only wasting my time with you!
Get me Gray!
Then what? What!
What do you want?
Tell me what you want!
Die.
What?
Die, bastard.
The thing you wanted.
Yeah?
What the hell have you done? Huh?
Oh jeez...
You must know that China is
pissed off at Kim Jong-un
for killing Jang Sung-taek.
Do you really think
they will let the North Koreans
access the money
from Jang's Chinese account?
An empty can, you idiot.
The Chinese cleaned it all out.
Seriously, you guys didn't know?
How can you not suspect a thing?
Isn't that something you should be
concerned about? Huh?
From now on,
you deal with your own shit.
Don't call for help.
You guys don't sign my checks.
And the next time I see you,
I promise,
I will snap your neck.
Yeah...
Get this shit out of here, now!
(V.I.P.)
(Kim Myung-min)
(Jang Dong-gun)
(Park Hee-soon)
(Lee Jong-suk)
(Directed by Park Hoon-jung)