♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ Chasing the future with passion
like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
♪ Living in the vast ocean of time ♪
♪ I'm trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity
and lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
=Light Chaser Rescue=
=Episode 34=
(I made three wishes)
(in front of the Lover Tree.)
(I hope you can)
(find them here.)
(I've rehearsed this)
(countless times in my heart.)
(Some are grand,)
(and some are whimsical,)
(but I guess)
(you probably also)
(don't care how many people)
(can witness this moment,)
(but want this day)
(to be like every other day)
(we've been together,)
(enduring and lasting.)
(So, my first wish)
(is about time.)
(I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.)
(I want my future)
(to start from today.)
(There was only Luo Yuan)
(in my world.)
(But when you showed up,)
(my life started to diverge.)
(One road leads to her,)
(the other leads to you.)
(Sometimes I just want)
(to run to you.)
(Yuan asked me
when I came back from Xishan)
(that if I thought about her)
(when I was trying to save you.)
(I lied.)
(All I could think about)
(was that I can't lose you)
(Therefore, my second wish)
(is about myself.)
(I wish I'd always)
(be able to protect you)
(and give you the courage to love me.)
What about your third wish?
Don't you have an answer?
I want to hear from you.
I got hurt,
but
I couldn't stop
thinking about you after I got hurt.
You were all over my mind
before I went to bed at night
and when I woke up in the morning.
Although injured,
I'm happy.
Every moment
we spend together
is precious.
I think it's necessary for me
to have a clearer direction
for my future.
So,
I healed my wound
and I got this for you.
♪ You're the only one in my eyes ♪
♪ Your eyes that look at me ♪
♪ Will always be my love ♪
♪ And always make me moved ♪
♪ Promise to the beating heart ♪
Zhan Yan.
I hope you can be
a part of my future.
Will you marry me?
♪ Let the wrinkles of heartbeat
coincide with life ♪
♪ Chase the exciting
or warm tears in eyes ♪
♪ Like stars
guarding the silent night sky ♪
♪ Fill the dark cracks with light ♪
♪ Always silently and gently ♪
♪ I feel on the opposite bank ♪
♪ I'll love you forever
and be moved forever ♪
♪ Behind each door
are different emotions ♪
♪ Quick footsteps in a busy life ♪
♪ When you pass by, time slows down ♪
♪ My yearning for you
flashes on and on ♪
♪ Flows of traffic in sweet dreams ♪
♪ You're the only one in my eyes ♪
♪ Your eyes that look at me ♪
♪ Will always be my love ♪
♪ And always make me moved ♪
♪ Promise to the beating heart ♪
♪ Love me as I am like you do ♪
♪ Let the wrinkles of heartbeat
coincide with life ♪
♪ Chase the exciting
or warm tears in eyes ♪
♪ Like stars
guarding the silent night sky ♪
♪ Fill the dark cracks with light ♪
♪ Always silently and gently ♪
♪ I feel on the opposite bank ♪
♪ I'll love you forever
and be moved forever ♪
♪ I'll always believe your love ♪
♪ Me like that ♪
Well, if that's the case,
you might need to
talk to the bank in person.
Mingming, why are you back so late?
Aiqi has been waiting for you
for a while.
He...
Well...
What's wrong with Mingming?
Perhaps he broke up
with Ding Dingding.
This child.
It's okay. Let's continue.
When did you take this one?
This was my first day at work.
I couldn't afford a new suit,
so I wore my senior's clothes
back in college.
You looked plain,
but your eyes were clean.
It's like
you lived in the silt but not imbrued.
Am I imbrued now?
Now all I can see
is pretentiousness,
pomposity,
and
not following the traffic rules.
Do you still hold a grudge?
I'll hold it for the rest of my life.
Fine, do it.
Just don't tell
our future children.
It will affect
my good image
in their mind,
and it's a bad example.
What's going on with these three girls?
The three of them
all had a crush on me
back in college.
Just keep bragging.
I'm not bragging.
You should have a little faith
in yourself.
You stood out
among all those girls
who had a crush on me.
Look how cute
you were as a kid.
Yeah.
Why did you
look so grumpy?
I was too little
and my features were close.
It was in middle school.
Wasn't I handsome?
You know what,
when we had parent-teacher conferences,
I didn't even know who could attend it.
Zhan Yan.
My parents would be so happy
if they knew
I'm gonna marry you.
(Light Chaser Rescue)
Dad.
Captain.
There's one thing
we should let you know.
What is it?
I proposed to Zhan Yan,
and she agreed to marry me.
Mr. Luo,
you just stole my daughter
without a sound.
Did you ask for my permission?
It's not hard to get your permission.
It's hard to get her to say yes.
Don't you know your daughter?
I'm happy for you two.
Well,
let's start training.
Don't think you can muddle through
just because
you're gonna be my son-in-law.
I know you won't go easy on me.
I'm prepared.
I'm gonna go to the welfare house.
Okay.
Go easy on him.
Rest assured. I won't tire him out.
Don't worry.
Let's use
exercise equipment today.
Okay.
(Heart&Heart Welfare House)
Lele!
Zhan Yan!
Have you been a good boy lately?
The teacher praised me.
Lele
has been doing well lately.
He helped us
take care of the younger kids.
Everyone loves him.
Sorry to trouble you.
Lele has made such great progress
because of you.
Zhan Yan.
I'm playing with blocks
with my friends.
Can you come later
to see us build a castle?
Okay.
Lele has been missing
you and Mr. Luo.
And you're here today.
In fact, I'm here today
to ask a favor of you.
Here.
This is an orphan
(A Civilian Hero Zhan Qingshan)
from the earthquake in Qingshan.
I heard that the orphans
were sent to
welfare houses in different places.
You also took in some of them here.
I wonder if he was here.
It was
over 20 years ago.
It's a little hard to find out.
Besides, we've been
renovating the archive lately.
It's kind of inconvenient.
How about this,
I'll contact you
when the renovations are done.
Is it okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
We have no record
of this kid here.
Thank you.
(Caritas Orphanage)
I'm sorry
that I didn't help you.
Thank you.
(Binjiang Oriental Caritas Orphanage)
Come on.
Cheers!
Come on!
I'm gonna get you some skewers.
Have more!
No problem.
Well done, Luo Ben.
Now you've won over the daughter
of our captain.
A barbecue
is not gonna be enough.
You have to treat us
to a big meal at least!
Exactly!
We are not that easy to put off!
As for how big the meal should be,
it depends on
how important Dr. Zhan is
to you.
Well,
let's find some time
and get the boys together.
You can pick any restaurant
you want in Linjiang.
Great!
That's my man!
Here.
All right, thank you.
Here. These are freshly barbecued.
Come on.
Congratulations.
Yuan has always
wanted you to marry Zhan Yan.
I'm gonna call you Mrs. Luo from now on.
What did she say?
She said
we should hold our wedding
as early as possible.
Did the smoke choke you?
Did you choke on the smoke?
Let's get back there
and eat something. Come on.
This boy.
Xiong Fei is quite attentive.
You don't have to envy her.
Your future husband
will do better than he does.
Just get a room.
I heard it all.
Are you jealous?
I'm so jealous.
Give me one of those.
Here.
Put it in your mouth.
Take this.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Barbecue some veggies.
They love that.
Looking at these young people
feels like
looking at the future of
Light Chaser Rescue.
I'm happy to see
you're getting along well
with Yan now.
It wouldn't have taken this long
if I'd listened to you sooner.
Enjoy your meal!
Thank you, Mrs. Luo.
Enjoy.
Yan.
Right, I forgot to congratulate you.
You and Luo Ben are finally together
after all that you've been through.
It's nice.
Why are you here alone?
Where is Zhou Mingming?
We broke up.
Why?
We were just having fun.
We had fun,
so we broke up.
Although you two
bicker all the time,
we can see
that you two do like each other.
So why?
I like a lot of people.
I don't need him.
His mother doesn't want us
to be together.
Ding Dingding.
You're making me look down on you.
My little cousin
is not gonna flinch
for such a reason.
Yan.
But I'm not
always invulnerable.
I give up this time.
Don't think about it.
Just go with the flow.
I trust Zhou Mingming.
I mean, he looks unreliable,
but once he makes a decision,
he is not gonna give up.
Like
becoming a rescue diver.
Go to a doctor if you need treatment.
Take it easy. Stop drinking.
He was dumped.
Let him drink.
Aren't you full of ideas?
Make another plan for me.
That's too hard.
I can't do it.
Figure it out yourself.
What am I supposed to do?
Mingming.
Dingding is your girlfriend.
I'm sure you know her better than we do.
If you still
want to be with her,
you have to find out
what she really wants,
instead of giving her
some ethereal romance.
But,
what does Dingding want?
Don't move!
That's a big diamond ring.
Something has been dazzling my eyes
since this morning.
You and Luo Ben...
He proposed.
Congratulations, Mrs. Luo.
When do you have time?
Junchi and I would like
to celebrate your marriage.
Are you calling him Junchi now?
What's happening here?
What else could happen?
We're in love.
At this rate,
maybe I'll celebrate
your marriage first.
Thank you for your kind word.
I wonder
when he is gonna give me
a big diamond ring.
Don't worry, you have a boyfriend now.
There will be
a big diamond ring one day.
Mr. Gao.
Yes.
The photographer has been found?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Something came up. Change my shift.
I took the picture.
There was
an aftershock at that time.
I saw a man
carry the child
out of the rubble.
Hurry!
I need a hand!
There's someone over here!
Coming.
Slowly.
Be careful!
Give it to me.
Be gentle.
Hurry.
At first, I thought
he was saving his son,
but when he gave the kid
to the paramedics
and went to save his wife,
I realized
that he saved the child first
in a life-or-death situation,
and his wife
died in the aftershock
because she wasn't
rescued in time.
I was moved,
so I sent the picture
and the story behind it
to the newspaper office.
Do you have
other pictures of this kid?
Yes.
Mr. Gao told me about it,
and I brought them with me.
- Here, have a look.
- Thank you.
Push yourself up!
The last ten seconds!
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Time is up.
Don't stop immediately. Do it slowly.
Slowly.
How are you feeling?
Thanks to Captain,
I feel like
this leg is mine again.
Thank you, Captain.
You're welcome.
That's because you kept it up.
I'm gonna take a shower.
You guys talk.
Okay.
Rehabilitation training
(Light Chaser Rescue)
is painful.
Most people can't make it.
I'm surprised
he's been able to keep it up.
That's why
he is making great progress.
He is a proud man.
He would go all out
for his leg.
The kid...
Did you find something about the kid?
I knew it.
It was many years ago.
It won't be that easy to find him.
If we find him,
are you gonna tell him everything?
Yes.
What if he won't forgive you?
After what I
did to him,
I can't ask him to forgive me.
But why would we
interrupt his life again?
Why would we
hurt him again?
Maybe not knowing the truth
is best for him.
Yan.
If I wasn't
made into
a hero who saved his life,
I shouldn't
reopen the old wound.
But the press
put me in that position.
He would think of me as a hero
and be grateful to me
after he saw the report.
He would see me as his lifesaver,
but the truth is I'm a sinner.
I can't keep it from him
after I hurt him.
Besides, he has the right
to know the truth.
I see.
Zhan Yan, I'm coming in.
What are you looking at?
I just took a look around.
Well,
did you find anything
about the kid today?
It's okay.
Your father's been
looking for him for so long
and still has no clue.
You don't have to be in such a hurry.
I know.
Captain has been
helping me with
the rehab training these days.
I think it's working really well.
I'll look for him with you
after my leg heals.
You said
there's no rush.
Just focus on your things.
I'll take my time looking for him.
Okay.
You've had a long day.
Go take a shower.
I'll be out.
(Binjiang Heart&Heart Welfare House)
Zhan Yan, I'm coming in.
Here, have a glass of milk.
Thank you.
Let me see.
Heart&Heart.
I told you last time.
I was transferred
to this welfare house
after the Earthquake in Qingsen.
Maybe the boy
you're looking for it
was also transferred
to this welfare house.
It's impossible.
I checked it there.
That's why
(Binjiang Heart&Heart Welfare House)
I crossed it off.
All right.
Speaking of that,
I haven't seen Lele
for a while.
Well, you were supposed
to wait for my leg to heal
and then we could go together.
Your leg isn't healed.
I don't want to put you
to too much trouble.
I went to see Lele.
Everything is fine.
Don't worry.
All right.
After my leg heals,
we'll have a lot
to do together.
Alright.
I'll take care of
the rest. Go to sleep.
Drink it.
There were meetings all morning.
Don't you need a break?
Notify all department heads.
We'll continue to discuss the plan
in the conference room in ten minutes.
Okay.
I've thought it through.
Even if Mingming and I
choose to be together,
no matter how much we love each other,
we can't stand his mother
stirring things up behind our back.
Though my parents
sound like they despise me,
I know
they are loving me
in their own way.
Even if I'm fine with
what Zhou Mingming's mom did,
I can't let my parents
suffer indignities.
Don't be so categorical.
You and Zhou Mingming
are not at the point
where you can't work things out.
Unlike some people who have things
that they can't fix
no matter how hard they try.
If you give up now,
you will regret it.
There will be regrets,
but some regrets
can't be helped.
Yeah, it can't be helped.
(Ding Xiaoxiao, will you marry me?)
(Yes.)
(Name: Light Chaser)
(Chapter: The Final Chapter)
(Upload)
You didn't eat anything today.
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
Here.
(The comic artist
Ding Dingding updated new work.)
If you care about her so much,
why don't you go to see her?
We broke up.
Well,
I've seen you and Dingding
have come a long way.
I knew
from the first time
you asked me to sign her
that she must have
a different place in your heart.
We grew up together.
I've never seen you
care so much about a girl.
It's rare to have
such a relationship.
Mingming.
Don't make yourself regret it.
(Let's be together.)
(Household Register)
What are you doing here
early in the morning?
Dingding, you were right.
I didn't get things right
with my mom and your family
and I got your feelings hurt,
but I've made my mind up.
Our relationship
is up to us.
No one can stop us.
Ding Dingding.
I want to spend the rest of my life
with you.
Marry me.
Dingding.
Will you marry me?
I'm not gonna go crazy with you
in the morning.
I'm serious.
As long as you say yes,
we'll go get
the marriage license right now.
Dingding.
You've been the one
walking towards me
under pressure.
From now on,
I want to protect you.
Okay?
Silly.
Mom, look.
We got the marriage license.
Don't squeal.
Mom!
Have you been waiting long?
Dingding.
Did you get the household register?
Let's go.
Hold on, Mingming.
What's the matter?
I think
we shouldn't do it today.
Dingding, you promised me.
You can't back out now.
Calm down.
Hear me out.
I also can't wait
to get the marriage license,
but what are you gonna tell your mom
if we do?
How am I supposed to face her?
Are we never gonna
see each other again?
Dingding.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of the rest.
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
That's not what I meant.
I trust you.
I just don't want to drive a wedge
in your relationship with your mom.
Trust me.
I know how to get her to accept me.
I would like to have
my future mother-in-law's blessing.
Well, you don't believe me?
I do.
Dingding.
You're so good.
Of course I'm good.
I went to
the rest of the welfare houses
on the list in the last two days.
There is no sign of that kid.
It's okay.
But your leg
is basically healed.
You should get back to the firm.
Yeah.
I should probably get back.
Then go ahead and do your things.
Don't let it keep you from your work.
You know,
going to the welfare houses
reminds me of old times.
Although the teachers
at the welfare house
were good to me,
sometimes
I still felt lonely.
Fortunately,
I met my foster parents.
They gave me
a happy family.
Haven't you been
taking care of Luo Yuan for them?
That's why Luo Yuan
is living a happy life.
But Luo Yuan can't speak
also because of me.
We can't always live in the past.
Yuan won't blame you.
But the scars of the past
can never
be eliminated.
You didn't do it on purpose.
But I can't
forgive myself.
Xiong Fei was in prison before,
but Luo Yuan doesn't mind.
By the way,
when did she find that out?
Xiong Fei confessed
before they got into a relationship.
If Xiong Fei had chosen
to keep it from her,
I wouldn't have allowed them
to be together,
let alone get married.
After all, it takes courage
to confess one's past.
If two people want to live together,
honesty is the most basic requirement
and the utmost respect for each other.
Have some shrimp.
♪ The world had no sorrow at first ♪
♪ Until fate came along ♪
♪ The soul never knew about wandering ♪
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
♪ All the good times
belong to the light ♪
♪ It will light up the scars later on ♪
♪ Catching the starlight ♪
♪ Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city ♪
♪ With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly ♪
♪ But I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪