♫  I'm a self-righteous foam  ♫
♫  I put out mountain fires  ♫
♫  and catch the sunset  ♫
♫  I leave the rhythms of life in my wake  ♫
♫  Happiness whispers in my ears  ♫
♫  Chasing the passion for the future  ♫
♫  Like a dream maker  ♫
♫  Reading the universe and stars  ♫
♫  My existence in the river of time  ♫
♫  With the body temperature of a moment  ♫
♫  I'm trying to be the extension of light  ♫
♫  If the world grants me a frustrating opening  ♫
♫  I'll chase back time like a dark horse  ♫
♫  Even though I know the truth, I won't be afraid  ♫
♫  I won't miss the moon because of mediocrity  ♫
♫  I won't lose the light  ♫
For an emergent disease, dialysis only helps maintain the status quo.
A kidney transplant is recommended.
For a kid over one-year-old, the earlier it's transplanted,
the less serious the rejection is,
the greater the possibility of curing it.
No problem.
The sooner, the better.
I can donate a kidney to my daughter.
No.
The kidney transplantation of kids differs from that of adults.
It depends on the donor which must be a child, so it's very rare.
How long will it take?
Don't be anxious.
If you decide to do the operation, we'll apply for transplantation typing
to organ transplantation banks of national major hospitals.
I'm sure you'll find a suitable one.
Be ready to pay for the operation.
Once we find a donor, she must have the operation immediately.
Thank you, Doctor.
Stop crying.
How much money left do we have?
We spent it all on goods, and the equipment newly bought.
Guoguo needs an operation and dialysis.
What shall we do?
It's okay.
Don't worry about the money.
I'll get it ready.
At any cost, we've to get her cured.
Don't worry.
Go visit her.
Mrs. Zhang.
Dapeng.
I'm fine.
Don't console me.
Tell me your bank account number.
No, thanks.
But... do me a tiny favor.
Don't tell the team members about Guoguo's illness.
I don't want to bother them.
I'll lease out the store first, and find other ways later on.
What ways?
If you lease it out, how will you solve the daily expenses of your family of three in the future??
Even if she gets the transplant, you still have to pay for her rehabilitation therapy.
What will you do then?
Thanks for your kindness,
but I can't take your money.
It's every father's duty to cure his kid's disease.
I can't shirk my duty to others.
In such a rush, don't stand on ceremony.
I'm different from others, Dapeng.
We're bros.
Bro, thanks.
If I'm really short of money, I'll turn to you.
- President Wang. Hi, have a seat.
- Mr. Luo. Okay.
President Wang,
why bother coming here in person?
You could have asked me to come to your office.
If so, I'm the boss and you're my legal adviser.
We talk about legal affairs.
If I come to you, our identities will be different.
You're the head of the rescue team, while I'm an outdoor product salesman.
Isn't it correlated?
Are you here for the rescue business?
Almost.
I want to cooperate with you.
Dapeng, you've been the one with the highest attendance rate.
Why do you ask for such a long leave this suddenly?
Tell me the truth. Do you have any difficulty?
No.
I just...
want to ease Chen Lin's burden.
For all these years, I've been wrapped up in our rescue team.
She has to look after both the store and the child.
It's too hard for her.
Yeah.
Your wife has always supported us.
All of society is concerned about public welfare rescue.
Our team is also developing fast.
Well, mind your domestic affairs first during your leave.
Captain, thanks.
Captain, the noodles are about to be ready. Get ready to eat.
Okay. Dapeng, let's have noodles.
- Come on, Captain.
- Well.
Taste Luo Ben's noodles.
Today's noodles are lightly seasoned.
- Hope they are fine with you.
- That's good.
Yan especially told me to keep a scientific diet
with lower sugar, salt, and fat.
Indeed. When will Zhan Yan return?
Luo Ben, have you gone to visit her?
Dapeng, just eat.
Besides, Captain.
I've news for you.
My client President Wang of Polar Land Group,
an outdoor product manufacturer, came to me this morning to promote their products.
He wants to sponsor a mountaineering party to climb a snow mountain in cooperation with us.
He should turn to a professional mountaineering party,
instead of us.
Our rescue team is getting more famous,
and is doing public welfare work.
He just hopes to enhance their brand image through our cooperation.
Tell him we won't commercially cooperate with other entities.
I said so,
but he still hopes that I can gain your approval.
He said as long as we'd top the snow mountain in their outfits,
he'd reward us generously for us to purchase advanced equipment.
Luo Ben, short of equipment as we are, we can get it in the right way
like public donations instead of being engaged in business activities.
As a captain, you've to keep these principles in mind.
All right, I see, Captain.
I see.
Want a little pepper?
I did some research before coming here.
The economy here is driven by husbandry.
Local people have a high risk of echinococcosis.
Yes.
When on duty at the county hospital,
I received five patients with hepatic echinococcosis in one morning.
They all require surgery.
How's the county's surgical condition?
There is no subdivision of general surgery.
Many local people refuse to have surgery at the county hospital.
For weekend and night emergencies,
routine appendectomy and cholecystectomy both need open operations.
Emergency laparoscopic surgery had never been adopted until I came here.
External support alone isn't enough to solve such problems.
A trustworthy and highly-skilled medical team must be built as soon as possible.
Dr. Zhan, be generous with your skills.
Cultivate several apprentices soon.
No problem. Let's do it respectively, and see whose is better.
Deal. Fair competition.
Many mountaineers come here to climb snow mountains every year.
However, only a few of them can top the mountain.
Judging from their equipment,
they don't seem to want to top the mountain.
How can you tell?
In childhood, my dad climbed snow mountains with me.
I took special training as well.
Though we didn't make it that high, let alone to the top of the mountain,
I know the difference at least.
You're really something.
What's wrong?
Dapeng.
Go.
Dapeng, you're a professional mountaineer.
Why can't your physical strength compare with us amateurs?
Duojie, you're so ungrateful.
When reaching the top, it was Dapeng who pulled us up one by one with ropes.
Dapeng consumed the most physical strength.
Or could you have made it yourself?
With no photo of topping the mountain, we can't even get the award.
Forget it.
We succeeded by topping it.
Uncle Da,
shall we find a place to rest?
I feel dizzy.
Dapeng!
Dapeng, what's wrong?
He has a fever with altitude stress.
He seems to be unable to return to the base camp.
Then we've to carry him up there.
If you ask for death, don't bring us with you.
It's hard for one to walk here. Is it possible to carry someone else?
Or leave him alone here?
We've no choice.
On the way to Mount Qomolangma, many mountaineers' bodies can't be carried down.
Their relatives also had no choice.
We're not climbing that mountain.
Stop quarreling!
It seems there'll be a snowstorm tonight.
We can't reach the camp now.
Let's camp here. Okay?
I have the phone number of a local doctor.
Let me ask if she can come here.
No doctor is willing to treat a patient here.
Give it a shot.
If she refuses,
that'll be his fate.
Uncle Luodan, did you take the medicine every day?
Yes, every day.
Your blood pressure has dropped, but you have to keep on taking it,
or the blood pressure will easily go up.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Is that Dr. Zhan?
Now, I'm on the snow mountain with my team.
A team member has a fever and can't move.
Can you come to save him?
How old is he? Any other symptoms?
Just has a fever.
I don't know if he has other symptoms.
I heard he was a member of the Light Chaser Rescue Team,
and saved a lot of people.
Can you save him?
Please!
Light Chaser Rescue Team. What's his name?
Zhang Dapeng!
Zhan Yan, will you really go up the snow mountain?
Dapeng has a fever with altitude stress.
If he's badly ill, many complications will be caused.
If I don't go, he'll be in danger.
Don't be impulsive.
It's a snow mountain with high altitude,
low temperature, a varied topography, snowstorms, glaciers and cliffs.
The danger is seen everywhere.
Don't worry.
I've been here for so long, and familiar with the environment and climate here.
I climbed snow mountains with my dad.
I know what you said. I'll be careful.
If you must go, I'll go with you.
You've no experience. If anything goes wrong, I've to protect you.
Stop arguing with me and persuading me.
There'll be a snowstorm tonight.
I'll pack up, and set out tomorrow morning.
Let's go.
All was well last night.
I had the soundest sleep since I came here.
Where's the snowstorm?
Uncle Da.
Are you cheating us for Dapeng?
The climate here is unpredictable.
Though it's sunny now, the snowstorm will come at any time.
I won't be wrong.
Stop fooling around with me.
Boy, you don't understand.
Each frequent mountaineer knows
sometimes helping others is helping himself, got it?
Will the doctor you turned to come here?
Take care.
Come on.
Give me your hand.
Over there.
Without Dapeng, we'd have had a celebratory dinner with awards.
We'd better leave together as we came together as a team.
Zhan Yan, there are tents ahead.
- Are they who we're looking for?
- Go.
Go. Hurry.
Never expected a doctor would come indeed.
We're here. Here!
Uncle Da!
Uncle Da.
- Uncle Da.
- Great.
Uncle Da, where's Dapeng?
Dapeng is unconscious in this tent.
Go. Okay.
- Give me the medical kit.
- Here you are.
Go.
Hurry to pack up your belongings.
We must arrive at the hillside camp before the snowstorm comes.
Hurry up. Hurry.
Snowstorm.
Snowstorm is just on your lips.
Get out.
Withdraw to the hillside camp.
Hurry.
- Dapeng.
He has woken up.
You're awake.
Zhan Yan, why are you here?
Lie down. Don't move.
Are you okay?
Rest first.
I'm asking you, why did you join the mountaineering party?
The resource isn't enough.
We can only help reduce your fever and inflammation.
Let's talk when we get down the mountain.
Don't talk or move.
Save your strength.
Hold on.
Bad news. The storm is getting bigger.
Peg down the tent.
What shall we do?
All kits and supplies are blown away.
We've no cellphone to communicate with people down the mountain.
No signal.
Uncle Da, what to do now?
Will it be okay if we reach the hillside camp?
I've never camped here as well.
We can only walk down the path in my memory.
This snowstorm hasn't ended.
I'm afraid it'll come again.
Now let's go down. Hurry.
What about Dapeng?
Please carry him down to the hillside camp
which is flat and sheltered from winds.
Then you may withdraw first.
Dr. Cai and I will stay to await the rescue.
Yes.
It's on you.
It's hard to walk while carrying someone, but if we do it together
and walk carefully, we're likely to reach the hillside camp.
Good.
Thank you all.
Thanks.
Come on. Let's get to it.
Look!  The rescue robot can be used with life detectors
and night vision cameras to replace our team members
to get into the ruins for detection.
Here.
Go on. Let me answer a phone call.
Now technology's getting more advanced.
Hello, President Wang. What happened?
What?
Did you call the police?
Okay, I see.
What's wrong?
The mountaineering party sponsored by Polar Land is missing at Mount Mayo.
They called the police.
Polar Land?
The group you mentioned that engages in outdoor products?
Yes.
We turned them down, so they employed a group of amateur mountaineers
at a high price to climb Mount Mayo for the promotion of their new products.
What a farce!
Zhan Yan and Dapeng are also in that missing party.
You're all elites of Light Chaser Rescue Team.
Although there is already a wealth of rescue experience,
the special geographical environment of snow mountain rescue missions is complex,
with heinous climate conditions,
and many unpredictable emergencies, so you must be careful.
No matter what happens,
you should follow orders.
Don't make decisions yourself.
Remember, our mission is to find the missing mountaineers,
not to risk our lives.
Enough.
When will they arrive?
They should come soon.
Thanks for your hard work.
President Wang, you may drink.
No, thanks.
That's...
Where did they get lost?
When they phoned yesterday afternoon,
they said they were coming down the mountain.
They've come.
What a grand scene!
President Wang's style.
Dapeng?
How could he endorse the brand?
Captain Luo. Finally, I was looking forward to you guys.
In such a critical time, I'm so anxious.
We came here as soon as we were notified.
We hoped you would come here, we will be saved.
President Wang, brief us on what happened.
The case is that we've six people in total including five members and a guide.
Yesterday afternoon, they topped the mountain,
but a man got sick on the way back.
A doctor was asked there but lost contact with us, too.
When did you contact them last time?
About 16:30 yesterday.
The weather report indicated a snowstorm.
My biggest concern is that they had an accident in the snowstorm.
Well, find two guides for us.
We'll go uphill right now.
The guides are ready.
This is Uncle Luodan. This is Danba.
Both of them are local mountain people, familiar with uphill conditions.
Okay.
Captain Luo, be free to tell me what you want and how much.
Money is not a problem.
We've to go uphill as soon as possible. Talk while walking.
- Let's go.
- This way.
- Yes.
Uncle Da.
Is the route wrong?
It didn't take us this long when coming.
Indeed.
Really?
I can't make it.
I'm exhausted.
I quit. I can't do it.
Hold on.
We're all in a bad state.
With no signal, we lost contact with the camp.
If we're not sure about this route,
we should find a safer place to rest, and wait for the rescue.
It won't do.
It's getting stormy.
On the snow mountain,
we can not leave our lives to others, but depend on ourselves.
Though deviating from the route,
we ought to be close to the camp.
I agree.
Get up. It's hard to get up once lying down.
Leave me alone.
Whether to go or lie down here, I'm doomed for sure.
Don't talk nonsense on a snow mountain.
We lost supplies and equipment, and we're lost.
In such weather, even if we don't starve, we'll be frozen.
Ma Yue, can't you shut up?
No! He's so burdensome.
Without him, we'd have long gone down.
What're you saying?
So what?
You've been picking on me. Do you want to fight?
Enough!
You'd better save your energy.
Let them go.
Leave me aside.
I'm fine.
Just need to rest.
So inhumane. I do want to kick your ass.
Come on!
What are you doing?
Stop fighting!
Stop!
- Stop.
- Hands off!
Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan, hold on! Never let go!
We'll pull you up.
Harder!
Hold on!
Pull on the rope.
- Dr. Zhan!
- Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan!
Look.
Here. There.
These suspicious areas are within 3.5 km of the camp.
Let's split into East Team and West Team, led respectively by me and Xiong Fei.
Expanding the search to the east and west sides,
the two teams will follow the descent route from the mid-level camp to the foot of the mountain,
and then each will go northeast and rendezvous in the northwest.
Everyone must follow orders.
Don't leave the team without permission.
Keep communication unimpeded.
Keep in touch. Understand?
Understood!
- All right.
- Let's get started.
Zhan Yan!
Dr. Zhan.
Are you okay?
I'm down here.
- She's alive.
- Fetch the rope.
Get the rope.
Zhan Yan, don't be afraid.
They're fetching the rope.
We'll pull you up soon.
Hurry.
Dr. Zhan, I'll drop the rope.
Wait for a second,
I can't move yet.
She can't get up herself.
One of us should go help her down there.
Hurry!
Move.
You're professional mountaineers.
You should know how to save her.
Who dares?
Let alone saving her, he may not be able to come back up.
We're not professional, but merely amateurs.
It's the first time for us to run into such a dilemma.
Cowards! If you refuse, let me do it.
- Give me the rope. Don't stop me.
- Calm down!
It's no use going down.
Can you climb the ice cliff?
Do you know how to use the rope?
It's no use wasting time here.
When we still have energy, go downhill and ask for help.
That sounds right.
If the snowstorm comes, no one can leave.
Uncle Da is the most experienced.
He even agrees with me.
At this time of crisis, face reality.
At best, we'll show mercy to take Dapeng back.
We really can't save this female doctor.
Come on!
- What're you doing?
What are you doing?
You can't leave her alone.
Brother Peng, you can't move now, let alone save her.
I won't go.
Dr. Cai, it's no use staying here.
Come with us.
I won't go.
I'll stay here with Dr. Zhan,
waiting for the rescue team you'll bring with you.
Let's go.
Go.
Cai Yuxiao!
Uncle Da!
Zhan Yan, don't be afraid.
They went to call the rescue team.
I'm here with you.
Follow me.
Wait, let me look.
There.
Almost there.
A drone!
We're here!
Xiong Fei, they've been found!
They've been found!
Here.
Yes, it's them.
About a kilometer straight ahead of us.
Over there.
- Go.
- Go. Go.
Eat something.
Thanks.
Have some water.
Xiong Fei, Dapeng is awake.
How do you feel?
- Hurry... Hurry...
- Hurry what?
- Zhan Yan...
- What happened to Zhan Yan?
Hurry to save Zhan Yan.
Wait!  Where's she?
In an ice crevasse.
- Which one?
- She fell into an ice crevasse.
Which one?
Hurry to save Zhan Yan.
Just... Just around that corner.
You left her alone there?
That direction is in Luo Ben's search range.
Luo Ben, we've found Dapeng,
but Zhan Yan fell into an ice crevasse right in your direction.
- Hurry to find her.
- Roger.
Keep in touch.
We'll go find you.
Understand.
Keep your distance.
Don't leave the rope's range.
There are crevices under the snow.
Watch your step!
Go.
- Yes.
Speed up.
Mind your step.
Hurry.
Faster! Faster!
Don't go further!
The snowstorm is coming!
- Before it comes, we've to...
- We've no time!
The weather here is different.
The snowstorm seems far away. It comes at any time.
You may withdraw, but we must go.
No, you can't, or no one will come back.
Clouds are low; the wind blows snow.
It's a force 8 gale.
Luo Ben, report your current location.
Luo Ben!
Let's go.
- Go.
Don't go!
Dr. Cai.
Where's Zhan Yan?
Where's Dr. Zhan?
Hurry... save... save her... In the ice crevasse.
Hurry to save... Hurry.
Zhan Yan!
Dr. Zhan!
- Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan!
♫  At first, there was no sadness in the world  ♫
♫  Until luck came and crossed the stage  ♫
♫  At first, souls were confused and wandered  ♫
♫  Until people hugged each other  ♫
♫  I've been on the road  ♫
♫  Trying to connect laughter and tears  ♫
♫  I suddenly have faith  ♫
♫  I can walk by millions of shining household lights  ♫
♫  I hope I can admire flowers in the sunset  ♫
♫  Shed tears and hope that you are well  ♫
♫  The good times I'm pursuing belong to the light  ♫
♫  It can light up the wounds that follow  ♫
♫  Catching the floating stars  ♫
♫  Watching as the memories flash by  ♫
♫  Traveling through market scenes  ♫
♫  With a fiery gaze  ♫
♫  I can't fly  ♫
♫  But I can look up  ♫
♫  I'm always on the road chasing the light  ♫