♫  I'm a self-righteous foam  ♫
♫  I put out mountain fires  ♫
♫  and catch the sunset  ♫
♫  I leave the rhythms of life in my wake  ♫
♫  Happiness whispers in my ears  ♫
♫  Chasing the passion for the future  ♫
♫  Like a dream maker  ♫
♫  Reading the universe and stars  ♫
♫  My existence in the river of time  ♫
♫  With the body temperature of a moment  ♫
♫  I'm trying to be the extension of light  ♫
♫  If the world grants me a frustrating opening  ♫
♫  I'll chase back time like a dark horse  ♫
♫  Even though I know the truth, I won't be afraid  ♫
♫  I won't miss the moon because of mediocrity  ♫
♫  I won't lose the light  ♫
What have you been up to these days?
I signed up for the training program of a non-profit rescue team.
Doing public welfare is a good thing.
I'm in favor of it and I feel happy for you.
But there are so many public welfare projects.
Why did you have to choose such a dangerous thing to do?
Have you ever thought about it?
Should there be any danger, what would you do?
Mom, the rescue team places special stress on safety, and only by keeping ourselves safe...
I know what kind of programs your rescue team has been working on.
When you're in those dangerous places, you don't get to choose life or death.
No matter what others do, I don't agree with this.
Mom!
You can't make such an arbitrary judgment.
I'm your mother. Everything I do is for your own good.
Ever since I was little, you've arranged everything for me and justified all of your actions.
Whether it was the school I attended, the major I chose, or the kind of people I made friends with,
I always listened to you.
But this time, I want to make my own decision.
- You want to make your own decision?
- Yeah.
Then try to manage the company well.
Mom, do you have to do this to me?
You just got spoiled by me.
It's time for you to learn something.
Up a little bit. Right here.
The rain is on and off all the time.
What if our son gets caught in the rain while delivering packages?
It's fine. Don't worry too much.
He's grown up. He knows what to do.
He'll be fine.
Our son is home.
I'm home, Dad.
Look! I'm making pot stickers. They'll soon be ready.
Mom, I just had lunch outside.
- Well, I'll save them for tomorrow.
- Okay.
Eat some fruit.
You want to work overtime?
You're watching such a popular drama.
Your sister called yesterday and recommended it.
She's been watching it, too.
You know what? It's kind of fun.
Fei, you don't get to have regular meals making all the deliveries.
It's bad for your stomach.
I'm fine, Mom. You know how strong I am.
What's more, the more I work, the more I earn.
I have to make money to honor you.
That's good.
We'll be honored as long as you get a girlfriend.
He's always busy with work.
There's no time for him to go out with anyone.
You said it isn't easy to get a job now.
Without a job, it'll be harder for him to find a girlfriend.
I didn't mean he doesn't have a job. I said he was busy.
Don't I know my son?
With his looks and condition, a lot of girls want to date him.
Your son, your son. Isn't he my son?
The jobs we offer are not very demanding,
but about your history...
I'm sorry.
It's fine. Thank you for your time.
- Am I next?
- Yes.
Look more carefully next time.
Why did you allow him to come?
It's just a waste of time.
Who'd hire an ex-con?
Next one.
Did you see Dr. Cai?
- No.
Did any of you see Dr. Cai?
- I saw him check in this morning. What is it?
He has an operation at 10:00 a.m.
Why does he still have an operation?
Both of his hands are hurt.
The appointment was made last week.
He's not answering his phone.
The patient is already preparing for surgery.
I'm afraid it'll be delayed.
I'll do it.
Zhan Yan, you're still recovering.
It's fine.
- How many surgeries do we have?
- Three.
Leave them to me. Let him take a break.
- Go get prepared.
- Okay.
Sir.
Yuxiao, come to my office when you have time.
Okay.
You're backing off just because of such a minor setback?
All the time, I've been proud of what I do.
Because saving lives is a doctor's duty.
But...
I just realized this time...
that I'm such a selfish person.
I...
I don't deserve to be a doctor.
For the choice someone makes at the moment of life and death,
you can respect his nobility,
but you can't accuse him of selfishness.
We all have the urge to survive.
It isn't wrong to subconsciously protect your own life.
Our country pays a great price to train a doctor.
You're a doctor.
Only in the hospital can you do your best and save more lives.
But now you're just going to walk away like this?
Sir.
I don't have the courage to stay.
When you were admitted to college,
your family couldn't afford that,
so you came to my office and told me you wanted to finish your studies.
Think about it.
What happened to your persistence and courage at the beginning?
It's my surgery.
I can handle it from here.
Let's continue.
What a crappy company.
It's going to be shut down.
Hello.
May I ask has Zhou Mingming come to work?
Not yet.
Loafing around. He'll be fired one day.
What's it that you have to call me this early?
What?
Are you new here?
I haven't seen you before.
I've been here a few times.
It's also the first time I've seen you.
You've got a good temperament. Do you also work here?
Which department are you in?
I... Comic Department, I guess.
Comic Department?
Why didn't I know about this department?
Who's the one in charge?
Don't get me started.
I don't even know his full name,
only that he's called Director Ming.
He's extremely unreliable.
I've been here a few times but I never ran into him.
You may not know.
Director Ming is the president's son.
I'm aware of this.
With what he's got, there's no way he could be a director.
I shouldn't go to Director Ming.
I should go straight to the president.
Why do you want to see the president?
To lodge some complaints, of course.
You see, even if he is the son of the president,
he's clearly not up to the job.
He just doesn't have that ability.
How could he become a director and ruin my comic career?
Auntie, have you seen the president?
I have.
Could you spill the beans?
What kind of person is the president?
Is it a stuffy old lady,
or... or a sloppy old man?
Am I right?
Your coffee is ready.
I'll make you a cup.
No need.
Auntie.
- What did you do?
- I'll help... Calm down! Calm down!
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
You come to see me in my office.
You...
You're so screwed.
Could she be the president?
Mingming, we've got a variety of business sectors, yet you had to choose to do comics.
Good then. Let's take it as a new business you just developed,
tell me what do you plan to do next?
Mom, actually, this comic is going viral online.
How? Have you done any market research?
Have you made a project and a development plan?
How will it make a profit? How will the business grow? What's its potential?
President, Mingming just bought the copyright
and the other work is underway.
Don't try to defend him.
Okay.
Since Mingming is interested in comics, I'll give you a chance.
The company will set up a comic department and you'll be in charge.
But I have to set a goal for the performance of this department.
Aren't you going to take some notes?
Do I need to do that? Mom, just tell me. I'll remember it.
Okay.
Within a month, the hits, popularity,
and trending searches will come out on top among other IPs of the same period.
Within three months, become the top ten in the ranking.
Within six months, the serialization will be finished and offprints will be published.
Besides, by the end of the year, incubate the IP comprehensively.
So? Do you get it?
Mom, are you really turning the comics into an IP?
If you don't achieve this goal, and no results are produced,
all the money invested in the Comic Department will be deducted from your annual salary.
That's all.
Well... Well...
We've never done this, and have no experience with it.
You know what your mom is like.
Every department must follow through on her request.
But look at those goals.
It's impossible to achieve them.
You're looking down on me?
No.
What your mom wants is for you to admit your mistake,
and this whole thing will stop.
Just quit this.
I just like to take on challenges.
It's a new business sector, and it gets me motivated even more.
Set up the Comic Department officially. It's a deal.
Yuan, keep packing.
I need to go out.
You'll soon be discharged.
Where are you going?
I... I just feel a pain in my back.
I'll get the doctor to check it.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Don't worry. I'll be right back.
I read your medical records.
You should be feeling fine by now.
So Dr. Zhan has been secretly paying attention to my injuries.
Yeah.
It hurts.
Does it always hurt like this?
No, just now.
Let me disinfect the wound for you again.
It's not healed anyway.
It's going to hurt a little bit, so just bear with it.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
After you leave the hospital, have a light diet.
Don't soak the wound in the water. And come to change your dressing regularly.
Okay.
Dr. Zhan, are you coming to my place this weekend?
Why?
We made a deal.
If we can come out alive, you'd come to my place
and taste my cooking.
All right.
6:00 p.m.
- Are you going out?
- I'm looking for you.
I think I should have listened to you.
They only know how to ruin my work.
It's like their humanity has been ripped.
Help me think. Is there any way to cancel the contract?
The terms of termination are clearly written in the contract.
Just pay the penalty.
I don't have that much money right now.
Or I wouldn't have turned to you.
If Sister Yan knows about it,
she'll definitely nag me and blame me for being impulsive.
You haven't told Yan about this?
I don't dare to.
Classmate Ding Dingding,
normally, you need to pay if you seek my consultation.
But considering our relationship,
you can pay me in another way.
You can't be serious, Mr. Luo.
You just showed your affection to Sister Yan,
and now you're coming after me. This isn't appropriate.
You surely are a comic artist,
seeing how rich your imagination is.
Fill out this form.
Questionnaire on Zhan Yan's hobbies?
History of allergies. Favorite...
How about this?
One answer in exchange for one contract.
Do you even have so many contracts?
I may have many in the future.
Okay.
Deal.
Favorite fruit.
Durian.
Favorite flower: Daisy.
Are you done? Let me see.
Not yet.
You're trying so hard to pursue Sister Yan.
Maybe we will become a family.
Do you need to be so calculative? Aren't you ashamed?
Take back the word "maybe" and I'll go easy on you.
Forget it, I'd better be on my own.
Have you finished?
Hang on.
Finished?
Yeah, yeah.
I still need to rely on myself.
Favorite fruit: Durian.
Starting tomorrow, check in at the company at 10:00 a.m. every day.
What are all these quirky hobbies?
What's wrong with these people?
Does a creator need to check in?
Time for you to fulfill your promise. Think of an idea for me.
I warned you before and told you to recheck the way you work,
but you didn't listen.
Now the contract has been signed,
and you also took the money. What else can we do?
So I suggest you go to the company every day and check in.
That's your conclusion?
You asked me to read your contract, and I did it in a very serious way.
Is there a problem?
I don't think this deal is worth it. Give it back to me.
I allow no refund on things sold.
- I'm going to tell Sister Yan.
-  I dare you.
- I'll definitely tell her.
- Just try it.
Yuan Yuan, you're practicing?
Go on.
Practice hard.
Yuan Yuan,
do you want to go shopping and buy some new clothes?
we ran out of tissues. Could you go buy some?
Yuan Yuan.
This is the weekend.
Don't stay at home all the time.
Why don't you hang out with your friends?
You like that lobster pasta, right?
I'll transfer you the money and you can treat everyone to it.
See?
Ben, are you expecting someone?
How do you know?
Just tell me if you want to send me out.
Leave quickly since you took the money. Go.
Show your sincerity earlier next time.
Good luck.
Just go.
Naughty.
Are you busy?
Do you have time for dinner tonight?
Miss, you're here to see Xiong Fei again?
He left. He doesn't work here anymore.
Didn't he tell you?
Ms. Luo.
Waiting for Xiong Fei?
Have you made an appointment?
Then, what if he doesn't show up?
This brat.
Xiong Fei, I want you on the team right now.
I've got something urgent.
All right, see you.
These need to be polished constantly,  or they will age.
Thank you.
Brother! Brother.
Here you are.
This is...
I made this...
You made this for Ms. Luo?
Ms. Luo, look.
The wontons Xiong Fei made are the best.
You don't get to eat them elsewhere.
Well. C-Can I have one box?
Okay, okay.
Why didn't you text me back?
I was busy with work.
A new job?
I know about everything.
Ms. Luo, I know you're busy, too.
Don't come here again.
You don't like me here?
No.
I didn't mean it. How would I not like you?
Then, why are you avoiding me?
Why do you want to be friends with someone like me?
You don't want to be friends with me.
So when my brother had the accident, why were you keeping me company?
And now you're ignoring me.
How could you do this to me?
Is that something a friend would do?
Do you think it's cool?
I care for you.
Don't you value me as a friend at all?
I...
No, you...
Don't get mad.
I was wrong, all right?
I...
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
I'll be the one who texts you.
Try the wontons I made.
Tastes good?
Don't you want to open a restaurant?
Open a restaurant?
Yeah.
You and your sister have kept your place clean and tidy.
I don't usually let Luo Yuan do housework.
She's a girl, you know.
Of course, I need to spoil her.
An able man does more work.
You do achieve an ideal balance between your work and private life.
There are not many men like me who have a successful career and are good at housework.
Attorney Luo, are you promoting yourself?
If I have intentions to persuade a client, of course I should promote myself.
What about you?
Do you have the intentions?
Let's look at the dishes.
Sit, please.
How are they?
Looks great.
They are just appetizers.
Here's the main course.
I reckon this must be your specialty.
Open it.
Zhan Yan,
when I knew you were trapped,
I was really afraid of losing you.
I regret that I didn't take my feelings seriously earlier.
But I'm grateful that fate has given me another chance,
and left me with an incredible memory.
Zhan Yan.
I like you.
And you?
I haven't really thought about this.
Let's eat first.
There's no rush.
You can take your time.
How is it?
Is it tasty?
Quite tasty.
What do you mean "quite tasty"?
Don't try to fence with me.
Let me try it.
How tasty it is?
You should have commented like this.
It's rich in flavor,
tastes salty and fresh,
and has an aftertaste that lingers.
I need to use the bathroom.
- Hello.
- Seven?
This is mine.
- Thank you.
- Be careful, it's hot.
Thanks.
You want me to learn first?
Come on, have a taste.
That's thoughtful of you. Thank you.
All right, all served.
Here. Be careful.
And this is yours. Enjoy.
Thanks.
Morning.
Mr. Ming, you're so early.
Ling Yiqin, good morning.
Ding... Ding...
Mr. Ming.
Ding Dingding.
You scared me. I thought you were the boss.
What time is it? Why are you so late?
I overslept. That's obvious.
Did the boss come?
He did, and he has waited two hours for you.
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Why would he wait for me?
You're late on your first day. Your wages will be docked.
I'm only a little late.
How many wages will be ducked?
I don't remember seeing this before.
The company had it installed just for you.
Ding Dingding, you've been working hard.
Your boss thinks too highly of me.
It's already11.06 a.m. Ding Dinggding.
According to your wages, ten yuan will be ducked for arriving one minute late,
so it'll be 660 yuan, because you're 66 minutes late.
Come on. I'm only a little late. That's too much.
Late employees will affect the company's luck.
So I'll make it 666. That's really outrageous.
You're as sick as him.
Wait.
How do you know my wages?
Because I'm in charge here.
Will you stop it?
I actually thought my wages would be ducked. I was worried there for a second.
It's true.
You didn't get enough sleep, did you?
It's all because of you.
All right, just go. I'm busy here. Don't annoy me.
Work hard and be quick.
I know.
Sorry, Secretary Li.
I worked late last night, so I got up late.
Get prepared. We're going to have a meeting soon.
A meeting?
Who said that?
Director Ming.
Good.
I can finally meet him.
Secretary Li, don't we have a meeting?
Why are just the two of us here?
Secretary Li?
Come on. This is not where you can sit.
This is the boss's seat.
Mr. Ming, everyone's here. Shall we start the meeting?
Yes.
Mr. Ming?
So you're the boss?
And your mom's the president?
Let's begin the meeting. Don't waste any time.
That explains, Zhou Mingming.
So you're the one behind all this.
Ms. Ding, we're having a working partnership.
It doesn't matter who's behind this.
Don't put on airs in front of me.
True. I've offended you before.
It's fine that you want to prank me.
But do you have to go through all the trouble?
The fact is I see the talent in you.
Very funny. If you have to do this, then you're going to have to do it without me.
Ms. Ding, when you get back, remember to pay the penalty.
What penalty?
Read it to her.
If Party B unilaterally terminates the contract due to personal reasons,
Party B shall return the deposit paid by the company
and pay three times the amount.
Aren't we having a meeting? Go ahead. Don't waste any time.
♫  At first, there was no sadness in the world  ♫
♫  Until luck came and crossed the stage  ♫
♫  At first, souls were confused and wandered  ♫
♫  Until people hugged each other  ♫
♫  I've been on the road  ♫
♫  Trying to connect laughter and tears  ♫
♫  I suddenly have faith  ♫
♫  I can walk by millions of shining household lights  ♫
♫  I hope I can admire flowers in the afterglow  ♫
♫  Shed tears and hope that you are well  ♫
♫  The good times I'm pursuing belong to the light  ♫
♫  It can light up the wounds that follow  ♫
♫  Catching the floating stars  ♫
♫  Watching as the memories flash by  ♫
♫  Traveling through market scenes  ♫
♫  With a fiery gaze  ♫
♫  I can't fly  ♫
♫  But I can look up  ♫
♫  I'm always on the road chasing the light  ♫