♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ Chasing the future with passion
like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
♪ Living in the vast ocean of time ♪
♪ I'm trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity
and lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
=Light Chaser Rescue=
=Episode 4=
No.
I really can't make it back today.
I only need one day.
Please hold it off just for another day.
Next time?
How long am I gonna wait?
I know.
I know you've tried your best.
All right.
Make sure you come to me next time.
(Grimm's Fairy Tales)
Kiddo.
You shouldn't be here.
It's dangerous. Come here.
What are you guys doing here?
We're looking for books.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Well...
I have nothing left here.
There are only two lollipops.
You can have it. It's sweet.
Thank you, Miss.
You're welcome.
Why don't you eat?
My mom's feeling pain in her legs.
I want to bring it back to her.
Good girl.
You must keep in mind what I said.
You'll have
new books and toys.
Don't come back here again.
Do you know?
Yes.
Go back.
Take care of your little brother.
Be careful with the wound!
I found one here!
I need two people to help me!
Hang on! Hang in there!
Where is the medical team?
Give me a hand here!
Medical team, come here!
One, two, three.
Be careful!
Come on!
Over there!
Hang in there!
Slowly.
Come on, hang in there!
Zhiqiang, move it.
Run!
There is an aftershock! Go!
Xiong Fei!
Zhan Yan.
You haven't closed your eyes
since last night.
Go get some rest.
I'll take care of the stitching.
(Emergency Medical Service Ward)
My good boy. Mom's here.
Mom, am I never gonna be
able to see again?
No.
You'll be fine.
Xiaolu.
Dr. Cai.
Where is Dr. Zhan?
She is exhausted
and resting over there.
Well, let's line up.
One at a time.
Next one.
Zhan Yan!
It's time for the next surgery.
Shh.
She's sleeping.
Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan asked me
to wake her up at this hour.
What are you doing here?
To do a good deed.
You're awake.
I'm here
with the Second Medical Team.
Well,
you don't believe me?
This doctor also saw it.
He was my witness.
All right.
Tell me about the situation
of the First Medical Team.
I'll leave you to your work.
Let's go.
Don't follow me.
Who's following you?
It's such a wide road here.
What makes you think I'm following you?
Fine, you can follow me if you like.
It's not an aftershock, you coward.
It scared me.
Who are you calling a coward?
I just don't want you to be scared.
I have such bad luck.
I have to go back.
Don't follow me.
I don't want to follow you.
I'm not following you!
Come on.
(Assistance from across
the country warms people)
Please!
Has anyone seen my daughter?
I haven't seen my daughter for two days.
That's what she looks like.
The bus is here.
(Fengxi-Linjiang)
(Emergency Medical Service Ward)
I think these wounded people
are pretty much healed up.
- Sister!
- It won't take...
Sister.
Is the bus outside
from your hospital?
Can I go back to Linjiang?
Sister?
This is my cousin
waiting for the bus to go back.
It is,
but we need to transport
the seriously injured.
I don't know if there is a seat for you.
I'm fine with the standing room.
Anyway,
I have to go back.
Save a spot for me, too.
I can pay for it.
Wait,
aren't you gonna stay here
and be a hero?
Why are you fighting for a seat with me?
Didn't I get hurt
because of you?
Why are you so annoying?
What's wrong with me?
Did I get hurt
because of you or not?
Dr. Zhan.
Can my sister
be transferred to Linjiang?
She's in
the transfer list.
What about you?
Are you the evacuees
that gonna leave with them?
What's the matter?
Dr. Zhan is
my sister's doctor.
She knows my sister's
condition well.
It would be the best
if she'll go back with her.
Yes.
All right, that's a relief.
I asked you to take some rest,
but you came back to do surgery again.
I'm going back to Linjiang soon.
I'll try my best to save
as many people as I can.
There are also television journalists
coming with us this time
who want to do an interview
with our medical team.
The director asked us to be cooperative.
I don't have the time.
There are two patients
who have postoperative reactions.
I'm going to attend to them later.
You know
I don't like
such occasions.
Okay.
I'll try to turn it down for you.
Thanks.
It's such a small child.
(Supplies)
What's your name?
- Okay.
- It's not enough.
Tent 3, right?
Yes.
Okay.
What's your name?
Sister.
Here are some instant noodles for you.
They're still warm,
but they have been soaked
in water for too long
and gotten soft.
Go ahead and eat.
Sister, you don't know
how hard it is to wait in line
to get some hot water.
When it was finally my turn,
there was no water left.
I had to start all over again.
It was too hard.
Have you eaten?
I ate while I was waiting for you.
Hot water didn't come easily.
Eat all the soup.
Thank you.
Don't just thank me. Start eating.
Zhan Yan, I remember I got into trouble
when I was a kid
and my mom wouldn't let me eat,
you just brought me food secretly.
Do you still remember it?
It was a bucket of instant noodles.
We ate it in turn,
and we really enjoyed it.
Be careful.
Slowly.
This way.
Be careful.
Put your feet on it.
Miss Luo.
How are you feeling now?
Knowing you're fine
with the kids,
the dean left rest assured.
Have some rest.
I'm gonna go.
Luo Ben.
You haven't apologized to him yet.
Take the medicine first.
He saved me.
I know
that he saved you.
Okay.
I'll go and apologize to him right now,
all right?
Have some rest.
Remember to take the medicine
I'll put it right here.
Xiong Fei.
What's the matter?
You saved my sister this time.
I'll remember
your favor.
We save people
not asking for anything in return.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I'll
return this favor,
but
I don't want you to get too close
with Luo Yuan.
You're thinking too much about it.
I'm not.
Maybe you're not, either.
But I don't want Luo Yuan
to think too much about it.
She is a simple girl.
I don't want her
to be influenced
by the things around her.
Don't worry.
I'm just a stranger
to Miss Luo,
and we won't meet again.
Good.
Well,
if you need
and advice or help
with legal matters,
you can come to me.
Come in with me.
Miss Luo.
How are you feeling?
Are you feeling better?
Dr. Cai.
Can you tell us
about Miss Luo?
Miss Luo.
They are reporters
from Linjiang.
What are you doing here?
Please leave.
Well,
I'm a doctor
from Linjiang Hospital,
Cai Yuxiao.
They are reporters from Linjiang
who would like to interview your sister.
Interview?
We don't need an interview here.
What my sister needs is rest.
Please leave.
Don't get us wrong.
They just want to
bring back some good news
to the viewers concerned about
the earthquake in Fengxi.
Good news?
Stop filming.
Put down the camera.
The citizens of Fengxi
are either sick, wounded,
or dead.
As a doctor,
you're not treating patients,
instead, you're here making interviews
and showing off you.
What good news can there be?
Just leave.
In this case,
I will
show you around outside.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Let's go.
Are you all right, Yuan?
Don't mind them.
Medical assistance after the earthquake
is urgent.
We can see
that there are
many simple operating tables here.
Dr. Cai.
How many operations like this
do you need to do in one day?
I've never counted them.
As long as there are patients
who need surgery,
we'll do it.
(Linjiang Hospital Rushed to the Rescue)
Thank you very much, Dr. Cai.
You've been working really hard
to save
all these lives.
What kind of belief
is supporting you?
It's our job
to treat patients as doctors.
Dr. Cai looks really good
on TV.
He's a good-looking guy.
He just acted
the way he usually does
and made the hospital look good.
That's so Dr. Cai.
When I heard him
saying in a trembling voice,
“Let me save one more”,
I was about to burst into tears.
The First Medical Team
did the job well.
Well done, guys.
Now that the Second Medical Team
has arrived,
we need attending doctors
in the hospital.
Zhan Yan.
You should come back
with critically ill patients
who need to be transferred.
Yes.
Now we're at
the temporary processing site.
Lele.
I'm going
to leave soon.
There will be other doctors
to take care of you.
Okay?
Lele.
I'll come to see you
when I have time.
Good boy.
Watch your steps.
Don't fall on your face.
What?
Let me do it.
Be careful. Slowly.
What?
He might want to say something.
He's dying.
Buddy.
Don't sleep.
Hang in there. Don't fall asleep.
Adrenaline.
Okay.
Hang in there, buddy.
Hang in there.
Please.
Please
save them.
Save...
Who?
Buddy!
The call leads us to believe
that the deceased's wife
is trapped in a place called
Cliff Guo.
She's probably
not the only one trapped there.
The communication team
is trying to locate her
based on cell signals.
We sent her a message
an hour ago,
but she hasn't replied.
Maybe her phone died.
There is also a chance that...
In that case,
we have to get there sooner
and see what's going on there.
Captain!
We've found Cliff Guo!
Good.
Where is it?
In Daxiang Village, Lulong County,
ten kilometers away from Fengxi.
Right here.
But images from the satellite
show no sign
of houses.
How is the road condition there?
They're making an urgent repair.
If we leave now,
I think we can get there
in the wee hours at the earliest.
We don't know
the situation there.
I suggest we leave as early as possible.
Then we'll have to
take the mountain road.
Yes.
After reaching the top of the cliff,
we'll rappel down.
This is the fastest way to go.
There can't be too many people.
Xiong Fei, Dapeng.
Get prepared
to go with me.
- Yes.
- Got it.
Keep your feet steady, guys.
Be careful, Captain.
Watch your steps.
Captain.
Look.
Get ready to rappel down.
Okay.
Yes.
Let's go.
Watch the rolling stones.
Put on your goggles.
Safety first.
Let's go.
Dapeng, Xiong Fei.
Scour separately.
Okay.
I'll go in the back.
Captain!
Miss.
Can you hear me?
Come on.
Tell me where you got hurt.
Save me.
Save my baby.
She's pregnant.
- Pregnant?
- Miss, get up first.
Sister.
I drew this for you.
Thank you, honey.
You must be a good girl.
Thank you.
Slowly.
Take good care of her.
Wait, wait.
There is no seat left.
Let me squeeze in there.
I have to go back.
I have something urgent.
It's not safe to overload the bus.
Just wait for the next one.
Attention, everyone.
The target is Cliff Guo.
We found a pregnant woman here
who is about to give birth.
Obstetricians are urgently needed.
I need to know which doctor
is available on the team.
This is Flying Fish. Roger.
I'm in the base.
All doctors on the team
have other tasks.
I can go.
You are...
I'm Zhan Yan, a surgeon
from Linjiang Central Hospital.
I minored in obstetrics in college
and have experience in midwifery.
That's great.
I'll check in with the captain right now.
Captain, this is Flying Fish.
You should take my seat and go back.
What about you?
I have a task.
Zhan Yan, stay safe.
How is it?
Dr. Zhan.
You might not be able
to go to Cliff Guo.
Why?
Our captain doesn't agree.
Captain Qingshan, this is Zhan Yan.
You need an obstetrician in Cliff Guo.
Why don't you let me go?
I understand how you feel.
You're a doctor,
but you don't have
professional outdoor skills.
The terrain of Cliff Guo is complicated.
It will be dangerous
for you to come.
Isn't it dangerous for other doctors?
Fine.
May I ask you
if you know how to rappel down?
No, right?
After arriving at Cliff Guo,
you have to rappel down the cliff.
That's why I asked for
the doctors on our team
to carry out this mission.
Do you understand now?
Though I don't know how to rappel down,
your team members
can help me.
Dr. Zhan.
We have no time right now
to teach a novice
how to rappel down.
Besides, we can't take the risk!
That's ridiculous.
Thank you, Dr. Zhan.
I'll try to contact other members.
I'm a member of
the International Medical Rescue Team.
For the safety of the puerpera at Cliff Guo,
take me there right now.
I got hurt because of you.
You shouldn't let me stand, should you?
If you can't stand,
just wait for the next bus.
My sister left the seat for me.
Your sister chose to stay here
to save more lives,
but you chose to run away
when you're totally fine.
You two are sisters.
Why are you not like her
at all?
Well...
I'll kick you out
if you scream again.
It's fine. Stop looking at us.
Sir, we can leave now.
Weren't you a doctor before?
But I was not an obstetrician.
I can help her,
but I'm worried about
special clinical circumstances.
Can we get her out of here?
No.
Her water broke.
That would be too much for her.
Can we use the car?
No, it doesn't work.
Save my baby.
I wish there was a helicopter.
What's the use to say that?
I'll make a call.
Hang in there.
Director Liu.
I'm Qingshan.
We're at Cliff Guo.
What?
That's great.
Got it.
Flying Fish.
I just got the news
that the road to Cliff Guo is clear.
Find a car
to bring Zhan Yan here right now.
A car?
Where am I gonna find a car?
Let's go.
The road to Cliff Guo is clear.
You don't have to rappel down.
Captain asked me to find a car
to take you there.
Where am I gonna find a car?
Dr. Zhan.
Get on it.
Hold on to me.
Dr. Zhan.
This is the second time
that I give you a ride.
Do you think I want this?
Is this
how you talk to people?
It depends.
Can't you stop
holding on to your preconception?
Hold on to what?
Preconception.
What?
Me.
Eyes on the road!
It's ready, captain.
It's ready. Come on.
Let's get her over there.
Slowly.
Come on.
Three.
Go.
Come on.
Okay.
Slowly.
Is there another way?
Yes.
We can go on foot first
and rappel down
like Captain Qingshan.
Are you kidding me?
Can the patient wait?
Dr. Zhan.
Have you ever played desert saferi?
Yeah. What?
Hold on to me.
♪ I believe in sincerity and kindness ♪
Doctor!
Where is the doctor?
Just hold on a little longer.
Dapeng.
Coming.
Dapeng, stay with her.
The doctor has arrived.
Just hold on a little longer.
♪ My dream is burning ♪
♪ Is boiling ♪
♪ Is blooming ♪
♪ Is shining ♪
♪ Become the light ♪
(Linjiang Hospital Rushed to the Rescue)
How do you make preliminary judgments
about patients in different conditions?
It's important to note
that just because
someone is moaning loudly
doesn't mean
he is critically ill.
Dr. Cai is also handsome today.
There are citizens sending flowers
and journalists making interviews.
All the outpatients are making
an appointment with him.
He's about to become a famous doctor.
Don't ever think about dating him.
When the earth trembled
and disaster struck,
you saved lives
and brought hope.
Salute to Cai Yuxiao,
the warrior in white.
Hello, Dr. Cai.
I'm a reporter from Linjiang Daily.
I would like to interview you
on the medical relief
this time.
That's not necessary.
As doctors, our job
is to save lives.
Therefore,
you can pay more attention
to the disaster area.
Zhan Yan.
You've been to the disaster area
the longest
and treated the most victims,
but he is the one
to be interviewed.
I don't care
who is being interviewed.
I don't want it anyway,
and I can't handle it.
You have to learn to handle it.
You're not representing
yourself this time,
but the First Medical Team
who rushed to the rescue.
What do you mean?
Don't you know it?
The hospital will select
an outstanding team.
If you don't strive for it,
and it keeps going like this,
Cai Yuxiao and the Second Medical Team
will be selected.
(After the earthquake in Fengxi,)
(leaders at all levels,)
(major enterprises,)
(institutions,)
(and the people of all localities
have taken actions)
(to give the greatest attention
and support)
(to the disaster areas)
(through various means.)
(Today, our reporter connected)
(the chairman)
(of the Midas Touch Media,)
(Mr. Ma Baoming.)
(Mr. Ma said)
(that when he learned of
the earthquake in Fengxi,)
(he immediately sent
the most urgently needed supplies,)
(which are 2,000 boxes of water)
(and 1,000 boxes of instant noodles)
(to the disaster area)
(to express his sincere greetings)
(to the affected people.)
(Just because)
(there are so many people like Mr. Ma)
(who did...)
(Ma Baoming)
Mr. Ma.
I just heard
the news of your donation
to the disaster area.
I'm calling to pay respects.
In the end,
I should thank you, Attorney Luo.
Thanks for dealing with Ding Dinging.
Our company immediately
sold the film rights
and got financing.
You only spent some money
on water and instant noodles,
but got the best publicity.
That's your style, Mr. Ma.
Well...
By the way, Mr. Ma,
I have a new idea
with the case of Ding Dingding
and I like to discuss it with you.
Hello, Weiwei.
Dingding.
How's the drawing going?
I'm working on it.
You'd better hurry up.
Don't miss the deadline.
I chose to work with you
because you're fast.
Don't worry.
I'll finish it on time.
By the way, Weiwei,
the deposit.
Well...
I'll transfer it to you soon.
How soon?
Hello?
What kind of person is that?
He rushed me actively
but hung up on me when it came to money.
(Receive 100,000 yuan
From Midas Touch Comics)
Holy cow.
That's fast.
Wait,
I shouldn't get paid a hundred grand.
(Ma Baoming)
Mr. Ma.
Ding Dingding.
Looks like you haven't
blocked my number.
How come?
I know you.
Although you're saying this,
maybe you've been cursing me
behind my back.
I transferred a hundred grand to you.
Have you received it?
The money...
Take it
and call my names less often.
Mr. Ma.
You must make it clear,
or I wouldn't dare take the money
in case this is another trap you set
to get me sued.
I can't afford that.
Rest assured.
My attorney
advised me to give you the money.
You little girl
can be impulsive
sometimes,
but you do
have potential.
We might
have a chance
to work together again.
We should leave the chance open,
right?
It was advised by your attorney?
Hold on, Mr. Ma.
Well,
please repeat what you just said
and let me record it as evidence.
Well...
Zhan Yan.
What are you doing here?
My dad made wontons in chicken soup.
He asked you to come home
for dinner on weekends.
I have to work overtime on weekends.
Tell auntie
and uncle thanks for me.
You said you had things to do last time.
If you don't come this time,
my mom will blame it on me.
Fine. When do you have time?
Maybe when I'm not this busy.
By the way,
please give these
to the E.R. doctors for me.
I caused them trouble
when I wanted to jump off
the building last time.
Are you feeling guilty?
You've become introspective.
Stop it.
I was desperate
at that time.
Unexpectedly,
that unscrupulous publisher
regained his conscience
and said something about sharing
the copyright of the film with me.
It's a hundred grand.
There is no such thing as a free dinner.
Are you sure
it's not a trap?
I don't think so.
He said his attorney advised it.
I've recorded it.
Luo Ben.
It's him.
I think he should
help me.
When his sister had surgery,
I mobilized everyone
to donate blood for his sister.
Anyway,
we're even this time.
Thank you.
Come back for dinner when you have time.
Yuan.
Is he okay?
Honey.
Sorry, he's sleeping too soundly
and having a nightmare.
Honey, why did you kick me?
I bought you some bread.
You fell off by yourself.
I didn't.
You must have kicked me.
Are you happy?
I didn't kick you.
You fell off by yourself.
Don't you know
I have a protruding disc in my waist?
Don't hit me. I'm telling you.
- Why are you being so mean?
- You can't be like this.
Are you happy because of the bread
or because of me?
Of course
it's you.
Go ahead and eat.
I just snored. Do you have to do this?
Every man snores.
Yuan.
Have they always been like this?
Look at
this disc in my waist.
All right, I get it.
It hurts more than ever.
Do they bother you?
- Are they too noisy?
- Keep your voice down.
I've tried to be quiet.
It's not that loud.
Luo Yuan.
I'm here to check
the recovery of your wound.
Do they care how I feel?
You snore too loudly.
Do you know it?
Is snoring
something I can control?
You know what,
you can find a doctor to treat me,
or just make me stop breathing.
I'm not gonna argue with you.
You can always justify yourself.
- I can't help it, can I?
- Come on.
Dr. Zhan.
Yuan is recovering well.
Thank you.
It's what I should do.
You don't need to thank me.
But Ding Dingding said
you helped her get the compensation.
It's not like I paid for it.
The rose's in her hand,
the flavor in mine.
Looks like there are a lot of things
an attorney can do.
It depends on
how cooperative that person is.
Dr. Zhan.
There's one more favor
I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
Luo Yuan needs rest.
You also saw
how noisy those two patients are
in the next bed.
They've affected
Luo Yuan's rest,
so I hope
you can move her
to a single room.
The single rooms are all occupied.
Do something about it.
The single rooms are occupied.
What can I do?
You're a doctor. There must be
something you can do.
Are you saying
we have available wards
but we won't let you use it
unless you
bribe the doctors?
What do you take this hospital for?
What do you take us for?
I just want to move her
to a different ward.
You don't have to take the high ground.
I'm not taking the high ground.
I'm just talking about the truth.
Well,
I thought your sister would come.
I made all these dishes
so that she can have
something nutritious,
but she doesn't come.
I'm your daughter, okay?
You just can't stop talking about her.
Yan has been a good girl
since childhood.
When has she ever
made us worry about her
no matter when it came
to school or work?
She is not like you.
Yes, I know.
You two are college teachers,
intellectuals.
But you failed
to make your only daughter
a high achiever.
I understand it.
Just wait and see.
You know what,
the high achievers end up leaving home.
I'm the angel
sent to stay with you
for the rest of your lives.
Mom.
When is our little angel
gonna grow wings
and fly out of this house?
I'm not leaving.
Dad, I haven't had enough of
the wontons you make.
Here.
Yan didn't make it back today.
I'll cook something tomorrow
and bring it to her workplace.
Don't.
She doesn't
like being in our house
nor being disturbed
by us.
That's nonsense.
When did Yan say
she doesn't want to go home?
That's the truth.
She doesn't like crowds.
Just don't bother her.
The misfortune of childhood
takes a lifetime
to heal.
I feel bad for Yan.
Yan is a little aloof,
but she knows
who is good to her,
right?
Yan's father
is good to Dingding.
He is Dingding's uncle.
They are also close.
Let's not bring the feud
of the last generation
to the young people.
Okay?
Why do you mention him
all of a sudden?
I will never
forgive him.
♪ The world had no sorrow at first ♪
♪ Until fate came along ♪
♪ The soul never knew about wandering ♪
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
♪ All the good times
belong to the light ♪
♪ It will light up the scars later on ♪
♪ Catching the starlight ♪
♪ Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city ♪
♪ With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly ♪
♪ But I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪