♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ Chasing the future with passion
like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
♪ Living in the vast ocean of time ♪
♪ I'm trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity
and lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
=Light Chaser Rescue=
=Episode 6=
Is it all right now?
Did you put the bag
into the microwave?
I forgot.
You forgot?
Did you just move here?
Don't tell me
you're living across the hall.
What do you think?
What a coincidence.
It's too much of a coincidence.
Hold on.
The property manager said the new tenant
is in the rescue business
with strong consciousness
of fire and safety.
That's why
I didn't stop by.
Who would know you...
It was just a mistake.
Just a mistake?
Don't you know
you can't take the elevator
when there is a fire?
I was in a hurry.
What's more,
this is my house,
not yours.
Why should I listen to you?
All right.
Then I'll keep filing complaints
with the property management
until your landlord ends the lease.
Fine.
Tell me what you want.
You can stay here,
but you have to
learn about fire safety first.
All right, I got it.
Yan?
Mr. Luo, I'm so sorry.
We haven't had a chance
to hand out safety manuals
to new tenants.
Please do us a favor
and stop filing complaints.
We will correct our mistakes
until you are satisfied.
What are you talking about?
I won't eat you.
Yes.
Mr. Luo!
I believe the tenant across the hall
has realized
her mistake.
Please let her go.
Here, give this to them,
just in case.
That's what happened.
Is he really gonna stop
filing complaints against me?
Yes.
Thanks.
That was really scary.
If we were
in the comic book world,
something romantic would happen
between Luo Ben and me.
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
At first, he helped
Ma Baoming entrap me,
then I saved his little sister
in the earthquake.
He helped me get
some money back,
and I rented an apartment with the money,
and now we live across the hall.
Who knows what might happen?
You should eat less junk food.
I'm going
to learn how to cook.
You could even trip the alarm
when you were using the oven.
You'd better study
the safety manual first.
Yan, why are you
on his side?
You just moved out like this.
What are you gonna do?
What can I do?
Keep drawing comics.
I can't do anything else,
and I don't want to,
but I have
hit a bottleneck in creation lately.
I don't know what to draw.
Go for a walk.
I dare not.
The last time when I went for a walk,
I ended up in an earthquake.
I lost my job
and met Zhou Mingming.
By the way, Yan,
you're full of ideas.
Help me think about it.
Don't you like superheroes?
Draw your own one.
Draw a superhero?
That's a good idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Look at those superheroes abroad,
the Hulk, Spider-Man,
Captain America.
We have superheroes around us.
Light Chaser Rescue.
Yan, if you don't want me
to draw them,
I'll draw something else.
This is your work.
Don't worry about how I feel.
Then I might
visit the rescue team a lot.
Will you be unhappy?
Why would I be unhappy
when you're doing what you love?
That's very kind of you, Yan.
(Linjiang Central Hospital)
(Nurses' Station)
Zhan Yan is here.
Zhan Yan.
Are you waiting for me?
Something happened.
It's so unfair.
We're waiting for you
to make a decision.
Let me tell you...
Slow down. The sky won't fall.
Are you sure about it?
I saw it with my own eyes in the office.
Cai Yuxiao's Second Medical Team
has been preselected
as the Advanced Disaster Relief Team.
They'll discuss it
during the meeting his afternoon.
We arrived at the disaster area
and started a rescue in the first place.
During the golden 72 hours,
for three days and nights,
Zhan Yan
barely closed her eyes.
It's too unfair if we don't
get a share of the honor.
That's right.
We made the same effort.
They can't ignore that.
Okay, I see.
Go back to work.
Go ahead.
Let's go.
(Fengxi Earthquake)
(Work Report of the First Medical Team
during the Earthquake in Fengxi)
What is Zhan Yan thinking?
Is she really gonna
let Cai Yuxiao have it
because she is shy of fighting for it?
Yeah.
Why would Zhan Yan be like this?
Rest assured.
That's not who she is.
It's really weird.
Please come in.
President.
I need to censor myself.
You've always been
on your high horse.
When have you ever censored yourself?
What is it? Tell me about it.
The Second Medical Team
has been preselected
as the Advanced Disaster Relief Team.
I'm responsible for this.
This is the decision of the hospital.
What does it have anything
to do with you?
As the head
of the First Medical Team,
after returning to the hospital,
I didn't report our work
to the leadership
and the hospital's Party committee
in a timely manner,
as a result,
the leadership isn't clear about
what the First Medical Team did,
and I'm responsible for that.
Therefore, I wrote up
a report on
the First Medical Team's work.
in the disaster area
(Work Report of the First Medical Team)
Please take a look.
I hope
the First Medical Team's work
can be evaluated objectively,
and we should be given this honor
if we meet the standards.
But there can only be
one advanced team.
That will be
your work.
President.
This honor
is not mine.
It belongs to my team,
so I'm going to fight for it.
Come on.
Well done.
- Keep going.
- Your turn.
A little higher.
Come on.
40.
Keep going.
Okay.
One more group.
Yes.
(Support for Light Chaser Rescue
(Water Rescue Gear))
What's the matter?
Mingming!
I know we can count on you.
Don't say that. I just lifted a finger.
You should lift your finger more often.
Lift your finger once you get a chance.
Falcon.
To be frank,
I'm here this time
to create a chance for myself.
I think you guys are really cool,
and I want to join you.
G-Guys.
What do you think?
The gear is pretty good.
The gear is good.
- That's nice.
- Yeah.
Why not, Uncle?
Joining the non-profit rescue team
is nothing to play with.
I'm not playing with it.
I take it very seriously.
Do your parents know about this?
I'm an adult now.
Look, I've become
a big girl.
I even moved out.
They don't need to know.
Dingding.
When we rescue lives,
every detail is a matter of life.
It requires professional rescue skills,
a strong body,
and a high sense of responsibility.
You've never engaged
in such things before.
How can you do it?
Don't worry, Uncle.
I can learn from scratch.
I won't be shy from working hard.
Okay.
Let me ask you,
why do you want to join
the Light Chaser Rescue?
I admit
I have a personal reason.
Can't you just put me
in a less challenging position?
You haven't joined us yet,
and you're starting to get picky.
Listen to yourself.
Uncle.
Actually, my cousin asked me to come.
Yan?
Did Yan put you up to this?
How's she doing?
Is she doing well?
She's been fine lately.
Rest assured, Uncle.
Well,
here's what it is.
A few days ago,
my new house almost caught fire.
Yan was really worried.
She said I should learn
something about safety.
I think
this is a ready-made
professional place.
It's perfect, right?
Safety.
Dingding.
If you just want to learn
the common knowledge of safety,
I can teach you right now.
You don't have to join us.
I want to join you
because I want to learn
more professional knowledge
of rescue.
Besides,
Uncle,
I also want to make a contribution
to the public welfare.
What's more,
I can come more often
and bring you news of Yan.
All right?
If you don't say anything,
I'll take that as a yes.
Thank you, Uncle. I'm leaving.
I'm not gonna eat the apple. Bye-bye.
Don't worry.
I'll put in a good word
for you later.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean?
If you can come, I can come, too.
Well,
Zhou Mingming wants to join
the rescue team.
I'm taking him to meet Qingshan.
He can't.
His integrity is questionable.
Not at all.
He just brought some gear to us.
This young man
is good.
Do you hear him?
The Light Chaser Rescue
is a non-profit organization.
We mustn't yield to the capitalists.
If you're truly generous,
you can leave the gear here.
If it's just for trading,
you should get out of here
with the gear.
No.
We can talk about it later
whether he should leave or not,
but the gear has to stay.
Doing rescue is not for him.
He faints at the sight of blood.
He can't even save himself.
You're not the boss here.
It's not up to you.
I'm a member
of the rescue team now.
I have the right to object.
What?
Are you also on the rescue team now?
Falcon.
She is selfish.
When we were in Fengxi,
she just wanted to escape.
You know, she didn't care...
Say it again.
Fire her.
Did you see that?
She is also prone to violence!
Who are you calling selfish?
It's dangerous
to let people like her join you!
- Stop!
- Say it again!
What are you two doing?
Hello, I'm also here!
She started it first.
Shut up!
Are you playing house?
You even brought up old scores.
Listen,
no one is perfect.
Take the guys in the rescue team
for instance,
everyone has advantages
and disadvantages.
If we make a mistake, we correct it.
If you two
want to join the rescue team,
you must keep in mind
that friendship comes first.
That's the rule.
No more fighting,
or neither of you can stay.
Nod if you two
understand what I'm saying.
There you go.
Shake your hands and make up.
(Advanced Disaster Relief Teams)
Dr. Zhan, Dr. Cai.
(Team leaders: Zhan Yan, Cai Yuxiao)
Congratulations.
That's awesome.
Thank you, guys.
Well, let's not gather around.
Go to work.
Congratulations.
I heard you went to the president.
It's nothing personal.
I just asked for what we deserve.
Got it.
I know you.
It's good.
The president pushed for another spot.
Everyone's efforts are appreciated.
You probably won't
feel that way by the time
when the associate senior doctor
is to be selected.
I won't complain
if I lose to you.
It's a fair competition.
You can try your best.
Okay.
If I get selected,
you mustn't cry.
Have you ever seen me cry?
No.
Cheers.
Zhan Yan.
Thank you for pushing for the honor
for our team.
Now we can hold our heads high.
Zhan Yan.
This is for you.
We deserve it.
Thank you, Zhan Yan.
The family of the patient in Bed 13,
the attorney,
you should buy him some coffee.
Why?
When you took a leave that day,
President Qiu made rounds
and he put in a good word for you.
He deserves credit for our team
getting the honor.
He did help with that.
Yeah.
This one's on me.
Okay, Dr. Zhan.
I heard you guys got selected
as the advanced team.
Congratulations.
That's why I bought you coffee
as a thank you.
If you're talking about the time
when I put in a good word
for you in the ward,
it was actually Luo Yuan
who asked me to do it.
I just passed on a message for her.
Well, thank you for passing on
a message for her.
You're someone who returns every favor.
So are you.
It tastes good.
(Savor Coffee)
It's raining.
Hurry!
Let's go. Go slowly.
Do you like it so much
that you're willing to wait in the rain?
You said Luo Yuan likes it.
I'm just trying to return her favor.
The rain stopped.
You can drop me
at the bus station ahead.
It's thoughtful of you
to buy snacks for Luo Yuan
in the rain.
I should at least
take you home,
or Luo Yuan will blame me.
Turns out you're afraid
to ruin your image
as a good brother to her.
My image as a good brother is solid,
but I think
my image as a bad attorney
can be changed.
Since when
do you care what other people think?
I didn't care before.
(Please tell me what you need.)
Play some soft music.
(Okay, playing soft music for you.)
The other company is insolvent.
If we,
as the guarantor,
have to bear the responsibility
of paying back the loan,
our capital chain
will go seriously wrong.
Therefore,
you've done a great job
in winning
this case.
I owe you one.
Don't say that, Mr. Fang.
I just did
what an attorney should do.
Speaking of that,
I think I owe you one.
Did you forget
that I broke your motorcycle
when I rode it
in the earthquake-stricken area?
You haven't asked me
for compensation yet.
Well, Mr. Luo,
you're not just good at your job,
you're also a good conversationalist.
We need to talk more often.
Then I'm looking forward to
further cooperation with you, Mr. Fang.
No problem.
Chairman, there is a call for you.
Excuse me.
What's the matter, Lansheng?
What?
Okay, I'll be right there.
My child is missing.
Jiejie!
- Jiejie!
Switch to the lounge room.
Okay.
It's Jiejie.
It's my fault.
How did I fall asleep?
We don't know
where he went.
What if...
What if he is in danger...
Don't scare yourself.
I've called the police.
Jiejie will be fine.
No, I have to go find him.
- Lansheng!
- I'm going to find him!
Manager.
Let me take a look at the drone footage.
Pause.
Zoom in.
Look, it's the boy's balloon.
He must still be at the stadium.
Keep looking for him.
I'll go check it out.
Okay.
The wind comes from
the southeast today.
The wind speed is
of category three to four,
which means the wind is
blowing towards the northwest
at six to eight meters per second.
The footage shows
that the last time he showed up
was 16 minutes ago.
(Construction Ahead, Stay safe)
Jiejie!
Mr. Fang.
I think I found Jiejie.
Jiejie!
- Jiejie!
- Mr. Fang.
Be careful!
Mr. Fang.
Jiejie might have fallen down.
We bought
this place
to develop it.
For safety,
there is always a safety net.
Well...
We don't know
how this kid got in here.
Listen,
if anything happens
to my son,
I won't let you go!
Well, Mr. Fang...
Sorry.
We need to make sure
if the child fell into the hole first.
We've called the fire brigade.
Mr. Fang.
I suggest we call
the Light Chaser Rescue
at the same time.
They have a professional rope team
who can go straight down into the hole.
Okay.
Good.
Jiejie.
It's all right.
Hello, This is Light Chaser Rescue.
(Light Chase Rescue)
(I've left the hospital.)
(I know a good noodle restaurant.)
(It's on the way
to the express station.)
(How about we eat there together?)
(I'm out on a mission.)
(It's okay.)
(I have nothing to do anyway.)
(I'll be here waiting for you.)
(I don't know how long it will take.)
(Don't wait for me.)
Is it here?
Right here.
Okay.
Captain.
The hole is 15 meters deep.
15 meters. That's deep.
Mr. Fang.
After our evaluation and judgment,
we decide
to carry out
this mission
with the Light Chaser Rescue.
It will take the shortest time
with the highest success rate.
Mr. Fang.
I've personally been
in one of the rescue operations
of the Light Chaser Rescue.
I trust them.
Please rest assured.
Captain Qingshan.
I don't know much about rescue,
but you must
save my son, please.
We're working on it.
The hole is 15 meters deep,
but there is security inside the hole.
Although in disrepair
and not solid anymore,
it still served
as a buffer.
Okay.
Don't worry, Mr. Fang.
Well, is it tight enough?
Yes.
Okay.
Stay safe.
Get the kid out as fast as you can.
Yes.
Okay. Put it on.
It's on.
Be careful.
Be careful!
Drop him down.
Come on.
Get ready! One, two, pull!
One, two, pull!
Pull!
Come over.
Pull the rope.
Jiejie!
Hold it. Hurry.
Go to the safety zone.
Come on. Slowly.
Put him down.
Let him go.
Be careful.
Stretcher!
Jiejie.
- How are you doing, bro?
- It's okay.
Hurry.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Oxygen!
Hurry!
Hurry up!
- Go!
- Be careful!
Okay.
Come on.
Xiong Fei is still down there.
Pull the rope.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm leaving, Hai.
Okay.
Take care.
(SSD Express)
Drive safely.
I'm leaving.
All right.
See you tomorrow, Hai.
Go to rest early.
Okay!
Be careful!
Okay.
Bye, Hai.
Stay safe.
Little girl.
Are you here to pick up your delivery?
Are you looking for someone?
Who are you looking for?
Look,
we're off work.
Why don't you
come back tomorrow?
(I know a good noodle restaurant.)
(It's on the way
to the express station.)
(How about we eat there together?)
(SSD Express)
It's late. Why are you still here?
Let me take you back.
Don't
come to me again.
You know that your brother
doesn't want us to keep in touch.
He always thinks too much.
He thought I was gonna
fall in love with you.
You don't feel the same way, do you?
No.
Do you think
the noodle restaurant is still open?
Have a try. Just...
Eat slowly. Okay?
What would you like to eat?
- Pork liver noodles?
- I'll have pork liver noodles.
Okay, I'll order it.
Bro.
I'll have two bowls
of pork liver noodles.
(Brother)
- Okay. - One spicy
and one not spicy.
All right, just a minute.
(I'll be home soon.)
(Don't bother me.)
It'll be ready soon. Wait a minute.
The not spicy noodles are for you.
You just had surgery.
You'd better not eat spicy food.
Do you also like vinegar?
Do you want some more?
There you go. Okay.
(Brother)
Come on, let's get you home.
Get on.
Sit well.
Yuan.
Where have you been?
Why are you back so late?
Brother.
You're still up.
You hung up on me.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous it is
for a girl to be out alone
this late at night?
If you're back any later,
I'm gonna call the police.
Brother.
When are you gonna
find a sister-in-law for me?
Why do you mention that all of a sudden?
Yuan.
Hey.
Is she going through a rebellious phase?
Thank you, Grandma Qin.
Thank you, Mr. Luo.
You're welcome.
Well done.
In this way,
you're the one who saved Mr. Fang's son.
The legal counsel of the Fangqin Group
will definitely be you.
Mr. Fang didn't say anything about that.
Mr. Fang owes you a big one.
It's only a matter of time for him
to return your favor.
We can't count on favors
to reach a deal.
I know,
but humans are
emotional animals.
What's happening right now
reminds me of the time
when we had our first case.
Was I really stupid
at that time?
I believed that God rewards
those who work hard,
and I could succeed
as long as I work hard.
But the truth is
it's all about
the right place at the right time.
Sometimes,
luck is also part of strength.
At that time,
He and Gao Junchi told me about
your glorious deeds all the time.
They did like
your dedication and persistence.
You were always the first one to come
and the last one to leave.
You also squatted downstairs,
eating instant noodles
and going through the info.
I remember
your first case
was against
the most famous attorney.
Everybody thought
you were gonna lose.
Even the client
asked He to replace you.
Gao Junchi was ready
to take the case over,
but you convinced He
on your own.
You got the evidence
and won the case.
That's why
Gao Junchi and I
started a feud.
But seriously,
the reason I chose you
to be my partner
instead of Gao Junchi
is because I thought
you had a more promising future.
Well,
I hope you're not disappointed.
Of course not.
You exceeded my expectations.
That's all for today's training.
Dismiss!
Bro, your wife is here.
Are you here to pick up Dapeng?
Good to see you.
Darling.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to see Captain Ruan.
Wait, why would you want to see her?
Just go. Go home.
Don't touch me. Get out of my way!
You brat.
Have you been a jerk again?
Have some water.
All these years,
I've been supporting him
no matter what he does,
but he doesn't
care about me
nor our family anymore.
I think we should
get a divorce.
I understand.
Is it because
Dapeng has been on mission too often?
Well,
I'll talk to him.
Dapeng.
- Your wife is really pissed.
- I'll ask him not to take every task.
You have to take this seriously.
As for the tutoring thing,
you should ask her to let it go.
Even a professor at Peking University
might not be able
to get his child into Peking University.
Right?
All right. Stop listening.
Come on, let's go.
Let's hear it for a while.
Take care.
He broke my heart.
Well...
Just coax her.
I'm not
a selfish person.
I just can't figure out
how come a man
who can't even take care
of his own family
has the right to save other people?
You're right.
Our principle
is that participating
in non-profit rescue
requires the support of one's family.
How about this,
we will make Dapeng
take a month off
and keep him away
from rescue missions and training.
No.
That's not what I meant.
I won't quit the rescue team.
Dapeng.
You must obey
our order in this matter.
It was my fault
that I forgot our wedding anniversary.
It was also my fault that I failed
to help you with the housework.
But now that we're married,
you can't bring up divorce.
This is the lipstick
you failed to snap up
in the online studio last time.
It was the last one in the mall.
I bought it.
It's too expensive in the mall.
So what?
As long as my wife likes it,
I would buy it no matter
how expensive it is.
(Light Chaser Rescue)
♪ The world had no sorrow at first ♪
♪ Until fate came along ♪
♪ The soul never knew about wandering ♪
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
♪ All the good times
belong to the light ♪
♪ It will light up the scars later on ♪
♪ Catching the starlight ♪
♪ Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city ♪
♪ With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly ♪
♪ But I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪