♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ Chasing the future with passion
like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
♪ Living in the vast ocean of time ♪
♪ I'm trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity
and lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
=Light Chaser Rescue=
=Episode 40=
Help her.
Hurry. Go.
Zhan Yan!
Dr. Zhan!
- Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan!
Are you there?
Xiong Fei, Xiong Fei.
We have found Zhan Yan.
Captain Xiong Fei,
we can't go any further.
The storm is coming.
Are you not afraid to die?
Yes.
We are all afraid.
But our teammates
are waiting for us.
We're like family.
If it was your family trapped inside,
would you not keep going?
But you don't have
to advance with us.
Just turn back.
Let's keep moving.
(Linjiang Central Hospital
Examination Report)
Wait for me.
I'm willing
to risk my life.
Without me,
the advancement would take longer.
Follow me, brother.
Thank you.
Follow me!
Watch out.
Are you okay?
Keep going.
OK.
Is the rope fixed?
In a minute.
The storm is crazy.
If it goes on,
you will die.
We'd better take shelter for now.
If I don't descend now,
the one down there
will be in greater danger.
Mr. Lordan,
you take Dr. Cai and the others
to find shelter.
OK.
Luo Ben.
Zhan Yan, hang in there.
Be safe, Luo Ben.
Is it ready?
Luo Ben,
the cordage is ready.
OK.
Luo Ben, be safe.
Zhan Yan.
Zhan Yan, wake up.
It's me, Luo Ben.
I'm here to save you.
Come on.
How do you feel?
Luo Ben…
It's me.
Is it a dream?
No, it's not a dream.
It's me.
I'm here.
Hang in there.
Come on.
Drink some hot water.
Easy.
So?
Feeling better?
I thought I'd never see you again.
No.
I'll get you out soon.
Captain,
he's expecting you
at home.
Zhan Yan.
Zhan Yan, stay awake.
Zhan Yan!
Zhan Yan, you know what?
After you left,
I made many phone calls to you.
Why didn't you pick them up?
I always wanted you to know
that I care
about the past,
but what I care
about more
is you, Zhan Yan.
I can't afford to lose you.
Zhan Yan, hang in there.
I'll take you out now.
Stay strong.
Watch out!
How do you feel?
Are you okay?
Come on.
Pull!
Very close!
Easy.
Be careful.
How are you, Zhan Yan?
I'm okay.
Good. Let's go.
Luo Ben! Luo Ben! Luo Ben!
Are you alright?
I'm good.
We'll get you out now.
OK.
I'm coming up.
Watch out! Fall back!
How is it?
Don't worry.
Guoguo's operation was a success.
You get some rest.
She'll be out soon.
Thank you, doctor.
Perfect.
Mrs. Zhang,
I just received the message.
Dapeng has been sent
to the hospital.
Don't worry.
He'll be okay.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Zhan Yan.
Don't worry.
They have gone to Luo Ben's rescue.
He'll be fine.
You listen to me.
Conserve your energy.
I will treat
your wound later,
or you'll get frostbite.
Luo Ben!
Luo Ben, can you hear me?
He should be down there.
Xiong Fei,
it isn't working.
We can't break the ice.
I must get him out.
Xiong Fei, calm down.
Xiong Fei.
You have to try, don't you?
Do you have any other ways?
Xiong Fei,
Luo Ben's life is in danger.
I, too, want to save him.
But the ice is too thick.
No way you're gonna break the ice.
Xiong Fei.
Get up!
Xiong Fei!
Luo Ben's in peril.
You're in charge.
Xiong Fei, have you found him?
Yes.
Dapeng and Zhan Yan are both safe.
Excellent.
Good work.
Xiong Fei,
on your way back,
make sure you're safe.
Captain,
Luo Ben…
What?
He got Zhan Yan out,
but he didn't make it out.
What?
He's fallen into a deeper place.
The entrance is blocked by ice.
It's all on me.
I…
I failed to protect my teammate.
Xiong Fei,
now is not the time
to blame yourself.
Luo Ben is trapped in a crevasse.
You gotta work out a method
to get him out.
Dad.
Yan.
You'll listen to Xiong Fei.
Tears are pointless at the moment.
Just level with me.
What are the chances?
Yan,
the survival rate
of a crevasse rescue
is very low,
but it is not
entirely hopeless.
(Judging from the falling time,)
(I should be under snow layer.)
(I'll most likely reach
an underground river.)
(Where there's a way,)
(there's hope.)
He's right there.
There must be a way
to get him out.
The chance seems slim to me.
Because the crevasse
is completely sealed.
I say
he's fallen into hell.
No.
There must be another way.
Even if we can get him out,
it's unlikely that he'll be alive.
He sacrifices his life.
And it's so high.
He trades his life for someone else's.
It's a real honor.
I won't leave him here.
Even if he's dead,
we'll get his dead body out.
Yan.
One English mountain climber
fell into a crevasse
on the Andes Mountain.
But he didn't give up.
168 hours.
He fought 168 hours.
Eventually,
he got out of the crevasse
and returned to the camp.
Sure,
I admit it's a miracle.
Yan, any news?
Dad,
what do the curved lines
stand for on the map?
Let me see.
Rivers, I suppose.
Rivers?
Yes.
The ice and snow melt
into rivers,
becoming the sources
of other rivers or streams.
Yan,
there may be underground rivers
beneath the crevasse.
What has occurred to you, Dad?
We have been looking for openings
above the crevasse,
hoping that Luo Ben will climb out.
But would it be possible
that he's going downward?
Going downward?
Once he finds an underground river,
he'll follow its direction
and get out of the snow mountain.
Yes.
There's still hope.
Mrs. Ruan,
do you think it's possible
that Luo Ben can be found
through my cousin's method?
It's theoretically feasible.
If they'll have more helpers tomorrow,
the chance should be higher.
Yuan, what are you doing here?
Neither my brother nor Xiong Fei
replied to my messages,
so I had to come.
What's going on?
Your brother
fell into a crevasse during the rescue.
We can't get hold of him.
What happened?
How did he fall into a crevasse?
My brother…
Yuan, calm down. Listen to me.
Now, everybody's working together
to find him.
We think
that no news
is the best news.
Trust me,
everything will be fine.
There, there.
Yes, Mr. Wang.
Local guides, villagers.
The more, the better.
Find every river
within the 3-kilometer radius
around the crevasse,
and go upstream.
If they find any clue,
notify us immediately.
OK.
We'll be on the move.
Bring a drone for the search.
- Yes, sir.
Luo Ben.
Keep going.
Don't give up.
You will get out of here.
Zhan Yan is waiting for you.
You must get out of here alive.
Alive.
We…
We go this way up.
Everybody,
you must be careful.
Don't be reckless, okay?
Thanks.
Is everyone ready?
- Yes.
We must be extra careful
during the night search.
Follow your guides closely.
You mustn't be separated.
Perform an inch-by-inch search.
Keep in touch.
- OK.
- OK. Got it.
Action!
You take a break.
The guide and I will check
the way ahead.
I'll come with you.
Me, too.
You have searched
the whole snow mountain
for the entire night.
Still no luck.
I think his chance of survival
is very slim.
He'd have no chance of survival
if we gave up.
The river is frozen.
Even if we can find
all the entrances along the river,
we'll still end up
getting his dead body.
But at least, we gotta have a try.
Sometimes, you have to resign to fate.
I never resign to fate.
Nor do I believe that fate exists.
Let's go.
♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ I yearn for the Milky Way ♪
♪ Like a night watchman ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
Wait.
Our team badge.
That's our team badge.
Quickly. Go upstream.
Go.
Over there.
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
I know you're worried about
Zhan Yan and Luo Ben,
but you need to eat something.
I'm not hungry.
♪ Become the light ♪
Dad, we found something.
We think Luo Ben's still alive.
Good.
Perfect.
♪ We rely on us ♪
Luo Ben!
- Luo Ben!
- Luo Ben! Luo Ben!
♪ Chasing the future with passion ♪
♪ Like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read the universe
and the stars ♪
- Luo Ben!
- Luo Ben! Luo Ben!
Luo Ben!
♪ With the brief warmth ♪
♪ I' m trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid
of the truth when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity ♪
♪ And lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
(Half a year later)
♪ I believe in sincerity and kindness ♪
♪ All those who are trudging
will finally find peace ♪
(Xiong Fei)
Xiong Fei.
♪ Courage will take us
to leap over the waves ♪
♪ My dream is burning ♪
♪ Is boiling ♪
Hello.
Where are you?
We need you
to host the recruit welcome ceremony.
Hurry up.
Are you tired?
Sit down for a while.
Your brother will come soon.
Come on, welcome gift
for every entrant.
Good.
Come on, everybody gets one.
Take a good look.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're welcome.
I read this book before.
It's a best seller.
Cool, right?
My girlfriend drew it.
Really?
Awesome.
It's published, huh?
Let me see.
Let me have one.
Am I cool in it?
I want one.
I want one, too.
Stay in order.
- Dapeng.
Hey, you guys.
Dapeng.
Hi, Mrs. Zhang.
It's for you.
Guoguo, you're so cool.
You're the youngest member
on the rescue team.
I will make a special edition
just for you, okay?
Say okay, baby girl.
Okay.
So cute.
I made a mistake
and left the team,
but you see?
My baby girl takes over my career.
Show-off.
Dapeng, behave well,
and return to the team,
or I'll portray you
as a super villain.
All right, all right.
You win.
Producer Zhou,
your film is a hit.
Can Guoguo play
a role in it?
No problem.
Guoguo is going to be a superstar.
She's shy.
How are the recruits?
So-so.
They can't
compare with us!
Cheeky.
You keep bragging.
♪ The world had no sorrow at first♪
Captain.
Everybody's here.
Yan will return soon, right?
How time flies.
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
Let's welcome the recruits!
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
Attention!
I hereby vow.
That I volunteer
to join Light Chaser Rescue.
By the spirit of volunteerism
of devotion, love, and mutual help.
I shall be assiduous.
And train hard.
I shall try my best to save lives
in face of all kinds of disasters.
The end.
Now, you'll divide into groups.
Dismiss.
♪ Words disregarded feelings at first ♪
Those who want to learn rappelling,
follow me.
Underwater rescue,
Rescue equipment,
follow me.
♪ People had no hometown at first ♪
♪ Till the road led to the distance ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Give you my shoulder
because I was once lonely ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
This is for you.
Will you meet again?
I told you
that we'd meet again.
♪ I hope the river wind
sweeps through the alley ♪
♪ May you have peace ♪
♪ May you be with those who you love
and those who love you ♪
♪ Look back on the past and feel calm ♪
♪ Catching the starlight
Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city
With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly, but I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪
(As our country's socio-economy develops
and people's living standard progresses,)
(along with the continuous
improvement of civic moral construction)
(and the public's awareness of
self-rescue and mutual rescue,)
(the emergency volunteer operation,
the two-century goal,)
(and building a modern socialist country)
(have become a significant symbol of the
social civilization progress.)
(Nongovernmental emergency rescue)
(has become a supporting force
in the national emergency rescue field.)
(It is the vivid demonstration
of the vision of the people)
(having faith, the country having
power, and the nation having hope.)
♪ The world had no sorrow at first ♪
♪ Until fate came along ♪
♪ The soul never knew about wandering ♪
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
♪ All the good times
belong to the light ♪
♪ It will light up the scars later on ♪
♪ Catching the starlight ♪
♪ Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city ♪
♪ With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly ♪
♪ But I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪