♪ I'm the proud foam amongst the waves ♪
♪ Fighting mountain fires
and catching sunsets ♪
♪ Although frustration in life lingers ♪
♪ I still remember the good times ♪
♪ Chasing the future with passion
like a dreamer ♪
♪ I look up and read
the universe and the stars ♪
♪ Living in the vast ocean of time ♪
♪ I'm trying to be a ray of light ♪
♪ If the world gives me a bad start ♪
♪ I'll be like a dark horse
to get it back ♪
♪ I won't be afraid of the truth
when I know it ♪
♪ I won't give in to mediocrity
and lose the moon ♪
♪ And the light ♪
=Light Chaser Rescue=
=Episode 29=
Zhuangzhuang.
Is school out?
You haven't been home for three years.
Go home with Mom this time.
Yeah.
I'll go home.
Go home.
Mom.
I'm Zhuangzhuang.
I'm your son.
Lanzhi.
He's Zhuangzhuang.
I'm Zhuangzhuang.
Zhuangzhuang?
No.
He's not.
Lanzhi,
you lost your memory.
He is Zhuangzhuang.
You saw his picture
on the hospital's wall, didn't you?
Picture?
Yes, Mom.
Look,
I'm Zhuangzhuang.
It's me.
(Cai Yuxiao)
I'm your son, Mom.
You don't even remember me.
Useless me.
I always forget that you've grown up.
I'm sorry, Mom…
- Zhuangzhuang.
- That you're ill.
Mom,
you're in the hospital now.
Don't worry.
The doctor will cure you.
You'll be okay.
I…
I believe you, Son.
Luo Ben.
I thank you
for this.
You take care of your mother.
I have decided to quit my job
to look after my mother.
The project in Fengxi,
Zhan Yan and I both value it.
Now that she's got the opportunity,
I congratulate her.
She's going to Fengxi?
Have some vegetables.
Dr. Cai said
he'd quit his job
to look after his parents.
He's worked so hard for so long.
It's a shame that he quit.
What would
your choice be?
You have made your
choice already, right?
You know?
If I didn't learn it from Cai Yuxiao,
you'd tell me
when you're in Fengxi, right?
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
I didn't make up my mind
at the time.
Then we could have had a discussion,
not like now,
it has become a notification.
This is a very precious
opportunity for me.
So you thought
I'd stop you
after you told me?
I don't mean that.
I…
I just wasn't sure
how to tell you this.
Zhan Yan,
I want to live with you.
I want to be able to see you
whenever I miss you.
But in the meantime,
I'll support
your pursuit of career.
A long-distance relationship
won't be a problem
for me.
It is my fault.
Why did you make the decision
without talking to me?
You really thought
I'd forbid you?
I see.
My feelings
are only your burden.
It looks like,
as a boyfriend,
I'm not good enough.
All right, let's keep eating.
I'll drive you home after dinner.
See? I told you
to talk to him about it.
You see
how difficult it is now?
No wonder he's mad at you.
You know what's unacceptable
for men?
What's unacceptable for them
is that women don't value them.
It is my fault.
But he doesn't have to be so mad.
You're a single-minded person.
I'm not surprised
that you are inconsiderate.
Am I?
What a dumb question.
You are!
You're so bad at dealing with
human relations.
What's your suggestion?
Am I supposed to give up?
Yes, that's what I mean.
Is that really necessary?
He's mad about me not telling him.
He said he'd support me.
And you believed it?
Men don't mean
what they say.
Just talk to him.
(Resignation Letter Cai Yuxiao)
Yuxiao's left.
And you
will go to Fengxi with Professor Koben.
Two core doctors are gone,
which puts me in a bad situation.
Considering the reality of the hospital,
I want you to stay.
However,
it is a rare opportunity to participate in
Professor Koben's project.
I hope you take this chance
and learn as much as possible.
I will.
Have you turned over
your duties?
I have.
What about your life?
Will going to Fengxi
cause any problems?
Just tell me.
Maybe the hospital can help.
No problem.
Hello, your package.
OK. Thank you.
Is there an end?
All packages are here?
Y-You bought all these?
What are you doing?
I'm about to leave.
I bought you
some clothes for the season changes.
You'll be away for years?
I'm not there yet.
I'm not sure.
Alright. I got it.
Thanks anyway.
Anything else?
Can you not act like this?
I will come home whenever I can.
What a happy life I live.
My girlfriend buys me
clothes for all year
before she leaves.
Can we have a normal conversation?
You're leaving.
What else can I say?
You're home.
Brother.
Why did you buy all these clothes?
I didn't.
Zhan Yan did.
You had a fight?
(Zhan Yan,)
(I'll have my
wedding pictures taken tomorrow.)
(Can you come and help me?)
(Luo Yuan)
Yuan,
I may run late.
How about you start without me?
We'll take some more over there.
Look here.
Very good.
You can be more relaxed, lady.
Groom, get closer.
Get closer, yes.
Bend down, yes, yes.
Together.
Good. Let's take this one.
Lower. Yes.
Good.
Smile, lady.
Smile.
Yes. Good, good.
Yes. Very good.
Yuan.
What are you doing here?
Luo Yuan asked me to come.
Yuan said
that you must be here
when we take the pictures.
They will take pictures
of us together.
Groom and bride.
We'll take the second one.
Go.
I see you're not busy.
I thought
you'd have a lot to pack.
I started packing a long ago.
I'll be there for three years.
I'll need to take a lot with me.
Is that so?
Well,
I'll certainly see you off.
You don't have to, if you're busy.
Many of my colleagues
are going to see me off.
Why didn't you tell Luo Yuan
that you'd go to Fengxi?
She takes you for a good friend.
She can see you off, too.
Luo Yuan is your sister.
Why didn't you tell her
that you've been acting like
you'll break up with me
after knowing I'm going to Fengxi?
You shouldn't keep it from her.
Come on.
Closer.
Yes.
Head.
Lean towards…
Yes, yes.
Good.
Great. Come on.
Try another pose.
Hey, dresser,
fix the bride's make-up.
Wipe off her sweat.
OK. Good. Good.
Luo Yuan seems very happy.
Yes.
She wants us to have her best wishes.
But she would never have thought
we'd be separated soon.
We won't if you don't want to.
So it's my fault, then?
It is my fault
that I didn't talk to you about it.
But are you sure
you share no responsibility at all?
You did the wrong thing first
and here you're blaming me?
Do we need to draw a timeline?
Don't you make it look like
you're completely innocent.
Don't you change the subject.
I'm talking
about your project in Fengxi.
And I'm talking about your attitude.
What's wrong with my attitude?
You think you have a nice attitude?
Do I not have a nice attitude?
Go get some rest.
Yuan, you look beautiful.
Guys,
please stand in position.
So
we can save a lot of time.
Go stand in position.
You go.
Go.
Closer.
Yes, get closer, please.
Yes. Good, very good.
Look at me. Look at the camera.
Keep smiling.
Good.
Change your pose.
Listen,
back to back.
Back to back.
Backs attached.
Good. Hold still.
Smile.
When will you leave?
After their wedding on the 7th.
Great.
Another pose.
How about
you stand face to face?
Get closer, sir.
A bit closer.
Face to face.
Arm on her waist.
Arm on the lady's waist.
Closer, closer.
Yes, closer.
Good, good. That's it.
Hold still, please.
Eyes.
Don't be so uptight.
Relax. Smile.
Yes, sweet smiles.
Please,
over there.
Good.
Now, look at me.
Smile.
Wait a minute.
I'd like them
to be in our pictures, is that okay?
Sure.
Come on. Come over.
You'll be in the pictures together.
Closer.
Good.
Another pose.
Come on.
You and Zhan Yan
are having a fight, huh?
It is her fault.
Be the bigger man.
As if you have
much experience.
No, I…
I learned all my experience
with Luo Yuan.
That's more like it.
I only asked for half a day off.
I'll go back to the hospital soon.
I'll take a cab.
He's an idiot.
Don't sulk.
I'm not any better than him.
I went to see Ding Dingding.
Mom,
it's so busy at the company.
Your workload is heavy.
Why did you go to see her?
If I hadn't,
you would have gotten married,
no?
No way.
I'd ask for your approval first.
So you did plan to?
I tell you what,
I won't allow it.
Why, Mom?
Do you hold any
misunderstanding against her?
Misunderstanding?
She always talks me back.
She's uncultured,
and undereducated.
You are the only one
who falls for her.
You're attracted
to her face, aren't you?
Yes, she does look pretty.
No, no.
It's true that she makes illogical
and wild speeches,
but she
has a good heart, Mom.
Stop saying good things about her.
Listen to me, Mingming.
You're out of her league.
I told you so many times
to date a girl
with good qualities.
A girl with good qualities
has to grow
in a good family.
These good qualities
don't develop in one day or two.
Mom,
her parents
are college professors.
And those college professors
raised a girl like her?
Stop. Stop.
Dingding.
What are you doing here?
Why didn't you pick up my call?
I was drawing.
I muted my cellphone.
Are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be okay?
I just learned that my mom
spoke to you.
Why didn't you tell me?
Your mom's little trick
couldn't work on me.
I grew up outsmarting
my parents.
She looks down on me now,
but it doesn't mean
she won't change her mind later.
Am I right?
I'm sorry.
I apologize to you on behalf of my mom.
Don't say sorry.
I just adjusted my mindset.
Your apology softened my heart.
And I don't want to be soft-hearted.
Attagirl.
Oh, right.
If your mother ever picks on me again,
I'll give you a hard time,
do you hear me?
Sure.
You said it.
Promise?
Promise.
What if you regret it?
Well, you'll give me
a hard time, won't you?
Are you serious?
Yes. Bring it on.
Come on.
Ouch.
Still hasn't arrived.
Are you sure it's today?
What time is it?
No rush.
Maybe it's just the traffic.
Could it be
that she doesn't know the way?
I'd better go find her.
Yeah, we'll go with you.
Come on.
Dad.
Mom.
You're home.
Your brother worried
that you didn't know the way home.
How could I forget the way home?
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
Good.
Glad you're home.
Your mom and I
will cook two more dishes.
Don't stand out here.
Xiong Fei,
take your sister home.
Go.
Come on.
Get inside.
Sister.
Welcome home.
You're still thin.
Take this.
What are you doing?
I don't need it.
I was abroad for years.
I didn't take good care
of you and our parents.
Now that you're getting married,
this is the least
that your sister can give to you.
Sister, I sell wontons now.
I can provide for the family.
I appreciate your goodwill.
But I won't take the money.
The steamed fish is here.
Here, Mom.
Be careful, it's hot.
Careful.
Come on.
Thank you, Mom.
Xiong Fei's getting married.
Xiong Dan's home.
It's double happiness,
double joy
for our family.
Yes.
Today,
we'll have a drink.
I'll fill you up.
Let me. Let me.
Thank you, Dad.
Dad, I didn't know you had this.
When did you buy this?
Your dad bought one
when you were born,
and another bottle
when your brother was born.
Did you?
He said he'd open it
when you got married.
You have some, too.
Easy, easy.
Here.
Happy marriage to Fei,
and a better future to Dan.
Great.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you, Dad, Mom.
- Thank you, Mom.
- Good health to you.
Cheers.
Good.
Let me. Let me.
You keep drinking with Dad.
We are bad drinkers.
Your mother sure is.
Pour some for your sister.
A little. Just a little.
We'll take six sets of pictures.
Not a small amount.
So
you'll keep smiling.
Sure.
I'll teach you the poses.
Just follow my instructions.
Sir.
Hi.
I'd like to know
if you have saved
our pictures on the computer?
Those pictures?
I'm sorry.
Your pictures
were to serve
as reference
for the groom and the bride,
so I deleted them.
Sure. No problem.
Wait.
I remember.
The man
with you,
he made a copy of every picture
on that day.
You can ask him.
The groom?
No.
The bride's brother.
(Business Management Service Contract)
Any problem with the contract?
No.
I'll print it.
What's the matter?
Nothing, but can't we talk?
Talk to someone else.
I'm busy.
Are we bros or not?
You won't tell me
that you're getting married?
Who's getting married?
How do you explain this?
Nothing to explain.
Won't you defend yourself,
Attorney Luo?
I guess it's happening, huh?
Luckily, I made a copy.
Enough of this.
Give me that.
Why so serious?
It's a good thing.
I'm happy for you.
I know you want me
to have the red packet.
But be patient.
You seize the opportunity,
and kill Ai Rui'er's hope
the sooner the better.
What are you talking about?
Go finish your work.
What's on your mind?
I don't know what my mother
will do with me.
It always intrigues me.
Your mom's like that,
so life mustn't be easy
for your dad, right?
My dad has gotten used to her
over the years.
How did your dad
fall in love with your mom?
My mom chased my dad, actually.
My mother's family disapproved
their marriage.
Because my dad
was just an insignificant reporter.
A reporter?
Did your dad
learn some illegal transactions,
and helped the police solve the case,
so your mother
fell for your dad
and married him?
Your head
is full of wild thoughts.
But
your mother really strikes
as a snob.
After they got married
and started up their business,
my dad was busy
covering stories out there.
He'd be away from home for months.
My mom undertook
the entire business.
The company
started to make money,
and then grew bigger and bigger.
My mother sacrificed a lot.
I get it.
Your mother
thinks her success
can be copied
after what she lived through.
See?
She has
this idler son like you
in the family.
She thinks
only a girl as good as herself
can be a match for you.
So that
you will achieve something.
It looks like
I am out of your league.
Don't worry.
I'm not like my dad.
I will take responsibility,
and I will protect you.
Louder. I didn't hear you.
I said, I will protect you.
Louder.
Come on.
Look at all the people here. Knock it off.
It's fine. Come on.
I said!
I will protect you.
OK. Fine.
Focus on your comic.
What is this?
My boyfriend.
(My Boyfriend)
Is this how I look?
Yeah.
Very handsome.
Redraw me.
You have no clue.
This is abstractionism.
Redraw me. Now.
I won't. Listen to me.
You will hang it on the wall
and frame it.
You will frame it, do you hear me?
Will you redraw me or not?
No, I won't.
Again, will you?
I will not.
Come on.
No. You pitch me!
Come on. Redraw me, quickly.
(Happiness)
Look.
Is it in the middle?
Yes.
Everything seems good.
Thank you, Sister.
Not at all.
After you're married,
you'll be nice to your wife.
Trust me, I will.
You'd better hurry up
and start to see someone, too.
Well…
What will be will be.
Yuan,
I won't be seeing you
in the morning anymore.
He's coming.
Look.
- Congrats.
Looks smart.
Best wishes to you.
- Go!
- Best wishes to you.
- Thanks.
Bro.
Hey, Guoguo.
Look.
Does he look smart?
Yes.
Yes?
He's the best, right?
Yes.
How about your dad?
He's the second.
I'm the second?
You little traitor.
Guoguo's the prettiest, right?
No, the bride is the prettiest.
I'm the second.
Bro, are you ready?
The bride is coming.
Yes.
Go, bro.
- Go for it.
- Go, go, go.
Go forth.
Xiong Fei.
- Go.
- Go, go, go.
You're gorgeous.
Relatives and friends.
My dear brothers.
I'm honored
to be here
witnessing
the wedding
of these two lovely ones.
Now, I announce
that the ceremony begins.
Yes!
Now, our groom Xiong Fei,
will get on stage.
Yes! Nice!
The groom
will walk up to his
most beautiful bride.
♪ I want to be a star ♪
Xiong Fei.
I'm now handing
Luo Yuan over to you.
♪ How does dream become lighter ♪
Xiong Fei.
You must take good care of her.
Brother,
trust me.
I will take good care of her.
♪ Like the shadow of a white dove ♪
Go, Yuan.
♪ You smile at me like in my dream ♪
♪ To be alone with passion ♪
♪ To shine with sincerity ♪
♪ I think I'm a star ♪
♪ That only shines on you ♪
♪ The world is lighting up ♪
♪ Glistening teardrops reflect love ♪
♪ Two free minds ♪
♪ Embrace and be the world ♪
Yuan looks so nice
in her wedding dress.
What, you want it, too?
You seem eager to marry me.
In your dreams.
It is a very
exciting day.
We'll give our best wishes
to the couple with our applause.
Congrats!
The people on the left,
you clapped hard.
I wish you a wonderful future!
Brilliant!
The people on the right
clapped with much enthusiasm.
I wish you a wonderful life!
Thanks!
When will you leave tomorrow?
I'll see you off.
At least, I'll bid you goodbye.
12 o'clock at noon.
OK.
(Fengtou Village Pit Rescue)
What's the matter?
It's none of your business.
Now, the groom
will tell us
how he managed
to steal the heart
of our beautiful Miss Luo Yuan.
Captain,
I know the pit in Fengtou Village.
It's very deep.
Only you
and Xiong Fei
have pit-rescue experience.
But it's
Xiong Fei's big day.
I'll lead the team.
When we're there,
we'll work out
a detailed plan.
Yes, sir.
Mr. groom,
do you need time to think?
It looks like your love story…
Wasn't so smooth…
Dingding, Mingming.
You'll be here with them.
Captain,
I sign myself up.
No, you don't.
Your job today
is to be the groom.
Only I have the experience
for a pit over 300 meters deep.
I must go.
I'm sure Yuan supports me.
Captain,
let him go.
OK.
Dapeng.
Go for it, daddy.
You'll leave tomorrow.
I may not be
there to see you off.
Be safe.
It's fine.
I'm off.
Take care.
OK.
Yuan.
Go.
I'll wait.
Family and friends.
I'm really sorry,
but we just got an emergency message,
and we'll have to go on this mission.
The wedding
will end now.
Please accept my apology.
People may die.
He has to go.
Wait for me to come back.
(Light Chaser Rescue)
All right.
Please back up, everybody.
Back up. Back up.
Back up.
This is it.
Get ready.
Here is Yuncheng Road.
Here is Miaoshanqian Village.
And this is Fengtou Village Pit.
The victim's parents called for aid.
The victim is named Hong Wei.
(Liu Wenbin Member of the CPC)
27 years old.
(Director of Provincial Rescue Coordination)
He and his friend
went to climb the mountain.
The road was slippery after the rain
at night,
so Hong Wei fell into the pit.
Any information about the pit?
It is the largest,
and the most dangerous pit
(Fengtou Village Pit Planar Graph)
around the area.
It's over 300 meters in depth.
You're the pit-rescue experts,
so you'll be the main force,
and we'll be supporting you.
OK.
Everything's on the blackboard.
You know what you gotta do.
This is an arduous one.
Even Director Liu is here
directing the mission.
We'll divide into two groups.
Xiong Fei and I, group 1.
Group 2,
Luo Ben, Dapeng.
- Yes, sir.
It's a deep pit.
We don't know what's down there.
We can't go down there at one go.
It'll be segmented descent.
Safety points will
be set along the descent.
Xiong Fei will take the special cordage,
and other necessary equipment.
I will go down first.
You will assist me.
Captain,
I have a stronger body.
I will go down first.
Captain,
I apply to
pair up with Xiong Fei,
and we'll descend together.
Captain, I…
Stop. Follow my order.
All right.
Go get ready.
- Yes, sir.
- Wei.
- Son.
Please save my son!
You must get him out!
We'll do our best.
He is still alive!
OK. OK.
We'll do the best we can.
I promise we will.
Xiong Fei,
I'll go down first.
Son.
Wei.
No. 1 reporting.
I am now 20 meters
deep in the pit.
All clear.
No. 2, descend.
Copy.
Xiong Fei,
be safe.
Luo Yuan is waiting.
Sure.
No. 1 reporting. No. 1 reporting.
We are now
50 meters deep in the pit.
No victim spotted.
Request for further descent.
Affirmative.
- Keep going.
- Yeah.
♪ The world had no sorrow at first ♪
♪ Until fate came along ♪
♪ The soul never knew about wandering ♪
♪ Until people embraced each other ♪
♪ I'm always on the road ♪
♪ Trying to bring laughter
and tears together ♪
♪ Suddenly I have faith ♪
♪ That every home can be shone upon ♪
♪ I hope there are flowers
to enjoy in the sunset ♪
♪ Tears are only for happy reunions ♪
♪ All the good times
belong to the light ♪
♪ It will light up the scars later on ♪
♪ Catching the starlight ♪
♪ Watching memories shine ♪
♪ Traveling through the city ♪
♪ With sincere eyes ♪
♪ I can't fly ♪
♪ But I can look up ♪
♪ I'm always on the road
chasing the light ♪