=The Silent Wife=
=Episode 1=
(You Don't Deserve to Bear My Child)
(Chiyan.)
(That accident cost your memory.)
(You forgot our past.)
(Qiutong tried to save you.)
Chiyan, be careful.
(And fell into a coma.)
(As long as you need it,)
(I can sustain her with my blood)
(until she wakes up.)
(For three years,)
(you've been taking me around)
(as your secretary,
hiding the fact that we're married.)
(I don't blame you.)
(You've lost your memory.)
(It's okay.)
(I will make you remember me.)
Trying to seduce me
when I'm drunk again?
Three years ago,
you and your mom forced me to marry you
with such despicable means.
You're playing the same tricks again?
Speak.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I forgot
you are mute.
(No, Chiyan.)
(Let me explain.)
(I made hangover soup for you.)
Song Qinian.
I've told you long ago
that I will never fall in love
with a wicked woman like you.
(If none of that had happened,)
(we wouldn't have ended up like this.)
Look at the willow catkin.
It's barging lustfully
into the room just like you.
You wait for me
to come home every night,
dressed like this.
Isn't it just for that?
Since you've been plotting it,
I'll give you what you want.
Untie it.
(Why can't I say "no")
(when I see his face?)
(It's been three years,)
(and we still haven't resolved
the misunderstanding between us.)
(But I am willing to wait)
(for another chance.)
♪Need to smooth out the temper♪
♪Need words that are crafted finely♪
(Hospital)
Hello.
Yeah, it's me.
What's wrong with Qiutong?
Okay.
Be right there.
Qiutong needs a blood transfusion.
Come with me.
(My dad fell ill.)
(He needs medical parole.)
(Please help me.)
Medical parole?
If Song Guanliang
hadn't kidnapped Qiutong
for money,
she wouldn't be bedridden
for three years.
Your family is in debt to her.
(He is wrongly accused.)
If you don't want your dad
to die in prison,
just do as I say.
If anything happens to Qiutong today,
I'll make your whole family pay.
It's not up to you
whether to come with me.
Mr. Shen.
This mute really has no shame.
(She climbed onto Mr. Shen's bed)
(when he was drunk.)
(Exactly.)
(If Miss Lin hadn't fallen into a coma,)
(trying to save him,)
(how would this woman be allowed here?)
(Just watch.)
(The day Miss Lin wakes up,)
(this woman will be ousted.)
(Chiyan, have you forgotten)
(all your promises to me?)
(No matter where I am,)
(as long as you blow this whistle,)
(I'll show up by your side.)
(I will be your voice.)
(How can we go back
to how things were before?)
Mr. Shen, Mrs. Shen left her phone
in the kitchen.
It's been ringing. It seems urgent.
Song Qinian.
What is going on right now?
It's been three years
and you still have no kids?
Think of something.
Or you might be kicked out
of the Shen family.
Remember.
Your only advantage is your good looks.
Try to conceive Shen Chiyan's child
so that he doesn't divorce you.
You want to have my child?
You and your family
should give up on that.
To the hospital.
Hurry.
Mr. Shen.
You brought Ms. Song
for another blood transfusion?
Yeah.
Miss Song.
Can you handle
a 300cc of blood transfusion?
It's fine.
It's not the first time.
Miss Lin is so lucky.
She has such a rare blood type
and Miss Song happens to have it too.
(She is indeed lucky.)
(But what about me?)
Please go ahead.
Okay.
Miss Song.
It's an emergency.
Only you can save Miss Lin now.
Qiutong.
How are you doing?
Mr. Shen.
What's wrong?
A message came from the prison.
Mrs. Shen's dad
developed an acute illness.
Dr. Chen wants to know...
Hush.
Qiutong is not doing so well.
Song Guanliang can wait.
I know you have concerns.
But the Lin family...
Mrs. Shen.
Song Qinian.
Calm down.
Don't get worked up.
Let's talk it out.
Okay, I'll stay here.
(Save my dad.)
Are you threatening me?
Song Qinian.
Take a good look at Qiutong.
She could have had
a completely different life.
But your father ruined that chance.
Now you're threatening me
with her safety?
Don't you have any sense of guilt?
Mrs. Shen.
Calm down.
(You won't believe whatever I say.)
(Then take my life)
(to compensate her.)
(Just let my dad live.)
Mrs. Shen.
Song Qinian.
Let's talk this over.
(Dad, I'm exhausted.)
(No one in this world loves me.)
(No one believes me.)
♪Need to smooth out the temper♪
♪Need words that are crafted finely♪
♪Need to remember the premise♪
♪Conceal the candid but harsh advice♪
♪In the heart♪
♪Need to practice repeatedly♪
♪With limbs that make a deafening noise♪
♪How should I bring it up♪
♪What kind of topic should I seek♪
♪How should I make the analogy♪
♪Is that love concern
or a torture device♪
♪Please♪
♪Don't♪
♪Recall♪
♪Don't forget♪