=The Silent Wife=
=Episode 22=
(Die, Shen Chiyan!)
I'll call the police.
They will arrest you.
The truth?
Make yourself clear.
You have no idea.
Three years ago,
if Qiutong hadn't protected you,
I would have hit you with the car.
And Song Guanliang.
I just showed him
a video with a face swap.
And he willingly
served three years in jail.
Shen Qiwen.
What else do you wanna know?
I'll tell you all.
Shen Qiwen.
Do you know what you're saying?
Shen Qiwen, are you crazy?
You idiot.
(Three years ago)
Chiyan.
It's my birthday tomorrow.
You must come.
Tomorrow.
I'm afraid I can't.
Tomorrow,
I'm going to confess to Qinian.
I've waited for too long.
I see.
Then
I wish you success.
Thank you.
See you around.
Happy birthday.
Qiwen.
I need you.
I know Chiyan too well.
If he likes someone,
then it's for a lifetime.
But why is he confessing
to that mute?
Qiwen.
You must stop him for me.
You will help me, right?
Yeah, I will.
Qiutong.
But even if Shen Chiyan
doesn't manage to confess this time,
what about
the next time?
What then?
Then let's make sure
that he despises Song Qinian
from now on.
You want to
ruin that mute's innocence.
Song Qinian's father is a freight driver
who takes on private jobs
for a quick buck.
What if he is in a hurry to make money
and ends up kidnapping me,
the young lady of the Lin family?
Qiutong.
Kidnapping is illegal.
He will be in jail.
That's right.
Song Guanliang will go to jail.
The reputation
of the Song family will be ruined.
I want her to look inferior
to Chiyan forever.
But what if he still
confesses his love?
Do you think the Shen family
would let him marry
the daughter of a kidnapper?
I see.
I'll work on it.
Qiutong.
No matter what happens,
I will be solely responsible.
Qiwen.
I won't let anything happen to you.
You're the one who matters.
That's right.
This is the place.
Where is the cargo?
There is a packed sack
to the left of the entrance.
It's so heavy.
What's inside?
I wouldn't take on this job
if not for the high payout.
Whatever.
Let's be done with it.
Who are you?
Qiwen.
Tie me up now.
Hurry.
Qiutong.
I'm tying a slip knot.
You can break free
with a little pull.
Qiwen.
A text message isn't enough.
Take a photo
of me with his phone.
Now.
I have checked this place.
There's only one camera.
And it's broken.
It's an abandoned factory.
There is
no one else here.
Where are you going?
I'm bringing the old man here
before he wakes up.
And you will
wait right here
for Shen Chiyan to come to your rescue.
What a lively night
you're having.
Song Qinian.
Miss Qiutong.
How does it feel to be bitten
by your pet?
You guys...
How come you guys...
Chiyan.
Everything
you said was a lie?
You've been lying to me?
What did he lie about?
Besides,
so what if we deceived you?
What have you done?
One lie after another.
Aren't you tired?
When
did it all start?
(Three days ago)
Have the hangover soup
while it's warm.
You remember, right?
I'm serious about us.
Please don't leave me.
I will compensate you.
The best compensation would be
for you to sign the divorce agreement
and disappear right away.
Qinian.
I remember now.
I remember everything.
Qinian.
Three years ago,
I fell in love with you
at first sight in college.
I wanted to meet you.
So I waited for you at the entrance
of your class
and bumped into you.
And I knew you couldn't speak.
So I learned sign language
from my grandma
just to communicate with you.
And I invited you
to the lighthouse
to confess my feelings to you.
I'm sorry.
I didn't make it that day
because I was in a car accident
and forgot everything about us.
I even forgot you.
I said I'd divorce you.
It's too late for you
to say this now.
Do you remember
this whistle?
I made you a promise.
No matter where I am...
As long as you blow this whistle,
I'll show up by your side.
This is yours.
It's engraved with my name.
Mine is engraved with your name.
And this cell phone
has been inactive
because I didn't know the password.
But then I regained my memory
and turned it on.
The password is your birthday.
Qinian.
I know that no matter
what I say or do now
can't make up for the past.
But please.
Give me one more chance.
One last chance.
Let me love you once more.
Okay.
I'll give you a chance.
I need you
to put on a show for me
until Lin Qiutong
and Shen Qiwen reveal their true colors.
I want to hear them confess their crimes
and pay the price
for what they've done
to my father and me.
Okay.
You heard everything?
Actually, when you asked me
for help in the hospital,
I already saw this coming.
Qinian.
Do whatever you want to do.
Just be happy.
We...
are friends.
Aren't we?
Yeah.
Lin Qiutong.
You're so heartless.
For your pathetic infatuation,
you used Shen Qiwen
to ruin my life and Chiyan's.
You even killed my father.
I did all this.
Qiutong is innocent.
Chiyan.
I have been by your side
for so many years.
I've given everything
just to be with you.
After so many years,
why can't I replace her
and win your heart?
Why?
Lin Qiutong.
Stop being so obsessed.
I think you are sick.
I'm not the one you need.
You need a psychiatrist.
I happen to know a good psychiatrist.
Should I pull some strings?
Don't talk to her like that!
Chiyan.
It's all because of you.
Die!
Chiyan!
♪Need to smooth out the temper♪
♪Need words that are crafted finely♪
♪Need to remember the premise♪
♪Conceal the candid but harsh advice♪
♪In the heart♪
♪Need to practice repeatedly♪
♪With limbs that make a deafening noise♪
♪How should I bring it up♪
♪What kind of topic should I seek♪
♪How should I make the analogy♪
♪Is that love concern
or a torture device♪
♪Please♪
♪Don't♪
♪Recall♪
♪Don't forget♪