[2009]
Chuan,
I want to ask you a question.
Tell me...
What's the scariest thing?
Your feet stinking up the place every day
is scary enough.
Be serious.
Mice, snakes.
Not that kind.
What's the most terrifying thing?
Death?
Not that either.
Let me rephrase it.
Hypothetically—
let's say a person's whole life
has already
been written out.
It's already set.
And you could know in advance
what's going to happen to you.
Would you want to know
or not?
Hey, is there anything wrong
with your brain?
How could it be set?
Hypothetically.
I wouldn't want to know.
It wouldn't be fun anymore.
Why?
If you could know,
you'd know
what bad things are going to happen.
and avoid them in advance.
Isn't that good?
Alright, then I'd want to know.
Wait, that's not right.
Didn't you say it's already set?
Then how could I avoid it?
Like in those
time-traveling TV series,
they already knew what was going to happen
and tried their best to change it,
but the outcome was still the same.
It hasn't changed.
You can't change anything. It's pointless.
What about you?
Would you want to know or not?
What kind of stuff have you been reading?
Mystery novels.
Chuan,
I just feel
that people
are too insignificant.
They know nothing
and can't see the big picture.
All they can see is
what exists within their own
limited perspective.
So sometimes,
it's really scary to think about it.
It's like fate
has blindfolded you.
Real life is the same.
Every day is uncertain.
So I know
what the most terrifying thing is now.
The unpredictability of life
is the most terrifying thing.
What?
Sis,
I realize you
have grown up.
I just hope
that my life will be smooth and easy,
like a straight, steady river,
without wind or waves,
smooth and steady all the way.
Life is hard—that's normal.
Nothing is certain in this world.
Live in the moment.
What you feel right now
matters most.
Alright, stop overthinking.
I'll always be here for you.
Here,
read it.
Okay!
Life is unpredictable.
Live in the moment.
I trust what I'm feeling right now.
Let's get married.
Okay.
[Sunsets Secrets Regrets]
[Episode 13]
Jiang Cheng, right?
The game now begins.
Cheng.
What does this mean?
You can't bring dangerous items
to meet Old Scorpion.
Old Scorpion is here?
You're not Old Scorpion, right?
What do you think?
You took our phones when we left,
and now you're searching us.
What's this supposed to mean?
Dahua.
Shut up.
You're taking this, too?
It's okay now.
Let's go.
Hold on.
What's your name?
Jiang Cheng.
I heard from Mr. He
that you used to be a cop.
Yeah.
Before he sent you here,
did he tell you
that Old Scorpion hates cops the most?
Is it fun?
Not bad.
Looks like Mr. He
finally has someone with guts under him.
I remember his cousin,
Lai San—
Before I even fired a shot,
he pissed himself on the spot.
Until now, I still can't forget
the stench on him.
I'm no match for you.
I give up, Godfather.
Do you know how to play Chinese chess?
Let him come over.
Come.
Sit.
Red moves first.
I heard
you've been in the limelight lately.
The bosses gave me the opportunity.
Why did you stop being a cop?
I got in the way of someone's promotion
and got set up.
It's not really a secret.
It was a badger game.
During the investigation,
a bag of white powder was found on me.
Not only was I kicked
out of the police force,
but I also did 3 years
in prison for nothing.
You were framed by others.
You were forced onto this path.
Just for the money.
Have you ever killed anyone?
Have you ever killed a cop?
I've heard about this.
Cops who fall into your hands
have no way out.
I mean you.
Seems like you haven't.
I'm just a nobody.
I'm nowhere near your level.
But I think sometimes
a living person is much more useful
than a dead one.
I work for Mr. He.
Sometimes, an extra friendship
means another way to make money.
To carry weight on both sides of the law,
you can't just rely on being ruthless.
You also need to have
the capacity to tolerate others.
What do you think?
Are you telling me what to do?
I didn't mean that at all.
Good.
I need someone like you working for me.
What do you want me
to do for you?
Kill this man,
and I'll give you a bright future.
Position 2 is confirmed.
They are unloading goods inside.
Copy that.
Leader Yao.
Where is the backup team?
SWAT will reach the pier in 5 minutes.
What is He Wu doing? Where is he going?
We tracked him
near an abandoned factory.
It's the opposite direction from Jingang.
It's on Beijiang Road in the northeast.
Keep an eye on him.
Report any situation at once.
Copy that.
Stay close.
Wan,
is there any movement from He Wu?
Follow my location.
Okay.
Boss, you...
So,
we're not doing business tonight?
What business?
You mean
the goods at Jingang Wharf?
All the bros here know
a batch of goods
will be shipped there tonight.
Hey, this...
This intel is fake.
We set this up just to…
just to kill him.
Just to kill him!
Hello.
Long time no see.
Leader Yao. Leader Yao.
The first batch
of reinforcements is in place.
Okay.
Act only after confirming the drug deal.
Wait for my command.
Copy that.
Move out.
Freeze!
Police!
Stop!
Get down!
Report.
It's all flour. No drugs.
Something's wrong.
Tell them to pull out, quick!
Tell me,
why so many police
showed up to raid
our cargo ship full of timber
at Jingang Wharf?
The police really went there?
A lot of them.
It seems we really
have a mole here.
Who could they be?
A mole...
A mole.
Wan, you guys pin down He Wu first.
Yes. Move out.
Sniper!
Everyone, take cover!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I can hold on.
It's the cops.
Boss.
Is there another exit?
Follow me.
Let's go.
We are ambushed.
Requesting backup. Requesting backup.
Senior,
they came prepared.
It's not an easy task.
Stay here.
Protect yourself.
Where are you going?
I'm going to draw him out.
No.
It's too dangerous!
Senior.
Interesting.
Here, quick!
Quick!
Interesting.
Very interesting.
Go!
Old Scorpion is waiting for you.
Hurry.
If you want to live,
I suggest you stop chasing.
You might as well shoot me.
Jiang Cheng.
Why are you here?
Don't touch me!
Stop chasing.
Don't touch me.
I should be the one asking you.
Why are you here?
Why is it you?
Jiang Cheng.
Are you really dealing drugs with them?
Why are you doing this? Answer me.
Stop talking. Stop talking about it.
Why?
Do you know
the man you just let go
was?
Do you know they kill police officers?
Do you know
the people you're dealing drugs with
killed Chuan?
Do you know they killed Chuan?
They killed Chuan!
Do you know that?
I know.
Zhou Jin,
are you okay?
Hansheng,
how did you find me?
I'm sorry.
I'm late.
Did Chuan let you down,
or did I let you down?
Do you know
the man you just let go
killed police officers?
Do you know
the people you're dealing drugs with
killed Chuan?
The tetanus shot hurts a bit.
Bear with it for a moment.
Ready for stitches.
Officer Jiang!
Killing people—
Is it exciting?
Officer Jiang has deep insights
in the field of psychology.
Can't you understand my work?
There's no other way.
If I don't kill them,
I can't calm down.
Just like you!
Officer Jiang.
Right now,
do you want to kill me?
Kill me!
Officer Jiang!
Come on.
Don't suppress your desires!
Kill me.
For the girl you love,
kill me!
Watch your diet recently.
Don't make big movements,
so you don't tear your wound.
Change the dressing in 3 days,
and remove the stitches in 7 days.
Got it?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Your husband went to the pharmacy
to get your medicine.
You can wait for him here.
Mentor.
What is it?
Are you alone?
Go ahead.
Has Leader Yao been rescued?
We're still searching.
How could you go looking
for the sniper alone?
What if you didn't make it back?
It was Jiang Cheng who saved me.
What?
He escorted the sniper away,
which basically saved me.
Chief Tan!
Okay, I got it.
Chief Tan, it's a call
from the Provincial Bureau.
Write a report first.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
Zhou Jin.
How are you?
Does it still hurt?
I'm fine.
Do you have something to tell me?
I'm a little tired.
Zhou Jin.
Don't do this again, okay?
Before you do anything dangerous,
think of me.
Okay.
By the way,
how did you find me?
Why are you able
to arrive so quickly every time?
Because you always make me worry.
Hurry up and brush your teeth.
Then, go to bed.
You must be tired.
Hansheng.
5 years ago, I let you
and your master down,
especially you.
I am deeply sorry.
If it really is a trap,
I will follow your path.
Dead or alive,
I'll bring back the clues.
You and Zhou Jin
must never give up.
Prof.
I was wrong.
Qi Yan is not dead.
Now, Leader Yao is in trouble.
I heard about it.
Don't overthink it.
Be careful.
Jiang Cheng.
Pass it! Pass it!
Pass the ball!
Why dribble if you can't get past him?
Jin.
Why are you here?
I'm back,
Jin.
It was my fault.
Don't cry anymore.
Jiang Cheng!
Jiang Cheng.
Did you have a nightmare?
I'm fine.
What did you dream about?
Nothing.
Go back to sleep.
Officer Jiang,
does your girl
really care about you?
Why aren't you sleeping?
I saw
Jiang Cheng today.
I almost got killed
chasing that sniper.
It was Jiang Cheng who saved me.
Leader Yao received a reliable tip
that there will be a major drug deal
at Jingang Wharf today.
So Leader Yao
will personally lead a team there
to make the arrest.
However, before your next move,
I hope
you can look into someone.
Who?
Jiang Cheng.
Why?
Aren't you supposed to ask
who he is first?
Attention, all units.
Maintain current duty status for 42 hours.
Increase patrol frequency at the station.
Thoroughly investigate
every suspicious person.
Seal off Hengyun Logistics,
Phoenix Fire Bar,
and other businesses
closely related to the suspects.
Conduct a full investigation
into their connections.
Any information related
to Comrade Yao Weihai
must be reported immediately.
Treat every clue seriously.
Verify carefully.
Their target was very clear,
and they moved very fast.
The tunnel was dug in advance.
The entrance was
in the container warehouse.
The container warehouse was just a cover.
After the explosion,
there was brief chaos.
That's when Leader Yao
was pulled into the tunnel.
[Director Wang Pengze]
They also left some cannon fodder
to resist the police.
It was actually just to buy time.
Where does this tunnel lead?
It leads directly
to the city's sewer system.
By the way,
after they left the tunnel,
they detonated explosives twice.
The entrance
has collapsed from the explosion.
Our SWAT officers
were almost buried alive.
Leader Yao has been missing
for more than 48 hours.
If this
really is
a trap set by Qi Yan,
the consequences could be catastrophic.
When Jiang Hansheng told me
that there was a fifth person
in this warehouse,
I got chills, too.
It seems they are
getting revenge
for what happened 5 years ago.
Director Wang.
How is your progress in Huaiguang?
Qi Yan
is quite a mysterious figure.
I need
to sort this whole thing out
from the beginning
based on the new clues we have now.
The top priority right now
is to find Yao
and the undercover cop.
Okay.
Don't worry,
we will definitely try our best.
Right now,
you're carrying a heavy burden.
You must hold on.
Okay.
Director Wang,
if there is nothing else,
we'll leave it at that.
If there is any new situation,
I will report to you immediately.
And,
emphasize it to Jiang Hansheng
and that little girl
once again,
make sure they are extra careful.
Did you hear me?
Okay.
Zhou Jin is right next to me.
Don't worry.
Okay, let's keep in touch.
Goodbye.
Didn't you ask what the situation is?
This is the situation right now.
What did Director Wang just say
about Leader Yao
and the undercover cop?
Before the Jingang operation,
Leader Yao once told me the truth.
Right now, there's an undercover officer
inside Old Scorpion's
criminal organization.
His code name is Cangfeng.
He had been in one-way contact with him.
Cangfeng?