Due to the absence
of a father figure in his birth family,
the killer developed
deep-seated inferiority
and an extreme craving for love
and attention.
I also believe that
he was abandoned by his mother
at some point.
How is it? Handsome, right?
Where did you get these videos?
Didn't you tell me
about Professor Jiang's
prime-time
legal program interview?
So I found it.
I searched too. How come I didn't find it?
How could you possibly find it online?
I asked the TV station for it.
I made a copy of it. Here.
Historical records of
the National Little Rose.
What the heck?
Na-National Little Rose?
At that time, the TV station
didn't know Professor Jiang's name,
but they were deeply impressed by him
and his red suit.
So they gave him this nickname,
and it stuck around.
National Little Rose.
But now
he's been privatized by you.
[Sunsets Secrets Regrets]
[Episode 15]
Mr. Wang.
Hit a snag, didn't you?
I told you not to come today,
but you wouldn't listen.
You might be a godsend elsewhere,
but here,
you're a total jinx.
Don't you know that?
And why on earth is that?
Ask him.
The case was already solved back then.
It was my appeal material
handed directly to
the provincial procuratorate
that made them take a big fall.
You can't be blamed for that.
Are you done with your PDA?
If so, let's get down to business.
Alright,
don't count on them for this.
About what you told me last time—
that you suspected
Qi Yan might be a twin—
I've actually found some clues.
Want to hear them?
It's been 20 years.
I'm already retired,
and you still come to bother me.
That's a bit too much, Director.
What do you mean by bothering you?
I'm just asking you to recall something.
You coming back to ask me
means this case
has hit a dead end, right?
What do you mean by hitting a dead end?
Isn't this a new clue right here?
Take a good look.
Look.
"The perpetrator
has serious cognitive bias against women.
Single-parent family..."
Alright, that's enough.
Let me ask you,
you've been in the Xiacheng District
for decades.
Has there been a family
with a woman raising a child
but unable to support the child?
Think carefully.
I need time to think.
Do you remember the first victim?
Yes, I do.
Going back a few years,
when we were visiting that area,
we checked the whole neighborhood
around there—
every corner of it.
And you know what?
One of the households told me
that their house
was for rent,
and they once
rented it to a woman.
That woman was exceptionally beautiful,
so they remembered her very clearly.
They told me
that that woman
had no job
and rarely went out.
But different men kept coming to see her.
Prostitution?
We couldn't be sure about that.
I remember 2 of her neighbors
kept gossiping to me,
saying things like
that family
took in an unclean woman
who earned dirty money.
Did she have a son?
Yes.
Two sons, twins.
Did you look into that woman?
You must be hungry, right?
After the vice squad got the report
back then,
they went to check,
only to find she had moved out
early that morning.
Besides knowing she was pretty,
they didn't even have a photo of her.
Plus,
the landlord hadn't signed
a formal lease with her,
so there was no further information.
Even the fact that she had twin sons
was only discovered by the landlord
by accident.
At that time, the landlord
told me a story.
He said one day
he went to read the water meter,
and no one was home.
He saw on the living room table
a photo.
Since the woman was very pretty,
he took a closer look at the photo.
He said
it was a photo of that woman
and her two sons.
The two sons looked exactly the same.
So that means
he only saw the photo
and never actually met the children
in person?
The current statements
all lack substantial evidence.
All the information comes from
the one-sided stories of
the landlord and neighbors.
So it could only be left at that.
Alright, tomorrow,
I'll go to the branch again
and have them check
the birth certificates.
If they're twins,
the scope
shouldn't be too large.
I already checked.
No one matched the criminal profile.
Do we have the address of
the place that woman rented?
Yes.
Since we can't find information
on the children, let's try the mother.
Is it really necessary
to go find the landlord?
No need to find the landlord.
Let's track down
the pimps operating in that area.
As for this matter you're investigating,
you don't even have a clear target.
It's been 20 to 30 years.
Where do you expect me
to find these people for you?
There must at least be some records of
vice sweeps, right?
We plan to start screening
people with prior criminal records.
Captain Li,
what do you think?
The computer records only go up to 2000.
What you want to check
is way past that time frame,
my dear comrades.
There must be paper records, right?
Hopefully the mice haven't chewed them up.
Li,
we won't hold you up...
Don't try to get chummy with me.
Let me tell you,
you've got no clout
with me!
The two of us really screwed him over
back in the day.
To this day,
he still hasn't been promoted.
Everything's here.
Leaders,
don't blame me for not assisting you.
As you can see,
I'm short on manpower here.
I hope you can understand.
I'll leave Xu with you.
He'll dig through all this with you guys
like searching for a needle in a haystack.
If you can find anything this way,
I'll admit you've got skills.
I've got other cases to work on.
Pardon me.
Li is right.
This is no easy task.
How about this?
Let's split up.
I'm familiar with
the vice sweep side of things.
I'll go out on the streets
and feel things out.
You guys keep sifting through
the files here—
focus on checking what
those with prior records are doing now.
Pull out the ones
who've been hanging around the same area
for 20 to 30 years.
Maybe we'll find some clues.
Zhou's idea is not bad.
I'll go with you then.
I'm okay on my own.
I can cover for you.
Take him. Take him.
Go ahead.
I've got this.
Alright.
Let's go.
Mr. Wang, we'll head out first.
Okay.
I'll take the left.
You take the right.
Let's meet at the intersection later.
Okay.
Hey, handsome.
Buy a balloon for your girlfriend.
We're already married.
Then buy it for your kid.
I'll wait for you
at the intersection ahead.
Handsome.
Buy one.
Both boys and girls love it.
Check out this doggy.
Isn't it pretty?
Hansheng, where are you?
The doggy's so cute.
Is it for me?
Let's go upstairs and chat for a while.
Come on.
It's fine.
Where are you from, handsome?
He already rejected you,
Miss.
Who are you?
Why did you grab me?
I hate it most when other women
get handsy with him.
What's your name?
Entrapment, huh?
You guys really went all out.
Just answer the questions.
Or do you want me to take you in?
Name.
Feifei.
Real name.
Feifei...
Li.
What do you do?
You caught me,
and you're asking what I do?
I should be asking you that question.
Be serious.
We want to ask you something.
So you're not the vice squad?
I knew it.
I recognize the cops around here.
I've never seen a woman in the vice squad.
I want to know—
who manages you guys?
Why should I tell you?
So someone does.
I was just saying that.
Hansheng.
Spit it out.
Well,
I usually find my clients myself,
but some
are referred to me by others.
800 a client,
and they take a 300 cut.
So who assigns you the work?
Hong.
Hong?
What's his full name?
I just know him as Hong.
It's not like we're students at school—
who uses full names?
How long has he been in this line of work?
He's always been doing this, I think.
Longer than me, anyway.
Is this him?
Named Hong Cheng.
Bring him in for questioning.
Well...
What's so hard about that?
It's not like we're searching for a needle
in a haystack anymore.
Li?
Li!
Um,
Wang.
Officer Zhou, Officer Jiang.
Hong Cheng
confessed.
Over 20 years ago, that area
was run by one of his senior guys,
named Yu Liang,
who was involved in this line of work.
That Yu Liang
did time for a few years
and is out now.
Did you ask about the twins?
I did.
This is the key part.
Hong Cheng
once heard Yu Liang brag
that when he was young,
he dated a woman
who was raising twins.
Do we have Yu Liang's address?
Yes, it's here.
I printed out a copy of
all the information
I could find for you.
Thank you.
Li.
So I've still got some clout
with you, right?
What do you mean you've got clout?
I'm doing this out of respect
for Officer Zhou, alright?
Li. Li!
I know who you are looking for.
It's Qi Zhen.
Back when I first met Qi Zhen,
she came to Huaiguang
to make a living
and stepped onto my turf.
As soon as she arrived,
the girls working under me
couldn't get any business.
So,
I went to her place to cause trouble.
The moment I saw her,
I understood.
Zhen was very beautiful,
the kind of woman
any man would be captivated by
at first sight.
Later,
I went to cause trouble a few more times.
Unexpectedly, we ended up
becoming familiar with each other.
I only found out then
that she wasn't alone—
she was with a child,
her own child.
They were originally twins,
but the older brother had died,
leaving just the younger brother.
What was the child's name?
I don't know
his full name.
His nickname was
either An...
Or Yan.
Zhen was very sensitive about people
asking about her child,
so I didn't ask much.
Why was she sensitive?
She was worried
that the child would be taken away.
I remember
one night,
it was raining,
she came banging on my door in a panic,
saying the child had gone missing.
Seeing her so anxious,
I picked up the phone
to call the police.
To my surprise, she suddenly snatched
the phone from me,
refusing to let me do it.
Well, Zhen had
lost a son
and had been traumatized.
You know,
she was a bit neurotic up here.
She always felt someone
was going to take this child away too.
Later, I
found the child
in her closet.
In a closet?
Yeah.
Right... In a closet.
So this child—
how old was he then? Was he in school?
At the time,
I think he was about 10 years old.
He didn't go to school.
Zhen wouldn't allow it,
and she wouldn't let him go outside
either.
They just stayed at home every day.
She said she'd teach him herself.
[1989]
Sometimes,
when Zhen
was sewing clothes
or doing handicrafts,
the kid would watch her.
Zhen liked to play the piano,
and the kid liked to listen to her.
I think
that must have been
the biggest entertainment
for the mother and son.
Is it pretty?
Yes.
The mother and son
had a very close relationship.
That kid
was hardly
ever out of Zhen's sight.
Even...
Even when
someone came to their house to visit,
she would find a place
to hide that kid.
You're in quite a good mood, huh?
I like the dark.
Jiang Cheng.
Do you know what it feels like
to be locked
in a dark, enclosed closet?
Suffocated?
Scared?
I like the night.
It makes you feel safe—
like an owl in the darkness.
Only you can see
and hear.
The whole world seems to be
under your control.
Yet
no one even knows you exist.
Please take a look.
Is this Qi Yan?
T-This is too blurry.
Besides,
he was just a kid back then.
I can't tell.
Then do you know where Qi Zhen is now?
I...
I thought you knew.
The mother and son
have been missing for many years.
Do you remember
where you saw her
for the last time?
I can't remember
when it was clearly.
I think
it was in 1992.
But I remember the place very clearly.
It was in Huaiguang Hospital.
She was sent to the hospital
because
she tried to commit suicide.
By slitting her wrists?
Yes.
I
went to the hospital to see her.
She was lying in the bed,
her face deathly pale.
I tried to talk sense into her.
I said,
"Even if you won't think for yourself,
you have to think for your kid.
What will happen to him if you die?"
She
didn't say a word.
Just lying there.
There was no light
in her eyes at all,
like a living dead.
Fortunately, at that time,
the police officers
were going door to door
conducting a household survey.
Otherwise,
she would have died.
Later,
when I went to the hospital again,
Zhen was gone.
I asked the doctors and nurses.
They said
she sneaked away by herself,
and they didn't know where she went.
From that point on,
she just vanished into thin air.
I...
But I always feel
she's not dead—
that she's still alive.
Maybe
she didn't go far at all.
Maybe she's right here in Huaiguang.
Over the years,
I think
I've seen her a few times.
Once, from a distance,
I saw her right at the alley entrance.
But when I ran over,
she was gone.
Once on the street,
it felt like we brushed past each other.
But when I turned my head,
she disappeared.
I can't tell if it was
my hallucination or if I really saw her.
You see,
a woman—
for her child—
was willing to do anything
and had done everything.
She already knew no limit.
But why...
Why would she commit suicide?
What would happen to the child
if she really died? I...
I just don't understand.
In your memory,
did Qi Zhen ever wear red clothes?
Yes.
She liked red.
She made most of
her own dresses herself.
They were very beautiful.
Qi Zhen attempted suicide
by slitting her wrists when she was young.
In all of our cases,
the fatal wounds on the victims' wrists
are a consistent criminal signature.
Chief Tan.
During the process of
committing the crimes, Qi Yan
kept setting up
scenes filled with ritualistic elements.
It should be a projection of the scene
when his mother slit her wrists
to commit suicide.
By recreating the scene,
he repeatedly brings himself back to
that moment,
seeking
some kind of psychological
comfort and relief.
But I still haven't figured out
why he does this.
Generally speaking,
painful memories
aren't something people deliberately
try to repeat,
and killing isn't meant to be
a form of self-torture.
The reason that drove Qi Zhen
to attempt suicide,
and the reason Qi Yan
kept recreating the suicide scene—
if we can figure out these two things,
then psychologically,
we can completely get a handle on
Qi Yan as a person.
I understand what you mean.
Mentor.
We want to go meet
the police officer
who helped Qi Zhen back then.
Sure.
Just go straight to
the local police station.
There shouldn't be many people
in charge of household registration.
He should be easy enough to find.
Well, you may not know this,
but our Professor Jiang
isn't exactly welcome here in Huaiguang.
We've already run into
quite a few roadblocks.
I didn't expect
Professor Jiang to have times
when things don't go his way.
It's fine.
I'll talk to them.
We'll just send an official letter,
alright?
Now that we finally have
conclusive evidence,
no one will dare to delay the case.
Okay.
Anything else?
Mentor,
there's nothing else.
Okay then.
Finding out about Qi Zhen
was not easy at all.
Thanks for your hard work.
Alright. Please rest early.
Alright. Bye.
Gosh.
My mentor is way too talkative.
We talked for over half an hour.
Get me a bottle of water.
You smell so good.
It's a floral scent today.
I'm the National Little Rose, after all.
Professor Jiang,
so you know how to joke now.
I always have.
He's lying.
Zhou Jin,
I thought you booked one room
because you wanted to be with me.
I am with you.
Are you?
Let's go to bed.
I didn't mean to.
There were really no other rooms left—
only a standard twin room.
Besides,
you are a light sleeper.
I want you to sleep more comfortably.
How do you know I'm a light sleeper?
When two people have been together
for a long time,
they know everything about each other.
Why do you think Yu Liang
cares so much about Qi Zhen?
He's waited for her for 20 years.
It can't just be because
she's pretty, right?
I guess everyone has their own obsession.
But I could tell
that he's truly waiting for her.
He could even wait for a lifetime.
If it were you,
would you be willing to do that?
I have waited.
Then I understood a saying,
"People who can bravely
say goodbye
will be rewarded with a new beginning."
Turn off the light, Hubby.
What did you just call me?
Hubby.
Jiang Hansheng,
you're a good husband.
Zhou Jin.
When we have kids in the future,
what should we name them?
I think I will be a qualified father.
[Yatou Pharmaceutical Factory]
We're here.
Untie our new friend.
Hands.
Get out of the car.
Where is this?
Are you going to kill me here?
Old Scorpion,
you didn't keep your word.
You did a good job with
what I told you to do.
Qiu Ye,
Boss He, and Qi
all strongly recommend you.
Looks like I should give you a chance.
Qi?
That's right.
Qi.
Who exactly are you?
Jiang Cheng,
welcome on board.
I am Old Scorpion.
By the way,
your marksmanship is just so-so.
I'll give you some guidance later.
Let's go.
Zhou Jin,
I will send you some files,
including the police dispatch records
and
the contact information
of the police officer
who saved Qi Zhen back then.
The officer is called Jian Liang.
Over 20 years ago,
he was a household registration officer
in the Xiacheng District of Huaiguang.
Later, he was transferred to
Huiping County
[Huiping, Jingzhou]
and became the head of the police station.
Huiping isn't far. You can drive there.
It only takes an hour.
He will cooperate with you.
Is this Chief Jian?
I am Zhou Jin
from the Nancheng Branch of Haizhou City.
Hello.
What case is it exactly?
We'd like to talk to you in person.
Chief Jian,
how about we meet directly
at the police station?
I got an emergency call,
so I'm outside right now.
Then how about
we just wait for you at the station?
I'm sorry,
but my wife
hasn't been feeling well recently,
so I have to go home in a bit.
How about this?
If you two don't mind,
we can talk at my place.
What do you think?
That doesn't seem appropriate.
It's fine.
I'm the host,
so it's only right to treat you to a meal.
Not to brag,
but my wife is a really good cook.
I mean it.
Then it's settled.
I'll send the address
to your phone number later.
Alright?
Let's go to his house.
602.
This should be the one.
Coming.
Hello.
We are here for Chief Jian.
Officer Zhou.
Professor Jiang.
Come on.
Please come on in.
Come in.
I've got the slippers ready for you.
Something came up,
and Jian hasn't returned yet.
Please, have a seat.
I'll go make some tea for you.
Please don't trouble yourself.
I'm his wife.
You are so young.
Just call me ma'am.
Come on in.
Make yourselves at home.
Please, come in and have a seat.
Funny, right?
Who would hang their police uniform
on the wall in their own home?
Like some kind of narcissist.
Not at all.
Since his first day as a police officer,
Jian has had this habit.
Every morning when he wakes up,
he has to look at it
to remind himself
to be loyal to his duty
and work diligently.
He also says
it's not safe for me to be
alone at home so often.
By hanging a police uniform here,
even if a thief broke in,
they wouldn't dare steal anything.
He's just that kind of person.
Please excuse him.
Here, have some tea.
By the way,
what do you want to eat for lunch today?
Tell me,
and I'll make it for you.
We are not picky.
Just not too spicy.
I can help you.
Sure.
See if the dishes I prepared
suit your taste.
We don't often have young people over,
so I don't know what you like.
Have some fruit first.
Let's go.
Make yourself comfortable.
Jian told me
that you guys are from
the CIB of Haizhou City, right?
Being a criminal investigator
must be tiring, huh?
It's alright.
It's just there have been
quite a few cases lately.
Jian is also like this,
busy all day without a moment to rest.
That's what it's like
to be a police officer—
working tirelessly around the clock.
By the way,
what case brought you guys
all the way here?
It can't be that
Jian got into some trouble, right?
No, it's not.
The perpetrator may not necessarily have
a deficiency in romantic relationships.
Rather, the issue lies in the mother-child
relationship from his early years.
He grew up in a single-parent household,
raised solely by his mother,
and he developed very serious
psychological problems.
It's also highly likely that
he experienced betrayal,
abandonment, or abuse by his mother,
which led to a distorted personality.
While obsessed with women,
he also harbors extreme hatred
toward them.
When Zhen
was making clothes
and doing handicrafts,
that child would watch her.
Zhen liked to play the piano,
and the child liked to listen to it.
The police officer
who saved Qi Zhen back then
was called Jian Liang.
When I went to the hospital again,
Zhen was gone.
This person
harbors extreme hatred toward the police.
Professor Jiang.
But I always feel
that she's not dead—
that she's still alive.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's okay. It doesn't hurt much.
I just wanted to bring the soup over here
to free up the stove for cooking.
I didn't expect
it to slip.
I'm sorry.
Do you have ice cubes?
I don't.
Maybe you should go to the hospital.
Please go to the hospital right away,
okay?
I'm really okay, ma'am.
I've been calling you ma'am.
I forgot to ask—
what is your last name?
M-My last name is Xie.
What about your full name?
Get out.
Get out of here.
Calm down, ma'am.
Put the knife down first.
Put the knife down.
Get out of here!
Get out!
Leave my house!
You're not welcome here!
Jian knows nothing about this!
She was
sent to the hospital because
she tried to commit suicide.
By slitting her wrists.
You don't have ice—
do you have anything else frozen?
Please get it for me.
Get out of here, do you hear me?
Get out!
Qi Zhen!
If you want to continue your current life
and don't want to cause trouble
for Chief Jian,
put down the knife in your hand.
Do not try to provoke me.
No. No.
Don't tell him!
No, no, I mean...
I'm not Qi Zhen!
My name is Xie Meng!
You've got the wrong person!
Please calm down.
Put the knife down first.
Let's talk,
okay?
Why...
Why did you find this place?
You...
You are his people?
Who are you?
You are not police at all, are you?
You are his people.
He sent you to take me
and my son back, didn't he?
Who is he?
Who wants to catch you?
Your son is Qi Yan,
right?
Where is he?
You are too late.
Go back and tell him
that I strangled his son.
His son has long been dead.
I should never have
expected anything good from that child
tainted with filthy blood.
He's a vile creature,
and his son is no better!
They both deserve to die!
You deserve to die too!
Go back and tell him
that I will never go back with you.
And I'm not afraid of him anymore.
Jian Liang is a clean person.
If you dare to lay a finger on him,
I will fight you to the death.
Tell me,
who is Qi Yan's father?
Y-You...
You don't know?
You weren't sent by him?
Qi Zhen.
I am Zhou Jin from
the Criminal Investigation Brigade
of Nancheng Branch, Haizhou City.
There's been a recent case in Haizhou,
and your son, Qi Yan,
is a key suspect.
We actually came today
to talk to Jian Liang
and get your information.
Don't tell me...
Don't tell me anything about him anymore!
Don't bring him up to me again!
But he is your son.
Just because I gave birth to him,
do I have to pay for his sins?
Alright.
If I die,
you won't come back, will you?
Jian Liang will be left in peace, right?
Alright...
Hansheng.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
This lock...
This lock won't open again.
Honey,
this lock won't open again.
Can you open the door for me?
Oh, alright.
It's open.
Honey, this door lock
really needs to be changed.
You arrived even earlier...
Than me.
W-What's wrong?
Are you okay?
This...
What happened?