=Go Back Lover=
(December 2017,
Fourth Year of University)
(Lu Xingyan)
Why do you look so pale?
Do you feel unwell?
It's that time of the month.
Did you drink brown sugar water?
If it doesn't work,
do you want to visit the doctor?
Lu Xingyan,
I miss you.
I'm here.
I won't hang up.
I'll be with you.
Just lie down
and sleep for a while, all right?
I didn't hang up.
Xingruo, I think
your boyfriend is downstairs.
He seems to be calling someone.
Is he calling you?
(Lu Xingyan)
Wear a jacket!
You wear so little.
You didn't change your shoes
and even wear a pair of socks.
Do you want to get worse?
Do you feel cold?
Yes.
Why are you here?
You said you miss me
so I bought the earliest flight here.
Do you feel better?
Do you need to visit the doctor?
No.
I'm fine when I see you.
Don't be silly. I'm not a doctor.
You are.
=Episode 21=
(Going to you because you miss me.)
(Year 2024)
(Operating Theatre,
Do not enter unless being called)
Lu Xingyan's family member.
Me!
The patient had an accident
causing a rib fracture
and pleura puncture.
He needs surgery immediately.
We need his family's signature.
I'll sign it.
This is the risk notice.
Are you the patient's wife?
I am his girlfriend.
Hold on.
The surgery consent form
should be signed by a family member.
Girlfriends are not
immediate family members in law.
Does he have other family members?
All of them are not around.
His parents are abroad.
This is an emergency.
Can't we help them sign it?
This is against the rules.
Rules are fixed
but we are flexible as humans. He...
Doctor, this is about life and death.
Please.
All right. I'll inform the superior
and apply for a green channel
for immediate surgery.
We can wait until his parents are here
to sign the consent form.
- Sure. Thank you.
- All right.
(Star City People's Hospital,
Out-patient)
(In Operation,
Operating theatre, Do not enter)
Xingruo.
Don't worry.
Lu Xingyan will be fine.
The scene of the accident
has almost been cleared.
Xu Chengzhou and the rest
are rushing here.
We are here. Don't worry.
(In Operation)
The operation is quite successful.
The rib fracture
and pneumothorax surgery
have been completed.
However, his intracranial haemorrhage
did not meet the indications
for surgical intervention.
The patient is in a coma.
In the next 24 hours,
the haemorrhage might get worse.
Are you saying
that it might get worse for him?
Which is why
he has to be observed closely.
Usually, if the situation remains,
he will wake up after a day or two.
However, there's also a possibility
that it might get worse.
So, we will observe his vital signs
and state of consciousness closely.
We will also follow up
with a brain CT scan
to monitor the amount
of bleeding in his brain.
If the situation gets worse,
we will have to intervene surgically,
which is a craniotomy.
Lu Xingyan.
Family members, make way.
Xingruo.
(In-patient Department)
I've troubled all of you today.
I can just stay here alone.
All of you should go home and rest.
I can also stay here.
The hospital only allows one person
to stay with him.
I should stay.
I'll come tomorrow to replace you.
You can't handle this alone.
You should let Xu Chengzhou replace you.
Actually,
I just want
to be with him for a while longer.
If something happens,
I'll call all of you.
Xingruo, you must take care of yourself
when you are alone.
(Love House)
Everything is damaged?
All right. Thank you.
Is everything all right?
What did the insurance company say?
They say the car
suffers from serious damage.
They will compensate
according to the car damage
after the traffic police's
accident report is released.
What's wrong?
I think this incident is strange.
Don't you feel it?
Zhai Jiajing borrowed the car from me.
Right after she returned the car,
Lu Xingyan had an accident
when he drove it.
Zhai Jiajing?
Why did she borrow the car from you?
I still have something to tell you.
I want to tell Shi Qin
about us.
I don't want her to misunderstand
because of this.
I will only tell Shi Qin.
I believe
she will never tell others.
I'll ask you for one last time.
Have you considered it thoroughly?
I have.
Fine.
I understand.
Can you do me one last favour?
Tell me.
I need to pick up a client
for the law firm.
Can you lend me your car?
Are you going to refuse me
for such a small favour?
All right.
We are all just assuming things.
Let's talk when the police release
the investigation report, all right?
The whole car was burned to the ground.
I'm afraid they won't find anything.
Let's eat first.
♪You♪
♪Will you♪
♪Think of me?♪
♪Can it be♪
♪Here?♪
♪I could still see♪
♪Your love for me♪
Don't treat me as a client
I hope you can
say anything on your mind
when you are with me.
Shen Xingruo!
Lu Xingyan.
♪I never let you go♪
I will keep adjusting my perspective
and think from another perspective
to look at the problem
from your point of view.
♪Want to find a way♪
Are you all right?
Emotional relationships
and emotional stages
are not important to me.
Lu Xingyan.
You are the only one I have.
I am here.
Lu Xingyan.
I used to think
that you would
take good care of yourself in the past.
Even if we weren't together,
you would also be well.
Just now,
when I got the informed consent,
every article on it made me feel scared.
I've never thought about
you being so far away from me.
Lu Xingyan.
I beg you.
Wake up.
He hasn't woken up. It's me.
Have you stayed here all night
without eating and drinking?
I don't have any appetite.
You should eat something.
If this goes on,
I'm not sure if he will wake up or not,
but you might faint first.
He will wake up.
Then,
you should go back and rest.
I'll accompany him for one day.
No need.
I want to accompany him myself.
I know
both of you love each other a lot.
But how long have you been here?
You haven't taken a bath for days.
You need to take a bath
and come back at least.
I've asked the doctor.
Lu Xingyan's brain haemorrhage condition
is under control.
He will wake up soon.
Do you want him
to see how unkempt you look
when he wakes up?
Don't worry.
As soon as he wakes up,
I will tell you immediately.
I'll go back to take a shower
and return immediately.
I'll leave
Lu Xingyan in your hands.
I wonder how is Xing now.
Calm down.
Are you still worried
when Xingruo is there with him?
Hospitals now are so bad.
They only let one person
accompany the patient.
Otherwise, I'll also
go and accompany Xing.
Xingruo, why are you back?
I've come back to take a shower.
Then...
I'll go there now.
No need.
Don't worry.
Yu Si is there.
What? Yu Si?
You let Yu Si accompany Xing?
Aren't you afraid that he might
remove Xing's life support?
I'll head over immediately.
Calm down.
It's the 21st Century now.
People don't hurt someone
in broad daylight.
I'm just worried about Xing.
I know you are anxious.
We will follow Xingruo's orders.
Don't worry.
He will be fine.
I'll trouble you two again later.
Go and rest for a while.
I'm going upstairs.
Lu Xingyan.
Look what has happened to Xingruo
because of you.
I'm telling you.
You better wake up immediately
and give her a normal life.
If you die like this,
I'll bring Shen Xingruo
to Germany immediately.
Do you hear me?
Thank you for taking care of him.
Sorry for troubling you.
Why don't you rest for a while?
I couldn't stay put at home,
so I thought about coming
to accompany him.
(In-patient Department)
Mr. Yu.
Lawyer Zhai.
Are you here to visit Lu Xingyan too?
Yes.
Xingruo has been busy in recent days.
I came here to help her.
Help her?
I help Xingruo because I like her.
Are you helping her
because you like someone?
Mr. Yu, you are good at joking.
Xingruo and I were classmates.
What are you talking about?
If there's nothing else, I'll go in first.
I think there's no need
for you to go inside.
The hospital only allows
one person to accompany the patient.
Xingruo is already inside.
Sometimes, the ward
is the same as a relationship.
Having one more person is too many.
What are you trying to say
by beating around the bush?
I want to say
that I know you like Lu Xingyan.
But I advise you
not to waste your effort.
They will get married soon.
It's no use no matter what you do.
What I do
is none of your business.
Of course.
What you do is none of my business
but I only have one goal
which is to make Xingruo happy.
Her happiness now
is being with Lu Xingyan
so anyone who tries to break them up
will suffer.
I hope you are not against me.
Hello. This is the nurse's station.
The patient at Ward 51 is awake.
Okay.
Lu Xingyan.
The doctor is coming soon.
How do you feel?
Do you remember
that you had a traffic accident?
You were in a coma
for two whole days.
I had
a very long dream.
In my dream,
I couldn't find you.
I walked
towards a very bright place.
However, the more I walked,
I felt the further you were to me.
However, I...
Stop talking.
I thought you won't wake up anymore.
You scared me to death.
Don't move.
Don't cry.
I'm fine.
Don't cry anymore.
Promise me.
Don't leave me again in the future.
Understand?
Silly Girl.
How can I bring myself to leave you?
I will always be with you.
Don't cry.
You shouldn't cry anymore.
I've finally found you.
I want to hold your hand.
Aren't you holding my hand?
(Star City People's Hospital,
Out-patient)
Ward 51's patient woke up last night.
He is the male lead
of the recently famous Double-Star CP
in the romantic variety show.
I watched the show.
I wonder if they will
get back together in the end.
I think they got back together.
Shen Xingruo was by his side
in the last two days.
Ward 51, it's time
to take your temperature.
Have I gone straight to the finale?
You want to take my temperature, right?
It's all right. Keep resting.
Take your temperature.
It's not what you think.
My parents are busy,
so she is here to take care of me.
She is my ex-girlfriend
but we are still friends.
We understand.
I read an online article
saying that both of you
are childhood friends.
I guess.
On the internet,
they said you had a big argument
when you broke up.
Is it true?
I think this should be done.
36.8 degrees. You are fine.
Let's go.
Does Chen Zhu really have a bad temper?
Let's go quickly.
Why did you shake my hand off?
The show isn't over yet.
We can't let them see us like this.
When did you start
to concern about the show?
I am the investor of the show after all.
I need to be responsible for the show.
The main reason
is no spoilers.
My head hurts.
It really hurts.
It hurts.
Hand.
Hold your hand?
It doesn't hurt if you hold my hand.
It doesn't hurt anymore.
Baby Zhou, are you awake?
Good morning.
I've prepared your breakfast.
You can eat at any time.
It hurts.
This isn't a dream?
What are you doing?
Sit down and eat.
Come here.
You...
Chen Zhu?
You woke up early
to make breakfast for me?
Are you Chen Zhu?
I am.
I am your dear wife, Chen Zhu.
I know it.
You have a parasite in you.
Sun Hotel is going to be invaded
by aliens.
My Baby Zhou is so cute.
Stop talking. Eat quickly.
It'll get cold later.
Tell me what you want.
I just want to treat you well.
From today onwards,
I'm going to work hard
to be a virtuous and gentle wife.
I will comprehensively take care
of your life and relationship.
I gave you my card and all my money.
I have no more money, Dear.
Be at ease today.
I want to treat you well.
I want to change.
I know I was too fierce
towards you previously.
No matter what you say or do
from now on,
I will not get angry.
I'll go and clean the floor.
It's too hot. Get me another glass.
How can you say it's hot
without drinking it?
I touched it.
Sure.
It's too cold.
I don't want to drink milk.
I want cola.
Yes, Young Master.
This is iced.
This is room temperature.
This is warmed.
I want a glass of sugarless cola.
Xu Chengzhou,
can you not take this for granted?
What's wrong?
You...
Don't cry.
I was just teasing you.
I'm angry.
Don't be angry.
I was too bad.
I'm not angry at you.
I am angry at myself for being angry.
I'm angry at being angry.
I'm angry because
I'm not supposed to feel angry.
I'm angry because I feel angry.
What are you talking about?
No matter how I treated you in the past,
you only compromised,
and spoiled me.
However,
I couldn't hold my anger anymore
because you asked me
to get you a few drinks.
The bullet comments
on the show were right.
I'm fierce towards you
and like to lose my temper around you.
I don't treat you well at all.
Not well at all.
All right.
I even swore this morning
to change.
I will never get angry at you.
I must hold it in.
But I failed.
I got angry at you again.
I couldn't even do such a small thing.
What should I do?
All right.
I just need to know
that you are nice to me.
I was too much.
I apologize.
No.
I knew you were teasing me
but I still got angry.
Sorry.
I, Xu Chengzhou,
like Chen Zhu who behaves like this.
I love to spoil Chen Zhu.
It's no use no matter who says anything.
Dear,
I will
never get angry at you for no reason.
I will change.
I will do my best to change, all right?
(Outpatient)
You recover well after the surgery.
You can be discharged today.
I've read
your examination report.
The brain haemorrhage situation
is under control now.
The rest is also recovering.
However, the patient will feel
that he cannot exert
any strength in his right hand
in the next month.
So, family members need to help him
with functional recovery training
for grasping and holding.
What else do we need to take note of?
After he is discharged
from the hospital,
he shouldn't do anything strenuous
for a month.
You must recuperate.
All right.
If there are no more questions,
just come back
for a re-examination in three months.
Thank you, doctor.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
You've worked hard.
I can finally be discharged.
Let me bring you back home.
How are you?
Let me see.
Are you all right, son?
It's all right.
I'm fine.
Brat.
What did the doctor say?
The doctor said he is recovering well.
How old do you think you are?
You can't even drive carefully.
You are really making people worried.
What did I tell you?
He is fine because he is lucky.
It's all your father's fault.
He was worried about you
and rushed back.
Speak with a conscience.
You were rushing back here
while dragging me along.
Son, let me tell you.
When we couldn't come back
a few days ago,
she was so anxious that she cried.
I didn't.
You can be at ease now.
I'm fine.
All my limbs are intact as well.
I'm not worried about you.
I'm worried about Ruo.
Look at her face.
She lost weight
because she was worried about you.
Let's go. Go back and rest immediately.
I'll make something nourishing for you.
I'm still here.
Who are you actually picking up?
Lu Shan, what are you doing?
Hold your son.
All right.
Be careful.
Slowly.
Why are you so careless?
(Door is unlocked.)
Be careful.
We are back home.
Change your shoes.
Xingruo,
I'll ask Liu to send you back home.
You've suffered in the last few days.
Go back and rest.
It's all right, Uncle Lu.
I know you care about me.
You and Aunt Pei have suffered as well
for rushing back here.
I'll stay
so I can take care of Lu Xingyan.
Xingyan is our son.
I must take care of him.
Lu Shan, be clear.
Who can take care of this brat?
Fine. You should rest.
I'll take care of him. How's that?
Dad, you should leave.
Where can I go?
I am your father.
I need to take care of you.
I'll stay to take care of him too.
Aunt Pei is also unwell.
It'll be too busy for you.
I can stay and help you out.
Yes.
What's wrong?
I rushed here the whole day
and felt dizzy probably.
I think my blood pressure is up again.
Go back and sit down.
What are you talking about?
I...
I can't hold on anymore, Xingruo.
It's like this.
I'm so dizzy now.
I can't help you.
I need to go rest
in the mountains for a few days.
On the mountains?
Let's go!
- Be careful.
- Just leave us alone.
Why are you going to the mountains?
Leave us alone.
Goodbye, Aunt Pei.
Let's go to the emergency room.
I'm fine now.
You're fine?
You scared me.
Let's go back.
You fool.
You are so senseless at your age.
Don't you know what was happening?
Not so loud.
Tell me. Where are we going now?
We'll stay at the mansion
outside the city for two days to relax.
Sure.
Turn around. Let me shave it for you.
Don't laugh.
Lift your chin.
It's done.
Why are you staring at me?
I was thinking.
Back in the hospital,
I thought
I missed out on
many opportunities to be with you
so
I want to make up
for the moments little by little.
♪Piece together♪
♪Every scene of what we belonged♪
♪How I wish in the future♪
♪Longing could turn into
staying together forever♪
What are you doing?
Aren't you trying to make up
for the moments you missed
little by little?
♪Holding you in my arms
just for that one second♪
♪Time pauses forever♪
♪It turns out♪
♪Every profound moment
is related to you♪
♪From the beginning to the end♪
♪It turns out♪
♪You've always been a part of my life♪
♪As if you've never left♪
♪I still remember loving
each other deeply♪
♪Searching for what you like♪
♪Getting used to your habits♪
Eat more.
(Go Back Lover Interview Time)
What was your last thought
at the moment of the accident?
(Your thoughts
during the moment of the accident)
It happened too quickly.
I felt nothing at that moment.
I didn't feel pain at all.
I only felt that everything around me
became slow.
Many moments of Shen Xingruo and I
flashed past my brain.
Just like a quick running
slide show.
Back then,
I was afraid, to be honest.
I was afraid
that I'd die just like that.
I was afraid of leaving Shen Xingruo.
After experiencing
the accident and hospitalization,
do you have a new view of love?
(Any new views about love
after the accident?)
I realised I love Lu Xingyan
more than I imagined.
What about marriage?
Actually,
I also have
some new thoughts about marriage.
On the day of the accident,
I couldn't sign the informed consent
because I wasn't his family member.
I remember
I was very helpless back then.
Later, I thought about
many things alone.
I have some new understanding
about marriage now.
=Go Back Lover=