=Go Back Lover=
(February 2018.
Senior Year Winter Break.)
What are you doing?
You're awake.
Are you doing something
behind my back?
No.
Is there anything I can hide from you?
What's this?
This is
hair.
Lu Xingyan.
You're not secretly
measuring my finger, are you?
No, definitely not.
I
heard online
that if two people's hair
can be tangled together,
they can be together forever.
That's what they say online.
=Episode 22=
(Ring finger's promise.)
(Year 2024)
Xingruo.
How is Lu Xingyan?
He almost recovered.
It won't affect our final shoot.
The popularity of our show
has now reached 18 thousand.
We'll soon surpass our rival,
"Love Diary".
Amazing, this is great news.
Speaking of, there's something
I want to discuss with you.
We found a new pre-show advert client,
which is L Trip app.
The person who contacted us
thought our show is good
and popular.
But they just couldn't get
their boss, Mr. Zhou, to approve it.
Why is Mr. Zhou in our way?
He thought that our show
isn't popular enough.
I think Mr. Zhou might not be
the target audience of our show.
His circle
might not be our target audience.
In order to make him feel
the popularity of our show,
we should let him
have more physical experience.
Physical experience?
Let him see our ads
wherever he goes.
Let's bombard him
with our show from all angles.
He'll feel our popularity.
But our funding is limited.
Then let's invest our money
where Mr. Zhou can see it.
Do you have his home address?
Yes, let me check.
It's this one.
Xinjiang Center's Tower B.
Xinjiang Center?
Xinjiang.
Xin...
Hello? Li.
I remember your company
is responsible for advertising
in Xinjiang Center, right?
I would like to consult you
about the advertising
in this residential area.
(Go Back Lover)
(Go Back Lover Is Currently Airing.)
Hello? Mr. Zhang.
I want to talk to you
about the adverts for the show.
- Are you okay?
(Zhang Xu)
Hello?
Hello? Xingruo.
I have good news.
You're clever.
Mr. Zhou just called me.
He said our show is very good.
Not only his employees are watching,
but his nephews and nieces
are also watching it.
He's elated.
He asked me to go to his company
to sign the contract tomorrow morning.
He's invest 3 million
in advertising for us.
That's great.
It seems my work wasn't in vain.
Xingruo.
Do you have time
to come to the company these days?
Let's discuss the subsequent shooting
with Director Jun.
No problem.
Okay.
Bye.
Are you done talking about work?
Are you not going to take care
of your boyfriend?
Sure.
(Go Back Lover)
(Double-Star CP is so sweet.)
(This variety show is so good)
(All living beings are suffering.)
(Waiting for new episodes.)
(Only the CP I like)
(Looking forward to it.)
(is sweet like strawberry.)
(Don't get remarried either!)
(Stick to the current situation!)
(Double-Star CP.)
(Warning ahead.)
(I can stay single,)
(Hurry and follow Double-Star.)
(but my CP must get married.)
(Waiting for new episodes.)
(Wish the show success.)
(Congee Cooking CP,
please don't get divorced,)
(and don't remarry.)
(Stick to the current situation.)
(I'm also an introvert.)
(I understand how When CP feels.)
(Sun Inn Hotel)
(Sun Inn)
(Trending Online.
Go Back Lover.)
(Best Performance
Among Same Variety Shows)
Last month,
the popularity of our competitor,
"Love Diary"
reached 19 thousand.
This can be said to be
the highest record of dating shows
in the past three years,
but the popularity of our show
has surpassed it.
It has reached 21 thousand
completely defeating "Love Diary".
(Breaking The Record And Catching Up.
Go Back Lover. Love Diary.)
Our show can be summed up in two words:
Way ahead.
This is due to everyone's efforts.
Everyone deserves credit.
Our show
has aired its third episode,
and the viewership is still soaring.
Everyone's comments and enthusiasm
for our show
continues to increase.
Ye Zi, tell us
about the netizens' opinions.
Among the netizens'
many comments on our show,
the most popular one
is that they hope
we can hold a livestream
so that the CPs can answer questions
and interact online.
I checked our budget.
We have no problem holding a livestream.
Director Jun.
Do you have any ideas
for the livestream's location?
We basically filmed the show
in the villa.
If we're holding a livestream,
we can find
a place
that's quite different from the villa
so that the audience
can see something different.
Sure, no problem.
Okay, let's start preparing then.
We'll invite
three pairs of permanent guests
to the livestream and interact
with the netizens online.
What about challengers?
Shall we invite them?
If we've already
aired the third episode,
it would be best
if the challengers can come.
In these two days,
sort out
the guests' relationship progress.
See what state their relationships is in
in the third episode.
Here's a reminded.
Don't give any spoilers to the netizens.
Let's not waste time.
Hurry up and get ready.
Our livestream
will be scheduled for this weekend.
- Okay.
Everyone.
Welcome
to our livestream shooting location.
Later, to prevent everyone
from interfering with each other
during the livestream,
we'll do it in teams.
Double-Star CP, When CP,
and Congee Cooking CP.
Each of you is a team.
Lawyer Zhai,
you and Mr. Yu Si are in a team.
There will be an interactive Q&A session
during the livestream.
We have no idea
what the audience will ask,
so we can't unify the answers.
The only thing I need to remind everyone
is that we have only aired
the third episode
on the platform.
I hope you can maintain
the status of your CP
in the third episode.
The challengers will appear
Follow PD
will give you a brief recap later.
Ms. Xing.
At this time,
you're having a date
with Mr. Yu at the archery hall.
Let me remind you
that you argued with Mr. Lu
during your last date.
Mr. Lu even stopped filming
because of it.
Okay, you two
are waiting to be chosen
by the challengers in the third episode.
You even argued with each other.
You dressed up and stood at the door.
She said you looked like a doorman.
She
looked forward
to being chosen by her challenger.
Be mindful
of the scale of your interaction.
This episode
is about you two
and your challenger, Zhai Jiajing,
going to a bookstore together.
Shi Qin, you're still unsure
whether He Siyue likes you.
Be careful
about your words and actions
in the livestream.
Maintain the state of your CP.
Don't reveal
the final coupling.
Okay?
Fellow Follow PDs.
Take our guests over.
This way.
- Let's go.
- We haven't started yet.
What are you doing?
The countdown for the livestream begins.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Welcome to the first livestream
of "Go Back Lover".
Thank you
for your continued support of our show.
So far our show
officially has over 20 thousand hits.
To satisfy the audience's curiosity
about our guests,
(Go Back Lover)
we have invited all the guests here today.
This include three pairs of couples
and two of our new challengers.
Firstly, let them say hello to everyone.
Hello everyone, I'm Shen Xingruo.
Hello, I'm Lu Xingyan.
- We're Double-Star CP.
Hello, I'm Chen Zhu.
Hello, I'm Xu Chengzhou.
I'm from the Sun Inn
that warms you and me.
On this bright
and sunny day,
welcome
to the special livestream
of "Go Back Lover",
exclusively sponsored by Sun Inn.
Welcome everyone.
Chen Zhu and I are Congee Cooking CP.
Hello everyone, Shi Qin.
Hello, I'm He Siyue.
We're When CP.
Hello everyone, I'm Zhai Jiajing.
Hello everyone, Yu Si.
The two of us...
Aren't a CP.
But I hope you'll continue
watching our show
to find out who we'll couple up with.
Okay, that's all for the introduction.
Let's move on to the interactive part.
I hope you
will be active in the comments section.
Comment, like,
and chat with our guests online.
Firstly,
Double-Star CP will answer
questions from the audience.
The first question is for Mr. Lu.
This question is a bit harsh.
The netizen asked
if you felt used by your ex-girlfriend
who is the producer
to participate in a dating show?
Every choice I make
is the result
of weighing the pros and cons.
The same goes
for participating in the show.
I don't know if she's using me,
but at least it proves
that I'm still valuable.
So ​​did you two team up this time
to make money together?
Producers are different.
You can even
use your relationship for money.
Since the show started filming,
I haven't participated
in setting the rules for the show.
So compared to other guests,
I just have
the title of producer.
It was very difficult
to find guests for this show
at the beginning.
I remember
that there was a lot of demand
for Double-Star CP online.
After careful consideration,
I chose Lu Xingyan
to be a guest on the show.
(They're so sweet. No way.)
A netizen asked again
if you and Lu Xingyan
are pretending.
Do you have a script for the show?
It's impossible that a variety show
doesn't have a prerequisite setting.
Because we have to decide
the dates' location
and the dating rules.
Under these premises,
we won't interfere
with the guests' relationships.
So please don't worry.
The guests' reactions
you see in the show
are all real.
Last question.
(Double-Star CP)
I saw Lu Xingyan hospitalized.
(You got back together, right?)
Shen Xingruo took care of you.
Have you gotten back together?
I was indeed hospitalized
for some reasons
some time ago.
My parents weren't at home at the time.
and and I had no other relatives around.
So her taking care of me
should be considered
a humanitarian concern.
Actually,
friends who know both of us
know that our families are old friends.
He's not only my friend,
but also a guest on my show.
If anything happens to him,
I won't be able
to continue filming my show.
Producer Shen's statement
made us anticipate how Double-Star CP
will turn out.
Netizens in the livestream
are calling on Double-Star CP
to follow the instructions
and take
three sweet consecutive photos.
Let's fulfill everyone's wish.
Camera, get ready.
Peace.
Heart shapes.
Fingers interlocked.
Okay.
Let's move on to When CP.
A netizen wants to ask He Siyue
why you have a crush on Shi Qin
for ten years,
but never told her?
I'm not expressive.
Many times,
I don't have the courage
to express my fondness and ideas.
That's how I missed
the best time to confess my feelings.
A netizen wants to know
when do you think is the best time.
I think
one is to see
whether the other person's state
is suitable for me
to express my feelings
and
whether I planned a future
for her.
The netizen asked
if you
hadn't planned for the future
in the past ten years.
Or is it because
Shi Qin was in a relationship.
It's my problem.
Your problem?
What problem?
I...
It's not him.
I was in a failed relationship.
I know this person.
The woman was divorced.
Shi Qin was divorced?
It's better not to listen
to rumors about such a thing.
It's better to hear
the answer of the person involved.
She works
at the law firm next to mine.
I also saw her ex-husband visiting her.
- Is she divorced?
- Why is she quiet?
Ignore them. Talk about other stuff.
Yes, I was divorced.
A divorced woman in a dating show?
What is she doing there?
Can't a divorced woman
take part in a dating show?
Do you want a married woman
to join a dating show?
Do divorced women
have no right to seek happiness again?
Firstly,
no show
seems to have explicitly rule out
divorced women.
Besides, I never thought
of deliberately hiding this matter.
Because I also know
that a failed relationship
isn't something I can just deny
and pretend that it never happened.
I used to be troubled,
guilty and insecure
because of this identity.
But my friends told me
that it's better
to accept the past and move on bravely
than to stay where I am.
That's why I came to this show.
He Siyue has always been single
and has never been in a relationship.
Wouldn't you feel at a disadvantage
to be coupled up
with a divorced woman?
Did you travel through time
from the Qing Dynasty?
Listen to what you're saying.
I think
we shouldn't be prejudiced
against divorced women.
Everyone has their past
and past relationships that have ended.
It's no big deal.
Instead of focusing on the past,
think more about the future.
It's almost time.
At the end of the Q&A session,
I would like to ask Shi Qin a question.
As a divorced woman,
is there anything
you want to tell everyone?
I want to tell everyone that
you have the right to pursue happiness,
no matter what you've been through.
Besides, we should encourage women
to break free from these shackles.
(I support Shi Qin. Good luck.)
(I support Shi Qin. I wish you luck.)
I saw a lot of friends supporting me
(Shi Qin, good luck. I support you.)
in the comments.
I'm grateful
that there are so many kind people.
Thank you for giving me
strength and courage.
Okay.
I see that netizens
have changed their focus
to our Congee Cooking CP.
The comment section
is already full of questions,
so is our Congee Cooking CP
ready?
Come on, everybody.
Calm down.
The first question is for Chen Zhu.
Okay, let's check out the first one.
(Chen Zhu is so pretty,)
Chen Zhu, you're pretty and rich.
(Unemployed internet addict)
Why do you have to get involved
with an internet addict
like Xu Chengzhou?
No, who are you
calling an internet addict?
What man doesn't play games?
I just like playing games.
If I were younger,
I would have gone pro.
Besides, I'm not unemployed.
I'm the vice president
and financial director
of Sun Inn.
Calm down.
This question is for Chen Zhu.
It'll be your turn soon.
You can answer as much as you want.
I think
Xu Chengzhou sometimes
seems a little
nonsensical and unreliable,
he's actually
very gentle and considerate to me.
So there's no problem.
And I think
I actually have a lot of shortcomings,
so I'm also working hard
to correct them
and try to get better slowly
so that I can get closer to him.
(What happened? Didn't they argue? )
Is Congee Cooking CP back together?
Didn't they
just have a fight at the judo gym?
Chen Zhu doesn't sound right.
Did I miss an episode?
(Play along!)
But
as I gradually improved and got better,
I realized
that he couldn't keep up with me.
A man like him
whose mouth is faster than his brain
needs me
to spend a lot of time and energy
to train him.
It will cause me to become irritable
and easily angry.
Okay, another netizen said,
Xu Chengzhou,
Chen Zhu scolds you every day,
you're so pitiful.
I'm so pitiful.
I consider it doing a good deed.
Another netizen said since you said so,
your relationship exists only in name.
Why join the show?
(Xu Chengzhou answered so quickly!)
This actually happened
(These two will argue again later.)
before we join the show.
(They're really dramatic.)
He asked Xingruo to ask me.
He also swore to Xingruo
that from now on
I'm the most important person to him.
He also said his buddies and games
will have to step aside.
He said
he'll be faithful to me till death.
He said he will still love me
even if I turn into a lamp.
No, come on.
It was you who found Xing and said
that you always
acted like a spoiled brat with me
and was always angry with me.
Only after we separated
did you realize how important I was.
Besides, you also said
that no one in this world
can stand you except me.
Didn't you say these?
No, how could you...
No, you said it yourself that...
Are... Are you really so mad at me
that you vomited?
I... I'm trying to be dramatic.
No.
I didn't vomit out of anger.
My stomach is just a little upset.
Sorry.
We had a small issue just now.
The questions in the comments section
are now directed to our challengers.
A netizen asked,
Yu Si, are you here for Shen Xingruo?
Of course.
I also occasionally read some comments
about my and Xingruo's
Rainbow Encounter CP
over the years.
I know what you're thinking.
But as to whether I'll succeed.
Again.
Just watch the show.
Another netizen asked Zhai Jiajing.
Why did you join the show?
The setting of this show
is Old Friends Reunion.
I really like this idea.
It lets me get back together
with the people I loved
back then.
(Mingli High School Year 2, Class 1
Entrance Exam Results)
They accompanied me through my youth
and are deeply engraved
in my memories.
Shen Xingruo is amazing.
She pushed He Siyue to second place.
Zhai Jiajing is third place now.
I'm fourth.
Mr. Wang.
Jiajing.
I came here
to talk to you about this year's
school anniversary performance.
Don't worry about it.
I've already practiced the songs.
This year's
school anniversary performance
is different from previous years.
Each class can only
participate in one performance.
Besides that,
all performances
after the school anniversary performance
will be ranked.
How about this? Every day after school,
I'll practice for two more hours
after finishing my homework.
There will be no problem.
Look.
I know you're hardworking
and that you play the piano well,
but I want Shen Xingruo to go this time.
Shen Xingruo
is also a grade 10 piano player.
Besides,
she has also won awards
in some major competitions.
I think she's more suitable.
You know
this concerns the class' honor.
I hope you can understand.
Especially Xingruo and me.
We later joined
"Race Against Time" together.
I witnessed the moment
when she won the competition
and also saw the touching moment
when Xingyan proposed to her.
I thought
we would go our separate ways
after graduating from university.
I didn't expect
the world to be so small.
After everything,
we were brought back together.
Xingruo.
So I'm grateful to the production team
for giving me this chance.
I'm willing
to work
with my old friends
to make our show a success.
What's the matter?
Mr. Yu, do you
have any comments about my answer?
I just didn't expect you
to change so quickly.
I never like
to make unnecessary efforts.
Mr. Yu's words last time enlightened me
and made me make my choice.
(We wish the show success.
The show gets better.)
(We exceeded 20 thousand hits.
Double-Star CP, get back together!)
(The show will get better. Good luck!
I wish the show success.)
Thank you very much
for supporting our show
all this while.
Our show
has exceeded 20 thousand hits.
We hope
you can continue to support
our show.
I wish "Go Back Lover" a great success.
Qin.
You slut.
Did you divorce me
to become a couple with another man?
What are you doing?
Hold him down!
He Siyue.
Everyone.
(This is so exciting.)
Turn off the livestream. Turn it off.
What's going on?
Give me.
Let me go.
Who are you? Do I know you?
Li Qi.
Someone provided your company
with information
and reported you for domestic violence,
so you were fired.
Who are you?
How did you know?
I'm a classmate
of Shi Qin and Shen Xingruo.
I came to you
to talk about your business.
Okay, now tell me
who took the information
to our company to report me.
I can't say who it is.
Logically speaking,
this is between you and Shi Qin.
If you two don't tell others,
who else would know?
Shen Xingruo.
It's her.
The show that Shi Qin is filming
is indeed produced by Shen Xingruo.
She met someone new
on the show
and had a great time every day.
I got it.
I've always wanted a child with her,
but she refused.
I got it now.
She just wants to be a slut, right?
Yeah.
If she
wants to spend her life with you,
how could she
not want to have children with you?
Yes.
So she started having an affair
with that guy from then.
Li Qi.
I really sympathize with you.
You had a job and a wife,
but now you lost your job
because of someone else.
Your wife left too.
If I were you,
I can't accept it.
If I can't accept it,
what am I supposed to do? Right?
Give them a taste
of their own medicine.
I'm telling you.
Without their meddling,
we wouldn't have turned out like this.
Let me go.
Let go!
Stay still.
I gave you everything.
I married you and gave you everything.
But what did you do?
You fell for another guy, didn't you?
Where's your shame?
Where's your conscience?
He Siyue, don't.
Let the police handle this.
- Everyone, please take the guests away.
- He Siyue.
Hurry. This way.
- Hurry.
- Listen to me.
Take him away.
Shen Xingruo!
You're good.
You went to my company and reported me,
didn't you?
- I won't spare you.
- Go.
Come back!
Did I let you go? Come back!
Hurry, take him away.
Come back!
Go.
How did this guy get in?
What have the stagehands been doing?
We only fenced off
one side of the beach.
He came in from the other side.
He seems to be familiar with our venue.
Now that this matter has become a fact,
let's think about it later.
Everyone heard
what Li Qi said.
And the incident
of He Siyue beating Li Qi.
Let's think about what
to do with this first.
We've communicated with the platform
about the livestream playback.
The part where Li Qi barged in
has been cut out.
Okay.
Our rival
has caught on to this incident.
Several relevant official accounts
have published articles.
Our publicity team has contacted them
and asked them to delete
the relevant videos and articles.
Ms. Xing, look at this.
Didn't we
already turn off the livestream?
This angle
doesn't look like our camera.
Did Li Qi arrange it in advance?
Li Qi can't do so much by himself.
I think someone must be helping him.
Who is it?
Calm down.
Go on with the meeting.
I'm going outside to call Lawyer Zhai.
(Go Back Lover's)
Hello.
(Male Guest, He Siyue,)
I'm a guest on "Go Back Lover".
(Publishes Apology Video)
He Siyue.
I published this video today
to express my deepest apologies
to everyone.
During the last livestream,
I lost control of my emotions
and hit Mr. Li Qi.
Regardless of the purpose,
hitting someone is definitely wrong.
(Lawyer's Statement)
(Star City Daoming Law Firm)
The official account
has debunked the rumors.
I guess Li Qi was the troublemaker.
Shi Qin is really scheming.
She looks soft-spoken,
- but she already found someone new.
- Does Li Qi have any other evidence?
(Li Qi received death threats.)
Lawyer Zhai Jiajing was appointed.
Hereinafter referred to as our lawyer.
(Li Qi released)
Gosh.
(a video of himself being threatened.)
Ask for proof, and you'll get it.
- (Variety shows now have no limits.)
- Aren't these the guests?
This is a gang crime.
How disgusting.
They even sent a lawyer's letter.
(I knew Shen Xingruo and Lu Xingyan)
Just two hours
(coupled up to make money.)
since "Go Back Lover"
released the lawyer's letter,
Li Qi released a video
of himself being threatened.
The video is quite blurry.
Who is lying?
How did it go?
Less than two hours
after we sent the lawyer's letter,
Li Qi released the video.
There are even an analysis video online.
With such procedures and operations,
someone must have planned this
to ruin our show.
Don't panic.
I'll think of a solution.
No, we have to hurry up.
Public opinion is unfavorable to us.
The platform producer
just arranged a meeting with me
tomorrow morning.
They must want to talk about this.
I think the blogger
who made the analysis video
must have been instructed by someone.
Then they must have met
with whoever put them up to it.
How about this?
I'll get someone to contact that blogger
and see if we can find out anything.
But I don't think
Li Qi alone
can cause trouble,
plant a camera at the venue,
and getting video bloggers
to edit videos.
Do you mean...
What I mean
is that I think someone on the show
is working with him.
We need to find a way
to find that person.
Have you come up with a plan?
Best actor, it's showtime for us.
(Go Back Lover Interview Time)
(Today's Livestream Has No Interview)
=Go Back Lover=