Proceed with the execution!
Protect His Majesty!
Over there! Chase him!
It's a coup!
A coup is happening right now!
It's a coup! A coup is happening!
Hundreds of soldiers apparently passed the fortress wall.
They will come to the palace in no time!
Please hide away for now.
Even the deposed crown prince's son's men are all over the palace.
Even if I go, I will have him killed, at least.
Move!
Your Majesty!
How dare you get involved?
Hurry up and run.
Slash us first. Otherwise, you will not reach him.
- Protect His Majesty!
- Yes!
- Let go!
- You must hide, Your Majesty!
Protect His Majesty!
Let go!
- Protect His Majesty!
- Let go!
Are you all right?
That way!
The traitor went that way!
It is a losing fight for you now!
An army to remove the deposed king will arrive soon.
Did you join the traitor's side? I favored you so much.
The deposed king... should step down from the throne.
Shut up!
I will not give the throne to Lee Seol even if I have to die on it.
His Majesty, let us go.
I will take care of the rest.
Your Majesty.
You should hide.
I will take Scholar Yoon with me.
Are you okay?
I am totally fine. Do not worry.
Royal Grandmother...
You should hide, for now, Your Highness.
We overcame a crisis, but we cannot do this without the help from the army.
The army will arrive soon.
The owner of Ihwawon agreed to help with opening the palace gate.
Is Dan Oh here?
Yoon Dan Oh.
What is that girl doing here?
Catch her right now!
- Chase her!
- Yes!
Look!  What are you doing?
Over there!
Kang San.
I did not like the look in your eyes from the beginning.
Did you join the Royal Guard to start a coup?
It is not a coup.
I am here to reclaim my place.
I...
I am Lee Seol.
If you are Lee Seol, who is the one who was arrested?
Answer me right now!
What are you conspiring, exactly?
The king has been caught in a trap.
He is causing his own death, trying to kill Lee Seol.
Whether you are saying the truth or not,
I have no reason to let you live anymore.
Are you okay?
Let us go.
It is okay.
It is okay as long as you are safe.
Queen Dowager and the deposed crown prince's son are safe.
Well done.
Let us find the king first, as planned.
Let us do that.
As long as the army enters the palace, we can definitely win.
Dan Oh.
You will have to open the palace gate using the written declaration.
Yes, I will.
They must have missed Yoon Dan Oh.
What is going on, anyway?
Did the geumgun not chase after the traitor? Have they not caught him yet?
(Geumgun- Imperial Army, bodyguards and guards who protect the court and the king)
Your Majesty,
I think there is a traitor within the geumgun, too.
(Geumgun- Imperial Army, bodyguards and guards who protect the court and the king)
It is hard to tell who is on our side and who is the enemy.
My Lord!
- Your Majesty!
- My Lord!
Your Majesty, you must run now!
You must!
Did Kang San... do this?
My Lord!
It is him.
He is, actually...
Lee Seol, the deposed crown prince's son.
Say that one more time.
What did you just say?
The...
My Lord!
Secure the gates since there was a report of a coup!
Yes, sir!
Open the gates.
It is Queen Dowager's declaration to depose the king and put the deposed crown prince's son on the throne.
Where is His Majesty?
The deposed king is imprisoned in the King's Royal Chamber by Queen Dowager's order.
I carry too much responsibility to open the palace gates based on a mere court lady's words.
You two! Go to the King's Royal Chamber and check.
Yes, sir!
What is this about?
Where is His Majesty?
The deposed king already abandoned the palace and fled.
Fled? Is that true?
Do not hasten your deaths by staying in the palace.
You should find a way to survive.
Let us go.
The army is in front of the gates!
What?
The declaration is true.
His Majesty abandoned the palace and fled.
Since we have a new king, please receive his order now.
- Open the gates!
- Yes, sir!
The palace gates are open!
March forward!
Your Majesty, the traitors are searching everywhere inside the palace.
You must run!
You have to stay alive for the future!
- The back gate is still—
- I must face Lee Seol.
You will definitely lose.
There is no future as long as Lee Seol is alive.
Lee Seol.
If I kill him, the traitors will naturally become powerless.
Royal Consort Park, run away with the geumgun and draw the traitors' attention.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The geumgun are moving toward the back gate!
(Geumgun- Imperial Army, bodyguards and guards who protect the court and the king)
What?
- Follow me!
- Yes, sir!
Find Lee Seol and tell him that I am waiting for him at the execution site.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What are you doing?
Do not blame me too much.
I am just trying to protect the king.
Were you Lee Chang's Watchman?
Please leave.
This is my responsibility.
Where is the king right now?
His Majesty is waiting for you in the Palace Main Hall.
Do not do this! Do I have to kill my own teacher?
You need to defeat me in order to protect the crown prince's son.
Be a proper Watchman!
Leave.
This is the last favor.
Kill me.
If you let me live, my sword will point at the crown prince's son right away.
I am not protecting him as the Watchman!
I am protecting him as his friend.
So as long as I am there, your sword cannot reach him.
You should finally put down...
the burden of your grave fate.
Open the gate.
Kang San, are you really Lee Seol?
That is...
Lee Seol.
You must really be Lee Seol.
Do you recognize me now?
I was circling around you all this time.
Who is Lee Seol you wanted to kill so badly, Uncle?
Does he even exist?
Do you remember?
I made you a slingshot when I was a child.
You could not kill a single sparrow with it.
Someone like that wants to kill his uncle now?
That is why you could not kill me while you were circling around me.
You are the one... who made someone like me...
come all the way here.
Do not get involved!
Are you here to avenge your father?
Do you want me to tell you how he died?
Shut up.
He died while begging me.
He desperately begged me to let you live.
I will not beg for mercy from you.
That is the difference between the one who became the king and the one who cannot.
This way!
Your days are already gone.
I am different than you.
If you surrender willingly, I will not kill you.
This country is mine.
It is my Joseon I protected by shedding the blood of many!
You are the same as me.
You are the traitorous king who rose to the throne
by killing his uncle!
Lee Seol.
My name is all yours from now on.
They say a lie does not become true.
If I become the king—
You said a person's will changes the world, not his origin.
- Left State Minister.
- Ever since we first met,
Seol begged me so desperately.
I made up my mind after deliberating for several days.
Gyeom, I think it would be good for Joseon...
to succeed to the throne.
I need to talk to him privately.
All right.
San.
- The reason I led Mok In Hoe was—
- I know.
It is because you dreamed of a better world.
While I was heading forward to defeat the king,
you imagined the future with the people.
That is why...
I thought I would like to... live the tomorrow you imagined.
A world where you can win without killing.
I believe... you can achieve it.
Oh, dear! Goodness, Miss!
You came quickly. I thought you would arrive in the evening.
We ran here as soon as we got the letter!
By the way, where are the scholars?
They are all still in the palace.
Scholar Shi Yeol, too?
Brother Shi Yeol left right away.
He asked us to forgive him even if he disappeared without a word.
He could just be leaving! Why say "disappear"?
I know.
As if he would no longer exist.
You must have waited nervously.
I took too long.
You should go back to the temple and rest today.
Please take us, too.
We need to avenge our late master.
As for that...
I already took care of it.
What... should we do now?
Survive.
Be sure to survive.
Then... how about you, Scholar?
One moment, please!
Just... listen to me from there.
I will resent and...
hate you... as long as I am alive.
So, please...
allow me to hate you to my heart's content.
You need to stay alive... in order for my hatred to reach you.
Letting go of life effortlessly...
is such a cowardly act.
Head Eunuch... what are you going to do from now?
After your coronation, I will have to leave.
I think my job has been completed now.
You may do so.
I heard you were a big help.
I was curious...
about what the two of you would decide... in front of the one and only throne.
So is this what you expected?
Power is a lot harder to keep than to take.
I thought you would fail to overcome that hardship and bring forth atrocity between brothers.
We cannot repeat such a mistake ourselves.
By any chance...
do not be mistaken and think you both established the throne on your own.
The throne exists because trivial beings such as this lowly one support it from behind.
This is the inn that produced a king, right?
They said the king used to reside here.
Just imagine the energy this place has!
There are so many of you, but I must apologize.
We do not have any rooms available.
Please let me sleep with the servants if possible.
I will pay double the rent.
I am sorry.
We have too many people who asked for that.
(Placed upside down.)
There is a line of guests first thing in the morning.
We'll become a grand merchant at this rate.
You are right. Please bring the side dishes from inside.
Oh, yes.
I can never get enough of this view... of such a vast ocean.
Let us come during sunset next time.
They said it is so beautiful.
Instead of next time...
there is something I want to do right now.
You should do it if you want to.
Whatever it is.
♫  Melting in again, baby, your love  ♫
♫  Drowning in my imagination  ♫
♫  Dazzles my eyes, like the sunlight  ♫
♫  Lost in a dream that is you  ♫
♫  When I'm walking for countless nights  ♫
♫  The star that shines on me  ♫
♫  Whenever it may be, let me be with you  ♫
I heard you are at the top of the class for this year's state exam.
Your loyal advice toward me was well displayed in your essay.
I am deeply grateful, Your Majesty.
Yoon Yook Ho, I will appoint you the King's Messenger in the Office of Special Advisors.
Please do your best to support me.
I will serve you with my body and soul.
Sir! You finally passed the exam!
I did not just pass the exam. I am the top scholar!
The proud and great first place!
Najudaek will be overjoyed to find out. Right?
Najudaek!
You are our village's pride!
What did I tell you?
If you just pass the exam, I will even hunt a boar and—
Wait! Did you hunt this yourself?
Well, I went and bought it in person.
A fresh one from the butcher shop.
I see, huh?
Ihwawon is doing great, and you are successful, too.
Goodness. There is no time for my smile to go away lately.
I am the King's Messenger in the Office of Special Advisors.
Address me as King's Messenger from now.
Yes.
Is anyone there?
I invited her.
Seo Yeon! Hurry up and take a seat.
Congratulations on passing the exam, Sir.
Right.
San, are you aware of Shi Yeol's whereabouts?
I did get contacted from time to time, but even that has stopped lately.
He seems to be wandering aimlessly, but where could he be now?
It would have been great for everyone to have gathered.
Are you still having a hard time... whenever you think about Brother Shi Yeol?
Dan Oh...
I already forgave him.
He probably did not want to live such a life, either.
It is only because of what fate had given to him was...
too harsh and cruel.
That is why I forgave him.
However...
I cannot...
forgive myself for...
forgiving him.
I am very glad to see you happy.
You seem more at peace now, too.
It is thanks to you who restored my status.
It was only the right thing to do.
One by one, regain the things you lost, Maiden.
The things I lost?
For example, happiness or memories...
The time I spent with you was... also happiness and memories for me.
It is great to see you for the first time in a while.
Have you been doing well?
Yes, Brother—
Gosh. Your Majesty.
You can address me comfortably when it is just us.
I cannot do that.
You are the absolute king.
Right...
According to what I heard from Mr. Yook Ho, you two are leaving Hanyang soon?
We plan to leave as soon as we are done preparing.
If it is because of me, do not do it.
I prefer to stay close to my friends.
I do not think that is being considerate of you, Your Majesty.
You are the graceful king this humble one has wished for.
Therefore, I will not provide any cause for political strife.
It has long been my dream... to travel far away.
All right. When will you be coming back?
I do not know.
I plan to travel without a specific goal and stay at places freely, too.
Please talk more with Dan Oh.
I will take my leave now.
I heard you got promoted. Are you now Captain Yoon?
Thank you.
It would have been great to have you with me, too.
How are things going at the Royal Guard lately?
We are all sleep deficient.
Since His Majesty even sacrifices sleep for work.
You are really paying back 100 silver ingots.
Since the people of Mt. Sobaek are having a hard time,
I will put it to good use in helping them.
Yes.
This is all thanks to you, Your Majesty.
Why is that thanks to me?
You are the graceful king Ihwawon produced, right?
The rumors are widespread, so we are full of guests.
That is fortunate.
It feels like yesterday we were worried about having no guests.
These days, I am conflicted if I should build
another guesthouse and where it should be.
There were days we used to talk and laugh like this.
I also... miss those days sometimes.
The days when we used to smile altogether.
Have you still not heard from Shi Yeol?
Yes.
Your Majesty, it is soon time for your council.
After today... it will be hard to see you.
Please take care... Brother.
Dan Oh...
can I... hug you just once?
Of course.
I will take my leave now.
Please sleep at night and be at peace from time to time, Your Majesty.
If the king is at peace, his people will suffer, do they not?
San...
wherever you are... be well.
Yes. I will.
Let us go.
You may go ahead.
Have you met with His Majesty?
I heard you are leaving soon.
Yes.
I intend not to enter the palace after today.
That is this humble one's loyalty.
San of the Kang family.
You are resolved to live as that name only.
I will take good care of His Majesty.
Since he has you, my footsteps are slightly lighter, Left State Minister.
Goodness. I said I would hang the sheets!
Have some sweets before you continue.
Later. I will eat them after I am done.
The moon is bright.
You should... walk around the yard sometimes, at least.
♪  When the petals fall from the wind that breezes by  ♪
♪  At every step my dear takes  ♪
♪  Only the angelicas bloom  ♪
♪  Gently and lightly—  ♪
Excuse me, Scholar.
Could you tell me where you heard that song?
I heard it from a scholar I met on the way here.
What is the matter?
Where did you hear it?
Where is that scholar right now?
He said he was going to the Mapo docks to set sail to the Qing Empire.
Come on! Hurry up!
Everyone, be careful!
There is no way he would still be here.
♫  Because I have been hiding these feelings  ♫
♫  The days I couldn't hope for  ♫
♫  They flow dimly by your side  ♫
♫  I only grow more distant from you  ♫
♫  This love that can't be seen  ♫
♫  These feelings I can't show you  ♫
♫  Because you're my everything that I can only watch from afar  ♫
♫  Do I just need to wait endlessly?  ♫
You... told me this before, right?
Although the man called Kim Shi Yeol may be an illusion,
your feelings for me are sincere without an inch of falsehood.
♫  Although it calls out to you like this  ♫
Do your feelings... still remain unchanged?
They did not change.
As time went by...
they only became clearer.
Then, let us walk through the door together.
♫  My heartbeat races toward you  ♫
♫  Its sound rings so loudly like this  ♫
♫  Although it calls out to you like this  ♫
All the lights are off.
Is everyone sleeping?
Indeed, you were not mistaken, Dan Oh.
I saw the two of them at the market on the way.
Your appearance lost its shine during those few years.
Did you have a tough time?
Welcome.
Your room has been kept empty all this time.
Under the authority of the hostess.
I am indeed ashamed of myself.
I made you all worry a lot. Right?
Bokshil?
It is our Bokshil!
I guess she followed her owner, who found her.
She came right on the day you came back, Brother.
Since Bokshil is also back, all of our family has gathered now.
Yes, you are right.
It is finally the Ihwawon I know.
- Goodness.
- Right, Bokshil?
Where have you been all this time?
Never mind.
That does not matter. What matters is that you came back.
I heard the royal family no longer raises Watchmen.
It was your request, was it not?
It was a cruel cycle that would have to be gone one day.
Thank you, San.
Thanks to you, the children of the hermitage will not live like me.
You should also go forward instead of looking back now.
Erase your dark shadow... and live your life now.
Each and every night...
How long do you plan to live, surrounded by work?
You need to find a queen as soon as possible and plan for your heir.
I am still young.
You are supposed to marry when you are young.
I will begin the queen selection process, so keep that in mind.
The country is finally stable.
I should focus on my duties for now.
Could it be that you have a lover whom you can not forget?
How pretty.
What are you doing?
You wanted to see the flowers together.
You cannot! Do not look yet.
It is my present to the bride whom I will marry.
Finally, you are more like yourself now.
It goes up like this...
and it droops down...
Letter s...
I was not fooling you on purpose.
But will it help me to learn to write them down without knowing the meaning?
"At that moment... King's Messenger's lips covered Yeon's lips."
You are my everything.
Goodness, seriously!
Gosh, the novel is shaking my heart—
Take your time to learn the letters.
- I will read it to you for the rest of my life.
- Oh, dear.
I plan to become a graceful king who sincerely... looks after his people's hearts.
Please look over me... Mother.
You are happy, right?
Since your final concern is smiling ear to ear like that.
Bride and Groom, bow and greet!
Vow to the heavens!
Vow to each other!
It feels sad to send you off.
We had finally gotten together.
Shi Yeol, the honeymoon stage only comes once.
- Do not be sad and have fun.
- "Shi Yeol"?
He should not call me by my name since I am of a higher rank than him.
Yes, he should not.
It is wrong in so many ways.
Family members should address each other properly.
So he says, Brother-in-Law Kang.
Gosh, I should have left earlier.
He is right in every way.
You need to call him Hyungnim now.
H-Hyungnim. Happy now?
Brother-in-Law Kang, what did you say just now?
- I could not hear you well.
- Hyung-
Cut it out.
I will make sure to protect Ihwawon... just the way you have been doing, Dan Oh.
You did not need to free me from my status.
I am sorry it was done too late.
Live happily ever after with Sir now, okay?
When you arrive, please send me a word.
Sir! I will be on my way now.
Do you not regret it, Brother?
Regret what?
The things you gave up for an ordinary day.
Not at all.
I have never regretted it, not even for a moment.
Since you are... by my side as always.
Channel Manager: crimac
Chief Editor: kakashiandme
Chief Segmenter: pilar_velasquez
Segmenters: pilar_velasquez, sabrinafair,
hana_860, nmelova, &amp; addictedtobooks
Thank you to our viewers.