Are you...
Are you really Head Eunuch?
Yes, Your Highness!
It is I.
Get up right now!
I thought I would never get to see you again.
I have no regrets, even if I die now.
Have you been well all this time?
I survived.
I put a lot of people in trouble, but I am safe myself.
How could you say such a thing?
You are the only hope in Joseon, Your Highness!
Father's belongings were received safely.
I thought they were gone.
Have you been keeping them?
Please come inside first.
I need to get going soon.
Why did you want to see me?
I am sorry, Your Highness.
The remaining ones... need to survive, too.
It's the king's order.
I was told to kill Lee Seol, the deposed crown prince's son immediately.
I heard warriors change the world with swords.
What exactly are you trying to change?
What changes by doing this?
To warriors... the king equals the world.
Lee Chang's era will... end eventually as well.
Just wait and see how this era ends.
On the other side.
Watchman?
Stop!
Stop it!
I do not want any more bloodshed!
Who are you?
Hyeon...
No...
You cannot do this!
Hyeon!
Is it because you all have been pampered while growing up?
You have no fear.
We are from Hanseongbu.
There was a report about a traitor sneaking inside an inn in Hanyang.
A traitor?
There is no one like that here at Ihwawon.
You had better be right.
If you want to protect this inn.
Take a good look. This is the last one.
Yes.
What do you think?
He is...
not here.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Could I see your identification tag?
Is there a reason you cannot show it?
The Jeong family of Naju?
What is your father's name—
His Excellency Jeong Yoon, the former Inspector General.
The curfew bell rang a long time ago.
Do you work regardless of day and night?
You are not from Hanyang.
Where did you come from?
Will you tell me only after I drag you to the Hanseongbu?
I am from Jecheon.
Jecheon?
I heard there is a village for the Kang family of Jinju there.
- The name of the governor of Jecheon is—
- It is Kang Gi Gap.
He is the head of my family.
I see.
Excuse me. I am here, too.
Your name is?
It is Kim Shi Yeol. His Excellency Kim Ho Ik's 14th...
No, was it the 15th?
- Anyway—
- A child of a concubine, I'm sure.
Yes, that is correct. A child of a concubine.
We looked all over Jungchon, but we could not even find a strand of Lee Seol's hair.
What do you think of that?
Let us wait a bit.
I am sure he will be caught soon.
Head Eunuch, I do not keep useless people around.
I cut them off.
You were cut off down there already.
So I guess the top will have to go.
(Referring to his head)
If there is anyone suspicious, I will report them to you immediately.
Let us go!
Ihwawon.
My god! It'll take forever to clean this!
Excuse me!
No need to see us off...
We will see each other again, anyway.
Where did you people come from?
I need to know so I can decide whether to pay off the debt or not.
We are from Buyounggak.
Buyounggak?
At this rate, Ihwawon might just become a courtesan house.
What?
One hundred silver ingots! How will they ever afford that?
It does not look like they have any money.
You should not be saying that when you are paying for the room with credit.
How about you?
You said you would only stay one night. And how many days have you been here now?
Seriously...
You are running away because you have nothing to say!
Here.
Have some.
My goodness! This!
I suppose Dan Oh is not home.
- No, she stepped out for a second.
- Wow.
This was the reason... why they have no customers.
Here.
Gosh, have some more.
The dumplings are very delicious.
Call the government office immediately if the thugs come back.
Yes, sir.
By the way, Ma'am...
Why does Dan Oh not get married?
I suppose...
she would look great in a wedding gown since she is good-looking.
Since her parents are gone, there is no one to look for a husband for her.
It just got delayed for those reasons.
It's always too late when you think it's too late.
Shall I look into a husband for her?
It is okay.
There are a lot of young men here.
Maybe we could look around us...
Around us?
You are hurting me without words.
- Geez! When did I do that—
- When?
Just now. Those shifty eyes of yours!
Okay. My, have some more dumplings!
Well, I...
My stomach! Geez...
You have such a clear head.
You act like a horse, too.
A horse? What do you mean by that?
You are like a crazy horse.
He is more like a foal.
- Well...
- You are a loose foal.
Stop! That is enough, everyone!
My... feelings are getting hurt a lot today.
Have some. Najudaek would get sad if you don't finish it.
(It means a woman from Naju)
Should I make you some tea?
It is okay.
There must have been a misunderstanding.
My father could not have owed money to a place like this.
No. He does not owe Buyounggak.
If so... who loaned him so much money, then?
Even if you find out, there is nothing you can do.
Tell me right now!
It is Judge Jang Tae Hwa.
What did you just say?
It is Hanseongbu's... Chief Administrator Jang.
Miss, you know what they say?
Poverty is just like a cold, apparently.
You cannot hide it even if you try.
No matter how you try to dress properly,
you cannot hide a stitched-up broken seam.
What are you trying to say?
I am saying that you... have no means to pay off such a big loan.
So why do you not just give me Ihwawon?
I cannot do that.
No matter what anyone says, I will protect Ihwawon.
It will be taken away in the end.
Unless you can offer something bigger than Ihwawon.
So you need physical evidence?
Yes.
Words disappear once you speak.
How could I trust something that I cannot see?
This is a promissory note your father wrote.
It is his handwriting, but... how come...
He borrowed it from me to care for his young students even though he was struggling.
You are no longer a child.
You had better pay off your father's debt now.
But still... how could he suddenly borrow such a large sum of money?
I made a promise to your father a long time ago.
One day, if my son and his eldest daughter
get married, and we became in-laws, I would cancel his debt.
However, they were engaged, but they did not get to have a wedding.
And the debt still remains—
- That is because your son—
- Shut your mouth!
She was a part of my family since she was engaged.
She should have lived as a widow at my house.
- Sir.
- However... your older sister...
used her illness as an excuse to be stuck in Ihwawon and passed away.
So... I am not in-laws with your family.
Brother!
Looks like that fixed it.
Check if it is good.
Please let your hand go.
Right?
Yes.
- You should have let your presence be known—
- Did you cry?
N-No!
I did not cry.
You did cry.
You lie habitually.
People usually pretend they don't see it at times like this.
- But you really had to—
- Do not cry.
I told you not to cry.
It makes you look ugly!
This is why they say you should not care for someone else's child.
You show up out of nowhere and demand money?
You are not just asking for a little. You want 100 silver ingots.
- If you give me a loan, I will make sure to pay you back.
- No.
I do not want to waste a single poon on you.
(Unit of currency)
I disliked you from the beginning.
Since Father brought you here, saying you were his hidden child.
Stop.
It is the mother of Lady Park.
She is here for post-natal care.
Did you go and bring her yourself? You did not send a messenger?
She was about to go into labor. It was an emergency situation.
Well, then...
Let us go.
Hold on!
Your Majesty, this is Eunuch Yoon.
Come on in.
Your Majesty, Lady Park delivered the child safely.
How about the child? Is the child okay?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Congratulations.
It is a prince.
In your fate, you do not have a son.
Is this a Sajudanja?
What is wrong?
What does it say, anyway? Gosh! It is so frustrating!
Just say something!
"I ask you to marry me, Maiden.
I heard that Ihwawon is full of debt.
If you marry me,
I will pay your debt of one hundred silver ingots right away.
Sir Ong."
Sir Ong...
It is him, is it not?
The one with eyes like this. The one who always follows you around!
How did he hear about your situation, anyway?
I will send it back right away. Give it to me.
Just leave it there for a bit.
Give it to me right now!
He is someone who buys people off.
I can never let him have my precious lady!
Precious, my foot.
No one thinks of me that way.
Since when was I an aristocrat?
To me, you are the most precious person in the world.
So you had better not say stuff like that!
I know.
But it still is an official proposal.
It will hurt his feelings if I reject him immediately.
I am okay.
Just drink it!
This might be... our last time having sujunggwa.
(Cinnamon persimmon dessert drink)
Who sent that sajudanja earlier?
Sajudanja?
Which family was it from?
Tell us!
Men understand men better.
Later.
You look very troubled.
He must be a really ugly man.
I mean,
they say you cannot live in a thatched cottage after living in a tile-roofed house.
You have seen this handsome man every day.
I am sure you are not satisfied with most men!
Yes, yes. Let us say that.
Just finish the rest of sujunggwa.
Wait. You said you will not have any!
I changed my mind.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, to the market.
I just ran out of paper.
I need to go there as well. Let us go together.
How great. It would have been boring to go alone.
Gosh, so boring.
How can my day be so full of boredom?
Do you want to come with us, Brother?
Sure thing. Get some fresh air the first time in a while.
It has not been that long, has it?
You are going as well?
- I also have some business.
- Why?
Are you going to get your sword sharpened by the carpenter?
Should I sharpen something else... besides the sword?
Wh-Where?
Anywhere.
I guess you are happy?
What do you mean?
You just... do not seem to be thinking of leaving Ihwawon at all.
Are we really one family now?
I am going to take a look at some swords.
You all can go ahead.
Sure, sure.
Goodness, you are here, Miss?
Dan Oh was also a woman, huh?
She cannot pass by the accessory shop without stopping.
There.
I had it made with special care.
I also used only the most precious materials, too.
Goodness, I know of your skills very well, Miss.
There you go.
Five nyang?
This does not even cover the cost of the materials.
I used only the best ones, such as coral and wheat flowers.
So do not be like that and let us do 10 nyang...
One hundred silver ingots!
I will buy them for 100 silver ingots.
As long as you will marry me.
Anyway, you are...
bound to fall into my embrace, so just give in at this point.
What makes you so sure to be saying that?
It is obvious what choice a woman struck in poverty has to make. Right?
Stop playing hard to get.
Am I doing this only for my own good?
- Who are you?
- That is enough.
Are you that guy from before?
He still could not fix his dirty habit.
How dirty, seriously.
How many men are you seducing with that innocent-looking face?
A noble family's lady should know what is shameful.
You, Sir Ong!
- What? Sir Ong?
- Yes, you!
You who are rude and ignorant!
I am going to say this only once, so listen up.
What is this bad feeling?
No matter how the world changes, marriage is between human beings.
What? I am not a human being?
It is better to drown in a lake like Shim Cheong than to marry a beast.
(Korean folklore character)
Wh-Why are you suddenly speaking informally to me?
Do people speak with honorifics to dogs?
What? D-Dogs?
I refuse... your proposal.
Let us go.
Poor thing. He got rejected.
- How pitiful.
- So embarrassing. Geez.
Is something wrong?
Nothing happened. Let us hurry and go.
It will be taken away in the end.
Unless you can offer something bigger than Ihwawon.
Something bigger.
Something bigger, huh?
Take a good look.
This is the last one.
Goodness, there was so much trouble.
They rummaged the rooms and checked each and every one of the scholar's identification tags.
They also came by Ihwawon.
By the way, who is that man?
He did not look like an officer of the Hanseongbu.
But he seemed to be their company.
I think they said he used to be a eunuch who served the king.
After that day, he frequents Buyounggak, too.
He drinks every day with courtesans.
A eunuch... is looking for a traitor?
Are you not curious?
Why Lee Seol came to Hanyang... when the place is filled with people who are after his life.
Lee Seol is warning us right now.
Warning us that he will come to take this seat soon.
Your Majesty... today is a joyful day.
Please do not worry your mind.
We never know.
He might be quietly building an army somewhere.
Lee Seol is a traitor.
Even if he has an army, your humble servant will eradicate it by the roots.
I will take your word, Left State Minister.
We must get rid of Lee Seol quickly... in order to secure the prince's future.
Stop there.
Where does the court lady go, that only the palace maids remain?
Well, Court Lady Yoon is gravely ill, so she has left the palace.
Gravely ill?
Is it really okay to do this?
If things go wrong while we kidnap a virgin who is not even a widow...
Does she have parents or siblings who will protect her?
- How could things go wrong?
- Okay.
Why did you approach me so quietly?
Gosh, my heart dropped.
Why are you so lost in thought?
I lost my voice from calling you.
- See? It is gone.
- Goodness.
The alcohol must be to blame.
You drink every other day when you have the state exam to take.
And you think your voice will be fine?
Are you nagging me right now?
It is nice to hear for some reason.
What is this now?
What do you mean "this"? His name is Boksil.
- Boksil?
- Yes.
Cute, is he not?
There was an empty dog house on the premise but no dog.
- So I brought one.
- Who said you can?
My god, you do not even pay the rent on time.
We just got one more mouth to feed.
Boksil, you need to mind your manners. She is the innkeeper.
"Sister, please take me."
Boksil... I am letting you go for your name.
His name?
It was Boksil.
The name of the dog I used to raise.
Really?
This is totally fate. We are fated to raise Boksil.
"Sister, wait for me."
Dan Oh— Dan Oh!
- Hey, tonight is the chance. Okay?
- Yes.
- I do not want to get wet, so carry me.
You there!
I advise you not to cross.
You will be crossing over into the netherworld.
- What a crazy bastard we have here! Hey...
- Yes.
- Hurry up and cross.
- Y-Yes.
I am telling you to go over first. Go.
That crazy bastard!
Hey, hurry up and cross!
Hurry up and take the lead!
All right, hurry up.
H-Hey!
We will go get more people.
Hey! Where are you going?
Hey!
Where are you going? Hey!
Hey! Where are you all going?
H-Hey! Hey!
Look here. Please spare me.
I am the second son of the Ong family, one of the most wealthy farmers of Jungchon.
What do you want?
I will give you anything. Okay?
H-Hey!
Do you know who I am?
How will you take responsibility for this?
Instead of bossam today,
(Means braised pork, same spelling/sound as kidnapping)
I must make radish kimchi today.
(Name of this kimchi sounds like "bachelor" in Korean)
I will withdraw my proposal.
I will not ever seek you out, so please give him a good word for me.
I am so scared of that man.
That man?
Wh-What does it... say?
O-Oh, here.
That man... yes.
He...
Yes.
Gosh...
For Brother Yoo Ha's character... he would not use his fists.
Brother Shi Yeol?
He would have been the one who got beaten.
That means the only one left is...
His martial skills were unlike the others.
Could it be?
Have you made an enemy with the ground?
Where have you been?
Could it be... you did not come in last night?
Do I need to report stuff like that, too?
Well, you do not have to, but I could ask.
Excuse me.
Brother, was it you, by any chance?
- What was?
- Sir Ong.
Just how much did you scare him?
S-Sir Ong? Who is that?
You really were not the one who did it?
I am not free enough to meddle in someone else's marriage.
You saw it all at the market, right?
Since you mentioned marriage.
You are the only one in this house... whom the reckless Sir Ong would fear.
No way.
That was the case, though.
Well, if you say it was, I guess it was.
By the way... why would you, Brother...
Do not get the wrong idea.
I did not do it for your sake, Dan Oh.
- For whom, then?
- The thing is...
Th-The sujeonggwa tasted good.
Sorry?
Here.
Eat it on the way.
You did not eat breakfast.
Thank you for the food.
Also, take this.
Could you not refuse and just accept it?
It is not that much money, either.
I thought you might be able to cover the byeonri for now.
It is because I want to stay at Ihwawon for a long time.
I will try to take care of it.
So you can stay at Ihwawon for a long time.
By the way, how did you know it was from me?
Come on. Who else would?
It is obvious to anyone with eyes.
Brother!
I will need to broom again.
Brother, you are... a really kind person.
You broom the yard when the flowers rain, too.
In that case... you should accept this as well.
I also have a sense of shame.
What kind of innkeeper borrows money from her guests?
Am I just a guest to you?
I am saying the inn is my responsibility.
No matter how close we are, you cannot do my work in my place every time.
All right.
I was being too selfish.
Not at all.
I will gratefully accept your heart only.
- Anyhow, are you going somewhere?
- Yes.
I am going to visit my head family. I will be back quite late.
I see.
Please have a safe trip, then.
I will be back.
You are here? Take a seat.
We are on the third page.
"A young lord tries to rule the world, calling himself a king.
During the first year of the young king's reign, a huge series of imprisonment takes place
and there will be rivers of blood."
The young king it mentions...
- Could it be?
- His Majesty had a son after more than a decade, right?
The rebellious monarch got his revenge.
Since he got a son who will inherit the throne, it will be a matter of time until
he finds and gets rid of the "jade dust."
Frankly, the "jade dust" is like a speck of dust to His Majesty.
Just how badly would he want to dust it off?
I was residing at Buyounggak a few days ago.
Hanseongbu officers suddenly barged in looking for the traitor.
Then, could that be the...
I also went to the tavern yesterday and they were looking for the traitor there, too.
He is trying to find and get rid of the "jade dust."
I am done for the day.
Huh?
I will be on my way now, too.
One more round and I can pay for three months' rent.
Are you the host of Buyounggak, who is rumored to be the heavenly beauty?
I heard you are staying at Ihwawon.
That is true. Did the word spread that far?
How is living at... Ihwawon?
It would be nice for it to be as bustling as this place.
But it is very quiet.
I guess there are not that many guests staying at that place?
Compared to this place, there are not many.
However, there is a lot of trouble.
Trouble?
Since three young scholars are staying there, there are small issues.
How are the scholars you are staying with?
There must be many compromises to make if you live together.
There are a lot.
However, you seem to have a lot as well.
Pardon?
A lot of what?
Interest in Ihwawon.
You seem to be deeply troubled.
Please do not feel rushed.
A figure who spent more than 10 years in hiding... will not get caught so easily.
That is why I must get him.
Without fail, this time.
If the "jade dust" is caught, what will happen to him?
Since he is the traitor of the age, he will kneel in front of His Majesty. Right?
The "jade dust" will not be able to meet His Majesty.
Because I will kill him before that.
How does it take forever for you to get dressed?
What are you doing here?
I was waiting.
To cheer for you, Brother.
Just do not get in my way. Move aside, so I can go.
Pass with a top score! You know, right?
The reputation of our prestigious inn, Ihwawon... lies on your shoulders.
I will consider it.
What do you mean you will consider? You have to pass.
Just pass if you can.
Her fingers will give if she has to twist another yeot.
(Korean traditional confectionery)
You made this yourself?
Of course. This much is easy.
You know my cooking skills.
Make sure to eat the yeot and pass!
It is now time.
- Go ahead and start.
- Yes.
We will now begin the Periodic State Martial Exam!
There!
♫  How beautiful, I hug you as I close my eyes  ♫
♫  You always bloom  ♫
♫  All the roads I will have to walk  ♫
♫  I want to walk them all with you  ♫
♫  Yeah  ♫
Bullseye!
What brings you, ladies, here?
We came to take a look at our new home.
I heard it was spacious, but the rooms are smaller than I thought.
Small, my foot.
Also, who said you could take a look around right now?
Stop being so stubborn.
This place will soon become Buyounggak anyway.
Have you found a new place to live yet?
Miss...
It's a little too small...
Wait a moment.
Can we let them be like that?
Even courtesans think this place is their home now.
Do not worry. I will take care of it.
But there is no way out of this.
You also know well, Najudaek.
I can never give up Ihwawon.
- So—
- I know... why you are trying to protect Ihwawon.
I know, but still...
That is why. Please do as I say.
Please, I'm begging you.
Just get rid of me instead.
What do you mean by that?
This rotten body is so old now, so you will not get much money for it.
- But you will at least be able to pay—
- Najudaek.
Miss...
I have been... a servant of this family since birth.
This is my fate.
- So—
- Najudaek... you were a mother to me when I lost my parents.
Never for a moment was it otherwise.
So, please... do not even mention such a thing again.
Fail!
Next up, Sang Yoon of Kangsan Kim family!
Get ready!
Start!
- Oh no!
- M-My goodness.
Fail!
Are you not Left State Minister?
What brings you all the way here?
You are all doing great work.
Would I be allowed to spectate?
I am curious about this year's martial exam students.
Oh, yes.
Please come take a seat here.
Next, San of Jinju's Kang Family! Get ready!
Start!
Wh-Whoa, he is going to fall.
Pass!
I heard men are lining up for Hong Shim after she saw the virgin ghost by the well.
I also heard that.
That is all because of the virgin ghost's grudge since she died without knowing the taste of men.
Can we really see her if we go to the annex?
- Of course.
- Let's go.
You cannot go there.
That place is—
It is indeed quite scary.
Should we just go back?
It is okay. Just follow me.
- Scholar Kim!
- I told you! It is already working.
- Come out right away!
- Sorry?
Do not look back!
Scholar Kim...
Look at me.
Come closer.
- Hurry.
- Gosh, Scholar Kim... did you miss us that badly?
How ignorant of us.
G-Ghost—
Move! Move!
A ghost! It is a ghost!
Is something wrong?
Where is she going this late at night?
Anyone there?
I came to meet Chief Administrator Jang.
What exactly is this place?
You could not have already gotten 100 silver ingots.
I did not.
Then... did you come to hand over your house?
I cannot... hand Ihwawon over to you.
What did you say?
Instead... I will hand myself over.
One hundred silver ingots are more than enough to house the most famous courtesans in my annex.
I am not a courtesan who sells laughter.
You cannot compare me to them.
How arrogant.
What value would a mere being like you have for me?
Will it be... enough if I find him for you?
How do you know whom I am looking for?
I heard... he is called by this name.
The "jade dust".
Deposed crown prince's son who disappeared.
Lee Seol.
Dan Oh is looking for the "jade dust"?
Where did you say you're going?
To Gwacheonhyeon. I must go.
Well, then. Let us go together.
I came because of you. Worried that you might get hurt.
Do you want to marry me?
Has it even crossed your mind?
Where he could be and in what shape?
What is your true goal?
The one who can find him the best is me.
Countless people died looking for the "jade dust".
Do not find him. Stop looking for the one you are trying to find right now.