Just like Itsuki-san said...
It's a beautiful town.
I wanted to know about the town
where Minato grew up.
Could you please tell me about it?
Why?
I want to go there and take some pictures.
He mentioned before...
that he can't remember
what his childhood home looked like.
I see.
He had this pained look on his face...
saying he couldn't...
bring himself to go near that town.
He seemed so sad,
and it's been on my mind ever since.
So I thought I'd go see it for him.
That's a wonderful idea.
Hold on a second.
In that case, this...
I'd like you to hold onto it for now.
A standalone house by the sea.
The attic there...
was Minato's favorite place.
It's a really beautiful town.
It really is.
"Therapy Game"
(Episode 8)
I was wondering what this place would be like.
It's even more beautiful...
than I ever imagined.
Let's check out the beach.
(Phone battery below 3%.
Shutting down soon.)
Oh, crap! Is there a convenience store?
(Call from Itsuki)
What's up?
You finally picked up.
I've been trying to call you since yesterday.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
Shizuma...
He came to my place.
Are you just going to keep avoiding him?
Listen, Minato.
Isolating yourself because you're scared of
getting hurt is just foolish.
I know what it's like to be afraid of getting close to people.
But you know...
if you just take that first step...
you'll realize it's not a big deal at all.
There's no need to be scared.
It'll be more freeing...
than you can possibly imagine.
I want to, I really do...
but I just can't be like you.
Shizuma came to see me.
He wanted to know about the town
where we grew up.
What?
The reason for that...
you of all people should know, right?
Shizuma...
hasn't given up on you yet.
I bet right now...
he's in that town.
Huh?
Since when was my little brother such a wimp?
Bro...
If I mess up again...
will you be there to comfort me?
What are you talking about?
You're the brother I'm most proud of.
There's no way you'll fail.
Everything will be fine.
You have to believe in yourself.
Thanks.
Bro.
Why couldn't I understand him back then?
From the very beginning...
he was always suffering.
Mom, I found a seashell!
You did?
Wow.
You really did.
Our family...
used to be just a normal, happy family.
Yeah.
But...
when Minato was still in elementary school...
our father started seeing another man.
After that...
Dad ran away with him.
Our mother had a nervous breakdown and killed herself.
In a small town like this, it became a huge scandal.
After that...
our father's body was found.
Apparently, his lover was a con artist
who was just after his money,
and then killed him.
Before our mom took her own life...
she would often take her anger out on us.
Minato was just a little kid back then.
It was truly agonizing for him.
This place...
it's so beautiful.
You know this place?
It's dead.
It's okay.
Shizuma is here.
The number you have dialed...
is currently out of the service area.
No way.
The number you have dialed...
- Hello?
- Shohei.
Shizuma won't answer his phone.
You must have heard where he went, right?
I have no idea.
Hold on, I'm gonna hang up for a sec.
Huh?
Shizuma...
- I heard he's unreachable.
- What?
You're the guy who returned his student ID, right?
You're the one from back then...
- Yep.
- Speakerphone, put it on speaker.
Um...
No matter what, I need to
see Shizuma and talk to him.
That's why I followed him to Miura.
But I can't get through to his phone.
If you know anything, please tell me.
What are you going to do when you see him?
I don't care if he ends up hating me.
I want to face him with everything I've got.
Please...
How long are you going to be a jerk about this?
Sorry about that.
We were worried too. He's been...
in a really bad mood lately.
Ah, but...
all we heard today...
was that he wasn't coming to school.
I found him.
I hadn't deleted the location-sharing app.
I can only see his last location
before his phone died, though.
Think of this as me repaying you
for helping with the calf birth.
Huh?
Even though you two had plans...
you said it was okay
and let him come find me.
Right?
That's what Shizuma told me.
Ah.
Found it.
His last location was...
at 2:24 PM.
Enami Pebble Beach.
Somewhere around there.
Enami Pebble Beach?
I heard the temperature drops around there at night.
You should be careful.
Thank you.
This helps a lot.
Shizuma...
That's all I can do to help.
Right.
By the way,
why wouldn't you delete the app after you broke up?
People will think you're creepy.
Sorry, I totally forgot about it.
I'll delete it now.
Shizuma!
Minato?
Hey, why are you here...?
Don't mind...
But why are you here?
Why wouldn't you answer your phone?
Sorry.
- What are you doing in a place like this?
- Ouch, that hurts!
I came all this way to find you.
Minato...
Damn it.
You shouldn't make people worry like that...
You came to find me?
Yeah.
This must be hard for you.
Coming here.
It is hard.
But I found you.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to understand why
you said what you did back then.
The only thing I could do...
was come here myself.
Yeah.
You didn't give up on me.
Thank you.
Hey.
By the way, how did you know I was at the beach?
Yuka found you.
Yuka...
The location-sharing app.
She never deleted it.
Tatsumi and...
someone else helped too.
You and Tatsumi?
Huh?
And Chikazawa.
Never mind all that.
I just really wanted to see you.
This...
Itsuki lent it to me.
The keys to my family's house.
He said he kept it because it's full of family memories.
He couldn't bring himself to sell it,
so he's been maintaining it.
Brother...
If you don't want to go back, you don't have to.
We can always do this another time.
I...
Let's go.
I want to go with you.
This road...
My brother and I used to walk down it all the time.
Back in elementary school?
Yeah.
I had piano lessons down the street,
and my brother would always come and get me.
Oh, so you play the piano?
Just a little.
My mom liked it.
She always made such a big deal out of my recitals.
I'd only play a simple piece,
but she'd show up with this huge bouquet of flowers
for me.
It was so embarrassing.
But...
I was actually really happy.
I was so proud of my beautiful mom.
Yeah.
My dad was gentle back then, too.
But...
he's the reason our family fell apart.
And while I hated him for abandoning us...
it was my mom, who completely lost it after he left,
that I was truly afraid of.
Even now, I can still picture
my mom's face, twisted with jealousy.
Does falling in love with someone...
turn you into that?
I couldn't help but wonder.
We're here.
Are you okay?
So nostalgic.
It's been over ten years,
but it looks exactly the same.
It's so spacious.
Right?
It's a loft.
This was your favorite place.
That's what Itsuki said.
It's just as I remember.
Was it always this small?
I can't believe I had a secret hideout like this as a kid.
My brother and I would hang out here every night.
It was cramped and dusty,
so my mom would never come up.
But blood ties are a scary thing.
When I look in the mirror,
I look just like my mother.
Just like that face, twisted with jealousy.
Getting betrayed hurts,
but hurting someone you care about...
that's what scares me most.
You only get betrayed because
you expect things from people.
If that's the case, then from the start,
all this stuff about love and affection...
isn't it better to just not believe in any of it?
That's the messed-up way I've lived my life.
Hey, Minato.
This house...
Do you know why Itsuki
never sold it?
No, I don't.
He said that no matter what happened in the past,
this was the precious home he shared
with you.
That's why he couldn't bring himself to sell it.
He worked so hard
for this house.
He told me that with a smile on his face.
He never told me any of that.
Oh.
And there's this.
- Please, you have to believe in Minato-chan.
- That's right.
I'm begging you, please believe in Minato-chan.
To get you to believe in Minato-chan...
I shaved my head.
Me too... I'll do anything.
- Please believe in him.
- I mean it.
Me too.
The guy actually shaved his head.
Just hurry up and open your shop already.
Why would they go so far for me...?
Because everyone truly loves you.
You're cherished by so many people.
Don't you think
you should start valuing yourself more?
What happened in the past
doesn't determine your future.
The only one who can
is the you right now.
The me...
right now?
I've made more mistakes than I can stand myself.
And I hurt you deeply.
That's why
I don't want to make the same mistakes again.
What about you?
Do you want to be with me?
Or not?
Of course I want to be with you.
But...
If that's how you feel,
then look at the man standing in front of you.
I love you,
Minato.
I want to know you better.
I want to be with you.
I want to make you happy.
No, it's cold.
Don't.
Don't you run away.
Decide.
I promise you won't regret it.
Choose me.
I've made my decision.
With everything you said...
I believe you.
Minato.
- We can't, Minato...
- I want to.
I want to be yours, right now.
(Next Episode)
Before I knew it, Shizuma was there.
With him, I thought everything would be okay.
Just your gaze,
just your touch...
is enough to make me feel so complete.
I'm holding nothing back.
You'd better treasure me.