(Remembrance of Things Past)
(I'll send it to you when I am home)
Why are you here?
Why don't you put on your pants?
(What time are you home?)
It's 4:30 pm, you're still in bed?
(Around 7 or 8 pm. Is it okay?)
What are you up to?
You invited me for dinner. Did you forget?
I didn't. Come in
(It's too late. Send it before 4 pm)
What's going on?
I'm sorry. I got drunk last night
It was my buddy's birthday
(I'm watching a movie, it ends at 3:30 pm)
and he insisted on having liquor
(Sorry, Mr. Huang)
I told him I am a light drinker
But he insisted
That's setting things back!
I didn't forget about it
(We're working overtime here)
I planned to pick you up from the bank
(and you are watching a movie?)
Luckily you didn't
I came here after meeting a client nearby
Do you feel better?
(First, weekends are days off)
I'm sorry
(I have the right to whether watch a movie)
I messed up our first date
(or go shopping)
We'll take a rain check
(As long as I don't break the law)
No! We can have it today
Let me do the wash-up, just a minute
(no one can interfere. It's up to the rest
if they want to work overtime)
(But I won't do so without a valid reason!)
(Fourth, I signed the employment contract
Not a slave contract!)
(Delete)
(Okay)
(Above are my questions)
(Episode 7: Decluttering and Detaching)
I have checked it
This is not vitamin supplements
but Paroxetine
What is that?
It is an antidepressant drug
Antidepressant?
It is a prescription drug
Generally, it is not available in pharmacies
Nan Jia
We've known each other for years
You may share your problems with me
It's not mine
That's great
If someone close to you is taking this
be more concerned about them
By the way, great that you're here today
This is your examination report
Is there any problem?
Everything is good
According to your current status
you need a follow-up check
only every half a year
You don't have to come every three months
I just want to be cautious
Well, I'll come back in six months
I remember you insisted
on preserving fertility during the operation
Do you still want to bear children?
I can only go with the flow
I do want to bear children
if I meet the right person
Why?
You have had an operation after all
Although your recovery went well
it still affected your hormone levels
at certain degree
Also, considering your age
if you consider conceiving a child
I suggest you not leaving it too late
How late can I delay it?
Getting pregnant
within these two years would be ideal
Else, your fertility will decrease over time
Also, childbearing will put you
at increased risk of health problems
Got it. You mean I won't be able to
get pregnant after this period, right?
This is not absolute
Just take it easy
My goodness
- Alright! Thank you, Dr Zhao
- No problem
(Beijing Yi He Hospital)
After meeting with Bai Fan
I can't figure out
why she played the stock market
and why she needed so much money
So I searched her belongings and found this
Was Jing Jing really taking this?
I saw her eating this
What are you eating?
It's vitamin pills, from you
I am not taking it regularly
If you're taking, you can take mine too
Alright. I'll get from you
after finishing mine
Okay
I didn't even think of that
Look, it is a prescription drug
To get it, Jing Jing had
to get the doctor's prescription
Do you mean we can know more about it
- if we have Jing Jing's medical record?
- Yes
- Let's go
- Let's find it
Look
Since college, Jing Jing
stayed around eight years in Beijing
In the end, her belongings
were just three boxes in total
People think they have plenty assets
but in the end, only these few are left
I can't accept it
I have to take away everything I bought
- Let's do it!
- Let's get started!
The medical record is easy to spot
There are only toys in this box
Why would she keep this?
- What's that?
- Isn't that her basketball club uniform?
Right! It's been so long
I remember Jing Jing was so determined
There were so many clubs
but she was hell bent
on joining basketball club to do scut work
Why did she join basketball club?
Did she love sports?
You reminded me of that
She were infatuated
with a boy during her time in college
She dated someone in college?
I didn't know about it!
Don't rush
She didn't
She was hell bent on joining the club
Xu Yan and I found it fishy
We were wondering if she fancied...
The basketball club's chairman
What's the senior's name?
- His name is Gao Tian Yang, right?
- What? I don't remember
How can you forget it?
You were so excited about it!
We egged her on to make
a confession. Did you forget it?
I have a bad memory
I can't remember everything
What's next?
Nothing, he got a girlfriend
Then, we stopped bringing it up
Jing Jing still kept the shirt
She was really in love with him
Her things are like nesting dolls
Xu Yan, do you remember this sweater?
Xu Yan! Why are you in a daze?
Nothing. There is an empty box
- It looks gorgeous
- It is empty
I found it
The medical record
I'll make an appointment
with this doctor to find out what happened
What's this?
Look! Why are there so many tickets?
Let me have a look
We have been here before!
But look, she got double tickets
for each attraction spot
That's right
Why did she revisit
the places we went together?
And look
She had double tickets for the same spots
But one of them isn't torn
- What's going on?
- Was Jing Jing stood up?
Let me check the dates
She didn't seem to be in a relationship
with Gao Yang at this time
So, who do you think
Jing Jing wanted to go with?
Let's go! Come on, cheer together with me
- What are you doing?
- I'm not going to cheer
Aren't you tired?
Which one are you talking about?
Did you see the one holding the ball?
Now he is passing the ball!
- Is it No. 23?
- No. How could it be No. 23?
But he looks okay. He's tall
This, the one getting the ball
No, No. 11. Did you see him?
Group Leader Lin!
- Brother Qiang
- Good morning!
Please don't call me that
It hasn't been officially announced
You're just an email away from it
I heard from the sales department
that your presentation was wonderful
In fact, I didn't perform well
out of nervousness
You didn't perform well?
I can't imagine how good you are
when you perform well
You oversea elites are brilliant
Please give me a leg up in the future
Brother Qiang, that's very flattering
I'm new in the company
I still need your help and support
You are overly modest
Well. I'll buy you a meal
to celebrate your promotion
No problem! I'll buy you a meal
- If you insist
- Sure
Come in!
Mr. Jian, may I know when
the product development officially starts?
You are here just in time
I was about to call you. Have a seat
Regarding the new product development
after the discussion
with the sales and R&D directors
I decided to adopt Qiao Xi Chen's proposal
As for the candidate
for the second group's leader
I need some time to think it over
Mr. Jian, I don't get it
Is my proposal not good enough?
It's the opposite
I think your proposal is extraordinary
especially the sales section,
it's distinctive
I can't get it
You bring the concept of craft beer to coffee
and make our cold brew stand out
At the same time
there's a breakthrough in the packaging
However, if my memory serves me right
a popular foreign coffee brand called Sanders
employed the same concept last year
You adapted their strategy wonderfully
However
it's still their idea
Mr. Jian, such adaptions
can be found everywhere here
- Also, most of them...
- That is their business
Yann Coffee is different
Just because everyone else is doing it
doesn't make it right
Also, domestic market is different nowadays
People nowadays are in clover
They will definitely realize it
if we put this on the market
I don't want to be doxed by the netizens
and labeled as a plagiarist
Lin Rui
I told you that I like
those who take shortcuts
but shortcuts may get you lost
I got it, Mr. Jian
What happened?
Beats me
Wasn't it almost finalized?
The winner is not determined yet
(Beijing Medical Institution)
(Medical Record)
Hu Jing Jing started her treatment
with me in March of this year
Her initial diagnosis was moderate depression
She was on medication over four months
She was supposed to come
for a follow-up visit three months ago
However, she didn't show up
The nurse hasn't been able to get hold of her
I thought she was getting better
and decided to stop medication
(Beijing Medical Institution)
(Medical Record)
Next week?
Yes, I'm free
Anyway, I'm not going home
on the National Day
Okay, you can count on me
- Who was that?
- Nothing
Nan Jia, is your Polo car still here?
I offered it to you but you said
you have nowhere to park it
That's right. Can I use it on National Day?
Aren't you going
for a business trip that day?
I'll tell the manager
to send someone else, it's okay
Can I borrow it on National Day?
Who is the important person?
It's just a college friend
Who is this college friend?
(National Stadium Beijing)
Mine?
Really?
Are you kidding me?
Do you think I have nothing to do?
I don't mean that
The rub is I didn't perform well that day
Indeed
But I remember I told you on the rooftop
that I like your proposal
I thought it was words of comfort
Well
It's half and half
In fact, I had another meeting
with the directors of R&D
and sales departments that day
We compared the proposals
of yours and Lin Rui's in details
At last, we found your proposal more suitable
What about the position
of the second group's leader?
You don't have to think about it now
I'm just curious
But it isn't Lin Rui
There is some problem with him
His proposal is suspected
of plagiarizing a foreign case
This is absolutely unacceptable to me
I guess
he was eager to win, just like me
Being competitive isn't an issue
but everything should
remain open and aboveboard
Just give me a word, yes or no?
It's a yes for sure!
Why are you still sitting here?
The R&D department is awaiting you
Mr. Jian, should I say thank you?
You are welcome
Anyway, it's part of your KPI
if it's not selling well
Forget it!
Open the door!
Ji Nan Jia!
- Who is it?
- You finally opened the door
I'm so thirsty
I talked for more than two hours
I almost lost my voice
I need water
You're taking here as your home
Don't be shy. I'm not here for the first time
Why are you here?
I got you a big business
- Thanks but no thanks
- Why?
Is it because of the banquet last time?
Listen
My boss will be in full charge of this event
Don't worry, he is still single
No one will pester you
Listen! I won't accept any order
from Yann Coffee again. Leave now
You got quite a personality. I like it
I don't need it, leave now
Please do me the favor
Can you please help me?
Aren't we friends?
Not at all
- Don't be my friend
- Wait!
To be honest, your couch is pretty good
- Lying here that night, I was...
- Hey, you!
Please do me the favor
The marketing department
is having a team building event
- I'll send you three contacts, go to them
- Don't!
Of course I know whom to contact
But I'm thinking to have you help me
- You don't want it? I'll delete it
- Don't! I want it
(Remembrance of Things Past)
Here! Hurry up!
- We're all waiting for you
- Long time no see
It's been a long time
You finally came back
- Have a seat
- He is getting more handsome
- You're more handsome
We have some meat to be served
Let's eat while waiting
We'll paint the town red tonight!
- Okay
- Okay?
I'm late, let me punish myself
- I'll drink with you
- Let's drink!
Come!
Qiao Xi Chen, hurry up
- It's getting cold
- I'm coming!
Oh my goodness!
You've ordered too much
Do you have other guests in this house?
How can you complain about
having too much food? We must finish it all
You're a spendthrift
Shen Zi Chang has really driven you mad
Don't mention his name, he's pesky
I've been on your side
but I'll be fair this time
Let me speak for Shen Zi Chang
Well, I'm not asking you to scrimp on things
but you can't just spend all you have
as if your salary were swinging by you
I didn't spend it all on myself
I want to make him happy
What do you mean?
He fancied a pair of shoes
but he begrudges
spending money on it. I see it
Also, each of his buddies seems to have one
So I was thinking to buy him one
and make him happy
I went to a lot of purchasing agents
and finally bought it 400 yuan cheaper
Enough talking, that's annoying
How dare he complain about me
You should've told him directly
How should I tell? I feel disgusted
upon thinking how his mother
and he criticized me behind my back
Alas!
Relationship is troublesome!
You get into a quarrel, either you say
everything or you keep everything
It's really a headache
Is something going on?
No
No? Well, Lin Rui is back
How are you getting along?
You want to know if we reconciled, right?
- Did you?
- What do you think?
Do you think it is possible?
You broke up because he went abroad
Now, he is back and you have been single
No. That wasn't the reason we broke up
The reason was
that I wasn't in his plan for future
I'm the gift for "buy one free one"
Besides, I am not in a relationship
because I haven't met the right person
I'm not waiting for him
You always use this as an excuse
What do you mean by "the right one"?
If you ask me
I'd say your thought becomes your destiny
- Do you remember our monitor?
- Yes
He was enrolled in graduate school
upon graduation
He was so enviable
- But you know what?
- What?
I saw him in our company two days ago
He was looking for a job
He went to your company?
He came with his resume for job application
Isn't he like a bachelor's degree holder?
All things are possible
That's because you're doing well
Some of our classmates are
still paper pushers after a few years
Please don't say that
To me, you are
the most successful one among us
Lin Rui, why would you come back?
Is the Pope a Catholic?
For sure it is
because the domestic offer is better
I believe the overseas elites like him
are paid annual compensation
Right?
We got it
- It is confidential
- This can't be tell?
I've eaten too much again. That's frustrating
I have to lose weight. I must stop eating
I've heard this for 20 years
I can only soothe my anger with food
Alas!
I feel like having a hot spring bath
in Hokkaido too
Alas! Forget it
I'll give you a big bucket
of hot water at home
You'll just sit inside
I can also adjust the temperature for you
The return ticket to Hokkaido is enough
to cover your water bills for three years
That's a dangerous speech
You must not say this before Shen Zi Chang
You're showing him bad examples
If we hadn't had a quarrel
I'd be enjoying the landscape
and taking nice pictures now
It's all your fault, Shen Zi Chang!
I can't afford to bring you to Hokkaido
but is Xiao Tang Shan okay for you?
Is your company having a team building event?
The place isn't bad
Who proposed it? He got a great taste
Don't bother about it. Are you going?
Why should I join your company's
team building event?
Why not? We are allowed
to bring family members
You are my family member, aren't you?
We just need to pay some additional charges
How much is it?
It's definitely cheaper
than your normal trip there
Three, two, one
Yes!
Should we invite Shen Zi Chang?
Don't say the three words!
- Let's go!
- Sorry
Why didn't you hire a designated driver?
Listen, this is a matter of principle
Don't take any chance! Do you hear me?
- Where's your car?
- Yeah!
I didn't drive. As you said
we were going to have a drink
I left my car at the company
Look! He is the smartest!
- Smart guy!
- Alright!
You look really drunk, let's get back
- Alright. Goodbye!
- Goodbye
Take care. We'll just leave you
Be safe! We'll drink again!
Regarding the new product development
I decided to adopt Qiao Xi Chen's proposal
As for the candidate
for the second group's leader
I need some time to think it over
(Qiao Xi Chen)
Are you really not staying over?
No. I'm going back to change this shirt
- It is smelly
- What do you mean?
Why don't you wear my clothes?
Look at yours. Look at what you are wearing
- I'll see you to the subway station
- It's fine
Get lost then. Hurry up!
Alright, I'm leaving. Goodbye!
Send me a message when you got home
Okay! Don't miss me!
- Drop over whenever you miss me
- Bye
Why are you here?
I got your address from Miao Miao
so that I can pay you a call
What for?
To be honest
I have been wandering around here
over an hour
Can we sit down and have a chat?
A cafe nearby is open till late night
Let's go there
Are you drunk?
Don't worry, I'm sober
Don't you know my tolerance for alcohol?
That's right. During our college time
the basketball club had a celebration
for winning a match
I remember you drank everyone under the table
I remember it too
You followed me with half a bottle of liquor
and stopped anyone
who wanted to drink with me
The next day, everyone started saying that
Lin Rui's girlfriend had
a higher tolerance for alcohol than him
Well. Thinking about it
that was the happiest moment in my life
Come on, in your life?
You still have a long way to go
We have to look forward
Didn't you say this before you left?
Xiao Xi
- It was because...
- Alright
It's over, let's not bring it up
Can we still be friends?
To be honest
I'm frustrated today
I read your proposal and it is impressive
If you had performed well
the winner would be hard to predict
I am speaking as if my proposal were selected
Do you know what I like about Beijing?
It's big enough
It's tolerant
You can make the grade if you are talented
If you are ordinary yet diligent
you can still make a decent living
And if you have nothing
but you are willing to work hard
you still can gain a foothold
So
don't push yourself so hard
I am quoting someone as saying. A while ago
someone told me this and I find it justified
Don't put yourself under pressure
Relax
Xiao Xi, you...
How have you been all these years?
It's kind of weird. I thought meeting you
would be awkward
because of the past
But somehow I don't have any special feelings
So you don't have to worry about it
Since we are colleagues now
we'll interact normally
and work in peace
We might have a chance
to work together, right?
I see
Wait a moment, I'm leaving home
Okay, I got it
- We have chemistry
- I have no time for jokes
I am tied up, go do your thing
What's going on? Why are you in a hurry?
I know!
They didn't mention
the expired date before shipping
We didn't ask about it too
So it's not their problem
Persimmons can't keep long
That's right
I know!
- I am going now
- I'm dizzy
Can't you understand my words?
You didn't get it but I did
The Fu Ping Persimmons
that your company bought
weren't stored well and have gone bad, right?
It is no big deal,
buy some more and it's settled
No big deal? I need them now
and they have gone bad
It's too late to get the seller ship it again
Don't waste my time. Hurry up and leave!
Wait
If you are not going to buy it,
where are you going now?
I'm going back to office
Where else can I go?
Don't go back, follow my lead
I can get you big and sweet persimmons
I have no time to play with you now
I'm not messing around
Do you want persimmons?
If you do, listen to me and go
Although I look unreliable
I never tell a lie. Here it is, let's go!
I'll kill you if there is no persimmon
How do you kill me?
- Navigation! Turn on the sound
- Turn right at the front
Hello, Qiao. Can you do me a favor?
I might be late
No. I have it all arranged
All the rooms are registered
You'll just distribute the keys later
Alright? I'll send you the contact
of the resort manager
Alright. Thanks. See you
Are you in the middle of something?
I told you, right?
I have a team building event
Just send me the location
and I'll go by myself
Listen, you won't get the persimmons
if I don't go along
- How is it?
- There is a bathtub!
Not too bad!
There is a pool outside!
It's no big deal, don't be so surprised
Take a picture for me
- We can come here tonight
- This is nice
- Let me take a photo for you
- Is this okay?
Come on, look here
- It looks nice!
- Is the pool captured?
Yes
Alright! Come in
Are you sure? Don't brush me off
My goodness, it looks great
Well, I'm just asking
We are staying here for a night
Why do you bring so many things?
You bumpkin. You don't understand it, do you?
- What are you going to do here?
- Look!
Why do you bring a lamp?
What is this?
- A dog?
- Is it a dog?
It is a panda, a bear
- The wine is good
- This!
This is for taking pictures
You'll pretend it were someone else's hand
- Are you filming a horror movie?
- Come on, don't be mean
- This is a magazine shoot idea
You have no sense of artistic at all
- A selfie stick
- Well, let's take pictures
I found a perfect spot for pictures
- Go to the front
- It's perfect
- Can you take pictures for me?
- Go to the front
I've been your photographer
I want to take pictures too
I want to take pictures!
Let's go, be my photographer!
You are too bad, Qiao Xi Chen!
Are you sure it's here?
Trustworthy is my middle name
Here we are!
Uncle Wei, you're still listening to this?
Haven't you got tired of it?
You know nothing about it
Each repeat brings something new
Why are you here again?
Nothing, I'm just wandering around
My uncle's Korla fragrant pear
is always sweet
What are we doing here?
Well. Uncle
Can you get me two boxes of
fresh Fu Ping persimmons?
Why are you getting picky about food?
No. Do you see it selling here?
I'm keeping it for myself
Let me give you a leg massage
It's for this beauty, not me
I told her that you have
the best persimmon in Beijing
She didn't believe it and so we have a bet
She will be my girlfriend
if she loses our bet
Talk properly
Don't play tricks
- It's true
- Uncle, it's quite urgent
Can you sell me two boxes if you have it?
I don't have Fu Ping persimmons
but I have two boxes
of Zhang Fang's Mopan persimmons
How about Zhang Fang's Mopan?
Mopan persimmon isn't sweet enough
Is he angry?
What did I say?
Look, we both tried to goad him
Why doesn't my trick work?
- Forget it. Let's go
- No
- I have to ask him
- Hold on
Don't irk him, lest he refuse to sell us this
Don't worry, Uncle Wei is absolutely reliable
Try it. Is it crispy?
How is it?
How is the taste?
Not bad. You know what?
Zhang Fang started planting persimmons
since the Ming Dynasty
They used to be the royal tribute
It's not worse than Fu Ping persimmon
The sweetness is really different
The flesh tastes better
Uncle, can you sell me two boxes?
Please, I need it urgently
Then, tell me
Have you lost the bet?
I didn't make a bet with him
Please sell it to me
Persimmons
Yes, I lost
This is the best persimmon in Beijing
Uncle, please, it's urgent
Boy, come here
That's all I can help you
You have my respect for good!
Yes, they are in my trunk
Okay, I'll keep them in my car
I'll take them to the venue tomorrow noon
Okay, are other details confirmed?
- Okay
- No one picks up such a big order?
- What's up?
- Get into the car, I'll give you a ride
Wait
I know you still care about me
I regret it, get out
Don't, please
I did you a huge favor
Besides, there is really
an emergency at the hotel
They are waiting for me
Sounds like you're important
You are right, I am
Turn on the navigation
Turn on the sound
It's okay. I'll navigate you
You are not as unreliable as I thought
Now you realized it
Frankly speaking, the bet just now...
- Is it...
- What's blocking? Check the map
Don't sidetrack me. The bet just now
- The bet
- Yes, we're in a traffic jam, it's red light
The bet
Another picture here, come on
(Remembrance of Things Past)
That's old school. Didn't you
take a picture at the water pipe?
Do I look good? Okay, come on
Let's have another one
Enough, let's go to the hot spring
Stop thinking of that
You can soak there anytime
until your skin falls off.
Listen, Ou Yang said
there are rabbits and peacocks
Can you resist them?
That's nonsense
Qiao Xi Chen
Are you hiding something from me?
- You're having a suspicious mind
- Which of us is acting weird?
Can you feel it?
- It's snow
- From this hotel?
There's artificial snow
- Silly girl
- You call me silly?
- Rabbit, peacock!
- Forget it!
What?
Did you call him here?
Don't pull a long face, it makes you ugly
Talk it out face-to-face
so that you won't have any regrets
Anyway, I've given you an out
The ball is in your court now
Well, go
Your cell phone
Baby
Qiao Xi Chen told me about it
You went to the purchasing agent
to buy me shoes
Why didn't you tell me?
You've caused me to misunderstand you
This flower is for you
What do you mean? Are you blaming me?
No, I am not!
It is my fault
I should have listened to you before I...
What do you mean? You can buy it but I can't?
I can't make it clear now
Anyway, I apologize
Please don't be angry
It's your fault! I had to cancel
the booking of the homestay!
I know, I am here to make up for my mistake
Look at this snow
- You made it?
- I made it
This flower is also for you
Hold it
Later
we have to take hundreds of photos of it
Then, you will post on Moments
that you are in Hokkaido
Are you stupid?
Is it snowing in Hokkaido now?
I'll check what places
are having snowfall now
Isn't it snowing here now?
- You're annoying
- Well
You're silly
I'm going to grab a bite
Let me know what you and Shen Zi Chang want
Since you are here, stay with us one more day
I have tons of work, enjoy yourselves
What?
It's fishy
Come on, wait a minute
You're taking pictures. One more
No, wait
Come on, Ji Nan Jia, come clean
Why do you come here all the way?
Are you here for the hot springs?
When did you start hanging out with him?
Since when? You look so close
We are not
We are
Get out and enjoy yourself
- Don't
No. You are already here, get out
Have a hot spring bath before you leave
Go away
I have other fish to fry
Xu Yan and Shen Zi Chang are being dramatic
Don't you want to take a look?
Great minds think alike
Let's join them, too
- I'll give you a bunch of five!
- Hey
You know what I saw?
There's a 24-hour chess and card room
Mahjong?
Shen Zi Chang can't play, we lack one player
The ace mahjong player is here
- I will park the car
- No, I'll do it
Look here
I'm coming after you
- Seven dots
- There are no more dots
No more dots
There are so many winds
West
- Can you play?
- Of course
I am thinking of the strategy
Just throw one, hurry up
- Nine bamboos
- Won!
- You won?
- I just won
You gave her the tile she wanted
I would've won by self-drawn
Okay, I lost, I'll drink
Wait, do we have the beauties
saving heroes nowadays?
You read too much into it
With us, only the winner is eligible to drink
- Come on
- Hurry up
Don't you have team building activities?
Let me introduce him
I'm sorry, brother
He's a newcomer in the marketing department
Be nice to him
Let me introduce him
I'm sorry, brother
Hey, brother
You've started drinking.
Are you going to join the activities?
Who is your brother?
- Sister
- What's so fun?
It's the same every year
Frankly speaking, the event this year
is planned only by me, it'll be exciting
It is. You even got Nan Jia here
Honestly
Wait and see
Not bad
- Very good
- I didn't know you were coming
so we didn't do any preparation
What preparation do you need?
I know that the marketing department
is having a team building event here
I happened to meet a friend nearby
so I just drop by
The marketing department has
worked hard and needs some relaxation
Everyone worked hard for the projects lately
Come on, everyone
Mr. Jiang has something to say
Well, don't make it so formal
I know that your department
is here for team building. I just swung by
to express our gratitude to you
Your department has been working hard lately
But I believe the hard work is worth it
Because the entire Yann Coffee knows
your department's performance is fabulous
I hope that under Mr. Jian's leadership
you will continue to work hard
Let's strive together!
Great!
Okay, that's all from me
I believe you won't enjoy my presence
I'll leave you be
- See you, Mr. Jiang
- I'll see you out, Mr. Jiang
Just stop here
The wines in this hotel are fabulous
I need to relax too
I'll have a drink by myself
- You'll stay with them
- Mr. Jiang, take care
Ou Yang
Introduce your activities
Copy that! I won't let you down!
Friends, let us get excited
Let me explain the rules of the game
As soon as I release it, you have to
find out the person holding
the opposite end of your rope
That will be your partner today
You'll complete all activities together
- Okay?
- Okay
Be ready, I'm going to let go
Three, two
one!
It seems that we're made to be a pair
Mr. Jian, we are destined to be partners too
Alright, you already know your partners
Be ready for the first game
Before you start
let me announce today's prizes
The prize for first place
is three-day paid leave!
Wow!
Okay, come on
Three, two, one!
Come on!
I hereby announce the game
goes to Luo Jing and Dan Jia!
What's the matter with you?
Next, we'll have Mr. Jian, Mr. Wu
Qiao Xi Chen and Lin Rui, come on
Mr. Jian, don't worry
With their sizes
you can fully rely on me and just rest
Just because they are the superiors
doesn't mean you should throw the game
They don't want the leave, but we do
Don't worry, we'll get it
as long as you want it
Bragger
Are you all ready?
Three, two, one
Come on!
Hey, easy!
I hereby announce the game
goes to Qiao Xi Chen and Lin Rui!
Next group, hurry up!
Can you fill me in?
I need to use the bathroom
The moon hang high tonight
But no stars come out
Baby, we've been watching
the moon for an hour
I'm dying, really, let's go out of here
What's wrong with being here an hour long?
I have to stay a little longer
Have you ever had a hot spring bath?
Don't try to drag me out
Honestly
Thank you
I found you familiar from the back
I didn't expect it would be you
Can I sit here?
Sure
Excuse me!
- I'll have the same drink
- Okay
You didn't change at all
But you did
Thanks
- Have you...
- I have fully recovered
Great
Nan Jia, you know what? Actually...
I've been asking myself
I often ask myself
what our relationship would be
if I didn't leave you that night
By the way, I'm so sorry about the banquet
I didn't know the person in charge was you
It's true
I didn't expect Han Yi Ting
would be so sensitive
I'm really sorry
I didn't know
you are Mr. Jiang from Yann Coffee
If I did, I wouldn't have accepted the order
Why?
Actually
everyone thinks I'm doing well
in the past few years
In fact, I'm not
Apparently, I am the powerful
general manager of Yann Coffee
who has married a beautiful wife
from a well-to-do family
It's said the men are spared
from working hard with such marriage
It's only known to myself
that Han Yi Ting and her dad
never treat me as their family
You have to be responsible
for your own choice
That's right
That's my choice
I chose to break up with you
I chose to marry Han Yi Ting
But this is different from what I thought
When we first knew each other
Han Yi Ting said she admired me
She said she didn't care about
the gap between our families
Now what?
It's hard for me to bare my heart with her
I can even read her distaste through her eyes
You don't need to tell me this
Maybe I've been keeping this all this way
and couldn't pour out to anyone else
Since I happened to run into you today
I am being long-winded
Don't take it to heart
I don't mean anything else, really
I am "somebody else" to you now
- No, Nan Jia, you are different
- I am not
I'm not different from others
So many years have passed
Living your own life well is what matters
I don't know why you are telling me this
Do you expect I'd comfort you
or join your tirade on your wife?
I can't actually do both
If any problems arose in your marriage
I think you should find a solution
I've seen Han Yi Ting only once
and it wasn't a happy encounter
But I think it is thanks to her help
that you're able to spread your wings
at a large company like Yann Coffee
Jiang Hao, be fair
While complaining about her changes
you should also ponder
if you're still the same person
whom she won't hesitate to fall in love with
I am leaving, I think I drank too much
What are you doing here?
If my boss knows
that I listened in on his gossip
he'll surely kick me out of the company
Why did you do that then?
The interesting story is worth it
Then again
you are Mr. Jiang's ex-girlfriend
No wonder you looked awkward that day
When and why did you break up?
Aren't you afraid that
I'll kill you after you know the story?
- What's up?
- Come on
I know you're upset right now
Take it out on me
Who told you I'm upset?
People normally get upset by this, right?
You know what?
Mr. Jiang is surely
still remorseful about leaving you
He surely is
Do you think I was dumped because he married
a rich wife and looks high-spirited now?
No, brother, I dumped him, okay?
You are really interesting
No, then
It stands to reason that I assumed
What's wrong?
Why?
I was diagnosed with cancer five years ago
It was cervical cancer
I had to undergo an operation
If it failed, my uterus would be removed
If it succeeded
it might recur at any time in five years
That's when he left you? He's not a man!
I told you I brought it up, are you deaf?
I didn't want him to waste time on me
What's more
five years is quite a long period
Humanity cannot withstand any test
I am not sure if my feelings
for him will change in five years
Instead of having an ugly breakup
we might as well end the relationship early
Then, we can leave a good impression
for each other
It's cheesy, right?
I do think you are cool
If I were you
I might not be as courageous as you
But if I were Jiang Hao
I wouldn't leave you
I've drunk too much, I'm leaving
Hey!
Don't tell Qiao Xi Chen and the rest
about my past with Jiang Hao
and my cancer, they don't know it
Don't worry
Hey!
You're super cool
Screw you
Some people are upset after losing the game
- I am not
- But you're pulling a long face
That's not the reason
What's wrong?
Leave me be, just enjoy yourself
Leave you be?
Why are you speaking so tartly?
What's wrong with you?
Let's call a spade a spade
Ou Yang is good at event management
The game, the atmosphere
and everything are pretty good
It's better than mine last year
Of course, all of these
are thanks to your support
The hotel room
is the best room I have
ever stayed in. Thank you
You finally know what is supposed to be said
- Qiao Xi Chen!
- You...
You're here. I've been looking around for you
- Mr. Jian
- Have the finals started?
No, it's still a while to the start
I have something to talk to you
We can talk about it while walking there
Go ahead
See you later
Hey, go get my phone and take a picture of me
Okay, I like the idea
Go quickly
It's cold outside
- Hurry up!
- Alright
Baby, what is this?
Don't leak it to anyone else
Anyway, you have no one to tell
This is
what Jing Jing gave to Lin Rui
Jing Jing to Lin Rui?
Jing Jing was so attached to Lin Rui
Really?
Don't you believe me?
Look, what is this?
A lock and a key
You can open it
In the basketball club...
Nan Jia
Why are you still here?
You've been here for quite a while
Your skin is about to fall off. Get her out
Remember what I just said?
I'll get you a towel, wait here
You are really good
Qiao Xi Chen stuffed her face
during the buffet last time
And now, you get shortness of breath
because of the bath
- Do you have any chocolate? Get her one
- Yes
Nan Jia, weren't you at the event?
Why are you here?
With whom do I build the team?
I'm not part of their company
Do I need that?
- Yan
- Yes
What happened between Jing Jing and Lin Rui?
Hey
Don't you have something to tell me? Say it
Tonight is my most relaxing day
since I returned
That's good
And then?
What do you think our relationship would be
if I hadn't gone abroad?
What's the point of
making such an assumption?
Of course there is
Maybe we can start again
Give me a break
That being said
Jing Jing bought the tickets when she
showed Lin Rui's parents around Beijing
No wonder she borrowed my car
I wondered with whom she was going out
She was on a business trip back then.
She even gave up the bonus
Why must she help Lin Rui?
Actually, they had been in contact
and Lin Rui always went to Jing Jing for help
Jing Jing helped him with all the errands
like his friend's wedding
and getting the degree certificate
She didn't hesitate to help
when Lin Rui approached her
Why did he approach Jing Jing
when his parents came to Beijing?
What did he take her for?
That's funny
Nan Jia
Actually...
Actually, the person
she fancied wasn't Gao Tian Yang
Xiao Xi
I didn't expect to see you again
and become your colleague after coming back
Lately, our past story came to me off and on
I remember them all
I just came to realize that you are
the one who really understands me
No one cares about me more than you
Xiao Xi
Can you accept me again?
I promise
I won't leave you again this time
I cross my heart
Back then, it was Jing Jing who brought
me and Qiao Xi Chen to his basketball club
Qiao Xi Chen got to know Lin Rui through this
But we can't blame Qiao Xi Chen
Qiao Xi Chen doesn't know
Lin Rui is the one Jing Jing fancied
She thinks it is Gao Tian Yang
Jing Jing didn't want Qiao Xi Chen
to get the wrong idea
so she kept quiet and acquiesced in it
Do you think Lin Rui knows about this?
You mean Lin Rui knows Jing Jing fancied him?
If he doesn't know it,
why did he contact Jing Jing
after breaking up with Qiao Xi Chen
while knowing they were good friends?
If he knew it...
He was making Jing Jing his back-up
- Where are you going?
- I am going to him!
In this? Get changed
I'm going to change clothes
It's inappropriate
Lin Rui, do you know
what broke my heart the most over the years?
I know
It is when I suddenly went abroad
and left you behind
I know, I can make it up to you
No, it's not
It's true
The most saddening part
is that I used to think that my world
would collapse after you left
But then I found out that it didn't
Not only that, I was doing quite well
The most saddening part
is that I wasn't as heartbroken as I thought
Xiao Xi
It means that we can start over again
Don't you think so?
Lin Rui, let me make it simple
I used to think love was everything in life
At least I really thought so for once
But now, I know it is not
There are so many important
people and things in my life
I love them and they love me too
I like my new life
Although my life hasn't been smooth sailing
there are sadness
and frustrations and even...
Even Jing Jing left me
But I still like my new life
I've grown up, you should grow up too
You will have your new life
True
- Xu Yan!
- What did you take Hu Jing Jing for?
Do you know she fancied you?
What did you think of her?
No, wait
Xu Yan, I'm here
Who fancied whom? What are you talking about?
I'm her sister, tell me
What did you take her for?
Xiao Xi
Let me explain it
It was probably the second year
I was overseas
I went abroad after finishing my junior year
It happened to be my graduation
There were tons of things to deal with
Besides, I was still adapting the life abroad
I was in a fix and didn't have any way out
So I emailed Jing Jing
and asked her to help me
deal with some school matters
Why did you approach her for help
since you broke up with Qiao Xi Chen?
Jing Jing and I were classmates
before I knew you
We were on friendly terms
Although we broke up
I don't think she would ignore me for that
Later...
She helped me settle everything very soon
I was really having a difficult time abroad
I couldn't keep up in class
I barely had friends
I couldn't help but pour out to her
Her encouragement and support
were to the point
I remember I mentioned
missing the taste of Lao Gan Ma
Then, she sent me a box of it
Only then I vaguely felt her feelings for me
So you exploited her feelings for you, right?
You bossed her around
Why did you get her to accompany your parents
when they came to Beijing?
She took your parents around
She bought an extra ticket
at all the attractions
Why did she do so? For whom did she buy it?
Lin Rui, that's not the way to go
Hu Jing Jing was cherished by her parents
She wasn't obliged to do that
Yes, Xiao Xi
I didn't think about that
What were you thinking then?
Do you think Hu Jing Jing's death
doesn't pain me?
Hmm?
But you can't push the blame to me
Did she commit suicide
just because I didn't reply to her email
and tell her that I fancied her? No way
Is it a rule that I must respond to her love?
Xiao Xi
You're the only one I love since then
Why didn't you tell me?
Xiao Xi
Hello, Mr. Jian
I need to talk to you
Okay, I'll be right there
Qiao Xi Chen
Mr. Jian
We like to cling to the past
It could be the old clothes
that we might never wear again
the old photos taking up the space
which we are reluctant to delete
and the ex-lovers
whom we occasionally think of
in those sleepless nights
The nostalgia for the good old days
is due more to uncertainty about the future
But the past is over after all
We should all learn to say goodbye
Move forward, be brave
- Just say it
- Qiao Xi Chen
- What is it?
What's up?
Sorry
What happened?
- It hurts
- Where does it hurt?
My stomach
Let's go
It's acute appendicitis
But luckily it's not serious
What are you doing?
It drips too slow
Does it hurt?
- How do you feel?
- A lot better, thank you, doctor
Generally, acute appendicitis
can easily become chronic
You should pay more attention to it
If there is uninterrupted pain
you must seek medical care
as soon as possible
- You'll be in trouble if perforation occurs
- It's so troublesome
You can also have it removed
to save you bother
The appendix has no other function
except for having inflammation
- That's okay
- I'll have it removed
I'll have it removed
- Take a rest, I'll make the arrangement
- Thank you