(Remembrance of Things Past)
Excuse me
Seriously? I left a note
saying I went to the washroom
Why did you clear my table?
Are solo diners not welcomed?
You cleared my table last time too
(I haven't finished my meal
I just want to enjoy a quiet meal)
(We shouldn't waste food
Please be kind to me! Thank you)
Hello, Miss. This is our mascot
Leave it on the seat
when you come here next time
Then we won't clear your table
I'm really sorry
- Thank you
- No problem
(Episode 4: A Place to Settle Down)
(Hu Jing Jing
please call us or settle your debt)
(within 24 hours of receiving this message)
- Get me one too
- How do you know what I'm getting?
What else? It must be booze
Here you go
I've heard of two of those platforms
But I've never heard of the rest
Here, drink mine
They are all third party debt collectors
See how it's worded. "We have called
many times to notify you, however"
"our messages remained unheeded
We will be submitting a report soon"
Pretty mean of them to lodge a police report
"Stop rejecting my company's calls"
So she really had debt
How did she end up with such a huge debt?
- Hey!
- You're here
What's going on?
Did Jing Jing really had debt?
I sent it to our group chat room
Didn't you look?
Miss Hu, looks like you're not serious
about paying your debt
I only made exceptions a few times for your
overdue debt because you had a good record
You can't give me excuses
saying you don't have the money
Please tell me exactly when
you can pay your debt
How could he say that?
During the first half of the year, I asked
if she had enough to spend, she said yes
The thing is, she was really in debt
Why would she need money?
She said nothing about it
Besides, she could have come to me
Why did she get a loan?
I'm just putting this out there
Do you think the reason for Jing Jing's
suicide was really because of her debt?
In my opinion, I'd be the only one
killing myself because of money. Not her
How much do you think she owed them
based on these messages?
- I don't think it's over 200,000 yuan
- That's even more unlikely
I'd say two million sounds more likely
Yes, it's only over 100,000 yuan
What else do you think she has kept from us?
Which means, that guy we met the other day
- What was his name? Right, Gao Yang
- Gao Yang
I think what he said is probably true
The calls that Jing Jing avoided in front
of him were probably from the debt collectors
- You're right
- That's why she was so secretive
I think her debt payment isn't due yet. Why?
If debt collectors can't reach you
they will contact your parents
I'm sure her parents haven't received
their call, otherwise they would've told me
I will talk to my aunt
to write a letter of authorization
So that we can check
her bank account transaction records
and find out who she sent the money to
We'll know once we see the records
Huh?
It's not her phone. It's mine. Calm down
Hello?
Yes, I know Hu Jing Jing
Who is this speaking?
This is Jing Jing's cat?
She's never said she wanted a cat
Don't look at me
I found out when you found out
You must be Gou Dan's parents
- Whose parents?
- The cat
That's great. Gou Dan can finally go home
Gou Dan was brought here two months ago
It was a stray cat at a parking lot
It wasn't doing so well
when it was brought here
Then its owner, Hu Jing Jing
said she would come get it once it recovers
But then she suddenly said she couldn't come
and left me a number
We've encountered many cases like that
with abandoned cats
She's not someone like that
I thought so too. That's why I called you
I didn't expect three people to show up
She probably gave your number
since I'm allergic to cats
- I can take care of it if you trust me
- We don't
I'll take care of it
but I have to talk to my roommate first
We rent the place together
So that's a bit tricky
Why don't you let her
talk to her roommate first?
- In the mean time, Gou...
- Dan
- It can stay here. I'll pay for it
- Yes
Once the problem is settled
we'll surely come back for it
My business card. Don't worry
- We won't abandon it
- Okay
Don't worry
Jing Jing is a dear friend of ours
We won't abandon what she left behind
Okay
Why are you looking at pet products?
You haven't brought the cat home
If your roommate doesn't allow it
I'd be taking it home anyway
Dream on. My roommate even brings home a man
I'm just bringing home a cat
It's Saturday. What are your plans?
I have a date
I'm going home to get some sleep
Why don't you have any social life?
At least Xu Yan has a date
Then what are your plans?
Going home to sleep
- How eventful!
- That's so exciting!
Knock before coming in
How could you barge in like that?
This is my home. Why do I have to knock?
- Why is he here again?
- Yes
How many times have I told you?
It's stated clearly in the contract
Only one person...
Only one person can stay in one room
Men aren't allowed
He's not staying here
- Can't he just visit me once in a while?
- No
Besides, the living room is a public space
Since it's a public space, who are you
to restrict me from doing what I want?
Unbelievable
How can I bring Gou Dan home?
Li Na, you're so skinny
Why are you still eating salad?
I put on 150 g
when I weighed myself yesterday
I indulged in hotpot over the weekend
The calories of a piece of meat
is extremely high
I'm too afraid to eat
Just eat it. As long as you're happy
It's okay
You look adorable when you're chubby
- You two are working early shift today?
- Yes
Want to go get an injection with me
after work?
- What kind of injection?
- Beauty injection
A clinic I've been following closely
is having a promotion
Bring a friend and get 20 percent off
Bring two, one person gets it for free
Isn't it too soon for us to get these jabs?
Not at all. We have to start
preventing aging after 25
If you start at 26, you can only maintain
your beauty at the age of 26
But if you start at 40, the best condition
you can maintain will only be 40
That is why we must think long-term
Who told you all these?
Everyone's saying it
Does that clinic provide slimming treatment?
- Yes
- Really?
There are many slimming treatments
these days. Want to go have a look?
Come on, girls
Just go have a look
You don't have to get the injection
It's not like they will force you to get it
Right. I'm curious about it. Count me in
I'll come along too
Sure
Hi, the tenant downstairs
said their bathroom is leaking
We checked and found out
the unit above had a water leakage
Your house must be affected
since it's in between
- So I quickly came to tell you
- I'll go have a look
Please, no!
Goodness gracious
Mr. Zheng, have you checked
the video I sent you?
I have a small suggestion
I've stayed in this unit for quite long
It's been quite a number of years
since it's been renovated
I wish to renovate the bathroom
if it's possible
Since some of the fixtures have gotten old
Don't worry about the money
The tenant upstairs said
they will compensate. I can pay for the rest
Qiao, any updates
on the agent who scammed you?
Good news. Officer Tan said many people
became victims of this scam group
They are trying to track my money now
I'll be notified once they have news
That's good news
You're bullying us
He's the eighth one
Four men, four women
If he's really dismissing one third
of the staff, then there's one more left
Help. I'm really nervous
Calm down. Just do your job well
You better watch out
The sales for your new fall products
aren't doing well, right?
It's gone downhill
But you can't blame it on me
Yi Ning planned everything
when she was around
From early stage R&D
to marketing and promotion
she never allowed us to take part
I only did an event
I can't be taking all the blame
But Yi Ning is on leave now
Do you think Yi Ning will take the blame
or the new director would?
Whoever it is. It just can't be me
- Qiao Xi Chen
- Mr. Jian
Prepare a summarized presentation
for the new fall products
From R&D to sales. Be as detailed as possible
It's only been launched for a month
Isn't it too soon for a summary?
This presentation will determine
if it's good enough to stay
Good luck
Was he referring to the new products or me?
I'm sorry I jinxed it
It's alright. What must be, must be
Why are you still here?
Where else should I be?
How do I know?
Shouldn't you be following Mr. Jian?
You're right
I hope I'll get to see you again. Good luck
- Good luck
- Thank you
Good luck
I have a rough idea
of all three of your conditions
Let's start with you, Wei Wei
I suggest you do a full-body liposuction
You can choose specific areas as well
Then you can do a full-face Lipo 360
- Lipo 360?
- It will give you a drastic change
Will it be very painful?
- It's worth it, though
- Women have to be meaner to themselves
Miss Xu, right?
You have the looks, the figure
and the elegance. It's just that...
You can do a minor adjustment
Your face is a little round here
Right? If you do a bone contouring
- your face will look sharp
- Bone contouring?
- That's right
- That's too much
- I don't dare to do it
- I'll be honest with you girls
We do more than ten minor surgeries
like that each day
Is my face that round?
Take a look for yourself
It is rounder compared to yours
So you're saying that I can't do anything
unless the landlord comes here personally?
That's right. Look
I personally came to talk to you about it
We have our rules as well. Never mind
Bring the property ownership certificate
and the house owner's original ID
Then ask the house owner
to record a video as proof of authorization
I've told you. The house owner is overseas
Besides, I've shown you the chat records
I've been given the green light
How can you prove that
it's really the house owner?
For crying out loud!
You see. We're seriously not trying
to make things hard for you
This house doesn't belong to you
Now you want to renovate it
If the house owner comes back
denies giving you permission
and blames us for failing our job
we'll end up in hot water
I really have nothing against you
I've been living here for six years
I just want to renovate the washroom
Even if you've lived here for ten years
your name isn't on the property
ownership certificate. Am I right?
Cool!
(Mrs. Lin)
There's a leakage in the washroom at home
So I'm staying at a hotel for two days
What luck you have there
Who knew there would be a leakage?
Did the tenant upstairs agree to compensate?
By the way
have you mentioned this to your landlord?
Otherwise, he'll ask you to pay for it
I'll be compensated
Good, then. Quickly get someone to fix it
I want to renovate the washroom
It's too old now
Your landlord is paying for it?
I am, obviously. I'm the one living there
Why must you pay for it?
The house doesn't belong to you
I'm living there
I should at least pay for some of the cost
Jia Jia, are you not right in the head?
You think you'll be living in
that house forever?
Can you bring the renovation with you
when you move out?
- The house owner gets to keep it
- What's with the fuss?
But I've got to use it already
Believe it or not. If you renovate it now
you'll be asked to move out next year
I've seen a lot of these cases online
Stop surfing the internet
Disconnect the cable
You're reading useless news
I can't talk now. You and Dad
should go to bed soon. I'm hanging up
Xiao Yi, the contract...
Forget it. I saw it
- Hello
- What are you up to?
Nothing much
I'm so envious of you
Xu Yan, don't you think
I'm paying rent for nothing?
I spend more time at the office
than I do at home
Move out of the house
and stay at the office then
I think that could work
Qiao Xi Chen, let me put it this way
There's no end to earning money
Besides, do you get paid
for working overtime?
I don't get paid for working overtime
But if I don't work overtime
I might lose my job
Are you seriously going to get fired?
Is it because of that director
who came out of nowhere?
I'm telling you
I'm seriously unlucky
I went for an interview
at a new company last week, right?
Of all people, I ran into him
And the new product I was in charged for R&D
isn't selling well
I keep getting on his bad side
What's worse is
I didn't get a reply after the interview
I'm thinking he must be behind it
He's so petty
He's not even leaving you a way out
when he's going to fire you
The new director is petty
Always idling away, not contributing anything
- Good description
- Hold it. Don't you laugh!
Okay, I've got to hang up
I need to finish working on
the presentation that holds my fate
- Qiao Qiao
- What?
If you really become jobless
don't worry. I'll take care of you
Thanks
I've got to go
Silly
Mr. Jian
I don't need the presentation done by today
You should go home
- You heard everything?
- I can say no if that's what you wish
So it's a yes
Mr. Jian
Just lay it on me
- What?
- Am I the last one?
Am I the last one on the list
to be dismissed?
- Why would you think I'd dismiss you?
- Damei
You caught me
There's nothing wrong with
looking for a new job
What's wrong is that you picked Damei
There's also the poor sales
for the new fall products
- You think it's your fault?
- Of course not
I wasn't the main person in charge
Then why would I want to dismiss you?
Someone has to be held responsible for it
It can't be Yi Ning
So you think I'm putting the blame on you
I feel that you're not fond of me
Do you think I should pursue you then?
No, that's not what I meant
What I meant was...
Like the incident with the quotation list
It wasn't my fault
but you urged me to take leave
And the 818 promotion. It was my project
But you gave it to Brother Qiang. And then...
I got drunk
So I thought, perhaps...
You have a problem with me
(Daily Morning News)
I don't have to explain this, right?
I was in the car that day
That's my car
I saw you at the hospital
You were devastated
I could tell that you two were close
She's my best friend
No one can feel the pain
you suffered from that
The only thing I can do
is giving you a few days off
so that you won't feel stressed
However
I'm very pleased with the way you handled
the Chinese Valentine's Day event
But as the current person in charge
of the new fall products
don't you think you should consider
if there's room for salvation?
So the presentation wasn't
to find fault with me, but to...
When something goes wrong with a product
I must find out the problem
so that I can tackle it
- If you don't want to be in charge of...
- I want to
I'm sorry, Mr. Jian
I'll give you
the presentation file by tonight
Thank you, Mr. Jian
It's pretty late. You should eat something
My goodness
How did she become so fat? Look
How is that fat?
She is fat. Her face is so round. My goodness
I thought you said my round face was cute
Yes, you're cute.
But I'm not saying you're fat
Liar! She's not fat. It's just the angle
How is this because of the angle?
Shen Zi Chang, if I become old
fat and ugly one day
- will you still love me?
- I will
Even if you become old and haggard
one day, you'll still be the cutest old lady
You don't sound sincere at all
Go home
- What?
- Quick. Go home
- I said go home
- Did I say something wrong again?
No, everything's fine. Just go
My gosh. Why waste your energy
getting mad at him when you're so pretty?
Of course I'm angry
What they say on the internet is true
Men are all visual animals
What was that phrase in
Empresses in the Palace?
Losing affection
when a woman loses her beauty?
Such wise words
Read more books
You're learning all that from TV
But they've got a point, right?
Everyone likes eye candies
I would take a second look
if I see a pretty girl too
Xu Yan, I'll talk to you later
I have to deal with something
I'll call you back later
- Bye bye
- Okay
(Beauty Metamorphosis, Current offer price)
Why is there no hot water again?
I need to take a leak. It can't wait
Hey, I'm still in there!
Don't you know how to close the door?
Close it for me then
Firstly, clean up your own mess
in the public area. Don't leave it overnight
Please clean up after using the kitchen
Don't leave the pots and pans
piling up in the sink
We'll take turns cleaning the living room
and washroom every week
What do you mean?
I didn't ask you to clear my trash
You offered to do it
Yes, I'm nuts
for cleaning your trash every day
I'm really curious
All these rubbish you left laying around
It's been here for days and starting to rot
Can't you smell it?
On top of that, you have your stuff
scattered all over the living room
You've taken up all the space
There's no space left for me
You can pile your stuff too. I won't stop you
Besides, shouldn't roommates
learn to give and take?
You can't force me to live by your standards
If you can't stand it, you can
tidy up the place. I don't mind it though
Fine
You're really something
Alright. I'll set that aside for now
Secondly, don't use my stuff again
I had no idea you were so petty
I just used a bit of your shampoo
It doesn't cost that much anyway
- It's not like I can't afford it
- Then buy your own. Why use mine?
You're a real piece of work
I'm fine if you only used it once or twice
But not every day!
I have short hair. You have long hair
You even let your boyfriend use it
I bought a new bottle last week
but it's empty now
How much is a single takeout?
Can't you save that money
to buy shampoo for yourself?
Yes. Takeout, you say?
Didn't we get your portion too
when we ordered food?
If I knew you were this petty
I wouldn't have used it even if you let me
Oh, please, thank you!
Don't bring back your leftover food
for me next time. It'll go to waste
And the most important thing
he isn't allowed to stay the night anymore
You two can do whatever you want as a couple
But why must you bring him home?
Isn't it better outside? A night
at a budget hotel isn't that expensive
You two act as if I'm not in this house
Even if you're not embarrassed
I feel embarrassed for you
And it's clearly stated in the contract
Only one person is allowed
to stay in one room, and men aren't allowed
- Qiao Chen Xi!
- Qiao Xi Chen
Qiao Xi Chen!
Why are you making so much fuss?
What now?
You have a problem with my boyfriend?
We all came here to work
Why don't you have any empathy?
And you do? Are you sure?
Your boyfriend walks around the house
shirtless all the time and never knocks
Not only did he not knock today
he even left the door open
I had to close it for him
I've got to give it to you. You are right
Roommates should give and take
But it's always I give, you take
Stop speaking as if you're so great
I let you ogle at my boyfriend for free
Bring home your boyfriend if you can
I can't be bothered
But who are you to blame if you can't?
You're just jealous of me
If you feel uncomfortable about it
then move out
I've never met such a fussy roommate like you
I'm staying! You can move out if you want
Co-renting is like buying lottery tickets
You need a stroke of luck to find
a trustworthy landlord and a nice roommate
It's much relaxing living alone
Living alone is nice, but so is the price
Look how much it costs
That's half my monthly salary
How can I afford it?
- I guess you're right
- I've been looking at this
- Look
- It does look pretty neat
- The flooring is new
- Yes
It's fully furnished
But the price does seem a little steep
It's at a good location too
These things belong to the landlord
But you'll be living here alone anyway
I'll look around some more
Sure, you can
What do you think about this?
It has lesser furniture
There's more than enough space
It's pretty nice and tidy
- Right?
- Even the walls are clean
I just tidied it up
Where is this room facing?
How come there's no sunlight?
It's probably facing the south
This blackout curtain is really good
This...
There's one more unit over there
and another over here
Wait, sir. Slow down
It's been years
since I've climbed so many flights of stairs
This is nothing. Just six floors
You'll get to save on gym membership
going up and down every day
- Am I right?
- Thank you
But I would still prefer
finding a place with an elevator
You can only get units in these
small old neighborhoods with that budget
I'll be frank with you
The landlord is often away from Beijing
The rent has stayed the same for three years
Otherwise, you won't find a place here
with that budget
The home appliances are almost as old as I am
That's true, but they last long
These big brand appliances
are still working after 20 over years
I still wish to find a place with elevator
Why don't we keep looking?
Alright, then. Let's go
It's hard to find a place here
with that budget
There is one that's a little far though
The tenant just moved out recently
after renting this place for over three years
He stopped renting
because he bought himself a house
The landlord even had the walls repainted
The television and fridge are new
It also has a squarish layout
What do you think?
Well...
To be honest, I like it
especially the bedroom. It's just that...
It's too far from my workplace
Not at all. Don't you work in Wangjing?
You can get straight to work
by taking the subway Line 15 here
So? What do you say?
Okay. I'll rent this place
Good. I'll go check on the home utilities
- Okay. Thank you
- Don't mention it
Thank you, sir
Thank you
- This is the last box
- Okay. Thanks for helping, Chang
I'm finally leaving
Thanks for taking care of me for so long
So long!
Are you tired?
Miss
You lead the way later
- We'll follow behind. Okay?
- Sure
- We'll lead the way
- Sure, I'll drive
- Thank you, sir
- Let's go
Watch your step
Sir, watch out for the threshold
- That's the last of it
- Thank you, Chang
Thanks for the help. Here's some water
Thank you. By the way, Miss
The wheel on this doesn't work, right?
It was already broken. It's not your fault
That's not what I meant
I had nothing much to do in the truck earlier
so I fixed it. Try it out
Yes, it wasn't working previously
Thank you, sir
I'll pay you back for fixing it
Don't worry about it. It's nothing
I just thought it'd be a waste
if you threw it away
If that's all, then I'll get going
- Okay. Thank you
- Bye bye
- I'll call you if I need help next time
- Sure
He's so kind. There's still a lot of
good people in this world
But isn't this place a little too far?
You think everyone lives
right across their workplace like you?
It is quite far
but I've done some calculations
I'll have plenty of time to watch dramas
and read books while I travel to and fro
So it's not a waste of time, right?
Didn't you guys notice on the way here?
There's a mall, cinema, gym
and such places nearby
The area here is so much better
than my previous place
Even if I stay at home during the weekends
next time, it's still good
Yes, but we're living so far away
from each other. It'll be hard to meet
- Move in with me then
- I think...
No way. What about me?
I had a feeling
- What kind of feeling?
- Well
The moment I stepped into this house
I suddenly had this feeling
I, Qiao Xi Chen
am about to start my new chapter in life
(Alarm)
- I'm really sorry
- It's fine
Good morning
- You're finally here
- What's the matter?
Mr. Jian was looking for you all morning
to talk about the venue
- Quickly go
- You're lying
What for? He's been waiting
This isn't my day
The one time I'm late in a thousand years
- and he caught me
- I mean...
Did you go fight for
Spring Festival train tickets or what?
Are you kidding me? I left my house
40 minutes earlier and I'm still late
It took me almost an hour just to get into
the station. It was insanely crowded
I've never ran like that
since my college entrance exam
- Hurry
- I'm a bit nervous
He was looking for you all morning. Quick
You can do this. Hurry
(Miss Ji, it's your birthday soon)
(Fully-furnished house
Massive year-end promo)
- See you, Qiao Qiao
- Bye bye
Qiao, we're going for supper later. Join us
I don't think I'll go
It'll be too late for me
to catch the last train
You can hail a car
Don't be ridiculous. Even ride-sharing
is expensive for me, let alone hailing
Fine. We won't invite you
for supper from now on
Come on! I'm not saying that
I'll never join you at all
- At least invite me out of courtesy
- Got it
- We'll get going then
- I'll leave in ten minutes
- Bye bye
- Go on. Bye bye
Gou Dan! Look!
The three of us are here
to take you home, Gou Dan
You've gone mad
Giving a cat a dog's name
What if it doesn't like it?
Isn't that her style, though?
By the way
We can get Jing Jing's
bank account transaction records now
Her parents have sent me
the letter of authorization
Okay
The paperwork is done
Here's the cat food you wanted
This toy is a gift from me to Gou Dan
I also wrote you a list of things
to take note since you've never had a cat
Send me a message anytime
if you have any questions
- Thank you
- Don't mention it
Bye, Gou Dan. I'll leave you to it
- Thank you
- Thanks
Show it some love
since it's in the carrier now
I will. I'll carry it. Like this, right?
- Let's go
- Relax
- Come on
- I'm relaxed
- Let's go, Gou Dan
- It's basically taking a chopper now
- Come on in
- My, my, Qiao!
- Not bad
- Slippers
It's so much better than your old place
This is really neat
It's so bright and spacious
You should hold a housewarming party
I don't have time for a housewarming
Come here, Gou Dan. Look
Our new home. Do you like it?
Nice. This is really nice
When I came here
I thought this place was nice
That's why I decided to move in
But it was all wishful thinking
I leave the house at seven in the morning
and rush to work
Even if I don't work overtime
I reach home after nine
I can't even be bothered to remove my makeup
I just want to lay down when I get home
At first, I thought it wasn't so bad
It is quite far, but I can play with my phone
or read books on the subway
But do you know how crowded it is
during the peak hours?
I couldn't even reach for my phone
I was the same when I just started working
I was staying in Yanjiao
Our office was in Guomao at that time
I'd have to travel
two to three hours to work every day
Sometimes when there's an event in Beijing
they'll have roadblocks in Yanjiao, right?
I'd always be stuck there forever
One day, I left for work at 7 am
and reached the office at 4 pm
People were about to go home
when I got there. My manager was furious
and said, "Why didn't you
get a place near the office?"
I felt so wronged
That's so mean
Did you fire back at your manager?
Of course not. My manager wasn't wrong
I just feel that...
Sometimes, you can't expect people
to understand your situation
Empathy doesn't exist in this world
Everyone who works here
is doing their best to charge forward
Doing your part
is the kindest act you can do for others
Why are you pitying me?
I'm doing great now. Look at me
I have a big house
and I don't have to take the crowded subway
What? Are you rubbing it in my face now?
You'll succeed too
I know I will
Not only that, I'm also not allergic to cats
I can have a cat. Plus...
- Bye. I'm leaving
- Okay. I'm sorry
- Are you free tomorrow?
- No
I mean after work
I have to go home
- Don't be silly
- I...
I'm treating everyone to dinner. Tomorrow's
the last day before the festive season
Give me a minute
You came back at the right time
Guys, since tomorrow's the last day of work
before the festive season
and as a new member of the team
I'd like to treat everyone to dinner
Please do come. Thank you!
- Sure!
- Thank you.
You know
I think you're really something
You've turned your onboarding
into a huge sensation
That's a must
- I'm not going. I live really far away
- Qiao
- It'll be really late by the time I get home
- Come on. Everyone's going
- Please. I'm begging you
- I'm so easy to convince
Fine. I'll go
Eat all you want. It's on me
- That's all I need now. Bye
- See you tomorrow
- See you guys tomorrow night!
- Okay
- Keep it up
- Thank you
- I'm telling you
- What is it?
Do you know how crowded the station is
nearing the festive season?
Don't worry
Gou Dan, what are you up to?
Gou Dan
Playing with your toy?
Gou Dan, were you playing by yourself?
Seriously, your name
I was out earning money to feed you
Am I great?
I brought you home
but I can't spend time with you
You must be really bored being at home alone
Do you want a Mid-Autumn present?
Gou Dan
Such a good kitty. You were waiting for me
Come on
Look!
What's this?
This is your playground from now on
Isn't it nice?
I even made you a little flower. Look
It looks amazing
My owner made this for me
even though she's tired
I love you so much
I love you too
Alright
Quiet, everybody. We just received a notice
from the headquarters
Our company will be updating our CI system
They want someone from customer service
to shoot the promotional video
Whoever is interested
can come find me after the holidays
Okay, that's all. Get back to work
Hello
Have you signed up for the promotional video?
I'm still undecided. You?
Of course I have. It's a great opportunity
Do you remember Wendy?
She grabbed her chance at the company's
Top 10 Prettiest Smiles contest
Now she's an executive secretary
with a bright future
Wendy is competent
Still, you need opportunities
to show your capabilities
I'll just watch on the sidelines
- Xu Yan, you can win this. Good luck
- Thank you
Fatty, you think only Xu Yan can win?
I think you can win too. Good luck
I must give my face a full treatment
during this holiday
So? Are you coming?
I'm...
- I'm coming
- Then...
- I'm coming too
- That's more like it
Hey, listen
I know an interesting psychological test
Want to try?
- What is it?
- Let's do it
First, think of an object
Let's start with you. Everyone, try it
- Basketball
- Okay, basketball. You?
- A ring
- Okay
- A cup
- Okay. And you?
Qiao, what are you doing?
- Connecting to the Wi-Fi
- Qiao. Try this psychological test
I don't play these stuff
- Afraid that I'll see through you?
- Yes, I'm really afraid
- Guys, I'm...
- Mr. Jian
Mr. Jian
Sit down
You see. I'm Mr. Jian's assistant, right?
So Mr. Jian should be here
for my onboarding dinner
- Let's welcome Mr. Jian
- Welcome, Mr. Jian
Alright. Sit down
Mr. Jian, what booze do you want?
I don't drink. But I brought you guys
two bottles of good wine
Drink this
- Thank you, Mr. Jian
- Quick. Open it
This is good stuff
Thank you, Mr. Jian
How about we drink to Mr. Jian?
- Thank you, Mr. Jian
- Thank you, everyone
- Cheers
- Happy holidays
- Thank you, Mr. Jian
Help yourselves to the food
- Eat
- Dig in
Guys, this is their signature dish
Try the fish. It tastes amazing. Try it
Mr. Jian, have you looked at
my presentation file?
If there's any problem with it
you can tell me
It's no longer working hours
and it's the festive season tomorrow
Whatever we discuss now can't be completed
before the holiday ends
So just focus on the dinner, okay?
It can be completed
I can work over the holidays
Qiao Xi Chen, why are you
going against your boss' orders?
He already said we've clocked out
- But you're talking about work over dinner
- I...
My bad. As punishment, I'll down a glass
- I'm sorry
- Let's all drink
Happy holidays!
Be careful on your way home
Don't drive if you've drunk. Hail a car
- Go on then
- Bye bye
Happy holidays
- Enjoy your holiday
- Happy Mid-Autumn Festival
- Where is Qiao Xi Chen?
- Washroom
Everybody left
- How are you going home?
- I'm taking the subway
It's the holidays. Treat yourself better
It's too expensive to hail a car back home
I can give you a lift home
No, it's fine, Mr. Jian
It's convenient taking the subway
- What about you?
- My boyfriend
Bye bye
- Be careful
Go spend time with your boyfriend
No, I want to bring you with me
- It's so slippery
- Slow down
I wonder which one of them
will get down first
I hope it's the guy
Sir, it's my stop
This is bad
If he gets down first
then I'll be left alone with the driver
It's so late at night
Both your destinations are in different
directions. Which one should I go first?
Ladies first
Thank you
Miao, I haven't arrived
I'm sharing a ride to the subway station
I'm almost there. You don't have to worry
(Construction Notice)
They're fixing the road so it's blocked
Why don't you get down here?
- The station is just right across
- Okay, thank you
- Hello?
- Hello
Why do you sound like that? Are you home yet?
I think I'm being followed
- Where are you?
- Near the subway station
Don't panic, Qiao Xi Chen. Listen to me
Find nearby stores that are open
and wait in there
There's a convenience store
Good. Wait inside and send me your location
- Don't come out until I've arrived. Got it?
- Okay
Welcome
What are you looking for?
I'm still looking
Hurry up. We're closing soon
I need to lodge a report
It's 26.80 yuan
I took this by mistake
- I'll put it back
- It's fine. Just leave it
- Okay. Thanks
- Just these two, then?
- It's six yuan
- I've already paid
Mr. Jian, I think the person
isn't following me anymore
Maybe I was just being paranoid
It's quite far here. You don't have to come
I'll just dash to the station
and I'll be home soon
Who are you?
Stop screaming
Who the heck are you?
Stop!
What's going on? Who called the police?
Let go of him
It was me
Officer Tan
It's you two. What a coincidence
My wife is pregnant so I came out to smoke
and get some milk for her
Then I saw them and suddenly got attacked
I don't even know them
He suddenly came at me
- Where do you live?
- Here. Room 901, Unit 3, Building 12
Okay. Be more cautious
during the night next time
- Alright
- Go home
Here's your ID. Please sign here
It's just a misunderstanding
Go comfort the young lady
We'll get going
Sorry for troubling you
Don't give yourself a fright next time
Sorry about that
I made you come all the way here for nothing
Whenever you're with me from now on
I'll take you home no matter how late it is
Your legs
(Ji Nan Jia's 36th Birthday Party
and Qiao Qiao's Housewarming)
(Happy Mid-Autumn Festival)
(The Strongest Women On Earth)
- Somebody said this was lame
- Now she's wearing this
- What about your outfit? Is this it?
- This is it. Can't you tell?
Let me guess. Are you Cheon Song Yi?
You are a Minion?
Minions wear overalls
- Where's your overall?
- A Minion
- Hey, you two
- A banana?
- This is heavy
- You should be able to tell right away
I was scouted to appear in a film
when I was in college
You two even said
you'd go to the cinemas to support me
- You didn't watch it?
- We did
I'm that...
- Sailor Moon?
- Who?
- She's a Minion
- No. Stand up
- I know what is that
- I even had a line
Stand here. You're the queen
and I'm the one who said
"My queen, no"
- I think you acted really well
- Yes, you're right. She was great
- You two didn't watch it
- We did. You were amazing
I played the role of Baba Fairy
Didn't you watch it?
- We did
- Baba Fairy! That's right!
- I remember it now
- You acted so well as Baba Fairy
If it weren't because I was worried that...
- Baba Fairy? Bala Bala?
- No, Baba Fairy
- It's called Baba Fairy
- Bala Bala
I shouldn't have given up acting
because of you two
- Who are you, Nan Jia?
- Isn't it obvious?
Nanny Rong
It's probably not a hopping vampire
Look at the hat. Nanny doesn't wear this
No, it's an important figure
Look closely
I know. It's a prince
- Which prince was it?
- It's Prince 14th
Let's quickly take a picture
The hat is heavy as heck
The prince is annoyed
- You don't want to be prince?
- Let's take a picture
- Do I have to pay?
- Yes
How much for a picture?
- Fifty yuan
- I'm famous
- Pay five yuan for touching
- Three, two, one
Hey!
- You two
- Get rid of the banner that says "36"
- Thirty-six
- What's wrong? Everyone reaches that age
- You just got there first
- We're 36 too with our ages combined
Grab her
We're following you
I really look like a guy in this
- Rock star
- This looks nice
- Who can tell it's a woman?
- Only you can be seen
- I look nice in this too
- I went all out
Thank you for today, girls
But this moon cake...
Don't these candles come with the cake?
If there's a candle, there's a cake, right?
- Didn't you get the cake?
- I thought you were getting it
I don't have the money
You said you'd get it
- Why didn't you get it?
- I don't have the time
It's fine. It's the same
I like moon cakes too
Who knew she'd make
unreasonable requests at this age?
Why do you still want a cake?
- I'm flipping this table
- She still wants a cake
- A cake
- She wants a cake!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to...
You!
- Lovely!
- Make a wish
- Quickly make a wish
- See the sign?
Read it out loud
"Love my Jia"
I hope this year, you'll find a good man
to stay by your side
To bicker with you and be really sweet
- Shut it
- Hurry up. Your turn
My turn. Nan Jia
Since you like making a fuss, I hope...
I hope this year, you'll find someone
who will bicker with you until you grow old
I'm stuffed. No more after this
I have to go on a diet
You're always going on about stuff like that
- You're not even fat
- What do you know?
I'm not just going on a diet
I'm getting Botox injection too
If that's not enough
I'll also get liposuction
- What has gotten into you?
- Don't be mean
If you live like me
I leave the house early
and get home late every day
I don't even join my colleagues for dinner
so that I can catch the last train
I walk into my neighborhood looking like this
I'm worried someone is following me
like a detective
I pretend to be a man when I order food
I'm not exaggerating
I answer the phone in a deep voice
If you lived like me
you wouldn't be thinking of those
You have persecutory delusions
Nan Jia lives alone too
Why isn't she afraid?
How can you compare our neighborhood?
Hers is great
I won't be staying there for long
Are you going bankrupt?
I'm planning to buy a house
- I shouldn't have asked
- You're buying a house?
Jing Jing used to convince me
but I thought it wasn't necessary
But I've changed my mind lately
The water leakage at my house
caused me so much trouble previously
So I thought, I should just buy it
Don't I always have a luggage packed at home?
I used to leave it there
when I had business trips
so that I didn't have to pack all the time
Now it's been there for ages
One day, I looked at it and thought
Is this really my home?
Hear that? What a sweet trouble
She's talking about buying a house
as if she's buying food
It burns a hole in my pocket too
I have things I want too
I'm just reluctant to spend the money
I'll just have more things to pack
when I move houses
You've bought enough stuff
If you buy some more
Shen Zi Chang will be crying
He should cry more
so that he gets a clear head
It's funny. Each of us
has our own problems to fret
I'm envious of you, you're envious of her
and she's envious of me
There's a saying by Haruki Murakami
"There's a kind of sadness in this world
that cannot be expressed in tears"
"You can't explain it to anyone"
"It remains the same forever"
"It settles quietly at the bottom of
your heart like snow in a windless night"
While you may disagree
you have no choice but to accept it
When you're unhappy with where you are
but can't find a way out
Anyone there? Your food is here
- Hello? Anyone there?
- Leave it at the door
Okay, I'll leave it here
When you're filled with worries
but unable to make changes
When anxiety becomes a norm
for every outlander
how are we supposed to complete
this mandatory lesson in life?
Is it mine? I wonder who it is
I'm talking to Gou Dan
I'm not listening to you
I'm talking to this person, not you
- Who's talking to you?
- I don't want to talk to you
I was talking to Gou Dan
Nan Jia, I've gotten the
bank transaction records you wanted
-We've got the transaction records?
- Yes
What are these for?
That's a lot
I think I know why Jing Jing was in debt