=Provoke=
=Episode 9 Dangerous Her=
What are you doing?
What do you think
I'm doing in the kitchen?
Are you hungry?
I haven't eaten all day.
How can I not be hungry?
I saw you walking here and there,
back and forth with a knife.
Were you looking for food?
There isn't any food
in this kitchen.
Weird.
How do you know where the food is?
You act like you were at your own home.
Don't you know how to cook?
I'm done talking with you.
If you continue to chop like this,
you'll awaken the whole family.
Watch me.
Eat.
How do you like it?
Good.
Take your time.
It's all yours.
What smells so good
in the middle of the night?
You almost scared me to death.
What are you doing?
Ma'am, I was hungry at night.
So I came downstairs
and got something to eat.
No wonder it smells so good.
Why is there an extra portion?
I made an extra.
Would you like to eat?
I'm not hungry.
An extra, huh?
We'd better not waste it.
It isn't bad.
I'll make do with it.
Shall I make you another one?
(Operating Room)
No wonder Du Jingchuang was so anxious
to go on the trip.
It turns out that our people
destroyed his opium business in Yuezhou.
It's such a shame.
We haven't uncovered the person
behind Du Jingchuang.
I must earn his trust
as soon as possible
so he'll take me to smuggle opium.
By the way,
how are things going with the Du Family?
There's a little situation.
But
nothing will go wrong.
Only now Mr. Zeng is dead,
and we can't find any clue about
Du Jingchuang using
the ship of Yongsheng to smuggle opium.
It's even harder to clear the name
of the Jiang Family.
What?
Do you think of Jiang Susu again?
I always have an illusion that
Susu is still alive.
If Du Jingchuang wasn't useful,
I would kill the traitor
right now.
(What is she doing now?)
Young Master.
Where is Mistress Jiang?
She is in the kitchen.
Young Master.
Mistress Jiang.
Xiaocui,
what soup do we have today?
West Lake Beef Soup.
Ma'am.
What's wrong?
There seemed to be a fly.
Ma'am.
What's wrong again?
This dish,
the cook told me it was salty.
You'd better not try it.
It isn't salty.
Ma'am.
What's wrong this time?
This dish...
Look at that tofu.
It looks dark and stale.
It definitely tastes bad.
I'm full.
Enjoy yourselves.
Already?
She just left like that?
It's rude.
Is this edible?
Sure.
(Jiang Ying,)
It's spicy.
(no matter what your purpose is,)
Who cooked this?
(I'll keep an eye on you.)
Young Master.
I found this guy.
Du...
Mr. Du, what can I do for you?
What did you trade with a woman
here yesterday?
Dr. Li,
what's this?
This is a new type of medicine,
which should've been
smuggled from abroad.
It's used for calming patients.
Speaking of which,
has your friend suffered from
serious mental irritation?
Serious mental irritation.
Do you mean
she is mentally disturbed?
Wu.
Ma'am.
Close the door.
Come here.
I asked you to keep an eye on
Mistress Jiang and Young Master.
Why haven't you found out
about anything?
There's nothing between
Mistress Jiang and Young Master.
All right.
Keep watching them.
Mistress Jiang went to...
Just go.
OK.
Ma'am, soup is ready.
Do you want to have some now?
Master isn't home.
Why would I want to eat soup?
I can't believe him.
He's been away for days
without a phone call.
How could he ask me
to look after his precious concubine?
What did you say?
Ma'am, Master asked you to
look after Mistress Jiang.
Shall I save her a bowl of soup?
Are you kidding?
Don't save her any rice or dishes.
Maybe some rice, no dishes.
Is she really
(mentally disturbed?)
(She took great pains to move in,)
(but she didn't do anything after that.)
(She's like a landmine)
(that makes people shake with fear.)
(So,)
(is her target Du Jingchuang?)
(Forget it.)
(As long as she doesn't
disturb my plan,)
(I don't care.)
(What is this guy thinking?)
(Isn't he tired of)
(following me?)
What's their problem?
Not saying a word,
they just eat rice quietly.
Why?
Because they have no dishes.
Why don't they?
Because...
That's your order.
Uncle Wu.
That's my red hair tie.
Could you please return it to me?
(Clean up this room,)
or you'll be the murderer
on the front page tomorrow.
This is the hair tie
I used when I was a child.
My dad bought it for me personally
when he was still alive.
I liked it very much.
Thanks for finding it for me.
Uncle Wu, could you let me go?
Miss.
I'm sorry.
Don't blame me.
Uncle Wu, don't.
Uncle Wu.
No, Uncle Wu.
No.
Uncle Wu.
I still have work to do.
I have to go.
♪To love someone to the end♪
♪Needs talent♪
♪Our eye contact♪
♪Is like a kiss♪
♪Two hearts yearn for each other
from afar♪
♪We're destined to touch
each other's figure from behind♪
♪But I'll still fall♪
♪Passionately devoted♪
♪I stay there still though
the early morning is getting cold♪
♪And the dusk♪
♪Look at my palm print♪
♪How tangled it is for love♪
♪You see me as dust♪
♪You mock me
for taking it too seriously♪
♪You shut your heart on me suddenly♪
♪But I'm quiet♪
♪As always♪
♪Waiting for you to ask me♪
♪You see me as a distant star♪
♪You mock me for not knowing
when to stop♪
♪Promising to forget you,
I don't have the heart to♪
♪My desperate efforts♪
♪Only earn me an uncertain fate♪
♪All this life♪
(The right of network communication
of this work)
(is exclusively owned by Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)