sorry
I'm afraid I can't take this up.
Why? Not enough money?
It's not because I'm not qualified.
No matter how much money you give me, it won't work.
Are you afraid of South Korea?
Yes
I was also at
11 years ago in that place
Do you believe it?
Nanjixi
Do you believe that those young boys killed him?
Do you think it's possible?
- Hello, Pastor.
- Good evening
- Hello
- Let's go in.
This weather is really
Where is Junmo now?
With Director Kim Chun-seok
Let him go to Yang Ping's safe house immediately
No, Director, please take him there yourself.
Also, have your men check with the police.
Go to the police to check?
Find out who was the first person to call the police in the Nam Ki-seok case
Who are the police officers in charge of the investigation?
Confirm whether it was those guys who did it
Find out all the circumstances
Understood
《Unforgiven Revenge》
(De Kro Hotel)
General Manager!
We have to go now
There is a safe house in Yangpyeong
The president asked me to take you there directly.
Let's go now
Just because my dad tells me to go, I have to go?
General Manager
South Benchmark is looking for you
Because of that bastard
Is that what made you so anxious?
You may not fully understand the situation.
South Benchmark…
What exactly is the South Benchmark?
Make you all so scared?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
All out
Who is this person?
What are you doing here?
Come on, I'll take you there.
What are you doing?
Send you to Yangping
How long do we have to clean up his mess?
yes
Can't pass this way
"Send Junmo to Yangping
If he doesn't obey, I'll beat him up."
This is the president's instruction.
Director Li, are you crazy?
Director Jin, you are incompetent, so you asked me to come
You bastard!
Is Gu Junmo upstairs?
Fuck! Let go!
Let him go!
Are you crazy?
Listen to the general manager, bastard!
Oh shit!
You have to leave now.
Leave now!
let go
Oh, please listen to me this time, okay?
- Hey, I'd like to see it.
- The General Manager is really...
This bastard is really here
Please stand up and listen to me, please!
Son of a bitch!
Brother Jiben! Please don't do this, okay?
Stop it for my sake!
Please!
Walking quite steadily
Is the executive all right?
Get up, stand up!
Take him away
Get up quickly!
Let’s go, let’s go quickly!
Hold!
How many times have I told you? You just won't listen!
Who the fuck is this?
Quan Haifan this madman
Goo Joon Mo!
- Why!
- Take your hands off!
- Stop the car!
- Get out of the way!
Damn it! Get out of the way!
What the fuck are you doing?
Is Junmo okay?
Well, I was just a little scared, but it's okay.
I'm taking him to Yangping now.
Strengthening security
No one must know where he is, understand?
Please rest assured
How far do we have to drive?
General Manager
arrive
Team leader, do you want to crush this one too?
Oh, I don't know either.
It’s up to you!
We're really going to be caught now.
He will definitely be severely punished.
Can we really just run away like this?
You bastard, do you think you are Kong Ming?
I asked you to clean up after dinner.
You took a shit for 40 minutes, you bastard
Run while there's still time, idiot.
- Look...
- Mr. Shen...
Fengshan Group
Now the South Base is in a mess
Now is the only chance to run.
I'll get you some coffee.
Are you going somewhere?
Nowhere to go
Just came back
Just got back from a business trip
I'm so exhausted.
Do you know where Gu Junmo is?
oops
I told you I just came back from a business trip.
This time he probably decided to hide.
Even if you dig three feet deep, you won't find it.
Find it out
Give you a day
What do you think, Director?
Will it really be worth the effort?
Prosecutor Lee
Why?
what why?
Eavesdropping Device
Why did you reveal this to me?
Director Cui
I'm a gangster in a prosecutor's uniform
So I know very well
Compared to individuals, organization is the most important
In this respect, prosecutors are very similar to gangsters.
Director Cui, what do you think?
Cover up the death of Director Nam
Is it really good for the company?
The chairman's decision is my idea.
I understand my father.
If Gu Junmo died, it would cause a violent conflict.
Of course he'll be scared.
I am afraid that everything I have worked so hard to build will collapse in an instant.
But I think this is an opportunity
Completely destroy the Fengshan Group
Let us take control of everything
My wife's garbage sorting this week
Can you handle this?
I really can't go home recently
- Can you...
- Director Kim!
Wait a moment
Wife, I have to hang up. I'm hanging up.
Director Kim Chun-seok!
You called me?
I will continue what I was halfway through saying yesterday.
What's up?
South Base
Tell me more about this guy.
Benchmark brother?
Are you finally curious now?
South Base
General Manager
How much do you know about the South Bend?
The South Base
To us, it is God
Because now Jiyun Group and Fengshan Group
The reason for existence
It's all thanks to Nanji
President! Busan Gang...
When Lee Eun-woon and Gu Bong-san were still under Chairman Oh
They clash with the biggest gang in Busan
Chairman Wu wants to enter Japan
Busan Port must be controlled
So they sent them both to Busan, but they were too late.
Busan Gang strikes first
They fought hard but couldn't hold on.
It's about to collapse
Kill them all!
At this time, the South Base appeared
Kill him!
Son of a bitch!
Go to hell!
You bastard!
What's going on?
We once again realized
No matter who the opponent is, no matter how many people there are
It doesn't matter to the South Datum
From that day on
The status of Lee Eun-woon and Gu Bong-san has been significantly improved
Oh, here comes Seungwon.
There are even rumors that
Chairman Wu intends to hand over the company to the two of them
Instead of giving it to your son
What's wrong, son? Do you want to say something?
nothing
grateful
Rumors sowed seeds of hatred
Angered Chairman Wu's son
Are you sure it was Chairman Wu’s son who gave the order?
Yes!
I'm thinking
I can only confess to both of you and ask for forgiveness.
Only then can there be a way to survive!
Please believe me, please!
this
Please listen to this
Listen to this
Listen!
How many times have I said
Li Yunyun and Gu Fengshan! Kill them both
In the end, Chairman Wu’s son went too far
Hire someone to kill them both
The truth came to light
Then something happened.
- Oh shit!
- Is there a power outage?
Turn on the lights
What the fuck are you doing?
Lee Eun-woon and Gu Bong-san
Bring them to me
What's going on?
I want to kill Chairman Wu's son.
It is good for the future of the company.
Are you fucking kidding?
- You're such a fool
- Boss, you have to make a decision.
Or just sit there and wait to be killed by President Wu.
Either we take the initiative
Benchmark
President!
This was all done by Jiyun himself.
I really don’t know!
I really don't know
You saved the president while I was away.
I thank you very much
I really hope...
This is not what you did.
sorry
Benchmarks
Why did you do that?
I really don't understand
I really don't understand why you would do this.
The president's son...
You didn't kill him, did you?
Does this matter?
sorry
I'm late
Just one day
Chairman Wu fell.
at the same time
Lee Eun-woon and Gu Bong-san
Take control of the overall situation
After that incident
In order to maintain balance, a new rule was born.
“Anyone
If you cause trouble, you must pay the price."
The first victim of this rule was Nan Jijun
He helped them get everything.
But he is also the source of the problem
But he did make great contributions after all...
So you only cut his hamstrings?
right
Maybe they are afraid of South Korea
Li Yun is afraid
Chairman Gu is the same
so…
You expect me to believe this bullshit?
Then stay here.
Right?
All right
Just live in fear all your life
sorry
I couldn't stop Gu Junmo
Don't worry about it.
I heard that it was Chairman Gu's son who killed Ki-seok.
Right?
Think about the benchmark again.
I understand your feelings
But only on our own
Unable to fight against the entire Fengshan Group
I'll solve it myself
That's not what I meant.
I'm worried about you
How about this?
I'll go talk to the president of the Jiyun Association...
The company has decided to cover up the matter.
What?
He knew it was Gu Junmo who did it but told everyone to forget it.
In the eyes of the chairman, Ki-seok is nothing.
Oh shit!
Let me out
You bastards
Let me out!
Is this where people live? It's basically a prison!
You bunch of bastards!
Let me out!
Let me out! Shit!
I want to go back to Seoul
- If anything happens, call me right away.
- yes
(Gu Junmo)
What's wrong, brother?
Hey, I have a job for you guys.
Big Job
I'll make it clear
This time
To get people
Make sure to do it neatly
Any work?
We will do it tonight and he will tell us the location when he comes back.
How many people?
Just one
Just one?
(Executive Director Gu Junmo)
Director
Director, what do you mean?
The problem is that Nan Ji Ben is still alive
As long as Nan Ji is dead
There's no problem.
What?
South Benchmark
I'll get him.
I looked into Nam Ki-seok's case.
Something feels wrong
“The first person to discover and report it to the police
Han Seok-yoon"
The police officer in charge of this case is Han Seok-yoon
He was also the first person to call the police
Go find him
Bring him to me
Go now
clear
Benchmark Brother
Were you not hurt last night?
haven't seen you for a long time
How are you?
It seems that Director Gu is not going to give in this time.
Brother Benchmark, no matter how great you are
The opponent is not just Gu Junmo
The entire Fengshan Group
It's really dangerous if you continue like this.
Does the entire Fengshan Group include you?
Hey, don't say that.
Now think about it
I used to follow you everywhere...
The square was the most imposing at that time.
At least people back then were willing to take responsibility for what they did.
Why did you ask me to meet you?
Take this
Gu Junmo is hiding here
What's wrong?
Am I going to run away forever?
Don't worry about me
I was planning to leave the company anyway.
Benchmark brother!
Go ahead
Just finish what you're going to do, okay?
(Renovation notice: 10th to 13th floors are temporarily closed)
Sorry, Benchmark
You go see Nan Ji
He will ask me where I am.
You just pretend to be helpless
Lead him into my trap
I heard your daughter just learned to walk.
Don't you want to watch her grow up?
Oh, Director Kim!
Is Nan Ji Ji more important than your family?
I want your family to survive.
He must be killed.
(Okur)
Is the mission accomplished?
Speak
Is that bastard dead?
You wait
I'll come to you
《Unforgiven Revenge》
(11 years ago)
The president's son...
You didn't kill him, did you?
Does this matter?