It is the 1950s,
following the devastating Korean War.
Female gukgeuk, or traditional theater,
captures the heart of the public,
and many girls dream of becoming princes.
Playing the role of Yoon Jeongnyeon,
a pansori genius
who dives into the world of stars,
is Kim Taeri.
Playing the role of Heo Youngseo,
an elite trainee skilled at singing,
dancing, and even acting,
is Shin Yeeun.
Playing the role of Moon Okgyeong,
the undisputed Prince of Maeran,
is Jung Eunchae.
Playing the role of Seo Hyerang,
the beautiful flower of Maeran,
is Kim Yoonhye.
And last but not least
is the director of all the girls
who dream of becoming princes,
Kang Sobok played by Ra Miran.
We want to thank you for your patience
as we proudly present
the story of Jeongnyeon!
"JEONGNYEON: THE STAR IS BORN"
"Narrator: Cho Yeongsuk
First-generation female gukgeuk actor"
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
THE SHOW CONTAINS JAPANESE EXPRESSIONS
TO REFLECT THE TIME PERIOD.
You're not the only one
with a temper or pride.
From now on,
I'll make sure to pay you back
for whatever you do to me.
I don't have any reason…
to be patient with you.
Oh yeah? What could you possibly do?
You really were raised like a princess,
weren't you?
You're getting worked up
over something as tiny as this.
Look at you throwing a fit
because someone saw you get scolded.
You have no idea how I feel.
Do you know what it feels like
to be denied by your own mother?
You wouldn't.
You don't have a care in the world.
Watch it.
You think you're the only one
who suffers in life?
Think of all the benefits you received
from having a famous mother.
What did you possibly lose out on?
My skills…
are purely the result of my own efforts.
It has nothing to do with my mother!
Hey.
You have no idea how much I struggled
to be recognized for my hard work.
This is what I meant
when I said you were raised
like a princess all your life.
Most trainees from Maeran
have jobs in town because they need money.
Did you ever have to worry about
not having enough money?
Your starting point
is already miles ahead of others!
And you have the audacity
to say that you got your skills
purely from your own efforts?
Forget it.
What's the point of telling you all this?
If you tell anyone
about what you saw today…
I'm going to kill you.
I don't care about you that much.
This is the last time we'll ever meet,
so let's just mind our own business.
The people at the party
must have really liked you.
They decided to invest more in us.
So we'll up your stage decor
and hire a better ensemble for your band
for you to have a bigger debut.
That was a great shot.
Thank you.
- It was a great performance.
- Thank you.
My Youngin here
is recognized for her skills
even in the States.
I see.
She makes me proud every day.
Oh my. Was I bragging
about my daughter too much?
It's fine.
You were just stating facts.
Thank you.
Act 5
Seoul Jongno Broadcasting Station
Come in.
Good morning.
Oh! Jeongnyeon.
You should have called me first.
You told me to come on time
for the interview.
Oh, was that today?
I guess I thought it was tomorrow.
- Come and have a seat.
- Okay.
So what were you hiding...
I mean, putting away?
You're making me curious.
Oh, this? It's nothing important.
Actually, the show writer
will be here soon.
Do you want some snacks?
Someone gifted me cookies from the States.
You should try some.
You can't get them anywhere in Korea.
Jeongnyeon.
Why do you have pictures of my mother?
You remember I told you
we needed some shots from your hometown?
These are just part of those shots.
You call that an excuse?
You said that
you'd just take shots of the scenery.
But all you have
are pictures of my mother.
So where are those scenery shots?
Answer me.
Why would you take pictures of my mother?
Fine.
You were going to find out
sooner or later.
"Prodigy rises
in national pansori contest"
This is your mother,
Chae Gongseon.
Prodigy disappears
Her first recording becomes her last
Chae Gongseon
of The Blooming Autumn Field disappears
I heard she sang pansori before, but…
Your mother
was no ordinary pansori singer.
She appeared out of nowhere
and won a title in the national contest
after competing
with the greatest masters in the nation.
Your mother did that.
I was there when she sang at the contest.
It was the moment that solidified her
as the undisputed genius of pansori.
I've never seen anything like it,
before or since.
And then…
you saw me at the coffee shop?
I couldn't believe my ears at first.
Your voice was the spitting image
of Chae Gongseon.
Then…
you approached me…
knowing I was her daughter
from the beginning?
Yes.
And…
you lied to my face?
What else are you hiding from me?
Wait…
The person who told the director
I was working at the coffee shop…
Was it you?
Answer me!
Yeah, it was me.
You're a total con man.
You completely deceived me
and had the nerve to tell me
that you'd like to invest in my talent?
You do have talent.
And I meant it
when I said I'd make you a star.
Just listen to my plan.
After we create some buzz with your debut,
we'll let it slip to the press
that you're Chae Gongseon's daughter.
That's when your mother
will appear on our show
and sing the legendary
Blooming Autumn Field!
So I'm just your bait
to get to my mother, huh?
But do you think things will go your way?
Television?
I'm done here!
If you walk out now,
you'll have to pay for breach of contract.
It's all written
in the contract you signed.
It holds you to a promise
that you'll pay damages
if you don't deliver on your end.
I never saw that on there.
You should have read the contract
more carefully.
If you can't pay damages,
then you'll get on our show and sing.
That was the agreement.
Dongbang Record Shop
The Blooming Autumn Field
It's been a while
since someone looked for this record.
You know of Chae Gongseon?
You seem quite young.
Was she famous?
She was beyond famous.
They sold
more than 100,000 copies of this record.
When people heard her name,
they immediately thought of this song.
Everyone was dying to hear her
sing this song for themselves.
Could you…
play this record right now?
Do you know
what's at the end of this path?
I poured out everything I had
into pansori.
And in the end,
I had nothing left.
Maeran Gukgeukdan Jamyunggo
Did you see that?
- I think our troupe is a whole lot better.
- I agree.
Our singing and choreography
are levels above theirs.
If we performed like that,
the director would kick us all out.
"Do you call that acting?"
What did you say?
That was hilarious. Do it again.
What is it?
Uh… it's nothing.
Were you with those friends again?
Aren't you going to check the script?
Nothing's new anyway.
The same narrative.
The same characters
but with different names.
The audition may change
who'll take the antagonist or minor roles,
but I'll take the male lead,
and you'll take the female lead.
Who else is good enough
to take the leads than us?
You're being weird nowadays.
Hyerang.
Should I quit gukgeuk?
Are you being serious?
I was just kidding.
How could I ever leave you?
Were you keeping watch in case I ran?
I guess paying damages
really does scare you.
I didn't stay for the damages
or my mother.
This is my performance.
I'm not going anywhere
until I finish my performance.
Is the band ready?
Costumes! Is that jacket okay?
All right, we're rolling!
Let's pan the camera out from the piano.
Coming to you
from the beautiful Mugunghwa Park.
With the end of the year approaching…
All right, you're good to go.
We'll keep one each
to remind us of our oath.
Oath? What oath?
That we'll always be friends.
And that we'll continue doing gukgeuk
until we're old and frail.
Jeongnyeon.
You can take it easy
since this is just a rehearsal.
But when we go live later,
you have to sing until the end
even if you make mistakes.
- All right.
- Okay?
- Let's start the rehearsal! Three!
- Okay.
Two!
One! Cue!
The sun is setting on the Mokpo docks
A lady looks for her love
Her cheeks
Are as rosy as the setting sun
Walking by gracefully
She lives by the blue ocean
When will he return…
She's good.
If this performance goes well,
it's all thanks to you.
She's doing everything
I told her to do, but…
But?
I don't think
I've ever seen her true self yet.
She's good enough for me right now.
At the slightest sight of his ship
What am I to do with this longing?
She goes on pacing
Lady of the Mokpo docks
The sun is setting on the Mokpo docks
A lad looks for his love
Cut!
Cut, cut!
Jeongnyeon, you're a lady.
Once you're on stage,
you should be sensuous and alluring.
Did you forget everything you practiced?
But…
the second verse
is when the man responds to the woman.
This isn't a gukgeuk performance!
Don't be silly,
lowering your voice like a man!
Just do as I tell you!
And if you're going to have gestures,
just use your hips and shoulders
like you did in the first verse.
Don't use those big gestures
like they do in gukgeuk.
Don't you know how to entice the audience?
Like a courtesan pouring drinks
and luring customers?
Am I a courtesan?
Is this how you're going to act?
Hey, you.
You can't go around being this arrogant
as if you're still in Maeran.
All you're good for is singing
when I tell you to sing
and smiling when I want you to smile.
Then am I your puppet?
If I can't perform the way I want to,
then I quit!
Hey!
I'll talk to her.
Do not ever forget
that you are artists
and make sure to act accordingly.
An artist…
Jeongnyeon.
I've had enough of this.
What's the point of performing
if my hands are tied
to his puppet strings?
He might as well
have a doll sing in my place.
Then what about your promise?
Promise?
Mr. Park tricked me from the start.
Are you telling me
that since I signed the contract,
I should keep my end of the bargain?
I'm not talking about your contract.
The moment you announced
that you'll sing on that stage,
you made a promise to your audience.
It's not a promise you can break
simply because
you don't feel like keeping it.
Forget about Mr. Park.
This performance
belongs to you and you alone.
Remember what I said before?
You need to own the song.
I'll be watching your performance
until the end,
so just focus on showing me
the kind of show
you want to perform.
The sun is setting on the Mokpo docks
- A lady looks for her love
- She's pretty good.
- Her cheeks…
- What a voice. Incredible.
You guys!
- Guys, guys, guys!
- What? What is it?
You guys!
Jeongnyeon is on television right now!
- What?
- Come on!
On television?
- Let's go!
- No way!
Hey! Jeongnyeon's on television!
Move!
- Come on, let's go!
- Careful!
- Here! Jeongnyeon!
- Move!
Really?
"Yoon Jeongnyeon Rising singer"
That's Jeongnyeon.
Raise the volume.
She lives by the blue ocean…
My gosh.
She's singing so well.
She looks so pretty all dolled up.
I barely recognize her.
Pretty, my foot.
My heart flutters
At the slightest sight of his ship
What am I to do with this longing?
She goes on pacing…
This is great.
Camera 2, get her face again.
Lady of the Mokpo docks
Amazing.
Bravo, bravo.
What? What is she doing?
Huh? What's she doing?
Why is she taking off her shoes?
The sun is setting on the Mokpo docks
A lad looks for his love
As dashing as the sea breeze…
I guess the second verse is sung by a guy.
But that's not pretty at all.
But it's funny.
I like that her acting matches the song.
What are you talking about?
She doesn't know a thing about pop...
Keep watching.
She's done it again.
My heart flutters
At the slightest sight of her skirt…
What is this, Mr. Park?
This is a disaster!
We can't even stop this since it's live!
What are you going to do?
She's doing whatever she wants out there!
I apologize.
She's new,
so she must not be familiar with our ways.
You said this would be a hit.
So what is this disaster?
Do something!
Lad of the Mokpo docks
That was Youth of Mokpo
by Ms. Yoon Jeongnyeon.
Ms. Yoon is a beautiful 19-year-old lady
who hails from the very city of Mokpo…
All right, that's enough.
But why?
- Turn it off.
- Do we have to?
That was fun.
I guess
television programs are pretty fun.
Jeongnyeon was pretty good.
We'll see her on television again, right?
I don't think we will.
Why not?
She sang the second verse
however she wanted.
That can't have been
what the studio told her to do.
Does that mean
she'll get kicked out again?
That's the least of her worries.
She'll probably have to pay damages.
Oh no.
All right, get up!
- Back to rehearsals.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't perform…
as a pop singer…
the way you taught me to.
No.
Don't be sorry.
That was the best performance
I've ever seen.
Really?
That would never have happened
if you only stuck to what I taught you.
That performance
was something only you could do.
So you should be proud of it.
I think I get what you were talking about.
From now on,
I won't deceive myself.
I can't live my life…
as anyone but me.
Remember…
don't make any choices that aren't you
under any circumstances.
Thank you for a wonderful performance.
Out of all the singers I've ever seen…
…you were number one.
So you're saying
that Jeongnyeon was only working
at the coffee shop for your sake?
Yes, ma'am.
And she didn't tell me any of this
to protect you?
Yes.
I'm the one who should be kicked out.
I'll of course take
whatever punishment you give me.
But please let Jeongnyeon come back.
Why were you working at the coffee shop?
My sister has tuberculosis.
I wanted to help pay for her medication.
All right.
You may go.
Do you know why I wanted
Jeongnyeon to join our troupe?
Others may say I lack nothing
since I've reached the peak of success
with gukgeuk performance.
But I was getting quite tired.
The same kinds of performances
with similar roles…
…and acting
that is no different from the next.
And since I had no rival to challenge me,
I had nothing to stimulate me whatsoever.
But when I heard Jeongnyeon sing…
I thought that one day
she'd be able to challenge my position.
That she'd quickly hone her skills
and come to threaten my place.
So…
you were looking for something
to stimulate you?
Our troupe needs someone like Jeongnyeon
as much as I do.
If we don't keep acquiring
young talent like her,
we'll become complacent,
and one day become completely stagnant.
You must know this more acutely than I do.
Hey, Yoon Jeongnyeon!
How are you going to fix this?
All the investors who trusted me
as well as the studio itself
will tear me to shreds!
So what are you going to do about this?
I was trying to keep my promise.
What?
That was my promise from the beginning.
That I'd perform
as much as my talent allows.
So what's wrong
with performing my heart out?
Why, you little…
Are you joking right now?
I don't care.
You're going to sing
the way I tell you to!
I'm not going to do that.
Then get your mother to come on our show!
Or pay up for damages!
And how much is that?
- Director.
- What are you doing here?
I heard that one of my trainees was here,
so I came to fetch her.
And by the way,
I know her mother very well.
You can count on me when I say
she'll never come on your show.
So I'll pay for her damages
and take her back.
Now, how much should I pay you?
I heard that you were working
at the coffee shop
in Jooran's place.
Do you still want to do gukgeuk?
Yes.
I do.
I really do.
It was my misunderstanding
that you had used Maeran's fame
for your personal gain.
So I shall take you back.
But you'll still be punished
for getting paid to sing
at the coffee shop.
I'll take whatever punishment you give me.
Director.
Did you also accept me at first…
because of my mother?
Why would you ask that?
I only just found out…
that my mother used to be
a famous pansori singer.
But others who have heard me sing…
said it immediately reminded them of her.
So you know
that your mother is Chae Gongseon?
Yes.
Finding out I was in my mother's shadow
without even knowing…
It's frustrating.
I feel like whatever I do in my life…
I'll get compared to my mother.
What a silly thought.
You are you.
There's no need for you to compete
with a mere idea of your mother.
And it doesn't matter
why I accepted you in the beginning.
What matters is what you will do
with the chance you've been given.
I only want one thing from you.
To not give up…
and walk your own path until the very end.
How about a dance for the chancellor...
Wait a minute.
I think it'd be better
if you had bigger movements
as you approach Mokryeon.
- What do you all think?
- I think that's good.
Hey, kids!
- I'm back.
- Jeongnyeon!
Jeongnyeon!
How are you here?
Did the director take you back in?
I… heard you told her everything.
How could you be so reckless?
You could have been kicked out too.
It's what I should have done
from the beginning.
I'm sorry, Jeongnyeon.
Are you crying again?
You must have been so distressed
because of me.
But thanks to you,
the director…
has decided to forgive me.
Really?
Then you'll be staying with us
like before?
I'm telling you, I am!
That's so great, Jeongnyeon!
Hey, let me through.
You're looking better
now that you've been on television.
You've gotten prettier.
We all watched you sing on television.
Where did you learn to sing like that?
I almost didn't recognize you.
- You all watched it?
- Yeah.
Move it. Come on.
What was all that about?
You're supposed to sing pop songs
like a delicate lady.
But you even took off your shoes.
It wasn't pretty at all.
But it seems like
you watched the whole thing.
- Admit it.
- You watched it.
I had to because everyone else did.
Admit it. Weren't you bored
because you had no one to pick on anymore?
Aren't you glad I'm back?
Nope.
It was nice and quiet.
Did you just speak with an accent?
- Did you?
- You did!
- I didn't!
- My goodness, my little Chorok.
Did you miss me that much?
I didn't have an accent.
I missed you too.
I missed you!
Come on, loosen up!
So what were you guys doing?
Let me in on it!
Is this really okay?
Taking a photo must be really expensive.
When else
are we supposed to take pictures?
Today's the day
you recorded your very first recording.
We need to take a photo on a day like this
so it will be commemorated
by generations to come.
Come on, I don't need any of that.
All I need are you and my father.
The camera's ready.
Please sit down.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Life really is unpredictable, isn't it?
I thought our relationship
died out years ago.
Who would've guessed…
that I would take your daughter in twice?
Hey.
There's something
I found out recently.
My mother…
was apparently a famous master of pansori.
Turns out…
that I also had an early starting point.
I thought having a famous mother
like you would be amazing.
But now I see that's not necessarily true.
I felt so small
and…
miserable.
So…
about what I said to you the other day.
- I apolo...
- I don't need your apology.
I hate rehashing what has already passed.
So she's still an expert
at cutting people off, huh?
January 18 Jamyunggo audition
What was that?
Dang it, I'm going to be late.
Jeongnyeon!
Okgyeong!
I'm back after experiencing
the world outside.
How was it?
It's more fun to perform
in front of an audience than a camera.
I'm so thankful
that the director took me back in.
She probably had no other choice
than to take you back.
Sorry?
I'm just glad you're back.
But weren't you going somewhere?
Oh, my goodness!
I have no time to chitchat!
I'll be off then!
If it's too heavy,
put it down when nobody's looking.
I'll tell you if someone's coming.
I'm okay.
This isn't that hard since I'm with you.
Really?
Put them down.
These are the director's punishments
for you two.
Yoon Jeongnyeon.
Until auditions are over,
you'll be cleaning the rehearsal hall
and doing the dishes and the laundry.
Hong Jooran,
you'll be cleaning the toilets
and the dormitories.
And the director forbids you
from joining any training
until you finish these chores.
- Okay.
Good job.
- Sorry?
- You protected your friend until the end.
Good job.
Han strikes from up north
And Nakrang attacks from the east
Alas, how my land suffers
The north wind quakes our earth
And the east wind brings forth a storm
How could anyone say that all is well?
You have no energy in your voices.
Again.
Han strikes from up north
And Nakrang attacks…
Jooran, Jeongnyeon
- Hey, Jeongnyeon.
- Hey.
- Come, come.
- I'm so tired.
Did you just finish?
I'm fine with getting punished,
but I don't think I'll pass the audition.
Why do you say that?
I can't attend any training
because I'm cleaning all day.
Then you could just train by yourself.
You're just making excuses
because you think you'll mess up anyway.
What did you say?
With that kind of mindset,
you definitely won't pass the audition.
It'll save you time
not to audition at all.
You can't say anything
in front of that brat!
My goodness!
Wait.
Did she just get mad at me
for not doing my best?
Jamyunggo
I ride my steed
And shoot my arrow
- Who dares stand in my way?
Who is this Princess of Nakrang?
The enemy princess who protects…
The enemy princess…
Oh, my goodness!
Their treasure is guarded by a woman
How incompetent…
Oh, no. Move!
It's my calendar.
Jamyunggo audition
Jeongnyeon.
- What?
- Here.
You should eat.
You didn't even have dinner.
My goodness.
Thanks for looking out for me.
You're the best.
Do you still have a lot to do?
Yeah, after I finish
cleaning the bean sprouts,
I have to organize the prop room.
I need to finish everything tonight
so I can audition tomorrow morning.
- What about you?
- I just have some ironing left.
Let me help you with the prop room
after I'm done.
It's fine.
You have your audition tomorrow too.
You should focus on practicing
when you're done.
Then what about you?
I'll be fine.
If I stay up all night,
I'll make it to the audition.
So if I help you, you'll finish faster.
No, I told you to practice.
If you still come even after this,
I'll really be angry with you.
You got that?
I got it.
I don't even know where to start.
Let's do this.
My goodness,
this is going to take forever.
We will now begin
the audition for Jamyunggo.
We have the following judges.
The scriptwriter, Mr. Kwon Yeongseop,
the choreographer, Ms. Cho Suyeon,
and our drummer, Mr. Lee Yonggeun.
When we call your name,
you'll enter and begin your audition.
Yes, ma'am.
The audition!
What the… Why isn't this opening?
What?
Hello?
I'm stuck in here!
Is anyone out there?
Which role will you be auditioning for?
Gomigeol, ma'am.
You're auditioning for the antagonist
and not the lead?
Yes.
All right. Begin.
Youngseo's auditioning for Gomigeol.
She's auditioning for the antagonist
and not the lead?
She must be going for it
because she obviously won't get the lead.
And is it easy to get the antagonist?
They'll never pick her over Doaeng.
She's much more experienced.
Hodong and Mokryeon have promised to wed?
That won't do. That simply won't do.
Goguryeo and Nakrang
are to remain enemies.
They need to keep fighting
and wear each other down
for the great Han…
to strike both at the same time.
Things will be bad
if they form an alliance.
What should be done about this?
You are as pretty as ever.
If it wasn't for Mokryeon,
I would have you as my concubine.
Dear Precious.
Have you heard
that Mokryeon and Hodong are to be wed?
They are nothing but rumors.
You poor, pretty little thing.
Deliver this letter
to Princess Mokryeon in secret.
I desire to have Mokryeon,
and you desire to have Prince Hodong.
If you deliver this letter…
the two will never be able to wed.
As expected of a seasoned antagonist.
This was always your role, wasn't it?
Yes.
Is Jeongnyeon here?
Not yet.
She said she'd come
after cleaning the prop room.
What's taking her so long?
Did she fall asleep?
I think I'll have to go fetch her myself.
Next is Hong Jooran!
Oh, no.
Pilsun.
I'm sorry, but could you fetch Jeongnyeon
from the prop room?
I can't go myself right now.
I don't know when they'll call me in.
I can't go.
Oh, you're right.
Hong Jooran. Are you coming in or not?
Could you give me some time?
- I just need to go and fetch...
- You should go in.
I'll fetch Jeongnyeon.
- Thanks, Youngseo!
- Hurry up and come in!
Yes, sir.
There, that's it.
What now?
What the heck?
My blasted butt!
You there! Heo Youngseo!
Oh my, it's good to see you!
What are you doing there?
That's not important.
Pull me out.
Hey!
We have a door!
Why would you come out the window?
Why else? The door is locked!
Come on! Pull harder!
Your arms are so weak!
I'm out.
I'm out!
Get off!
You're crushing me!
Thank you so much, Youngseo!
You really saved me!
Hey, we don't have time for this!
The audition's about to end!
My goodness! The audition!
Oh, come on!
The last one…
Yoon Jeongnyeon.
Is Jeongnyeon here?
If she's not here,
then we'll end the auditions.
No, please. She's coming.
Please wait just a bit.
I'm here!
Jeongnyeon!
Come on.
I'm here for my audition.
Hurry up and come in.
Yoon Jeongnyeon.
Which role will you be auditioning for?
The soldier, ma'am.
The soldier?
You mean the soldier
who informs everyone of the war?
- Yes.
- And you're aware that it's a small role?
I'm aware.
All right then.
You may begin.
Let's start from the scene
with all the soldiers.
I'll read the other lines.
My goodness,
I guess we are going to bed starving
once more.
Provisions are running short,
so they are only able to give us
one meal a day.
I wonder how my parents are faring
back at home.
I am worried sick for them.
It is the same for me.
My son had just started walking
around the time I left home.
He probably cannot recall my face anymore.
How can anyone expect us
to fight in battle
when we are all absolutely starving?
Do the high and mighty nobles
at the capital
have any idea of our plight?
Watch what you say.
Someone might hear you.
Then let them hear.
I do not go to battle
for those in the palace.
I go to battle for my family
back in my hometown!
Let's move on to the next line.
General!
The soldiers of Goguryeo
are swarming in!
All right, that's enough.
You know you need to prepare for any role
no matter how small it may be, right?
Yes, of course.
You may go then.
How was it? Did you do well?
I don't know.
I did my best though.
Thanks for earlier.
You really saved me.
I didn't do it for...
For me, I know.
I know, okay?
But I still wanted to thank you.
So…
why did you help me?
I need to check something.
- Check what?
- Your acting in Chunhyangjeon.
I need to know whether that was
a stroke of luck or your skills.
So I need to see you acting again.
I don't get it.
Forget it.
So why couldn't you open
the prop room door?
I have no idea.
I think someone locked it
without knowing I was in there.
See? It's locked.
So that's when it was locked?
Was it on purpose
knowing Jeongnyeon would be in here?
Of course it was on purpose.
Really?
Hey, we need to keep this a secret, okay?
Keep what a secret?
Oh, my goodness!
You guys locked Jeongnyeon in
so she'd miss the audition, didn't you?
- No!
- It wasn't us!
We also just heard
that she was locked in here.
- Right! It really wasn't us this time!
- It wasn't us.
Then what were you talking about just now?
We were just…
I guess I have no choice.
Let's continue this conversation
with the director.
- No!
- You can't!
I'm telling you, it wasn't us this time.
It was actually…
You can't!
Who else knows about this?
Just me and those three.
All right. Thanks for telling me.
Now we need to decide
who will play Gomigeol.
I think Doaeng's take on Gomigeol
was very manly and charismatic.
I could see
why she's the go-to actor for antagonists.
I have no doubt
that Doaeng's acting is amazing.
But I think Youngseo's acting
was quite on par with hers.
It was a refreshing take on the role.
Gomigeol who's not just a bad guy,
but also a strategist.
What is your opinion, Mr. Kwon?
As you two have already mentioned,
each actor had
their own very different strengths.
Since we can't come to a conclusion,
I think the director will have to decide.
I will now announce
the results of the Jamyunggo auditions.
First, as our male lead, Prince Hodong,
Moon Okgyeong.
As Princess Mokryeon, Seo Hyerang.
Next is Gomigeol.
As Gomigeol…
Heo Youngseo.
But Doaeng has always played
the antagonist.
Some people even buy tickets
for all showings just to see Doaeng.
Would they still come
if they knew that Youngseo was Gomigeol?
Right.
As Precious,
Hong Jooran.
As Prince Hodong's friend…
What?
I didn't even know
you auditioned for Precious.
I didn't know I'd get the role either.
You're amazing.
As Soldier 1…
Yoon Jeongnyeon.
I did it!
My gosh!
As Soldier 2, Shin Woncheol.
- As Soldier 3, Woo Migeum.
- Yes.
As Soldier 4, Oh Pilsun.
All right.
We'll start our read-through
of the script tomorrow.
Come prepared.
Yes, ma'am!
This is amazing.
Remember what I told you
when you were being so stubborn
about becoming a gukgeuk actor?
That you and I
will no longer be aunt and niece
once you're in Maeran.
I know you had no choice.
Youngseo's singing is far above my level.
Do you think your talent
only lies in playing the antagonist?
It was normal for other girls
to only analyze their own roles
for a performance.
But even when you were a trainee,
you analyzed all the roles in the script.
You knew how to look
for the hidden messages
within each line and even the play itself.
You have the talent
to become a stage director.
Auntie.
If you're up for it,
help me direct Jamyunggo
as the assistant director.
You can start a new journey
to become a director.
General! The soldiers of Goryeo are...
No, Goguryeo.
The soldiers of Goguryeo are…
I keep having an accent.
The soldier isn't Bangja.
He's not supposed to have an accent.
By the way,
why did you audition
for a small role like the soldier?
With your skills,
you could have had a bigger role.
Youngseo told me last time
that the reason I played Bangja so well
was because she matched my performance.
And that kept bothering me.
So instead of going for the big roles,
I thought I'd go for a smaller one
and focus on learning
how others act instead.
I see your point.
There's a reason why the director
only lets trainees play extras.
Let's talk about you.
You said you'd audition
for an extra last time,
so how did you get the role of Precious?
Nobody even knew
that you auditioned for Precious.
You're the one
who actually made me go for it.
- Me?
- All this time,
I didn't think I'd be able to play
anything other than an extra.
Then you told me the other day
that I can't know until I actually try.
And I started wanting more
after seeing you play Bangja.
Well, I'm honored to hear
that I helped you.
I have a dream too.
A dream?
What is it?
I want us to stand on stage
face-to-face one day
with you as the male lead
and me as the female lead.
Just like Okgyeong and Hyerang right now?
Yeah.
I'd love to!
Wait a minute.
Then I'll have to work a bit harder
to achieve that.
It's a promise.
Here, pinky promise.
This again.
You really love stuff
like oaths and promises, don't you?
Come on.
Fine.
Jamyunggo is our troupe's
signature performance.
And we'll be raising the scale
for this rendition
by renewing everything from stage design,
costumes, props, and the like.
It'll be our best performance yet.
I'm expecting phenomenal acting from you
worthy of this monumental performance.
Yes, ma'am.
Doaeng will be
the assistant director of this show,
and she'll be helping me oversee
the entire stage directing.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's start from Bau's line.
The children are singing.
How merry.
This is all thanks to our great king.
Can you really say that all is well?
Han strikes from up north
And Nakrang attacks from the east
Alas, how my land suffers
The north wind quakes our earth
And the east wind brings forth a storm
How could anyone say that all is well?
My Prince.
Precious has returned.
Your Precious has returned
from her espionage mission.
Stop.
Precious had to come back
because she was fatally wounded.
She can't sound cheerful.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's move on to Gomigeol.
Dear Precious.
Gomigeol.
You are another country's chancellor.
What are you doing in our prince's hall?
My dear Precious,
you are as pretty as ever.
If it wasn't for Mokryeon,
I would have you as my concubine.
Dear Precious.
Have you heard
that Mokryeon and Hodong are to be wed?
They are nothing but rumors.
You poor, pretty little thing.
Deliver this letter
to Princess Mokryeon in secret.
I desire to have Mokryeon, and you…
desire to have Prince Hodong.
If you deliver this letter,
the two will never be able to wed.
Youngseo.
Are you going to keep that tone?
Uh… yes.
Is that so?
All right, next.
Next!
Nakrang soldier!
Jeongnyeon, what are you doing?
What? Oh, sorry!
General!
The soldiers of Goryeo are swarming in!
It's Goguryeo, not Goryeo!
How could you mess up such a simple line?
Quiet.
That's enough.
Enough!
You poor, pretty little thing.
Now, deliver this letter
to Princess Mokryeon in secret.
I need to be more intimidating.
Now,
deliver this letter
to Princess Mokryeon in secret.
What are you doing?
That's not your Gomigeol.
It's Doaeng's.
You did this at the read-through too.
It's not like you to mimic
someone else's acting.
What do you know?
Those who consider Doaeng's take
as the right Gomigeol…
may not want to see my version.
Don't you remember what you said to me
during Chunhyangjeon?
You gave me such a hard time
because I didn't have my own Bangja.
And now you're telling me
you're going to mimic
Doaeng's take on Gomigeol?
Worry about your own acting.
Who are you lecturing
when you can't even say a simple line?
You're right.
I've got my own problems.
Sorry for overstepping.
I'm just saying,
I'd like you to enjoy
playing your own Gomigeol.
Just wanted you to know that.
How in the world
am I supposed to enjoy it?
Okgyeong told me the same thing,
to enjoy it.
I guess it's possible for the two of you.
But I'm always so nervous before a show,
so how am I supposed to enjoy anything?
Sure.
Maybe you can enjoy everything
on stage or off stage.
But I'm different.
I have to prove myself
every time I'm on stage.
What in the world are you trying to prove?
That I'm worthy enough
to be Han Kijoo's daughter!
My mom has to acknowledge that!
So that's it.
That's your real weakness.
From what I see,
you're not able to focus on your acting.
You're too hung up on
getting approval from your mother.
Don't you dare assume things about me.
Actually,
a soldier is perfect
for your level of skill.
At least my soldier…
is my own take and interpretation.
It's mine!
Yoon Jeongnyeon's acting!
It's different
from your sad copy of an act.
You better wait.
Wait and see how I put you in your place.
You'll only be playing roles
like that soldier
as you stand behind me forever.
You're going to put me in my place?
Let's see who actually gets to do that.
Who knows?
Maybe one day…
I'll stand in front of you.
The Blooming Autumn Field
JEONGNYEON: THE STAR IS BORN
The basis of good acting is confidence.
I just need to show everyone
my own soldier.
What are you talking about?
Would you look at this punk?
I had my reasons for taking the soldier.
Get out of your head.
The audience is not here
to see you tonight.
Jeongnyeon is supposed to be
a simple soldier.
General…
…the soldiers of Goguryeo are…
Translated by Jin Yu