YUYA SHOZUI, 28
FORMER PROFESSIONAL BASEBALL PLAYER
HOZUMI HASEGAWA, 43
FORMER BOXING WORLD CHAMPION
YOSHIO ITOI, 43
FORMER PROFESSIONAL BASEBALL PLAYER
- We're back.
- Déjà vu.
- For sure.
- Totally.
- It's a little cold.
- It was warmer last time.
I wonder who's still in it.
It's exciting, you know?
- Yeah, seriously.
- So exciting.
This is gonna be intense, this battle.
- Right.
- There were a lot of tough competitors.
- True.
Oh! Who's this?
Hey there. Welcome.
- How are you doing? Been a while.
- Long time no see.
It really has been.
Looks like we've got
the soccer players and the ladies.
- Right!
- All soccer players.
Just the ladies and the soccer team.
- Totally.
- What?!
Who is this?
Look who it is.
- How's it going?
- Hey, everyone.
None of us know who's coming.
You didn't make it?
- The two of us left in a pretty sad way.
- Yeah, it was rough.
Really?
Honestly, it made sense.
You were eliminated?
- The studs!
- The elite squad.
- You were favored to win.
- That's insane.
- You were heavily favored.
- Look who it is.
- Well, well.
- Our team got beat.
- Our team lost. Yeah.
- Your whole team?
I wonder who's gonna win this thing.
Yeah, I don't know.
Attention.
We are about to begin the Red Stage.
- I'm nervous just watching.
- Who'll it be?
I'm feeling nervous.
Why are we the ones who are so anxious?
- Who is it?
- I can't wait to find out.
- Kenta.
- Yeah, or Itoi.
I really hope Kenta's in.
- There they are.
- They're here.
- Wait, who is it?
- No idea.
Look! Hozumi!
- Who else?
- It's Shozui!
- Shozui!
- Go, Shozui!
- Look, there's Itoi!
Itoi!
Let's go!!
Crazy!
- Really?!
- Amazing!
- Hey, Kurihara's not there, is he?
- Yeah, Kurihara's gone!
Come on.
Oh man.
- Takashi, what happened?
- He's injured.
- Nice.
- Great job!
Congrats.
Nice work!
- Thank you!
- Amazing job.
- Well done.
- Is that a sprain?
- What happened?
- A full sprain, yeah.
- Oh man, that's rough.
- It looks crazy, right?
This battle.
All of them are absolutely insane.
They overcame some crazy challenges.
For real.
Attention. Round one will now begin.
Each round is 30 minutes.
Whoever pushes the goal button first
will earn one point.
Each time a competitor earns a point,
their button will move
one meter further away.
If the match ends without a winner,
everyone's goal buttons
will move one meter closer.
The first competitor
to earn two points will win.
The winner will claim 27 million yen
in prize money.
At the sound of the buzzer,
begin Round 1.
One is a champion, the other superhuman.
Competing against these elite athletes
means that I must be
more determined than ever,
even if I die trying.
I wanna fight
in a way that I can be proud of
and hold my head high.
Of course I'm confident.
I wanna give it everything I've got.
- Amazing! Unbelievable!
- That was incredible.
That was brutal.
One point is awarded to Yoshio Itoi.
If he reaches the goal again,
he will be the winner.
Yeah, yeah. I could feel Itoi's power.
He's incredibly strong.
I thought I might be able to stabilize
if I could reach the holds.
But I couldn't…even get that far,
and it made me realize
how tough this challenge was going to be.
I could feel the difference
in strength between the three of us.
But there was no way
I would let it end like that.
I didn't experience closure as an athlete.
I want another chance
to achieve greatness.
When you were cut from the team…
WIFE: HONAMI
…you weren't sure
what you were going to do next.
I stayed in Sendai
instead of going back to Osaka.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And I joined a sales company.
That was such a challenging phase for us.
During that time, so many things happened
that worried you or put you on edge.
Sure, but I knew
that somehow it would all work out.
I know you so well, and I think
you're someone who works incredibly hard.
If you decide
that you're definitely going to win,
then I have no doubt that you will.
I have so much faith in you.
Do your best. Okay?
I'm definitely gonna win.
I'll reward your faith.
Oh!
I can't afford to lose
this competition to Itoi.
I need to defeat the superhuman.
I'm excited to be
in the same room as Itoi.
- Your swing is pretty good.
- Yeah, but I couldn't hit.
With that much potential, I think
you definitely could have gone pretty far.
Obviously, Itoi is a well-known athlete,
but I have to defeat him.
Shozui comes from
a baseball background, just like me.
But I'm a veteran player,
so a lot of pride is at stake.
I can't afford to lose to him.
From here on out,
it's all about endurance.
- This is where it starts.
- This is so insane.
We will now begin the second round.
One point has been awarded to Yoshio Itoi.
His goal button
has been moved to a new position
one meter further away.
Whoa, crazy. This is gonna be tough.
If Yoshio Itoi wins this round,
he will be the Final Draft champion
and claim 27 million yen in prize money.
At the sound of the buzzer, begin Round 2.
Come on.
Five minutes have passed.
Yoshio!
I was barely hanging on.
My right arm was saving my life.
- Shozui's too far off the ground.
- He's too upright.
He has to get lower.
- Itoi's making a move.
- He's locking his foot in.
Yeah, to save energy.
Ten minutes have passed.
The longer the battle goes on,
the more tired they'll get,
and I've got better stamina.
- Wow!
- A little more. Hook your foot!
- Wow! That's incredible!
- Itoi's unreal!
Nothing left to grab onto.
Getting to that button
is still a long way off.
Fifteen minutes have passed.
- Fifteen minutes?
- What?
It's become a standoff.
This is insanely difficult.
Don't give up. You can do this.
Just don't quit.
No!
Look at that! Shozui!
Come on! Let's go!
Man, this looks so hard.
Endurance. That's what it's about.
That's how Shozui wins.
Twenty minutes have passed.
That's crazy!
Ten minutes remaining.
Shozui!
Come on, come on, get up!
- Hang in there, you got this!
- Go, Shozui!
Oh no, this is bad.
Okay. Let's do this.
Let's go. You got this.
Here we go.
Keep going.
Just pull. Pull forward.
Keep pulling.
Pull forward.
Damn it.
Twenty-five minutes have passed.
Five minutes remaining.
Hang in there, Hozumi!
- Hozumi's holding up pretty well.
- Most people would be spent.
Hozumi's holding strong
with these guys pulling.
I thought they might be tired,
so I tried to pull, but I couldn't move.
I just couldn't move anymore.
It's so far.
There's so much ground to cover.
Thirty seconds remaining.
Damn it.
He's so strong.
Seriously.
Ten seconds remaining.
The second round is a draw.
At this time,
we will take a 30-minute break to rest.
What a battle.
This was the hardest by far.
I mean, the first day
up the mountain was tough, too,
but for me, this was way more challenging.
I never imagined it would last 30 minutes.
I'm not sure how,
but I managed to maintain my grip.
I wanted to reach it.
The button was close,
but still so far away.
There were a few times I almost gave up.
But Kurihara fought through worse.
Compared to what he went through,
this was nothing.
Ah, that hurts!
So painful.
- Oh man.
- That's incredible.
We will now begin Round 3.
Since no one reached their goals
in Round 2,
everyone's buttons were moved
one meter closer.
The only thing I'm thinking about
is winning.
- Shozui!
- Hang in there!
- Come on, Hozumi, let's go!
- Yeah, you got this, Hasegawa.
- Good luck, Itoi.
- You got this!
At the sound of the buzzer, begin Round 3.
Wow, Shozui!
- No way!
- So fast!
Shozui!
Yuya Shozui has now earned one point.
I kept my hope alive.
Yoshio Itoi or Yuya Shozui
will become the Final Draft champion
and claim 27 million yen
if they win again.
I can't run anymore.
We had a short break,
but afterwards
I felt like my legs were completely spent.
I might be reaching my limit.
I can't run.
I mean, he's young,
so I'm sure he recovers faster.
Come on, don't let this slip away.
It's victory or death.
I must win this.
Ready, up!
I see myself fighting for my teammates
who ultimately lost.
I fought my way here.
- Nice!
I'm not just competing for myself
but for all the other athletes here.
I'll do my best.
I'll win it all.
Thanks so much.
- Okay.
- Nice!
Nice, Shozui! I'm counting on you to win.
I have to give it
everything I've got and claim victory.
This is a great match.
I bet the match will go
a lot faster this time around.
It's incredibly tough.
It takes a toll,
both mentally and physically.
I think this is
where I have to push past my limits.
We will now begin the fourth round.
I'm definitely gonna win this.
One point has been awarded to Yuya Shozui.
As a result,
his goal button has been moved
one meter further away.
At the sound of the buzzer, begin Round 4.
- Amazing!
- Itoi!
- This is incredible!
- He was strong.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- Great job. Seriously.
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Great job.
The champion of Final Draft
is Yoshio Itoi.
Great job.
Thanks.
Look at everyone.
- Look, they're all here.
- What's this?
Wow.
- Congrats!
- Great work!
You killed it!
Yeah!
- That was amazing. Great work!
- That was amazing, man!
That was a real gift to watch.
- Incredible.
- Amazing. For real.
- Congratulations!
- That was just insane.
- Thank you.
- You gave it everything.
- I tried.
- Hozumi, you did a great job.
Ah, thanks so much.
- Great job. Thank you for that.
- I did my best.
- Oh man, I'm so sorry.
- Shozui.
Man, I felt for you.
Great fight. So moving.
You did great.
- That was amazing.
- Great job.
- Thank you.
- Hey, Shozui.
Nice work. That was so close!
- You were awesome.
- I came up short.
- Great work.
- Sorry.
- Let's go.
- That was so cool.
I'm so sorry.
Well, of course,
in the end, I couldn't win it,
but honestly, I have no regrets.
I still think it matters
whether you win or lose,
but this reminded me again
that what matters most
is accepting the challenge.
So I will continue to challenge myself
in all areas of my life.
Thank you all so much.
Uh,
I mean, I lost the first time
during the team battle,
and I tried to carry the hopes
of those who wouldn't return.
I truly wanted to win.
And I wanted to say to you all,
"This win was for you."
But… I came up short and couldn't win it.
Still, I gave it everything,
and I'm happy with that.
I'm grateful for this experience.
Thank you all.
Will the Final Draft champion,
Yoshio Itoi,
please open the box in front of him?
- The box?
- No way.
It's all in there?
Here I go.
Real money!
The Final Draft prize,
27 million yen, is yours.
This is insane.
Thank you.
I mean it.
I was able to meet some amazing athletes.
And, ever since I retired,
it's been rare to feel what I felt
when I competed with you all.
I don't think there are too many people
that can inspire others
with their physical abilities.
Everyone here is capable of doing that.
Seriously, I was so moved.
I got goosebumps
competing against you all.
So I am extremely grateful
to this competition,
because it reminded me
what it feels like to be an athlete.
Thank you all so much.
- Congrats!
- Such a great speech!
Shall we lift him?
Hold on. I'm heavy!
What?! You're saying
we're not strong enough?
What?
- Are you okay to be the base?
- I'll be fine!
Ready, lift!
So heavy!
I got to meet a bunch of athletes
from a lot of sports and other disciplines
that I wouldn't have met otherwise,
and I'm grateful for that.
You could hit a homer
with that branch, yeah?
Yeah, definitely.
The experience was invaluable.
Thanks to Final Draft,
I let go of some feelings
I'd held onto from my professional days,
frustration about not achieving my dreams.
Even though I couldn't claim victory,
I never imagined
I'd end up feeling so at peace.
So now
I can step away from sports
with no regrets.
Thank you so much.
At first, I really hated the crew,
and I hated the other athletes too.
I didn't wanna talk to them
and certainly didn't wanna live
under the same roof.
But in the end, we became friends.
And for that, I'm grateful.
I think one of the great things
about this competition
is how it gives the spotlight
to some less popular sports.
And maybe people saw those athletes
and thought, "I wanna try that."
So I hope this competition
reaches people all over the world.
You know that tension before a match
or that emotional high,
it was so great to experience that again.
In the end, I'm just so grateful.
I agreed to join this competition
for redemption after the Olympics.
And if I'm being honest,
I didn't quite achieve that.
But it really inspired me
to keep moving forward
with the work I'm doing right now.
Getting to compete against elite athletes
in this kind of competition
feels like a dream, even now.
You know,
I chose a totally new line of work,
but this reminded me how great sports are.
Yeah, I just had a ton of fun.
It was great.
Now that I've retired and become a mother,
it felt good
to return to a competitive environment
and be an athlete again.
My child might grow up and watch this
and think "Wow, Mom is amazing."
That would be so great.
I'd love that.
I told myself I wasn't gonna cry!
Athletes are incredible.
I realized just how pure-hearted
we truly are.
I gotta say,
I don't think I've ever formed
such strong bonds with people
so quickly in my life.
As fellow athletes,
they were irreplaceable.