New teachers!
Hey, hey.
You guys are being too dramatic.
Be quiet.
I know you're all excited and looking forward to it.
Because I, your Mr. He,
am going to attend a teaching seminar,
I won't be able to attend all the classes.
So, I've invited Mr. Zhao Xi to teach you
physics and chemistry with me.
And by the way,
the person next to him is your new history and geography teacher,
Lin Beiting, Mr Lin.
I'm telling you,
both of them are outstanding talents who have studied abroad
at universities which would blow your mind.
You must learn well from them.
Now, let's have the two teachers introduce themselves.
Hello everyone,
I'm Zhao Xi.
I'm your senior,
and I'm also from Tamsui.
I'm not your senior,
but I do like people from Tamsui.
I'm Lin Beiting.
Feel free to ask me any geography or history questions.
Okay.
Let's welcome these two teachers.
So for the next physics class,
I'll have Mr. Zhao Xi give you the lesson.
Don't give him a hard time.
Alright, I'll leave now.
Bye, see you.
Okay.
Today we'll learn a new law.
What is this law?
The Law of Conservation of Energy.
In English, it's called the Conservation of Energy,
and it's also known as Bernoulli's Principle.
Please sit down.
Thank you.
Bernoulli's Principle has many examples
in our daily lives.
Do you know
what the most common one is?
Airplanes.
Due to changes in airflow, different air pressures are created,
which causes the airflow to move.
Just like these two balls:
when we try to blow them apart,
they actually come together.
When the wind stops,
they separate
and return to their original positions.
This is called...
Bernoulli's Principle.
Okay.
Now you can try it.
I just don't like it.
Make it clear. What don't you like?
I don't like Bernoulli's Principle,
or Qi Jiahao.
He works too hard.
Just like now.
Who...
can help me?
It sucks.
Using this method to prevent me from taking the exam
sucks.
I'll never let you get your way, no matter what.
You're good at fighting, huh?
You're good at it.
Put it down!
Stop running!
[The On1y One]
[Episode 5, Closed: Everything Happened Because of the Wind]
May I come in?
You're late for the exam?
Where have you been?
Miss, I went to see a doctor.
What have you got?
I have a problem with my brain,
so I was fooled.
Miss, can I take the exam now?
Oh, hurry up and get in.
You're 12 minutes late.
The listening test is already finished.
Hurry up and write.
Although I missed the listening part,
I can refer to the questions.
The questions in the first section are standalone,
so there's nothing I can do for now.
For the second section,
the dialogues correspond to each other.
By finding the frequently occurring words,
I can grasp the main point of the dialogue
and understand the meaning.
This way, my chances
of guessing correctly will be much higher.
Then,
by using this to backtrack, I might
get some of the first section's questions right.
Time's up. Stop writing.
Pass the exam paper forward.
You might as well just choose C instead of choosing randomly.
Otherwise, what if you end up with no points at all?
Miss, do you teach English?
No, I teach geography.
Have you seen the answers for this exam?
No.
Alright, hurry up and pass the papers forward.
Hey, Sheng, Tian, there are seats over here.
Hurry up. There are seats.
I called Sheng and Tian over. Why did you come along?
Sheng,
what happened to you during the English exam this morning?
Yeah, I heard about it too.
You didn't hear the English listening section?
Yes.
Keep your voice down.
I don't want to hold a press conference here.
Someone messed with you!
Keep your voice down!
Anyway,
someone tricked me, saying that Ms. Jin was waiting for me at Joy.
When I got there, I found that Joy was closed
and the owner was nowhere to be found.
Then, as I turned around,
two hooligans blocked my way,
and we ended up fighting.
Did you beat them up?
Did you win the fight?
How is that possible?
Then how did you come back to take the exam?
I took the chance and ran away.
I ran really, really fast,
but still missed the English listening section.
Who holds a grudge against you anyway?
Should I ask my dad
if he can let you retake the listening test?
Will your dad agree?
I don't know.
Anyways, I think
we should let Big Mouth Xu know about this and have him handle it.
The person who did this has really gone too far,
don't you think?
Yes, yes, let's go find Dean Xu.
Sure, let's go together.
There's strength in numbers.
Let's go.
Sit down.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for not killing me.
What does that mean?
During the last exam,
I got scolded by him for fighting.
This time, when he asks why I was late
and we explain, he'll definitely find out about the fight.
I would definitely get scolded by him.
That's true. We don't have any evidence.
And we can't prove that those two hooligans
got into the school and started the fight.
Alright, then we won't go to my dad for now.
This is really strange. I thought about it.
Why would two hooligans from off-campus
be able to get into our school?
Who holds a grudge against you?
There's only one truth. I got it.
It must be Zhai Tao.
Oh, Zhai Tao.
Zhai Tao? Who?
Zhai Tao.
The trash who kicked Uncle Mute last time.
Oh.
What did those two hooligans look like?
I don't remember clearly.
Anyway,
they were both not very tall, about 1.7 meters.
Black hair.
I also forgot what clothes they were wearing.
I don't really remember
much else.
I'm not criticizing you.
You have face blindness
and can't remember their names.
How do you expect me, a little detective, to figure things out?
They were there to beat me up.
Should they introduce themselves?
I don't know their names.
That makes sense. You're so stupid.
Who usually protects you?
Are you feeling strong and confident now?
Who protects me usually?
Who?
My dad protects me.
Stop picking and eat.
I'm going to Joy.
What for?
To buy some water.
To buy some water?
Doesn't Tian use a kettle?
I don't know.
He didn't even take a bite.
Are you done picking?
Are you going to eat or not?
The knife for cutting the ribs must have been used to cut garlic today.
It smells like green onions and garlic.
I can't eat them.
It's really a miracle that you've made it this far.
How did you grow up?
Uncle Zhao.
Don't you have exams today?
What are you doing here in the afternoon?
Buying water.
Oh.
[Waterproof and Breathable Bandage]
Are there still people stealing things?
Of course.
It's dark and empty here at night,
so it's hard to guard against.
Uncle Mute and I have caught several.
Why are you buying band-aids?
How much?
Here.
Just take it.
I'll head out then.
Okay, get back to the exam.
I bought it while I was buying the water.
Are we going to pickle or stir-fry
the cucumbers later?
You're back, Wang.
Yes.
Take a rest. We're going to eat later.
Okay.
This one.
It's done.
Let me help you.
Don't help me. You can't even carry a bowl properly.
What are you doing here? Are you supervising me?
Are you afraid I'll make something awful?
Hello?
Hello.
Are you kidding me?
You only got two points on your Chinese composition?
How come you're as bad as the guy next door to me?
Wow, you're laughing at me.
I even went around asking for answers for you last time.
Wang.
Wait!
Don't come over.
The one in the kitchen is the one who will accompany you for the rest of your life.
As for me, I'll leave the nest after turning 18.
Otherwise, people will say I'm living off my parents.
Don't mess things up for me.
You little brat.
You know what?
The grading teacher actually wrote
that my essay was incoherent and misused idioms.
Please, that teacher has no taste.
So, do you want me to go next door
and borrow some guidance on writing lyrical essays for you?
No need.
Come on. I'm Shakespeare.
I don't need that.
Sheng, do you know that the two hooligans who beat you were caught?
Hey, Crab, I'll call you later.
What are you...
Hello, Sheng.
How did they get caught?
It was Xi.
They were causing a scene at the café,
so Xi and his team gave them a beating and sent them to the police station.
Also,
Joy has installed a new security camera,
so the incident with them beating you got exposed too.
What a coincidence!
They were out of luck.
Xi doesn't even know them.
I told him that they beat you this morning,
and he was shocked.
Hey, I'll send you another picture.
See?
This is called divine justice, the heavens are watching,
and justice prevails.
Take care of Wang.
No need.
Is Tian back?
I'll talk to you later.
Tian's here.
What?
The two hooligans who beat me today were caught.
Do you know?
Yes.
Gao Tianyang showed me the live stream.
Was it you?
What do you mean?
It was captured on the security camera.
Your shoes.
Impossible.
Impossible?
I was so far away.
Yes.
It was me.
Tian, you're back?
Yes!
Wash your hands and clean up.
We'll eat soon.
Okay.
This afternoon, I went to Joy to buy some water
and happened to see two security cameras.
The owner of Joy must have installed them
because he was concerned about thieves at night.
So, I downloaded the footage and sent it to Zhao Xi.
I figured that with so many people coming and going in the store,
there might be a chance to catch them.
But I didn't mention that you got beaten.
It was a coincidence
that those two hooligans were causing a scene.
Would you have told me
if I hadn't found out?
Do you just enjoy doing good deeds?
Would you have kept quiet if I hadn't asked?
I was just thinking
that you must have been very scared at that time,
really hoping someone could help you,
but there was no one.
There was no one there
but yourself,
two hooligans out of nowhere,
and the fear of not knowing whether you could win.
If I were you,
I would probably have been panicking too.
I didn't know about it at the time, so I couldn't help you...
but I didn't want to do nothing at all.
Better late than never.
It's not a big deal. Don't worry.
What?
Well,
I twisted my leg
while fighting this morning.
Carry me upstairs.
Go upstairs.
Don't let my dad or your mom see.
Why are you going upstairs? It's time to eat!
We're here.
Thank you.
Aren't you getting down?
Well,
help me all the way
and take me to the door.
Open the door for me.
Thanks again.
You should skip dinner.
Why?
You need to lose weight.
I take back my thanks.
Hey, wait a minute.
Give me your hand.
Don't get too emotional.
You gave this to me this morning.
There's one piece left.
Does it hurt?
I can be pretty careless.
If it does hurt, let me know.
Okay.
Thank you.
Oh, right.
Did you beat them up for me today?
No.
When they tried to run away, they happened to pass right in front of me,
so I just blocked them a little.
Well, he hit me 6 times today.
Did you block him 6 times?
Definitely more than 6 times.
You two can come down for dinner now!
I'm not eating today.
I'm on a diet.
This guy
must have gone back to bed for a nap.
I'll send the samples to you as soon as I get them tomorrow.
Yes.
Okay.
Everything was made as we discussed before.
Don't worry.
Okay, bye.
Time to eat.
Okay.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Morning, Wang.
Morning.
Come on.
Sit here.
You're finally willing to come down to eat.
Wang,
didn't you say you want to eat Shaomai?
I specifically learned how to make Shaomai online.
Have a try.
If you like it, I'll make it for you again in the future.
Oh.
Where is Jiang Tian?
Oh, he went to the Little White House.
Oh.
Aren't you two going to the English competition today?
Yes.
It's this afternoon.
I'll go later.
Good luck.
Eat more.
Yeah, I don't know what's wrong.
It just isn't cooling anymore.
There's no problem.
There's no problem?
But why isn't it cooling?
Did you accidentally adjust the temperature?
I didn't adjust the temperature.
But sometimes the engine makes this noise,
then it stops for a bit,
and then it makes the same noise again. It sounds weird.
Alright, I've adjusted it back.
It's fine now?
It will gradually get cold.
Let me know if there are any more problems.
Okay.
I'm leaving then.
Hey, wait.
Where are you going in such a hurry? You haven't eaten yet.
I have an English competition this afternoon.
I have an appointment with someone to take the subway together.
You have an appointment with someone?
Yes.
Who?
The person who freeloaded last time.
Wang?
Yes.
How could you say he was a freeloader?
He's so well-behaved,
polite, and not cold like you.
He hasn't come here to eat for a while.
Does he not like my cooking?
No, he actually thinks the school's food is worse than yours.
So, does that mean
he likes my cooking?
Then why didn't he come today?
Did you invite him?
I...
I didn't invite him. But you didn't invite him either?
How did you make friends with him?
Give me your phone.
What are you doing?
Give it to me. Hurry up. No more nonsense.
Wang. Wang.
Wang.
Wang,
Jiang Tian asked you to come over for lunch.
Okay. Hurry up.
Alright.
I'll go cook now.
By the way, there's a bit of a leak in the toilet.
Could you take a look?
What happened to your hand?
It's just a scratch.
I'll take care of it.
Hey, Wang, come.
Let's eat.
Hurry up and eat.
Where is Jiang Tian?
My house is old.
The toilet and the pipes are leaking.
I asked him to check it out for me.
Oh.
Eat up.
So, he invited me over today
just for lunch,
or can I come here to eat in the future as well?
Actually, it was my invitation.
Oh.
Well...
Today's...
You first.
Well...
Did Tian get into a fight?
I noticed he had a band-aid
on his hand today.
He said it was just a minor scratch by accident.
Even if I ask him,
he won't tell me the truth.
So, did you invite me over today
just to ask about this?
Honestly,
I've never seen Tian be this close
to anyone before,
including me.
He's always been reluctant to interact with others,
so,
he's very cautious
and doesn't want to hurt anyone.
Maybe because he's been hurt himself,
he particularly understands other people's wounds
and needs.
You know,
he's like a martial arts master in those martial arts films—
if someone gets within three feet of him,
they'd be knocked away by his protective aura.
He's been on his own since he was young.
His grandmother and parents have ignored him,
so he isolated himself from them.
No one can see
what's going on in his mind.
He doesn't let anyone get close,
so,
no one can enter his inner world.
You're
the first friend I've seen him
bring over here.
So, I want to ask you
for a favor:
don't let him push you away.
I hope you can get closer to him, okay?
[Qi Jiahao]
How to buy this?
There are so many stations; where do I need to go from and to?
Use this.
I guess you don't have an EasyCard, right?
Here.
Oh.
How much do I own you?
It's okay.
As long as you do well in the English competition.
Even if you don't come in first,
at least aim for the top five.
Okay, I'll keep it with me during the exam
and carry it with me usually,
like an amulet. Okay?
Can you be more dramatic?
[Wang]
Let's go.
Okay.
Everyone, remember what I said:
aim for victory from stability and score from risks.
Write down what you know first
to secure your base score.
For what you don't know…
Why are you two so late?
I'll say it again.
You two listen carefully.
Write down what you know first to secure your base score,
and leave what you don't know until the end.
If you have time, make sure to attempt them as well.
Check your answers several times
and don't hand the paper in early.
I've emphasized this many times already.
Don't hand the paper in early.
The exam is about to start.
Get ready to go in.
I'll help you both check in.
Thank you.
Hey, I just called you.
Why didn't you answer?
Oh, sorry about that.
What's wrong?
No. It's just that Ms. Jin asked me to tell you
that it's okay if you didn't do well on this week's test.
Focus on doing your best in this competition.
After the exam, she'll talk to you tomorrow.
But didn't Ms. Jin say to tell him this after the exam?
You're affecting him right now.
It's okay.
I heard you.
It's about time to go in. Let's go.
Hey, wait a minute.
This time I won't sit behind you.
If you run out of pen refills during the exam,
I won't be able to help you.
I brought pencil leads with me.
Take it.
Oh.
What Qi Jiahao did earlier
was to discourage you because you're highly capable.
So, do your best in the exam.
Have faith in yourself.
Do you believe in yourself?
What about you?
Do you believe in me?
Don't let him push you away.
I hope you can get closer to him, okay?
Just like these two balls:
when we try to blow them apart,
changes in airflow
create different air pressures, which causes the airflow to move,
and they actually come together.
Run.
Aren't you good at running?
Keep running.
Playing cool, huh?
Didn't I tell you not to hand in the paper early
and to check your answers several times?
How many times have I told you?
We tried our best.
Miss, we were wrong.
You should admit that you were wrong.
Do you know your score on this week's test?
91,
which is 9 points lower than last time.
In listening, which is your strong suit, you lost 7 points.
And your handwriting—
the grading teacher couldn't even read it.
That's another 2 points off.
I see.
You'd better.
You'd better remember what you said before,
that you would improve by 50 places.
Otherwise, Big Mouth Xu...
Dean Xu will kill you,
and you'll lose your spot as an Excellent Model Student.
Got it?
May I ask how the other students did?
Besides you two,
no one else scored above 90.
What should I do?
What?
Are you two feeling so proud of yourselves now?
After
the competition results come out,
I'll give you a good talking-to.
-May I come in?
-Get out.
Come in.
Oh.
Qi Jiahao.
Luckily, I didn't listen to the proctor and chose C for every question.
Otherwise, I would definitely have lost more than 7 points.
So, you want me to praise you for being good at guessing?
-Why are you so annoying when you talk?
-Hey!
Qi Jiahao, the little English teacher, messed up this time.
He only scored in the 80s.
Ms. Jing asked him to go to her office.
So,
even though your English score might be a bit dismal this time,
you've definitely made
the most progress.
Actually, my English score...
Gao Tianyang,
lend me your math textbook.
You didn't bring it?
Yes.
Sure, I can lend it to you.
But I'm going to charge you.
Since we're so familiar, I'll give you a discount.
Go on a date with me after school.
Forget it. Sheng.
Hey, alright.
I was just kidding. I'll lend it to you.
Let's go.
Gao Tianyang, you got the accommodation form?
Yes.
Sheng,
you asked me about accommodation before.
Give this form to me after you finish it.
Okay.
Did you get it?
You want to stay at school?
No.
I just casually asked the monitor for one earlier.
Tian,
this is yours.
After you finish the accommodation form,
make sure to give it to me by this Friday.
Remember.
Why are you laughing?
Stop it.
Why do you want to stay at school?
Well...
I just asked the monitor for it casually.
And at that time,
I wasn't familiar with you.
How about now?
Do you still want to stay at school?
No.
Now I'm already quite familiar with you,
right?
And you?
Do you still want to stay at school?
I think I will in the future.
Class begins. Go back to your seats.
Those who are sleeping, wake up.
Before we start, I'd like to announce
the results of the last Excellent Model Student vote.
The winner is Qi Jiahao.
Congratulations to Qi Jiahao.
This time, we're implementing a seating arrangement based on rankings.
So, you'll know your rankings when you see your seats.
I'll distribute the score reports now.
Here.
Sheng,
you've improved by over 50 points in total,
with top three rankings in physics and chemistry school-wide.
Your overall ranking has risen by 47 places.
47?
Unfortunately,
if you had listened to the English listening section,
your ranking could have risen by another 7 or 8 places.
What a pity.
Indeed.
All that effort seems to have been in vain.
Just like these two balls:
when we try to blow them apart,
changes in airflow
create different air pressures, which causes the airflow to move,
and they actually come together.
This is called...
It's not poisonous.
Haws help with digestion and prevent diarrhea.
I remember I told you
that when I was young, I was very afraid of the dark
and always slept with my mom.
Later, my mom got sick,
so I slept with my dad.
At that time, our house was very small,
but there was always someone by my side.
As the house got bigger,
it seemed like more people came into the house,
but I found myself alone.
Do you know why I hate Bernoulli's Principle?
Because it sounds like "effort in vain," and I hate that.
Effort
without results.
The same goes for trying be an Excellent Model Student.
And the same goes for wanting you to stay.
Do you know why I hate Qi Jiahao?
Because the harder one works,
the more pitiful one seems.
Everything
happened because of the wind.
Once the wind stops,
everything will return to normal.
[Jiang Tian's Very Moment]
[Your friend Wang Wang Xianbei has changed their profile picture and name]
A teenager's mind is like the weather in June.
When it's pouring rain and overcast,
it feels like the clouds will never clear.
But as soon as the rain stops,
everything brightens up immediately
with the sun shining brightly.