WELCOME TO SAMDAL-RI
You're all done now.
-What is this?
-Take a look.
Hey, Yong-pil!
I think I like you. What should I do?
That floral pattern buoy.
I think it belonged to the haenyeo leader.
On the day of her accident,
he ran out in the middle of work,
so he was disciplined for that.
He went to the Weather Service division,
and he's busy helping a photographer.
Gosh, that fool.
Why would he get himself
into trouble like that? Gosh.
I heard the photographer who was chosen is
also the daughter of the haenyeo leader.
Dad, what are you doing here?
You…
I begged and pleaded.
I told you I couldn't live without my son.
I begged you eight years ago.
So why did you come back?
Why did you come back?
Sir, I--
Dad, what are you talking about?
You promised me.
Why come back and cause
another rift between me and my son?
Why?
Hold on.
Dad, what are you talking about?
Please just leave.
Go back to the mainland!
Dad!
Does he need to lose his father as well
for you and your family to be happy?
Will you only be satisfied
once you take my son away from me too?
Hold on, Dad.
Dad, eight years ago…
did you beg Sam-dal to break up with me?
Is that true?
Hey. Is that why we broke up?
Not because he gave your mom a hard time,
but because he begged you to?
Is this true?
That's right.
It was me.
I begged and pleaded.
Why did you come back
and mess with his feelings again? Why?
Sam-dal.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
His mother died because of yours.
And yet, he still likes you.
Doesn't he seem pitiful to you
as he blindly cares
for the woman who killed his mother?
Why am I pitiful, Dad?
Why am I pitiful?
It's not Sam-dal or her mom
who's making me seem pitiful. It's you!
Will I have to cut ties with my son
for you to finally stop?
Dad, please.
-Don't do this.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-I'm sorry.
-Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do anything wrong,
so why are you crying?
Come with me.
-No.
-Come on!
Sam-dal, why…
Why didn't you tell me about this?
Why didn't you tell me my dad
had said something like that to you?
You should've at least told me.
Why did you keep it to yourself?
How could I…
possibly tell you that?
Because it's about us.
And he's my dad.
Exactly, he's your dad.
Your one and only dad.
I couldn't bear
to take your dad from you as well.
How could I do that?
Dad! No!
Dad!
Dad, what are you doing?
Come to your senses!
My head.
Goodness.
Dad…
Don't do this, Dad.
I can't live without you!
-Dad…
-God, I'm such a fool!
I am so foolish!
I knew full well you
and your father only have each other.
How could I tell you that
just for my sake?
You know I couldn't keep you by my side.
Still, why is this something
you have to deal with?
Isn't this what I have to deal with?
This is my problem.
This is about my dad and me.
Yong-pil…
I like you a lot.
I really do.
I went out with all kinds
of guys just to get over you.
But I never lasted long with them.
Do you know why?
Because they weren't you.
We'd walk or eat together,
but all I could think was…
"Why is the person in front of me…
not Yong-pil?"
"What am I doing here?"
Ever since I was born,
I've only leaned on you,
and my heart's only raced for you.
That 23-year-old Cho Sam-dal
is someone I can be only in front of you,
so how could I possibly like anyone else?
-Sam-dal, let's just--
-So I've decided.
I'm going to like only you.
Yeah.
But that's all.
For me, it'll just be…
a one-sided love.
How can you when I like you too?
I realized it again
after seeing your dad today.
I can never overcome him.
I have my mom, my dad, and my sisters.
But he's all you've got, Yong-pil.
I can't do it. I'm not that shameless.
So I'll just love you from afar.
Even if it means I'll be single forever,
I'd rather do that.
That's what I'll do.
Sam-dal.
I don't want that.
I don't want a one-sided love.
I did it for eight years.
I can't do it anymore.
I won't ask you
to overcome my dad either.
I know you and your mom aren't able to,
so leave that to me.
So,
please just wait where you are.
Don't think about anything,
and stop feeling guilty.
I won't make the same mistake
I made eight years ago.
So don't think about
being in a one-sided love either.
I'm not going to go through it again.
That damn one-sided love.
EPISODE 13
THAT DAMN ONE-SIDED LOVE
Hey.
Did you eat something?
Yes.
What's wrong with her?
Is that you, Sam-dal?
Wait.
She looked exhausted.
What is it?
I told you. I'm going to
deal with myself first.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
Do you still
like Yong-pil that much?
What?
You asked if you could like him.
You can.
Like him all you want.
Just follow your heart.
Don't let what his dad
or I think stop you.
You two can do whatever you want.
We've kept you apart for eight years,
but if you still like each other,
what else can you do?
Why hold yourselves back
when you're innocent?
You two didn't do anything wrong.
I'm the guilty one.
So just follow your heart.
What if I end up liking him too much?
I don't think I'd be able to
break up with him again.
What if we need to separate again?
What should I do then, Mom?
If that happens…
I don't know what
I'll do with myself, Mom.
I'm still a kid so I can't protect you!
Ha-yul…
You don't have to worry about such things.
So she's your daughter, not your niece.
It finally makes sense now.
I actually checked out
your social media since it seemed odd.
I didn't mean to deceive you.
It just kind of ended up that way.
I'd always thought
Ha-yul was mature for her age.
But I realized today she's definitely
just a kid who wants to protect her mom.
Right.
You must be fascinated and curious.
It's not common for a 29-year-old
to have a 9-year-old daughter.
to be a dolphin's dad either.
Right. That's true.
Come to think of it,
we were the same age
when you met Namchun and I had Ha-yul.
I was 21 too.
Right, since she's nine.
Yeah.
I moved to the mainland to pursue
my dreams right when I turned 20.
But my dreams changed when I was there.
She's my new dream.
What was your original goal
when you first moved?
To be a professional swimmer.
Seriously?
You must be good at it
since you're from Jeju.
Not all Jeju natives are good at swimming.
I may not look it, but I was accepted
to the Korea National Training Center.
-I was handpicked by my university too.
-Wow.
You gave up on a huge dream.
Doesn't that mean you were really good?
I didn't give up my dream. It changed.
You have more questions, right?
Well, I do.
But you don't have to answer
just because of my curiosity.
I'm a widow.
What?
Really?
I see.
You sound really silly right now.
What do you mean?
It's okay to be surprised.
It's weirder if you're not.
Right.
Thanks. You made the trip home
easier on us.
It wasn't a long trip anyway.
You should visit
our center with Ha-yul often.
We have many kid-friendly programs.
She'll have fun since she likes dolphins.
I bet.
But I have no idea
why she's suddenly so into dolphins.
Anyway, thanks. Bye.
Wait.
I felt this
after seeing you all day today.
Actually, I think I felt this
the first time we met.
You two make a great pair.
What?
At times, you're like friends or sisters.
And if you look, like mother and daughter.
Anyway, I always thought that
about you two.
I never thought
it was fascinating or uncommon.
Go on in. I'll see you later.
Good morning, Man-su.
Yong-pil's still asleep, right?
Come on, Gyeong-tae.
What?
You shouldn't barge in there this early.
You should respect his privacy.
Not if he's staying here.
-Come on, now.
-What?
Sam-dal might be sleeping in there too.
-Last time--
-Sam-dal?
Sam-dal…
-I said they needed our permission.
-Stop…
Hey, Yong-pil.
What? Where is he?
What?
Where did he go?
You're seasoning top shells?
But why are there two batches?
What?
That one doesn't have any cucumber.
Is this for Sang-tae again?
Don't give him any.
He'll throw it away like always.
Give it back.
Even if he does,
I'll keep giving him food.
I'll continue to do that,
so he takes all his anger out on me.
He's done that for the past 20 years
and he's still angry.
It'll never end.
-Give that to me. I'll take it in.
-No, let's go together.
Just give it to me. I'll take it in.
I don't think
you should see my dad right now.
Did he run into Sam-dal
yesterday by any chance?
Did something happen?
By the way, Mom.
I'm not going to run anymore.
So don't forget to take your medication,
and make sure
to get that checkup tomorrow.
You never listened no matter
how much I nagged you to stop diving.
But you stopped immediately
when your daughters told you to.
I'm a bit hurt.
It's not that. I can't dive
because they keep hiding my suit.
I should've thought of that.
By the way, Yong-pil…
I'm no longer afraid of your father
taking his anger out on me.
You're not alone.
I wonder what's suddenly gotten into you.
Don't worry about me,
and just hold on tight to Sam-dal.
Okay.
Just how much did he drink?
Why are you here?
To cut ties with your father?
No.
Then,
did you cut ties with Sam-dal?
No.
Then, why are you here?
Get out.
Damn it.
Give it to me. I don't need…
Did you come here just to upset me?
Yes, that's right. I'm here to upset you.
I'm going to keep upsetting you.
Until we drift apart?
I'm going to keep upsetting you
so that I can take care of you.
I'm also going to take care of Sam-dal,
and Ms. Ko,
and myself.
What did you say?
You know what?
I thought if I was the only one
who suffered, everyone would be okay.
I thought you, Sam-dal,
Ms. Ko, and I would all be okay.
But no one's okay right now.
So from this moment on,
I'm going to tell you all of my pain.
I'll tell you how much pain I'm in,
how much I've endured,
and how much I love Sam-dal.
I'm going to tell you everything.
You think…
that's going to help me?
Yes.
Dad, I know
ever since the day Mom died,
you've never been able to move on.
Your one and only son
and Ms. Ko,
who worries about you every day.
You need to know how much we're suffering
so that you can move on too.
Right?
Sam-dal,
it's not the end of the world.
JEJU ATMOSPHERIC PHENOMENA
Hey, Eun-bi. Let's go to work.
When is Ms. Ko going to start
diving again? We gave her a new suit.
She said that one disappeared too.
-What?
-Again?
Goodness. Her daughters
must be dead set on not letting her dive.
Hiding her diving suit is nothing.
If she finds out that Jin-dal
is involved in the theme park project,
she'll kill her on the spot.
I see.
By the way, what was
the result of the votes on that?
Did anyone vote "Yes"?
Are you crazy?
I'm sure everyone voted "No."
No one from this town would support that.
-Right.
There could be some who did.
-What?
-Don't you think so?
Did you vote "Yes" or "No"?
I voted "No"!
-You voted "Yes," right?
-Damn it. You're so annoying!
You did, didn't you?
AS OUT! NO THEME PARK!
FROM RESIDENTS OF SAMDAL-RI
PROTECT THE BLUE SEA
SAY NO
AS OUT! NO THEME PARK!
THE THEME PARK WILL SAVE
THE LOCAL ECONOMY!
ALL RESIDENTS OF SAMDAL-RI
WELCOME THE THEME PARK
What is this?
This is bad!
We're in big trouble!
What is it?
The voting results are out.
What's the result?
"Yes" won by five votes.
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
You see, Ms. Ko, 66 people voted "Yes."
They voted "Yes"?
So by five votes,
the majority really voted for "Yes"?
That's right.
What about you? Did you vote "Yes"?
-No!
-Gosh, we voted "No"!
No one here would vote "Yes."
Goodness, we all listened
to you and voted "No."
-Right.
However…
apparently you voted "Yes."
-What?
What are you talking about?
I never voted "Yes"!
You, your husband, and Jin-dal.
In any case, six people
from your family voted "Yes."
-My goodness.
-Oh, dear.
That's 57, 58, 59, 60.
And six from you.
That's 66 votes for "Yes."
Are you sure about this?
Mom will be livid if she finds out
that you were behind this.
She'd beat us to a pulp
if she saw us just sitting here.
This isn't anonymous,
so she'll soon find out about this.
I don't get why this was an open ballot.
It should've been anonymous.
Mom is abusing her authority.
It's to catch people like you.
Hey, whose side are you on?
Aunt Jin-dal?
If they build the theme park,
Grandma really won't have to dive, right?
Yeah, that's what they said.
But you promised not to worry about that.
Don't get ahead of yourself, Mom.
I'm just concerned about Grandma.
Fine, but you should leave it at that.
What's going on?
You don't need to know.
Did Dae-yeong really bring this project
to our village because of Mom?
But why?
Don't tell me it's love.
If he still loves you after what you did
to him, he must be a bit--
Hey, watch what you say.
He used to be family.
He's older than you too.
Don't you dare call him an idiot.
I never said he was an idiot.
You didn't?
Cho Jin-dal!
That little…
-You crazy brat!
-Mom.
-You've gone insane.
Are you trying to ruin your hometown?
-Mom, let's talk.
-Why are you sitting here?
-Calm down!
-Stop hitting me!
Please calm down!
Hear me out, Mom.
Move, will you?
Get over here, Jin-dal.
-Let's talk it out.
-Move!
Mother, please!
It…
It hurts, Mother!
It hurts!
Look, don't just blindly be against it.
Mom, hear me out.
The majority of the people voted "Yes."
I may have lied and voted "Yes"
under your name and Dad's name.
But even if I hadn't,
there'd still be more "Yes" votes.
She's right.
We didn't know so many would vote "Yes."
-We really didn't.
-They all just didn't tell you…
they would.
Right.
What did you say?
I don't care what other people did.
But how could you vote "Yes"?
AS Group?
Everyone here knows
about your history with them.
Are you out of your mind?
Then, stop diving!
Your heart…
They said you shouldn't dive.
Do you think I…
AS Group…
I'm the one who hates them the most!
Just the thought of them
sends chills down my spine!
But if I didn't do this,
you'd continue to dive.
And that's what I hate even more!
She's right. You really need to stop.
Don't do it.
What about you then?
Did you ever ask for my permission
to do things in your lives?
You. Did you receive
my permission to get divorced?
And you…
So don't tell me
what I should or shouldn't do.
I've been diving for decades.
I've done fine with medication.
So don't suddenly start worrying about me.
The only way that theme park
will be built in our village is
if it's over my dead body. Got that?
Yes, my child?
I'm scared, Grandma.
Goodness.
I'm sorry for raising my voice.
It's not that.
Just like it took your old friend,
I'm scared the sea will take you away too.
A photo exhibition for an office
of meteorology wouldn't be your specialty.
I have no specialty.
And I'll be using my real name,
Cho Sam-dal, not Cho Eun-hye.
Even though the office of meteorology
is hosting it, I still need a theme.
Can you find and send me
material on exhibition themes
and on-site photos taken
from my previous exhibitions?
Okay, will do.
We'll fly down as soon as we send them.
We'll be there soon!
CHO EUN-HYE'S EXHIBITION MATERIAL
3MOON
Ms. Cho used to only do
large-scale exhibitions like these.
It doesn't matter.
At least she's still taking photos.
Do you know how worried I was
that she'd quit forever?
Let's send these over quick
and go help her.
Okay.
Wait, aren't these messages
from her visitors?
They're from that message tree.
Yeah, you're right.
Should we send these over too?
We even have the guest book too.
Why don't we pick out the good ones
from these and send them to her?
Okay, sure.
I heard you lied
about what happened to you.
I heard you denied it yourself!
Why won't you tell me?
Why did you try to jump into the river
if it wasn't because of Eun-hye?
You too?
I'm so irritated and my pride is hurt.
I'm about to go insane.
So stop it.
How could you lie about that?
She's completely--
Like you're any better?
You betrayed her first
and came to me. We're accomplices.
Don't try to change the subject.
Why did you try to kill yourself?
I just did it
because I wanted to die! Happy?
Hey, Sam-dal!
What? What brings you here?
By the way,
I heard you're dating Yong-pil again.
What? Who told you that?
Who do you think?
Man-su said he saw you two together.
-At our hideout.
-Man-su…
Did you think it through
before deciding this?
We'd have to cut ties again
if you two break up.
Gyeong-tae, please…
I don't have to but really want to
cut ties because of that mouth of yours.
Why?
Gyeong-tae, you're so…
clueless.
Me?
You have no manners either.
Was that déjà vu?
Did you do this
to Yong-pil for eight years?
While cluelessly mentioning me?
Is she psychic? How did she know that?
Hey, you better not break up
this time around.
You two better stay together!
FORECASTER CHO YONG-PIL
WEATHER SERVICE
You should've come in the afternoon
when Mr. Cho would be here.
That's why I told you
he took the morning off.
That's okay.
Here. I've yet to decide
on the interior theme.
But after looking through
the locations and photos,
I think I'll have
a rough idea of the theme soon.
Okay. It doesn't take long
to decorate the exhibition hall.
So take your time to decide
on the theme and let us know.
You might naturally decide on it
as you take and select the photos.
This is nice.
-Forecaster Cho!
-Yes?
If you look here, right now…
Cho Sam-dal stopped by just now.
I told her you'd be late,
but she came early.
So just us two had the meeting.
-Just now?
-Yes.
Really? I see.
-Mr. Cho.
-Yes?
Are you okay?
HEY, YONG-PIL!
I THINK I LIKE YOU. WHAT SHOULD I DO?
Hey, Sang-do!
We're closed today,
so this is all we have for snacks.
You can't drink when you're full anyway.
This is good.
This is perfect.
Try some.
Then, I'll eat it.
It makes me crave alcohol.
Why are you staring at me?
Fix your hair. You look exactly
like a crazy person right now.
You know those times
when you want to open up
your head and remove your brain?
So you can get rid of
thoughts filling it up.
In those times, you feel better
once you get some fresh air.
Who do you want to get rid of?
Who's filling up your head?
No one specifically.
Yong-pil?
Hey, why are you suddenly bringing him up?
By the way, are you guys
still not getting along these days?
Let's not talk about him.
Is it that bad?
No, it's just…
Let's not talk about Yong-pil.
Can you hear me out instead?
Sure, let's hear it. What is it?
There is
someone I've liked
for a very long time now.
Seriously? Who is she?
Hold on. If it's been that long…
No way.
Do I know her? Have you told her yet?
Want me to help?
Look, I'm old enough to need your help.
And you of all people
can't help me with this.
Come on. You don't have to be that cold.
But the thing is
she likes someone else.
Did you tell her you like her?
I've just thought,
"I'm sure I'll have my chance someday."
I waited for that day.
And I'm still waiting.
But you know what?
I think my chance might have come.
But I also think it might never come.
I don't really know.
If you think now's your chance,
then you should at least tell her.
What if it feels
like that chance will never come?
Then…
You should give up.
Give up… Is that so?
Then, should I just give up?
Yeah.
If it will never happen,
just give up, Sang-do.
That's one-sided love.
What about you?
Do you also give up if it can't happen?
No.
I'd rather have unrequited love.
But you shouldn't do that.
I'm speaking from experience.
Don't do it, Sang-do.
If you keep loving someone
even when there's no hope,
it's too painful.
So I hope you won't do that.
Damn it.
What?
What in the…
Don't throw that picture away, Dad.
If you keep throwing it away,
I'll keep bringing it back.
Okay?
Dad, I know ever since the day Mom died,
you've never been able to move on.
Mr. Cho.
We got a call about a crack
in a building. You should go see.
Is that so?
Where is it?
Samdal-ri Gallery.
What's the matter?
What? It's nothing.
Am I the only one available right now?
Yes, everyone else is dealing
with other complaints.
-Really?
-Yes.
SAMDAL-RI GALLERY
-Hello, Mr. Cho.
-Hey.
Where's the crack?
It's inside. You can go in.
Okay.
Where are you going?
There's a crack in the wall.
You're not going to check?
Where is it?
Over there. Can't you see it?
You saw them, right?
Mom and Ms. Ko back then.
I was still in her womb,
but you must've seen them.
What are you doing?
Can't you see? I'm trying to upset you.
What difference will this make?
Don't waste your time.
I know you loved Mom very much.
But…
she was my mom too.
She was also Ms. Ko's best friend.
And to Grandma and Grandpa,
she was their daughter.
So?
What are you trying to say?
I'm just saying…
that we were all in pain.
Is that why
you've all forgotten about her now?
I'm the only one…
I'm the only one who still remembers her.
You
and Ko Mi-ja
have both forgotten
about that day and that accident.
-Dad…
-That's why
at least I should remember.
If no one remembered her,
think how pitiful your mother would be.
JEJU HOSPITAL
I think everything will be fine
as long as I take my medication.
I've been doing fine all this time.
Mom, you think the accident happened
because you didn't take your meds?
You'll be okay for now
since we upped your dosage,
but it could change
if you develop a tolerance.
And we don't know
when we'll have to up the dosage next.
Here.
This is her medical chart
starting from eight years ago.
We upped her dosage
but not at regular intervals.
From when she first came here
to when we upped her dosage,
it was a period of one year.
Then, it was after two years.
Then, five months.
Inconsistent, isn't it?
I'm not a child.
I could've gone there by myself.
I don't get why your dad sent you as well.
Mom,
I saw the first time you visited
the hospital eight years ago
was on May 28th.
Was that when you collapsed the first time
and Yong-pil took you to the hospital?
You saw that?
Yes, it was.
Really?
It's exactly…
what you think it is.
Get out of my house!
Dad, please stop!
You listen up too!
I will never forgive her family!
If you want to see things like this
keep happening, go ahead.
Mom, what's wrong?
What's wrong, Mom?
Mom! Mom, what's wrong?
Mom, what's… Hold on!
Yong-pil didn't break up with you
because of his father's disapproval.
He broke up with you
because he saw that I was sick.
EXHIBITION THEME
WHAT SEASON IS YOUR STREAM IN?
PHOTO LOCATION
SAGYEMUL
Forecaster Cho.
Ms. Cho went to take photos today.
You didn't go with her?
No.
You two were always joined at the hip.
Where did she go today?
I think she said
she was going to Sagyemul.
I don't know
how she even found out about that place.
Sagyemul? Today?
Yes.
But it's high tide.
I'll be back.
Let's get to work.
Let's go.
OFF LIMITS DURING HIGH TIDE
DROWNING HAZARD DUE TO HIGH SURF
Forecaster Kang, you know
the highest tides start today, right?
The sea levels are the highest today.
Check flood-prone areas in advance.
Get ready to send out advisories
for strong winds and high waves.
The wave period is ten seconds.
These waves are so strong
they could flood the coast.
Really?
Yes. Look at this.
Goodness, a Weather Service member
can't just barge in here.
I just need to check something.
CHO SAM-DAL
Why isn't she picking up?
Baek-ho.
What are the numbers
for Sagyemul's wave buoy?
Hey, your punishment isn't over yet.
Okay, I'll get them for you.
Okay, thanks.
What?
Mi-ja!
Mi-ja?
Hey…
Hey, Geum-ok.
Oh, no.
Hey.
Geum-ok!
You saw how it ruined that other village,
and you still voted "Yes"?
Still, it's free money.
We won't be able to dive or farm anymore.
Isn't it hard to both dive
and run the business?
Do you even know
what you want to do with that money?
I have over 100 business ideas--
Oh, dear.
-Hey, isn't that Yong-pil's grandfather?
-What?
Hey.
-Mr. Bu.
-What's wrong?
-Geum-ok's disappeared!
-What?
Geum-ok!
Goodness, Ok went missing again?
-Where could she be?
-Let's go!
Mr. Bu, wait for us!
Mother!
Mother.
Ms. Yang!
Geum-ok!
Gosh, where could she be?
-Ms. Yang!
Ms. Yang!
-Did you check their house?
-She's not there.
-Ms. Yang!
-Goodness, Ms. Ko!
What's the matter?
Goodness, Ms. Yang has gone missing again.
She'd been doing well for a while,
so why did this happen again?
The rest area.
Did you check there?
Of course, we looked everywhere.
-Ms. Yang!
Ms. Yang!
Oh, God.
Goodness!
Gosh, what are you doing here?
Let's go.
Tell me. Are you hurt?
Mi-ja?
Where have you been, my sweet daughter?
You're the one who killed my daughter.
You're the bitch who killed my daughter!
You evil bitch!
You vile bitch! You deserve to die!
Die! You should die!
Why did my daughter have to die?
Die!
You deserve to die!
Why did my daughter have to die?
You should die!
You're the one who deserves to die!
Die! Why did my daughter have to die?
-Gosh, Ms. Yang!
-Ms. Yang!
Ms. Yang!
Goodness!
-Goodness!
-Goodness, ma'am!
Sang-tae.
Just me…
Just direct your hate only towards me.
I'll take all of it.
I'll take it until you let
all of your anger out.
I'll do it even if your anger
never goes away.
I'll still take it.
So…
couldn't you give…
your blessing to Yong-pil and Sam-dal?
Just hate me instead.
If Mi-ja
knew Yong-pil was suffering,
wouldn't she be heartbroken?
Ko Mi-ja!
How…
How dare you utter her name?
How dare you?
How dare you say it?
How dare you? Get off me!
How dare you?
Mr. Cho!
How dare you!
You're not the only one.
You think you're the only one in pain
and the only one who's grieving her?
What did you say?
I'm in just as much pain as you are.
And I miss her just as much as you do.
I do too!
I miss Mi-ja too!
You're not the only one who's grieving.
I miss her too…
I lost a friend too.
You're not the only one who's in pain!
Mi-ja!
Ko Mi-ja!
I also…
I also miss my friend.
I miss my dear Mi-ja too!
WARNING: HIGH TIDE
DROWNING HAZARD
CHO SAM-DAL
PHONE
CHO YONG-PIL 18 MISSED CALLS
Ms. Cho, here are the on-site photos
of the exhibition you asked for.
We covered all the exhibitions
starting from six years ago.
This sure is a lot.
It was indeed Cho's exhibition.
It was full of grace.
It was a very memorable exhibition.
It was the best exhibition
I've been to in a while.
I applaud her perfect composition.
Please do this more often.
I'll be waiting.
LOVE BUT DO IT IN SILENCE
I'm so sick of this.
Are you having fun?
Why are you reading
that poetry book with so much focus?
What's the story about?
There's no story to a poem.
There are only emotions.
What are you talking about?
All right. Tell me about these emotions.
-So it's like this.
-Okay.
Love that develops after a breakup.
They had no choice
but to break up with their love.
-Okay.
-And this is how they feel.
-They hurt.
-Okay.
-Their heart is torn to pieces.
-They cry.
-Okay.
All they can do is cry.
They wrote this poem with their tears.
What? That's just unrequited love.
Why would they break up
if they love each other? It's ridiculous.
Are they Romeo and Juliet or something?
How can you lack such emotion?
It's Christmas.
You're supposed to read poetry
with your heart and emotions. Okay?
Just go and read your textbook.
I'm so bored though.
Just read me something.
-You're just going to fall asleep.
-No, I won't.
-You always do.
-I won't.
I won't fall asleep.
I'll try to open my heart and listen.
-You won't fall asleep?
-No.
"Love
But Do It In Silence."
2016 FIRST EXHIBITION OF CHO EUN-HYE
Hello, Ms. Cho.
"Afraid that even the shortest encounter
would be a disturbance to you…"
"After leaving, how far apart are we now?"
"However far away, wherever you may be,
I know it hurts,
but without anyone knowing,
love in silence."
LOVE BUT DO IT IN SILENCE
"Just like a sharp blade
that becomes dull over time,
just until that pain
starts to dull,
let me love alone."
PARIS MAGAZINE WORLD TOUR
FIRST PHOTOGRAPHER OF 2023, CHO EUN-HYE
LOVE BUT DO IT IN SILENCE
Someone wrote this in the guest book
for the Paris Magazine Gallery.
CHO YONG-PIL
Cho Sam-dal!
Let's get out of here right now.
WELCOME TO SAMDAL-RI
Yong-pil…
I don't want a one-sided love.
Let's just be in love, okay?
I don't have even the slightest opening
to get in between them.
What more do you want?
Every night for ten years,
my wife cried by herself under a blanket!
I said how against it I was…
do you have to keep seeing her?
Bu Mi-ja is the woman
you'll forever love and remember.
And for me, that's Sam-dal.
Even if your dad
never gives us his blessing,
let's always hold onto
each other even if it hurts.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim