WELCOME TO SAMDAL-RI
There's an uninvited guest
that visits Jeju every April.
As if it's jealous of the upcoming spring,
the bracken rain falls.
This uninvited guest visits us
every spring without fail.
And it never comes alone.
EPISODE 8
THE BRACKEN RAIN OF JEJU
Hello.
Are you guys
back together?
Come on, Dad.
Why would you ask such a thing?
It's not like that, sir.
I'm sorry… I mean…
Have a nice day.
Where have you been all…
What?
What is it?
-Did you just--
-Mom.
Was the Jeju Olle Trail always this hard?
I thought walking
would relieve the soreness,
but it just didn't work.
My body hurts so much.
Maybe I'll just take a nap.
Want some food?
No, I'm good.
Why are you drinking
with just pickled seafood? It's so salty.
Are you showing off how you're a widower?
And turn on the lights
when you drink. It's so dark in here.
The top shells are seasoned well.
They're great when steamed.
They're not salty either.
They're perfect with alcohol. Have some.
Here.
It has cucumbers.
You know I don't eat cucumbers.
Did you have to put them in?
You can't make this dish
without cucumbers.
Just pick them out then.
You don't like ginger,
so I leave it out when I cook.
You don't like ginger either.
Right.
All right, just go.
I wanted to drink alone,
but you've ruined the mood.
Forget it.
I'll mix it with some rice
and eat it myself.
By the way, Dad…
Do you still
resent her?
Yes.
EIGHT YEARS AGO
Dad!
Please don't do this!
Open the door, Dad!
Dad…
Dad!
Open the door!
Please…
Please, don't do this!
Is Mom sick?
You startled me.
Why are you so jumpy?
What is it?
What do you want?
Is Mom sick?
Your mom?
Why would she be sick?
I mean, you were taking
water to her in her room.
She could get it herself.
I can't even get your mom some water?
Here you go.
They almost found out.
I said "almost."
I think we should tell them.
They have the right to know.
Gosh, save it.
They're only going to make
a big fuss about it.
It's not a life-or-death situation.
What are you talking about?
It is a life-or-death situation!
Here. This. Your heart.
They said it could be a ticking bomb.
Don't you make the situation worse either.
If I die, I die.
It doesn't scare me.
-Ko Mi-ja!
-Goodness.
How could you say such a thing?
For goodness' sake.
Damn it.
Gosh.
Sam-dal ran into Yong-pil's dad earlier.
What?
What happened?
Did he say something to her?
No, it's not like our kids
are dating anymore.
Did he yell at her about the two of them
going to the mainland together?
Is Sam-dal in her room?
No, don't.
I don't think she'll talk about it.
I feared this would happen.
We should've just moved
had we known Sam-dal would return.
That's what I suggested back then.
Why are you still worried about Sang-tae?
Here's our next story.
AS Group's market value has fallen
out of the top 20
for the first time in four years.
In 2019, the conglomerate family
was accused of abuse of power.
CEO Jeon Gwang-ok's wife and eldest son
were also accused
of providing illegal political funds.
Since then, they've been in plummeting…
Well…
Have you been well?
They've reported
continuous losses in profits.
And now, they're experiencing
their worst crisis yet.
The market--
Damn it.
-Ha-yul.
-Yes?
Yesterday…
Well…
So…
About yesterday…
What about yesterday?
I mean…
Why did you call me "Aunt"?
-No reason.
-That doesn't make any sense.
Did you…
not like it when that strange man
helped me?
Is that why?
No.
Then, why did you do it?
I just wished that you were
my aunt at that moment.
That makes no sense.
I don't like it.
Why did you want me
to be your aunt? I'm your mom.
She's your aunt.
Mom, does it really matter?
Can't you see that I'm reading?
I know, but…
What was that about?
What?
For crying out loud!
Be careful, will you?
She even knows what
the curse of the nines is.
It's not like I was on a date with him.
He just saved me from falling.
-What does he do for a living?
-How should I know?
Wait. I do know.
Well…
Something about dolphins…
I don't know.
He said he's a dolphin's dad.
A dolphin's dad?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
Ha-yul might feign ignorance,
but she remembers everything.
Don't you remember?
I think you were ten.
Dad once invited his old classmate
over to our house.
You started crying as soon as you saw her.
You kept asking who she was,
so she couldn't set foot in our house.
She had to leave.
I only did that because Dad
brought home a strange woman.
I was just a kid.
Exactly.
Ha-yul may seem mature,
but she's still just a kid.
Jeez.
Be careful.
I'm in no position to lecture others.
"A newborn dolphin
breathes for the first time above water.
The mother dolphin lifts the baby up."
Ha-yul.
Are you going to bed?
Yes, I am.
Then, I'm going to bed too.
Here you go.
Ha-yul.
Get me some hangover tonic.
Oh, God.
You're unbelievable!
Did you drink alone again last night?
Show some respect to your older sister.
Ha-yul.
I'm really nauseous.
Get me some hangover tonic.
God, what a drunk lunatic. Jeez!
I really might vomit.
I'm dying here.
You know what?
Seeing how Yong-pil and Sam-dal
got back together
as soon as they reunited,
they must've pined
for each other so much while apart.
I mean, Yong-pil hasn't dated anyone
since he broke up with Sam-dal, right?
So he never went on those blind dates
his father set up for him
because of Sam-dal.
Goodness, I feel so bad for him.
Gosh, that's enough. Ms. Ko
will give you an earful if she hears you.
She's right.
Ms. Ko said they weren't dating.
That's not true.
They went to the mainland together,
so it's a done deal.
It's not like they're going to
be friends again.
I went too.
To the mainland.
So the three of you went together?
-Yes.
-Jeez. I told you.
The three just went on a trip.
What…
Sang-do.
Why would you tag along with them?
You should've given them privacy.
You're unbelievable.
You're so dense.
Yong-pil hasn't been able
to get over Sam-dal.
You should've given them some space.
Don't you know anything about romance?
Why are you getting upset?
Mom, why were you zoning out?
You'll get into an accident.
Where are you going?
Me?
To give you this.
Forget it. I said I didn't want it.
Mom, I ate those top shells you gave me.
I added some cucumbers and onions
and ate them with rice too.
You did?
Of course. I know you caught them
just for me, so I ate them all.
What about your dad? Did he have some too?
I thought they were for me.
So I ate all of them myself.
All of them? I gave you so much.
Yes, every single one of them.
All right. Good.
Sam-dal is here.
She'll be here for a while,
so try not to run into her.
Don't tell my mom
that we went to Seoul together.
Mom.
Are you mad at me?
Did I do something wrong?
No.
You didn't do anything wrong.
All right, then.
I'll see you there.
Grandma! Grandpa!
Hey.
Speak of the devil. Yong-pil's here.
-Hello!
-Hey!
You're all here before Ms. Ko today.
-Yes.
-Of course.
Hey.
Did you guys fight or something?
Why was that greeting so awkward?
-We didn't fight.
-What's wrong?
We're too old to fight.
-Is that for Ms. Ko's buoy?
-Yes.
No one cares about her
more than you do. You're like her son.
What? Don't be her son, Yong-pil.
Be her son-in-law.
Jeez, there you go again.
-Ms. Ko is here!
-Goodness.
Hello, Ms. Ko!
Mom!
Ms. Ko!
-Goodness.
-Gosh.
What's gotten into Sang-do?
-What's with him?
-No idea.
My son has never carried my buoy,
but there he goes, carrying Ms. Ko's.
Sang-do is a true businessman now.
He knows exactly who he needs
to curry favor with.
You're right.
Ms. Ko might give him
a free octopus if he treats her well.
-And the Fisheries won't complain.
-Right.
Goodness, your buoy
is all covered in flowers again.
There's a reason
why Yong-pil is so persistent about this.
What?
He wants everything to come up roses
even when she's diving.
Cut the nonsense.
The area where we're diving today
is full of reefs,
so watch out for the current.
-Okay.
Let's go!
Okay, ladies.
Don't be greedy.
Only go as long
as your breath allows, okay?
You too, Mom!
Only go as long as your breath allows!
Good luck today, everyone!
Be safe!
-Be careful down there!
-Okay!
Hello, Director Han.
Gosh, your arm must be tired.
What are you doing there?
What? Were you watching me?
Mr. Han!
Hurry back here, you brat.
COAST OF SAMDAL-RI
What?
That little…
That knucklehead.
He doesn't want to go, so what can I do?
I've tried to persuade him for years now.
Come on. Try harder, will you?
By the way, why are you suddenly
interested in sending him to HQ?
You've always stayed out
of your son's affairs.
What?
You said HQ kept offering him a post.
As a government employee,
he should follow orders.
I see.
I'll keep trying to persuade him.
Hey, Forecaster Kang.
Bring me Yong-pil's appointment notice.
Again?
You should give up. He doesn't want to go.
He seems to love it here in Jeju.
Don't make me laugh.
When he first joined,
his goal was to go to Geneva, Switzerland.
The World Meteorological Organization?
That place…
only accepts one employee
from each country.
He had high aspirations.
Then, why doesn't he want to join HQ now?
Beats me. How should I know?
What's that?
To Cho Sam-dal,
who yearns to find herself.
A gift from her ex-boyfriend.
Hey, Sang-do!
Where are you headed?
-Do you want another bottle?
-What?
-You didn't waste a single drop.
-Right.
-Where are you headed?
-Well…
I was taking a walk.
-A walk?
-Yeah.
Then, I saw a young lady
chugging an entire bottle.
So I had to stop.
What? "Young lady"?
Let me join you on the walk.
I'm still sobering up, and I wanted
to walk to get some fresh air.
-I just need to change. Wait just a bit.
-Okay.
Hey, close the window!
Right. I'll be back soon.
Hey, let's go. Here.
It's just a walk around the neighborhood.
Why the water bottle?
We'll get thirsty later.
Let's go.
You've been showing up
near my house often.
What?
You were here when your dashcam
recorded that reporter last time.
Right.
-The street's wider--
-Let's go this way.
Sure.
Let's go past that tree
and walk along the sea.
Then, we can go around Namdal-ri
on our way back. Okay?
Sure.
It's just a walk though.
Why do you have it all planned out?
We can go wherever the road takes us.
You still have to decide on the route.
We might take the wrong route
while walking and talking.
Come on. We won't get lost here.
You're totally a mainland person now.
Hey, this has nothing to do with that.
Jeez.
You know what?
I'm fascinated by mainland tourists
who visit our restaurant.
They wait in line for two hours
but don't eat the food right away.
They take tons of photos first.
Then, they meticulously plan out
their schedules while eating.
I wonder if they even
really appreciate the food.
I feel bad that they might not
fully enjoy their trip.
They're just planning,
because time is precious to them.
You don't have to pity them for that.
It just means that they're trying
to spend their time wisely. Jeez.
What? Do you do that too?
Yes, I do. I'm all about planning.
So I'm saying you should let relax a bit.
You're not here on a trip.
Relax and go wherever your feet take you.
Eat what you want. Wear what you want.
You blended right in
with the other hikers yesterday.
-I thought you were an expert.
-Come on.
This is your hometown.
No one cares if you
do things halfway or wear whatever.
It's hard for me to do things halfway.
That's not true.
The Cho Sam-dal I know
used to be called "Halfway Cho."
Stop annoying me.
-What do you know?
-All right.
You're so ridiculous.
But it's true.
What's the matter?
PERSONNEL APPOINTMENT PROPOSAL
Jeez, stop doing this. I'm not going.
I'd given up on you too,
but your father asked me to persuade you.
My dad?
Deep down, I know you want to go.
I'm near retirement, and even I'd want
to go and do real work too.
You're so passionate about your job,
so not going makes no sense.
I heard you've been analyzing
the weather in Korea and around the world.
That's just…
I just do that when I'm bored.
It's a hobby…
Hobby, my foot.
Yong-pil, don't just turn it down.
You should think about in various ways
and look at the big picture.
Think about all the opportunities
for analysis you'll have at HQ.
You've always wanted
to go to Geneva, Switzerland.
Are you okay?
What were you so distracted by
to end up near these reefs?
You seem more relaxed
after returning from Seoul.
And you're not fixated
on telling people "I didn't fail!"
Don't tease me.
I'm not relaxed.
Finding myself and inner peace
isn't easy to do.
I start to think about focusing
on just finding myself.
But suddenly, I feel my anger rising.
And then, it goes away.
Everything feels so unfair, so I feel
like going back and make a scene.
Then, I calm myself down.
It's an emotional rollercoaster each day.
I'm relieved.
Why? Because of how differently I act?
Yes.
That just means you have healthy emotions.
If you gave up on everything
and said you forgave everyone,
I would've taken you to a shrink.
What's gotten into you?
You're so good at this.
You're on a roll today!
Good at what?
Comforting me.
Come on.
I used to take care of you
when we were kids.
When did you grow up
and learn how to comfort me so well?
Don't tease me.
Hey, they must be done diving.
Let's go. Come on.
Goodness. Are you okay, Ms. Ko?
I'm fine. Don't overreact.
You even hurt your hand.
You've always been cautious,
so why were you so distracted today?
Sam-dal!
Hello, ma'am!
You better stop
giving your mother trouble.
They say even monkeys
fall from trees sometimes.
Your mom almost had a big accident.
What?
Did you hurt yourself, Mom?
How did this happen? Oh, no!
I'm fine.
-Oh, no!
-Eun-u's mom raced in to save her.
Thank you, ma'am.
I know it's hard to believe,
but she's agile underwater.
What was that? Were you teasing me?
Cut it out. Let's go.
Let me carry this, Mom.
-Move.
-Okay.
It's very heavy.
Mom, I can…
-We'll get going.
-Bye.
Mom…
Hold on tight,
or you'll fall off.
Okay.
Mom, do you enjoy diving?
No one enjoys working.
We do it to make ends meet.
Then, don't work.
I said I'd send you money.
Goodness.
No, thanks.
Why would I take money from my kids?
I'm going to earn my own money
until the day I die.
Jeez.
I haven't done anything
to deserve your money.
Jeez.
What do you mean?
You've done a lot for me.
Going fast on the bike was refreshing.
What?
What's wrong?
Are you in pain? Are you okay?
Does your chest hurt?
It's the coffee.
I had a cup in the afternoon,
and it's making my heart race.
You had instant coffee, didn't you?
I told you to have
only one cup a day. Jeez.
Don't touch that.
Just go inside. It smells.
-It's okay. Your hand is--
-Don't fuss over me.
Go on, now.
I need to dry my buoy too.
Really?
All right, then.
I think you need another tub…
Where is she going?
Once the theme park is built here,
this neighborhood will be prosperous.
Sir, this is the rest area
for the Namdal-ri haenyeos
before they go diving.
This area is shallow,
so we can build a children's pool here.
It'll be a perfectly safe depth.
-All right, then.
-Okay.
-Should we go over there?
-Sure.
Watch your step.
Look--
-This way, please.
-Let's go.
So the theme park…
So…
Yes, sir?
What is it, sir?
Hurry and say what's on your mind, sir.
Well…
So you'd been in touch
with her all this time?
And you didn't tell me?
Did she ask you not to?
I don't know.
Come on, now.
Why is she in Jeju?
Is she working at the airport here?
Once again, I don't know, sir.
Come on.
Why are you playing dumb?
What did you guys talk about?
Sir,
she asked me to keep you out of her sight.
What? Me?
Yes.
Well…
I see. Is that right?
The ice cream is going to melt.
Let's go home already.
Your grandpa's watermelon ice cream
is turning into juice.
Did you hear me?
Darn it. I don't see them today either.
Are you coming down?
Be careful.
Why dolphins all of a sudden?
You were never interested.
No reason.
We're in Jeju,
so it's nice to appreciate them.
Yes, we are in Jeju.
Wait up.
AS THEME PARK CREATES 10,000 JOBS
Ten thousand jobs.
Then, all the villagers could make
a living working at this theme park.
No wonder they were so cooperative, right?
By the way,
why did you insist
on driving past Samdal-ri?
So that she'd notice?
I want to see what's around the theme park
and the nearby villages, okay?
It's our job to look around.
Isn't it your job too?
Is it only my job?
This place is nice too.
I'm happy every time I see you
Where are you going, Ha-yul?
Hi, we meet again.
Darn it.
Did you see it?
See what?
The dolphins?
Did you see Namchun
lifting Oryong up for his first breath?
What?
Of course. I even saw
Namchun give birth to Oryong.
You did your homework, kid.
Hello.
What's going on?
Why are you standing there?
Who is he?
Stop, Secretary Ko. Stop.
Stop!
It's Ha-yul, right?
If you want to learn more about dolphins,
come visit our dolphin center
with your aunt.
I'm not her aunt, I'm her--
Mom!
"Mom"?
What?
TAMRA LINER
JEJU HOSPITAL
REGULAR CHECKUP 3:00 P.M.
FOODS GOOD FOR THE HEART
Goodness.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Are you sick?
Of course not. I'm perfectly fine.
Then, why would you get
regular checkups at a hospital?
What?
That's…
Why are you looking at that?
I'm taking care of Mal-suk,
the old lady next door.
I make her doctor's appointments for her.
Dad…
What's wrong?
Are you in pain?
It's the coffee.
I had a cup in the afternoon,
and it's making my heart race.
THE PRIDE OF SAMDAL-RI!
CHO YONG-PIL'S HERE!
CAPTURING JEJU'S WEATHER
PHOTOGRAPHY EXHIBITION
My goodness!
Excuse me, Ms. Sam-dal.
Is peeking into my room your hobby?
Why were you in the van?
Because I just got back from work.
I see. Right.
But why were you sitting in the van
instead of going inside?
I was folding a paper airplane.
I was making this in the van,
but since you came outside,
it won't get to fly.
And it'll just land on you.
I told you I'm not going to enter,
so stop wasting paper. Take it back.
A waste? I have tons of flyers.
I'm going to fold all of them into planes.
So just make up your mind.
Do you have nothing better to do?
No, nothing at all.
Look…
Forget about the contest.
I…
I have something to ask you.
Are you free right now?
What is it?
Do you know if something
is wrong with my mom?
What do you mean?
I mean, you know
practically everything about her.
My sisters and I
have been away for so long.
Do you really not know anything?
Has she been sick
and going to the hospital?
Or has she been looking ill?
I think something's up,
but my dad is being tight-lipped too.
I'm not sure.
What? You don't know either?
Maybe I'm wrong.
If you think something's up,
then you could be right
since you know her best.
Just take her to the hospital
if you're that worried.
Given how stubborn she is,
it might be difficult to do though.
Hey!
What are you two doing there?
Hey. What are you doing?
Are you planning to follow me inside?
My parents are going to grab
a harpoon the moment they see you.
A harpoon?
Well, you don't want to know.
So if the child
is about this tall,
she must be around four?
That means you had her four years ago.
She's not your kid.
And what kind
of four-year-old is this tall?
She's nine.
Nine…
Nine?
Then…
Nine years ago would've been--
She's my niece!
Okay?
Grab the hijiki from outside.
Goodness, people probably think
this family is full of alcoholics.
Your niece. I see.
So she's your niece.
It makes sense now. Yes.
-Look, Jeon Dae-yeong.
-Yes?
I guess you didn't get
what I said last time.
Go focus on reviving your company
instead of wasting your time here.
Instead of being here with me…
What's wrong with you?
I was just…
happy to see you.
I kept feeling happy,
so it made me want to see you again.
And even if I work hard
on the company's problems,
you know they won't be solved.
Yeah.
I'm fine with it.
I'm the one
who caused those problems.
It's not your fault--
Father…
Who…
Who is that?
Damn it.
Just go. Get lost. Right now.
Dad.
Where are you going?
-I was sorting the trash.
-I see.
-Who was that?
-Directions.
Someone who asked for directions.
Just keep going straight on that road!
I'll take it. Let me throw it out.
But if he goes straight,
that's a dead end.
Go back inside, Dad.
I didn't know when I was little,
but this is a great spot.
Didn't you see this
when you came here last time?
I did?
She was in no condition
to look around then.
She was drunk and bawling. Gosh.
What?
What is it?
-What?
-You little…
What are you going to do?
Hey, by the way,
it's been ages since all five of us
were together like this.
I thought this moment would never come.
This is nice.
Enjoy it all you want.
Hey,
you two.
What's going on?
-What?
It's so late at night.
-So what?
-Why were you two out here alone?
What is it this time? What is it?
Are you two back together--
Gyeong-tae, have a drink!
What about you guys?
What were you three doing here so late?
We're friends.
So are they!
If they're not friends,
then what else would they be?
Right?
Right.
You're right.
My dear friend Gyeong-tae,
who's awfully kind but clueless.
"Yes, we reminisced
about the beautiful time we shared
as we walked together late at night."
Is this the answer you wanted to hear?
What?
What "beautiful time"?
Jeez.
Everyone here knows about our past.
They're not quiet about it
because they don't know.
They're just being considerate, okay?
Being considerate! Okay?
But of course,
I understand that must be hard
for someone like you
who's been single all his life.
That's why, right?
Because you didn't know?
-I--
-Of course. How would he know?
Jeez. I knew she'd get you.
You're no match for Sam-dal.
What did I do?
You said something was fishy too.
-When did I say that?
-You did.
What is this?
What?
Isn't that the exhibition
our work is holding?
Are you entering?
Hey, this isn't bad.
Give it a try.
How did you know about this?
Only a handful of people
know about this exhibition.
What are you talking about?
I told her about it.
Hey, I'm a trend-setting
fashion photographer.
I don't do landscape photography.
You used to do it often.
I have a lot of your photos.
What?
Are you sure I took these?
They're all out of focus.
Yeah, they're yours.
SPRING AT DODUBONG PEAK
Spring?
Was this really during spring?
Wow, I've never seen Dodubong Peak
look so dreary before.
Darn it.
Hey, why do you have my work?
Your work?
They're no different
from the photos that I take.
Cho Eun-hye would be ashamed of this.
That little…
Let's see.
I have more embarrassing things here.
You're going to let them make fun of you
for these embarrassing photos?
That darn Gyeong-tae…
Even I don't have these photos.
Is he some obsessed fan or what?
By the way, isn't it better to take photos
than go on the Jeju Olle Trail?
You…
One thing about me is
once I say no, it'll always be a no.
-Bye.
-Okay.
Bye.
If you change your mind,
be outside by 7:00 a.m.
-I'll go with you to submit your form.
-I said forget it.
Seriously, at 7:00 a.m.!
I'll wait five minutes.
They're all out of focus.
These are ridiculous.
Damn it.
CAPTURING JEJU'S WEATHER
PHOTOGRAPHY EXHIBITION
APPLY
ONLINE APPLICATION ENDED
He recommended what's already over?
ON-SITE APPLICATIONS OPEN UNTIL MAY
There's a type of rain exclusive to Jeju
that falls as if it's jealous of spring.
The bracken rain has begun.
Due to the drizzling rain and dark clouds
hanging over their heads,
many people feel depressed
around this time of year.
Some people also get lost
in the mountains while picking bracken.
The bracken rain is here once again,
and we hope you all remain safe.
Once a no, always a no, right?
But look who's here.
What? You're the one who told me to enter.
Honey.
Are you going diving today?
The weather isn't that great.
We agreed not to, but I'm going
to check how things are just in case.
Don't overdo it.
You know…
You know your doctor's appointment
is tomorrow, right?
You should ask them
to change your medicine this time.
You've been out of breath a lot lately.
All right.
I'll see you later.
Breakfast's on the table! Get up and eat!
Gosh.
Thank you.
Here's the application form.
Fill it in and submit it.
And submit your work before the deadline.
Okay.
What?
You better not have
a change of heart and back out.
-Okay, I won't.
-Okay.
Aren't you leaving?
What? Yeah, I'm leaving.
And since Jeju's weather
is so unpredictable, I think--
Just go.
-Go?
-Just go. Now.
You want me to leave?
-Should I go?
-Yes.
Good luck.
What are you smiling about?
Has the gloomy weather
messed with your head?
Hurry up and go so I can work.
All right.
Damn it.
Gyeong-tae.
Yeah?
Did your mom go to work today?
I don't know. I slept at our hideout.
I doubt she did though. Ms. Ko told them
not to because of the wind.
Really?
Ms. Ko's instincts are far better
than any supercomputer.
She knows what's best.
Have a good day.
MS. KO MI-JA
-Baek-ho.
-Yes?
Can you put up
the eastern coastal wave buoy data?
Sure.
COASTAL WAVE BUOY - 1610038
TIME, WAVE HEIGHT
There's no wind, Ms. Ko.
And the current seems to be okay.
Then, I think we can go in.
Pack it in.
The weather's a bit strange.
Let's just rest today.
WHY DID YOU BECOME A WEATHER FORECASTER?
I became a forecaster
to protect my loved ones.
Sam-dal?
Hey, Eun-u.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you in the Observation Division?
I just planted a tree
for weather prediction.
I see.
You made the right decision!
I want to see you keep taking photos.
Let me give you a tour
of the Forecasting Division.
No, it's okay.
Are civilians allowed to tour around here?
Come on. You won't be alone.
I'll be with you, okay?
Follow me.
You're right.
Look at your authority!
This is who I am.
Let me see data from the west too.
Sure.
Yong-pil, why do you keep checking
the east and west?
Because the wind waves keep changing.
I kept telling you something was off.
-Buoy data from the far east too.
-All right.
The east is going to face
some seriously bad weather.
Prepare a weather advisory now.
Yes, sir.
You little punk.
You're good.
COAST OF SAMDAL-RI
-Go to shore!
Go to shore!
Ms. Ko!
-Where did Ms. Ko go?
-Ms. Ko!
Ms. Ko!
Hello, this is Jeju Meteorological Center.
It's a request for the coast guard!
A Samdal-ri haenyeo
went missing while diving.
-They're searching for her.
-What?
Okay.
What?
What…
Eun-u, isn't that our town?
No… Mom.
Sir, Mom is missing.
Put up the coastal long wave monitoring
and buoy data!
Yes, sir!
Hello, this is Forecaster Cho Yong-pil.
I checked where she went missing.
There's a strong southeastern wind
and high waves of 1 to 3 meters.
Please do a thorough search
both underwater and on the surface
of the 600-square-meter area
from her last location.
And a floral pattern.
Yes.
The missing haenyeo's buoy
has flowers on it.
No, I'm not sure about that.
Please start the search
of that area as fast as you can.
-And her heart--
-Yong-pil.
Are you talking about my mom?
Is it my mom?
The missing haenyeo…
suffers from a heart condition.
Please check her pulse
and heart rate as soon as you find her.
Check her heart first, please.
Sam-dal.
Go to your mom right now.
Eun-u.
-Yeah?
-Hurry.
-Take her to her mom.
-Okay.
-Sam-dal, let's go.
All right.
Okay.
-Baek-ho.
-Yes?
Put up all data from floating
and coastal wave buoys out at sea.
All right.
The probability of Mom
drifting out to sea…
The probability of her
I'm so thirsty.
Get me some water.
Damn it.
-Hey.
-Jin-dal!
Is someone calling me?
-I think so.
What am I going to do?
Jin-dal! My goodness!
Goodness, Jin-dal!
Jin-dal!
Your mom…
My goodness, your mom!
Hurry!
Ms. Ko!
No…
-They're over there!
-Okay!
Honey!
What in the world happened?
Are you okay?
What about Ms. Ko?
Ms. Ko!
Hurry up!
-Hey!
-Hurry up!
-Hey.
Mom!
-Mom!
WELCOME TO SAMDAL-RI
Yong-pil!
Cho Yong-pil!
The uninvited guest visits
every April without fail.
The bracken rain.
Mom!
-No, don't!
-Mom!
Cho Yong-pil!
No!
Don't go in there!
Yong-pil!
Oh, my god!
No!
Mi-ja!
Mi-ja…
Mom!
Mom…
You can't die, Mi-ja!
No…
Mom!
Mom…
Mi-ja…
What if that sea takes away
my grandmother?
Sam-dal, Mom will be fine.
Nothing will happen.
Did the sea take someone away again?
I am also cramming in everything here.
I'm holding it in.
It pops out a dozen times a day.
You should hate her too.
Your mom.
Why did your mom die?
Aren't you scared of the sea?
How can it not be scary?
The sea is the scariest thing
in the world for me.
It took away my old friend as well.
Hey! Ko Mi-ja!
I'm very scared of it.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim