=Marry Me Again=
=Episode 4=
This is the DNA Testing Center.
The comparative analysis
you submitted is complete.
The final report has been sent
to your email.
Please check your inbox.
Alright, thank you.
(DNA results for Lu Nianbai & Tang Jingxing,
Confirmed)
(Subjects: Lu Nianbai, Tang Jingxing)
(Test results)
(Samples are
from different individuals.)
(0% chance of the same person.)
So it's really not him.
Boss!
Coming!
Five signature skewers, please.
We're out of them.
Would you like something else?
But I really want them right now!
Tang Jingxing loved those.
The last portion
was just bought
by that customer over there.
- Which one?
- That one.
♪A single glance becomes eternity♪
♪The wind wrinkles my longing♪
♪An irresistible fate, when I met you♪
♪When we intertwined,
when we began to lose♪
♪When I replay every moment,
when I think of you♪
- That girl looks pretty good.
- Yeah.
Let's have some fun tonight.
Sure.
Sister, why are you here?
It's nothing.
I just realized
you've grown up.
The memory
of bathing you as a child
still feels so vivid.
Let me take these dirty cups for you.
Get some rest early.
Thanks, Sister.
(The sad vacation is over.)
(For the sake of mine
and Tang Jingxing's shared business,)
(I must pull myself together)
(to be worthy of being
President of Wanmao.)
(Tang Jingxing,)
(it's been so long since you left.)
(I thought I'd moved on,)
(but Lu Nianbai's arrival)
(made me realize)
(I've been drowning in grief,)
(and unable to face your absence.)
(Maybe...)
(it was too sudden.)
(I'm just suffering
from love withdrawal.)
(Today,)
(let's say a proper goodbye.)
(Who knew this girl could)
(dress so well?)
Miss Hua, going out tonight?
Meeting friends.
Be careful on the road.
(Tang Jingxing, goodbye.)
(I can't keep wallowing like this.)
(I need to pull myself together)
(and live properly.)
I heard you grew up abroad,
so I went with
a Western-style greeting.
Isn't cheek-kissing
also a thing overseas?
But that'd be
awkward for us.
I'd just smear
the foundation on your face.
Well...
bye!
(She is still crazy.)
(Hua Rucheng, Hua Ruoyi's father)
Darling.
Nianqi, you're back.
Why does your head hurt again?
We lost the diamond mining bid.
That's just business.
Isn't this normal?
I'm just a bit frustrated.
After all that preparation,
some no-name
American company
snatched it with a 0.5% higher offer.
Can you believe it?
How's that even possible?
Darling,
profits can wait.
Your health matters more.
(Nianbai, well done.)
(Notarial Will)
He always wanted to leave the group
to his eldest daughter, Hua Ruoyu.
Now that Hua Ruoyi's back,
the inheritance will
definitely go to her.
She's his biological daughter.
She'll definitely inherit.
As for the amount,
it depends on the will.
It's odd though,
I've searched the house and the office,
but I can't find the will.
Who knows where he hid it?
If it favored Hua Ruoyi,
he'd have given it to her
to keep safe.
That old man is infuriating.
Help me get into Wanmao Group,
and I'll help you find the will.
(Wanmao Group)
Since Honey Love was launched,
its sales have been sluggish.
It is a three-year-old design.
We should update it.
But the brand story
is based on your love with Mr. Tang.
If we're making changes...
We won't change
Mr. Tang's original designs.
However,
we can add
a new line
to complement
Honey Love.
In this way...
Yi.
Aunt Nianqi, what brings you here?
Wanmao
is now a Hua Group subsidiary.
As the director,
I'm here to inspect.
Carry on with the meeting,
I'll just listen in.
Verification failed.
(Need Mi Chuxia's fingerprint.)
Okay, I'll find a backup for you now.
I'll look for the documents.
(Mi Chuxia, what are you thinking?)
(He's not Tang Jingxing.)
Why are you here?
I'm here with my sister.
Then why follow me
instead of her?
You keep saying
I look like Tang Jingxing.
So I wanted to see
how alike we really are.
His fashion sense is mediocre
and nowhere near mine.
What nonsense are you talking about?
He was more interesting
and better-looking.
You're way off.
Really?
What are you up to?
Hua Ruoyi,
I won't be anyone's stand-in.
You're really confusing me.
Who said you were?
Then why did you kiss me that time?
It really was a misunderstanding.
I was drunk
and craving skewers.
And why did you sneak into my room
to peep at me showering?
I wasn't peeping! It was...
It wasn't what you think.
Really?
♪Don't say you're sorry, it's too cruel♪
♪So much left unspoken, all forgiven♪
♪Singing softly, echoes lingering♪
♪All the stubbornness I regret♪
♪Can't forget, you were my sun♪
♪Yet I feared the light you shone♪
♪Singing lightly, tinged with sorrow♪
♪I return to every place we knew♪
♪My growth, your reflection♪
♪I truly hope♪
♪Singing softly, echoes lingering♪
♪All the stubbornness I regret♪
♪Can't forget, you were my sun♪
♪Yet I feared the light you shone♪
♪Singing lightly, tinged with sorrow♪
♪I return to every place we knew♪
♪My growth, your reflection♪
♪I truly hope♪
♪I could have been there
for you all those years♪