=Marry Me Again=
=Episode 30=
He's strapped explosives on me.
Explosives!
Run...
Mu Huaijin, are you crazy?
Stop talking!
You'd better let us go.
Or I'll blow you all up.
Sister, you go first.
Nianbai,
be careful.
She is Hua Ruoyu's biological sister.
If Hua Ruoyu were alive,
would she want this?
Yu...
Yu will be back soon.
I'm about to get my Yu back.
It's all because of you.
Now she's not Yu anymore.
She'll never become Yu.
Tang Jingxing,
you ruined everything.
I should've ended you back then!
Huaijin,
come at me.
Let Hua Ruoyi go.
Spare Hua Ruoyu.
Don't you hate me?
Come at me.
You want to save her, huh?
Alright.
If you want to save her,
stab yourself with this.
No, don't listen to him, Tang Jingxing.
Don't listen to him.
Mu Huaijin, are you crazy?
Stop arguing!
Huaijin, I'm begging you.
I'll become my sister.
I'll marry you, okay?
- Hurry up!
- Don't push him!
Tang Jingxing!
I beg you, let him go.
Tang Jingxing,
don't listen to him.
- I beg you.
- Hurry up.
You can't leave me again.
- Stay calm.
- I beg you.
Don't listen to him, okay?
Mu Huaijin!
Chuxia,
I said I wouldn't lie to you anymore.
I'm begging you.
Be good.
Close your eyes.
No.
No!
Tang Jingxing!
Tang Jingxing,
don't!
Tang Jingxing...
♪Today, the sky outside is gray♪
♪It's the color of missing you♪
♪There's no cloud in the sky.
It's raining in my heart♪
♪These are sobs of my longing for you♪
♪A single glance becomes eternity♪
♪The wind wrinkles my longing♪
♪An irresistible fate, when I met you♪
Don't scare me.
Does it hurt?
Let's go to the hospital, okay?
I'll take you, Tang Jingxing.
Please don't...
♪In the crowd, no one passing by is you♪
♪I don't know where to go♪
♪A single glance becomes eternity♪
Why?
♪An irresistible fate♪
♪When we intertwined,
when we began to lose♪
♪When I replay every moment,
when I think of you♪
♪Like a spinning coin that won't land♪
♪Every shadow♪
(Mu Huaijin has been arrested
and imprisoned on charges including)
(attempted murder
and intentional assault.)
(The case is currently in court.)
(Clinic Building)
How is he?
Just finished surgery.
The doctor said
he'd wake up in a few hours.
I heard Mu Huaijin
confess everything
at the police station.
Actually,
he had always loved my sister.
They were about to get married.
After she passed away,
he couldn't handle it.
That's why he changed his mind.
When I appeared later,
he wanted
to make me her substitute.
That's why he acted that way.
I always thought he was crazy,
but surprisingly,
he was a romantic fool.
Yi,
I'm sorry for what happened before.
I admit defeat.
It's not for you
but for him.
He truly loves you.
Treat him well.
The doctor said your right leg...
It might stay like this forever.
Maybe it's karma
for my past bad deeds.
I have something for you.
(Divorce Agreement)
(Hotel Transfer Agreement)
Nianqi Grand Hotel?
I bought it long ago.
I was going
to leave it to you in my will.
I know you have management skills.
But I can't give you the Hua Group.
This hotel in England
has over a century of history.
I hope you can manage
your own career well.
You're young and beautiful.
For these past years,
you've been through a lot.
Rucheng...
(Room 1111)
Tang Jingxing,
you're awake!
Finally, you're awake.
Who are you?
♪Don't say you're sorry, it's too cruel♪
♪So much left unspoken, all forgiven♪
♪Singing softly, echoes lingering♪
♪All the stubbornness I regret♪
♪Can't forget, you were my sun♪
♪Yet I feared the light you shone♪
♪Singing lightly, tinged with sorrow♪
♪I return to every place we knew♪
♪My growth, your reflection♪
♪I truly hope♪
♪Singing softly, echoes lingering♪
♪All the stubbornness I regret♪
♪Can't forget, you were my sun♪
♪Yet I feared the light you shone♪
♪Singing lightly, tinged with sorrow♪
♪I return to every place we knew♪
♪My growth, your reflection♪
♪I truly hope♪
♪I could have been there
for you all those years♪