[English subtitles are available]
[My Wife is A Thief]
[Episode 17]
Have a seat.
Lord Xu, why are you here
instead of healing your wounds at home?
Are you here to confess your crime?
I'm here to tell you that the Zichen Department
will handle the case of Lord Chen.
Did I hear it right?
What's your rank, Xu Muchen?
How dare you come to the Ministry of Justice and ask for a case?
Lord Chen is innocent.
I've found some clues.
I will definitely clear his name
in a few more days.
Xu Muchen, what do you mean?
You mean I'm incompetent?
I didn't mean that.
-It's just... -You can leave now.
You have no right to interfere with the case handled by the Ministry of Justice.
Give this case to me.
If I succeed,
all the credit will be yours.
If I fail,
I will be at your disposal.
Okay.
I'll let you handle this case.
If you can solve it,
I'll take the credit.
If you fail,
you will be convicted of the same crime as Lord Chen.
Files and exhibits
will be delivered to the Zichen Department later.
Thank you.
What's the relationship
between Lord Chen and Xu Muchen?
Why is Xu Muchen willing to take such a risk?
[Chang An Restaurant]
Miss Su.
The person you asked us to find is in the restaurant.
He's been drinking inside.
I gotta go.
Okay.
Young Madam.
Shall we wait for Lord Xu?
That guy will be gone when he finishes the procedure.
You guys are so inefficient.
Go in now.
What a good match.
What a fierce couple.
Are you going or not?
Okay. Okay.
[Chang An Restaurant]
Guards.
Give me a bottle of wine.
Zhong Aba, right?
Who are you?
Mrs. Chen asked me to bring you a bottle of wine.
But I am not sure whether you want a toast
or punishment.
Let go of me!
My Lord.
Didn't you say we're here to drink?
You didn't mention I would be tortured.
Do you know why I brought you here?
I don't know.
Tell me.
How did you collude with outsiders
to frame Lord Chen?
My Lord, I'm innocent.
I'm indebted to Lord Chen.
How could I frame him?
You're right.
Lord Chen did treat you well.
But you are ungrateful.
You were an orphan.
The Chen family has raised you for ten years.
You squandered money of the Chen family
before Lord Chen is convicted.
I'm innocent, My Lord.
Innocent?
Tell me then.
The night before yesterday,
why didn't you move the swill out
at 11 p.m. as usual
but at 1 a.m.?
I...
I had diarrhea
for the whole night.
So it was later than usual.
There was only one courtyard
between the backyard and backdoor.
Why did you put the swill wagon
outside Lord Chen's warehouse
and spill the swill on his wall?
That... That's...
You don't want to tell me the truth?
My Lord.
Wu Zhao.
Do you recognize your fingerprint on the title deed?
You spent 100 taels of silver seven days ago
on a house in the suburbs
and saved 150 taels in the bank,
an amount
equal to Lord Chen's annual salary.
How did you get the money?
Anyone who fabricates evidence
and frames a court official
shall be convicted of frame-up according to the law.
Given Lord Chen's post,
the culprit who framed him should be executed.
My Lord, please spare my life!
I don't want to die!
Stop shouting.
Let me show you the way.
If you testify against the person behind the scenes,
you won't be the culprit.
Besides,
your deeds will be considered as redeeming yourself by good service.
Lord Chen might ask a favor
to spare your life.
Fine.
I'll tell you the truth.
A mysterious person
did
come to me.
He said he would give me a large sum of money
if I helped him transfer the goods.
This is all I...
Zhong Aba.
My Lord.
He's dead.
Dead?
My Lord.
The Ministry of Justice sent the exhibits here.
It was deliberately erased.
Wu Zhao.
How many biggest banks are there in the capital?
The biggest one is Changshun,
followed by Ji'an and Yongan.
[Yong]
Lead some men
to check Yongan Bank.
Yes.
You guys, follow me.
-Yes. -Yes.
Lord Gongyang.
Are you here for Lord Xu?
I'll inform him.
Lord Gongyang.
What are you doing?
This is Lord Gongyang.
Sit down.
What's up?
I heard you found
clues to Lord Chen's case.
That's right.
Zhong Aba, Lord Chen's servant,
admitted himself
that he was instigated
to frame Lord Chen.
Where is Zhong Aba?
He died during the interrogation.
He was poisoned.
We're still investigating.
In other words, the witness died
before the testimony was taken down.
Are you clear
that the evidence you have now
cannot prove anything?
That means
Lord Chen's case
has been settled.
Lord Xu.
Do you remember
what you promised me?
If I can't solve the case,
I will be convicted of the same crime as Lord Chen.
Arrest him!
Yes.
-What are you doing? -What are you doing?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
My Lord.
I found it.
In Yongan Bank,
there was the account statement
of Lord Chen's family.
The owner of this batch of silver
is Moyan from Pharmacy.
The Watermill?
Lord Gongyang.
Although there is a witness,
this case involves the Watermill.
That means Lord Chen
can't be convicted soon.
Time for you to leave.
You...
Wu Zhao.
Good job.
My Lord.
What should we do next?
Keep investigating.
[Peaceful Residence]
Darling.
How is Lord Chen's case?
We still can't prove his innocence due to a lack of evidence.
How could it be?
Didn't the servant confess his crime?
But he died
before he signed the testimony.
He was imprisoned in the Zichen Department.
How could he be poisoned?
It was chronic.
Even he himself didn't notice it.
The big boss
knew our every move
to the nearest second.
If the case is settled in two days,
we won't have any chance to save Lord Chen.
There's another way.
Other than the Ministry of Justice,
the Grand Court is also investigating this case.
If we can ask for the transfer of Lord Chen's case,
there might be a chance of survival.
How will it work?
Since Lord Chen was wronged,
there must be something wrong in his file.
If the file can be transferred to the Zichen Department,
I can say there are so many doubts
that the case must be re-investigated.
Then transfer the case now.
But the procedure of the Grand Court is very strict.
It takes at least half a month to transfer a case.
It will be too late.
What should we do now?
Don't panic, darling.
If it doesn't work, I will...
What will you do?
Mother.
I...
Lord Gu.
Isn't this Young Madam?
It's been a few days since we met last time.
You look much prettier.
Old Madam.
I won't disrupt
your family time.
I have something to deal with in the Department.
I have to go.
Wait, Lord Gu.
You must have something to tell me.
Nothing.
Think about it.
Ah, yeah.
I have something of great importance
to tell you.
The Ministry of War
lost a newly revised map.
They asked us
to cooperate with the Ministry of Justice to investigate the case.
This is serious. Let's go.
Let's go.
Wait.
Tell me
about Lord Chen's case.
Mother.
This is confidential.
I can't tell you.
You can't?
I heard you two
talking about that just now.
It's fine
if you can't tell me.
Zhen.
Tell me what happened.
The Ministry of Justice
has convicted Lord Chen of corruption.
But Muchen thinks...
Honey.
Speaking of which,
the case
was not under the jurisdiction of the Zichen Department initially.
Rather, you asked the Ministry of Justice for it.
I also heard from Lord Gu
that you promised with your life
to the Ministry of Justice in order to investigate this case.
You'll be at the disposal of Gongyang Maocai
if you can't solve the case.
Don't look at me.
I accidentally spilled the beans.
How could you promise that
to Gongyang Maocai?
If he has something on you,
he will definitely give you a hard time.
Are you crazy?
Mother. Darling.
No need to worry at all.
I'm completely confident.
Don't worry?
Your life is hanging by a thread.
How can I not be worried?
Mother.
I have sufficient evidence
that Lord Chen is wronged.
As the Governor,
I can't sit by and watch.
So what?
Countless people are distancing themselves from the affair.
What's the use of taking the risk
when your word doesn't carry much weight?
I've asked for leave for you from Lord Gu.
From now on, you are not allowed to leave the mansion.
I will ask a favor of Gongyang
for you tomorrow morning.
Mother.
It has been decided.
Zhen.
I'm tired.
Take me back to my room.
Yes, Mother.
Well,
I'll leave if there's nothing else.
Stay here.
Since you're here,
have some tea.
Mother.
I burned some soothing incense.
You may go to bed early.
I'll stay here.
Zhen, thank you.
Mother.
Muchen was impulsive to say that.
The worst-case scenario is he will be discharged from the position.
He is intelligent.
In addition, I can borrow some money from Jinning.
We can live a decent life by running business.
Don't be angry about this.
I hope he could be laid off,
so that he wouldn't get himself into trouble.
At least it will spare both of us
from worries every day.
If he can't investigate this case clearly,
I'm afraid he won't be able to live in peace for the whole life.
Zhen.
There's something you don't understand.
Lord Chen's case is not that simple.
Mother, why do you say so?
Forget it.
Zhen, you may leave now.
Okay.
[Memorial Tablet of My Husband, Xu Chengsi]
Madam.
Lord Jiang had an accident
and fell down from the cart.
What about the other ministers?
They also went to investigate the case of Chengsi.
Lord Wang was framed
for colluding with the enemy
and was exiled to the border.
Duke Sheng was sent to the Yue State to direct operations.
Now he's trapped in the mountain.
The other ministers are in the same situation.
Madam, we...
Bad news!
Bad news! Bad news!
Old Madam.
Young Master is missing.
Find him.
Hurry up.
-Yes. -Yes.
Madam.
Stop it. You are not a good drinker.
It's getting late.
Can you let me go?
Let me go.
Let me go back early.
You did it on purpose.
What do you mean?
You deliberately told my mother
my promise to the Ministry of Justice.
How could that be possible?
How could I?
How could I say that on purpose?
At that time, I was just chatting
with Old Madam.
I accidentally
spilled the beans.
Don't interfere
with Lord Chen's case.
But you know it.
I know it.
Lord Hu lost his life
because of a ledger in Taizhou,
while Lord Chen
was imprisoned right after he took office in Taizhou.
Do these things
have nothing to do with the flood in Taizhou?
I know
you want to save Lord Chen
for dealing with the flood in Taizhou.
Lord Chen's case should be investigated by the Ministry of Justice.
But you volunteered.
Muchen.
Can you stop causing this mess?
Lord Chen and my father are old friends.
How can I just sit by and do nothing?
You are right.
But the Zichen Department is an institute of the government.
It's not at your disposal.
If someone has something on you,
you won't be able to
explain it easily.
How about this?
I'll return this case
to the Ministry of Justice tomorrow.
Do we stop investigating it?
It's beyond your duty.
Not only you,
but the whole Zichen Department
can't investigate Lord Chen's case.
But this case...
What do you want to say?
You are really stupid.
Think about it.
What else is there besides the flood in Taizhou?
The Moon Star Herb.
You can go to Taizhou to investigate
in the name of the Moon Star Herb.
You can do whatever you want then.
The Zichen Department will fully support you.
Gongyang will have no reason
to interfere.
You are right.
I've offered you the idea.
It depends on you to take actions.
But I'm still grounded.
Grounded?
You want me to
plead for you in front of Old Madam?
No problem.
But I dare not.
Father.
What is this?
Lord Chen's testimony.
I sent someone to copy it for me
from the Ministry of Justice.
Xu Muchen is investigating
Lord Chen's case.
He wants to clear Lord Chen's name before the case is settled.
He needs this.
Besides, Gongyang has a grudge against Xu.
There's not enough time
to go through all the procedures in the Ministry of Justice.
And then?
You need to find a way to put it in Xu's Mansion.
I'll inform the Ministry of Justice.
The Ministry of Justice will search the Xu family.
Xu Muchen will be dismissed and under investigation.
Then I'll ask His Majesty
to grant them a divorce.
All of this will be reasonable.
Do you understand?
I've considered
everything for you.
As for what to do,
it's up to you.
[Cherish High Aspirations]
Young Master.
Have you prepared everything I need?
It's done.
OK.
Invite Miss over for tea.
Yes, Young Master.
Brother.
Why did you invite me here?
Nothing.
I prepared some desserts.
Have a try.
Have some.
Rong, eat slowly.
Tell me which one you like.
I'll ask someone to pack some to your residence.
No need.
I can buy whatever I want.
Although Xu Muchen is not as rich as you,
he can afford desserts.
I heard
he got hurt in Pharmacy.
There was a fire in Pharmacy.
He went there with his men
and fell into the trap of the secret tunnel.
If I hadn't saved him,
he would have been dead now.
Did you get hurt?
My head was hit.
Nothing serious.
Your head was hit?
Don't do
such a dangerous thing again.
Xu Muchen is not worthy of your care.
Brother, don't say that.
Xu Muchen is my husband.
I can't just let him die.
Husband?
What kind of husband is he?
You should remember that you are a substitute,
not his real wife.
Rong.
Do you have feelings for Xu Muchen?
Brother, what are you talking about?
If Master and Senior heard what you said,
they would scold me heavily.
So you admit it?
I didn't. Don't talk nonsense.
I know what you mean.
You really know what I mean?
Yes.
You are my brother.
You care about me.
Yes, I'm your brother.
Rong.
I have something to do today.
I gotta go.
Which one do you like?
I'll ask someone to pack some to your residence.
By the way, Rong,
I was given some toys made in the neighboring country.
I can tell they are what girls like.
They are in the back room.
Go pick one.
Take what you like.
Okay, thank you.
Here you are.
Miss.
Young Master said
you could pick anything you liked on the table.
Why is there a logo of the Watermill?
Miss.
Have you found the one you like?
I like them all.
Wrap them up
and send them to my residence.
Yes, My Ladyship.
[Zichen Department]
Brother Chen was wrongfully imprisoned
before he set off to Taizhou.
There must be a backstage manipulator.
It seems that the manipulator
pertaining to the flood case
has done more than corruption.
Uncle Liu.
An initial investigation of Uncle Chen's case
has been carried out by the Zichen Department.
Please don't worry.
Although Uncle Chen is in custody,
he's safe now.
Lord Chen shouldn't have suffered.
I also found some clues
to the case of Hei Limao.
Hei Limao didn't get along well
with his younger brother at all.
Hei Limao even sold out his younger brother to the government
to protect himself.
So I think that suicide note
must be a misleading clue by the backstage manipulator.
I found this letter
in Hei Limao's residence.
[Kill all the corrupt officials in the world. I'd die without anything to regret after I avenge my brother's death.]
In that case,
the backstage manipulator forced Hei Limao to die
to cover up his evil purpose.
So the key to this case
is Lord Hu's ledger.
I have a guess about the ledger.
I'll let you know if there's news.
The flood
was the trigger of
both the cases of the Hu family and Lord Chen.
The person behind it is getting more and more unscrupulous.
You must be careful.
Don't let the evildoer take advantage of you.
Thank you, Uncle Liu.
I'll be careful.
I will find out the truth
and bring the culprit to justice.
[Xu's Mansion]
Why is there nothing
on the scroll Master gave me?
Who are you?
This is Xu's Mansion.
You can't enter without permission.
He Wei, stop!
The Ministry of Justice is ordered to search here.
Move!
How can the Ministry of Justice hit people?
Apologize!
Wu Zhao.
Wu Zhao, forget it.
Don't make trouble for Young Master.
Apologize!
What if I say no?
Wu Zhao.
As a constable of Zichen Department,
how dare you stop the investigation?
Xiao Qiu, step back!
Wu Zhao.
What happened?
Officials from the Ministry of Justice wanted to search the mansion.
They even hurt Xiao Qiu.
Take Xiao Qiu back to the mansion.
My Lord.
Go back.
I don't know why you
broke into my residence at night
and hurt my maid.
Lord Xu.
The Ministry of Justice received a tip-off
that Lord Xu might have something to do
with the missing map of the Ministry of War.
Under the order of the higher-ups,
we are here to search your mansion.
How dare you search my residence
without any solid evidence?
Is this how the Ministry of Justice works?
Xu Muchen.
The Ministry of Justice is searching for the missing map.
Anyone who stands in the way
will be considered as a suspect.
You'd better be sensible.
Do you have an order?
I wonder where the Ministry of Justice got the tip-off.
It's confidential.
Since you have the order,
I dare not disobey.
But you hurt my maid.
I will go to the Ministry of Justice to ask for an explanation.
If Lord Xu
has nothing to do with the missing map,
it's up to you
to go to the Ministry of Justice or not.
But if we find any clue here,
Lord Xu,
you have no choice but to go with us.
Search!
Yes.
Chen.
Search carefully!
Mother.
Chen.
What happened?
Nothing.
They probably got a wrong tip-off
so they're here for a routine check.
I'll ask them to speed up.
Darling.
They kept mentioning a map.
What is it?
It is a map drawn by every municipal government.
It is necessary for military operations.
The map is usually kept by the Ministry of War.
Even three Councilors are not allowed to see it.
Anyone who steals it
will be executed according to the law.
Who will be that crazy
to steal such an important thing?
The map is priceless and not tradable.
Ordinary gangs won't want it.
I guess it was not a thief
but a foreign spy who stole it.
My Lord.
My Lord, we found this.
Xu Muchen.
What is this?
I don't know.
This doesn't belong to me.
Guards!
My Lord.
This is silverstone powder
designed for decrypting secret letters from the Yue State.
Xu Muchen.
How dare you!
I told you
this didn't belong to me.
This is obviously a frame-up.
Mrs. Xu, what's your basis?
Because...
Lord Xu is really extraordinary.
You know the way to encrypt letters for the Yue State.
I guess you stole the map
to claim credit in the Yue State.
Arrest him.
Yes.
[Xu's Mansion]
[Jinxin Embroidery House]
Master.
I'll buy you some
beautiful hairpins.
Master.
Rong.
What's the matter?
Master.
Why is there a map
in Watermill's box?
What map? What box?
It's a box in the Duke's Mansion
with a map of the Jing Dynasty in it.
The Watermill hasn't put any box
in the Duke's Mansion.
And I know nothing about the map.
Who could it be?
Have a seat.
What on earth happened?
I found a box
at Jinning's residence.
There was a logo of the Watermill on it
and a blank scroll inside.
I thought it was a new task from Master,
so I took it back.
But why did the Ministry of Justice
come to search Xu's Mansion?
And how could they know that the blank scroll
was the map of the Jing Dynasty drawn in a secret way?
The map is related to the spy of Yue.
They arrested Xu Muchen
in the name of treason.
So you think
Xu Muchen was framed by the Watermill?
I dare not to doubt that.
I'm sure the Watermill won't collude with the Yue State.
There's no reason for the Watermill to frame Xu Muchen.
But...
Are we being used?
How dare you!
Rong.
Why are you so anxious
that Xu Muchen was arrested?
Because...
Because I haven't found the jade pendant yet.
If he gets caught,
I won't be able to complete the task you assigned to me.
Now you want to finish the task?
Why don't you finish it earlier?
Don't be sarcastic.
Stop it!
I promise you
the Watermill has nothing to do
with the map.
Rong.
Don't forget who you really are.
You're not Su Jinzhen.
Your marriage is just an expedient.
You need to come back sooner or later.
Don't fall in love with him.
[Vigor and High Spirits]
Rong.
Come here and have a seat.
What happened?
Anyone bullied you?
Xu Muchen was arrested.
Finally.
I knew he would be arrested one day.
What did he do?
It's my fault.
Who put the box of the Watermill
in your room yesterday?
Why was there a box of the Watermill
in my room?
[Vigor and High Spirits]
I don't know.
But Master said
the box didn't belong to the Watermill.
Then who put it?
Let me ask you.
Did you see anyone
put anything in the mansion yesterday?
Young Master.
No outsider came here yesterday.
I see. You may leave.
Yes, Young Master.
Rong.
If someone is good at martial arts like you
who can fly over the eaves
and walk on walls,
I don't think my servants
can notice him.
Who is trying to frame Xu Muchen?
Rong.
It's a good thing that Xu Muchen is arrested and imprisoned.
We can take this opportunity
to divorce him.
It's justifiable.
It won't ruin Zhen's reputation either.
No.
It was my fault.
I can't leave him alone now.
What are you going to do?
I must save him.
-My Lord. -My Lord.
My Lord.
Your father committed corruption,
while you
dare to collude with the enemy and betray the country.
Lord Xu.
You are more audacious than your father.
Nonsense!
The map is our military secret.
It's the key to the deployment.
Once it falls into the hands of the enemies,
our landscape
will be exposed
to them completely.
At that time,
the opponents will know every move we are going to make,
while we
will be like their prey.
Now Lord Xu planned to give the map to the Yue State.
Does that mean you want to give the whole country to them?
Lord Gongyang.
You're really silly.
You can't even notice this is a frame-up?
The evidence is solid.
It won't work even if you try to deny it.
[Diligence Hall]
What did His Majesty say?
Lord Xu is suspected of treason.
It's extremely serious.
His Majesty has made it clear
that the case must be investigated thoroughly.
The Ministry of Justice has been in charge.
Princess.
Please leave here.
I believe His Majesty
will clear my son's name.
But my son has been framed and imprisoned.
I'm really worried.
Sir.
Please ask a favor of His Majesty for me.
Let me see Muchen.
[Diligence Hall]
How could Young Master give the map
to the Yue State?
Who is trying to frame Young Master?
What should we do now?
If Young Master is convicted of treason,
he'll have no chance to survive.
Xiao Qiu, stop crying.
I feel even more upset when you cry.
Mother.
How is it?
I asked His Majesty for his grace.
Come with me to the prison of the Ministry of Justice tomorrow morning
to visit Muchen.
[Ministry of Justice]
Has Xu Muchen confessed?
He has been severely punished.
It might be hard for him to recover if the punishment continues.
We can't afford
if anything happens.
He's indeed tough.
My Lord.
We have arrested the spy from Yue who sneaked into our country.
Is he still alive?
Yes.
The spy wanted to take poison
but we stopped him.
Good job.
Where is he now?
He's in prison.
Xu Muchen is not willing to confess, right?
Let's see if his accomplice can endure the punishment.
Let's go.
Let's interrogate that spy now.