[English subtitles are available]
[My Wife is A Thief]
[Episode 4]
How do I play the next one?
What comes next?
Why did she stop?
Why did she stop playing?
What's going on?
What happened?
Why did she stop?
I broke the string
and changed it afterwards.
Could she tell?
What should I do?
That was great!
The music is echoing around the roof beams unceasingly.
Miss Zhen indeed possesses profound musical skills,
and lives up to her reputation.
Even if she's Duke Su's daughter,
there's no need to flatter her to this extent.
Exactly.
She's lying through her teeth.
Zhen.
Play.
Should I just say I don't know how to play?
No.
Wouldn't I be openly admitting that I'm a fake?
Why don't I play badly
and leave the problem to Madam Gongyang?
No.
I can't use the same method twice.
I wish I could find a hole in the ground and crawl into it.
Honey,
I'll tune it for you.
Old Madam.
Young Master came back from the administrative office.
Madam Gongyang, I wonder why
you brought this out-of-tune thing
to my residence?
I... I...
My wife hasn't played anything
and yet you said that the music is echoing around the roof beams.
Did you want my wife to take this
and ruin my reputation?
I definitely didn't mean it like that.
Since you gifted us this instrument
to celebrate our marriage,
I don't want to spoil the fun.
We'll play an evening song
as a return gift.
Okay.
We agreed on this rule.
To maintain our image as a couple when we're around other people.
♫Hands over the sadness♫
♫Tears fall like stars at that moment♫
Give me your hand.
Trust me.
♫The grass and trees seem weathered and worn too♫
♫We gaze at each other, distant as mountains and wide as rivers♫
♫When will old ones glance back?♫
♫In this worldly dance, parting brings so much bitterness♫
Not bad.
♫We can't be together♫
♫Yearning floods like a river♫
♫Who's right and who's wrong?♫
♫There's no right or wrong in this world♫
♫We're strangers, but we're on different sides♫
♫Amidst the tumult of life's fireworks♫
Go on.
♫I'll land on your heart even if I have to keep circling♫
♫Who made an honest mistake♫
♫The world is painful♫
♫Without you, what's the point of having the world in my hands♫
♫How long until we meet again?♫
♫I'd rather spend the rest of my life with you♫
♫The sea of love is too desolate♫
♫And life is full of ifs and maybes♫
♫The colorful clouds are like fragments♫
♫But I hope we'll be together in the end♫
♫When will old ones glance back?♫
♫In this worldly dance, parting brings so much bitterness♫
♫We can't be together♫
♫Yearning floods like a river♫
♫Who's right and who's wrong?♫
♫There's no right or wrong in this world♫
♫We're strangers, but we're on different sides♫
♫Amidst the tumult of life's fireworks♫
Sister Xu,
♫I'll land on your heart even if I have to keep circling♫
Muchen and Zhen are really a good-looking couple.
Look at them sitting there,
it's as if they walked out of a painting.
♫Who made an honest mistake♫
So beautiful.
♫The world is painful♫
That's right.
Yeah.
♫Without you, what's the point of having the world in my hands♫
Yes.
♫How long until we meet again?♫
♫I'd rather spend the rest of my life with you♫
Great!
That was great!
I didn't expect that
an untuned instrument
could produce
such a unique melody.
Exactly.
The evening song
not only evoked the beauty of the flowers and the full moon,
but also captured the harmony of the couple.
Madam Gongyang.
What do you think?
I'm happy to see that Chen and Zhen
are so well-matched.
Sister Xu,
you seem to be in a good mood.
You must be very lucky.
It's rare that we got together today.
My hands are itching.
Why don't we play two rounds,
and get some luck from Xu's Mansion?
Sure.
Yeah.
It's been a while.
Yes, my hands are itchy.
Sister Xu, play your hand.
Come on.
Don't rush me.
Mrs. Xu, play your hand.
Wait.
Tea.
Does mother have a grudge against mahjong?
No.
Family scandal.
6 Circles.
I win!
Wait.
My Pearl and Jade give me three dragon tiles,
so it's double the pot.
Madam Gongyang.
You are so lucky.
Thanks to my lucky bracelet.
I've never lost with it.
She's lost five rounds.
How long will this take?
3 Circles.
Do you want to take it?
Don't rush me. Wait.
How much is my husband's monthly salary?
She's losing almost 100 taels.
Look at Madam Gongyang's demeanor,
Old Madam can't refuse just like that.
Sister Xu,
it's been so long since we last played.
Yes.
No one is allowed to leave before dark.
Madams,
would you like some cakes?
-No, thanks.
-We don’t need that, we're playing.
Mother.
I think you must be tired after a long day.
How about I play a few rounds for you?
Zhen, you're so considerate.
It's just that I haven't seen them
and played with them for a long time.
I don't think it's good to leave now.
How about this?
I'll sit next to you and give you advice?
Is that appropriate?
Right?
Mother,
I'm not good at playing mahjong.
If I sit next to you,
I can only be a lousy advisor.
Let her sit.
It's rare for someone to be so filial.
Sit.
Come on.
Go.
Go to the side.
Hurry up.
Come, Zhen.
Sit here.
Okay.
This one.
Play this one.
Nine Characters.
Miss Su is so filial.
Six Characters.
Four Dots.
Take that one.
I won!
I drew the winning tile.
Pay up.
Hurry up.
Mrs. Xu.
-You finally won.
-You’re so lucky.
You are so lucky.
Mrs. Xu,
your luck changed.
Come on.
Well,
Zhen plays mahjong in Su's Mansion too?
Not very often.
I'm just lucky.
You sure are lucky then.
Yes.
You guys let me win.
That's what we should do.
Four Bamboos.
I drew the winning tile!
I won!
Pay up.
Another round?
Yes.
Sister Xu, your luck has really changed.
Come on.
Give it to me.
Once Zhen sat next to you,
your luck started to change.
This is great.
I drew the winning tile, I won.
This...
I won!
Three dragon tiles.
-Pay up.
-You won again.
Here.
You're amazing.
I won.
Thirteen Orphans.
Sister Xu is so lucky.
Yes.
I lost all my money.
I'm almost out, too.
Servants.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Where is the money?
Your Ladyship,
that's all we brought today.
Well,
let's end it here.
Let's go eat.
Let's go.
No way.
You think I don't have money?
I'll use this.
Madam Gongyang.
Your jewellery
is all pretty expensive.
We don't have anything to offer you.
Yes.
Let's call it a day.
Let's end it.
It's okay.
Madam Gongyang.
If you really want to play,
everything on your arm is too expensive.
That bracelet looks nice.
It's lucky,
but it should only be worth 10 taels.
Why don't you bet on that?
How can I bet on this bracelet?
This is my lucky bracelet.
Well...
Why don't we go eat then?
Let's eat.
Let's go.
Wait!
Wait, wait.
I'll put it down.
Is this bracelet too bright for me?
No.
It suits you perfectly.
Look at you guys. What's the rush?
You're leaving without eating,
Madam Gongyang.
I'm not eating.
My chest hurts a little.
Go home and have a good rest then.
Let's play again next time.
We'll have a good time.
[Live with integrity and purity]
We're leaving.
See you, Mrs. Xu.
Goodbye, Madam Gongyang.
Don't bring loose taels next time.
Notes will do.
I don't know what's wrong with my luck today.
Yeah.
238 taels.
How much?
238.
Zhen.
You really helped Mother
let out my anger today.
You won all these.
Take them.
No way.
This is too much.
Mother should be in charge of the money at home.
Take them.
Am I someone who covets my daughter-in-law's money?
We're a family.
Take them.
Do my words not work?
I told you to take them.
Mother.
This is really too much.
I have nowhere to spend this even if you give them to me.
If you really want to reward me,
you can give me some
jewellery that's not too valuable
or accessories
as a token of appreciation.
Chen really married a good wife.
I'll reward you.
I should.
These are all my mother's treasures.
Take a look,
pick whatever you like.
That's all?
Is there nothing you like?
No.
I just think these are all too expensive.
This one's solid gold.
This was my favorite when I was young.
Try it on.
Mother.
This is too ornate.
Only you can pull it off.
It doesn't look good on me.
What about this?
Pearls?
I don't think it's suitable for my age.
Well...
Then...
Mother,
don't you have
any simple jade
or jade pendants?
Did I ask too directly?
You like jade?
I do have some treasures hidden in the Treasure Pavilion.
Treasure Pavilion?
Yes.
Look.
[Treasure Pavilion]
It's specially kept in the Treasure Pavilion.
Maybe the jade pendant is inside.
These
are my most precious things.
But I can't give them to you now.
Work hard
and give the Xu family a grandson.
These will all be yours.
For now,
this solid gold one is not bad.
Take it.
Thank you, Mother.
[Elegant Residence in Spring Sunshine]
You want me to give birth to a fat grandson for you?
No way.
[Treasure Pavilion]
The jade pendant might be there.
I'll go now.
You're back.
Aren't you going to the study to read?
I'm done.
That in your hand, Mother gave it to you?
She wanted to give me all the money she won today.
That won't do. It's too much.
Then she gave me a piece of jewelry.
You played well.
I'm not very good.
I was just playing blindly.
Madam Gongyang's skills
are considered very good in the capital ladies' circles.
Today, you won her two months' worth.
Maybe I'm gifted in playing cards.
Then I'll play more
so I can win some personal money.
I don't think you're only gifted in playing cards.
Miss Su
is famous in the capital for your music skills.
Although Madam Gongyang's strings hadn't been tuned
and affected your performance,
But mine is fine.
Play a song.
We're a couple in name
in public
so it's fine if we had to play together.
Now that we're in private quarters,
it's not appropriate for us to play together, right?
Is it inappropriate or you can't play it at all?
At the Spring Banquet today,
you already knew I couldn't play.
Now, you still want to make me play.
You just want to humiliate me.
Yes.
I can't play it.
Not only can I not play this,
I can't do music, chess, calligraphy and painting.
Although I'm Duke Su's daughter,
I've been on the road since I was a child.
I was brought back by my father only when I was 12.
I didn't learn music, chess, calligraphy or painting.
I can't even read.
I learned it slowly after I grew up.
My famous music skills
were all created by my father
so that no one would look down on me.
Are you satisfied now?
Are you disappointed?
You think I don't deserve you?
No, I...
I didn't mean that.
You just want to divorce me.
He's indeed suspecting me.
Got it.
Sorry.
The bed is my territory.
You've crossed the line.
Rest early then.
That was close.
Looks like I can't go to the Treasure Pavilion today.
[Zichen Department]
Come, let's eat.
Coming.
Not bad.
The food is good.
Yes.
Good morning, My Lord.
Morning.
Wait, I'll take another one.
Still eating?
He's eating a lot.
Good morning, My Lord.
Morning.
-Morning, My Lord.
-Help yourself.
Wu Zhao.
Bring me a pot of tea.
Okay.
My Lord, why are you here today?
My wedding leave's already passed.
Can't I work?
Of course you can.
But you can't go home
even if you want to go home today.
There's a big case?
It's more troublesome than a major case.
Today, the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom is coming to the capital.
The mission of escorting him
has been assigned to us by Honglusi Department.
The safety of foreign envoys
in our country is a serious matter.
This concerns the relationship between the two states.
If we guard him properly
and nothing happens,
we just did our job.
If we don't guard him well and something happens,
it will be a big problem.
To put it bluntly,
this is a hot potato.
Don't worry.
My Lord.
[Prosperity for the nation, peace for the people]
It seems that the Nanxiang Kingdom has been sending envoys to Jing Dynasty
pretty frequently in recent years.
[Wuxing Building]
We must be close.
Who knows?
Don't forget that 5 years ago,
we went to war with each other.
Of course.
Although we are in contact now
and harmonious,
[Wuxing Building]
maybe
we'll get into a fight.
You're right.
Entering the downtown area.
Everyone, be alert.
Yes.
Come in, please.
Play a few rounds.
You're here.
[Metal]
Goodbye, sir.
Sir, two of you?
Please come in.
You're so unlucky.
[Metal]
Sir.
Please come in.
Play a few rounds.
Please, my lord.
[Inn]
My lord.
Please.
[Verdant summer hills]
-My lord.
My lord.
You must be tired
from all that traveling.
There's food, wine and hot water inside.
Have a good rest.
Tomorrow at Honglusi,
we'll welcome you officially.
Okay, thank you.
[Verdant summer hills]
By the way,
I'm a little tired.
I'm going to bed after dinner.
Tonight, if there's nothing important,
don't disturb me.
Wu Zhao.
Tell our men to keep a close eye
and protect the envoy.
My Lord, don't worry.
I've arranged everything.
Stay alert.
Don't let your guard down.
It's already evening.
Why isn't Chen coming home yet?
Old Madam!
Wu Zhao just sent a letter saying that
Young Master is on night duty at Zichen Department today
and won't be coming back.
Why is he on duty all of a sudden?
Doesn't he know he should come home to daughter-in-law?
Go get him.
Mother, don't worry.
My husband must have his reasons.
Did he say why he was on night duty all of a sudden?
The envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom came to the capital.
They are in charge of security.
That's a big deal.
A man should focus on his career.
As his wife, I shouldn't be a burden.
Xiao Qiu,
send a lunch box to Zichen Department later.
They can't go hungry on night duty.
Sure, Young Madam.
It's hard to find
such an understanding and considerate daughter-in-law.
This silly boy is lucky.
I'm just afraid that you, Xu Muchen, won't be on night duty.
I haven't got a chance to go to the Treasure Pavilion.
My Lord.
Aren't we on night duty together?
Are you tired?
Go back if you're tired.
I'm not tired.
Xiao Qiu!
Why are you here?
Young Madam was afraid that Young Master would be hungry tonight,
so she asked me to bring some food.
She's afraid that I'd be hungry?
I treated her like that yesterday
yet she's still concerned about me today.
Did she really ask you to send it?
Xu Muchen.
What are you talking about?
How could you say that?
If it's not from Young Madam, who would've sent it?
Come on.
I'll eat if you're not hungry.
Who said I'm not eating?
Look at you.
Thank her for me.
Yes.
Do I get any?
Of course.
Thank you.
Lord Gu, why don't you have one too?
You really ate it?
It's good to be young.
Xiao Qiu.
It's good.
Thank you, Lord Gu.
The weather is dry,
beware of fire.
You just want to divorce me.
Yesterday, I suspected her for no reason
and made her angry.
But she even gave me snacks today.
At the end of the day,
what happened in the last life has nothing to do with her.
Even if I have no feelings for her,
I should be more polite.
[Verdant summer hills]
[Elegant Residence in Spring Sunshine]
Young Madam.
Young Master's lunch box has been delivered.
Where is Young Madam?
This was supposed to be a tribute to His Majesty.
I hope you can sell it at a good price this time.
Don't worry.
What about last time?
We've prepared the money.
Have some tea inside.
I'll get it now.
Who are you?
[Xu's Mansion]
[Elegant Residence in Spring Sunshine]
Xiao Qiu. Xiao Qiu?
Xiao Qiu.
Young Madam.
You're finally back.
Where did you go
in the middle of the night?
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
My husband is not around, so I couldn't sleep
so I went to the garden to relax.
I understand.
This is what they call "a day apart
feels like three autumns", isn't it?
Why are you here
in the middle of the night?
After Young Master received your lunch box,
he was so touched that he cried.
He solemnly asked me
to convey to you
his gratitude and joy.
I was entrusted with such a great task.
Even if I die sleeping here today,
I must convey this beautiful love
to you.
In a tale of such profound love between two lovers,
my name, Xiao Qiu, must have a place.
Thanks.
[Verdant summer hills]
My lord.
My lord, are you awake?
[Be Righteous and Enforce the Law]
I fell asleep again.
I haven't worked all night for a long time.
Wu Zhao.
Why are you making such a ruckus
in the morning?
You're disrupting my dream.
It's been hard on you two.
You slept the whole night,
so you must be tired.
Look at this young man. Can't seem to say anything nice, huh?
Sleeping is a good thing,
as it means things are peaceful.
Is peace not good?
That's right.
Go get some water.
Report!
Report.
My Lord.
There was a fire in the Treasure Pavilion last night.
The Treasure Pavilion was on fire?
If the Treasure Pavilion was on fire, go find the defense officers.
The defense officers said,
after they put out the fire,
they found someone dead inside.
Someone died?
Who is it?
My Lord, bad news!
My Lord.
The envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom is missing.
According to the defense officers,
the victim is
the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom.
He's totally unrecognizable.
My Lord.
[Order]
This was found on the victim.
Yes.
That's right.
This is the token of the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom.
Oh no.
Everything is over.
Manager Zhou. Manager Zhou,
calm down.
How about this?
You can start by detailing what happened that day.
The Nanxiang Kingdom often sends envoys here.
Each time, they offer a lot of tributes.
The envoy would always
keep several treasures for himself
and ask me to help him convert them into money.
This time, as per usual,
I dealt with his gifts as I always do.
I went to get the money I got last time
to give it to him.
As soon as I got back, I realized that a fire had broken out.
As soon as I realized there was a fire,
I brought my men
and rushed in to save the envoy.
B-B-But...
The fire was too strong.
We had no choice but to escape.
Wasn't there anyone else there?
The envoy arrived at night,
and no one else was here.
If the one who died is really the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom,
Mu Chen, do you think
I should just visit His Majesty,
and ask to retire early and return home?
There hasn't been a fire in the Treasure Pavilion in years.
Why did something happen at the very moment the envoy arrived?
My Lord. My Lord.
This was found in the ruins.
This is a Willow Leaf Dart.
Could this be
the work of the Willow Leaf Thief Liu?
This...
Willow Leaf Thief Liu only steals things and never kills.
Why did they kill the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom?
Why did they burn down the Treasure Pavilion?
It's them.
The murderer is Willow Leaf Thief Liu.
As a thief,
what reason do they need to
do things like murder and arson?
My Lord.
My Lord!
My Lord, please help!
Manager Zhou.
I can't take the blame for such a huge crime
as murdering an envoy.
Manager Zhou, get up first.
Help me! Help me!
Manager Zhou. Manager Zhou.
Get up and talk. Get up.
Let me tell you.
If the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom
really died,
I'd be in trouble too.
How about this?
Let's trust Xu, okay?
There are too many things that are suspicious in this case.
Judging from the current evidence,
we can't be sure that the deceased
is the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom.
Let's wait for the autopsy
before we come to any conclusion.
Well said.
Your analysis is perfect.
Just follow your train of thought and investigate this.
The rest of our lives
depend on you.
I...
Do you have wine?
I need to calm down.
Get two pots, two pots.
Let's go.
Come on.
[Piles of gold and jade]
Lord Gongyang.
If it isn't Lord Xu!
Why was the Ministry of Justice alerted to
a small matter like a store fire?
Muchen, you did well.
You arrived even earlier than the Ministry of Justice
to protect the scene.
I appreciate it.
The 12 districts outside the palace
are under the Zichen Department's jurisdiction.
What does it have to do with the Ministry of Justice?
The store fire
obviously has nothing to do with the Ministry of Justice,
but what about the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom?
You're the Ministry of Justice indeed.
You are well informed.
After all, the safety of the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom
is a matter of diplomatic relations
and the fate of the people of both countries.
The Ministry of Justice naturally has to
put in tons of effort,
unlike some government officials
who can't even protect one person
and made the envoy
lose his life in front of the Emperor.
Lord Gongyang, tread carefully.
We can't jump to conclusions
about the life or death of the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom yet.
We can't jump to conclusions yet?
Weren't you guys supposed to protect him?
Where is he now?
The Zichen Department will find the envoy as soon as possible
and find out the truth.
It’s a pity that you don’t have the chance.
The Nanxiang Kingdom case has reached the Emperor
and His Majesty is furious.
He ordered the Ministry of Justice to investigate this case thoroughly.
From now on, the Zichen Department
is not allowed to intervene in this case.
Please hand over the evidence.
Men!
Yes.
[Xu's Mansion]
It's already morning.
Why isn't Chen back yet?
Does he still care about this family?
He must be delayed by something.
Bad news! Bad news!
The envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom was killed.
Wu Zhao said
Young Master may be suspended.
Suspended?
That Willow Leaf Thief Liu killed the Nanxiang Kingdom envoy.
The wanted posters are up.
The Willow Leaf Thief Liu actually killed someone.
In the storybook,
[Bounty on arrest]
didn't they say she's a righteous thief?
You believe what's written in the storytelling script?
I don't know how much it's been embellished.
The was pasted by the Ministry of Justice.
How could it be fake?
She dared to kill the Nanxiang Kingdom envoy.
This Willow Leaf Thief Liu is really lawless.
Yes.
I heard that
this Willow Leaf Thief Liu is a woman.
A woman?
I heard that she is 8 feet tall,
is really strong.
and is extremely ugly.
If anyone sees her in the middle of the night,
they would be scared to death.
She looks so scary?
Do you think this Willow Leaf Thief Liu
is too ugly
and can't get married,
so that's why she went out to kill?
We have to be careful.
If we run into the Willow Leaf Thief Liu,
it's better to be killed
than to be dragged back to be her husband.
That would be terrible.
You've never seen Willow Leaf Thief Liu.
How could you say that about her?
Why not?
Tell me.
Whose daughter would
be a thief?
They have to get married and take care of the family.
Only someone like her
whom nobody wants
would go sneaking around.
Exactly.
Yes, you are right.
Now she even dared to kill the envoy of the Nanxiang Kingdom.
In my opinion,
she's trying to start a war between the two states
to torment the people!
How vicious!
Yes.
I'm going home.
It's not safe outside.
Let's go.
[Catch-and-kill order] [Bounty on arrest]
[Pharmacy]
Why is Master in such a hurry to see me?
Is anything the matter?
To be honest, I don't know.
Look,
she asked Mumu to come back too.
Senior is back?
Let's go find her.
Great!
Bravo! Bravo!
Who else?
Me! Me! Me!
You, come here.
Okay.
Are you okay?
How is it?
Senior,
you've gone too far.
That's right.
That's too much.
Yeah.
What's wrong?
I'm doing this for his own good.
Master said
you have to train like you're on a mission.
You can't be distracted.
You were a little heavy-handed, no?
-Yeah.
-Exactly.
Yes.
I have more.
Do you want to try?
Go! Go!
Don't be afraid. Junior.
I'll try.
Come on, Junior.
Come on! Come on!
We support you.
Come on, Junior.
Come on! Come on!
Junior. Junior, are you okay?
Are you okay, Junior?
How is it?
Junior,
is this all you've got?
Junior, are you alright?
Mumu.
Why did you hit so hard?
What?
She's the one who has inferior skills.
How do you figure this?