[English subtitles are available]
[My Wife is A Thief]
[Episode 11]
Here, Rong.
Drink more hangover soup
so that you won't have a headache tomorrow morning.
I'm not Willow Leaf Thief Liu anymore.
Why should I carry out the mission?
I want a divorce!
Rong.
Why do I feel like...
You're mad at Xu Muchen?
Why would I be mad at him?
I have been robbed of my title.
Can't I be mad?
You are you.
No one can take your title away from you.
My head hurts. I'm so sleepy.
You should leave now.
Rest early.
I'll close the door for you.
[Treasure Sincerity, Embrace Excellence]
Young Master.
What is it?
Lord Xu is here.
Xu Muchen?
You may leave.
Yes, Young Master.
You came just in time.
Lord Xu, you're really busy tonight.
What?
Even visiting the brothel couldn't satisfy you,
and you still want to have some fun at my humble house?
I went to the brothel for business.
I understand.
You're a man.
How could you not have some official business
to discuss at the brothels?
Where's Zhen?
I’m here to take her home.
No need.
Zhen is sleeping well here.
If you can't sleep alone,
there are plenty of girls in Liufang Pavilion.
Brother,
Zhen has married me.
It's inappropriate for her
to stay at your place all the time.
You finally got the point.
If she can't stay out as your wife,
what about she divorces you?
What?
Divorce.
We got married per our parents' wishes, and as arranged by the matchmaker.
We can't divorce casually.
You're not very good-looking.
In terms of status,
you're just a low-ranking official of Zichen Department.
How much can you earn?
In terms of background,
you were the son of a sinner who survived out of luck.
Zhen's marriage to you
is like a fresh flower being inserted into cow dung.
How dare you go to the brothel?
What?
Shouldn't she divorce you?
Where is Zhen?
Let her come out and talk to me face to face.
She doesn’t want to see you.
Guards!
See the guest out.
[Su's Residence]
So funny.
It's already a great blessing
for a low-ranking official from Zichen Department
to marry our lady.
How dare he not cherish it
and go to the brothel?
Exactly.
Why doesn't he look into the mirror
and see what he is like?
[Elegant Residence in Spring Sunshine]
Didn't I sleep at Brother's house last night?
Why am I back?
I carried you back.
You...
You carried me back?
Well.
Did you forget the rules?
Did you ask for my permission?
How dare you carry me here and there?
This is your home.
You are my wife.
You should live here.
I don't want to be your wife anymore.
Let's divorce.
I don't agree.
Why?
You wanted a divorce before.
Why do you disagree now?
What about you?
You didn't want to divorce before.
Why do you want to divorce now?
You went to the brothel.
Why can't I ask for a divorce?
I went to the brothel to investigate a case.
To investigate a case?
You have so many excuses.
Listen to me...
Don't come over.
This is my territory.
Back off!
I've figured it out.
I don't want to waste time with you.
I don't want to play the game of of being a fake couple.
The sooner we get a divorce, the earlier I can be free.
Do you really think so?
I won't force you to stay married with me.
But divorce is a big deal.
We have to let our parents know.
And my mother likes you very much.
If she suddenly finds out that we're going to divorce,
I'm afraid she can't take it.
Let's think about it.
Fine.
I'll do it for your mother's sake.
Don't drink alone.
Pour me a cup too.
I'm thirsty.
Don't move.
Why are you so mad about me going to the brothel?
[Notice]
My Lord.
I'd like to take the afternoon off.
Where are you going?
I want to buy something.
What are you going to buy?
To buy some cosmetics to cheer Xiao Qiu up.
What did you say?
I want to buy some cosmetics...
No, the second half.
To cheer Xiao Qiu up.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Well.
Why do you want to go with me?
[Pharmacy]
Isn't this Mrs. Xu?
What
brings you here?
Master.
About the title...
You've caused a lot of trouble for Watermill.
How dare you want your title back?
Master.
I have nothing to do with Lord Hu's case.
I've helped Zichen Department catch the murderer.
They can prove it.
You want Zichen Department to prove it for you?
Do you remember
you're a disciple of Watermill?
I once told you
your most important task is to find the jade pendant.
But not only did you fail to complete the mission,
but you acted on your own
and caused trouble one after another.
If Mumu didn't help you this time,
how would you end up?
I was careless.
Senior, thank you for your help.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that.
Maybe Xu Muchen
would let you off the hook
considering your marriage.
You...
What?
All right.
Master.
Rong acted recklessly
for the image
of Willow Leaf Thief Liu.
Besides,
with Mumu being out there to assist,
no big trouble will be caused.
Rong.
Your priority now
is to find the jade pendant
and get out of there safely.
Mumu.
You still need to keep Gongyang under control
to prevent him from causing more trouble.
Yes.
Master.
I'll go back to the Embroidery House and arrange it.
I searched everywhere in Xu's Mansion,
but I couldn't find it.
Maybe the jade pendant
is not in the mansion.
Things are hidden away by people.
Your aimless search is like looking for a needle in a haystack.
Why don't you search it on people?
To search it on people?
Junior.
This is the potion I've developed
over the past few days.
It's called True Heart.
Just pour it into Xu Muchen's wine.
When he gets drunk,
more or less, his true thoughts
will be exposed.
Senior, you're amazing.
What secret can't I get
with such an amazing potion?
More or less.
It's just "more or less".
However,
it also depends on the respondent's willpower
and the guidance of the questioner.
Anyway, be flexible.
Whose family is this young master from?
He's so handsome.
Exactly.
What a handsome young man.
Thank you for your compliment.
Excuse me.
Please make way.
Get out of the way.
My Lord.
I can do it myself.
Why do you have to come with me?
Now that you're here, you are also not helping me make a selection.
I don't know about this.
Pick quickly.
Let me have a look when you're done.
My Lords, welcome.
Help yourself.
We have products of all price points
and all kinds of styles.
Ma'am.
Do you have any recommendations?
Yes.
Come in. They're all inside.
Come on.
Ma'am.
Didn't you say you have recommendations?
The front row consists of the best-selling ones.
But you two...
This one. This is a new design.
And this.
And this. Try them all.
Which one do you think looks better?
I don't know about these, either.
As for rouge,
you have to try it on your face
before you know if it fits.
Which one of you wants to apply it?
Not for us.
Ma'am, go ahead.
We'll take a look on our own.
Okay, you guys go ahead.
I'll leave you alone.
How can we try it on?
We can't ask Xiao Qiu to come.
I can't believe they have such a fetish.
I'm an imperial official.
It's inappropriate for me
to apply the rouge in public.
An imperial official
came to buy cosmetics on duty.
It's inappropriate.
How about this?
You resign.
Don't come to Xu's Mansion again.
And don't see Xiao Qiu anymore.
But I'm willing to try it on
for you.
Look at this side of my face.
Do I need to try again?
How is it?
You're too dark.
But My Lord, you're white.
I've decided.
I'll take this one.
Ma'am.
Two boxes of this.
Okay.
Darling.
You're back.
Have a seat.
Let me pour you some tea.
Actually,
I've reflected on myself today.
I didn't listen to you a few days ago.
I went down the mountain
and got mad at you.
It was my fault.
So I
prepared some dishes
as an apology.
I don't think it'll work.
It doesn't suit my temperament.
Xu Muchen.
Although you left me
alone in the mountains
which was an inhumane action,
I'm broad-minded.
How about this?
After you drink this,
I'll forgive you.
Not really.
Wu Zhao.
It's been almost a day.
Why don't you remove the rouge on your face?
Why remove it?
I must let Xiao Qiu see it.
I did this for her.
For her?
What if she sees you like this?
She will be so touched
and fell in love with me deeply.
Young Master.
Give this rouge
to Young Madam later.
She must be happy.
Nonsense.
Did I say I would give it to her?
Did you buy this rouge
for yourself?
Or is there another girl out...
Stop analyzing blindly.
Go send the rouge.
Xiao Qiu.
Why are you here?
Wu Zhao.
Which brothel did you go fooling around in again?
I didn't.
Brothel.
Fooling around.
The opening is inappropriate.
I did apply it myself.
Didn't you say you ran out of rouge a few days ago?
I happened to pass by a rouge shop today.
So I selected a box for you.
To try this rouge...
Didn't you say
you ran out of rouge?
I happened to...
Just to show you...
No.
Zhen didn't say that a few days ago.
Is it okay?
You remember that?
How can I forget about your things?
It sounds so frivolous.
You're glib-tongued.
It smells good.
Right?
How is it? Do you like it?
I picked it carefully.
It was carefully selected by me.
You picked this shade for me?
Do you know what the shade is called?
It's called Nine Hells Banana Pink.
-Banana Pink.
-Doesn’t the name...
Sound good?
It's from a famous poem.
The passing of time easily leaves people behind,
making the cherries red and the bananas green.
This shade will make people
look pale,
like dying men.
Wu Zhao.
You picked this shade for me?
What do you mean?
Well, Xiao Qiu.
Young Master picked this for me.
You're so good at shirking responsibility.
You just said you picked it.
I'll kill you today.
Come back!
Xiao Qiu.
-Stop!
-Listen to me!
-It’s really Young Master who picked it.
-Wu Zhao.
Such an ugly shade.
This Wu Zhao...
What does he mean?
How could you
pick this shade for me?
What's wrong?
Who made you angry?
It's Wu Zhao.
He said he picked a rouge for me.
This is what he picked.
Young Madam.
Do you think he believes I'm so ugly
that I only deserve this color?
Is it ugly?
I think the shade is not bad.
Not bad?
Let me apply it and show you.
Do I look good?
I'm speechless.
How could he pick this shade?
Young Madam, let me tell you.
As girls,
we can care nothing else.
But in terms of cosmetics
and clothes,
we can't compromise.
A man who gives you this shade of rouge as a gift
can never
be accepted.
[Xu's Mansion]
I cooked all these.
They're just so-so.
Please don't mind.
Thank you.
Before dinner,
let me give you a toast.
It was awkward
that I sent you white chrysanthemums.
It's my fault.
I apologize.
Since the misunderstanding has been resolved,
I would say it was not your fault.
Even if it wasn't my fault,
I caused the misunderstanding.
If you don't drink this cup of wine,
I will feel bad.
I feel so guilty.
I thought it over and over again. I thought...
Cheers.
This is the potion I've developed
after these days.
It's called True Heart.
Just pour it into Xu Muchen's wine.
When he gets drunk,
more or less, his true thoughts
will be exposed.
I wonder if it works.
I need to test him first.
You can't just drink.
Have some dishes.
Try this.
Okay.
How is it?
Delicious.
It's delicious.
This dish is so salty but he says it's delicious.
Looks like he didn't take enough of the potion.
I'm making the second toast
because you left me alone in the mountains.
But I'm broad-minded.
After you drink this,
I'll forgive you.
This is called using a cup of wine to resolve grievances.
Okay.
Using a cup of wine to resolve grievances.
He drank two cups.
It should be effective.
You can't just drink.
Have some dishes.
Try this.
How is this one?
It's a little...
Not bad.
It's good.
It's so spicy.
But he's still not telling the truth.
The third cup...
-Honey.
-Is…
I can't drink as much as you thought.
Let's take a break.
What if the potion efficacy wears off after a break?
Yes.
We need to take a break.
I just
killed her mood, didn't I?
But this is too important.
The misunderstanding has been resolved,
and the suspicion has been eliminated.
Let's have a drink
and get along with each other.
Right?
She is giving me an out.
I need to drink this.
Let's get along well.
I told you not to just drink.
Have some dishes.
Try this.
It tastes terrible.
What did I say?
The potion is taking effect.
Darling.
Honey.
Do you have any secrets?
Secrets?
She still remembers the time I went to the brothel?
Yes.
What secret?
For example, something so precious
that can't be given away easily.
Yes.
Where is it?
What is this?
You said the wrong line.
You should ask me
which brothel I went to fool around in.
I didn't.
Then you should ask me,
"What is this?
Did you apply it yourself?"
You did apply it yourself.
A few days ago,
you said you ran out of rouge.
I happened to pass by the rouge shop today,
so I specially picked one for you.
When... When did I say that?
How could I forget about your things?
You should ask me for the rouge.
Can you give me the rouge?
I carefully selected it for you.
See if you like it.
A man who gives you this shade of rouge as a gift
can never
be accepted.
But why is this rouge so precious
and can't be given away easily?
Wu Zhao gave it to Xiao Qiu.
Xiao Qiu was unhappy.
I don't want you to be unhappy.
You... You don't want me to be unhappy?
I always made you angry.
I was wrong.
Why?
Because I've fallen in love with you.
Why is he talking about that?
I have to find out where the jade pendant is.
Have a seat, Darling.
Let's sit down.
If you want to make me happy,
you can give me something I like.
Like jewelry,
or small pendants.
For another example...
Another example, a jade pendant.
Okay.
What jade pendant do you want?
The precious ones
that are kept for a long time.
Or the ones
given by your father.
My disobedient mouth
said the wrong thing again.
Are you alright?
I miss my father.
Well...
I'm sorry.
I'm a little drunk.
I need to go back to sleep.
Well...
Why are you leaving?
Why are you lying down?
You just had a few drinks.
You want to pretend to sleep?
No way.
Get up.
Xu Muchen.
Get up and drink three more cups.
You're not getting up?
Are you getting up or not?
Are you really asleep?
So fast?
Did I put too much potion?
Senior Moyan was so careless.
He didn't tell me the dosage.
Not only did I fail to get the truth out,
but will it make him die?
Father.
I'm here.
Good boy.
I've got a son after drinking with him.
It's not a loss.
You're good-looking.
But as a man,
why did you apply the rouge?
Let Daddy remove it for you.
Father!
Let go!
I miss you.
Why are you acting so miserably?
My father is gone too.
You're awake.
Why are you here?
Why am I here?
I fell asleep here last night.
Then why did you keep...
What?
Don't get me wrong.
I didn't want to hold you.
You were drunk yesterday
and kept holding on to me.
Do you think I want to sleep here?
Impossible.
I don't remember I was drunk.
Try to recall it.
Last night,
you were so drunk and crying.
Recall what you did.
I remember you said to use a cup of wine to resolve grievances
and let's get along well in the future.
Yes, after that?
You don't remember, do you?
You can't even stand
three cups.
Don't be so confident anymore.
Did I do anything when I was drunk?
You want to know?
Guess.
What time is it?
Why don't you go to Zichen Department?
I took a leave from Lord Gu today.
So I won't go.
What's your plan today?
I...
Logically speaking,
you finally don't have to work,
and you drank too much last night,
I should stay with you.
But I promised Xiao Qiu yesterday
to buy storybooks with her.
I'll have to leave you
to take care of yourself.
Here.
Okay.
Thank you, Darling.
Well,
let me ask you something.
Go ahead.
Did you see a box of rouge?
Rouge?
You mean this?
Yes.
You carefully selected this one
and gave it to me as a gift.
How can I return it to you?
I have to use it properly.
I've never seen such a beautiful shade.
Well.
Stop standing here.
I need to change.
If Rong uses the rouge,
she would definitely want to divorce me.
I need to find a way to make up for it.
My Lord,
our men of the Zichen Department are ready.
Tomorrow at 7 p.m.,
Liufang Pavilion will be a trap.
Good.
My Lord.
I'll go back if there's nothing else.
Wait.
Have a seat.
What's the matter, My Lord?
Li from the Zichen Department
told me yesterday
his wife had a quarrel with him
and wanted to divorce him.
He asked me how to stop his wife.
Which Li?
The one you rarely see.
Li has asked you for advice.
He must like his wife very much.
What do you mean by likes?
It's not serious at all.
Husband and wife should respect each other
and grow old together.
They can't just divorce each other like that.
Right?
Yes.
Did Li do
something wrong
or go somewhere he shouldn't have gone?
It's unavoidable for us from the Zichen Department
to go to some inappropriate places.
But it's all for our missions.
We're sacrificing ourselves for noble causes.
Yes.
That makes sense.
It's just that when the wife found out...
Well...
Did Li explain to his wife?
He did.
But she didn't believe it.
How is that possible? Young Madam is so...
Mrs. Li likes Li so much.
Really?
When you just got married,
Young Madam was so enthusiastic about you.
I saw that.
You must be too cold to her
and make her sad.
Is that so?
There's another possibility.
What is it?
My Lord.
I still have a pill called Butterfly's Love here.
Do you want to try it?
Why should I?
We are talking about Li.
Yes, Li.
If you ask me, My Lord,
you should...
No, I mean Li.
It's not enough to just give gifts.
He should also
show his manliness.
Why is she leaving?
I haven't finished yet.
Women
also lack a sense of security.
You should stay with her more.
Even if you're not by her side,
you need to report
your schedule to her all the time.
Let me report to you.
I need to go to the study to work.
Does Senior's potion have such strong side effects?
Did it harm his brain?
Honey.
Eat this.
Here.
You finally look like a husband.
Enough.
Thank you, Darling.
Does he think
his wife's death is more dignified than divorce
so he wants to stuff me to death?
Women can't stand gifts.
If Li prepares a gift with care
for his wife,
I'm sure his wife will be happy.
Do you like it?
Is he testing me?
Why did you give me this?
How can you give this as a gift to a girl?
It's ominous.
This is my favorite item that I've kept for years.
I'm giving it to you as a gift.
So weird.
Women
need tender care.
Your care for her
should be demonstrated in every detail
of life.
This is...
Mother asked you to send it here?
Let me have a taste.
Why are you smiling?
Luckily you've got a good mother.
Take it in.