Boss.
Director Tang invites you over for dinner when you're free.
What a fake display of family affection.
Exactly.
They clearly saw we absorbed the Hong Gang
and now they're eager for a piece of the pie.
Good thing you made arrangements in advance, Boss.
They'll only find old ledgers
and a pile of worthless junk.
Oh, right.
The Huo family sent a message.
They said the measurements for the formal attire
were lost by their servants.
They're asking if you could go to the tailor shop again
to get measured in person.
Just to try on clothes?
Do I really need to go there myself?
Alright then.
I'll tell the second young lady
to figure it out herself.
By the way,
you asked me to investigate her.
She was indeed raised by fishermen.
However...
However what?
That family didn't treat her well.
She was often beaten and scolded.
Her life was quite miserable.
Did I ask you to find out if she had a hard life?
What I want to know is
why she's come back with such calculation
and what her true intentions are.
If you're suspicious of the Second Miss,
why let her get involved with the engagement party?
Aren't you afraid she'll sabotage it?
It's better to keep dangerous things close where you can watch them.
That's all. You may go now.
Second Miss, this is the pipa.
The First Miss specifically asked you to take it for maintenance.
She wants to play it herself on the day of the banquet.
Please be careful.
This pipa
was left by the madam for the young miss.
The young miss's skill
truly lives up to her mother's teaching.
Don't damage it.
This is mother's favorite pipa.
It's fine.
Here.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Let me try it.
Our young miss doesn't like the pipa.
The madam's musical skills were wasted.
Who would have thought a new miss would come
who has such a connection with the madam.
Unfortunately, this new miss...
Actually...
Well...
Oh no!
Miss, are you alright?
It was perfectly fine.
How could you?
This is the young miss's favorite pipa.
What happened?
Oh!
Young miss, please don't worry.
I'll have someone replace the strings right away.
You did that on purpose.
Yes. I don't like it.
I'm not happy.
Do you know
every string was tuned by my mother herself,
every crack was repaired by her own hands?
Go kneel in the ancestral hall
and apologize to my mother.
A fake heiress
actually treating someone else's mother as her own.
What did you say?
I said
I'll go.
Hand it over.
Mr. Wen, you're here.
Please.
When you broke into my warehouse that day,
you weren't this polite.
Mr. Wen knew I was from the Huo family,
but deliberately didn't mention you're the Huo family's son-in-law.
Didn't you just want to see my surprised reaction?
Since you're my brother-in-law,
I should naturally be more polite.
Your time is valuable.
Let's begin.
I'm scared.
I'll do it myself.
If you're thirsty,
I can pour you some water.
That won't be necessary.
Who knows if you'll put something in my drink.
What did you do to me?
Brother-in-law,
are you afraid?
Thank you,
brother-in-law.
Boss, what's wrong?
Something serious has happened.
Get up.
Let's go.
Later,
I escaped.
Hello.
Okay.
I slept under bridges
and fought with stray dogs for spoiled food.
When I was twelve,
I learned to stage accidents and steal wallets.
Stop!
Don't run!
When the patrol officer's baton came down,
I didn't shed a single tear.
But every time
whenever I closed my eyes,
I would see you letting go of my hand.
Mom, help me!
Jiayu.
Huoran.
Mom!
But it doesn't matter.
Now that I'm back,
I won't give up easily.
Sister,
since that marriage arrangement is what matters most to you,
I'll destroy it.
Something terrible has happened!
There's trouble.
Song Jiayu.
Damn it!
If we let this slide,
others will surely look down on us.
Where would the Huo family put their face?
But if we don't tolerate it,
the Dragon Tiger Gang and Tang Jing will both harm the Huo family.
Such a simple logic,
don't you understand?
Don't think I'll treat you like my real daughter.
If you lose your usefulness,
you know the consequences.
Hmph!
Mother,
when you abandoned me,
did you ever think
that one day I would return to this house?
Is Huo Ran really that wonderful,
so wonderful that for her sake
you would abandon your own daughter?
Do you want to hear
how I've survived all these years?
Back then, when the train broke down.
I was all alone
wandering through the wilderness.
Later I passed out from fear.
Fortunately,
there was a fishing village nearby.
A passing fisherman rescued me.
But to my surprise,
he immediately sold me to traffickers
for just one bag of brown rice.
How about it? Can you add a bit more?
A little fool like this
is only worth this much.