= Love Like The Galaxy=
=Episode 34=
Does it still hurt?
It doesn't.
I'm sure you've heard about
my parents' divorce.
But don't worry.
I just want you to meet my mother
before we are engaged.
In the future,
both of you
don't have to see each other often.
I am never afraid.
Your mother is just sick
but she is not at fault.
The one at fault
is the person who ruined her life.
Marquis Chengyang is nice to me
but I am cold against him.
Everyone says
I am cruel.
They say I am unfilial.
What's this talk about being filial?
A person can only be filial
when his parents are good to him.
The parents are
obviously the ones at fault.
They have no right
to say the children are unfilial.
Zisheng.
I don't think you are a cruel person.
Also.
You don't have to
worry too much about your mother.
That man I met just now
was very caring towards Madam Huo.
I'm sure he can take good care of her.
That man
was General Cui You.
He loves my mother when he was young
and wouldn't get married.
After that,
he was forced to get married
by Old Madam Cui.
However, his wife
passed away from difficult labour.
Soon after,
my mother divorced Marquis Chengyang.
Uncle Cui
also swore
to not marry again.
He stays single for my mother.
There's still
such an affectionate man in this world.
Someone who
loves sincerely.
His affection
cannot be exchanged with gold.
It's the same
for me towards you.
Madam Huo still doesn't know me.
I will visit her in your place often
in the future.
Sure.
When you marry me,
you will be
a lady of this place.
You can come here as you wish.
No one dares to stop you.
Zisheng.
There's no need to send me
before the sun rises.
It's too difficult for you.
What if I miss you?
If I miss you
and want to see you for a while more,
what should I do?
Just wait for me
in front of the palace gates
and we'll go inside together.
How is that?
In that case,
don't you need to wake up
an hour earlier?
It's fine.
I can yawn in front of Her Majesty.
But you enter Changqiu Palace
to learn from Her Majesty.
If your progress is hindered
because of me,
won't it...
I can't do two things at once.
I can either focus
on Her Majesty and palace matters
or focus on you.
Pick one.
I want you to focus on me.
Oh.
At night,
if you are busy,
I can wait for you.
We can eat dinner at Changqiu Palace
and walk home after that.
Think of it as digesting the food.
If you are not busy,
we will eat at home. How is that?
I want to marry you soon.
Why does time
pass so slowly?
Shaoshang.
Why don't we
throw a banquet
and get engaged tomorrow?
How is that?
Sure.
Sure?
That's impossible.
I'm just kidding.
Three days later is the earliest date.
If we are getting engaged tomorrow,
it would be too rushed.
I can only wish
for these three days to pass quickly
so I can be relieved.
That's not necessary.
When I got engaged previously,
many people were invited too.
But the marriage still ended up...
Why did you kiss me again suddenly?
In the future,
if you still say something
that I don't like to hear,
I will also use this method
to block your mouth.
A banquet in three days?
That's too rushed.
Zisheng said
to leave everything to him.
We don't have to worry.
We only need to
give him a guest list.
He will prepare the invitations.
Niaoniao.
How can an engagement be so sloppy?
The banquet is less than two days
but parents from both sides
have yet to meet each other.
We can't even
prepare for other things.
Yangyang.
Zisheng already thought about that.
He said
all the preparations
will be decided by us.
There's no need to care
about other people's opinions.
I've never thought
Ling Buyi to be such a rash person.
He is not cautious
in his actions as well.
Madam. Young Ladies.
Marchioness Chengyang is here.
Why is she here?
She pretended to be sick
and wouldn't send betrothal gifts then.
She wouldn't even meet us
when we went to visit her
yet she came to visit today.
Lianfang.
Bring Young Lady
back to her room to change
and welcome the guest at Jiuzhui Hall.
Yes.
Shaoshang
is a pretty lady indeed.
I like her the moment I saw her.
No wonder Zisheng is
in a rush to marry you.
I didn't send betrothal gifts
because of my weak body.
I won't miss the opportunity this time.
Marchioness Chengyang is so forgetful.
We met in Lord Ruyang's Mansion before.
You even wanted to punish me
for Lady Wang.
Besides,
Zisheng is not young.
How is he in a rush
to get married?
Yes.
You are not Zisheng's biological mother.
Maybe you forgot about his age.
Shaoshang.
You must be feeling dissatisfied
because you heard Zisheng's complaints.
But everything's in the past.
Even if you ignore me,
can you ignore the Marquis?
Zisheng has to stay firm
because of Junhua.
I have to be the one
to take this step.
Marchioness Chengyang
is well-informed.
As Shaoshang's mother,
I just found out
about their engagement in three days.
You do act quickly.
I know everything about Zisheng
as long as my heart is with him.
Madam.
I have a question to ask you.
Go ahead.
When did you start living as a widow
in the Ling Family?
Was it before Madam Huo
married over there
or after that?
I am unlucky.
I had nowhere to go
when my former husband passed away.
I had no choice but to
rely on my aunt's family.
I'm grateful to Junhua
for taking care of me.
That means it was after the marriage?
Apparently, Marchioness Chengyang
got along well
with Madam Huo just like sisters.
You were always
serving her considerately.
I did get along well with Junhua.
That was why I'm willing to sacrifice
and serve my cousin and Junhua.
But I don't know why
Junhua
was still angry at me.
-She wanted to kill me.
-I know.
I'm sure it's because Madam Huo
likes to sleep on a big bed
and didn't want to share it with you.
It's better
to not talk about the past.
I came here today
to discuss the arrangements
for the marriage in three days.
Oh.
I also brought some gifts for Shaoshang.
I bought these two servants
from the south with 100,000 qian.
They are good at
performing and cooking.
They will stay in your house
and serve you and Zisheng
in the future.
Marchioness Chengyang
is really interesting.
Right now,
I haven't even touched Zisheng's bed
and you're already
sending me two beautiful servants
to share my future husband's bed?
What now?
Do I need to thank you for that?
Little Lady.
How can you say something so vulgar?
Madam, do you think this is vulgar?
There's actually someone
who can do vulgar things
but can't listen to vulgar words.
How is that logical?
Cheng Shaoshang.
How dare you humiliate me like this?
Did I ever offend you?
Is that how
the Cheng Family treat your guests?
Marchioness Chengyang,
Zisheng is a future husband
in our family.
The Cheng Family
will definitely stand together with him.
Instead of trying to
probe around at my house,
why don't you go and look for Zisheng?
If he thinks
it's water under the bridge,
all of us
will naturally treat you as a guest.
Otherwise,
we'll definitely not act
against Zisheng's will.
Mother is right.
Your words are exactly my thoughts.
Marchioness Quling.
Do you know
Shaoshang can be punished
for being unfilial
for what she said today?
If you spread the news,
we will definitely not admit it.
Although my husband
did not contribute to the empire
as early as Marquis Chengyang,
he is still reputable
among the generals of the capital.
Even His Majesty and Her Majesty
are always praising Shaoshang
and granting us gifts.
I wonder who in this capital
will believe in your words.
Fine.
I finally know your true nature today.
Cheng Shaoshang.
If you won't recognise me
as your mother-in-law,
you can just forget about
the engagement banquet
in the next few days.
Don't even think of
marrying into the Ling Family.
Let's go.
Qingcong.
Send her off.
No need.
I can't afford to be your guest.
Niaoniao.
Why did you keep
making Madam Chunyu angry today?
Although she isn't
Zisheng's biological mother,
she is still
his mother in name nonetheless.
Even if you don't get along with her,
you will still meet her.
Seriously.
How can you be so capricious?
You are not even afraid
of causing trouble for the family.
Mother.
I met Madam Huo yesterday.
If it wasn't for her,
Zisheng and his mother
would not have suffered.
I hate people
who steal other people's love.
I can't bring myself to act courteously
with these people.
Young Lady.
If she really
stops you from entering the banquet,
won't it become a joke?
No bride-to-be
would be stopped at the gate.
Just wait.
We still don't know
who is the one who can't enter the gate
when the time comes.
(Ling's Residence)
Isn't it General Ling
and Lady Cheng's
engagement banquet today?
Why aren't there any guests?
Marchioness Chengyang,
you've made a mistake.
The banquet today is not
being held at Young Master's residence.
It is being held
at Marquis Quling's residence.
Zisheng is not
going to marry into their family.
Why is the banquet being held
at the Cheng's residence?
Why did no one tell me
about something so important?
I was wondering as well.
Why did no one
tell Marchioness Chengyang
about something so important?
Come. Let's go
to Marquis Quling's Residence.
Young Master instructed
for all guests
to Marquis Quling's residence
to show their invitation.
Without an invitation,
no one can enter the place.
It's better for you
to not go there, Marchioness Chengyang.
You might waste your time
travelling there.
Give me the invitation.
I've sent all the invitations.
I didn't miss out on anyone
that should be invited.
Trying to make a joke out of me?
Without me today,
don't even dream of getting engaged.
Marquis Quling is really lucky
to give birth
to such an outstanding lady.
Everyone in the capital
wants General Ling
to become their husband
but he picked
your daughter Fourth Lady Cheng.
I can finally
live a good life now.
When Shaoshang is married,
it's time for Song
to get married as well.
Am I right?
Is there a marriage between
the Cheng and Wan family?
Why isn't there any news?
Didn't the Thirteenth Lady only
want someone to marry into her family?
Everything in my family
is decided by the general
and my mother-in-law.
I know nothing about it.
Marry into her family?
Don't speak nonsense.
The Wan Family did not say this.
Why didn't I see General Ling?
It's the day of the engagement.
Why is the groom not here?
Indeed.
Come.
Raise your wine glass.
Let's be joyful for this occasion.
Young Lady.
General Ling asked me to send a message.
He wants you to not be worried.
He'll be here soon.
No matter who you meet
and what happens today,
you don't have to panic.
You can scold and throw a tantrum.
He will cover for you.
(Marquis Quling's Residence)
Please come inside.
Sure. Please come inside.
Young Master.
Don't you hate coming
to banquets like these?
You said it was a waste of time.
It's better to read books
at home
rather than watching others getting married.
So, why did you come here today?
You know nothing.
I'm here to rescue my student
from a life of suffering.
The thing that harms one the most
is getting married.
I used to be
Cheng Shaoshang's teacher after all.
I can't put her in danger
even if I know
she will lead a life of suffering.
If getting married is suffering,
why do so many men and women
want that?
Because not everyone
sees the world as clearly
as your young master.
All right.
Young Master
who has seen the world clearly,
may I ask who are they?
Madam, your invitations.
I have no invitations.
I'll see who dares to stop me,
Lady Ruyang.
Move!
Great.
There's no need for me
to interfere now.
Where is Cheng Shaoshang?
I'm here.
Lady Cheng.
Why aren't you kneeling down
and admitting your crimes?
What are my crimes?
You are not talented, virtuous,
loyal and filial.
Isn't that a crime?
Lady Ruyang.
Please forgive me for not welcoming you
after your long trip.
Why don't I invite you
to the upper seat of the banquet?
I didn't receive your invitation.
How can I be so shameless
to attend the banquet?
Without my guards,
I'm sure I couldn't even enter
the gates of Marquis Quling's residence.
Upper seat?
I have no right to be there.
It was careless of us.
Lady Ruyang has a noble status.
You may enter
even without an invitation.
It sounds nice.
The young people now
forgot about their elders' grace.
It's fine if you don't invite me
but you didn't even invite
your future mother-in-law.
Isn't that
too rude of you?
Marchioness Quling,
I will
help you educate
this rude lady today.
Someone.
Take her away.
Yes!
This is crazy.
They are humiliating the Cheng Family.
Madam.
Lady Ruyang.
You might be a noble
but my husband
is not a normal citizen as well.
Everyone here today
is a family member
of court officials.
Isn't it too much for Lady Ruyang
to punish my daughter unauthorised?
Even His Majesty has to
greet me with the title of Aunt.
You are just a wife of a general.
Helping you educate your daughter
is to make you look good.
How is that too much?
Someone.
Slap Cheng Shaoshang's mouth.
Yes.
Who dares to do it?
Go away!
Old Consort.
They even hit people
from Lord Ruyang's Mansion.
They are obviously shaming you.
Everyone in the Cheng Family is rude.
How can a daughter
from a rude general's family
match for Zisheng?
I might be rude
but I know about shame.
Unlike someone
who did something shameless
like climbing
onto her cousin's bed.
You...
How dare you humiliate
your future mother-in-law
in front of all the elders?
I didn't mention who it was.
Old Consort.
There's no need to
assume who I'm talking about.
Besides,
I just went to visit
my future mother-in-law
a couple of days ago.
She is currently recuperating
at Xinghua Side House.
I don't know who is the mother-in-law
who came today.
How dare you!
I'm talking about Marchioness Chengyang!
It's the Marchioness Chengyang
who climbed onto her cousin's bed?
You...
This is getting out of hand.
I have to teach you a lesson.
I'll see who dares to stop me!
Aunt.
What if I'm the one
who's going to stop you?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Spare the formalities.
I came here today
for Zisheng and Shaoshang's engagement.
Just treat me as a normal elder.
There's no need to be polite.
Madam Cheng.
Do you have
a quiet place in your residence?
I want to have a talk
and not spoil other guests' fun.
Yes.
Your Majesty, let's go together.
Aunt.
Marchioness Chengyang.
Let's go together.
Yes.
Shaoshang.
You too.
Yes.
Zisheng
had a good marriage.
She is His Majesty's niece
and Lady Ruyang's granddaughter,
Princess Yuchang.
However, he rejected the marriage
and angered the Old Consort.
Now, he chose
a daughter of the Cheng Family
who lacks knowledge
and likes fighting.
If he really marries this lady,
I'm afraid his ancestors
will also feel humiliated.
I thought
the officials of the court
are all righteous people.
I didn't expect them
to gossip like the women on the streets.
Attending the Cheng Family's banquet
while laughing at their daughter.
I think
all of your ancestors
were the ones who will feel humiliated.
How is it?
Calm down.
Let's wait for a while.
Aunt.
In the few months
that Shaoshang was serving me,
she has been kind, courteous,
benevolent and open-minded.
There has been nothing wrong with her.
You came here furiously today
and even wanted to detain Shaoshang.
Your actions might be too much.
I was only educating the young people
about being filial.
The Cheng Family was too much.
Besides having the banquet
in the bride's family,
they didn't even send an invitation
to their in-laws at
Marquis Chengyang's residence.
It was so unfilial of them.
Marquis Chengyang is sick today
and can't be here.
He asked his wife to handle this
yet she couldn't even enter the house.
It's the Cheng's Family's
first time marrying their daughter.
There will be some mistakes.
Besides,
Zisheng asked His Majesty's opinion
about organising the banquet
at Marquis Quling's residence.
If you don't believe me,
you can send someone to ask His Majesty.
How is that?
There's no need
to trouble His Majesty
for a trivial matter
like punishing the young people.
Your Majesty.
You really don't have
an opinion of your own.
Her Majesty has her own opinions.
Consort, it is too rude of you
to simply criticise Her Majesty.
You are the rude one.
Who are you
to even interrupt when we are talking?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty
is not as strict as Consort Yue.
A servant like her
should be slapped
so she will not talk back in the future.
Aunt, you really do miss me.
You keep mentioning me.
Aunt.
Your Majesty.
Cheng Shaoshang is full of nonsense.
She is a disgrace to the royal family.
You must not spoil her any longer.
The Old Consort also said
there's no need to trouble Your Majesty
for such a trivial matter.
Right now, she is the one
who is troubling Your Majesty.
You're rebelling now.
This lady
is obviously belittling
the royal family's might.
She's rebelling.
I think you are the one
who is rebelling, Old Consort.
Are you going to tell
His Majesty what he should do?
When did I do that?
Isn't it the
young people's responsibility
to beg for an elder's love?
Look who's speaking.
Did Zisheng propose to Shaoshang
because she is loved by you?
You did love Yuchang a lot.
Did she get married?
Don't even mention Yuchang.
She became a nun because of you.
Are you dead?
Why are you staying silent
when they are
badmouthing your granddaughter?
Shut up.
Who are you to scold me?
If you didn't instigate Yuchang,
I would've found a husband for her.
She wouldn't have to
suffer at the temple.
My Yuchang
is a hundred times better
than this lady of the Cheng Family.
Let me ask you.
What will you do
about humiliating Marchioness Chengyang
a few days ago?
Zisheng's fiancee.
Stand up and answer her.
Thank you, Consort Yue.
Your Majesty.
I have never humiliated
Marchioness Chengyang.
I only spoke the truth.
I swear...
What's the use of swearing, Old Consort?
Were you there?
Did you hear or see anything?
You only listened
to Marchioness Chengyang's words.
Perhaps
you were even fooled.
I swear on my life.
Your Majesty.
If I also swear on my life
and say Marchioness Chengyang
had the intention to harm General Ling,
will the Old Consort be just
and punish her as well?
Why are you swearing?
You are always misbehaving.
Marchioness Chengyang's oath
is more honest.
Old Consort.
That's wrong.
I got married honestly
by listening to my elders' instructions.
I can't be compared to
Marchioness Chengyang
who organised her own marriage.
She relied on the Huo Family
and stayed by Madam Huo's side
for many years
only to replace Madam Huo
when she didn't notice.
So,
my oath can be trusted.
Her oath
cannot be trusted.
Although I have a poor background,
I still can't allow Cheng Shaoshang
to humiliate me.
If Your Majesty won't say anything,
I'll have no choice but to kill myself.
I'm impressed with Madam's courage
to die instead of being humiliated.
Marchioness Chengyang,
if you were
this courageous back then,
Madam Huo won't have to be divorced.
Many things
might be different today.
Zisheng.
Your future wife is really smart.
She just said what's on my heart.
Consort Yue is right.
Consort Yue.
Who is Huo Junhua?
You hated her back then
but you are
helping her right now?
You are obviously against me.
My grudge against Huo Junhua
is one matter.
But she has never done
anything bad to the Ling Family.
She even meant a lot to Ling Yi.
She helped him in every aspect.
But Ling Yi
had an ambiguous relationship
with Madam Chunyu
when his wife and son
went missing for less than a year.
Can he face the Huo Family with dignity?
When Huo Junhua and her son
were left with nowhere to go,
she wrapped Zisheng in leather
and gave him the remaining food.
Where was Ling Yi back then?
He was preparing
with his marriage to a second wife.
When Huo Junhua was found,
she was only skin and bones.
I couldn't even recognise her.
Yes. Her behaviour is bad
but she is
also a good mother.
She never let Zisheng down.
So, Zisheng shouldn't let her down
by flattering Madam Chunyu.
Not even if His Majesty says anything.
I will say this today.
From today onwards,
Madam Chunyu
cannot enter the palace
without being summoned.
I feel disgusted
when I see people like her.
Your Majesty.
No matter how
Madam Chunyu has misbehaved,
she is still my saviour.
Humiliating her today
is the same as humiliating me.
If you don't give me an explanation,
I will...
Kill yourself?
That's wonderful.
I'm going outside
to scream for injustice!
All the family members
of the officials are here today.
I want to show them
how His Majesty
treats his aunt
who protected his siblings.
I want to show them
whether their reputation
can be protected!
Your Majesty. Look.
What a crazy woman.
She starts throwing a tantrum
when something doesn't go her way.
I wanted to abandon her
but you told me not to abandon
a wife who suffered with me.
You even gave me a bad idea
about living separately.
You wanted me to become a friar
outside of the capital.
Seriously.
I don't even know much
about Tao Te Ching.
Why would I go study?
Fine.
I won't abandon her.
I'll divorce her.
I want a divorce!
I gave birth to your children
and helped you with your chores!
I have some contributions at least!
All of you
are treating me like this?
You...
This is ridiculous.
Your Majesty.
I can't take this anymore.
I can't stand her anymore!
No way.
Uncle, please stand up.
It is not my intention to trouble you.
Confucianism is popular nowadays.
If you start to talk about divorce now
and abandon your wife,
the students
might gossip about you.
Uncle loves having fun.
Why should he go study?
In my opinion,
Old Consort
should go to Sancai Temple
to nurture her character.
You...
What Consort Yue suggested
is a perfect solution.
All of you...
Lady Ruyang is old and senile.
She will sometimes act crazy
and disgrace me.
Send her to Sancai Temple
to nurture her character.
Your Majesty!
Zisheng.
Send more men
to take good care of her.
Don't let outsiders
disturb her anymore.
Yes.
Your Majesty!
Guards.
Take good care of the Old Consort.
Yes!
All of you are bullying me!
All of you!
I heard Marquis Chengyang is sick.
Marchioness Chengyang
should take good care of him.
From now on,
you shouldn't step outside
your residence anymore.
Today is Zisheng's marriage.
It is also an auspicious day for me.
A few days ago, I just
received a few jars of good wine.
It is pure and fragrant.
Let's have a drink.
Come. Let's drink!
Let's go!
The beacon-fire has knocked
over the white snow
I caress the scars gently
from the past
Your back to the light,
your eyes contain the galaxy
I hum as the sun
and the moon mutter back
The light between your brows
Was put out and rekindled
by the secular world
The sky, the mountain, and the ocean,
whom do I part them for?
As I wake up from the blue sea,
stone steles stand like a mountain range
Under the lantern, criticisms were thrown,
the narrow door could not contain my feelings
The joys and woes of this mortal life,
we speak as we dream of the future
Both of us will be
In the sea of stars,
burning bright with our sincerity
Our sincerity