= Love Like The Galaxy=
=Episode 42=
This hairpin looks more exquisite.
It'll complement your elegance.
You should wear this for the wedding.
You mustn't.
White accessories are inauspicious
during joyous occasions as such.
You should wear
the golden hairpin instead.
Everyone in the capital
is concerned about Niaoniao's marriage.
We mustn't disgrace our family.
The golden hairpin
must be thick and heavy.
Only then, it can show
prosperity and good fortune.
Old Madam,
I think she should look dignified
and elegant instead.
What about
this sandalwood hairpin?
She's getting married here!
She's not trying to be a nun here.
We have a gem crown for her.
There's agate on top of it.
It's very valuable.
This accessory doesn't
fit her attire at all.
I do think
that we do not need
such luxurious accessories.
The key is to be elegant.
Look at how nice
this fan-shaped hairpin look on her.
Only a few ladies in
the capital wear this.
Ladies from the younger generation
like you all
have no rules at all.
A fan
signifies separation.
It's too inauspicious.
Here's a Dragon and Phoenix Hairpin.
Let me put it on for you.
All right.
Stop.
Mother,
Grandmother,
you guys don't need to be worried.
Her Majesty had already prepared
the wedding accessories for me.
They're all crafted by the craftsmen
in the palace.
They're top-notch.
Really?
That's great! We can save some money!
Not only can we save money,
but we will also be respected!
Niaoniao,
did Her Majesty prepare them
for you long ago?
I didn't expect Her Majesty
to be more thoughtful
than your mother.
That's not it.
It's because Her Majesty and His Majesty
always hoped that
Zisheng could get married.
That's why they would
buy them every year.
They've bought a lot of them.
They can finally
put them to use this year.
If everything goes smoothly,
I should be getting married
within the palace.
Her Majesty said
she had already
prepared a boudoir for me.
That's better.
That's the reward His and Her Majesty
are giving to the Cheng Family.
We've honored our family's name.
If so, we shall follow
Her Majesty's will.
You should get married
within the palace.
Why are you standing there
like a woman waiting for her husband
when you're engaged?
Why do you make no sound when you walk?
You're so annoying.
It's clearly because you were
too absorbed in your longing.
That's why you didn't
detect my presence.
Do you know how exhausting
these days were for me?
I had to try on the wedding dress
and accessories.
Jewelries that weigh over 10 jin
were placed all over my head
and my neck.
If you were in my shoes,
you would feel the soreness too.
Wait, you can't be in my shoes.
You're not getting married.
You wouldn't know how I feel.
What do you mean by
I don't need to get married?
What's the big deal
about getting married?
Don't tell me
that you think you're the only person
who can get married?
Besides,
what's so good about getting married?
It's tiring and has no benefits.
Only a muddle-headed person like you
would cherish such an idea.
Look at you now.
You look worried and listless.
You looked much better in the past.
It's obvious that you don't understand
how it feels to be in love.
You also don't know
how it feels like to long for someone.
However, it'll get better
after the wedding.
After I get married,
I can see him every day.
I do not need to long for him again.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely get married before you.
I will find out how it feels like
to see my partner every day
faster than you.
Yuan Shanjian,
you don't have to get married
if you don't want to!
No one is forcing you!
Did you hear me?
This is what you meant
by a peerless noble lady?
Official Cai graduated
from Bailu Academy too.
But why is his daughter...
I heard that Lady Cai could
recite poems when she was three
and write rhapsodies when she was seven.
And, she was famous in the capital
for her intellect.
The matchmaker said
she was the best candidate
for you.
When did the matchmaker go blind?
How is Lady Cai
the best candidate for me?
I don't ask a lot for someone
to be the Yuan clan's madam.
Her brain
must not be slower than Lady Cheng's.
Her personality must not
be more perverse than Lady Cheng.
Understood.
Her looks must not be uglier
than Lady Cheng.
Young Master, your expectations
are still pretty high.
I...
I am
a rare male intellectual
who has both looks and intellect.
The Yuan Family is
a renowned family as well.
Isn't it reasonable for me
to have higher expectations?
That's not it.
However, Young Master, why must
you compare your fiancee
to Lady Cheng?
I just don't want her
to look down on me.
You must pay great attention to this.
It's best if we can skip
the wedding gift process
and get straight to the marriage.
We will get married
on the day of Lady Cheng's wedding.
By then,
all those guests will come and
congratulate me instead of her.
I'll see what Cheng Shaoshang
can do about that.
He must be out of his mind.
I'm sure he's out of his mind.
Are you out of your mind?
Can't you tell
what's different about me today?
I can tell you're crazier than usual.
Today,
I'm betrothed.
Which lady is so desperate?
You're just envious of her good taste.
She's Lady Cai of Henan.
She's a perfect match for me.
She can
recite poems when she was three
and write rhapsodies when she was seven.
She's a famous figure.
What are you laughing at?
Don't look as if
you've rid yourself of a burden.
I've never
pestered you like this before, right?
I was laughing because I wanted you
to stop being pretentious.
You aren't a reckless person.
You always think twice before you act.
Since you're getting engaged,
I'm sure you've assessed
the Cai Family beforehand.
And, this engagement
will produce the best result for you.
That's why you agreed to it.
This has nothing to do
with her talents.
Don't make me sound so sordid.
I got engaged
because I truly fancy her.
It's a pity...
Why?
Is it a pity that you can't afford
the betrothal gifts
that the Cai Family is asking for?
Why don't I ask my Zisheng
to lend you some money?
Nothing good comes out of your mouth.
I was taking pity on you.
From now on,
there's one less
dashing
and elegant bachelor in the world.
You just need two people to be in love.
Getting engaged isn't a business deal.
It won't be a pity
if you two love each other.
What's so good about loving each other?
My mother wasn't
married to my father initially.
Although we have parents,
it's as if we don't.
Initially,
I thought you would be like me.
I thought you would take your time
to find the most beneficial husband
for yourself.
I didn't expect you to...
You didn't expect what?
You didn't expect me to be so lucky
to encounter Zisheng, right?
If so, I pray
that you can meet someone
as good as him too.
Wait.
I forgot.
You're engaged.
It's a pity that you won't get
to encounter anyone else.
However, this is better for you.
At least it's a marriage
of equal status.
You should be grateful.
(List of guests)
There are so many guests
attending Fourth Lady Cheng's wedding.
However, you can actually remember
all of their titles and ranks
without any mistakes.
I wonder
who's lucky enough to marry
an excellent lady like you?
Young Marquis Ban,
you're teasing me again.
Actually, I've made up my mind.
I'll stay single
so that I can
take good care of First Aunt.
You're the smartest lady
I've ever encountered.
If you're staying single,
I'm afraid some guys
will be heartbroken.
I wonder which guy will be heartbroken
that Yangyang isn't
planning to get married?
Is it you?
That's right, Young Marquis Ban.
You visit us all the time.
And, you're interrupting Yangyang
when she's preparing for the wedding.
Could it be that
you harbor ulterior motives
toward Yangyang?
Marquis Ban went to Shouchun
with his troops.
He was worried about
Young Marquis Ban's safety.
That's why he told him
to visit us more often.
That's right.
My grandfather
told me to join you guys
during mealtimes.
So, you're just here to eat, huh?
The food here tastes great.
But the people here
are better, right?
This is bad!
It's an omen!
Such audacity!
I had high expectations of him.
However, he sold the country out
and caused great distress
to the people of Tongniu County!
All these old fools
are useless!
They cannot write anything useful
except for things like eradicating
Marquis Quling and his entire clan!
Why should I keep them around?
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Attendant Cao,
please notify His Majesty for me.
I seek an audience with His Majesty.
Your Majesty,
we just received news that
Tongniu County had been taken over.
Some subjects had joined hands
and requested His Majesty
to punish Marquis Quling and his family severely
to serve as a warning to the public.
His Majesty has thrown a tantrum
for the last hour because of this.
He doesn't wish to see anyone today.
If so,
I shall wait outside the hall.
Your Majesty, it's cold outside.
Why don't you return
to Changqiu Palace for now?
Your Majesty, I shall notify you
once I receive any news.
It doesn't matter.
I will wait outside the hall.
This...
Your Majesty,
why aren't you heading inside?
Consort Yue.
Heng, great timing.
You should go and persuade His Majesty.
His Majesty hasn't taken his meals yet?
Yes, His Majesty said
he didn't have any appetite.
He didn't even want
to take a sip of water.
Such nonsense.
Does he know how old he is?
He really thinks that
he's made of iron, huh?
I'll check on His Majesty.
Consort Yue.
His Majesty said he wouldn't see anyone.
This is...
Didn't I say I wouldn't see anyone?
All of you, scram!
Heng, what are you doing here?
Were you hurt?
Hurry! Summon the physician here!
No need for that.
Your Majesty, you should continue.
Continue with what?
You can continue to throw objects at me.
You thought you were pretty cool,
didn't you?
We should summon the physician here
to see if you're hurt.
It'll be terrible
if your face is wounded.
Throwing things around
does feel satisfying.
Your Majesty,
if you think throwing
these memorials around
isn't satisfying enough,
I'll order the servants to bring us
some charcoal pots.
Isn't it more satisfying
if we can burn these memorials?
I know my fault now.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have
vented my anger on them.
Let me see if you're hurt.
Let me see.
I'm not that stupid.
I won't just stand there
and let you throw things at me.
Your Majesty, you haven't taken anything
since this morning.
That's why I was worried about you.
To repay the favor,
I have to make you worry about me.
Only then, we'll be even.
I'm glad that you're fine.
You're still the same.
You were always unwilling
to get the short end of the stick.
Are these snacks not sweet enough?
Or are these pastries not crispy enough?
Why are we having short sticks
when we have snacks here?
You're right.
I'm sorry.
The county magistrate of Tongniu County
and Marquis Quling had defected.
I understand why you were disappointed.
However, I know
that Your Majesty threw a tantrum
not only because of the lost county.
You also felt sorry for those
who come from a poor background.
Heng,
you do know me well.
Initially,
I planned to promote several students
who had a poor background.
However, I was always restrained
by those noble families.
They would rather practice cronyism
than selecting people
from poor backgrounds.
Cheng Shi and Yan Zhong,
both of them were selected by me
even though my subjects objected to them
as they came from a poor background.
But now,
both of them have
defected to the enemies.
I'm afraid it would be even harder
for me to promote those
from a poor background.
That spells the end of poor families.
Even so,
Your Majesty doesn't
need to be that angry.
Is there
a secret reason behind this?
Is it something inconvenient
for Your Majesty to announce in public?
Why don't you tell me about it?
Two deputy county magistrates
saw for themselves that
Cheng Shi and Yan Zhong
defected to the enemies together
with 2,000 jin of refined copper.
They have ironclad evidence
of their crime.
And now, we can't even locate them.
Even if I said
they were maligned,
it's hard for me
to prove their innocence.
If I do have to punish them both,
what should I do about Lady Cheng?
What should I do about Zisheng?
What should I do about their wedding?
It's going to be ruined again.
Your Majesty,
as a ruler, you mustn't be indecisive.
You can only convince
the people to trust your rule
by following the rules.
Your Majesty, I trust you.
I trust Country Magistrate Yan
and Marquis Quling too.
I'm sure there's more to this case
than meets the eye.
However, Your Majesty,
you don't need to be conflicted.
You just need to go by the book.
We can investigate the case
at our own pace.
We won't frame anyone
innocent.
Since His Majesty
is having his meal now,
I'm sure he's already appeased.
Your Majesty, if you're still worried,
why don't you head inside?
Since Consort Yue had already
consoled His Majesty,
I shouldn't head inside
and cause any trouble.
I think the edict will be out soon.
Attendant Cao,
how does His Majesty
plan to deal with Marquis Quling?
His Majesty said...
His Majesty said
that Marquis Quling's entire family
will be imprisoned.
His two siblings,
Cheng Cheng and Cheng Zhi, will be
removed from their posts and imprisoned.
The eldest son of the Cheng Family,
Cheng Yong and his wife,
will be detained in
the border area's military camp.
Marquis Quling is a patriotic subject.
There's no reason for him
to commit treason at this time.
Moreover,
even if Marquis Quling had defected
to the enemies,
it has nothing to do with his family.
Shaoshang lived in the palace
during the wedding preparation.
She has no idea about what happened
in Tongniu County.
Why must she be imprisoned as well?
Regarding Marquis Quling's defection,
His Majesty will definitely
get to the bottom of it.
However, the nation has its own rules.
His Majesty cannot practice favoritism.
As for Lady Cheng,
Your Majesty, you don't need to
worry about her.
His Majesty said
that since Lady Cheng
was engaged to Zisheng,
she could be counted as
part of the Ling Family.
His Majesty will spare her.
Your Majesty, you don't need to worry.
His Majesty is going
to spare Lady Cheng.
Your Majesty, this is bad.
Lady Cheng insists on leaving the palace
after hearing about what happened
to Marquis Quling.
She said she would
die together with her family.
What?
Stop!
Shaoshang,
get in my carriage.
Have you heard about it?
Official Zuo has already reported this
to His Majesty.
Now, everyone in the court knows that
General Cheng has defected.
You should return home for now.
I shall make an appeal for you
in front of His Majesty.
Even if I were to offend His Majesty,
I will do it.
Do you believe in my father?
When I was teaching in the Cheng Family,
I made acquaintances with General Cheng.
No matter who believes
that he has defected,
I won't.
Moreover,
he's your father.
I won't just sit here
and do nothing about it.
Get in my carriage.
Thank you.
(Marquis Quling's Residence)
Who has the Cheng Family offended
for the Commandant
to send his men after us?
Cheng Shi
bewitched the county magistrate
of Tongniu County and defected
to the enemies with
2,000 jin of refined copper.
His Majesty has already issued
the imperial edict.
Madam Cheng, you should surrender.
Are you trying to rebel here
since your husband has defected
to the enemies?
You and your men
barged into our residence
indiscriminately
and humiliated our family.
Don't tell me
you want us to welcome you
with a warm hug?
Did you forget
that I was by my husband's side
during the warring period?
I've rendered meritorious deeds too.
If you wish to arrest my family,
you have to get through me first.
I'm here to seize
Marquis Quling's Residence
and arrest criminals like you all
under the order of the Commandant.
Madam Cheng, your deeds
are nothing in front of
His Majesty's imperial edict.
It's impossible
for my husband to defect to the enemies.
I'm sure there's more to this case
than meets the eye.
We can follow you to
the Commandant's Residence
and be interrogated.
(Virtue Flows Like Water)
However, we're not criminals,
and we won't yield to this defamation.
You don't get to say
if you all are criminals or not.
You guys are being overbearing here.
How will you face your fellow officials
if General Cheng comes back right now?
You!
If you dare to touch my family members,
I'll fight you until the end!
If you dare to hurt my family members,
I shall make you all pay!
That's right.
If anyone tries to resist, kill them.
We'll report to His Majesty after that.
General,
His Majesty had always ruled the nation
with virtues and moral obligations.
He has never tortured his people.
The case hasn't even been
brought to trial yet.
The Cheng Family isn't convicted
of the crime yet.
But now, you're trying
to intimidate us with violence.
This is highly inappropriate of you.
Excellent words!
Highly inappropriate?
Today, I shall see
who thinks this is inappropriate.
Me!
His Majesty will decide
if the Cheng Family
has betrayed the nation or not.
But you're abusing your power
to exact revenge.
Are you tired of living?
What nonsense are you saying?
I'm executing His Majesty's order.
How am I abusing my power?
Your niece pushed me into the water.
And I rewarded her with
a splash to the face.
Your brother, who was
working in the Censorate,
had one of his legs broken
by my husband-to-be.
What?
Do you think we're being unfair here?
Is that why you're asking for
a beating right now?
You!
Don't get too ahead of yourself.
Now that the Cheng Family
has lost its prestige,
your husband-to-be
will no longer support you.
Are you guys dumb?
Take her and her family members down!
Stop right there.
(Pass)
According to His Majesty's edict,
Lady Cheng isn't involved with the case.
General Zuo,
are you trying to defy
the imperial edict?
Official Yuan,
as the Attendant Gentleman of
the Ministry of Justice,
are you trying to hinder me
from executing public duties?
His Majesty has issued another edict.
The Ministry of Justice
shall handle this case.
He has ordered me
to escort the kin of the suspect
to the Ministry of Justice
for interrogation purposes.
We're to escort them,
not to arrest them.
General Zuo,
do you understand
what His Majesty means?
Let's go!
His Majesty has ordered me
to interrogate you all
in the Ministry of Justice.
I'm executing my duties here.
Madam, please pardon me.
Thank you, Official Yuan.
My sons and I only went against the edict
as I was too anxious.
However,
there's more to this case
than meets the eye.
In order to prove our innocence,
we're willing
to be interrogated in
the Ministry of Justice.
Why must the entire family be there?
Because General and I
are the loyal subjects of His Majesty
and the protectors of the nation.
Since we're paid by the nation,
we have to obey the rules.
We have to go!
Please.
Old Madam.
Yangyang,
bring your grandmother there.
Grandmother.
Why are you following us?
His Majesty is treating you
as a part of the Ling Family
as you'll be married to Ling Buyi soon.
This case has nothing to do with you.
Return to Changqiu Palace immediately.
I'm the young lady of the Cheng Family
as long as I'm not married yet.
If my kin is convicted of this crime,
I shall suffer together with them.
Thank you, Mr. Yuan.
First Aunt, calm down!
Niaoniao did so because
she was worried about us!
I slapped her because I was
angry at her ignorance!
We don't know
if your father is dead or alive.
If we cannot
clear our names,
you'll be the last descendant
of our family.
Cheng Shaoshang,
listen up.
No matter what happens to
the Cheng Family,
you must live on.
You must survive.
If not, the ancestors of
the Cheng Family
will never forgive you.
Your father and I
Understood?
Official Yuan,
what punishment awaits those
who defect to the enemies
and sell one's nation to the enemies?
According to the law,
their entire clan will be massacred.
Men will be tortured and executed.
Women will be banished
to the border areas.
I'm sure
that day will never arrive.
(Yongle Palace)
Lady Cheng, you should head back.
You!
You're putting His Majesty on the spot
by kneeling here.
His Majesty will never see you.
Your Majesty!
It's impossible for Father
to sell his nation out!
I know I'm insignificant.
However, this is
the only thing I can do!
Your Majesty, I request an audience!
Lady Cheng,
it's pouring out here.
What should we do
if you get sick?
It's best if I can die here.
My father had served the nation
and its people his entire life.
But now, he's framed for
such a ridiculous crime.
Even the heavens cannot stand this.
The heavens are crying
because our family is maligned.
Due to that, it's snowing in the summer
and there is thunderstorm in the winter.
That's how it is.
Listen to her.
What the heck is she saying?
It's snowing in the summer
and there is thunderstorm in the winter?
What does she mean by that?
It's obvious that she's saying
that I'm a fatuous ruler.
Your Majesty, if you're worried about
Lady Cheng,
you should summon her.
You're stretching your neck
just to hear her words.
I'm afraid your neck will be sore.
Who's worried about her?
She can get drenched all she likes.
I won't feel sorry for her.
This little lady,
how could she
have such a stubborn temper?
If she does fall sick,
Zisheng will be upset
when he comes back.
I don't feel for her.
I just feel for Zisheng.
Your Majesty, if you don't
uphold justice for my family,
I'll seek justice from the gods
of Mount Taishan!
Your Majesty, if you're
not seeing me today,
I will kneel here until you see me!
Your Highness, great timing.
Please persuade Lady Cheng to stop.
Why are you kneeling as well?
You don't have an umbrella!
Your Highness.
I also don't believe that Marquis Quling
will defect to the enemies.
Since you're seeking an audience,
let me join you.
Your Highness, if you fall sick,
Her Majesty will be worried.
Besides, Your Highness,
you were only released from
detainment just recently.
If you get yourself involved,
what should we do if His Majesty
punishes you again?
Lady Cheng, you once risked your life
to investigate my case.
I will not turn my back on you.
Let us seek the gods
of Mount Taishan together.
Look at you guys!
What should we do about you two?
Your Majesty!
-Shield His Highness from the rain!
-Your Majesty?
Shield His Highness from the rain!
-Shield His Highness from the rain!
-Don't be afraid.
I will join you guys.
His Majesty is cold-hearted!
He will never see me!
Your Majesty, you should head back.
Please don't fall sick.
Why is the empress here as well?
Her body won't be able to take it.
She always takes a long time
to recover from her sickness.
And, what is the Crown Prince doing?
He's not even afraid of detainment now.
Her Majesty won't be able
to stand the harsh weather.
You should check on her.
I won't go.
Just go.
No, I won't.
Just go!
Enough!
Stop bowing!
Return to your palace!
Have some ginger soup
and warm yourselves up!
Cheng Shaoshang,
don't think that you can
threaten me
with your foolish behavior!
And you two!
On usual days,
you two
do not go against the palace rules!
What's wrong?
Are you guys influenced by
Cheng Shaoshang's boorishness
after she joined the palace?
Your Majesty,
this is not Shaoshang's fault.
Even if Shaoshang wasn't here,
I would demand an explanation
for the Cheng Family too.
Your Majesty, please grant Shaoshang
her wish.
Marquis Quling has
defected to the enemies.
This case will be brought to trial.
I've already issued an imperial edict.
No changes are allowed.
You should stop trying
to plead for them.
I've already spared Cheng Shaoshang.
I've already done enough
to spare her from the case.
However, Your Majesty...
Your Majesty, you have a weak body.
Why don't you join me in Yongle Palace
and have some ginger soup?
Your Majesty,
Lady Cheng isn't an ignorant lady.
She wouldn't
put you on the spot like this.
I assume she's just
worried about her father
and that she wants to know more
about the case in Tongniu County.
Your Majesty,
you should grant her an audience.
Your Majesty.
Just grant her an audience.
Enough!
Cao Cheng,
get some ginger soup.
You may come in.
Thank you, Your Majesty!
Master?
Are you here to visit us?
Do you have news from Niaoniao?
Mr. Yuan, do you have any news
of my father?
Mr. Yuan, is Niaoniao doing okay?
She looked distressed today.
You should console her.
Official Yuan,
did His Majesty say
how he would punish
Cheng Cheng and Cheng Zhi?
Yangyang was implicated because of us.
Since His Majesty has spared Shaoshang,
can His Majesty
spare Yangyang as well?
First Aunt,
I won't leave.
I was happy
that I could be together with you all.
Although I'm not as witty as Niaoniao
and I can't think of a way
to save you all,
at least
I can take care of you and Grandmother
when I'm here.
I have no complaints.
First Aunt,
please allow me to stay here.
Don't worry.
Cheng Cheng
was only detained in Bailu Academy.
County Magistrate Cheng and his wife
were detained in Hua County.
Your eldest son and his wife
were detained in the military camp.
However, the military didn't make
things difficult for them.
Don't worry.
The Ministry of Justice will get to
the bottom of this as soon as possible.
As long as the truth is out,
you all will be released.
Sir!
Sir, was Zhi arrested as well?
God! Open your eyes!
Sir, it's just 2,000 jin of
refined copper, right?
How much are they? I'll pay for them!
I'll pay His Majesty for it, okay?
I'll pay for the amount
that Shi has taken!
I'll pay for everything!
Old Madam!
Do you know how much 2,000 jin
of refined copper will cost you?
Do you think you can afford them?
Besides, this case isn't over yet.
Why are you saying as if
my husband was guilty?
You jinx!
You shouldn't have brought my son
to the battlefield back then!
You just had to be a great general, huh?
I would rather he come back
and become a peasant!
Sir!
How much do you need to free him?
Tell me.
This heartless woman
isn't willing to save her husband.
I will save my son myself!
Sir, I have all the money you need!
I'll save him!
Old Madam,
His Majesty is handling
the case himself.
I do not dare to abuse my power here.
I'm here
to deliver your meals to you.
Why don't you all have dinner
before we talk about anything else?
I won't eat.
Instead of being beheaded,
I would rather starve to death.
At least my corpse is complete.
Even if Old Madam doesn't want to eat,
we shall eat.
It takes time to get
to the bottom of this case.
We shouldn't starve ourselves to death
before our names are cleared.
Yes, Mother. I will eat.
Yes, me too.
Keep some for me. I will eat too.
Open the meal box.
I've lost my appetite
thinking about Marquis Quling's case.
But you do seem like
you're enjoying the ginger soup, huh?
A tragedy has befallen your family.
I have to take good care of myself.
Only then, I will have the strength
to do something about it.
Naturally, I have to drink.
You turned yourself into a mess
after Zisheng left the capital
for a few days.
Do you know that
you've let Zisheng down?
If I don't let Zisheng down,
that means I'll let my parents down.
I was just
going by the book.
Instead of
speaking out against
your father's injustice,
why don't you ask him
why he defected to the enemies?
I have something I don't understand.
Your Majesty, please explain it to me.
My mother, my brothers,
and I are in the capital,
leading a comfortable life.
And, I will get married to Zisheng soon.
My father doesn't lack anything in life,
and he has a harmonious family.
Why did he defect to the enemies?
That's right.
I wish to know the answer to that too.
I always treated your father nicely.
Why did he defect to the enemies?
I have no idea.
Your Majesty,
I assume you have no idea too.
It's obvious that Father
doesn't have a reason
to betray Your Majesty.
Therefore,
Father was surely maligned.
I've always treated Lord Yong
and Peng Kun nicely too.
Even so, they betrayed me.
Therefore, you cannot prove
that your father was maligned
with those words of yours.
How could you compare those traitors
to Father?
Father isn't as stupid as them.
Just look at you.
I assume your father
isn't that much smarter than you.
Your Majesty, you can insult me.
But you mustn't insult my father.
My father
is the person
who loves his children
the most in the world.
If Father was here,
I'm sure he wouldn't
let me get drenched.
If so, tell me then.
Cheng Shi headed to Tongniu County
to assist the county magistrate
to allocate military supplies.
Why would he and
County Magistrate Yan Zhong
run away with 2,000 jin
of refined copper
if they didn't betray the country?
Even now, we have no news of them.
If so, why were
the deputy county magistrates
so sure
that both of them
had betrayed the country?
Shaoshang,
even if
I trust your father,
I have to make my subjects
in the imperial court
trust him as well.
Now,
if we cannot locate the stolen
refined copper of 2,000 jin,
I'm afraid
I cannot ensure your family's safety.
Your Majesty,
allow me to head to Tongniu County.
I'll locate the 2,000 jin
of stolen refined copper for you.
Stop spouting nonsense.
Why would I send a little lady like you
to Tongniu County?
That county is close to Shouchun.
Peng Kun has taken over the county.
It's very dangerous.
I'm not afraid.
Back then, when we encountered
danger in Hua County,
I once defended the family
with our servants.
Zisheng taught me how to defend myself.
I can ride horses
and create machines.
Your Majesty,
the longer my father is out there,
the more danger he'll be in.
Your Majesty, I beg you.
Please let me seek my father.
Say no more.
I will leave the case
to the Ministry of Justice.
You don't need to interfere.
Just stay in the palace
and wait for Zisheng's return
so that you can get married to him.
Your Majesty, I beg you!
Please let me seek my father
in Tongniu County.
Your Majesty, please!
Why are you so stubborn?
Cao Cheng!
Yes, Your Majesty?
Your Majesty.
Bring Lady Cheng
back to Changqiu Palace.
Tell Her Majesty
that she's a sinner as well.
From today onward,
she is not to leave Changqiu Palace.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The beacon-fire has knocked
over the white snow
I caress the scars gently
from the past
Your back to the light,
your eyes contain the galaxy
I hum as the sun
and the moon mutter back
The light between your brows
Was put out and rekindled
by the secular world
The sky, the mountain, and the ocean,
whom do I part them for?
As I wake up from the blue sea,
stone steles stand like a mountain range
Under the lantern, criticisms were thrown,
the narrow door could not contain my feelings
The joys and woes of this mortal life,
we speak as we dream of the future
Both of us will be
In the sea of stars,
burning bright with our sincerity
Our sincerity