= Love Like The Galaxy=
=Episode 32=
Third Prince has
a bright future ahead of him.
We still have to rely on you, Marquis.
All of us are from the same hall.
It's only right
for us to help each other.
Don't worry.
It's getting late.
We won't disturb you any longer.
We will be leaving.
Sure.
Take care, everyone.
Take care.
The rumour of
replacing the crown prince
has yet to be verified.
These people
are really opportunistic.
It will happen sooner or later.
Right now,
the Yue Clan is very influential.
It's normal for the officials
to seek connections.
Mr. Tian!
Do you have any more Qianlizui?
I want to drink with them
until I'm drunk.
Your Highness.
I've saved all the Qianlizui for you.
Greetings,
Your Highness.
What a coincidence.
Let me introduce you to them.
He will be my future father-in-law.
Your Highness is
really enjoying yourself.
I wonder if Changqiu Palace knows
that Your Highness is here today.
I have yet to marry into the Yue Family
and you're already trying to control me?
I am a princess, Marquis Yue.
The empire belongs to
the Wen Family and not the Yue Family.
The only one on par with the Wen Family
is only my mother's clan,
the Xuan Family.
Mr. Tian.
Marquis Yue.
I know you can hire musicians.
My son's future wife is unrestrained.
She likes to make friends
with handsome men.
Since I'm her father-in-law,
I should prepare a gift
that suits her.
I understand.
Also,
she should know about
the rumours at the royal court.
After all, we'll soon become a family.
She should share our burden as well.
Don't worry.
I am not capable.
I only manage many restaurants
that have many guests.
News at my restaurants
spread faster than others.
Mr. Tian.
You are someone who is very capable.
The Crown Princess is here.
There are many princes
and princesses as well.
Why did His Majesty
give all these troubling tasks
to me?
I think Father's decision was wise.
I have to use a few days
to calculate the purchase expenses
but it only took you half a day.
Besides, birthday banquet of the Changqiu Palace,
only the Crown Prince,
Zisheng and Fifth Princess
are Mother's children.
Do you think Fifth Princess
can be depended on?
It's fine
if I'm just doing the calculations.
Why do I need to arrange the seats
of the officials' family members?
I don't even recognise everyone.
Father and Mother
want you
to be familiar with
everything in the palace.
That is why they have me to support you.
It's hard being Zisheng's future wife.
It's harder than governing a county.
Now that I think back to
the rebuilding of Hua County,
it didn't trouble me as much as this.
I've never thought
my husband
would be the Crown Prince as well.
My mother's family
wanted to rely on me
to become successful
but they don't know I am powerless.
They are always saying
that I forget my roots
in front and behind of me
but none of them knows
the troubles I've faced.
Crown Princess, don't say that.
His Highness and you
are both benevolent.
All of them are just greedy.
His Highness helped
cover for General Wang
because he prioritised their bond.
But the imperial family is cruel.
Prioritising their bond
was actually wrong.
I don't get it at all.
How is that wrong?
It is only shameful
if His Highness loses his benevolence.
Everyone in this world
talks about principles
but I think
it's good enough
if we have a clear conscience.
Where is my brother?
I want to see him.
Your Highness.
His Highness
is meeting someone in his study.
He won't be seeing anyone today.
Who are you to talk back to me?
Are you even fit to be here
in the Eastern Palace?
Get out.
Father ordered Shaoshang
to prepare
for Mother's birthday banquet.
I have to help her as well.
That is why Shaoshang is here.
The Eastern Palace's position
will soon be lost.
How can you still pretend
to be virtuous at a moment like this?
That's all for today's meeting.
Brother.
Your Highness.
We will be leaving.
Fifth Sister.
Why are you making noise here?
Just let Wang Long die.
Do you think it's worth it
to anger Father and get replaced
as Crown Prince
because of a plebeian like him?
Fifth Sister.
Wang Long is your cousin as well.
How can you say something so heartless?
I'm heartless?
The Third Prince of Yongle Palace
has his eyes on
the position of Crown Prince
yet you're doing such a silly thing?
If you don't keep your place
as Crown Prince,
do we still have a foothold
in the future
as the children of Changqiu Palace?
Do you only have power and not family
in your heart?
If I only protect myself
without caring for my family's safety,
I'd rather not become
the Crown Prince.
Do you think
you are fit to become the Crown Prince?
If I am a man,
you won't even become the Crown Prince.
Your Highness, please mind your words.
You are saying this
because you know His Highness
will forgive you.
If His Highness is as decisive
as you said,
Fifth Princess,
you would have been convicted.
Fifth Sister.
You have been saying
His Highness should not anger Father.
Aren't you making Father angry
by refusing to get married as well?
His Highness never said anything
about your marriage.
Why did you get angry at His Highness
because your status is at risk?
Brother will definitely
not interfere with my marriage.
Didn't he marry you
no matter how reluctant he was?
Everyone in the palace knew
who Brother liked.
Brother pitied your family
for being poor
and you have nowhere to go
after your divorce
so you can become the Crown Princess.
You...
Fifth Sister, you should go back.
There's no need to come here
to the Eastern Palace
if there's nothing important.
When you marry into the Yue Family,
I will definitely prepare gifts for you.
You are really stubborn!
You just have to suffer
with the people of the Wang Family.
I'll go and find Mother!
How is Her Majesty?
Fifth Princess went inside
and angered Her Majesty
until her heart was palpitating.
She won't speak and eat right now.
I'll advise her.
But Her Majesty
doesn't want to see anyone.
I'm afraid it's useless
even if Lady Cheng goes in.
When parents are sick,
they might say
they don't want to see anyone
but deep down,
they want their children to rush in.
Don't you believe me, Madam Zhai?
I have a way.
You've never eaten for a whole day,
Your Majesty.
Have some food at least.
Don't believe
the rumours out there.
Your Majesty.
Look
what I brought you.
Her Majesty has a bad appetite.
She doesn't want to eat.
I'm not here
to persuade Her Majesty to eat.
I'm here to seek Her Majesty's help.
Your Majesty, look.
What is this?
This is...
I planted these cucumbers myself.
I finally grew them after a lot of time.
Cucumbers are tributes
from the Western Regions.
I've never eaten them
but Your Majesty did.
Please help me try them
and see if mine
is the same
as Western Region's cucumber.
Why is it so salty?
I marinated it with salt
but when I removed it
I added salt again.
I forgot about it.
Since it's that salty,
you should eat some porridge.
It's still salty, right?
Have some more.
Your cucumber
is really appetising.
I've eaten now.
You should be relieved now, right?
I'm not here to see you eat,
Your Majesty.
I'm here to seek your help.
You have yet to tell me
if my cucumber is better
than the Western Regions' cucumber.
You always have many wicked ideas.
How can I compare them
when it is so salty?
In that case,
I'll make
some sweeter ones later.
Why don't you try some sweet ones?
Sweet ones might not
balance out the saltiness.
Some sour ones then.
Sour ones will definitely do.
You are really shameless.
With your skills,
how much porridge do I need to eat
if I'm going to try them all?
I'm happy to see Your Majesty
willing to eat more porridge.
I still feel salty in my mouth.
Eat more porridge then.
Come on.
Let's go.
With Lady Cheng inside,
both of us should not disturb
Her Majesty's chat with Lady Cheng.
I didn't expect Her Majesty
to meet such a person
who can put her at ease.
Zisheng really got himself a good wife.
Lady Luo, why aren't you
inside serving Her Majesty?
Shaoshang is talking to Her Majesty.
Madam Zhai ordered us
not to disturb them.
This general's daughter
is good at making connections.
She only
entered the palace for a few days.
What?
Can we not step into the places
with her around?
We have yet to be married
to the Northwest
yet she is the one
to achieve a higher position instead.
Besides striving Her Majesty's favour,
even General Ling is...
If Lady Luo can marry General Ling,
we won't have to go to
a harsh place like the Northwest.
Chun Tiao, Shut up.
Don't speak about this again.
No matter how harsh the Northwest is,
it is still our fate.
Some people are born lucky.
They can marry a good husband
and receive
the imperial family's blessings.
Both of us can't complain about that.
Lady Luo.
You have such a good temper.
None of the princesses
will forgive her easily.
She didn't even see
if Her Majesty's children would agree
before trying to make connections.
Your Majesty.
This cucumber will be
the appetizer for the banquet.
What do you think?
We should use something normal.
The palace is promoting frugality.
How can I
use these ingredients
from the Western Regions?
I've already studied the method
to grow these cucumbers.
We can grow them ourselves.
It won't cost a lot.
I can even ask Zisheng to help
plough the land and build the sheds.
We just need a plot of land
in the hall to grow them.
We should let the officials
taste the cucumber
of the Western Regions.
How is that?
In the future,
I have to learn how to educate
a caring and clever child
from your parents.
I failed
to educate my children
because I knew nothing
about being a parent.
Your Majesty.
You need to summon my parents
to the palace soon.
My parents
always think I'm incapable
and ignorant.
There's nothing good about me.
Your Majesty,
after summoning my parents,
you have to praise me
so they know
I'm not incapable
and it's because they don't know
how to cherish me.
They always
envy other people's children.
Also,
you need to let them know
that a parent
who doesn't punish their children
like you
is a good parent.
No one uses the person in front of them
to replace their own parents.
However,
you are wrong.
Every parent in the world
is proud of their children.
Envying other people's children
is just a way to educate their children.
Just see if they are willing
to exchange you for someone else.
But making comparisons for a long time
will cause hatred
in children's hearts.
I'm sure parents
know such a simple theory.
However,
you only live once.
The responsibility of educating a child
is like sailing against the current.
You'll fall back if you don't progress.
There's no turning back.
Only when the child is stronger,
the parents can feel more relieved.
Forcing you
is actually
forcing ourselves in truth.
How is Mother feeling?
If Your Highness wants to know,
you can just go inside and have a look.
I am incapable.
Besides disappointing Father,
I even make Mother sad.
Father said
I appoint people by favouritism
and act emotionally.
Perhaps
I'm really not suitable
to become the Crown Prince.
Does Your Highness think
Her Majesty feels sad
because you are not a good Crown Prince?
It's because you are sad,
lost,
depressed,
criticised
and can't get up after you fell.
That is why she blamed herself
and felt sad.
She feels
she didn't protect you well enough
as a mother.
Your Highness is the Crown Prince,
but you are still
His Majesty and Her Majesty's son.
You shouldn't help General Wang
as the Crown Prince.
However, you can help your cousin
as a son.
There's no crime
in helping a family member.
Perhaps,
His Majesty might be disappointed
by the lenient Crown Prince.
But as a father,
how can he be disappointed
by a righteous son?
Your Highness.
If you grow apart
from His Majesty and Her Majesty
because of this,
they'll be really disappointed.
They'll only think
it is their education's fault.
Thank you for the reminder, Lady Cheng.
I understand.
I have yet to do anything
but these officials
are already thinking of
replacing the Crown Prince.
All of them are very ambitious.
Your Majesty, calm down.
The officials are only
guessing Your Majesty's intention
to follow your instructions.
They are not qualified to judge
whether my son
can handle an important responsibility.
Your Majesty.
His Highness is asking for an audience.
This child
is finally getting anxious.
Call him in.
Your Highness.
Greetings, Father.
Stand up.
Do you have anything
to say to me
by coming here late at night?
Father.
I want to play chess with you
because I can't sleep.
You are quite in the mood.
Sure.
Speaking of which,
it's been a long time
since we played chess.
When you just started learning chess,
you were always moving
and wouldn't sit still.
I had to stop myself
from sticking you here
beside the chessboard.
Did something good happen today?
You look like you're in a good mood.
I wasn't feeling happy at first
but I solved a trouble
so I feel happy.
Third Princess was punished
during my uncle's anniversary of death.
Did it
make you happy as well?
Sorry.
I didn't destroy
General Huo's altar on purpose.
I was just...
You always get angry because I do things
without discussing it with you
but didn't you
act on your own will as well?
Niaoniao.
It worries me
if you keep doing things recklessly.
Aren't you scolding me?
If you believe in me,
you can leave anything you want to do
to me.
You don't have
a foundation in the palace.
You should leave
making enemies to me.
Although I said
I will protect you
no matter what you do,
you still need to give me a chance.
Actually, today...
What happened today?
Her Majesty was not in a good mood today
because there was a rumour about
His Majesty replacing the Crown Prince.
Oh.
Did you know who was the person
acting against His Highness
at Yanhui Tower that day?
Shaoshang.
Over the years,
His Highness has been too benevolent
and never restricted
the actions of the people around him.
That is why incapable people
can be in a high position.
Many people in the royal court
are not satisfied with this.
This issue involves many parties.
Remember.
Don't interfere with this.
You should go to
the Eastern Palace less.
Oh.
What was
the good thing
you mentioned?
Her Majesty had
another bowl of porridge today.
Father.
I lost.
You lost?
Do you think I didn't realise it?
You were giving me a handicap
halfway through the game.
What's wrong?
Have you
followed the ways of the sycophants
of flattering me
and dare not win against me?
Father.
Do you still remember
how I learn to play this game?
In the past,
Father had yet to go out to war
and I was not the Crown Prince.
Father was making the board
using stones to carve out words
at the old house
just to teach me the game.
Father always gave me a handicap
to get me interested in the game.
A child like me
who just learned the game
could actually win against Father
in every game.
Father could
win against me back then.
Why did you give me a handicap?
It was because
Father cared about my feelings
more than the result of the game.
It is the same for me today.
In my heart,
a family member's feeling
is more important
than the result of the conflict.
Even if I lose in the end,
I still
won't regret anything.
I understand.
It's already late.
Go back and rest.
Don't miss
tomorrow's morning assembly.
Yes.
I've read
all of your memorials.
The Crown Prince
is
forgiving, benevolent,
loyal and filial.
He was not as incapable
as all of you said.
I have decided
for Crown Prince to hold the tiger seal.
The three armies
will be under his command.
Grand the tiger seal to Crown Prince.
Thank you, Father.
I will never disappoint Father's trust.
Your Majesty.
I have something to say.
Wang Chun
allowed his son, Wang Long
to leave camp and suppress the bandits.
He put the army in danger.
Your Majesty.
They were
ignoring a military command.
Marquis Yue, you are wrong.
The bandits disturbed
the peace of the people.
As the defending general,
General Wang Long
had to maintain peace there.
How can suppressing bandits for the people
be said as ignoring a military command?
I'm not done talking.
Why are you interrupting me,
Grand Tutor Lou?
Did he go to suppress the bandits?
As far as I know, Wang Long
has already
fallen into the bandits' trap.
We don't even know
whether he's dead or alive.
Your Majesty.
General Wang Long is in danger
because he was leading the army.
I don't understand
why Marquis Yue
is taking pleasure in his misfortune.
What do you mean?
They are just
some bandits
that we didn't eliminate in the past.
Wang Long is incapable.
What's the purpose
of judging whether he's right or wrong?
In my opinion,
we should send troops
and eliminate these bandits.
We can use this opportunity
to fill our treasury as well.
That's easy for you to say.
General Wu is retiring soon
and General Ling is getting married.
Who will lead the troops?
Your Majesty.
I'm willing to become the vanguard
and kill them all.
We are discussing
how to punish Wang Chun for his crimes.
You should stop meddling.
How am I meddling?
That's enough.
All of you have stated your opinions.
It's time for me
to say something.
The bandits
disturbed the peace of the people.
It was reasonable
for Wang Long
to send troops to suppress them.
However,
he was reckless
and caused his army
to be caught in a dangerous situation.
He is not fit to become a general.
However,
this is Wang Long's mistake.
How is it related to his father,
Wang Chun?
From today onwards,
the command of Wang Long's troops
will be handed over to his father.
He will be
demoted immediately.
As for suppressing the bandits,
Zisheng.
Yes.
You should discuss
with the other generals
and depart
when you have decided on a strategy.
Crown Prince.
Yes.
I've handed the tiger seal to you.
When the time comes,
you will send the troops
on the Command Altar.
Yes!
Father finally agreed
to send troops to rescue Cousin.
Zisheng.
I've been thinking a lot
and I still think the tiger seal
is not safe at the Eastern Palace.
Why don't I
give it to you to keep it safe?
His Majesty handed over the tiger seal
proving His Majesty's trust
in Your Highness.
The tiger seal
needs to be kept by Your Highness
and not be given to anyone else.
When the time comes to send the troops,
Your Highness needs it
to command the troops.
But...
But I...
Don't worry.
The palace has tight security.
As long as you don't take it
out of the Eastern Palace,
no one dares to steal it.
I still have something
I don't understand.
His Majesty wanted
to punish General Wang at first.
I wonder how
Your Highness persuaded His Majesty.
It's all thanks to Shaoshang.
I had a game with Father yesterday
and spoke about my childhood.
Father decided to give General Wang
and me another chance
because of our family bonds.
Zisheng.
Both you and your wife
are really my lucky star.
Oh.
What was
the good thing
you mentioned?
Why are you staring at me
without saying anything?
You asked His Highness
to express goodwill to His Majesty?
His Majesty will no longer
punish Wang Chun now.
Are you satisfied with that?
What do you mean?
Because of your plans
to help His Highness,
His Majesty has decided
to let the Wang Family go.
Shaoshang.
I've reminded you time and again
not to interfere
with the Eastern Palace's matters.
Don't involve yourself
in the conflicts of the court.
Why wouldn't you listen to me?
I just want to help Her Majesty out.
Do you want me to see Her Majesty
suffer all by herself
without helping her?
I don't care about
what happens to Wang Chun.
Her Majesty treats me sincerely.
I need to think for her.
What if the things you did
cause me trouble?
Her Majesty sees you as her own son.
His Highness sees you
as his own brother.
They raised you.
Why are you not happy
when His Majesty is no longer punishing
Her Majesty and His Highness?
Do you think what you did was right?
Didn't you see how Madam Wen Xiu
threatened Her Majesty?
Now that His Majesty
has forgiven the Wang Family,
all the officials of the court
will shift their hatred
to Her Majesty and His Highness.
Do you know
someone has been eyeing
the position at the Eastern Palace?
What you did
might harm His Highness
instead of helping him.
Not only will you harm him,
but you might also
involve Her Majesty in this.
You are putting them
in grave danger.
All of these...
I know nothing about all these.
I never thought so much about it.
Since you don't know,
you should stop doing things recklessly.
Shaoshang.
I'm going to tell you again.
Matters in the palace
will be affected
even from a very trivial matter.
It is not as simple as you think.
The most complicated thing
in this world
is you.
You always say I don't understand.
But you've never wanted
me to understand.
Your plans, your stratagems
and your thoughts.
You didn't tell me any of them.
How can I avoid them?
It's not that I don't want to tell you.
It's because all of these
are too complicated.
But...
But I don't have to care about
all these complicated things at first.
I could marry a normal man
and live a normal life.
The royal court,
the palace
and His Majesty
are none of my business. Ling Buyi.
You are the one
who dragged me into this.
We were supposed to be
people from both ends of the world.
I was flustered and hesitated
at the beginning of this marriage.
When I finally decided to be with you
and do something that I don't like,
you kept telling me
that your world
is too complicated for me.
A fool like me
is not supposed to get involved in this.
I'm not teasing you, Shaoshang.
I just don't want you to be in danger.
I just want the best for you.
My mother used to say this to me too.
All of you want the best for me
because I'm not good enough,
right?
I really don't know
how I can satisfy you
and still stay who I am.
But this is who I am.
I don't care about the consequences
and only do things of my own will.
Sorry for disappointing you.
Shaoshang.
I will go back on my own today.
(Do you think what you did was right?)
(Now that His Majesty)
(has forgiven the Wang Family,)
(all the officials of the court
will shift their hatred)
(to Her Majesty and His Highness.)
(Do you know)
(someone has been eyeing
the position at the Eastern Palace?)
(What you did)
(might harm His Highness)
(instead of helping him.)
(Not only will you harm him,)
(but you might also
involve Her Majesty in this.)
(You are putting them)
(in grave danger.)
It's so troublesome
being married to Ling Buyi.
The beacon-fire has knocked
over the white snow
I caress the scars gently
from the past
Your back to the light,
your eyes contain the galaxy
I hum as the sun
and the moon mutter back
The light between your brows
Was put out and rekindled
by the secular world
The sky, the mountain, and the ocean,
whom do I part them for?
As I wake up from the blue sea,
stone steles stand like a mountain range
Under the lantern, criticisms were thrown,
the narrow door could not contain my feelings
The joys and woes of this mortal life,
we speak as we dream of the future
Both of us will be
In the sea of stars,
burning bright with our sincerity
Our sincerity