= Love Like The Galaxy=
=Episode 22=
As ruler and subject,
gold is the element.
As father and child,
wood is the element.
As siblings,
fire is the element.
As husband and wife,
water is the element.
Seems like she's going to
have good luck in love.
Seems like Niaoniao
might find a better man
after losing out on Lou Yao.
Excuse me.
(Ban Jia)
Do you know the way back?
Oh no.
She's going to suffer
bad luck in love instead.
This...
Qiqi,
didn't you say
that Young Marquis Ban held this hunt
in order to make acquaintances
with everyone?
Where is he then?
That's right.
Shaogong
isn't here as well.
He needs a quiet spot
to perform divination.
Li.
Someone is shameless indeed.
She loves to flock
to places filled with men.
What are you saying?
She's one to talk
when she's present herself.
How could you put us on
the same level as you?
Lady Wang's father is
the Cavalry General.
She has been practicing mounted archery
with her father all along.
She's here to have a competition,
unlike someone else.
Who do you mean?
She wasn't embarrassed even though
her marriage was canceled.
She actually has the guts to go outside.
Shaoshang only canceled the marriage
out of her respect
for the heroes of the He Family.
She fulfilled their dying wish.
Lady Wang, why did you make it
sound like something embarrassing?
Could it be
that you think slaying enemies
on the battlefield and sacrificing
one's life for the nation
are embarrassing deeds?
Qiqi, you may ignore her.
When have I said that sacrificing one's
life for the nation is embarrassing?
Since when did I say that?
Besides,
my father is the Cavalry General.
He taught me mounted archery before.
I'm not inferior to you.
Someone is trying to show off
even though
she's only a beginner.
We grew up
on the back of horses.
Even so, we never
bragged about our skills.
Shameless wretch.
Wan Qiqi,
don't be too full of yourself.
Have a competition with me if you dare.
Come on then.
Do you think I'm scared of you?
Come on!
Qiqi.
Qiqi!
I'll spar with her.
This is bad.
I never expected
the proud Lady Cheng
to be this subservient.
I've already told you the story
of Changmen Fu, haven't I?
Why do you still not understand?
A life without love
is truly free.
Seems like the talented gentleman
of Mount Bailu
has turned into a bigmouth.
Yuan Shanjian, listen up.
I don't wish to talk to you today.
You better shut up.
You can enjoy your free life
without any love.
Master,
regarding Changmen Fu...
All right. I understand.
It's Mr. Yuan Shanjian!
Mr. Yuan Shanjian!
Ladies,
please calm down.
I heard that there's a path ahead.
Calm down.
Slow down.
Please calm down.
You actually got lost
when we're this near to the campsite?
Even if you can't recognize the road,
you can actually tell
from the loud noise over there.
I really wonder how you managed
to survive until now.
My parents said
that I was difficult
to raise since young.
That's why they didn't allow me
to head outside.
You and I are fated to meet.
You're my first friend.
This is ill-fated.
I wouldn't have gotten the ill love lot
if you didn't kick my divination
by accident.
What is the ill love lot?
-Mr. Yuan.
-Mr. Yuan, wait.
Slow down.
Calm down.
-Mr. Yuan.
-Mr. Yuan, slow down.
Please stop chasing after me.
-Slow down.
-Slow down, Mr. Yuan.
This is
the power of the ill love lot.
Please stop following me.
It's scary when there are so many people.
It's even scarier
when all of them are girls.
-Mr. Yuan, wait.
-Mr. Yuan, slow down.
The peach tree beams so red,
how brilliant are its flowers.
The maiden’s getting wed,
good for the nuptial bowers.
Seems like I'm in luck today.
(Yanhui Tower)
(So, this is how they build towers.)
(It's actually structured
like an umbrella.)
(The sole pillar acts as the support.)
(The scattered bucket  structure)
(will shoulder the weight of the tower.)
(This is amazing indeed.)
(Yanhui Tower)
(I just lost a husband-to-be.)
(So what?)
(I am still me.)
Now that Lou Yao had married
the daughter of the He Family,
His Majesty felt sorry
for the Lou Family.
He's being more and more
lenient toward the Lou Family.
His Majesty even turned a blind eye
to Grand Tutor Lou's despicable deeds
of suppressing officials
of ordinary birth by taking advantage
of the Eastern Palace's influence.
If we want His Majesty to be entirely
disappointed with the Eastern Palace,
we need...
The Eastern Palace
houses a bunch of useless fools.
I'm sure His Majesty will strip
the crown prince of his position.
Who's there?
Go and check it out.
Don't move!
Don't be scared.
Don't move! Hold tight!
Don't let go!
I heard a sound from
three floors below us.
How did the person disappear
all of a sudden?
Let's go and check it out.
Get up!
Come inside!
You can head back for now.
I'll send some men to search the area.
Don't worry.
I'll find the culprit
even if it means I have
to flip the hill upside down.
General Ling, are you okay?
What about you?
Were you frightened?
General, did you sustain this injury
in Feng Yi County?
It's just an old injury of mine.
It doesn't matter.
Lady Cheng,
what did you hear just now?
I heard something about
stripping the crown prince's position...
You heard nothing.
Do you understand?
That's right.
I heard nothing.
I was just passing by
while I was taking my walk.
You've never passed by this area before.
You must keep today's matter
a secret.
Do not let anyone know about this.
Let's go.
Let me send you back.
No need for that, General Ling.
General Ling, thank you for rescuing me.
My horse is nearby.
I will head back myself.
It's unsafe for you to do so.
Let me send you back.
Let's go.
Wang Ling,
it doesn't matter
if you fire the last arrow or not.
What about this?
I'll go easy on you.
You don't need to do mounted archery.
You can stand in front of the target.
It's your win if you hit it.
What do you think?
Good boy.
Fine!
Stop!
Wan Qiqi!
Be careful! Stop now!
The horse was startled! I can't tame it!
Song!
Song, were you hurt anywhere? Get up!
Don't move!
Don't look!
Why can't I look?
Cheng Song, listen up.
If you're crippled
because of this incident,
I'll support you forever.
You mustn't look!
I've seen plenty of situations
like these in the military camp.
Why can't I look?
I did tell you not to look, didn't I?
You just had to look, hadn't you?
Now,
you have to be responsible for me
for the rest of your life.
We're here.
General Ling, thank you
for saving me once again.
I don't know when
I'll be able to repay the favor.
Before this,
I even said I would play the flute for
you when you returned victoriously...
This is not the time for this.
Lady Cheng,
are you truly not
worried about your life?
Why do you say so?
General Ling,
that is my jade pendant.
My nickname is on it.
Ruoruo?
That's an interesting nickname.
What Ruoruo?
It's Niaoniao.
But half of the pendant is missing.
If those two got a hold
of your pendant,
they would know that
you eavesdropped on their conversation.
Say, do you think it's better
for them to keep it?
Or do you think
it's better for me to keep it?
Both choices
are terrible.
You should let me keep it.
However, even without the pendant,
they can find out who eavesdropped
on their conversation
by doing a headcount.
Why are we still here then?
We should hurry back before
they do a headcount.
General Ling, your injury...
I'm lucky that I was injured before.
What a disgrace!
(Empress Xuan)
People are easily excited during spring and summer.
Young Marquis Ban prepared
so many exciting events for them.
Those lads and ladies
are young and vigorous.
I can understand
if they get carried away.
What do you mean?
The lady from the Wan Family and Ling
almost lost their lives
because of a trifle!
The brat from the Cheng Family
was even wounded because of it.
And those ladies,
they chase after Yuan Shanjian
whenever they see him.
What a disgrace!
And,
I've already heard
that some young couples
have been caught.
They went overboard this time.
Why do you think I came to Mount Tugao?
I came here to pray for
my people's fortune.
Yet, they came here to commit
such audacious acts?
Ridiculous.
It's an utter disgrace!
Your Majesty, it's my fault
for not disciplining Wang Ling well.
(Noble Consort Yue)
Your Majesty, why are you
taking the blame for everything?
Your Majesty, in my opinion,
this isn't a huge deal at all.
Your Majesty, in the past,
you scaled the palace wall
to reach the backyard so that
you could meet me in secret.
You even fell into the drain before.
It's not strange for young people
to mingle around and have some fun.
Heng,
why did you bring up the past?
So, Your Majesty,
how do you plan to deal with them?
Naturally, I'll punish them severely.
Say, do you think His Majesty
will blame us for this?
Why don't I tell His Majesty
that everything was my fault
and that it has nothing to do with you?
How could it have nothing to do with me?
His Majesty wouldn't have been furious
if I didn't bleed during
the prayer ceremony
and render the ceremony inauspicious.
Even so, you did so to save me.
In my opinion,
it's all Wang Ling's fault.
It's all because she bore
a grudge against Niaoniao.
That's why she hated it
when I stood up for Niaoniao.
Be careful.
The wound is getting wider and wider.
I'll fix it for you when we get back.
His Majesty is here.
Both of you, shut up.
Dear, you do not need to worry.
Song was wounded
because he tried to save someone.
His Majesty won't punish him severely.
I'm not worried about Song.
General, have you seen
Niaoniao around today?
What if His Majesty found out that
Niaoniao didn't return here?
What should we do by then?
You're right.
Where's Niaoniao?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, General Ling has returned.
He returned together with
Fourth Lady Cheng.
I heard that General Ling
risked his life to save
Fourth Lady Cheng when
she almost fell off a cliff.
Due to that, his old wound opened up.
Fourth Lady Cheng is crying profusely.
She said she would repay
General Ling with her life.
He went to save Fourth Lady Cheng again?
Good.
Zisheng
does resemble the past me now.
Your Majesty, you haven't told me
how you plan to punish them.
Our goal is to pray for our people
and have some fun while we're here.
It's common
for young people like them to be playful
and impulsive.
Besides,
didn't I behave just like them
when I was young?
Am I right?
All right. I shall not
pursue responsibilities
against those young people.
Cao Cheng,
let's go and check on Zisheng.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, slow down!
My dear subjects.
Get up.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'm not talking to you.
Go.
Cheng Shi, please get up.
Your Majesty.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Be honest with me.
What exactly happened?
I almost fell off a cliff.
General Ling's old wound
reopened after he saved me.
I feel terrible.
All right.
That's good enough.
Just repeat the same thing
to His Majesty when we see His Majesty later.
His Majesty?
All right.
General Ling,
please rest well. I shall take my leave.
I got injured because of you.
Is this how you treat me?
His Majesty has arrived.
Zisheng.
Did you get hurt again?
You were too careless.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Shaoshang,
you better greet His Majesty properly.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Tell His Majesty your name
before you initiate your greeting.
Your Majesty,
my daughter, Cheng Shaoshang,
is not familiar with imperial customs.
Please pardon her.
Let me ask you something.
How exactly did Zisheng's
old wound open up?
Lady Cheng was riding a horse
when she almost
fell off a cliff by accident.
I was passing by.
Therefore, I saved her.
That's why the old wound
on my shoulder reopened.
So, it's because you saved her?
Lady Cheng,
have you met Zisheng
before this accident?
We've met several times before.
That's why I could not ignore her.
I'm asking Lady Cheng, not you.
Lady Cheng,
if so, where have you met
Zisheng before?
Your Majesty,
you could've asked me the same thing.
Don't speak.
I only want her to answer me.
Lady Cheng,
Zisheng
is one of my most important subjects
and the pillar of the nation.
Now, he got injured because of you.
I've lost one of
my trusted aides as well.
Do you know your fault?
Your Majesty,
she didn't mean to fall off the cliff.
Please forgive her.
Your Majesty, I wouldn't have gone
to save her
if I knew you were
trying to frighten her.
Cheng Shi,
Zisheng is the pillar of the nation.
His old wound was reopened
due to your daughter.
He has saved your entire family.
You should remember his kindness
until the end of time
and repay his kindness.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I will definitely repay his kindness
in return.
Forget it.
Lady Cheng has suffered
a minor shock.
You two may leave
for now.
I will speak to Zisheng in private.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Shaoshang.
Be honest with me.
You and Lady Cheng...
I was just passing by,
and I saved her
purely out of coincidence.
It's nothing to talk about.
Fine.
Whatever you say then.
Tomorrow, you should
follow me back to the palace
and let Physician Sun
treat your wounds.
Your Majesty,
thank you for your kindness.
However, physicians in my residence
are experts in treating
traumatic injuries.
I can recuperate in my residence.
What?
Do you think your physicians
are better than Physician Sun?
I assume someone
wants to be in the residence
just in case the lady he had rescued
wants to visit him, huh?
I'm afraid of His Majesty.
Who are you afraid of?
I almost lost my life there.
Do you think I'm not afraid?
Why did you return with
that Ling Buyi again?
Today, I...
I just...
Father,
I would've fallen off the cliff
if General Ling didn't save me.
You wouldn't be able
to see me again by then.
Don't tell me it was purely
a coincidence
that he saved you in the nick of time
right before you fell off the cliff?
There are plenty of
coincidences in the world.
Just like how you married Mother.
That was also a coincidence.
If you had married Madam Ge,
your daughter would be Yangyang
instead of me.
-Such nonsense!
-If your daughter would be Yangyang...
Your mother and I, we...
I'll make a move now.
Could it be that I was overthinking it?
I'm sure Zisheng
is recuperating at home on purpose
so that Lady Cheng can visit him.
In my opinion, not only is Lady Cheng
ordinary,
but she also lacks courtesy.
You should take a nap.
This...
Why is this fruit so bitter?
Your Majesty.
A few years ago, some of your subjects
had sent some
beautiful women to Zisheng.
Your Majesty was afraid that Zisheng
might marry them
instead of being as pure-hearted as Huo.
You were so worried that
you couldn't even sleep at night.
Did that truly happen?
Yes, it did.
I was worried
that he might fall prey to temptation
and ruin his conduct.
Was I wrong for thinking that?
After that, Zisheng sent
all the women back.
He never touched a single woman.
He was always alone.
Your Majesty was worried that he might
rise from the common herd
and stay alone forever.
Did that truly happen?
Yes, it did.
I was afraid that he might be
too pure-hearted.
It would harm his bodily functions.
Was I wrong for thinking that?
After that, I heard Zisheng
had someone he fancied.
Your Majesty was afraid that the lady
might be already betrothed.
Did that truly happen?
I was just afraid that
he might lose out on a potential mate.
Was I wrong for thinking that?
Now that this lady had
canceled her marriage,
Your Majesty looked down on her
for being too ordinary.
But Your Majesty frets about
Zisheng's relationship
every day.
That's why I thought
this unripe fruit was best for you,
Your Majesty.
It's sour and bitter,
just like your heart.
How could anyone
know how sour and bitter I feel inside?
Zisheng had a rough life since young.
Your Majesty, I'm getting tired.
His uncle and the Huo Clan
had sacrificed everything
for the nation's sake.
Your Majesty, I'm tired.
Now, every official in
the imperial court
is...
What are you doing?
Since you have a court
full of imperial officials,
why did you need a woman like me
to come up with ideas for you?
Your Majesty, since you're busy,
I shall not see you off.
Heng, listen to me.
I just wanted to have a chat with you.
I don't mean anything else.
Cao Cheng, tend to His Majesty's needs.
His Majesty has arrived.
Shen'an.
You may drop the formalities
when we're outside.
I feel troubled,
and I think you can
come up with solutions for me.
I dare not interfere
with state affairs.
Your Majesty, you should return
and discuss them with
your loyal subjects.
It isn't about the state.
Sit down.
I was just fretting over
Zisheng's wound.
That's why, my dear,
I hope you can think of an idea for me.
Your Majesty,
I do not dare to make the call here.
I think we should head back
and let Physician Sun
examine his wound for now.
Actually, it isn't about his wound.
You've heard it as well.
Zisheng was injured
all because
of that young lady of the Cheng Family.
Seems like Zisheng fancies her.
Zisheng is still young.
He knows nothing
about true love.
Your Majesty, you're right.
Although Zisheng has seen countless
people, he has never fallen for anyone.
We can see
that he isn't infatuated with love.
Not necessarily.
As the saying goes,
gentlemen desire fair maidens.
If so, why can't Zisheng
desire a partner?
Your Majesty, you're right.
Heroes are always prisoners of love.
It's common for Zisheng
to fall for someone.
It's pretty uncommon too.
He just had to recuperate
in his residence.
If I knew this would happen,
I wouldn't have granted him a residence.
Your Majesty, you have a point.
The physicians he has are definitely
inferior to the imperial physicians.
Why don't we
summon him into the palace?
Summon him into the palace?
He will be restricted
if he has to recuperate in the palace.
I don't think it'll do his recovery
any good.
Your Majesty is wise.
I shall obey you.
Your Majesty, slow down.
Tell me then.
Do you think Lady Cheng
is good enough for our Zisheng?
Your Majesty,
God is the only one
who can decide
if she's good enough for him.
Your Majesty's worries are unfounded.
Great answer.
Cao Cheng,
you are
better than the two of them.
I do not deserve such praises.
But what if
God is blind?
Your Majesty!
You are
nothing.
General,
can you stop pacing back and forth
in front of me?
You're making me dizzy here.
How many times has it been?
What do you mean?
How many times has Ling Buyi
saved Niaoniao?
That's right.
It's been several times.
This won't do. I have to ask Niaoniao
about the details.
Dear, you should stop.
Even if they do have feelings
for each other,
I guess Niaoniao will be too stubborn
to admit the truth in front of us.
I'm just afraid that our worries
might come true.
Dear, you might not know,
but His Majesty was clearly
on General Ling's side yesterday.
His Majesty even reminded me
to thank him
and repay his kindness.
If so,
why don't you and Niaoniao
visit General Ling together?
I'm not proper to go.
Naturally, you should go.
This is the time
for you to shine.
It never rains, but it pours.
This is so worrying.
Time's up.
Song is still injured.
I'll deliver the medicine to him.
Song cannot turn his body around now.
I'll help him out.
Hurry up.
Stop right there.
I haven't permitted you guys to go yet.
Who permitted you guys to leave?
Cheng Song only suffered a scratch.
There's no need for three people
to tend to his needs.
You guys should've kept quiet
if that was the best excuse
you could come up with.
Since you guys are so absent-minded,
it'll make me look bad
for keeping you guys here.
Leave now.
Let's go!
Wait.
The others may leave.
But Shaoshang,
you will stay.
Let's go.
Three mistakes in five words.
Fourth Lady Cheng, your writing ability
is truly
impressive.
I've been busy lately.
I didn't have time
to practice my writing.
Master, I'm sure you know that well.
Ling Zisheng got injured for saving you
right after
you canceled your marriage with Lou Yao.
I guess you were busy indeed.
Master, you don't need
to beat around the bush.
You may get straight
to the point.
I just wish to advise you
to learn more about
how to be a decent human.
If you intend to use marriage
as an excuse to seek freedom,
you'll regret it sooner or later.
You're still green to the world.
Did you think you could escape
your family and lead a carefree life
after you got married?
Little did you know
that another person
would be tying you down.
Do you think getting married
into a noble family is a great thing?
Don't you understand the truth
after your dispute with the Lou Family?
There's no need for you to be in a rush
and approach Ling Buyi.
Who said I was using my marriage
as an excuse to seek freedom?
Who said I approached
Ling Buyi on purpose?
Yuan Shanjian,
you must be sick in the head.
Did I offend you in any way?
Why must you think of people
in such a lowly manner?
That's far from being the case.
I just can't bear to see you falling prey
to people's trickery
due to your ignorance.
I'm just giving you a friendly reminder.
You should stay away from Ling Buyi.
I told you already.
Yuan...
Shaoshang,
I met Father just now.
He told me to ask you
to head to General Ling's residence
to repay his kindness for saving you.
Master,
we study in order to reason.
However, listening to our parents
is a must.
My father wants me to visit
my benefactor.
I assume you have no reason to stop me.
Lady Cheng, you forgot the pain
now that your wounds had healed.
I just hope
that you won't regret it in the future.
♪The beacon-fire has knocked
over the white snow♪
♪I caress the scars gently
from the past♪
♪Your back to the light,
your eyes contain the galaxy♪
♪I hum as the sun
and the moon mutter back♪
♪The light between your brows♪
♪Was put out and rekindled
by the secular world♪
♪The sky, the mountain, and the ocean,
whom do I part them for?♪
♪As I wake up from the blue sea,
stone steles stand like a mountain range♪
♪Under the lantern, criticisms were thrown,
the narrow door could not contain my feelings♪
♪The joys and woes of this mortal life,
we speak as we dream of the future♪
♪Both of us will be♪
♪In the sea of stars,
burning bright with our sincerity♪
♪Our sincerity♪