Don't be mistaken
thinking that you know me so well.
I doubt you have any idea
what kind of a person I am.
I was wrong about you.
I really have no single idea
of what kind of a person you are, Platoon Leader.
I don't even want to know anymore. But...
I do want to know what happened to Song I.
You should mind your own business.
No, I must know.
Say it now. Say it.
I said, "Say it!"
Please hold yourself back, Platoon Leader.
That comrade is quite awful, but please just let it go.
Enough is enough. How dare you disrespect your superior!
Lloyd, you can get locked up for this, you idiot.
Say you're sorry, man.
Why don't you just take this?
I was wrong about you.
I really have no single idea
what kind of a person you are, Platoon Leader.
I don't even want to know anymore.
Relax, man.
Tell me what happened, Lloyd. What's going on?
Lloyd, I knew that
you'd get beaten up one day by Comrade Platoon Leader.
You aren't any better than her.
How long have you known about the latest mission?
Before the filming?
What do you mean? You were the only one who didn't know about it!
You said we were fellow soldiers.
You said we were on the same team!
Comrade No, we had no idea
that you didn't know about it.
We thought that you knew all about the mission.
Isn't it odd that you were the only one who didn't know about it?
Don't you think so?
You're going to get locked up.
It's Han Song I's jacket found in Comrade No's locker.
I didn't find anything noteworthy.
You may go.
Unification.
I'll give you a holiday pass.
Go rest up for a few days.
I have guard duty for the upcoming event—
I said, rest up.
Thank you, Comrade Vice Commissioner.
Hello, Yeon Gyeong? It's me, Lloyd.
My goodness. You're finally answering my call.
You ignored my text message too.
I'm not doing it.
But you can't say no before hearing me out.
Whenever you call me, it is never good news, Vice Commissioner Lee.
This time, it's good news.
It's a party. A special garden party.
No, thanks.
It's the mayor's order.
You must attend.
I'm not interested.
Wait.
Quality information. Quality information.
There will be guerrilla training soon.
It'll be very rigorous.
I'm hanging up now.
Guerrilla training…
But guerrilla training is really rigorous.
Then, right before the peace treaty,
they were all named warriors. Is that right?
Because they were dispatched to the South concealing their social class from the start,
the Republic gave them social status and compensation thereafter.
I see.
Is everything well with Comrade Director?
Yes, my father is well.
Sorry to bother him with a trivial request when he's so busy.
It's not a problem.
You may go.
Unification.
I've been looking for you everywhere.
You have time for that?
Don't you have guerrilla training soon?
I'm in great shape. Please don't worry.
You must survive on your own at this guerrilla training.
If you fail, you die.
Don't you know why I came back here?
It's because of Song I.
Stop leaving me out of things and cooperate.
Must I repeat myself?
It's none of your business.
Complete your military duty diligently
and get discharged.
Okay, okay.
If that's how you're going to be,
I'll just figure it out on my own.
Figure what out on your own?
I can think for myself.
Don't bother thinking.
If you behave flippantly,
I'll not let it slide then.
Not let it slide? What can you do anyway?
Going forward, you won't be allowed
to leave or stay out overnight.
Got that?
That's too harsh.
But…
Hello?
Attorney Seo Hee Ji?
Wait.
Didn't we agree to be friends?
Oh, right.
We're friends.
You agreed too easily.
It seems like you have a favor to ask.
Were you able to find out anything about Han Song I?
I want to be the first one to know.
There isn't much information in the South.
Other than the fact that she's a big fan of FITA.
Pyeonghwa City's security is on the line.
And it really seems like she has ties to North Korea.
The key thing is there's information that she's a hacker.
A hacker?
Anything else?
At this point, it should be "give and take."
Do me a favor too.
A South Korean conglomerate is hosting
and Pyeonghwa City is supporting this fundraising party.
Will you attend it as my partner?
I'm sorry, but I don't want to go to that.
You don't want to go?
But I have another important piece of information.
No, I don't want to…
Important information?
Where are you going?
You sister is coming.
I'll be right back.
I heard someone's giving out free gifts.
Don't go too far. Okay?
Okay.
Don't run!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Here.
Are you heading to the store?
Yes. Why?
Well, my sister said she was coming,
but I'm not familiar with the streets, so I'm really late.
Then she must be worried.
Should we head over together?
Mi Rae.
Where have you been?
I was worried.
Sis.
Don't scold her too harshly.
I think she got lost trying to get back.
Don't go out by yourself again.
Understood?
You got lucky.
You ran into me, so you didn't get lost,
and you got a nice gift too.
Thank you, Comrade Seong.
Come on. Don't call me, "Comrade Seong."
Just call me "oppa" from now on.
That's how they all refer to each other in South Korea.
Bye, Mi Rae.
Let's go.
Don't go around by yourself again. Okay?
There you go. All finished.
You need to take your medicine now.
It doesn't taste good.
You don't take medicine for its taste.
Don't make me worry and just take it. Okay?
"Don't run. Eat slowly."
"Don't skip your medicine."
Did I nag that much?
Your hand looks just like Mother's.
Your hands take after Mother's.
I take after Father.
Mi Rae, when you grow up,
you're going to become such a beauty like Mother.
- Really?
- Yes.
So take good care of yourself until you get surgery. Okay?
And don't get into trouble.
Gosh, you're nagging again.
So just tell me exactly what that is.
You'll be in danger if you hold on to that.
No, actually,
I need to make sure you don't have it
to ensure your safety.
I'm about to go insane. Seriously.
What's this?
Is something wrong with Mi Rae?
Her heart
has some issues.
Have a quick drink and sleep tight.
If you worry too much,
you'll grow old.
Comrade Jae Hoon.
Call me Jae Hoon.
Is that the right name?
Weren't you, along with your name, reported dead?
So you knew already.
Seong Jae Hoon of the Republic did die.
The person who is here now
is Lee Jae Hoon, the bartender of Uno Pub.
This one thought came to mind after being on the verge of death numerous times.
"For once,
I want to live an ordinary life like everyone else."
You've never thought that way?
You need to eat a lot to be healthy.
Try this too.
Look.
Which one is prettier?
They're both pretty.
Are you going somewhere nice?
The old man from Uno Pub
and I were invited to an event for separated families.
I heard that many high-ranking officers of Pyeonghwa City will be there too,
so I plan to ask them to grant all our requests.
Is that right?
Then I'll call a taxi for you.
You can ride it there with Mr. Seok.
The owner of Uno Pub was invited too,
so don't worry about our transportation.
I never thought I'd have to take care of you while you were in the military.
- Hey.
- It stinks here.
I have a question.
When I joined the military, I heard someone at the company was so excited
that he or she even clapped. Do you know who that was?
I'm so happy that I even canceled my vacation to be with you.
Do you have any desire to re-enlist with the Unified Armed Force Unit?
You can even eat chocolate here.
Lloyd, there's a more urgent task here.
A Carlini suit is a must.
What do you think, Lloyd? I've got good sense, right?
Your partner in crime and everlasting stylist.
Jeong Man Gong, you know?
I'm so amazing.
Where are you going?
What's it to you?
Aren't we combatting separately on our own?
I thought I told you, you aren't allowed to leave.
Did you forget?
I told them that I didn't want to go to a formal, fundraising party.
But the people at the top
insisted that I attend as a VIP.
That's why I'm going.
The unit members all went in security vehicles. Why don't you come with me?
I'm not interested.
It's not that you're not interested,
but perhaps you've been excluded from guard duty.
Don't you know me well? That's not the case.
How would I know what kind of a person you are, Platoon Leader?
It's not like we were close.
I didn't complain, but frankly speaking,
whenever we run into each other, don't terrible things happen?
I got stabbed, shot, fell off a cliff,
and swimming in the water and kissing…
Have you ever thought about why you keep
endangering yourself?
If anyone overhears you, he or she might mistakenly think you're concerned about me.
I'd never be, so don't you worry.
Wait!
This is...
my leave pass.
Keep up the good work. Unification!
It seems small in scale and private,
but quite a lot of political and business leaders come to this party.
They can be cold-blooded when it comes to their own benefits,
but they act nice on the outside.
Enjoy networking.
Why is today's party
noted on Song I's schedule?
The owner of Uno Pub was invited too,
so don't worry about our transportation.
And...
what's "dress code"?
"Dress code"?
It says, I must wear something purple.
You can't go in looking like that.
What do you mean?
This is a party.
You can't go in wearing a military uniform.
I'll be quick. Step aside.
The mayor will be here too.
Don't you know the manual?
Platoon Leader!
We meet again, Vice Commissioner Lee.
Yes, hello. What brings you here?
This is the mayor of our city, Pyeonghwa City—
Mom, this is my friend, Lloyd.
Lloyd, please say hello. It's my mom.
Thank you all for coming looking stunning.
Especially, Mr. Lloyd,
nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Wait,
mom and daughter…
Aren't I a little more beautiful than my mom?
Yes, of course.
Excellent.
Mr. Lloyd.
I really look forward to your speech
regarding the donation after dinner.
Sp… Speech?
Sure, the speech. Yes.
What happened?
Come on. Please.
Speech, my foot.
Thank you.
Can I get a refill, please?
I didn't make a fuss to save your face.
But I can't do this anymore.
But you asked me to help you.
Just one more. Just one more.
Just one last time with this one.
Please.
These shoes go with that dress. Make sure she wears them.
Otherwise, she'd just come in her military boots.
Excuse me.
Can you tell me where these shoes are?
These shoes, please!
The man who makes impossible possible.
Gong Jeong Man.
­Damn!
Did you come because you were worried about me?
I'm regretting my decision to come, so don't talk to me.
You look pretty.
Comrade No.
Hello.
So this is the guest you mentioned earlier?
Yes, I guess so.
- Let's go.
- Where?
Mayor Won is looking for you.
Well then, enjoy the party.
Today's event
is to support the organization, which is the reason for Pyeonghwa City's existence
and the largest civic group.
It's an event to support the Separated Families Council.
I hope that you enjoy the games set up at all parts of the party hall
and provide various sponsorships and meaningful donations.
I wish you an exciting party
and an enjoyable dinner.
That's a lovely dress.
Would you like some?
Challenge! Let's get started.
That was close.
Sadly, he was eliminated.
Okay, not much time is left now.
Does anyone else want to go for it?
I'll go for it!
All right, we've got the final contestants.
Okay, if this couple wins the game,
no less than 100 million won will be donated.
- Yes, that's right.
- 100 million won?
It's 100 million won.
Isn't that amazing?
It's by an anonymous sponsor.
Lloyd, the lead dancer and the lead singer of FITA,
requested the donation to be made to establish the Children's Heart Foundation in Pyeonghwa City.
Is that correct?
Yes, it is.
Of course, in order to donate, you must complete this successfully.
Okay.
Please come on the stage.
If you're ready, we'll get started.
Please take a deep breath. Let's start it
with a loud cheer.
Please go for it whenever you're ready.
Put me down now.
I don't want to.
It's 100 million won to establish the Children's Heart Foundation.
Children's Heart Foundation?
This isn't a scam, so don't worry.
Okay, your hand.
My hand?
You have to put your arm around me in order for me to balance myself.
Do it now.
Hurry.
Here we go.
Successful! Amazing!
Okay, Lloyd, who is as tough as steel.
With his strong willpower,
he's able to donate 100 million won to the Children's Heart Foundation.
That was amazing. Congratulations!
Excuse me.­
Can I ask you a question?
What's your hometown?
Well…
Wait. The owner of the Michelin restaurant?
Hello.
I grew up in Seoul.
Your entire life?
Yes, my entire life.
I was born in Masan
and grew up in LA. When I was in LA—
You really aren't from North Korea?
No.
This is the last time.
Shadow?
I ran out of patience a long time ago.
Don't expect any more chances.
Two weeks.
There will be an agreement ceremony between two Number Ones
for both North and South to go in and out of Pyeonghwa City freely.
If you miss that timing,
that will be your end. Don't you forget.
It must be hard for you, Comrade No.
You're always in the center of attention and have to endure any criticism.
You only realized that now?
But what can I do?
My fans say I'm an idol that will only happen once in a thousand years.
I accept it as my fate.
How pretty.
You look so pretty today.
Don't bluff.
I wasn't bluffing.
Please excuse us for a moment.
Darn it.
That guy is so rude.
- Look, man.
- Lloyd.
The mayor is looking for you. Come at once.
The mayor? What now?
The speech.
You were sitting in the van again, weren't you?
Where have you been?
They're pretty, but they don't suit you.
You're right.
Why do women of South Korea
wear such strangely-shaped sandals like these? I don't get it.
People on the other side aren't like you and me.
Be careful.
Don't you worry.
There are only two groups of people.
Either enemies or comrades.
Targets and nontargets.
Which one am I?
Pyeonghwa City has become...
very special to me now.
♫  Believe that you will return  ♫
♫  Whatever it is, I believe in you  ♫
♫  I can't find you anymore  ♫
♫  I believed in our hearts in those days  ♫
♫  Even though it may be foolish to turn around  ♫
♫  Back to that time on my way  ♫
♫  How are you doing? Goodbye  ♫
♫  Who will understand my feelings? Oh, my heart  ♫
♫  Only you can know. Know my heart  ♫
♫  I can't breathe no more  ♫
♫  A little more, a little more  ♫
♫  I'm getting closer to you  ♫
♫  Don't look back and don't hesitate  ♫
♫  This day won't come again  ♫
♫  Tonight  ♫
♫  Don't turn away  ♫