(Jun Hee, Ko You)
(SEHUN)
(Jo Joon Young)
(Jang Yeo Bin)
(All That We Loved)
Smile a little, okay?
Think of us as your friends.
Pluck up some courage.
Have you lost your mind?
Yes.
I've lost my mind.
I steal.
That was my secret.
Can you understand it?
How could I understand that?
If you're going to lose it, do so nicely.
You prick.
Are you pleased you got beaten up?
I got in a few punches too.
Unbelievable.
You must be so proud of yourself that you fought back.
Aren't you a fast runner?
So run when you meet punks like him...
rather than letting your pride take over.
I threw the first punch.
- What? - I went after him.
You've lost it for sure.
I'm not always there to protect you...
which makes it reckless.
I met So Yeon earlier.
She had my grandma's necklace.
Didn't she tell you that she had stolen it?
She said found it...
and that you were mistaken.
She told me she had stolen it.
I also saw her stealing Yoon Jung's mp3,
and I discovered the necklace...
when I opened her bag to check.
- Am I still mistaken? - You're wrong about the necklace.
And you believe that?
If you had seen for yourself...
I did.
And you're still taking her side?
There seemed to be a story behind it.
I found her crying.
Not everyone commits crimes when they're sad.
Anyway, stop talking about her with me.
This is none of your business.
(Episode 7: If You Don't Let Go Even When Things Go Awry)
(Year 2023)
If it's painful to talk about,
you can put it off until later.
No, I want to tell you.
I've always regretted it.
If I had told you guys back then,
things would've been much different for us.
You two understanding it should've come last.
But judging by the look on your face,
you'll be understanding no matter what I say.
When I was 16,
three days before my period,
I stole my friend's bracelet.
I saw it all the time...
and never did I want it for myself.
But one day,
my heart thumped at the sight of it,
and I got the urge to steal it.
Did anything like that happen during your previous periods?
That was the first time I stole something,
but the urges were there.
But the urges...
grew uncontrollable.
And they grew stronger.
Are you asleep?
(Year 2006)
Do you know what cellular memory is?
I'd rather not hear English in the middle of the night.
Can we just go to sleep?
Hey, that sauce has peanut in it!
What?
- Oh, no! - Where's the medicine?
- Oh, dear. - Darn it.
(For allergies)
Goodness.
Ms. Mo, try this.
This is as good as You's.
Really?
I can outdo him if I put my mind to it.
(Right-handed, vision, ornithophobia, basketball,)
(and Son Ye Jin equals Ko You.)
What on earth?
Guys!
You're louder than any other class in the school.
- Sir! - My gosh.
- Hush. - Got it.
- Sure. - All right.
Thanks for yesterday.
Right. Thanks for this.
How did Han So Yeon get it?
Don't drink it.
What do you mean?
Just don't drink it.
Then I'll drink it instead.
Mom, what can you tell me about cellular memory?
Cellular memory?
It's a phenomenon...
that presents itself with organ recipients like Jun Hee.
It means that cells have the capacity to remember.
Organ recipients acquire...
personality traits of their donors, as well as habits,
preferences, memories, and even their taste in romantic interests.
Some instances were reported abroad.
Are you drunk?
I can see just fine without my glasses.
Ms. Mo.
Is Jun Hee afraid of birds too?
- I got in a few punches too. - Unbelievable.
I threw the first punch.
There was a heart recipient...
who fell in love with the donor's girlfriend.
Thanks for yesterday.
Right. Thanks for this.
Have any of your patients experienced that?
No, and it's something...
I find it hard to believe as a doctor.
It must be a psychological effect of organ transplants.
Do you know what cellular memory is?
- Where are you headed? - Right.
To see You.
He sounded off on the phone.
Right.
CPCR, code blue. ICU.
CPCR, code blue.
- It's an emergency. - ICU.
- Let me handle it. - Would you?
I can't make it either.
Yes, I'll be there soon.
So Yeon.
Let's go out.
Jun Hee.
What are you doing?
I saw her by chance.
And I helped her as she was having it hard.
Having what hard? Stealing?
She didn't steal anything.
And there's certainly a reason behind that.
Yes, of course.
But that reason can't justify her behaviour,
so she wouldn't tell us.
Can't you know that much?
Or maybe you didn't seem ready to hear it.
Are you defending her?
I mean, you shouldn't defend her for this.
Snap out of it.
Are you being like this to her...
because of the cellular memory?
No.
It started when I saw her for the first time at the infirmary.
It was the same as you.
Now we're just friends.
Not everyone around us should be perfect.
But at least...
if anyone can put us in danger,
we cannot be friends with them.
Stop however you feel about her.
Even if it's hard, stop.
I'm not meddling with your business here.
Whether I become friends or whatever with her, it's up to me.
So stay out of my business.
What? My wallet.
I shouldn't lose my wallet.
- Look for it. - Gosh.
- Isn't it over there? - No, it's not.
Search carefully.
- Maybe it's deeper inside. - Keep looking.
- It's strange. - It must be somewhere.
I doubt it's stolen.
Search carefully.
- Check there. - Could anyone have stolen it?
- No way. - I doubt it.
Did Han So Yeon steal it?
- Maybe it's her. - It can't be stolen.
Didn't you go to Yeonga Middle School?
I found it!
- Are you kidding me? - Come on.
- What on earth? - You startled us.
It was here.
- What the... - You're too sloppy.
You brats would still be happy even if I gave you...
doenjang sauce mixed with faeces, wouldn't you?
Your friendly homeroom teacher went for his training today, right?
- Yes. - Yes.
Unfortunately, I'll hand you your reports for the finals.
Before that, I'm going to call those who placed 1st to 5th.
Ko Jun Hee, Han So Yeon,
Choi Yoon Jung, Kim Young Rae,
and Jeong Eun Joo. Come up front.
All right.
They're the ace students of this class. Give them a hand.
Good job.
Now I'm going to call those who placed 28th to last.
Once your name is called, go stand at the back.
Choi Kyu Sik, Jeong Joon Beom,
Kang Jin Hee, Kim Jae Hee, Ko You.
Sir, You had to miss a day of the finals due to the game.
You brat, studying comes first for students, not sports.
Go stand at the back!
Good job slacking off.
Give them a hand too.
All right. You brats at the back...
and front, look at each other's faces.
Take a good look at each other now.
You guys will never cross paths once you graduate.
And those of you seated, make a wise decision...
whether to study hard...
and join those in the front...
or join those punks at the back.
Think carefully as you look back and forth.
Make a wise decision, got it?
Got it?
- Yes. - Yes.
I used to be stuck in my studio apartment all the time.
So it's really nice to be out here.
Why aren't you eating?
You said you liked drumsticks.
Eat up.
It's good that you at least have an appetite.
Didn't you leave work yet...
Han So Yeon?
Hey, So Yeon.
Oh, my.
Soon Tak?
Hey, I didn't recognize you. You lost so much weight.
Hold on. Are you a doctor here too?
Yes.
You're still pretty.
It's good to see you.
Is he out of his mind?
(Year 2006)
- Soon Tak. - You!
Who told you to study?
We have a quiz today.
As if you've ever studied for it.
Did you eat?
She's like that.
Isn't it crazy?
- Hey. - The thief is here.
- The thief is here. - The thief.
- Goodness. - Can you believe it?
- She's... - Isn't she so creepy?
What a thief.
I mean, she said so.
Goodness.
- Where are you going? - To the gym to practice.
Good luck.
We have to memorize up to here, right?
Yes, here.
What's wrong?
Let go of me.
She's so proud for a thief.
- Who's a thief? - Han So Yeon.
Didn't you hear the rumour?
Did anyone see her steal something?
No, I just heard it.
But as far as I know, You doesn't talk to her because of it.
Weren't you aware of it too?
(Hara High School)
What? Are you here to get me?
- What? - Did you tell the others?
- Tell them what? - About So Yeon.
What about her?
There's a rumour about her.
Did you spread it?
Why can't you say it clearly?
Did it spread in the school that she stole stuff?
Why? Did she get caught stealing something again?
Are you insane?
Snap out of it.
She isn't important enough for us to bicker like this.
Do you only care about what you think?
Then tell me what you think clearly.
You said you'd choose friendship.
Is this what you call choosing friendship?
Why can't you say that you like So Yeon?
I'm not mistaken about her stealing habit.
That's a fact.
Will you go out with her even when everyone finds out?
- What's going on? - I think they're fighting.
And...
a fact isn't a rumour.
It's just that the truth got revealed.
Why can't you say anything?
All you can do is staring, isn't it?
Let's stop.
Jun Hee, what are you doing?
Gosh.
Hey, you're a PE major. Go stop them.
This is enough! Stop!
Come to your senses, Ko Jun Hee.
- Hey. - Stop them.
- Go get the teacher. - Stop it.
Hurry and stop them.
(All That We Loved)