​
♫  My everything, it grows within me  ♫
♫  It seems they will last forever always  ♫
♫  Our youthful days  ♫
They say you can't keep secrets in your heart because they are too hot.
They say you have to tell someone for sure.
So, if you don't have anyone to tell, come to me.
I will keep it a secret for you.
Go Yoo, the security man came!
Geez, why would he yell out my name!
Let's hurry up and go!
Hurry! Hurry! We'll be caught
- You guys go first!
- Stop right there!
Let's go.
- Are you okay? Let's hurry!
- Yeah...
Hey, punks! Stop right there!
This way! This way!
So Yeon.
♫  Even when I hurt so much that I can't walk  ♫
♫  Even when tears blind me  ♫
♫  I want to smile even when I'm in front of the one I love but cannot have  ♫
♫  Even if it's temporary, our happy memories  ♫
♫  I will keep them in my heart  ♫
♫  The countless stars that fill my eyes  ♫
I think you have a phone call.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go out.
- Are you hungry again?
- Yeah.
Oh, Joon Hee!
You're here?
You must have been busy today.
Are you done for the day?
Yeah.
Can you be with me today?
Let's go to my house.
What's wrong with your glasses? Did they break?
No. I just took them off.
I will go home after I take So Yeon home.
Let's go.
You're not hurt anywhere?
You looked good with So Yeon when you walked over here earlier.
She looks good with Go Yoo, too.
I will go home after I take So Yeon home.
Let's go.
Since when were you close with Joon Hee?
Since elementary school.
We lived together until junior high school.
Really? Are you guys relatives?
Well, not really.
It didn't seem like you guys were just friends.
You guys look really good together.
You guys are very different but are also very similar if you look closer.
What is it?
Let's go.
We're here.
You live here, I see.
Yeah.
Thanks for today.
Strange...
Are you drunk?
Am I really drunk? I can see well even without my glasses.
Give them to me.
Gosh! So dizzy!
Your glasses are perfectly fine.
Two.
Three.
Then, how about this?
Geez. Seriously.
Come on, let's try it once!
What does this say?
Then, for the last time, what does this say?
I told you I'm done with this. Just go home.
I'm not going anywhere.
I told you, I'm done! Just go home.
You have something to say. Right?
Do you like Han So Yeon, too?
I think I'm going to feel different in the morning from the way I feel now.
We've never liked the same person before.
So Yeon is really...
What are you talking about?
I'm not interested in Han So Yeon.
She's not even my type.
Are you going to sleep over or just go home?
I'll sleep over.
You'll let me, right?
Geez...
I should make Madam Mo some coffee in the morning.
Just get rid of the whites.
And just add the yolk, splash!
Okay! Finished!
Wow! Madam Mo, how are you so pretty in the morning?
- Did you sleep well?
- Yeah.
I feel more comfortable here than in my own house.
How is it?
It's good!
Oh? Where is your necklace? Did you lose it?
It ran away somewhere.
When? You should have told me.
- That's important to you, isn't it?
- It's all right.
Gosh, you must have been upset.
That was the necklace that Joon Hee's mother used to wear.
Gosh!
I slept so well.
Go Joon Hee should eat three meals a day like me
and exercise more instead of just studying all day.
Madam Mo!
Give me some food, too!
What? "Madam Mo"?
Our Madam Mo is so pretty from the morning.
"Madam Mo"?
Stop it. I just tried imitating you.
Hey, it's so awkward! Don't do it!
Did you put on contact lenses?
Just wear glasses! You're ugly either way!
Get your faces away from me, you two!
- Don't you guys have anything else to focus on?
- Nope!
- Just once, just once!
- Gosh, darn it!
I give up on dieting. I just can't restrain myself!
Girls, let's go to the convenience store.
- I'll get the corn dog!
- Convenience store?
Corn dog!
- Going to the convenience store?
- Yeah.
You're going to the convenience store?
Yeah.
What? What? What are you doing here?
- Hey, why are you here?
- Ow, that hurts!
Oh, Han So Yeon!
Hurry up. The corn dog is mine.
Hurry up!
It's mine!
Excuse me...
Wow.
Your house is so nice!
Modern interior design!
Wow, the night view is so pretty, too.
This is why I came to see you.
As expected, my predictions were correct.
Although you're living in the city, you have no interest in the world.
Do you want something to drink?
I'm in a pretty crappy mood today, so how about a drink?
The base is what's important.
It's different when you pour alcohol into coffee or the other way around.
For a day like today, you pour coffee into alcohol.
A day when I want to get really drunk.
Aren't people the same?
The ending is decided by the base of the person.
Whether you go from love to friendship,
or from friendship to love...
If you go from friendship to love, that's a happy ending,
but if you go from love to friendship,
it's a sad ending.
Gosh, it's sad.
What do you really want to say?
You can tell me now...
Your secret.
I enjoyed the food.
Will you be able to get in?
Go Yoo, thanks!
Hey, hey, hey, let's hurry up and go.
Thanks a lot!
- Oh, a pigeon?
- Just leave it alone, Soon Tak.
Just leave it alone. It will leave soon.
- Gosh, it's no big deal!
- Soon Tak! Just let it be!
I can just chase it away like this! Shoo!
Hey, why are you running?
Why is Go Joon Hee running?
So, you're afraid of birds?
You found out.
Is that your secret?
It's not really a secret...
since Soon Tak and Joon Hee know about it.
But is Joon Hee afraid of birds, too?
He isn't!
Maybe that pigeon was unusually large?
Why don't you have money?
Do you have anything you're scared of?
I do. It's gym time.
My scores for gym practicum are crappy,
but only my scores for basketball came out high.
By chance, could you teach me about sports?
Yeah.
That's right!
♫  Everything in that moment, the two of us  ♫
♫  Shining so brilliantly  ♫
♫  Our shining days, you and me, and the cloudless skies  ♫
♫  Even now, after time has passed  ♫
♫  You fly into my memories  ♫
♫  You make me smile, you make me smile again  ♫
♫  You always do that to me  ♫
♫  Sometimes I'm tired and lose my way  ♫
♫  But whenever I turn my head and look  ♫
♫  I can feel you in those moments  ♫
♫  All that I loved, my everything  ♫
♫  It grows within me  ♫
♫  It seems they will last forever always  ♫
♫  Our youthful days, someday  ♫
Hurry up! Hurry!
Come! Hurry! Hurry!
♫  So we don't lose each other and stay together until the end of this road  ♫
- Let's go!
♫  All that I loved, my everything  ♫
♫  You are there in that day  ♫
Footwork.
Watch the ball to the end!
Put more strength into your wrist!
Nice! That was good!
Oh! So Yeon did a trick shot!
- Trick...
- Trick Shot?
Yeah, trick shot! Trick shot!
Oh! Both of you are good.
Okay, you did well.
That's right!  My goodness!
♫  Someday  ♫
- Your kidney is functioning well. Everything's good.
- Yes.
Your creatinine levels are good, and your BUN levels are stable as well,
so you won't have to come to the hospital often.
You're not experiencing any discomfort or anything off, right?
Why? Are you experiencing some discomfort?
I...
I'm a lefty, but I use my right hand,
and my eyesight suddenly became good,
and breakfast is tasty, even though I don't usually eat it.
Really? That's so good!
Oh... well...
Yes, it's good.
That's a relief. That's such good news.
I'll be going to the restroom for a bit.
The parfait you ordered is here.
They say you can't keep secrets in your heart because they are too hot.
They say you have to tell someone for sure.
So, if you don't have anyone to tell, come to me.
I will keep it a secret for you.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
Have you seen a necklace on the floor here?
No. I have not.
I see. Thank you.
Hello. Have you seen a rose-shaped necklace on the floor here?
No, I don't think so.
I see. Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Have you seen a necklace on the floor here?
- No, I haven't.
- Oh... Okay, thank you.
- Goodbye.
Geez! I won't have him do it!
What's the point of being good at studying?
He will always be in a place like this living my fate.
My son is a basketball prodigy!
He literally flies around!
You don't have the proper form.
Joon Hee!
Hey, if you came all the way here, you should at least say hello to me!
Come here for a moment.
Say hello. This is my son.
Hello.
Goodness, he's handsome!
He's tall and handsome.
- He's the top student in his school!
- Top in his school...
Didn't he just say he played basketball?
- Move to the music room.
- Move.
Go Yoo probably won't come. Right?
Probably not.
Hey, Go Yoo!
Did you win the match?
Did you win or lose? Let's have a talk.
Hey! Come here for a bit!
Han So Yeon.
Should I tell you my secret?
This is my secret.
My secret that only you didn't know.
Top Actress Han So Yeon is involved in an unbelievable theft case
and has made headlines all over the celebrity news.
Han So Yeon is claiming that the employee mistakenly forgot to scan the item.
The stolen item was an expensive wallet worth 800,000 won.
Today...
Since it was not deemed too pricey, so...
the world has been talking about my secret all day.
There is a fierce debate among netizens right now.
I saw it wrong just now. Right?
Can I check your bag?
​
Hey.
Seriously...
- Actually, I...
- You thief!
♫  Coming to me as if I was dreaming  ♫
♫  My star that is unusually bright  ♫
♫  Shining brilliantly  ♫
♫  The starlight shines over my shoulders  ♫
♫  Stop being so sad  ♫
♫  Holding my hands tight  ♫
♫  It touches me and embraces me warmly  ♫
♫  Even when I hurt so much that I can't walk  ♫