♪On a quiet night somewhere♪
♪I longed
to hold your fading silhouette♪
♪Yet my hands grasped only air♪
♪Mocking my own persistence♪
♪Turns out it was nothing but a dream♪
♪Perhaps love
will blossom with the next spring♪
♪Yet I can't help but feel the ache♪
♪For you're no longer mine♪
=Misaligned Lover=
=Episode 20=
(Adapted from
a Himalaya Qiji Literature novel)
(Written by Xiang Bei, author
of Heard You Got a Dog Outside? Divorce!)
Dad.
You're awake.
How do you feel?
Why am I here?
Did something happen?
Don't touch.
My head hurts...
Your head hurts?
Where's Yucheng?
Why isn't she here?
You...
You don't remember what happened?
Not even a little?
Did something happen?
Doctor.
What's going on?
Why has my daughter
forgotten everything from before?
She can't remember anything.
Post-traumatic amnesia.
People instinctively forget
what they don't want to remember.
In cases like this,
treatment requires medication
and regular psychological counseling.
Only then can she recover.
Thank you, Doctor.
Dad.
Where's Yucheng?
Why hasn't she been around for days?
I killed Yucheng.
It was my fault...
(I've already lost one daughter.)
(I can't lose another.)
Here.
Yuling.
These are your favorite strawberries.
Come on, have one.
Here.
Okay, thanks, Dad.
Good girl.
Sir, the strawberries are washed.
Leave them there.
Yucheng.
These are fresh strawberries
delivered today.
They're really sweet.
Try one.
Here, for you.
Thanks, Yucheng.
Eat more, okay?
Yuling loves sweets.
Let her have them all.
There's plenty.
You should have some too.
Good girl.
Yucheng, don't leave me.
Yucheng is dead.
Dad, is Yucheng really dead?
No way...
Yucheng is dead.
How could she be dead?
Yuling...
Come here.
How could Yucheng be dead?
It's all right.
Yucheng is dead.
Dad is here. Don't think about it.
How did Yucheng die?
No...
Yucheng.
Don't do this.
Yucheng!
Yucheng...
Chenxi.
What's wrong?
Another nightmare?
It's all right now.
Don't be afraid.
It's all right.
I just dreamed of Yucheng.
Was it because of me?
Did she die
because of me?
If I
hadn't gone out alone that day,
she wouldn't have died.
No, Chenxi.
This wasn't your fault.
If anyone's to blame...
It's that crazed stalker fan.
Get some rest.
When you wake up,
everything will be fine. Okay?
Here.
Don't go.
All right, I won't go.
I'll stay here
with you.
Yucheng.
Yucheng, are you okay?
Yucheng!
This is a video taken by a bystander.
It's already spreading online.
Mu Chenxi is one of the people involved,
reporters and influencers
will definitely swarm in.
They want to interview Mu Chenxi
and will definitely gather at the set.
It'll slow down our filming progress.
How about
we replace her?
Give me back my social media account.
All right.
But you have to promise me
you won't comment on this incident.
Even if the media asks,
you can only
express sympathy for the victim.
The internet
is full of baseless speculation.
Mu Chenxi has nothing to do with this.
Zhiqing.
Forget about everything else,
but not this.
I'm begging you,
cut ties with Mu Chenxi.
I've made myself clear.
That's not happening.
I'm standing by her.
Zhiqing.
At this point,
even her former agency
is cutting ties with her.
Do you really
have to get involved in this mess?
You've seen the news, right?
Yeah.
What they're saying isn't true.
I see.
Yan Lidong...
Of course, I believe Mu Chenxi.
She's definitely not like they say.
But...
The public reaction
is intense right now.
Look...
For the sake of this project,
should we find someone else?
No.
Lidong.
The company has spent years
investing so much money and resources.
Now everything's on hold
because of this.
I can't explain this to the chairman.
Then Mr. Fan
can just get a new male lead.
You think I don't want
to replace the male lead?
But when it comes down to it,
it's all because of you.
Being an employee is exhausting.
♪The coastline at dusk♪
♪The summer sky painted in sunset humor♪
♪And on my left shoulder,
your face glows with happiness♪
♪As joy keeps spreading♪
♪With endless affection♪
♪Writing the chapters of us together♪
♪A scorching June♪
♪Melting memories in the heat♪
♪Like a sweet and creamy dessert♪
♪Gazing up at the endless Milky Way♪
♪Stars twinkling bright♪
♪I wish to stay by your side forever♪
♪I'd promise you
the world beneath the moon♪
♪I'd wait for you at dawn
when dreams fade too soon♪
♪I'd do anything,
no matter what it takes♪
♪As long as I'm with you♪
♪I'd stand with you
in the rain and storm♪
♪I'd chase the clouds
just to make you laugh♪
♪I'd walk through
time's endless journey♪
♪Because you're the only view I need♪
♪So sweet♪
♪I'd promise you
the world beneath the moon♪
♪I'd wait for you
at dawn when dreams fade too soon♪
♪I'd do anything,
no matter what it takes♪
♪As long as I'm with you♪
♪I'd stand with you
in the rain and storm♪
♪I'd chase the clouds
just to make you laugh♪
♪I'd walk through
time's endless journey♪
♪Because you're the only view I need♪
♪So sweet♪