♪That dangerous temptation♪
♪Like a whirlpool churning deep♪
♪Like a moth darts into the flame♪
♪Falling towards the light♪
♪Watch as everything drowns in shadows♪
♪Have no fear, do not retreat♪
♪See the blazing sparks ignite♪
♪Believe this all has cause and effect♪
♪No evil escapes untouched♪
♪From the stormy torrents in this life♪
♪The memories howl as they flash by♪
[Miss Mystery]
You father and daughter are so similar,
over-confidently stupid.
[Episode 21]
Mr. Zhu Jr.
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
Bao'er.
She went back long ago.
Stop drinking.
Let's go!
Let's go back home.
Home?
No!
I don't have a home.
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
Leave me alone for a while.
Oh my, stop drinking!
I can't understand you two.
Sure, you had an argument,
but why did you drink so much?
You don't understand.
No, I don't.
I don't want to understand.
Romance and love,
too much trouble.
Let's go.
Go!
Come on!
Slow down.
You are wasted.
I'll sleep on the couch tonight.
Zhu Guanwen!
Put me down now!
Zhu Guanwen, what are you doing?
I have to go.
Don't call my name.
Zhu Guanwen, are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
Why would god make me love you?
Let me meet you...
And now he's breaking us up.
Why am I a Zhu?
Why?
♪Falling towards the light♪
♪Watch as everything drowns in shadows♪
♪Have no fear, do not retreat♪
♪See the blazing sparks ignite♪
♪Believe this all has cause and effect♪
♪No evil escapes untouched♪
♪From the stormy torrents in this life♪
♪The memories howl as they flash by♪
♪Breaking free from
heavy shackles held tight♪
♪In the darkness a lone lamp glows♪
♪Light and shadows
criss-cross in the night♪
♪Can't get rid of it♪
♪Everything drowns♪
♪No escape can yet be found♪
♪The outline of sin♪
♪On the bargaining table
right and wrong confound♪
♪See the raging fiery light♪
♪It will finally break free
from its plight♪
♪Flooding over everything in its wake♪
♪The escape will be found♪
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
Time to get up!
What happened
with you two last night?
But she went downstairs for breakfast.
Master Zhu is there, too.
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
Bao'er!
Father.
Sit here.
I had our cook make this nourishing soup
specially for you.
Have some.
I hope you will soon give our family
a child.
Thanks, Father.
From the first moment I saw you,
I had a familiar feeling of you.
I didn't expect that, in the end,
you would really become
my daughter-in-law.
Perhaps this was destined to be.
Father,
have some more.
You have to live a very long life.
Me? Forget that!
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
Go upstairs and get dressed!
Look at you!
Where is your sense of decency?
I...
I'll go upstairs to change.
Qiang,
does Master know
that Guanwen was drunk last night?
Master was in the study all night.
He probably doesn't know
that Mr. Zhu Jr. drank.
The study...
[Huamei Clothing Store]
Ten for two of these.
Ten? How about this?
Mr. Zhu Jr.!
What?
Mrs. Zhu is kidnapped!
Who kidnapped her?
Dou Lili!
Where did they go?
I have no idea.
She was in a car,
and I couldn't catch them.
Should I call the police first?
Listen,
you go get help,
and I'll go to the Dou manor.
OK!
Well, well, Lin Bao'er.
I thought you were afraid of nothing
in the world.
If
I press this thing
on your face...
Will Zhu Guanwen still want you?
Now you are scared?
Too late.
If it wasn't for you,
I'd be Mrs. Zhu by now.
I'd still be the mayor's daughter.
If it wasn't for you,
everything wouldn't have happened!
Zhu Guanwen, save me!
At this point,
are you still thinking
about Zhu Guanwen?
Alright then,
I will send you both
to hell!
♪The end has now been reached♪
♪Yet we face each other in silence♪
♪Looking away from you♪
♪Emotions like a flood
they spread and grew♪
♪Who would like to be fooled♪
♪Love, how could it be a lie♪
♪In a moment♪
♪Flitting images flashing♪
♪Eyes fall shut♪
♪Fingertips gently touched♪
♪Risking fate and danger venturing♪
♪Dancing on the tip of the knife♪
♪Put on a show wholeheartedly♪
♪In a moment♪
♪The memory in my mind♪
♪Surging at me♪
♪Beliefs hidden deep inside♪
♪In an abyss perhaps inescapable♪
♪Under a ray of light in the darkness♪
♪I may reopen my eyes♪