♪That dangerous temptation♪
♪Like a whirlpool churning deep♪
♪Like a moth darts into the flame♪
♪Falling towards the light♪
♪Watch as everything drowns in shadows♪
♪Have no fear, do not retreat♪
♪See the blazing sparks ignite♪
♪Believe this all has cause and effect♪
♪No evil escapes untouched♪
♪From the stormy torrents in this life♪
♪The memories howl as they flash by♪
[Miss Mystery]
[Lianhe Police Station]
Reporting for duty!
Come in.
Now that I've given you
the position of Chief Detective,
you must work diligently
and get things done for me.
Yes, Sir!
Receiving your trust
is my honor, Mr. Mayor!
I will spare no effort and remain loyal!
Alright.
Enough fancy words.
Remember,
and remember forever
who your owner is.
Since you chose to be a lackey,
act like one.
[Episode 12]
You're awake!
Yes.
How did I do yesterday?
Yesterday...
I fell asleep, so I don't remember.
It was fine.
That sounds right.
Give me a second.
The coffee is almost ready.
Bao'er,
for a long time,
I haven't been drinking coffee.
Why?
When I was little,
my mom used to like coffee,
just like this.
Watching her drinking coffee,
I wanted to taste it too.
My mom couldn't stop me,
so she added some sugar
to the coffee,
telling me
that coffee is sweet.
But after she passed away,
I realized...
Oh,
turns out coffee is bitter.
So,
I stopped drinking coffee
ever since then.
I'm sorry, Guanwen.
Then let's forget about coffee today.
It's fine.
Bao'er,
lately,
I'm especially grateful to fate,
because having you
has added some sweetness
to my bitter life.
♪It seems to be changing♪
♪The familiar yet strange face♪
♪I want to get close♪
♪To those once bright eyes♪
Taste it.
♪Unable to touch♪
♪Between us♪
Sweet?
Tasty.
♪Looking away from you♪
Actually, I should thank you.
I originally thought
after my parents' death,
there would be no more joy
in my dreary life.
♪Love, how could it be a lie♪
Little did I expect
God would give me a piece of candy,
which is you.
♪Flitting images flashing♪
♪Eyes fall shut♪
♪Fingertips gently touched♪
♪Risking fate and danger venturing♪
♪Dancing on the tip of the knife♪
♪Put on a show wholeheartedly♪
♪In a moment♪
♪The memory in my mind♪
♪Surging at me♪
♪Beliefs hidden deep inside♪
♪In an abyss perhaps inescapable♪
♪Under a ray of light in the darkness♪
♪I may reopen my eyes♪
We don't know
what is up with Southeast Asia,
and they won't let us through this time.
But please rest assured.
I can solve the problem these days.
Father,
Mr. Dou.
The shipment to Southeast Asia
has been cleared by customs.
Wha-
Really?
I've heard you talk about it.
Our goods in Southeast Asia
are always getting held up by customs.
It just so happens my father
has some connections in Southeast Asia,
so I made a call
and pulled some strings to help out.
Well,
in the future, we'll inevitably have
more dealings with Southeast Asia.
I think we should
hand the Southeast Asia route
over to Bao'er from now on.
I need to consider your decision.
After all,
Ms. Lin is new to the business.
She is bound to be inexperienced
in some areas of the work.
Also, Ms. Lin is not a local.
That is not accurate.
Since Bao'er took over
the shipping company,
the operations have been
much smoother than under Qian Tong.
Of course,
this is also thanks
to your wise judgment.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you, Mr. Dou.
I need to leave now.
Go.
Dou,
come here with Lili for a meal someday.
Let us old folks enjoy tea,
raise birds, and live in comfort.
Doesn't that sound nice?
But...
Look how carefree the bird lives!
Tweet, tweet!
[BABY RESTAURANT]
Baby.
Bao'er,
don't you love this restaurant?
I bought this place for you as a gift.
From now on,
you can make me coffee every day.
What about the Blooming House?
Blooming House?
I'll get rid of it.
I will only do whatever you like.
Alright, just spit it.
What exactly do you want?
Nice, I can't hide anything from you.
Actually,
I'm worried about you.
My dad and Mr. Dou's business is shady.
I don't want you to be in danger.
You know
that I have no choice
but to get to this point.
Okay.
Since you insist on doing this,
I will do it with you.
If your next target is Mr. Dou,
I will help you.
Okay.
I promise you
to face them together.
[BABY RESTAURANT]
Father.
I knew
there was more to this Lin Bao'er.
How surprising!
It's too late to make any remarks now.
How much have we got on Lin Bao'er?
No need to rush.
Let's just sit back and enjoy the show.
♪The end has now been reached♪
♪Yet we face each other in silence♪
♪Looking away from you♪
♪Emotions like a flood
they spread and grew♪
♪Who would like to be fooled♪
♪Love, how could it be a lie♪
♪In a moment♪
♪Flitting images flashing♪
♪Eyes fall shut♪
♪Fingertips gently touched♪
♪Risking fate and danger venturing♪
♪Dancing on the tip of the knife♪
♪Put on a show wholeheartedly♪
♪In a moment♪
♪The memory in my mind♪
♪Surging at me♪
♪Beliefs hidden deep inside♪
♪In an abyss perhaps inescapable♪
♪Under a ray of light in the darkness♪
♪I may reopen my eyes♪