♪That dangerous temptation♪
♪Like a whirlpool churning deep♪
♪Like a moth darts into the flame♪
♪Falling towards the light♪
♪Watch as everything drowns in shadows♪
♪Have no fear, do not retreat♪
♪See the blazing sparks ignite♪
♪Believe this all has cause and effect♪
♪No evil escapes untouched♪
♪From the stormy torrents in this life♪
♪The memories howl as they flash by♪
[Miss Mystery]
So will I.
- So will I.
- I also want to wear a wedding dress.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- What's this?
Have you become a boss?
What's on your mind?
Master,
there's a first time for everyone.
Take it easy.
That's strange.
She's been up there so long.
She needs to do her makeup carefully.
Maybe she's even more nervous than you.
I still have a bad feeling.
Now, I need you
to assign some extra men to this place.
Master, aren't you being too cautious?
What could happen at a wedding?
We better be careful.
Alright.
I'm working on it.
[Episode 10]
I see.
The bride is here!
The bride is here.
Look.
How does she look?
Yeah.
Bao'er!
Keep still!
What's going on?
I'll kill her right now if you move!
Yang Jian!
What are you doing?
Do you realize who you are seizing?
She's the new bride of the Zhu family!
Of course, I know.
The Zhu family,
the most powerful family in Lianhe Town,
is the family we all work for.
Yang Jian,
I'll give you whatever you want.
I can give you money.
You can leave here
and go wherever you want.
Shut up!
I don't want anything!
I don't want to go anywhere!
Why do I have to escape,
and you get to enjoy the rewards?
I've been loyal to you over the years,
but what have I gained?
A broken family!
You hate the Zhu family?
Well,
I'll be your hostage.
Let go of Bao'er.
Stop right there!
No!
Don't move!
Yang Jian!
Back away!
I said back away!
Yang Jian,
calm down.
Don't act impulsively.
Your dedication to Lianhe Town
all these years
has been witnessed by all of us.
We're all very grateful to you.
Now,
take a moment to calm down
and release the bride.
We can discuss any matter.
Dou Huaizhong,
I know your intentions!
You want to protect me.
You want me to keep quiet, right?
But you're not the one
who has the final say!
Step back!
For so many years,
the Zhu family
has always enjoyed the cake,
and you can only taste the crumbs.
Are you happy with that?
You said
you don't want to be
at the mercy of others all the time.
Enough!
You're out of your mind!
I'm not!
I just want to seek justice
for all the dirty jobs we've done
all these years,
and for my family members
who have all been killed!
Here we are again,
Xue Tong.
You're right.
I'm Xue Tong,
from the family
that has been murdered
and robbed by you.
If you kill me now,
do you think Zhu Mao
and Mr. Dou will let you go?
Maybe not if I kill Lin Bao'er,
but who I'll kill
is Xue Tong.
Right.
If you kill Xue Tong,
Zhu Mao will be pleased.
But the truth is,
given that Zhu Mao is so ruthless,
do you think he'll let you survive?
You've been loyal to him over the years
and take on all the dirty work,
but in the end,
he enjoys the whole cake.
You just hurt his second wife
by mistake,
and he wiped out your entire family.
What?
Do you remember this?
It's my son's longevity lock.
You killed my family!
In Lianhe Town,
who else could kill your entire family
except Zhu Mao?
He's not just trying to kill your son,
but the rest of your family as well.
When I sent my men there,
your son was the only one who survived.
I know
you're just one of Zhu Mao's dogs.
I also want to approach Zhu Mao
by marrying Zhu Guanwen.
We both want the same thing.
This longevity lock was broken
by being hit by a bullet.
I just want to seek justice
for all the dirty jobs we've done
all these years,
and for my family members
who have all been killed!
Qiang!
Call a doctor!
Right now!
Mr. Mayor,
are you happy with that?
Call a doctor.
It scared me.
He's bleeding heavily.
I'll call a doctor.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Why are you so foolish?
Why did you take the bullet for me?
You're Madam Zhu,
so I have to protect you.
Looks like Lianhe Town
is not a safe place anymore.
♪The end has now been reached♪
♪Yet we face each other in silence♪
♪Looking away from you♪
♪Emotions like a flood
they spread and grew♪
♪Who would like to be fooled♪
♪Love, how could it be a lie♪
♪In a moment♪
♪Flitting images flashing♪
♪Eyes fall shut♪
♪Fingertips gently touched♪
♪Risking fate and danger venturing♪
♪Dancing on the tip of the knife♪
♪Put on a show wholeheartedly♪
♪In a moment♪
♪The memory in my mind♪
♪Surging at me♪
♪Beliefs hidden deep inside♪
♪In an abyss perhaps inescapable♪
♪Under a ray of light in the darkness♪
♪I may reopen my eyes♪