Lookkai.
You know more than
what you've told me, don't you?
Lookkai.
It's time.
It's time for you to finally step out
of your mother's shadow.
From now on
you need to start living your own life.
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid to reveal the truth.
Okay.
The truth is
P'Venus
didn't just vanish into thin air.
That waiter was actually
Khun Pakin
Khun Pakinai's older brother.
Khun Pakinai
Khun Saturn's
ex-boyfriend?
The one who committed suicide?
Then what does that
have to do with Khun Venus?
He has nothing to do with it.
It's my mother's fault.
It's all my mother's doing.
It's alright.
You don't have to be afraid anymore.
Everything is going to be fine.
Should we start our investigation now?
Right here
Don't you dare think
that just because you did this
and that for me
I'm going to forgive you.
For what you did to my brother.
I never thought that way.
Because I know
that a person like you
doesn't even know
the meaning of the word 'forgiveness'.
Wait.
These are the documents to transfer
the position of Chief Executive Officer
to Khun Khaeng Khae.
Granting full authority to manage
everything related to the hotel
and all businesses under
the Prakayfah Pradabdao conglomerate.
Madame, is there anything
you would like to amend?
No.
In that case, please sign here.
Madame, please don't sign it!
Mavin
You're getting too nosy
for your own good!
Madame, you cannot sign
the power of attorney
over to Khun Khaeng Khae.
Because the person
behind the disappearance
of Khun Venus and Khun Saturn
is Khun Khaeng Khae!
Mawin!
What nonsense are you spouting?
How dare you frame me?
You're just jealous
and delusional.
Did you think that working for Madame
would get you promoted
to be the top executive?
I've never thought that way.
Unlike you.
Who would do anything evil
just to seize
Madame's fortune.
Mawin!
Listen to me.
The reason Auntie
let me manage this place
is because she sees how much of my life
I've dedicated to it.
Exactly.
Apart from Khae
I don't see anyone else fit for it.
Therefore
I will proceed as I intended.
Grandmother.
What P'Mavin said is true.
I have proof.
Dao Lookkai!
What the hell are you saying?
Mom...
I'm sorry.
But I won't let you
do the wrong thing anymore.
Everyone, look at this.
If you really want revenge
I have a way.
How?
This Saturday, there's a birthday party
for Dao Kang Fah.
Saturn will be the main organizer.
If you want to get your hands on him
it won't be hard.
And how will I get into the party?
I told you...
it won't be hard.
Give me that phone!
No!
Give it!
Stop it
Give it to me, I said!
You're the one who needs to stop!
No... give it!
Khun Khaeng Khae.
The evidence is this clear.
Do you have any more excuses?
It's AI.
It's AI!
It was completely fabricated!
By...
by Mawin and this wretched child!
Auntie.
You have to believe me!
No.
I don't believe anyone!
Stop it, all of you!
There will be no transfer of power
Until...
until I find my two grandsons.
Madame! / Grandmother!
Mr. Lawyer!
Call an ambulance, quick!
Madame!
I really never thought
that things would go this far.
That it would come to this.
It's not your fault, Lookkai.
Yes, it is.
Because I knew everything all along.
But I still let my mother
do those terrible things.
Without trying to stop her
or stand in her way.
Mavin! Lookkai!
It's because of you two
that everything is completely ruined!
Khun Khaeng Khae.
Please keep your voice down.
We're in a hospital.
Get this through your thick skulls.
You two will never be able to stop me.
What else are you planning to do, Mom?
I'm planning to take back
what's rightfully mine.
I built it with my own sweat.
I built it with my own bare hands
It has to be mine!
Come back with me.
No, I'm not going!
Come back with me!
Khun Khaeng Khae!
Let him go.
Please, just let Dao Lookkai go.
What's it going to be, Dao Lookkai?
Are you coming with me
or are you going to be an ungrateful child?
Huh?!
What are you doing?
Am I not making myself clear?
Go to work.
No.
Are you testing me?
I will only do it when I want to.
I refuse to be your slave anymore.
Fine.
Hey!
Stop, stop, stop!
Oh, enough, enough!
What is wrong with you two?
Hey!
Aunt Tammy.
You don't have to stop him.
If he wants to kick me
or punch me
whatever he wants to do, j
ust let him do it.
Let him satisfy his vengeance.
Come on.
Punch me.
Let's just get this over with.
Why aren't you doing it?
Do it.
Go ahead
Just beat me to death right here!
Because I don't want
to live like this anymore either!
Why?!
Why won't you do it?!
Come on!
Do it!
Damn it!
So much anger
so much revenge
when will it ever end?
And you
you're quite something yourself
So provocative
you're so incredibly tempting.