Can you check this for me?
I need more shots with people and food.
Okay.
Come on, camera two.
Focus more on people with food.
Thanks.
For this head-to-head round,
the list of contestants who will advance
is right here in my hand.
Ladies and gentlemen,
those advancing today are...
Shi Shi Zai Zai and Mo Ling.
Congratulations!
Congratulations. Good job.
Excellent work.
Now for today,
between San Francisco Beauty Salon and Time Lag team,
one contestant will temporarily leave our stage.
Tonight,
the one eliminated is...
San Francisco Beauty Salon.
Cut!
Why? Let's pause the recording.
Sorry, sis.
Xiaojie, I was on a roll.
Why take a break? I need to pick up my kid.
It's okay, sis.
You're so capable. Why don't you record it yourself?
Sis, I can ask my assistant to pick up your kid.
Wait, let me tell you something.
I've called you here
because there are flaws in this competition.
The four of you
someone must know exactly what's going on.
A competition demands fairness and justice.
I don't know about other shows
if they have predetermined winners or bribes
or under-the-table dealings.
But the show I produce
absolutely does not allow any fraud.
We've already had internal discussions
and one of our judges, Waizui Ji,
will be leaving the show.
I'm giving you two options.
First,
since Shishi Zaizai got the lowest score this round,
they will be eliminated.
Second,
I can make public the fact that Shishi Zaizai bribed a judge,
exposing everything,
and you'll have to face the consequences yourselves.
I'll give you five minutes
to think it over and tell me.
Sister Junni.
What's going on now?
I don't know either.
I just got a call from my boss.
You're hurting me by doing this.
I didn't mean to.
But I was kept in the dark too.
I didn't know it would...
I only found out when I called my boss
this afternoon.
It's outrageous.
You're going to get me in trouble.
I'm sorry. I know.
But there's nothing I can do.
So what now?
What are we going to do?
I don't know. Wait a moment.
I'll call my boss.
Sorry.
Group 2 has been filming until now.
I said I'd treat you to dinner,
but ended up being very late.
I ordered a beer for you.
Thanks.
Is everything going well?
How could it not be?
We just need to find a replacement judge
to fill in for Wai Zui Ji.
I've used every connection I have.
What happened today
was entirely our production team's oversight.
Order whatever you want.
It's on me.
You said it.
Please, order freely.
I'm going to order a lot.
That's fine.
If you hadn't discovered it,
we'd still be in the dark today.
Speaking of that,
I really need to talk to you about something.
Do you know how many heartbeats I skipped because of you?
I messaged you before the competition
to check if someone was taking bribes,
but you didn't read or reply at all.
I've been so busy with this competition
that I haven't eaten anything yet.
How could I have time to check my phone?
Luckily I saw it at the last minute.
How did you know about
the situation between Shi Shi Zai Zai and Wai Zui Ji?
Fine. Since you've already paid,
I'll pretend I don't know anything.
But I'm begging you,
don't do this kind of thing again in the next round.
That's it for now. I need to go prepare.
Jun Ni,
check your messages.
I need to tell you something.
I've looked into the crab incident.
It has nothing to do with Shi Shi Zai Zai.
I've also confirmed with Niu Yifei.
He did put the crab in the refrigerator.
I haven't finished yet.
I asked someone on site
to check the surveillance footage for me.
Before the competition,
the last person who opened the refrigerator
was that temporary female assistant.
But I find it strange.
You're in the same group as that temp.
It's not like we don't know each other.
She has no motive to sabotage you, right?
Right.
There's definitely no motive.
Maybe the crab crawled away by itself.
The crab crawled away?
Is that some kind of joke?
Let me ask you something.
Have you ever had that feeling
when you know a problem is definitely going to happen,
but you just don't want to deal with it,
to the point where you ignore its existence?
All the time.
Especially before we start recording a show.
If I were to investigate everything,
we'd never get to film anything.
That's true.
If you're lucky, you dodge the bullet.
And if you're unlucky, you just face the failure.
Once you've imagined the worst, there's no such thing as the worst anymore.
That's right.
At least today's outcome was good,
right?
Niu Yifei.
Table three's egg pancake.
Table four's braised pork wrap.
Ask if they want drinks. No problem.
Okay.
Table three, your food is ready.
Thank you.
You wanted drinks, right?
Okay, no problem.
I'll get it for you in a moment.
Just wait a second.
You can sit anywhere there's a seat.
Okay, here.
Alright, put it here.
It's all yours.
Okay, no problem. Thanks.
Niu Yifei, table one's braised pork wrap.
Good, okay, no problem.
You can sit anywhere inside.
Table one, your food is ready.
Thank you.
Boss.
I want to try the award-winning pie you made in the competition.
So you watched the TV show?
Yes, I did.
Thank you.
Would you like to try
the blood cake egg pancake?
It's our signature dish.
Ma'am, please come in.
I look better on TV.
It's cooler inside.
Here's more. I'll put it here.
Okay.
Zhihao, table four ordered blood cake
and the dragon-phoenix special.
You can sit anywhere here.
Blood cake and dragon-phoenix, right?
Niu Yifei.
Table one gets two complimentary drinks.
Two drinks for table one.
Okay.
Ms. Chen, party of two.
Please come in.
Good, thank you.
Hello, may I have the last three digits of your phone number?
507.
Mr. Wang, party of one.
Please come in.
Good, thank you.
Hello.
May I have the last three digits of your phone number?
Dad.
Sit down.
It doesn't matter where.
Everyone is here.
Let's eat.
I heard from my assistant
that you took on some commercials.
The response after the show aired was quite good.
Some long-term clients reached out with offers I couldn't refuse.
It's good that you can manage both.
Actually, I should thank you, brother.
If he hadn't poached Jason away,
I wouldn't have had this opportunity.
Is it true?
But this isn't a bad thing.
If I can win the championship for Linlin,
the whole group's image
will keep getting better too.
You've really grown a lot.
Keep it up.
Thanks, Dad.
Here.
This is your favorite.
Thank you.
World's first non-stick pan inventor.
French cookware brand.
Even heat distribution.
Lightweight and handy.
Making cooking full of endless possibilities.
French cookware brand.
Busy working?
Why are you working so hard?
Nobody cares anyway.
You're okay with him being so arrogant?
Just like you were before, isn't it?
When I was in that position,
you did everything to bring me down.
Now an outsider sits there,
and you feel nothing.
I do have feelings.
His financial reports
are much better than during your tenure.
If his arrogance
can make the company better,
then let him continue this way.
You may leave now.
A familiar gaze across the distance.
Separated by unfamiliar desolation.
Those unforgettable snowflakes.
Melt away at the slightest warmth.
The innocence of kindred spirits.
Carrying the lingering warmth of regret.
Trying to preserve all treasured memories.
Only to watch them sink away.
Who can restore those loves.
And heal the wounds of ignorance.
Even restless moments of peace are destroyed.
Only understood after tears have fallen.
Some twists of fate.
Shooting stars turned to dust.
By the once brilliant darkness.
Your drinks will be served shortly.
Thank you.
Here's your food.
Excuse me, sir.
We can't share this table.
But everyone else is sharing tables.
Yes, but this is a VIP table.
It's reserved for important guests.
So...
Let me ask first. Alright, I'll get it to go then.
OK, you can wait outside. Thank you.
I'm here.
I've arranged seats for you.
Great, thanks.
I want black tea. This lady here.
Can Miaomiao share the table?
Hello.
This isn't a VIP table.
Yes, she's a VIP.
I made a special new dish today.
Would you try it for me?
Really? Sure.
And Miaomiao gets the same. The same for Miaomiao.
Yes, the same.
That's her favorite. OK, what would you like to drink?
Lin Liying, where are you going?
Do you know what VIP means?
Lin Liying.
Um.
Miaomiao, here's your seat.
I'll go prepare your order now.
Get me a straw first.
Okay, a straw, right? Here you go.
Thank you.
Wait for me. Take your time, it's fine.
I've confirmed it for you.
Jiang Zhihao will attend your stand-up show.
Just focus on your class.
Don't worry about everything.
You've been preparing your confession for so long.
It would be a shame if he didn't go.
That's just a comedy bit.
I just added a little something.
Right, the confession.
You're too young to understand.
Jiang Zhihao, I'm available.
What do you mean you're available?
I'm the one who's available.
Stop trying to steal him.
Here we go.
Eat up. It's special, give it a try.
Let me know if it's good.
Alright. Here, Miaomiao, your smoked chicken.
Thank you. Here.
Enjoy your meal.
I need to get back to work. Okay.
Go ahead.
Eat up.
Niu Yifei.
Please give this to that gentleman.
Sure, no problem. Just a moment.
I'll make it for you now. Wait a moment.
You look very handsome today, sir.
You just noticed?
Not bad, right?
This suit from my younger days.
Still fits me perfectly.
It's still so well-fitted.
Dad.
Why are you dressed like this?
My memory is really failing me.
I forgot to tell you.
We're having dinner with Weiyu's family tomorrow.
Don't forget.
You can go as our representative.
No way. I'm not going.
Let me tell you.
A dinner between these two families is a big deal.
Besides, our families are so connected.
Think about it.
You and Weiyu are good friends.
Now he's your sister's boyfriend.
And his father
used to be your boss.
He's now my chess buddy.
Chess buddy?
Yes, we just met recently.
What a coincidence, right?
So you must attend tomorrow.
Don't forget.
Did Chairman Chen and Chairman Li visit your store?
Yes, they did.
Uncle, please stop asking them to come.
We have too much wine at the store already.
It's money that should be spent anyway.
Why wouldn't we let our own people profit?
Right.
I've prepared some wine today.
Let's have a drink.
Drinking?
I'm very sorry about that.
Recently, I've been having
acid reflux.
I can't drink alcohol anymore.
Sorry.
There's a Chinese medicine clinic near Zhongshan Station.
They're very good.
I'll call them personally later.
Then I'll send you their information and address.
When you get there, just mention my name.
Really?
That's too kind of you.
I'm troubling you again.
Thank you.
It's no trouble at all.
We're practically family now.
Just go easy on me when we play chess.
That's no problem.
Next time I'll give you a rook advantage.
Good, it's a deal.
Chairman.
I was your executive assistant.
I never knew you played chess.
Good thing my dad isn't a dragon or lion dancer.
Chess is good.
In chess, before we make each move,
we have to think about the next step.
Just like how we worry about our children's future.
We hope they have a good life.
Yet we fear they might take the wrong path.
But it's alright.
Helping our children find their way home
is what we parents should do.
Right, well said.
What's this about dragon and lion dancing?
What are you doing?
Chili pepper.
I bit into a chili.
Really now.
I'm sorry.
He's been like this since he was little.
Talking nonsense.
It's fine.
This son of yours
is so different from your personality.
Completely different.
Have you ever thought about
Jiang Zhihao's biological father
suddenly showing up?
Yes, I think about it every day.
I can't wait for him to appear
and take this rascal back.
He's been mischievous since he was little.
Still mischievous now.
I simply can't discipline him at all.
Dad.
Kick me out.
I'll tear down the door to get back to you.
And you, Jiang Zhilu.
Don't tell me if you need sales.
I can bring lots of friends to your place.
Your friends are here.
He's the only one who'll pay.
I have tons of friends.
Chairman Deng.
I'm working at 168 now.
So all these fancy meals in the future,
don't come looking for me anymore.
And those two getting married,
that's their family business.
We're two separate families.
Two families,
right, Dad?
What are you talking about?
Sit down.
I'm full.
Jiang Zhihao, what are you doing?
Pack this up for me. It's fine.
Let him go. Uncle, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
As long as you're happy. My brother.
Sister Peng has prepared a wonderful meal.
Let's all dig in, shall we?
Jiang Zhihao.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
You want to hear me say sorry?
Yes.
Deng Yongkuan is my father.
You think I was just pretending to be a hotel receptionist?
I had my suspicions.
So has he talked to you privately?
He wants you to return to the Deng family.
I'm so outstanding.
Everyone wants to claim me as their son.
That's funny.
Jiang Zhihao.
If you don't see me as your sister,
you can get out right now.
What are you talking about?
Otherwise, why is it that for everything,
Dad and I are always the last to know?
You always do this.
You don't talk about your problems,
or when you're unhappy.
This is just my background.
Everything is the same as before.
It won't affect you and Deng Weiyu.
It's like this.
The same goes for your fight with Deng Weiyu.
If you're going to act, do it better.
Don't let me find out.
Otherwise,
every time I know you're not okay
or in trouble,
but I can't help at all,
it feels really awful.
From beginning to end,
have you ever considered me family?
Isn't family supposed to be
able to talk about everything?
What?
Jiang Zhilu.
Is your heart strong enough?
Want to hear a soap opera story?
Okay.
It didn't happen that long ago.
Anyway, when I was sorting through Mom's belongings,
I found a notebook.
And inside it said
Deng Yongkuan is my father.
Then,
about his relationship with my birth mother,
they separated because of some misunderstandings.
After the last round of team competition,
we eliminated two contestants,
leaving six competitors.
To discover what makes the perfect breakfast,
we've made an important decision,
which is
to pause filming
and let everyone rest.
But during these next three days,
I'd like you all to find the perfect bread,
using what you consider the finest bread
to create an unforgettable breakfast.
This is your next challenge.
Good. Cut!
That was good.
Thanks. This segment works well.
We still have interviews to record later.
Everyone please don't rush off.
What about me?
Should I leave, sis?
You look beautiful in that outfit.
I almost lost the last competition,
but I won't slip up this time.
How to win this competition?
I think I just need to make sure my ingredients don't disappear.
I'll guard my bread carefully.
That's good. Thank you.
Meizi, you're next.
I thought
we could fight side by side like before.
But if you want to play dirty,
fine.
From now on,
I'll defeat you as a competitor.
Just wait.
Cut.
Next person, please.
That's good. It works.
Okay.
Do you have any competitors you're afraid of?
I'm not afraid of anyone.
Yes.
Your sales this month are not acceptable.
So I need to talk to you.
Just a moment.
What is it?
The store manager meetings have been changed to
3 p.m. every Thursday.
I know.
Your handover was very clear. Thank you.
Yes, I'm quite busy since I just got back.
Your things...
So I'll schedule you for 3 p.m. tomorrow, okay?
Shanru,
I've already completed the handover.
Good.
Do you have anything to say?
I want to tell you that
these past few months have been challenging,
but also incredibly exciting.
Thank you for giving me this opportunity.
Good work. You may leave now.
Shanru,
please let me stay.
I want to continue working here.
Please hear me out.
Even though I don't have formal education in this field,
and I stumbled into this job by accident,
I may not be as good as you think,
but when I see my proposals
being implemented,
I'm truly happy.
Really happy.
I never knew what I could do before,
but now I have a goal.
My life,
just like Noto Toast,
once hit rock bottom,
but now is climbing up step by step.
Noto Toast hasn't even reached its peak yet.
I can't leave.
Please let me stay.
I beg you, don't reject me.
Shanru, I'm here.
I've interviewed her for you.
She'll join the planning department tomorrow.
Take her with you.
Good. Thank you.
Why did you bring me here?
It's lonely watching this alone,
and I already bought the tickets.
Before I Confess.
You also invited Jiang Zhihao?
How could I possibly invite him?
Why are you here?
Junni has a performance today.
What are you two doing?
Dating?
I'll go get more drinks.
Dating my ass.
You're the one dating.
What did you say?
What are you drinking?
Coke.
For my next bit,
I want to talk with everyone about
whether there can be
pure friendship between men and women.
Impossible.
No way.
Let me speak first.
I believe there is.
Don't you think
when paired with the word 'pure',
everything becomes very clean
and sacred?
What? Why are you laughing so loud?
Don't believe me?
Let me give you some examples.
My former supervisor
looked like Captain America.
His body was like
his clothes were about to burst open.
He had a perky butt
and his
you know
was impressive.
One day he told me,
'Feel free to come to my place.
We'll really just be
purely watching streaming platforms.'
Come on!
At that time we were
young and full of energy.
I planned to watch for just 10 minutes.
But we ended up watching the entire Harry Potter series.
That's so lame.
Eight hours,
folks, eight hours!
Next, I went on a dating site
swiping on my phone
and saw someone's profile that said
'purely cuddling to sleep'
so I immediately arranged to meet.
Please, just purely cuddling to sleep.
We're best at purely cuddling to sleep,
thank you.
Next is about my husband
who one day told me,
'You have to believe me.
That place
is really just for
pure massage.'
I believed him.
And now we're divorced.
If anyone dares to talk to me about pure friendship again,
I'll twist their head off.
Okay, let's change the mood.
Actually,
there are many people
who love someone in their hearts
but don't dare to say it.
Alright, I'm one of them.
Who?
Wait, okay.
Huang Xiaohu has a song
'Oh My Love.'
That's a bad joke.
Sorry, let me try again.
Huang Xiaohu has a song
called 'More Than Friends'
'You never knew I wanted to be more than friends.'
I think this line isn't quite precise enough.
How do you think it should be changed?
'More than friends with benefits.'
That's vulgar!
Someone drag him out of here!
You know, many people know
I'm a show producer
and they always tell me,
'Your shows are all scripted
and planned in advance.'
Let me tell you,
he's my joke writer.
Shut up. No more.
You took the money, now do your job properly.
Don't just stand there.
Right. I was just...
Nothing.
Okay, it's fine.
Um.
I'm so nervous.
Actually, I'm performing today because
I want to confess to someone.
Who is it?
And that person is in the audience.
Who?
Tell me who.
Who is it?
Jiang Zhihao.
Can we stop being just friends?
Which one? That...
You?
Did you hear that?
Get together!
We
are really just friends.
No chance.
See?
No script for this.
So awkward.
God, I'm so miserable.
Is anyone here stuck in the friend zone?
Raise your hand.
Make me feel better.
Put that down. I...
You can get lost.
Anyone else in the friend zone?
Can you raise your hand so I can see?
Miss, you...
Wait.
You seem to be sitting between
two people I hate.
Was this planned?
All set up.
Just kidding.
Which one is your 'just friend'?
Left or right?
We also 'just' watch streaming platforms together.
Just cuddle and sleep?
And just massages?
Lin Liying, what are you doing?
You already confessed to me
and then pretended it never happened.
If that's not being a jerk, what is?
You kissed her.
You kissed her
and then refused to be with her.
What's that about?
That was for the pork belly.
Pork belly?
You'd kiss her for a piece of pork belly?
No, it happened so suddenly.
What could I do?
That's hilarious.
How sudden was it?
Like this?
What are you doing?
I'm thirsty.
Your parents' bed?
Why did you ask me to come?
This is by appointment only.
Miss it and it's gone.
Here?
What are you doing?
Checking the price.
Price?
Happy birthday to you.
That sounds nice.
Make a wish.
I wish I could win the lottery.
Remember to share.
Okay.
My second wish
is that someone will give me a massage later.
I bought this.
Don't you like it?
I want to make my third wish now.
What are you doing?
Mosquitoes.
There are mosquitoes on both sides.
So many of them.
Yeah.
You didn't think I was going to kiss you, did you?
Of course not.
I was just thinking,
who gets this many mosquitoes on their birthday?
Has anyone ever asked you this question?
What question?
Why aren't we together?
Dating?
If you're not curious about the other person at all,
wouldn't that be too boring?
Like I know you so well.
You sneeze when the seasons change.
And when watching movies,
you always want half salty, half sweet popcorn.
Also,
your birthday cake must be mango flavored.
There's no excitement left, right?
We know each other too well.
Even if there is love,
it's probably just habit.
Pure Friendship.
Thank you everyone. No script.
I'm Wang Junni.
Table for one. Do you have any seats?
We're fully booked at the moment.
The wait time might be about an hour.
One hour?
What a coincidence.
Do you two know each other?
If you do,
would you mind sharing a table?
Thank you. All dishes are served. Enjoy your meal.
Is this your first time performing?
I think you were the funniest one just now.
And don't you think that line we added at the end
worked pretty well?
Thank you.
You had so many opportunities before
to cut in,
but you just had to interrupt
when I was confessing my feelings.
You've ruined my love life too.
So I guess that makes us even now?
I can't believe this.
If you hadn't confessed to him just now,
would they have had this chance?
Let me tell you something.
Many things are all about timing.
Have you ever wondered
why they've known each other for so long
but never got together?
Because they were waiting for
someone to make the first move.
And who just created the perfect moment
for them?
It was you, wasn't it?
You're really clueless.
How did you know
that's my name?
Excuse me for interrupting.
We have a promotion where you get pork belly
if you kiss. Are you interested?
- Sure.
- No.
Come on, it's just pork belly.
Call the police for me, thanks.
The bus won't be here for another 15 minutes.
So what should we do now?
Well,
we can only wait.
Wait.
We still have to wait like this?
You just kissed me.
You...
Jiang Zhihao, you're such a jerk.
I was talking about the bus.
Or maybe we shouldn't wait anymore.
So are we taking a taxi?
What I mean is,
should we give us a try?
Lin Liying.
I thought I knew you well,
but you still surprise me.
Do you think I'm beautiful?
For example,
your lips are drier than I imagined.
Do you know lip balm exists in this world?
Lin Liying.
Will you be with me?
Just try making me wait again.
I don't want to stand in the way of your love anymore.
If my son can be happier than I was,
then I'll be happy.
You look a bit
chubby.
You're the one who's fat.
You've been fat for years,
and I've never complained about it.
We're breaking up.
The day your mother died,
I was there.
Don't touch me.
Mom already knew
you were Deng Yongkuan's son.
Deng Weiyu's mother was afraid you'd recognize each other,
so she watched Mom die without doing anything.
Is it that anyone
who gets involved with us
will come to a bad end?
I'm begging you to stay away from my life.
Just live miserably,
the more miserable the better.