[theme music playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
[doorbell chiming]
-Seok-ryu.
-Hey, right now…
Hear me out first. [panting]
I won't delay it any longer.
I said I'd wait until later,
but that was an excuse I made
to pretend to be considerate.
I lied to myself.
It was out of fear. I was scared.
So…
[mellow music playing]
The thing is…
I'm going to say it this time.
When I said you were driving me crazy…
When I said I was losing my mind
because of you…
What I meant by that was…
I…
like you.
[dramatic music playing]
[boiling]
That's hot!
Hey!
-Are you okay?
-[Seok-ryu groans]
-Yeah, I'm fine.
-Let me see.
No, I'm okay.
-You burned yourself.
-[Seok-ryu] No, I'm fine.
You're going to form blisters.
You should've been careful!
You're the one who made it
so I couldn't be careful.
I didn't know you had water boiling.
I was burning inside.
What are you saying?
[Seung-hyo] Stop moving.
We have to run cold water over this.
[romantic music playing]
Hey, why are your hands so warm?
What?
My body usually gives off a lot of heat.
-Should we go to the hospital?
-No way. It's fine.
Your hands are already a mess.
What if they're scarred too?
It's not a big deal.
I'm sure this will be
a daily occurrence now.
Now that I've decided to cook,
I'll get burned and cut
while battling water, fire, and oil.
Jeez. I can't even tell you
to stop either.
[laughingly] Who are you
to tell me what to do?
I'm just worried.
And why would you worry about me?
Do you really not know?
From morning until night,
since childhood until now…
it's been my fate and my task.
They're shackles weighing me down.
I wonder if you're going around
acting like a decent human.
I worry your mom will give you
a beating for saying something dumb.
Hey!
You've cried a bunch of times
after meeting so many bums.
What else?
You get hit and shoved all the time.
Are you a bumper car or something?
This is a kitchen. It's full of sharp
and blunt objects, okay?
That's why I'm worried you might get hurt.
I wonder if you're skipping meals or not.
And I hope…
you have good people around you.
That's just how I feel.
So…
think about…
how you feel too.
I know you just got out of a relationship.
I know you're confused
because he's here too.
So I'll give you some time.
I answered you first…
but you can answer me later.
Gosh, it spilled everywhere.
What were you boiling?
I was going to make meatball soup.
[scoffs]
[Seung-hyo] I left
your gift in the drawer.
I hope you like it.
[chuckles softly]
[serious music playing]
[chuckles]
[chuckles softly]
This is prettier.
[doctor] Professor?
You said it was
an important day, so you left early.
Why are you back?
I must have made a mistake.
I thought it was over…
but I guess not.
[doctor] I see.
Are you talking about work?
-[bell rings]
-[female announcer] Code blue.
-Emergency medicine, TA code blue.
-[doctor] Let's go.
HIS SECRET
[exhales]
[sighs]
You're really not going to swim?
You don't like the water?
Why?
I'm scared.
And I can't breathe.
It's dark, and it feels like
something's pulling me down.
[muffled] In the water,
you hear the same sounds
as when you cover your ears like this.
So there's no need to be scared.
[pleasant music playing]
[Seok-ryu] Seung-hyo might not know,
but I think I liked him first.
It was when I was really young,
and I gradually forgot about it.
Strangely, those feelings…
[inhales] …are still so vivid. [exhales]
[exhales]
But, Seung-hyo…
is just Seung-hyo.
You lunatic.
I actually did it.
Was I too hasty?
Did I make it too overwhelming?
No.
[amusing music playing]
If you've drawn the knife,
you should cut something.
No, I think I cut something
I shouldn't have cut.
No.
It was decisive.
It was good. I did great.
I can't keep hesitating forever.
But was that all I could say?
That she was driving me crazy?
This really is driving me crazy.
That I was losing my mind because of her?
I really am losing my mind. This is nuts.
[exhales] How do I face her tomorrow?
Damn it.
[groans]
Damn it, I'm going lose it.
[gong clangs]
[chants playing in background]
[pop song playing]
No, it wasn't too much for her.
It wasn't.
It was too much. Way too overwhelming.
Damn it, how do I face her tomorrow?
I won't… How could I not?
Damn it, I'm going insane.
Is she asleep right now?
[dog barks distantly]
She's not asleep.
This is insane.
But why isn't she asleep?
For crying out loud. Why isn't she asleep?
This is driving me nuts.
I think I was too hasty.
I think I was.
[groans softly]
[Seung-hyo] Why isn't she sleeping?
Jeez, I'm going nuts.
This is nuts.
I didn't get any sleep.
[song ends]
[Hye-suk] Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Of course, I did.
But you look a little tired.
Did you have trouble sleeping?
I was pretty busy.
-Do you want coffee?
-No, I'll drink some tea today.
[liquid pouring]
Do you like your gift?
[chuckles softly]
I was waiting for you to notice.
Yeah, I love it.
You know so well exactly what I like.
It looks good on you.
Thanks. I'll cherish it forever.
I'll get you something nicer next time.
[chuckles softly]
Come on. You promised. It's for real.
Of course.
Wow, I can't wait.
Oh.
Welcome home.
Were you on night duty?
It was Mom's birthday yesterday.
[liquid pouring]
Was it?
I was so busy. I must have forgotten.
-I'm sorry.
-It's fine.
Birthdays come every year.
They're not important.
-It's late, but let's have a meal--
-I should go in and rest.
I'm a bit tired.
[door opens]
-[sighs softly]
-[door closes]
[sighs]
Jeez, look at these bags under my eyes.
The Grim Reaper would look better than me.
[mellow music playing]
Hey, stop the blood with this.
You'll get blood on it.
Isn't it expensive?
That's not important.
Why would you come here? It's dangerous.
Who wipes a nosebleed
with something like that?
I should give this back.
Gosh, the windows weren't even open.
Where does all this dust come from?
-Mom.
-What?
I was wondering
if you've ever thought about investing?
Investing?
Yeah.
I'm sure you've heard,
but it's the era of marketing these days.
It's become crucial for fitness trainers
to promote themselves.
Have you heard of Instargram?
Yeah. You take pictures
with your phone and post them, right?
I saw it on TV.
-I knew it. You're so trendy.
-[scoffs]
You can become an influencer
if you get famous on Instargram.
Then, you'll be able to take in
all the money in this country-- [grunts]
How dare you go
and spew your nonsense again?
Hey.
Excuse me, my dear older sister.
How about you butt out?
I'm only 13 months older than you.
Where the hell do you get off
acting as if you're some cool kid?
Did you forget what your face value is?
You know,
I was going to live the rest of my life
in a beautiful, nonviolent way…
[Mi-suk] Jeez!
Are you two fighting
in front of your mother this morning?
Mom, let's continue
our deep conversation later.
Mom, don't listen to this punk.
You say that nonsense again,
and I'll end your life. Got it?
-Yeah, right.
-[Mi-suk] Enough.
Hey.
Why aren't you in a T-shirt today?
I put them in the laundry.
No way. I folded several of them
and put them in your room.
No, they're gone.
[Mi-suk sniffing]
You wore perfume too?
Me?
Yeah, you.
[quirky music playing]
Very fragrant. [chuckles softly]
Did… Did you sleep well?
Of course!
I was stretched out comfortably
and slept without any thought. You?
When I lay down and closed my eyes
for a second, it was morning.
I snored so much my nose is sore.
I was grinding my teeth so much
I thought I dislocated my jaw.
[groans softly]
-You grind your teeth in your sleep?
-What?
I almost forgot.
Thanks for letting me use this.
I appreciate it.
Look. I got all the blood out.
I wish it hadn't come out.
Why? To ask for something better?
No, so I could be buried in it later.
It would've looked pretty nice.
Are you insane? Do you think
you're in some melodrama or something?
And why would you be buried?
We have to make it to 100.
Make it to 100? Together?
No, I misspoke.
You know that saying
about living for a long time…
-What?
-Good health and longevity.
Eternal life and 100 years of marital…
I mean, there's a saying
that's about 100 years.
What was it? A hundred years…
What's wrong with me?
So about my answer…
Can I really tell you later?
Yeah, think about it
thoroughly and carefully.
Really?
Does that mean your answer
has no expiration date?
Still,
life is finite,
so no expiration date is a bit unfair.
I guess so.
Then…
[amusing music playing]
We should decide on an item.
How about canned goods?
Aren't there too many kinds?
Peaches, pineapples,
corn, ham.
-Tuna.
-Let's go with whelks.
The expiration date is…
Three years? Hey, that's too long.
Then, what about Pacific saury?
No stainless steel cans.
How about instant rice?
This has six months left.
This one is eight months.
-This one's for a year.
-How about this stuff?
Your period of careful deliberation
lasts as long as refrigerated foods?
You said I could answer later.
You told me to think it through carefully.
The depth of thought is more important
than how long it takes.
Since they're fermented,
don't yogurt drinks have
the longest shelf life?
Let's go with milk.
Why did you even bother to ask then?
But it'll be based on the back row.
Deal.
[heart thumping]
[thumping stops]
Hey, there's plain milk
and strawberry milk.
There's also chocolate, banana,
and coffee. Which one do we pick?
Did she leave? When did she go?
Then, I'm going to pick the one
with the shortest shelf life.
[store clerk] Excuse me.
I've been watching you.
-What are you doing?
-What?
I barely make minimum wage,
and I had neatly arranged all of those.
What am I supposed to do
if you mess them up like that?
I'm sorry.
You scared me.
[Na-yun] What's this?
-Snacks. Share them with everyone.
-[both exclaiming]
Oh, darn you. You're so heartless.
Hey, don't you know
I'm lactose intolerant?
There are canned goods too.
[both exclaim]
Hey, wait.
I get why you'd buy
pineapples and peaches,
but why did you buy
Pacific saury and whelks?
I'll take this one. I'm on a diet.
Sorry, but this one's mine.
-But you like banana milk.
-Really?
[Na-yun] Yeah.
I normally do,
but this one has the shortest shelf life.
Goodness. Why did he smile like that?
I have butterflies.
Whelks for breakfast? Gosh.
How about a can of beer?
Soju?
Soju and beer?
[groans softly]
-You want to write about your experiences?
-Yes, one special per week.
[chuckles softly]
It's a trend these days.
Pick a topic each week, cover it,
and write an article on it.
Can you do it?
Didn't you want to transfer departments?
In movies,
superheroes always have two jobs.
They have two personas too.
I'm just an ordinary person,
but I wanted to give it a try.
Can I ask you why
you suddenly changed your mind?
I received the undeserving title
of Mudflat Man. [chuckles softly]
-What?
-You won't kill the idea, will you?
[chuckles softly]
What's with that confidence?
Okay.
Where will you go first?
HYEREUNG 911 SAFETY CENTER
[Mo-eum] Excuse me?
An emergency responder for a day?
Yes, I'm here for the experience,
not an interview.
I'm here to participate, not observe.
I'll work your hours and respond to calls.
-But…
-Don't worry.
I won't cause any inconvenience.
Yes, but you can't just
will that to happen.
From what I can see, I don't think
you'll be able to ride the ambulance.
And I don't think you'll be able
to carry anything heavy either.
[quirky music playing]
Goodness.
What are you doing?
I want to clear up
any misunderstandings about me.
I'm confident in my stamina.
Not just anyone can survive
the social affairs team.
[heart thumping]
-[grunts]
-Please help me out!
I want to be in the field,
not behind a desk,
and put my body to use
to write a good article.
All right. I get it.
Goodness. Please get up.
What are you doing?
I said it's not up to me. Please stop.
Who do I need permission from?
What?
Mr. Kang, I look forward to your article.
[chuckling] Thank you, sir. I look forward
to working with you.
[chuckles] Also, feel free to let me know
if you need anything.
-Yes, sir.
-There she is. That's Jung Mo-eum.
-She'll be responsible for helping you.
-[chuckles softly]
I'll be on my way now.
Wow, I didn't think he'd be good
with people enough to be a reporter.
But he's totally sociable.
-What was that?
-[Mo-eum] Yeah.
What?
-[door lock chimes]
-[Geun-sik groans]
Why is this here?
Did I leave this here?
[humming]
What on earth?
I wiped everything down before I left.
Why is this dirty?
What?
Gosh.
Did I not wipe it down?
What?
-What is this?
-[delivery man] Your delivery's here, sir!
Hey.
You're already working hard this early.
Well, that's how work is.
Today, it's two radishes,
two cabbages, two carrots,
and a bag of onions, right?
Okay.
[man on TV] Excuse me?
Have we met somewhere…
Watching this show has been
my source of pleasure these days.
-It's so good.
-Yeah.
What was that actress's name?
She's become the nation's sweetheart.
Hey, do you watch this show too?
No, it's such a waste of time to watch TV.
I'd rather read.
Of course, you would. [scoffs]
So, what's it about?
It's a romance story. It's about a man
and woman falling in love.
See? It's so predictable.
Most things are predictable.
And it's what everyone likes.
-Yeah, right.
-[phone vibrating]
Jeez.
Yeah, I like that actor too.
-Yeah, me too.
-Me too.
So, how did the two meet?
They met abroad.
HYEON-JUN: COULD WE MEET?
It was so romantic too. [chuckles]
[pleasant music playing]
[in English] We went over all the items
with the engineer,
including their feasibility.
Yes, so we now need to schedule
a time for the briefing before we go live.
Yeah. Hello?
Hello?
[in Korean] My battery's dead.
[sighs] I didn't bring my charger.
-Use mine.
-What?
It seems urgent. You can use my charger.
Okay. Thank you so much.
But it might be too loud
if I take the call here.
It's fine.
Thank you.
[lounge music playing in background]
[Mi-suk sighs]
Thank you for meeting with me.
I didn't come for you.
I wanted to hear what you had to say.
Let's order your coffee first.
We can order some cake too.
You used to love cheesecake.
Why did you do it?
Seeing you two together
made me happy and content.
Why did you do it?
I'm sorry.
I don't have any excuses I can give.
You didn't cheat on each other.
But you both won't tell me why.
[scoffs]
You're all so tight-lipped.
You've already broken up,
so I can't weld
or patch things together again.
But I can't let it go,
because it's all so strange.
If you called off the wedding,
you must've seen each other's worst.
-How come you don't hate each other?
-I've never hated her.
I still love Seok-ryu.
[exhales]
[exclaims]
What's this?
What?
Why the hell is she with him?
[phone vibrating]
[Seung-hyo] I took this from the back row.
EXPIRATION DATE JUNE 29
Only 11 days?
[amusing music playing]
My goodness. Excuse me.
-I'm so sorry.
-[all chuckling]
That's okay.
Seok-ryu's roar woke everyone up.
Okay, shall we start class?
-Yes, ma'am.
-All right.
I'll have to store this well.
Stay fresh in here.
I'll see you in 11 days.
[music ends]
You scared me.
Why are you sitting there like that?
Did you close up and come home?
No customers again?
Why did you meet Hyeon-jun?
What?
Did you think I wouldn't know
if you kept it from me?
I'm Seok-ryu's dad.
How much more of a fool
will you make of me?
Don't say it like that.
I met him
because he suddenly contacted me.
I was going to tell you.
[inhales]
What did that punk say?
-He said he still loves Seok-ryu.
-[scoffs]
He wants to go back to the US with her.
How dare that bastard say that?
So, what about you?
You just sat there
and listened to him as he said that?
I told you.
I'm all for Seok-ryu going back.
Jeez, there you go again
with that US nonsense!
Are you obsessed with the US or something?
-Are you trying to sell your daughter off?
-What?
You know how you are.
As long as the conditions are met
and it makes people jealous,
you don't care,
no matter how Seok-ryu feels!
That's right. I am self-serving.
She'd send me bags
from US outlet stores every season.
She even sent shoes,
but I'm heartbroken now that's all gone.
So what? I was hoping to brag
that my son-in-law was a lawyer.
But I'm sad it's over now. Are you happy?
[sighs softly]
Look, I just…
I don't want her
to be a failure and live like me.
to live a poor, shabby life!
[exhales]
-You don't know anything. [sniffles]
-[door opens]
-[door closes]
-Damn it.
[sighs]
Oh, hi.
-Hey, Gyeong-jong…
-Geun-sik…
Do you want to get a drink?
That's what I wanted to ask.
-Okay, let's go.
-Okay.
[Geun-sik] Gyeong-jong.
What's it like to live as someone
who's successful like you?
Is it nice like this crunchy fried squid?
For me,
my life's like this soggy piece. So soggy.
It's soaked in my feelings of inferiority.
[sighs audibly]
Since I'm incompetent,
I worried something went wrong.
I was so scared
that I couldn't even ask why.
[chuckling] All I could do
was pester my wife.
Mine's bone dry.
My family could crumble
at the slightest touch.
But this tteokbokki…
[Geun-sik] Yeah?
Is it made from flour or rice?
This?
This is made from rice.
Why?
Don't get me wrong.
Ones made with flour are good too, but…
I like ones made with rice.
-Why?
-Because it's…
It's so chewy.
But usually, snack shops
often sell ones made with flour.
Why?
Well, because it's…
So this is what you're curious about?
Ones made with rice bloat more
and get soggy more easily.
The sauce doesn't soak all the way in,
so it's tricky.
Why?
Well, because that's how they are.
And so, I told you why.
But you keep asking me why,
so I'm telling you why the ones
made with rice are naturally like that.
Why?
Damn it.
[amusing music playing]
[exhales]
I'm trying to be serious here.
Why do you keep joking around?
This tteokbokki…
Is it made from flour or rice?
Jeez, this guy has
a terrible habit when drunk.
Why did you go back to the start?
What are you, a repeat sign?
Come on.
-Why?
-Stop it! I swear!
It's scaring me now.
[door opens]
Goodness.
That scared me.
[chiming]
What is this?
-Why is this here?
-[door opens, closes]
[footsteps approaching]
Did you…
put this here?
-What is that?
-I don't know. I've never seen it before.
I don't know what it is either.
Wait, did it break?
[Gyeong-jong] Lily of the valley…
Lily of the valley…
[slurring] Why do you keep saying
"lily of the valley" over and over again?
Why? Lily of the valley… What?
Are you talking about the song?
♪ Late night at Mapo Terminal ♪
♪ A night train with nowhere to go ♪
[Gyeong-jong] Lily of the valley.
Lily of the valley…
What is it then? It's not the song?
-Lily of the valley…
-[Geun-sik] Yeah?
-They're her favorite.
-They are?
No.
-They were her favorite.
-Okay.
[inhales]
They were hard to find.
So you had a hard time
finding lily of the valleys, Gyeong-jong?
Okay, then.
I'll get them for you. [chuckling]
I'll do it.
I'll get them for you. Wait here.
Wait right there.
I'm going to get you
those lily of the valleys.
I'm off to get them.
[groans softly]
-[wind blowing]
-[groaning]
[dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
[snoring]
[pleasant music playing]
[music ends]
[scoffs]
That fool. What gives him the right?
Now, he spends the entire night out?
Unbelievable.
You've never done this before.
You're scaring me.
A son can't help his mom do the dishes?
Use hot water. Get rid of the grease.
Yes, ma'am.
-Wash that too.
-[exhales]
As I do the dishes,
shall we continue
our conversation from before?
-Give them back!
-Come now!
Don't be like that. Hear me out, Mom.
In order to become an influencer,
I need admirers… No, worshippers.
I need followers.
Why would people follow you?
Based on what?
You're so objective. Right?
[Mi-suk] Yeah.
So that's why
you can buy followers with money.
With tens of thousands,
they say you can live comfortably.
You can do group buying
and get sponsorships.
I only have two million won.
Mom, it's an investment.
That's not nearly enough.
-[Seok-ryu] You damn lunatic.
-Damn it.
-Come here.
-Hey!
You punk. A parasite would have
more of a conscience than you.
You've mooched off
your parents your whole life.
And you still want to live like that
in your thirties?
Damn it.
Hey, watch your mouth.
You better watch how you act.
You always have your head in the clouds
instead of working hard to earn money.
[exhales] Don't you even feel bad for Mom?
Cut the crap.
What makes you different from me?
What?
Say that again.
-Hey, that's enough!
-What?
I already have
a terrible headache as it is.
Why do you two always fight
whenever you see each other?
Seok-ryu, stop it. Dong-jin, go inside.
-You're the worst.
-You have no right to act mad.
[Mi-suk groans softly]
-Mom.
-[door closes]
That punk's tricked you before.
You better not give him any money.
-I'll take care of it.
-What do you mean?
He's like that
because you always baby him!
That's because…
he's had a hole in his heart since birth.
The doctor said not to make him cry
as he might need surgery.
I've heard it a thousand times.
But he didn't have surgery.
The hole closed up on its own.
You should've been stricter on him.
How could you let him
be this immature for so long?
Try having kids of your own.
See if you can treat
your sick child that way.
-Are you taking his side again?
-[objects clattering]
Is being sick that big of a deal?
[objects clattering]
[sighs]
-[door opens]
-[sniffles]
[door closes]
[mellow music playing]
THERE ARE TEN DAYS LEFT
HAVE A GOOD DAY TODAY
Damn.
[exhales]
-[Tae-hui] What are you doing?
-What? Nothing. Let's go in.
-Take this.
-Okay.
[phone chimes]
[Seung-hyo] There are ten days left.
Have a good day today.
Did he just send me an emoji?
He's never done this before.
[man] Did something good happen?
Hyeon-jun.
I'm glad I caught you before it got cold.
What is this?
It's jasmine tea.
I've changed my strategy.
The "lasts" didn't work,
so I'm going back to the beginning.
[pleasant music playing]
You looked busy earlier,
so I didn't get a chance to tell you.
Thank you for the charger.
I owe you one.
It was no big deal.
Yes, it was.
On that note, can I treat you to a drink?
No, it's okay.
It's not okay with me.
I'll buy you some coffee.
But the coffee here…
isn't good.
I see.
Do you like osam-bulgogi?
What?
-You don't?
-I do.
Let's go then.
It's jasmine tea.
-Why are you giving me this?
-It's good for digestive health.
It looked like
you were drinking too much coffee.
I'll be outside.
[door opens, closes]
I'm going to start over again.
If I do that,
you might smile at me as you did before.
Well, that's it for today.
Bye.
Maybe we shouldn't have done so well.
I can't believe Fresco likes it already.
Isn't that good?
No.
Then, our collaboration
will end too quickly.
You should've drawn them
with your foot so they'd reject us.
I wanted to be pressed by deadlines
so we could pull all-nighters.
I'm way too competent for that.
[scoffs]
You know how to joke now?
I'm mad for some reason. I think
you've become comfortable around me.
I walked into the fire on my own.
Like you said, you won't know
what happens until it goes in the kiln.
Wait, did you…
I told Seok-ryu how I felt about her.
[exhales]
What did she say?
She hasn't answered me yet.
I see you're stuck in that kiln
with nowhere to go.
[exhales]
You could say that.
I hope it cracks.
I hope it swells up inside and bursts.
I'm already burning and suffering.
I don't need your help as it is.
So this is how it turns out.
Is this why people say men
and women can't be friends?
The reason why I can't stay
as Seok-ryu's friend
isn't because she's a woman.
It's because she's Seok-ryu.
[mellow music playing]
It makes me angry, but I agree.
I don't think you deceived me
while having feelings for her either.
You were a great person when we dated.
I was very emotional back then.
I'd be crouched in a dark corner alone,
and you'd always bring me
back into the light.
That's probably why…
I couldn't forget you.
Does this mean I've been dumped?
No, you could be dumped too.
-What?
-The man from the restaurant that day.
He seemed formidable.
They seemed pretty close.
Not to mention,
he's a sexy and mature man who's at ease.
Just out of curiosity,
has the social perception
of what's sexy changed?
Or should I be questioning
your eye for beauty?
You're feeling threatened.
Of course not.
I'm only asking
as a concerned business partner.
Call me if you come out
of the kiln broken.
I'll buy you a drink.
Why are you being so negative--
Let's make it makgeolli.
I'm not drinking. And I never will.
Tell Myeong-u I'll send him
the bowl I promised soon.
[phone vibrating]
BAE DONG-JIN
[Dong-jin] Seung-hyo,
are you free tonight?
TRANSFER 2,000,000 WON?
[automated voice]
Your transaction is being processed.
TRANSACTION AMOUNT: 2,000,000 WON
BALANCE: 180,002 WON
Please take your card.
Please check if you have
all of your belongings.
Thank you.
Hey, it's been a while.
No, it's just…
I was wondering if you knew
of any good part-time jobs.
That was so fun. [chuckles]
-[lady] It's fun every day.
-What?
No, like last time…
I'll call you back later.
Excuse me. What kind of place is this?
Oh.
It's a cooking school.
We also hold cooking classes.
-Cooking?
-Yes.
[exhales]
[muttering]
Good grief.
Mister, can I get an order of tteokbokki?
Goodness, I'm sorry.
I don't think I can sell this to you.
Why not? You have so much.
[chuckles] I don't think
I can sell this in good conscience.
It's too soggy.
What can you do?
Okay. Goodbye.
Goodness.
I'm sorry. Come back next time.
[chuckles]
[grunting]
How about we start over again?
That's right. It's the bag from before.
What is this?
What is this? I didn't put this in here.
Honey.
What?
[exhales]
[Seok-ryu] I'm home.
Hi.
Why are you sitting here?
Is no one home?
Dong-jin said he needed to talk to me.
He said he'd be late
and told me to wait inside.
Why would he need to talk to you?
I don't know.
He said he has something to propose.
Damn it. That bastard.
He even asked you?
This punk must be out of his mind.
What? What is it?
Mom, do you know what Dong-jin's doing?
He asked you for money, and now, he asked…
KOREAN FOOD CRAFTSMAN
PRACTICAL SKILLS
What are you doing?
What is all of this?
Mom, don't you think
this is a little much? Come on.
Why are you inspecting stuff in my bag?
What is all of this?
Aunt Mi-suk, you should calm down first.
-Sit down…
-Can't you tell?
It's a cooking book.
Why do you have it?
Why would you have this?
Because I want to cook.
What?
Let's hear what she has to say first.
She's had her reasons.
Seung-hyo, did you know?
You knew she was taking cooking classes?
Yeah.
Goodness.
After running wild
and being reckless together,
were you conspiring together too?
I'm sorry.
-But--
-[Seok-ryu] He didn't do anything wrong.
-This is my business. My dream.
-How dare you?
[Geun-sik] So…
that's why you've been coming to my shop?
To secretly use my kitchen?
I'm sorry.
I didn't have a place to practice.
I was going to tell you both
after I got my certification.
[Geun-sik] Certification?
Seok-ryu, do you really want
to do this type of work?
Yeah, I do.
I worked really hard to find my dream.
Goodness.
What about your old work?
Well?
What about all the studying you did?
And your experience?
It was a valuable experience.
That time is precious to me.
But…
I think this is where it ends, Dad.
[Mi-suk sighs]
[Geun-sik exhales]
We raised a smart fool.
Seok-ryu, did all of that praise
go to your head?
-Dad…
-You couldn't stay at a job for ten years.
Do you really think
you can handle this kind of work
with that kind of mentality?
[door opens, closes]
What's going on?
Why is the mood so awful again?
[exhales] Was it you again, Seok-ryu?
[scoffs]
Don't you two ever think
you're being too hard on me?
Why are the standards different for me?
Why are you so strict with me?
What's Dong-jin done up until now?
He wanted to be a soccer player
but ran away from camp.
He wanted to learn music,
so you bought him instruments,
but he quit right after.
He tried four times
and couldn't get into college.
He joined a theater troupe
to be an actor but quit immediately.
Why the hell are you bringing the past?
Do you know why
I've worked so hard up until now?
You've both suffered so much
because of Dong-jin.
I didn't want to add to your worries.
But what is he doing now?
He's got another wild idea,
and he's pestering you, Mom!
Shut your mouth!
Keep quiet.
[Seok-ryu] How do you
always put up with him
but never allow me to make
a single mistake?
Why…
Why can't I do what I want with my life?
-[Mi-suk sighs]
-Fine.
Seok-ryu, do whatever you want.
You can do it all.
But not cooking.
[sighs]
-[Geun-sik] I'm sure it's fun now.
-[sniffles]
[Geun-sik] You imagine your customers
happily eating your food
in a charming restaurant.
-I'm sure it's like a fairy tale.
-[sighs audibly]
[Geun-sik] I was like that too.
That's why you can't.
You can't because I've tried it. Okay?
[sighs wearily]
Hey.
You're not the only one who feels wronged.
You're not the only victim!
I've spent my entire life
being criticized by you!
Damn it. So annoying.
As if she's the only one feeling wronged.
[exhales]
[door opens, closes]
-[Geun-sik exhales]
-[sighs]
[sniffles]
[sniffles] Don't follow me.
Follow me.
[Seok-ryu] How did you know
about this place?
[Seung-hyo] I've kept it
in mind for times like these.
Times when I'd need to comfort someone.
[Seok-ryu] So you came here with Tae-hui.
[Seok-ryu] There's a thing
called business ethics.
But you know…
knowing everything
about each other's past in detail
isn't much of an advantage
for me right now.
Look at those flowers!
They're so white. They look like popcorn.
How does your brain work?
How do you go from flowers to food?
I mean, they look delicious.
I want to drizzle caramel over them.
What do you think they're called?
Bridalwreaths…
are neighbors to these, the fringetree.
They say the leaves look like rice.
I see.
Such interesting names.
[pleasant music playing]
[exclaims]
-[Seung-hyo] You're not tall enough.
-[exclaims]
Damn.
Do you feel a little better?
I'm just a little embarrassed.
How do you end up seeing
all of my embarrassing moments in life?
I can recall all of your dark past…
Wait, this won't help me much either.
[groans]
This is so annoying.
I've felt so wronged for the longest time.
I thought getting it off my chest
would make me feel better.
I only feel worse.
I know that feeling.
Parents aren't always right.
They make mistakes
with their children too.
When you argue over it,
you end up feeling guilty for no reason.
Exactly.
How did you know that?
Did you fight with your parents too?
No.
I'm so jealous of your family.
Your parents are cultured,
and they watch what they say.
Also, you don't have a dumbass sibling.
I envy that the most.
When will that punk grow up?
Where am I supposed to
practice cooking now?
Do it at our office.
-What?
-Use the kitchen after everyone leaves.
Everyone's on a business trip this week.
Still, I can't do that at your office.
Did you forget I'm the president?
You've gotten a taste for power.
You can't be reckless
just because you're the boss.
-You want to use it or not?
-I'll use it.
-[chuckles softly]
-[Seok-ryu] But just once.
And I didn't ask for this favor.
You offered it to me first.
Who's saying otherwise?
Right. [inhales]
[exhales] The view is nice.
They really look like popcorn to me.
It's past midnight.
You have nine days left.
Wait for me.
HYEREUNG 911 SAFETY CENTER
I'm Kang Dan-ho.
It's nice to meet you.
Welcome to the team!
I heard you were coming,
and I couldn't sleep.
Why?
Because I was excited.
Are we taking pictures today?
I used a sheet mask last night.
-[Mo-eum] Jeez.
-Are you here to have fun?
Just act normal.
That way, he'll know
how serious our job is.
-Yes, sir.
-We all put our lives on the line.
-You should know that.
-Yes, sir. I'll keep that in mind.
[Mo-eum exclaiming]
That last statement
sounded a bit old-fashioned even for me.
He's a great person
when you get to know him.
He has a very strong sense of duty too.
I can tell even if you don't tell me.
Okay. Shall we get going?
Yes, ma'am!
[amusing music playing]
[sighs]
Okay. You're going to use
this locker for today.
-Okay.
-Your basic equipment.
You have your safety helmet,
vest, thermal jacket, and camera.
You can put the camera on your vest
wherever it's comfortable for you.
-Okay.
-Next.
Now, we ride in this vehicle
when we're dispatched to a call.
-[Dan-ho] Okay.
-Let me show you.
This is… Get in.
-I'll tell you about the first-aid kits.
-Okay.
The smallest bag is the vitals bag.
-Vitals.
-[Mo-eum] The biggest one is for wounds.
This is the cardiac arrest bag.
This is the fluids bag.
I'll take each one out
and explain them to you.
[announcer] Emergency dispatch.
15-3 Boun-dong, Seongbuk-gu.
-[Mo-eum] Seat belts on.
-My helmet.
[siren blaring]
["Eine kleine Nachtmusik" playing
over speakers]
[music fades away]
[slow classical music playing]
[Gyeong-jong] Wow!
It's seasoned fernbrake!
Wow.
[sniffs]
It looks so good.
Mmm.
It's so good.
[Gyeong-jong] Eat.
What about you?
I have to go right now.
Thanks…
-What?
-I said, thanks.
[chuckles softly]
[pleasant music playing]
[door opens]
[door lock chimes]
[door closes]
[phone vibrating]
[Gyeong-jong] Our son is grown,
and time has passed.
It's time.
It's an important decision in life.
Think about what I said.
[inhales]
[exhales]
-[Mo-eum] We're paramedics. We got a call.
-[man] Over here!
[exhilarating music playing]
[Jeong-u] Are you okay?
[bees buzzing]
[man] I think he hurt his back.
He won't move.
We're doing tree maintenance when he fell.
There must've been a beehive here.
[Dan-ho] Should I get the protective gear?
[Mo-eum] No, we can't delay any longer.
His condition could worsen.
[Jeong-u] They're not wasps.
You won't die.
Come here.
[Mo-eum] Sir, don't move.
[groans softly]
[Dan-ho] I'm glad the patient's condition
isn't serious.
Yeah.
But I can't say the same about your face.
It doesn't hurt at all. I feel fine.
Yeah, and you could've just left the scene
if things looked dangerous.
Why did you keep helping?
How could I? We're a team today.
United in purpose.
[Mo-eum] Whatever.
Get treated. We have to get back.
No, I want to complete the day together.
How can you rescue anyone
looking like that?
You should speak for yourself, Mo-eum.
Your face is fine,
but you got stung all over.
Why did you just say my name?
Oh.
Calling you anything else
feels less personable.
-What shall I call you?
-[Jeong-u] Captain Jung?
We got a call from Gongsin-dong.
I think we can get there faster
than the station.
-[Mo-eum] Let's go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
Yes, Captain Jung!
[pop song playing]
[Jeong-u] He has a herniated disk,
but there's no elevator.
[Mo-eum] But we have legs.
-Let's go quickly.
-[Jeong-u] Let's go.
[man 1] This way.
-[man 2 groans]
-[Mo-eum] Sir?
[man 2 groans]
You can't move, can you?
No.
[Mo-eum] Can you help us?
-[Jeong-u] Put some power in it.
-[Dan-ho] Okay!
[Jeong-u] Go slow.
[Mo-eum] We're paramedics.
-Did you call it in?
-[lady] Yes.
-What did he eat?
-Shrimp. He didn't say he was allergic.
-[Jeong-u] Give me the oxygen tank.
-[Dan-ho] Okay.
-Give me that first.
[Mo-eum] Sir, allow me.
-[Jeong-u] I'll check his pulse.
-Okay.
Doctor, the patient seems
to have anaphylaxis.
Yes.
I'll inject him with
the epinephrine saline.
-Give me the epinephrine injection.
-[Jeong-u] Okay.
[Mo-eum] Sir,
I'll administer the injection.
-Grab his arms.
-[Dan-ho] Okay.
[Mo-eum] Roll up his left sleeve.
[groans softly]
[Dan-ho] Can you see his vein?
I know I contacted you,
but I didn't think you'd be doing
the remodeling project.
These days,
boundaries are blurred more than before.
Not to mention, I think it'll be fun.
-A theater is such an exciting place.
-Hmm.
I want to amplify that excitement
and turn it into a space where people
can experience a variety of things.
We're so grateful.
But it seems you have just as much
affection for the theater as we do.
I have a lot of memories at the theater.
You do?
Yeah, the first movie I ever saw
in a theater was Toy Story.
Did you watch it with your parents
when you were a kid?
No, one of my favorite friends.
Mmm. [chuckles softly]
[pleasant music playing]
[inhales]
Since I'm here,
I want to see the staff areas inside.
-Is that possible?
-[owner] Sure, of course.
Let's go.
I'm on my way back to the office.
Are you coming to practice later?
Can I really go?
No one will be there,
and I already told Myeong-u.
Okay, I'll come.
See you later.
[line disconnects]
What's going on?
-Why are you with him?
-[clears throat]
What happened was…
I waited in front of her cooking class
and we came together.
-[sighs]
-[Seung-hyo] Look.
Don't you know this is stalking?
Will you learn your lesson
after I call the cops?
I didn't follow Seok-ryu here.
I came to the architecture office.
I came for a consult.
[Myeong-u] Look at that.
Seok-ryu and Mr. Choi
have brought our new client. [chuckles]
Come up slowly.
We'll serve you with love and care.
What's going on?
What's he here for?
[groans softly]
I didn't eat anything, but I feel sick.
So you want to build a house.
[Hyeon-jun] Yes.
My parents just retired,
and they're thinking of coming back home.
We have some land in Gapyeong.
It'd be nice if we had a house
they could visit like a vacation home.
Oh, my. That sounds nice.
What a beautiful idea, right?
We at Atelier In
want to gift your parents with
a peaceful and contented retirement.
Did you have a budget
or construction timeline in mind?
[Hyeon-jun] For now…
-I'm aiming for next year.
-[phone vibrating]
Just a moment. Sorry about that.
Hey, Hye-ran.
There's a cockroach? Just kill it.
What?
-Okay, I'll be right there.
-[line disconnects]
Did something happen at home?
I think Ro-hui ingested
some roach pesticides.
What? Isn't that serious?
[Myeong-u] The kids are playing just fine.
But I think I have to go.
I'm sorry.
You can finish the consult with Mr. Choi.
Okay, you should go.
-[Myeong-u] Yeah. I'm going.
-Myeong-u, call me later.
Yeah, I will.
I'm sorry.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[Seung-hyo exhales]
[Hyeon-jun sighs]
Mr. Song Hyeon-jun.
Is this consult an excuse?
More of a pretext.
The plans for my parents are true.
I see.
Unfortunately,
I have no intention of taking this on.
[Hyeon-jun] I see.
That's too bad.
I heard you were a skilled architect.
Of course, from Seok-ryu.
Don't say her name anymore.
Don't show up like this either.
It's over between you two.
No, it's not.
We can't break up that easily.
That's what you think.
You'll see it in time.
You'll see what type of relationship
we had
and what we meant to one another.
I'm not curious about what's in the past.
I only believe what Seok-ryu says.
Is that belief purely based on friendship?
Of course not.
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
[Seung-hyo] How's the practice going?
[Hyeon-jun] Were you waiting long?
-Are you following me? You're not leaving?
-No, I'm not.
If you keep this up,
I'll have to report you for trespassing
and squatting.
Are you arguing legal principles
in front of a lawyer?
Did you forget this was my company?
I'm sorry, but can you both leave?
You're disrupting my cooking.
-I'll be good.
-I'll just watch from here.
[Seung-hyo clears throat]
If you both sit in a chair,
I would be so grateful.
Okay.
-[Seok-ryu] Both of you.
-Okay.
Thanks.
[quirky music playing]
Are you really not leaving?
No, I cleared my schedule.
Also, I plan to eat the food
that Seok-ryu makes.
I'm asking because I'm genuinely curious.
Was your personality always like this?
Yeah, she liked this about me.
I'm strategic and have a clear purpose.
How much longer do I have to wait?
-Are you done yet?
-Are you hungry?
I just have to fry the pancake
and boil it in the broth.
Take your time.
I'll wait for as long as it takes.
[Hyeon-jun] By the way,
it smells so good.
The aroma is nutty and fragrant.
[sniffs]
-It smells like it's caramelizing.
-That's not my cooking.
I could smell it too.
Oh, right.
I bought this for you.
What? Popcorn!
You said you wanted to eat some,
but what can I say?
It's cold now.
It's fine. I was hungry.
Don't eat that.
Why would you eat this?
What are you doing?
You act like I poisoned it.
Trans fats aren't exactly healthy food.
[exclaims]
That's so good.
This devilish sweet-and-salty flavor
flowing through my veins.
Do you remember watching
Toy Story with me?
Of course. I remember the lines.
-"To infinity and beyond!"
-[Seok-ryu] You remembered?
-Of course.
Leave me some.
Have some.
[grunts]
Great job.
-Yeah, great job.
-[exclaims]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
You look like you might pass out.
You lied about your stamina, didn't you?
That's because everyone else's stamina
is absurdly good.
[Mo-eum] I swear.
[Min-ho] Goodness.
What happened to your face?
He was valiantly stung by bees.
You did great today.
It wasn't so bad.
You went out in cooler weather.
Our undies get soaked
in sweat in the summer.
You should've experienced
that dry and flaky feeling.
Do you prefer the start, middle,
or end of summer?
I'll come back.
[Min-ho chuckles]
Did you have lunch?
[Dan-ho] Well…
[Min-ho] Go get changed.
Let's have dinner.
-[Mo-eum exclaims]
-Yes, sir.
-Let's go.
-What are we eating?
[indistinct chatter]
[sizzling]
You can eat now.
-Thank you!
-Mmm.
-[exhales]
[Jeong-u] Mmm.
This place is good.
The meat is so tender too.
Captain Yeon specially brought you
to his favorite place.
It means he's opened up to you.
Try the garlic sauce.
It tastes much better.
-Okay.
-Try it with fresh kimchi too.
It's like honey.
I'll pass on the honey.
I have a grudge against bees now.
[Mo-eum chuckles]
It seems we'll get a proper article.
You know we lack time to eat.
It's not just that.
There was no time to go to the bathroom.
That's where our occupational disease
comes in.
Bladder infections.
Captain Jung suffered from one
just last month--
-Eat this!
-[groans]
Eat up.
My mouth was full.
Are there other difficulties?
Feel free to speak openly.
-[all] Mmm.
-[snaps fingers]
We don't listen to classical music.
Did you hear it?
It plays over the speaker.
Yeah.
The warning sound startles everyone.
They changed it for our mental health.
But classical music startles us now.
I was in the bathroom of a bookstore,
and I was startled
to hear a cardiac arrest sound playing.
I forgot my pants were down
and almost left.
Mozart.
-Mozart?
-Yeah.
As one of our occupational diseases,
we suffer from arrhythmia too.
Since we're always stressed.
How do you relieve that stress?
-Dating?
-[Min-ho chuckles]
That's more wishful thinking though.
I'm single right now.
Do you even have time to date?
We make time.
Since we work in such small spaces,
we end up dating each other.
Office romances?
-Do you all have experience in that?
-I married my office romance.
He dated a girl in the academy.
What about you?
Excuse me?
I'm not interested in that.
[exclaims softly]
Captain Jung likes heroes
from Marvel and DC.
I've never seen her be impressed
with a real man.
No! There is one! Back then!
The man who cleared the road.
-Mudflat Man?
-[Jeong-u] Yeah, Mudflat Man.
I should've looked at his plates.
If you want to break down her defenses,
you need to be impactful like that man.
You should eat it while it's hot!
It's hot!
You're taking such good care of him.
I want one too.
[amusing music playing]
-[Jeong-u] Gosh, it's hot.
-[Mo-eum groans]
I'm sorry.
Have a drink.
[Hyeon-jun] Oh.
-What?
-[Seok-ryu] Here.
Why are there two bowls?
-Are you really giving him one?
-The more taste testers, the better.
Evaluate it objectively.
Will you be understanding
of harsh feedback?
It's a necessary process for growth.
You're putting a lot of significance
into tasting the food, aren't you?
We had an ideal relationship where
we constantly helped each other grow.
-Sure.
-Don't eat it.
-Thank you for the meal.
It's good.
[groans softly]
[exhales]
-Are you okay?
-[Seung-hyo] Hey, Seok-ryu?
-What's wrong? Does it hurt?
-It's my stomach…
Where and how does it hurt?
-What are your symptoms? Can you get up?
-[groans]
[breathing heavily]
This won't do. Let's go to the hospital.
-I'll take you.
-[Seok-ryu exhales]
Hyeon-jun, grab me.
[Hyeon-jun] You can lean on me.
[solemn music playing]
[Seok-ryu exhales]
Miss, is the abdominal pain severe?
When did it start?
Can you describe your symptoms?
Three years ago…
I received surgery in the States.
Just a moment.
This is Bae Seok-ryu's medical records.
Give it to her doctor.
[doctor] What surgery was it?
Stomach cancer.
I was diagnosed with stage 2.
They removed 70% of my stomach.
I underwent chemotherapy.
[sighs]
[exhales weakly]
[labored breathing]
HIS SECRET
HER SECRET
[gloomy song playing]
LOVE NEXT DOOR
[Hyeon-jun] Seok-ryu isn't a child to me.
She's a woman.
[Mo-eum] How are you feeling right now?
[Seung-hyo] There's a parenthesis
between Seok-ryu and me.
And Hyeon-jun
is inside of it
with a part of her that I don't know.
[Hyeon-jun] If you're doing this,
I want you to take
a proper path so you won't fail.
[Seok-ryu] Hyeon-jun proposed to me.
[Seung-hyo] How could you
not tell me that?
[voice shaking] This is how little
I meant to you?
Even as a friend,
I meant this little to you?
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce