Hi, Ma Ri.
Hello. I want to give it a go.
Really?
Good thinking.
I know...
he won't be fooled by a clumsy act.
I want to prepare for it thoroughly.
Send me the information about Ms. Woo.
Okay, I'll send you the information about the gallery...
and on recent trends in the art field.
And also I'll send you a list of paintings...
that Gunha Group will be interested in.
I just need the information about the gallery and Ms. Woo.
I already know the trends in the art field,
and about his liking,
I'm well aware of it.
You must be.
Okay then.
(Episode 17: I've Been Bewitched by Love)
Did you get the laptop that I sent you?
The documents are all in there.
Also, the meeting is at 3pm.
Come by 2pm, so we can prepare beforehand.
We look so alike.
We're almost the same person.
Let's monitor the necrosis...
and set another surgery date.
All right.
By the way,
I decided to work here just because of you.
The others think I did it because of the money,
but that's not true.
I told them that I will become your partner.
I was very confident and...
We need to talk.
Is he here again?
No.
Even if he does,
don't meet him.
I'll contact him and meet in person.
I talked with your mom,
and she said you'll visit her.
I should go.
Are you going...
to tell her?
How much are you going to tell her?
I'll be back.
Be safe.
Tell her I miss her.
Can I go there dressed like...
Ms. Woo?
The employees here don't know her face.
Dr. Ha is the only one who knew her,
but he'll be busy working.
Jung Won will be away as well.
"Hello, I'm Woo Ha Kyung."
No.
"I'm Woo Ha Kyung."
The number and address to a hair salon are written.
Pick your clothes, and get your hair done there.
I bought the same wedding ring as Ha Kyung's.
You're here early.
Don't be afraid.
You're not Yoon Ma Ri now.
You're not Yoon Ma Ri.
I didn't touch your bedroom...
since her belongings were still there.
Your albums are in here...
as well as your poems and books.
Take them.
You lost so much weight.
I know it's hard.
But what can we do?
We need to be strong and move on.
If you still haven't let go of her,
you need to stop.
Stubbornly holding on isn't always love.
Letting go is also a form of love.
Finally,
I got the chance to meet you.
I've been focusing on my personal work.
I apologize.
Before signing,
He asked for a few paintings for his lobby.
Show them to him, and then sign the contract.
This is a list of the recommended paintings for your lobby.
Please take a look.
I'd like to see the paintings myself.
They're on display, right?
This painting is...
Excuse me.
You could've just looked at the documents.
I'd like to appreciate them in peace,
so vacate the area.
But...
How about we take a look after the customers...
are gone?
I think...
you should close for today.
I'll pay you a year's worth.
Well...
I'm very sorry.
The gallery has an emergency and will need to close for today.
Could you come back next time?
The exit is over there.
I apologize.
I'm sorry.
- Goodness. - Why suddenly?
Vice-Director Joo.
You should leave as well.
It's finally quiet now.
You can start.
What could it be that it's this hard for you to talk about?
I'm sorry.
I...
I did something very horrible.
This is the second piece that I recommended.
The composition and colors are unique.
It's been quite popular lately.
What...
did you say?
You did what with Ha Kyung's face?
How could you do such a thing?
Please forgive my son.
Please...
I've explained five pieces so far.
- Is this enough? - Please go on.
I need more pieces.
Do you know...
how beautiful your neckline is?
I'm the only one who can touch it.
Could you give it back?
Thank you.
Ha Kyung.
On the day I buried you here,
I felt like...
my heart was being ripped apart.
I can't go out right now.
It's midnight. What are you saying?
Of course, I miss you.
But I can't go out right now.
You're being like a child.
Do you have to hear it?
Fine. I'll say it.
Honey.
Are you happy now?
I love you. Are you happy now?
My goodness.
I wanted to ask you...
who you were talking to.
I wanted to ask you what kind of relationship you had with him.
But I was afraid.
So I decided not to.
The excuse I wanted to hear from you...
and the hope of starting everything over...
were all buried here...
with you.
Ha Kyung.
The thing that hurts me,
Ha Kyung,
is that your face...
will let her hide.
I gave your face...
to her.
I still have so many things to say to you.
I still have so many things to do with you.
So I gave your face...
You saw all the paintings we have in the gallery.
That's it?
There aren't a lot of paintings than I expected.
I'm sorry about that.
Do you want to head to the office now?
One more thing.
I want to buy...
"A Self-Portrait" I saw last time.
I'm not sure which one you're referring to.
The self-portrait with the Cistus.
I believe the name of the artist...
was Leah.
It won the exhibition.
I don't think I can sell it.
I want to know more about that artist.
I can't keep in contact with the artist.
I'm sorry.
In that case,
Yoon Ma Ri,
I...
know.
I don't think...
there's an artist by that name.
That's the name of the artist I'm looking for.
Yoon...
Ma Ri.
If you know that artist...
personally,
we can try to reach her.
I'll try my best to protect her.
I'll try my best...
to let her live.
I don't want to...
regret anymore.
Your eyes are...
so dangerous.
Underneath the innocence,
they're filled with fear.
It includes...
betrayal...
which drives me crazy.
Your eyes look like...
you're planning to run away from me someday.
Before I came here,
I looked through your past activities and performance.
Usually, people sign their names on the contract,
but I see you brought a stamp instead.
I guess...
you like to thoroughly investigate before you sign a contract.
It's the key to a successful business.
The stamp is the first sculpture...
I made after I recovered.
It's very meaningful to me...
as it feels like I'm starting my life again.
I can see that this contract...
is quite meaningful to you as well.
This stamp suits well with this contract.
Let's finalize the contract with a handshake.
Thank you again for the support Gunha Group...
will provide.
Her eyes are so familiar.
Tell me what you're hiding from me.
You'll never know...
who I really am.
(Director's Office)
You know about...
the fact that I'm looking for...
my wife, right?
- Yes. - I will...
find her...
regardless of where she is hiding.
Regardless of how she is hiding,
I will find her.
I hope you find her soon.
Sir, you have to head back to the company.
The chairman is looking for you.
If by any chance,
you know my wife, please tell her that...
we'll see each other soon.
(Doctor Seo Jung Won's Office)
(Doctor Ha Seong Ho's Office)
Look at these wrinkles.
I should ask Dr. Ha for help.
That's ridiculous.
You better not do anything to that face.
My gosh. What's it to you?
Well... It's because you look so young to begin with.
If looking young is a crime, you'll be sentenced to life.
Gosh, that's so corny.
Is Dr. Seo available right now?
He's out.
Ms. Kim, what's my schedule...
Dr. Ha.
You and Dr. Seo are alumni and business partners, correct?
How much do you know...
about President Kang?
I know that he is one mysterious man.
Could you...
look into him for me?
I'm Kang In Wook.
I'm surprised that you know me. It's an honor.
What brings you here?
I came to see Dr. Seo, but he's out.
Dr. Seo?
What is this regarding?
Can we talk?
Let's go to my office.
Sir, you'll be late for your meeting.
Sure. Where is it?
This way.
Wait in the car.
Good work. It's a success.
Are you okay?
I am.
You don't seem to be.
I'll take you home.
It's really fine.
I hope...
you won't need me to be...
Ms. Woo anymore.
I heard that you were the one who drew the Cistus painting.
Please, keep painting.
I'll sell them here.
I know you need to keep painting.
Since we know your situation,
we'll allow you to keep painting under your stage name.
I don't think that's a good idea.
If you went to the same school,
you must be close to him and his wife.
Of course.
We always hung out together.
You're quite close.
I think we'll meet again.
(President Kang In Wook)
Okay. I'll wait for your call.
I'm leaving now.
Okay.
I should go.
This is quite disappointing.
We couldn't talk much.
We should meet again soon.
I bet we'll have a lot to talk about.
- Doctor... - Ha Kyung.
Ha Kyung.
When should we meet?
What day are you free?
I'll let you know after checking my schedule.
I'll have to check my schedule as well.
All right, then.
It's disappointing, but we'll meet again soon.
We will.
You're much more handsome in person.
You have good skin as well.
I'll contact you soon.
Sure. It'll be my honor.
Goodbye.
I'll be waiting.
He's gone.
I haven't seen Dr. Seo. Did he go somewhere?
His afternoon schedule was empty, so he went to his mother's.
I see.
Why did President Kang come here?
Did Dr. Seo...
perform surgery on a VVIP without my knowing?
- Doctor... - Ha Kyung.
I'm sorry for this inconvenience.
I should go.
- I'll drive you. - No.
I'll go alone.
- Hongyi-dong, please. - All right.
Please drop her off safely.
(Art Gallery Agreement)
Did you visit her?
You're back early.
I think it's best that I ask you...
why Ma Ri was here.
If by any chance,
you know my wife, please tell her that...
we'll see each other soon.
Once you get a place,
call me.
- Doctor... - Ha Kyung.
I had no choice.
I told you this was our only way.
No one benefits from this.
At least,
the gallery benefits from it.
I'm going to cancel the agreement.
- What? - Just know that.
To you, this gallery is nothing but a memory of Ha Kyung.
What about me?
After she got into that accident, no...
Ever since she told me that she was going to open...
a gallery under her name even though she knew nothing about it,
I was the one who sacrificed everything to run this gallery.
Sure.
This place must be a beautiful memory for you.
But for me...
For me,
this is my life.
Still, you shouldn't have used her.
Why not?
Ha Kyung's face saved her life.
So what's the big problem about acting like her for a brief moment?
Hae Ra, listen.
You risked someone's life just so we could live.
I don't want to be disappointed in you anymore.
You...
You were always on my side.
Why have you changed?
What is she to you?
Tell me.
What kinds of feelings do you have for her?
Make it clear.
What is she to you?
I'll look over the contract before canceling.
The feelings I have for her...
may be...
Hae Ra told me.
- I'm sorry that... - I know why you did it.
- I'm... - I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Had I not given you my wife's face,
you would've been able to live in peace.
Imagining how painful it must've been for you...
hurts me.
I'll make sure you never have to see him again.
Are you doing all right?
I'm worried about you.
Yes, I'm doing all right.
I should...
go.
Goodnight.
Don't worry about anything.
Woo Ha Kyung.
Who are you?
Who in the world...
are you?
That's ridiculous.
That can't be.
The feelings I have for her...
may be...
Perhaps, I can't let go of Ha Kyung.
- Doctor... - Ha Kyung.
Or...
If that's not it,
then perhaps,
I want to start...
all over again.
I've Been Bewitched by Love.
(I've Been Bewitched by Love.)