There are a lot of branches. Be careful.
- Look in every nook and corner. - Do you see anything?
Search carefully.
They found the bag.
If he found out that I'm alive,
what am I going to do?
What do I do now?
(Episode 7: Tell Me)
I'm Oh Cheol Young who gave you a call.
After I got your call, I checked it in advance.
It's like playing detective. This is amazing.
Is it?
Help us catch the criminal then.
Here. Do you see this serial number?
This is our dress.
Speaking of which, I need to check the customer list for this dress.
Pardon. That's...
Why? I can't?
Once we increase surveillance and start a compulsory search,
you'll be in bigger trouble.
- All right then. - No, please wait for a moment.
It's a limited edition dress, and there are 30 purchasers.
It's a dress of great value, so they all would still have it.
We confirmed that these three still have the dress.
We can single out a suspect...
by narrowing them down to one.
I'll be back then.
Yoon Ma Ri.
Hello? What do you think this is?
This is Kang In Wook.
Kang In Wook or whatever...
I'm Ma Ri's husband.
I'll appreciate your help.
Okay. Sure.
Once Ma Ri calls me,
you will be the first one to know that.
I'm sorry.
- Sir. - Wait.
Here.
President Kang.
Let's move on to the next purchaser.
I already gave her a call.
Why is it so hard for the three of us to get together?
It's been so long.
That's because Doctor Seo's busy.
Isn't that because of your busy schedule?
That's not my fault.
I want to rest too.
Then you should say this from time to time.
"You don't need this surgery."
You always say that you can do it.
It's not like you're a money-grubber.
You like Jung Won, don't you?
What are you talking about?
You always take his side.
That's...
Don't you know that we grew up like brother and sister?
No, not like that. I mean, as a man.
Gosh.
Have I lost my mind?
He only cares about his wife even when she's dead.
Gosh.
Why are you upset? Whatever.
Doctor Seo.
Did you recently do surgery on someone without telling me?
It's a little disappointing.
Who is the VIP that you'd keep it secret from me?
You're supposed to keep things secret because they're a secret.
Why would you pry?
I should get going.
You know how he feels now.
He must miss Ha Kyung a lot.
Can't you just let it go?
I'm also sad that Ha Kyung died.
It might be a good chance for you.
You liked Jung Won even before he met Ha Kyung.
If you have a secret crush, do it right.
You're not supposed to show it. You're such an amateur.
I didn't show anything.
I think it's one of these two.
Number one.
Jung Won knows everything, but he pretends not to know it.
Number two. Jung Won...
only cares about Ha Kyung,
so he really doesn't know.
Number three.
Ha Kyung is the only love of Jung Won's life.
And it's fine by me.
So I like Jung Won.
It's number four.
Both of you are crazy.
I'm Oh Cheol Young who called you about the dress.
- Is this it? - Yes.
President Kang, I think this is it.
Thank you.
(Employment placement agency)
Hello. I heard you are looking for an employee.
We already found one.
(Wanted: a waitress)
I came here for this job.
Not even one position?
Hey, Miss. You have nowhere to go?
Do you want to come with us and have a drink?
I know a good place.
Hey.
Hey, let's have fun together.
Hey, we have a big umbrella here.
You don't even have an umbrella.
Here's an umbrella.
Hey.
My gosh.
Hey, Miss.
Why are you...
Hello?
Hey! What are you going to do?
This is an expensive suit. This is a limited edition.
Gosh, please stay quiet.
Her family is coming over.
So why did you complicate the situation?
I won't let her get away with it.
This is an expensive suit.
How dare you...
Darn it.
I have a witness.
Hey.
Are you Mr. Seo Jung Won?
- Yes. - It seems like...
a drunk man provoked her to a quarrel.
I guess his suit got ruined a little while she scuffled with him.
She could've just given him some money,
but she wouldn't say a word.
I asked her over and over again...
to get your number.
Do you know her?
How have you been?
Well...
I've been around looking for a job.
I can do anything if they hire me.
I thought...
I'd be able to do anything with a new face.
But...
it turns out there isn't much I can do.
I thought I would be...
free once I change my face.
With a new face,
I thought...
I would be able to get away from him.
But I can't.
I'm still scared...
and pathetic.
I feel lost.
Eat it when it's warm.
(Chicken soup, pork rib hangover soup, pork backbone stew)
We have 10 people left.
Give me.
(Purchaser list)
(Woo Ha Kyung)
Let's call it a day. I'll see you tomorrow.
Ma Ri...
Ma Ri is out there.
It's raining now.
She must be really cold.
She must be terrified.
Where are you?
Where are you, Ma Ri?
Come in.
Then...
I'll be in your debt.
This way.
There's nothing in this room.
I'll buy things you need tomorrow.
Get some rest then.
You're up?
I've been trying to keep quiet.
I'm sorry. I didn't even ask you.
I just wanted to make you breakfast.
It's okay. It smells good.
The food is ready. I'll just put the soup in a bowl.
Are these from my fridge?
Yes.
I just made them with the ingredients you have.
I hope you'll like them.
Of course, I will.
I don't even know how long it's been.
Since I had breakfast with someone like this.
I'll make your breakfast every day.
Please let me do that while I stay here.
I'm a good cook.
I used to be a full-time housewife.
No, you don't have to do this.
Please let me at least do that.
Then...
I'll be more comfortable staying here.
Please.
Thank you.
While you stay here,
I want you to feel comfortable and plan for the future.
Okay. I'll do that.
By the way,
can I ask you something?
Did your wife go somewhere?
I shouldn't have asked that.
I'm sorry.
- Good morning. - You're early.
I should work hard.
The gallery is going through a financial crisis.
(Seo and Ha Plastic Surgery)
Any hope with this artist is done for.
Why?
I can't reach her.
I'm sure another gallery contacted her.
I think I lost to my rivals even before I knew it.
Because you can't hide your light under a bushel.
And there's a secret you can't hide.
Going up.
The doors are closing.
(Seo and Ha Plastic Surgery)
So you finally performed the surgery on her, right?
What?
The woman who asked you...
to change her face to get away from her husband.
Am I wrong?
I heard a patient without a name was hospitalized for a month.
So I was curious who she was.
And it occurred to me last night.
Right, that's her.
She was an emergency patient.
I guess she was thinking about killing herself.
It was about a month ago.
Was it around Ha Kyung's funeral?
It was that day.
That's why I wanted to help her.
I can't believe this.
So you're Seo Jung Won Theresa.
You're such a philanthropist.
If you find the painter, ask her if she wants to sell it.
I want to meet the painter too.
I'm sure there are more paintings of flowers.
Flowers that beckon people to take a look at them.
Can't you just look at me?
Now that Ha Kyung is gone, can't you...
What am I doing?
Where's your pride?
I'm back.
Hey.
I heard you're busy these days.
You're busy with your new business...
and busy looking for your wife.
I'll take care of everything without making any mistakes.
Your mother...
was a very nice person.
She ran away numerous times,
but she eventually came back.
With black and blue bruises all over her body,
she came back home with a limp.
Why do you think she did that?
Please don't talk about Mom.
It was because of you.
She had no one but you to turn to.
No one understands you, but I do.
You take after me to the bone.
Have a baby as soon as your wife comes back.
Once she has a baby, she can't run away from you.
She will come back even if she gets beaten to death.
Call your mom.
Tell her to come back now.
You take after me to the bone.
No. No!
Ma Ri.
Please come back.
Come back and comfort me.
Come back...
and console me.
Now!
(Find a job, prepare for a contest, go to Woo Seon)
I can do this.
Everything will be fine.
Let's survive and live a happy life.
You and me.
What are you doing?
You're home.
I was looking for a vacuum.
I'll take it out.
I'll do this.
He seems fine on the outside, but I doubt it.
He must be in shock.
You know he always keeps his worries inside.
He must be doing the same about Ha Kyung's death.
Exactly.
He hasn't reported her death either.
Okay, I understand.
I'll take good care of him. Don't worry, Mom.
Are you home?
Who are you?
Ha...
Ha Kyung?
Let's talk outside.
Ha Kyung is dead.
So how...
How is this possible?
Explain.
What did I just see?
It's a long story to tell. Let's go talk somewhere.
Explain it here. Who is she?
The woman with Ha Kyung's face. Who is she?
Tell me...
it's not what I'm imagining. It's not true, is it?
What...
have you done?
Is there a certain face that you'd like?
You know what?
If you have a face that you like,
feel free to make me look like it.
Did your wife go somewhere?
I shouldn't have asked that.
I'm sorry.
I was just wondering...
if I could stay here without her permission.
My wife...
passed away.
I suffered for a long time,
and I think my mother got rid of all her pictures...
in case they'd remind me of her again.
What are you doing?
What were you thinking?
You've done something crazy.
Are you aware of that?
If people find out,
then...
you'll lose your medical license.
I think I know...
whom...
I look like.
What do you want me to do now?
Just...
act like you don't know.
What about you?
What will you do?
I'll be cheering on that woman...
who looks like Ha Kyung.
So that she can be happy at least from now on.
Ma Ri.
I know...
whose face I have.
I finally found the reason...
why you looked surprised...
when the bandage was removed from my face.
I'm sorry.
I'm not mad at you.
I was the one who said I was okay...
with any face.
I think...
it was a miracle...
that you came to me that day.
A miracle given by a deity...
so that I could...
live my life anew.
And I'm grateful for it.
You saved me.
Your wife...
must've been wise and brave.
I want to...
be that kind of person too.
I won't go back to being my old self...
who went in hiding and ran away out of fear.
So...
don't be sorry.
I don't think...
I can stay by your side in this face.
Otherwise, you'll be faced with difficulties.
Seeing my face...
will be a torture for you too.
I can deal with it.
You may stay...
until you find something stable.
No.
I shouldn't put my savior in trouble.
I'll leave.
Why don't we have dinner together for the last time tomorrow?
I want to serve you a decent meal.
Let me show off my cooking skills in a while.
She looks like her.
So much like her.
I was quite stunned yesterday.
Ha Kyung...
was my long-time friend.
Jung Won first met her because of me too.
I watched the two the longest of all.
Ha Kyung is the only love in Jung Won's life.
She was in a coma...
for five years due to a car accident.
He was devoted to her like always even during that time.
The night when he operated on your face...
That day...
was Ha Kyung's funeral.
Jung Won...
is a thoughtful man,
but that day, he suffered a mental breakdown...
which made him...
do something unacceptable.
He created someone...
who'd replace Ha Kyung.
I pity you...
for having your face changed into hers without knowing any of this.
The result...
may be considered that way.
But I have no intention of blaming him.
He saved my life.
I am...
truly grateful to him.
Did you say your name is Yoon Ma Ri?
His feelings aren't for you.
Don't be mistaken.
Please forgive...
Jung Won.
Overlook his foolish mistake,
and leave...
quietly.
Please smile with that face...
from now on.
Cherish...
and love yourself.
No one is more precious than yourself.
His warm comfort.
His kind consideration.
His happy heart.
Everything...
was for the owner of this face.
Welcome home.
I wanted to dress up for our dinner,
so I wore this dress without your permission.
It looks good on you,
but please don't make me surprised.
The princess sheds tears for losing someone she loves.
And the lavender blooms where her tears have dropped.
Lavender means, "Tell me."
His warm eyes are gazing at the face,
but whose face is it?
I know I can't, but my heart insists on asking.
Thank you for your cooperation. Bye.
There are only two left now.
(Purchaser list)
(Joo Hae Ra, Woo Ha Kyung)
I'm Oh Cheol Young, who called you earlier.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Let's go in.
It's been confirmed that you purchased the same dress.
Can we take a look at your dress?
Why do you need it?
It's an important clue to a missing person case.
Are you going to buy that one too?
You too?
Did Jung Won lend Ha Kyung's dress to that woman?
What's the matter?
Is Ms. Woo Ha Kyung inside?
Why are you...
looking for my wife?
Where is your wife?
Tell me.
(Lavender, Tell me.)
(Love in Sadness)
I'll find you however you look or wherever you hide.
So you better give up on running away from me.
Is that woman all you think about?
What does Ma Ri mean to you?
You're doing this because she looks like Ha Kyung.
What? That's not it.
Ms. Woo. You know me, don't you?
Why act like you don't, when you do?
Ma Ri. Ma Ri.
Honey.