♪I don't know
when I fell in love with you♪
♪Want to be spoiled by you
when the night falls♪
♪Your presence disturbed my life script♪
♪How can we know each other's heart♪
♪In this colorful world♪
♪I only want you
no matter when and where♪
♪Shift the center of gravity
Embrace the wind and rain♪
♪Stop at this moment
Even though it means we will start over♪
♪We'll still finish our song♪
♪I'll ask you one last time♪
♪How many years will you love me♪
♪Undetectable feelings spread♪
♪I'm missing you
Our memories keep me awake♪
♪I'll remind you one last time♪
♪When flowers bloom♪
♪We'll meet again♪
♪It's our vow to be fulfilled♪
=Night of Love With You=
=Episode 18=
Mr. Mu.
The monitoring data was destroyed
before the wedding.
Luo Qing!
Are you still going to deny it?
You're framing me!
If it's not for the sake of the seal,
why did you propose to marry Nanchen
all of a sudden
and then change your mind?
Do you have a better reason?
You wanted to steal the seal
of Mu's Group.
Aunt Mu
discovered your plan by chance,
so you killed her to keep her quiet!
Nanchen.
Don't be fooled by him.
Otherwise,
the board of Mu's Group
won't let it go easily.
You're a jinx!
Why do you freeze up at this time?
Let me take a look.
You don't believe me?
No one here believes you.
I do.
No matter how big Mu's business is,
you can't convict someone
without evidence.
Mr. Leng, you meddle in
the affairs of Mu's Group at this time,
does Leng's Group have anything
to do with the theft
of the personal seal?
Mr. Leng.
Do you want to be friends
with a murderer who killed Mrs. Mu?
There's no hard evidence yet.
Miss Song,
it's too early to say that.
Leng Yehan.
Are you sure you want to help her?
You don't have to threaten me now.
Your hands aren't clean
in the theft of the personal seal.
If it's said out loud,
it will do no one good.
Fire! Fire!
Go! Go!
Mr. Mu.
What should we do?
Catch Luo Qing first.
Yes.
I dare you!
Get out of the way.
You can't take her away!
Mr. Mu, in what position
are you talking to me?
She's my fiancée.
Mr. Mu, as the president of Mu's Group,
how could you not know
the definition of fiancée?
Luo Qing.
(Jiangbei Hospital)
How are you feeling now?
I don't know what happened to me.
It's Song Ruoyun.
The doctor will be here soon.
Your associative ability
is still as good as ever.
Did you mean what you said
at the wedding?
What?
You mean
I said I like you.
I just made up an excuse.
That would be the best.
Well,
don't be mad.
It was emergent.
I did need your help.
Why should I be mad?
Miss Luo, besides dizziness
and fatigue,
do you have any other symptoms?
No.
We need to run specific tests
to know the details.
Where is Doctor Liu?
Doctor Liu is on a business trip.
I'm filling in for him for these days.
Miss Luo.
Please come with me
to run the tests first.
Her family member can wait here.
Miss Luo.
Here are the clothes
for you to put on for inspection.
I'll wait for you outside.
You left it in the car earlier.
To be honest,
your wedding dress is ugly.
(I think I'm fine now.)
(What do you think)
(Song Ruoyun is up to?)
Doctor, it looked like
you were eating in a hurry.
It's okay.
Mr. Leng.
What's wrong?
I feel there's something wrong.
Miss Luo, besides dizziness
and fatigue,
do you have other symptoms?
Did you get the doctor here?
No.
I ran into him in the hallway.
Before I said anything,
he said he would come soon
after he got ready.
How did he know Luo Qing's name then?
Something happened to Luo Qing.
(Strategic M&A of Song's Group
Signing Ceremony and Press Conference)
Miss Luo.
I advise you not to waste your energy.
If you don't show yourself,
your brother
will die.
What a sucker.
I mean,
can't you try something else?
I'm tired.
Listen to yourself.
It's not about how many moves we have.
It's about if it will work.
Am I right, Miss Luo?
Come with me.
Someone is waiting for you.
Well,
I'm good, right?
Well done.
You got better.
I've been planning this for two days.
Sister.
I'm not dragging your feet
this time, am I?
Impressive.
(Where are they?)
(Take a look over there.)
Come on.
Let's get out of here first.
(Strategic M&A of Song's Group
Signing Ceremony and Press Conference)
Mr. Leng.
Song's Group can be merged
with Leng's Group.
Once you sign the contract,
Leng's Group will become
the most valued company in Jiangbei.
Just move your finger
and you can take over Mu's Group.
What's in it for you?
The benefit is
you'll be trapped here.
Leng Yehan.
Once you sign the contract,
your secret will be buried forever,
and you can
take revenge soon.
Luo Qing.
Luo Qing will die for sure.
Here is a piece of friendly advice.
Stick to the schedule
and go along with it.
This is your fate.
Stay out of Luo Qing's business.
Otherwise,
you will die for sure.
What's wrong, Mr. Leng?
Are you not feeling well?
You killed Mrs. Mu
and blamed it on me.
Yes.
So what?
Song Ruoyun.
Are you out of your mind?
You actually killed people
just to get Mu Nanchen?
Wrong.
I killed her
not for Nanchen.
because I wanted you dead.
It's a pity
that Leng Yehan saved you.
Well,
you can drop the idea
that Leng Yehan
will come to your rescue.
What happened to him?
He?
He's doing well.
Thanks to your recording,
I've been able to threaten him
to work for me.
It's always been you.
I was such a fool
trying to turn you against Nanchen.
What good would that do?
I should just kill you
and everything will be over.
In your dream!
Go ahead.
If you don't kill me,
I'm going to kill you.
Don't think I dare not!
Can the leading role
kill people?
What did you say?
I think
only supporting roles can kill people.
You took my life away from me.
Now you should give it back to me,
Luo Qing.
♪Get used to living alone♪
♪But can't stand the silence♪
♪Talk to myself sometimes♪
♪What can be done by thinking too much♪
♪Let tears wet the heart♪
♪Do you think of me sometimes♪
♪I feel lonely and disappointed
after passing over you♪
♪After a long time
I'm still sad from time to time♪
♪People stand in place at a loss♪
♪I was waiting but you didn't show up♪
♪I blame the past and you laugh it off♪
♪Once I embraced you with joy
and thought we would never part♪
♪The sun the moon and the stars
are not as affectionate as you♪
♪Time goes by little by little♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪I can't stop picturing you♪
♪I can't erase the past with you♪
♪I use up all my strength♪
♪Collapse silently every night♪
♪The stars fall quietly
There is no way to avoid it♪
♪Like a puzzle with no solution♪
♪Finally I realize
the furthest distance♪
♪Is your silhouette when you escape♪
♪You turn around and walk away♪
♪I can't quit missing you
I'm addicted to love♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)