♪I don't know
when I fell in love with you♪
♪Want to be spoiled by you
when the night falls♪
♪Your presence disturbed my life script♪
♪How can we know each other's heart♪
♪In this colorful world♪
♪I only want you
no matter when and where♪
♪Shift the center of gravity
Embrace the wind and rain♪
♪Stop at this moment
Even though it means we will start over♪
♪We'll still finish our song♪
♪I'll ask you one last time♪
♪How many years will you love me♪
♪Undetectable feelings spread♪
♪I'm missing you
Our memories keep me awake♪
♪I'll remind you one last time♪
♪When flowers bloom♪
♪We'll meet again♪
♪It's our vow to be fulfilled♪
=Night of Love With You=
=Episode 7=
I saved your life.
Saying thank-you
is not going to be enough.
Leng Yehan,
I'm hungry.
Let's go home.
♪Can't fake stubbornness♪
♪Set obstructions for you♪
♪A tug-of-war with loneliness♪
♪A disastrous failure♪
♪What's to be afraid of♪
♪I'm here with you♪
Leng Yehan.
Since you have chosen to act against me,
I won't be civil anymore.
The man who took you away,
he works for Song Ruoyun, right?
What happened between you two
that makes her want you dead?
She has to be jealous of me.
Women, huh?
She's the beloved daughter
of a rich family.
You are in
a huge debt.
No way
you can compete
with Song Ruoyun.
Well, there's no need
for you to be so specific.
I'm hungry.
Me, too, actually.
- You go make some food.
- I don't know how.
You've been taking care
of your little brother, haven't you?
How come
you don't know how to cook food?
You weren't born with a silver spoon.
How come you can't cook, either?
Who is it?
Luo Feng?
Sister,
are you in there?
Sister.
Sister,
I've found you at last.
You know?
After I jumped out of the window,
I passed out.
I woke up and wanted to go back
to rescue you,
but your car left.
I ran after you all the way,
Um…
There, there.
Sister,
I'm so glad that you're okay.
You know what?
They were so mean to me.
They didn't give me food
or drink.
They also abused me.
I went through hell.
So…
Can you cook?
Yes.
It's late.
Time for you to leave.
You…
I-It's…
Sister.
Let's go.
She won't leave.
I see.
So you're my brother-in-law?
Mind your language.
I'm his…
Maidservant.
This is the perfect explanation, right?
Yes.
Master.
I need to deal with some e-mails.
You
will go make my bed.
As for you.
Bye.
What the heck is going on?
Sister,
please say yes.
He asked you to leave.
There's nothing I can do.
But our house was destroyed.
And I'm not sure
if anybody is there expecting me.
Sister,
who did you mess with?
You little boy,
stop asking me questions.
I was only born
6 minutes 24 seconds later than you.
A lot could happen in 6 minutes.
Sister,
I know that you dropped out
of school and found jobs
to keep me in school.
But you're in real danger right now.
How can I let you face it on your own?
I thought
you were a leech brother.
It turns out
that your conscience remains.
Sister.
(Leng Yehan)
He's the president of Leng's Group.
If you two are married,
will he buy me a bicycle?
I always want a bicycle
of my own.
He wishes.
You wish as well.
Pack up and go.
What are you still doing here?
You have three seconds
to leave this room.
You,
two seconds.
Three.
Two.
(Mr. Leng,)
(this is maintenance day.)
(There will be a night of outage
in your community.)
Is that so?
Thank you for your timely notification.
Mr. Leng,
calm down, please.
During the outage,
the electronic lock won't open.
Sister,
how about
we sleep on the floor?
Um…
This…
This is but an accident.
You see, the bed is big enough
for all three of us.
Mr. Leng,
you won't mind, right?
You see,
we only need this little space.
This part
is for you.
I'll sleep in the middle.
That's fine.
Can't sleep?
I fell asleep several times,
but Luo Cheng always woke me up.
Change the lock tomorrow.
T-That's what I think, too.
The thing
between Song Ruoyun and you,
Mu Nanchen must be involved, right?
The first time we met,
Song Ruoyun was looking for you.
It was the contract-signing ceremony
of Song's Group and Mu's Group
on that day,
but Mu Nanchen wasn't there.
Later, we received the message
of his hospitalization.
Anyway,
she did something bad, and she didn't
want to get caught.
She set up a trap,
but it accidentally harmed Mu Nanchen.
You managed to escape
and found out her plan.
So she
wants you dead.
You've got very good
imagination.
If this is what Song Ruoyun
wants to achieve,
then she could be the end
of Song's Group.
Now you believe that she set me up?
Why wouldn't I?
But
as far as you know,
I'm a cunning woman.
You've got good memory.
Yes, you're cunning,
but you won't really harm anyone.
Plus,
it means you're smart.
It's better than being dumb.
If anyone says this about me,
I'll say,
he's got good eyes.
♪The lamp stretches my shadow♪
Luo Qing.
♪Try not to look back at you♪
♪Prevent our love from happening♪
Luo Qing.
♪My lovesickness jumps
Out of the corner of my eye♪
♪How can I stop clinging to you♪
♪Intertwining♪
♪Routine love♪
♪Good ending or bad ending♪
♪It's fine, I still walk towards you♪
Here's the breakfast.
Sister,
I remember
you enjoyed cooking before.
How come you don't cook anymore?
Such a great opportunity
should be given to young people.
But
I slept well last night.
What about you?
Me, too.
Mr. Leng.
Mr. Leng?
You didn't sleep well, did you?
But that's strange.
So something happened
during the outage?
Aren't you talkative?
Hand-copy
the quarterly financial statement.
(Mr. Song: Mr. Leng, Room 2406,
Jiangbei Hotel. Business meeting.)
Didn't Mr. Song reject him sternly?
A disgrace!
Don't ever call me again.
Oh, no.
Give me your cellphone.
I dropped it when they kidnapped me.
Where are you going?
Something bad will happen to Leng Yehan.
Come on.
He's a president.
What can possibly happen to him?
Miss Song.
Kevin.
Miss Luo,
how did you find this place?
I went to the company
and they told me about it.
Where's Leng Yehan?
Please, no.
I won't fall for your trick again.
Please don't disturb Mr. Leng.
You don't understand.
It wasn't Mr. Song
who wanted to see him.
He's in danger.
Where is he?
Room 2406.
I'll drive the car.
It seems you don't have a cellphone,
Miss Song.
I was only worried
that you wouldn't come
if it wasn't Daddy who contacted you.
Well,
I'm here
to talk business, of course.
It's a proposal that
you'll definitely benefit from.
Tell me about it.
Song's Group
will cooperate with Leng's Group.
But
on one condition.
Just let me have Luo Qing.
That's quite easy,
isn't it?
I do know where Luo Qing is,
and I can let you have her.
♪Get used to living alone♪
♪But can't stand the silence♪
♪Talk to myself sometimes♪
♪What can be done by thinking too much♪
♪Let tears wet the heart♪
♪Do you think of me sometimes♪
♪I feel lonely and disappointed
after passing over you♪
♪After a long time
I'm still sad from time to time♪
♪People stand in place at a loss♪
♪I was waiting but you didn't show up♪
♪I blame the past and you laugh it off♪
♪Once I embraced you with joy
and thought we would never part♪
♪The sun the moon and the stars
are not as affectionate as you♪
♪Time goes by little by little♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪I can't stop picturing you♪
♪I can't erase the past with you♪
♪I use up all my strength♪
♪Collapse silently every night♪
♪The stars fall quietly
There is no way to avoid it♪
♪Like a puzzle with no solution♪
♪Finally I realize
the furthest distance♪
♪Is your silhouette when you escape♪
♪You turn around and walk away♪
♪I can't quit missing you
I'm addicted to love♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)