♪I don't know
when I fell in love with you♪
♪Want to be spoiled by you
when the night falls♪
♪Your presence disturbed my life script♪
♪How can we know each other's heart♪
♪In this colorful world♪
♪I only want you
no matter when and where♪
♪Shift the center of gravity
Embrace the wind and rain♪
♪Stop at this moment
Even though it means we will start over♪
♪We'll still finish our song♪
♪I'll ask you one last time♪
♪How many years will you love me♪
♪Undetectable feelings spread♪
♪I'm missing you
Our memories keep me awake♪
♪I'll remind you one last time♪
♪When flowers bloom♪
♪We'll meet again♪
♪It's our vow to be fulfilled♪
=Night of Love With You=
=Episode 12=
♪My boy, I want to be
your round of moon♪
♪My boy, you're gonna take me
to your world♪
♪My boy, boy. My boy, boy♪
♪My boy, I'm gonna give you my dream♪
♪My boy, give me
all of your future euphoria♪
♪My boy, boy My boy, boy♪
What a coincidence!
I...
I was just passing by.
The kiss...
Thank you.
I've got something else to attend to.
I should go.
Me, too.
It doesn't feel right.
- Something must be wrong.
Oh, I see.
He must have been worried
that Mu Nanchen may realize
that his kiss could relieve
my palpitation
and then got closer to me.
By then,
I will expose his secret.
Right.
I bet it does.
Once Mu Nanchen knows who I really am,
my revenge plan will be disrupted.
But...
He could have refused to save me
and stopped Mu Nanchen
so that I would have a heart attack.
In this way,
I would have died with his secret.
Or...
Or I should have just killed her.
Why did I show up to help her?
- Too weird.
Mrs. Mu,
I was too obsessed.
My only intention was
to punish Luo Qing.
I didn't know
Nanchen would drink it by mistake.
Please trust me.
Mrs. Mu,
I'm so ashamed.
I used to
spoil my daughter.
Forget about it.
My son is
all right now.
I watched you grow up.
I know your nature.
Thank you, Mrs. Mu.
What...?
What about my engagement with Nanchen?
I don't like Luo Qing.
But last time Nanchen...
Nanchen...
He must have picked Luo Qing casually
because he couldn't
accept our engagement.
She isn't good enough
for Nanchen at all.
Xiaoyun,
you'd better not
do anything stupid again.
If I hadn't signed the contract
with him,
Leng Yehan wouldn't let you get away.
I'm not sure
about Luo Qing's relationship
with Leng Yehan.
If you keep making trouble,
Leng Yehan will not let you off anymore!
I...
Leng Yehan
can't be underestimated.
It took him only three years
to make his company
among the top three in Jiangbei.
Mrs. Mu,
the Leng family is gunning for ours.
I'm afraid
if we let him develop like this,
you and I will both have a tough time.
Our cooperation
will be the safest solution.
You make sense.
However,
I have to consider Nanchen's health.
He's allergic
to all the other women.
Only Luo Qing
can touch him.
Be patient.
Let me think about it.
(March 14, Monday)
Luo Qing,
I won't let you go.
Mr. Leng,
I hope we will work well together.
We will.
Mr. Leng,
what a coincidence!
It's been three months
since we last met, right?
I always wanted to thank you
for taking me in last time.
Is the car out there yours?
May I drive it?
No.
You're a petty man.
I thought
you could be my brother-in-law.
Can you drive?
I have a driving license.
But...
Are you and my sister
not on speaking terms?
Why didn't you contact each other
in the past three months?
I don't know.
Have you not professed your love yet?
What do you mean?
Come on,
why do you only appear to be smart?
Now that you adore my sister,
you have to let her know.
What do you mean
by "adore"?
It means
when she's away, you miss her.
When she's with someone else,
you feel upset.
When she's in danger,
you'll save her,
regardless of your own safety.
Most importantly,
your heart
will thump
at a moment.
I...
I'm not sure.
Well, you're in the middle of it.
No time like the present.
How about
I ask my sister out for you today?
What do you think?
Sister,
come over.
Why?
Just wait.
It's indeed the comic world.
However poor I am,
my home still looks nice.
Come on.
What are you doing?
You've got an important date today.
You should be dressed beautifully.
Not interested.
Mr. Leng
had the best restaurant arranged.
Leng Yehan?
Yeah.
He said
he had something important to tell you.
He...
He and I
have nothing to talk about, I'm afraid.
Two idiots.
Hurry.
It doesn't look good.
Mr. Leng,
you've tried on
all the ties
of different brands,
materials, and patterns.
Go buy some more.
All right.
Mr. Leng,
long time no see.
you have quite good taste.
Everything in your home
is quite expensive.
Miss Song, I don't remember
we have any history.
I'm not here for business.
Today,
I'm here to give you a mission.
I really hate Luo Qing.
But she's protected by Nanchen
and also taken care of by you.
I find it hard to get rid of her.
So, I need you to do something for me.
After that,
Nanchen will misunderstand Luo Qing.
And I
will naturally
be in a relationship with him.
Miss Song,
what makes you mistakenly believe
that I'm good-tempered?
Don't get angry, Mr. Leng.
Why don't you
hear this out first?
(How do you know)
(I'm the illegitimate child
of the Leng family?)
(Who else knows it?)
I planned to unlock her phone and check
whether Luo Qing started
to seduce Nanchen
a long time ago.
Unexpectedly,
I got a surprise.
Leng's Group appeared three years ago
and has been against Mu's Group.
It not only competes with Mu's Group,
but also wants to cooperate
with my father's company.
So, you're doing everything
just to take revenge.
Mr. Leng,
you can reject me,
but you can't reject
the chance of taking revenge.
Right?
If you threaten me,
you won't end up well.
I don't care about business.
I don't care about who you are, either.
I just want Nanchen to love me.
And you...
As long as you help me,
you can continue your revenge plan.
I won't interfere.
Mr. Leng,
what do you think?
No...
Wish us nice cooperation.
It doesn't feel right.
Why am I a little bit nervous?
What makes me nervous?
Miss Luo, someone left this for you.
What's this?
(Underground garage)
What's all this about?
Luo Cheng?
Luo Cheng.
Leng Yehan?
Miss Luo.
♪Get used to living alone♪
♪But can't stand the silence♪
♪Talk to myself sometimes♪
♪What can be done by thinking too much♪
♪Let tears wet the heart♪
♪Do you think of me sometimes♪
♪I feel lonely and disappointed
after passing over you♪
♪After a long time
I'm still sad from time to time♪
♪People stand in place at a loss♪
♪I was waiting but you didn't show up♪
♪I blame the past and you laugh it off♪
♪Once I embraced you with joy
and thought we would never part♪
♪The sun the moon and the stars
are not as affectionate as you♪
♪Time goes by little by little♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪I can't stop picturing you♪
♪I can't erase the past with you♪
♪I use up all my strength♪
♪Collapse silently every night♪
♪The stars fall quietly
There is no way to avoid it♪
♪Like a puzzle with no solution♪
♪Finally I realize
the furthest distance♪
♪Is your silhouette when you escape♪
♪You turn around and walk away♪
♪I can't quit missing you
I'm addicted to love♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)