♪I don't know
when I fell in love with you♪
♪Want to be spoiled by you
when the night falls♪
♪Your presence disturbed my life script♪
♪How can we know each other's heart♪
♪In this colorful world♪
♪I only want you
no matter when and where♪
♪Shift the center of gravity
Embrace the wind and rain♪
♪Stop at this moment
Even though it means we will start over♪
♪We'll still finish our song♪
♪I'll ask you one last time♪
♪How many years will you love me♪
♪Undetectable feelings spread♪
♪I'm missing you
Our memories keep me awake♪
♪I'll remind you one last time♪
♪When flowers bloom♪
♪We'll meet again♪
♪It's our vow to be fulfilled♪
=Night of Love With You=
=Episode 17=
(Mu Nanchen & Luo Qing)
Thank God.
You're finally here.
Is this the end?
I can finally get out of the story.
Look.
I was this close
to ending the story on my own.
You were this close
to being gone forever.
What?
I can only stay here for a while.
Remember this,
because you are in the wrong character,
if you die in the story,
you'll be gone forever.
It turns out
this wedding
is a farewell party for me.
But I don't want to be Luo Qing.
I'm here to be Song Ruoyun.
There was a mistake.
I've asked Comic Book Centre
to terminate the story.
However,
you've been forcing the plot to move,
which leads to
the incoherence of the story
and unreasonable relationships
of the characters.
The plot
might get more and more out of control.
Before the story officially ends,
you must be careful.
How long am I going to wait?
Time in the comic book world
is independent.
I don't know when it will stop.
Anyway,
don't create new problems.
Meaningless things
are not allowed to exist
in the world of comics.
Can't you just take me out of here?
I'm not
getting married.
Let's get out of here first.
Luo Qing.
Why?
Because...
I
got cancer.
Luo Qing.
Mu's Group has
specialized medical institutions.
We can cure you.
It's not what's important.
The important thing is
we're
actually
brother and sister.
We can't be together.
But
my parents couldn't
have any more children
after they had me.
Luo Qing.
What is your reason?
Because...
I...
The person I like is Leng Yehan!
When you like someone,
you will miss her
when she's not around.
You'll get upset
when she's with someone else.
When she is in danger,
you'll save her
without concern for yourself.
The most important thing is
your heart will pound
at some point.
Help me.
Come here first.
Mu Nanchen.
Marrying you will actually kill me.
Mr. Mu, you heard her.
Luo Qing and I only had a fight.
Put all your spending today
on Leng's Group's account.
Mr. Mu,
you're welcome.
There is no need to badger her,
otherwise,
it will do us no good.
Ma'am.
Luo Qing refused to marry Mr. Mu.
You should come out and take a look.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am!
Mr. Mu.
Something happened.
She is dead.
Who is dead?
Mrs. Mu is dead.
You were the last person Mrs. Mu met!
It wasn't me.
I haven't seen her at all.
No one
is allowed to leave right now.
Please sit down!
Miss Luo.
Please come with us.
(How does the romantic drama)
(has a crime scene all of a sudden?)
(What's going on?)
Mr. Leng.
Is there anything wrong?
Why haven't I seen Song Ruoyun?
It must be her!
She was the only one who met Mrs. Mu!
I didn't meet Mrs. Mu at all.
Besides,
I have no reason to kill her.
(With the leading male character
being here,)
(I'm still free to defend myself.)
(Is this not the plot
of the original comic book?)
You've been pushing the plot to move.
The plot might get more and more
out of control.
You have reasons.
Mrs. Mu said
she wouldn't allow Mr. Mu to marry you.
If you insist on getting married,
she would disinherit Mr. Mu.
In order to get our money,
of course you would
have a dispute with Mrs. Mu.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You're only talking about my motive,
but it's not enough.
Look at the ground.
There are obvious traces of dragging.
The blood on the corner of the table
might be the cause of the fatal injury.
But the strange thing is
this person
doesn't seem to want to cover it up.
No matter what,
it would take some time
to do these things.
There was no one in the room
when I came in,
so I left right away.
If you don't believe me,
you can check the security tape.
Between the time I came in and left,
it's impossible for me to do it.
Go get the surveillance video.
Yes.
Well,
who else would hurt Mrs. Mu?
Ruoyun.
Where is Ruoyun?
Mrs. Mu.
Miss Song.
Where are you going?
You have to think differently.
It's not about who would hurt Mrs. Mu.
It's about who would set me up.
Song Ruoyun's goal in life
is to marry Mu Nanchen.
She definitely doesn't want me
to become his wife.
You...
You're slinging mud at her!
Mr. Song, don't get ahead of yourself.
I wonder
why Miss Song
was in such a hurry to leave here.
What's going on?
Miss Song always dresses beautifully.
Why do you look a mess all of a sudden
as if you had a fight with someone?
It's Luo Qing.
She pushed Mrs. Mu.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Where is the evidence?
Because Mrs. Mu found something on you
that she shouldn't have.
What is it?
My personal seal.
I went to Aunt
to stop
your wedding.
But I happened to see
Luo Qing and Aunt fight.
They seemed to be snatching something.
I wanted to go in and help,
but Luo Qing pushed her to the ground.
I was too scared.
I was afraid Luo Qing would kill me
if she found me,
so I hid myself.
I didn't come in
until Luo Qing had left,
but Aunt
was not breathing
at that time.
This is just
one side of Miss Song's story.
How would Mr. Mu be convinced?
If what you said is true,
why didn't you call for help
in the yard
instead of running away?
Luo Qing.
It's not the time for you
to question my whereabouts.
You should explain to everyone.
Nanchen always
carries his seal with him.
He will have an allergy
when he gets close to women.
But you've been
staying with Nanchen these days.
Who else could it be but you?
Mr. Mu.
The monitoring data was destroyed
before the wedding.
Luo Qing!
Are you still going to deny it?
You're framing me!
If it's not for the sake of the seal,
why did you propose to marry Nanchen
all of a sudden
and then change your mind?
Do you have a better reason?
♪Get used to living alone♪
♪But can't stand the silence♪
♪Talk to myself sometimes♪
♪What can be done by thinking too much♪
♪Let tears wet the heart♪
♪Do you think of me sometimes♪
♪I feel lonely and disappointed
after passing over you♪
♪After a long time
I'm still sad from time to time♪
♪People stand in place at a loss♪
♪I was waiting but you didn't show up♪
♪I blame the past and you laugh it off♪
♪Once I embraced you with joy
and thought we would never part♪
♪The sun the moon and the stars
are not as affectionate as you♪
♪Time goes by little by little♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪I can't stop picturing you♪
♪I can't erase the past with you♪
♪I use up all my strength♪
♪Collapse silently every night♪
♪The stars fall quietly
There is no way to avoid it♪
♪Like a puzzle with no solution♪
♪Finally I realize
the furthest distance♪
♪Is your silhouette when you escape♪
♪You turn around and walk away♪
♪I can't quit missing you
I'm addicted to love♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)