[Debit Queen]
[Episode 14]
You have to think carefully.
Who in Linchun City
can still come up with
30,000 taels of silver?
If you miss this chance,
the only way to get cash again
is to sell your daughter.
You all!
Get lost!
Get out!
Let's go.
Get out.
Miss Tao, you're here.
Help yourself to whatever
you want to drink or eat.
But you have to pay.
Stingy Girl.
I'm finished.
What happened?
I have a vague feeling
something has gone wrong at home.
I never thought my father would be
at the point of selling off our family assets.
I'm so scared.
I don't want to marry someone I don't love
just to pay off debts.
How could that happen?
Your father loves you so much.
He wouldn't do that.
I'm about to lose everything.
Will you despise me?
How could you lose everything?
You still have me.
You still have this shop.
You still have Ping'er.
You still have the Bosslady.
I said before
that we sisters will share good times
and bad times together.
As long as I'm here,
you'll never be alone.
I don't want your pity.
My dear lady,
how could I dare to pity you?
You're a shareholder in this shop.
We said
we'd open more than ten,
even more than twenty branches.
If we work a little harder,
we can still live a good life.
But I'm not good at anything.
Who says you're not good at anything?
You have a good eye.
You invested in me!
Ling Se.
Thank you.
You're right.
I can live well
on my own too.
As long as I try a little harder in the future,
nothing can
knock me down.
Alright, stop crying.
That's not like you.
I'm fine now.
Why are you here?
I felt a bit upset.
What's wrong?
This afternoon,
Tao Meili came to see me
and said something had happened at her home.
I've heard a bit about that.
Although Mr. Tao
deserves it,
seeing Tao Meili like that,
I can't help but feel a bit sorry for her.
Do you want to help the Tao family?
What can I possibly do
to help the Tao family?
It's just that Tao Meili is my friend,
and I want to help her.
I understand.
Don't think too much about it.
Go home and rest early.
How can I have time to rest?
I need to go back and develop new products.
You have no idea
how hard it is to do business lately.
That popular
Linchun Tea Shop
even went out of business.
I guess it's because
they set their prices too high and made their stuff too awful,
so they got what they deserved.
Alright, you get busy then.
I'll head back to work on the new products.
[Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop]
Bring out your bosslady.
I want to see her, I'm her mother.
Tell her to come out!
Young Madam, she...
Se.
Did he send you here?
For the sake of your father
who gave you life and raised you,
please help your family.
Madam, please get up to speak.
Qian, don't bother with her.
Go out.
Yes.
How did I end up with such a hard life?
Everyone, please judge for yourselves.
We worked so hard
to raise our daughter,
even marrying her off to the richest Xu family
as a young madam.
Now that her family is in trouble,
this daughter
doesn't care at all.
How did I end up with such a miserable fate?
What exactly do you want?
500 taels.
Help your father pay off his debt.
If you don't have the money,
your husband does.
Don't even think about it.
Oh heavens,
everyone, please judge for yourselves!
Other people's daughters are as dear as a small cotton-padded jacket,
but our family
raised a thankless wretch!
She’s determined to force her father and me
to sleep on the streets and freeze to death.
Is this right?
You tell me, how can this be?
Go ahead and make a scene.
Even if you ruin my shop,
I won't give you any money.
Ling Se.
Darling, you're back.
How is it?
Did Ling Se agree to give you the money?
I knew
this tactic wouldn't work.
She's always been like this since she was a child.
No one could control her
except her mother.
Since you say that,
why don't you let her mother
handle her?
Mr. Xu.
You're here to mock me, aren't you?
What
are you planning to do now?
I've made a big joke of myself this time.
Are you satisfied?
Now that you've had your laugh, just leave.
I need to
find a place where I can
cry alone.
I'm not here to mock you.
I have a solution.
Are you interested?
What big idea
is Young Master Xu plotting this time?
Go ahead.
It doesn't matter to me anymore.
I have
the ready-made Jiuchongtian tea blend.
You can take it to fulfill your orders.
We'll count it as our families' joint venture.
From now on, we'll work together,
splitting the profits evenly.
What do you think?
After the way I treated your Xu family,
why would you help me?
Why?
To err is human.
Although
you’ve done things
that weren't in Xu family’s favor,
those things happened
because of me,
so I bear some responsibility too.
For so many years,
your Tao family has conducted business
with integrity.
I don't want to
see an honest merchant
fall like this.
Harmony brings wealth.
This is the foundation of prosperity.
Mr. Tao.
Do you
forgive me now?
Zilu.
Young Master.
Your methods are sharp,
and your vision is grand!
Young Master.
You are truly both sharp and grand!
Stop flattering me.
Get back to work.
Young Master.
I have to say something to you.
You've been doing things
you shouldn't do,
but you need to do the things that should be done.
What things?
The Young Madam.
Confessing your feelings. Did you forget?
But I don't know
how to create
that opportunity.
If you don't know, I do!
Young Master.
That's why I'm here to help you.
I've thought it over.
This is actually very simple.
You just need to cater to her likes.
Go and ask
Young Madam what she likes,
then buy that thing
and give it to her.
After that, just go with the flow,
and the matter will be settled, right?
If Young Madam is happy,
if Young Madam is delighted,
if she gives you a hug...
Right.
Taking the first step is the hardest
and most courageous.
Go!
Young Master!
Come on!
Ask her what she likes.
Do I need you to teach me?
Of course, I know.
Xu Zilu.
Where are you going?
I was just looking for you.
Have you prepared the item
for the auction?
I forgot about it.
I'll go prepare it now.
What's wrong?
What do you like?
I like money.
What else could I like?
No, I mean,
what kind of person do you like?
I like someone who reeks of money.
Stop talking to me.
I need to think carefully
about what I should prepare.
Don't disturb me.
Then I'll go.
Goodbye.
Are you two having a little spat?
Why do you look like
it just snowed in June?
I've got a bunch of things bothering me.
What's going on? Tell me.
I won’t talk about
family matters.
Let me tell you about business.
Xu Zilu wants me to join
that Linchun Chamber of Commerce.
I thought
having some backing would
bring me some benefits,
but now I have to attend
that charity auction.
I have to prepare
an item with collectible value.
And you know anything with collectible value
won't come cheap.
Why don't you just say
you don't want to
spend money?
You're so stingy.
Now that you're
a big boss.
can't you be a little more generous?
The better the item you prepare,
the more it will sell for, and the more you can donate.
It's a good deed.
That's easy for you to say.
Why don't you give me something?
I don't have anything.
How about
you learn a craft
and make something yourself?
That'll have to do.
You really have it easy,
talking while standing up.
Right.
Why did you come here?
Where is my flower cake?
Oh, my brain!
I finished it,
but I almost forgot to bring it.
Come, let me show you.
Let me see.
Gosh, Se.
Your skills are now truly
exceptional!
In a few days,
someone is celebrating
their 80th birthday at my place.
Can you make peach-shaped birthday buns?
That's easy.
And what about a figure of the the God of Longevity?
That's no problem either.
Then I'll place an order
with you.
But make sure the God of Longevity figure
is festive
and realistic.
The dough figure artist outside
is too expensive.
so this will definitely cost less.
I've got it!
I know what I'll donate for the charity auction.
I guarantee no one else will have it.
What is it?
Se.
Master Ling sent a letter for you.
He said if you don't gather
500 taels of silver by the end of today,
he'll throw out your mother's
memorial tablet.
How can someone be so wicked?
Is he even human?
He must have let the dogs eat his conscience.
He actually has the nerve to ask you for money.
Has he ever spent a penny on you
since you were little?
And now he's using his deceased wife
to threaten his own daughter.
He's truly shameless.
My Lord.
Will it work?
Don't worry.
This girl loves her mother more than anything.
She'll definitely come back.
As long as Ling Se brings the money
to get us through this tough time,
our Ling family will rise again.
Only by sticking with me
will you live in luxury.
Marrying Ling Se
into the Xu family
was the right choice back then.
It's my duty
to ease your burdens, My Lord.
So you know how to come back?
Master Ling, you went to great lengths
to get me back,
so drop the act.
We both know
I never wanted
to set foot in here again.
You...
My Lord.
The money is what's important.
Fine.
You've seen the letter.
Hand over the money quickly,
or
I'll throw out your mother's
memorial tablet.
I can give you the money,
but I have a condition.
Name it.
I must see
my mother's memorial tablet with my own eyes.
Otherwise, you won't get
a single coin from me.
Butler!
My Lord.
Go with her.
Yes.
There's no need.
I'll go myself.
Arms out.
Young Master.
This is ridiculous!
What's wrong?
I understand you want to express
your feelings to the Young Madam,
Then go and buy the yard.
but why are you making me go through all this trouble?
She said
she likes people who smell of money.
Exactly, Young Master,
so you should be wearing this!
Didn't I say
I would design the style first?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Shut up.
Come here.
Brother-in-law.
This is...
Brother-in-law,
you must go to my house!
My father...
My father wants to
throw out my sister's mother's memorial tablet.
My sister is storming over there!
[Xu's Fragrance Shop]
Young Master!
Young Master.
Should I go or not?
What are you doing?
I have only one purpose in coming here.
To take my mother's memorial tablet.
No need to trouble Master Ling
to throw it away.
Se.
How could you
do such an unfilial thing?
You want to take your mother's memorial tablet away,
But she is a member of the Ling family.
Aren't you worried about
what people will say?
A member of the Ling family?
When my mother was sick,
no one called a doctor for her.
She was left to die from neglect.
At that time, did any of you consider her
a member of the Ling family?
From childhood to adulthood,
I only asked you for one thing.
I asked you to let me study
at the academy like Ling Shuo
You said I wasn't worthy of spending your money.
Did you ever consider
that I was part of the Ling family then?
Mrs. Ling, when you sold me off
for five hundred taels,
did you remember
that I once called you "mother"?
Now that you're in trouble,
suddenly you remember I'm part of the Ling family?
How can there be people in this world
with such thick skin?
Ungrateful wretch!
Why bring up
the past?
Aren't you living well now?
I'm living well
because of my own efforts.
What does it have to do with you?
Everyone in the business world
knows.
Making money is due to oneself,
and losing money is also due to oneself.
But how is it that when Master Ling loses,
he expects others to bear it?
Let me tell you,
no matter how you
slander or threaten me,
I won't give you
a single coin.
You...
Give it to me!
Xu.
Are you going to meddle in our family's affairs now?
Ling Se is now part of the Xu family.
If you dare to touch her again,
you'll be opposing the Xu family.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
On my way here, I thought
if you feel
felt even a little remorse for me,
I'd consider the money
as never earned.
But now I see that I was too naive.
I'll take this slap
as my repayment to you.
From now on,
we are no longer father and daughter.
Rebellious!
You've really turned against me.
I've raised a heartless ingrate.
I'll beat you to death!
What are you doing?
Ling Se has already said that your relationship is severed.
If you dare to hit my wife again,
I'll make your life
even worse than it is now.
I advise you
to stop thinking of using your daughter anymore.
Think carefully about what to do next.
Let's go.
[Guanyin Temple]
This is the quietest place
in Linchun.
I think
your mother would like it here.
Thank you.
My mother would definitely like it.
[The Divine Tablet of My Wife Wang]
What kind of person
was your mother when she was alive?
My mother passed away early.
Actually,
I can't even remember
her face anymore.
But I remember
her smile, so beautiful,
so gentle.
Xu Zilu, you know what?
My mother
was very skillful.
The pastries she made
were exquisite and delicious.
I probably
inherited my skills from her.
She
was the gentlest,
purest,
and also the most foolish person
in the world.
She believed that man's lies
and married into Linchun City all by herself.
She even gave him all her dowry
to start his business.
My mother spent her whole life
living for others.
Even on her deathbed,
she was telling me
that she couldn't watch me grow up,
couldn't protect me anymore.
She said that from now on,
I'd have to walk my path alone.
So
that's why
you work so hard to make money?
Mother.
Ling Se is living well now.
I promise,
as long as I'm here,
I won't let anyone
bully her.
I won't let her suffer anymore.
You can rest assured.
Still touched?
Who's touched?
I'm just
heartbroken.
Heartbroken over those five hundred taels of silver.
It was so hard to earn.
Actually,
if you take the seal to the money exchange,
you can get the silver notes back.
Really?
Xu Zilu.
You're really my lucky star!
I'm going to worship you every day.
By the way,
Ling Shuo tore up
one of my 100 tael notes before.
Can I get that back too?
That means I have 600 taels now.
I'm rich!
You money-grubber!
Young Master.
How is it?
I've thought about it.
This thing
should be sewn onto the clothes after all.
What do you think?
Am I smart or what?
Take it apart.
We don't need it anymore.
Young Master.
Aren't you going to express your feelings to Young Madam?
The timing
isn't right now.
Let's just forget it.
It’s okay, Young Master.
As long as your intentions are there,
the Young Madam
will definitely feel it herself.
Isn't there an old saying?
"A determined suitor wins the lady."
Keep at it.
Go back.
What’s going on?
Did you go out stealing last night?
Of course not.
I put a lot of effort
into preparing
this valuable auction item.
I hope
today’s auction ends quickly.
I’m really exhausted.
What is it?
I can’t show you now. It’s a secret.
You’ll find out soon enough.
Let's go.
[Linchun Charity Sale]
Mr. Xu,
big spender, huh?
What about you, Madam?
It's the thought that counts,
right?
Of course.
I made this
God of Wealth figure
by hand.
Which business
wouldn’t want the God of Wealth
to stay in their home?
Am I right?
Yes.
Let me see.
Young Master.
This God of Wealth does look a lot like you.
It really does.
Let me see.
I’ll take it.
Can this be fixed?
It’s fine.
Manager.
When you hand it over later,
be sure to support
its head like this.
Maybe the head is too big and heavy.
Why don’t the two of you rest in the backyard for now?
I’ll come and get you
when the auction starts.
-Young Master, I’m leaving.
-Thank you.
How did I do?
Isn’t it both meaningful
and valuable?
The best part is it didn’t cost anything.
I made it myself.
It really is meaningful.
Brother Xu.
Your wife is here too?
Se.
I haven’t had a chance to congratulate you
on joining the Chamber of Commerce.
Thank you, Mrs. Qiu.
Once
the auction is over,
let’s have a good drink together.
Sure.
This sago drink is really good.
I’ll reserve some.
I’ll come get it from you later.
See you!
Miss Ling.
Mr. Wu?
You’re here for the auction too?
I’ve visited your shop several times,
but you weren’t there.
I was quite disappointed.
I’ve had some personal matters recently.
But don’t worry,
I’ll be around for the next few days.
You should come by.
And who might you be, sir?
What business do you have with my wife?
So he’s really your husband?
A girl as interesting as you
is already married?
What a pity.
Sir,
that’s not
a very appropriate thing to say.
Now that you know I’m her husband,
I suggest you stop bothering my wife.
How can you call it bothering?
We’re just friends,
aren’t we?
I need to introduce my wife
to other friends.
We don’t have time
to continue this conversation with you.
Aren’t you curious
about who I am, Mr. Xu?
I’m Wu Qi, Imperial Merchant of Furong City.
I've long heard of your great reputation, Mr. Xu.
Mr. Wu, you're actually an Imperial Merchant?
Miss Ling,
do you really want to chat
with those old men and women?
Why not
continue our conversation instead?
Everyone,
the auction is about to begin.
Please take your seats.
See you in a bit.
This way, please.
Everyone,
Let's go.
This item up for auction
is a jade flute, a royal tribute
provided by Wu Qi,
the young master of the Wu family from Furong City.
The starting bid
is 100 taels.
Who is this Wu Qi?
He actually has
a royal tribute item!
I’ve heard
he’s an Imperial Merchant from Furong City.
He became an Imperial Merchant
at just 24 years old.
That’s impressive.
I should get to know him.
150 taels.
200 taels.
250 taels.
Stop,
that’s high enough.
250 taels, going once.
Forget it.
I'm out.
250 taels, going twice.
Sold!
Congratulations to Mr. Li.
Congratulations!
This...
This is such a valuable item,
It costs so much.
You...
Next up
is a hand-crafted
dough figurine provided by
Ms. Ling Se, the wife of Mr. Xu from the Xu family.
Starting bid...
You're auctioning off this little thing?
20 coins.
20 coins. for one.
Ten taels?
Interesting.
Miss Ling, you have quite the skill.
Thank you, Mr. Wu.
This man doesn't lack money, does he?
50 taels.
Xu Zilu.
It's from our family.
Why are you bidding?
80 taels.
100 taels.
150 taels.
300 taels!
500 taels.
Are these two crazy?
800 taels.
1,000 taels.
1,500 taels.
Stop bidding.
This little dough figurine
is only worth two copper coins.
If you really want one,
I can make you another.
I only want this one.
I can make an identical one for you.
Besides,
its head is already broken.
It's not good.
Really?
Forget this one.
Okay.
Wu Qi.
1,000 taels, going once.
Mr. Wu wants it.
Is it possible we’re missing something?
Indeed.
Se
seems to have quite the charm.
Wu Qi, 1,000 taels, going twice.
Sold!
Congratulations to Mr. Wu.
Congratulations.
One thousand taels just for a girl's smile.
Mr. Wu really knows how to spend!
Why did Mr. Xu
back down at the last minute?
Maybe you didn’t like
the figurine that much after all.
Mr. Wu, you're from out of town.
I’m simply letting you have it.
If I truly wanted it,
I’m afraid you couldn’t afford to outbid me.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
But the more I look at this figurine,
the more I like it.
The more I look at it,
the more it seems
to resemble me.
Don’t you think, Ling Se?
Really? What a coincidence.
Mr. Wu, you sure are full of yourself.
Keep the figurine then.
There won't be another one like it.
Unlike me.
If I want one,
my wife can make it for me anytime.
Ling Se and I are friends.
I’m sure if I asked,
she would make one for me as well.
It’s getting late.
I’ll take my leave.
Ling Se.
Let’s meet again another time.
See you.
Let’s go.
Wu Qi
is definitely not a good guy.
Stay away from him.
Men's
inexplicable competitive streak
is really childish.
Ling Se.
You didn’t touch
your food tonight.
How about
I go with you to get something to eat?
I’m not eating anymore. I’m going to sleep.
I'm so sleepy.
Well…
I have something to ask.
What is it?
You have to make one for me too.
Make what?
You didn’t let me bid on it.
You said you’d make another one for me.
The dough figurine, right?
Alright, if you want one so badly,
I’ll make you one when I have time.
Well,
I want it to be even better.
Okay, an even better one.
I’m so tired I can barely keep my eyes open.
I'm going to bed.
Don't forget.
Okay.
Young Master.
Which place will you stay at when you go to the mountains
the day after tomorrow to look at the timber,
Songhe Pavilion or Tangquan Inn?
Neither. I’ll return to the mansion.
You’re surely coming back
to accompany the Young Madam, right?
To accompany you.
Mr. Wu?
Miss Ling.
I happened to pass by today
and remembered that you mentioned
wanting to experiment with some new foods.
I wonder
if I might have the honor
of trying them today?
There is indeed that honor.
Mr. Wu, please have a seat.
Ping'er.
Bring out the new products.
Okay.
Mr. Wu.
This is a pastry I made
by reducing the moisture
from one of our milk teas,
using the method you mentioned.
Please try it.
Does it contain taro paste?
I only put a little bit in.
You can taste it?
Mr. Wu, you really have a refined palate.
Not really.
It’s just that
I really like seasonal foods.
If you have time,
we could go to the suburbs together
to look for local seasonal ingredients.
With your innovative ideas,
I’m sure you can develop
unique local specialties.
Sounds good.
When are you free?
I happen
to want to go
and gather some inspiration.
Alright.
Next time, do come and taste more of the new products.
Okay,
and remember
to make plans
to visit the suburbs with me next time.
Alright, we’ll meet then.
Mr. Wu, you seem very leisurely.
Why are you
visiting
my wife's shop?
I'm not like you, Young Master Xu,
who is always busy with your own affairs.
I really enjoy
the desserts in Ms. Ling's shop.
Once I taste them, I can’t forget them,
so I end up coming often.
I have other matters today, so I’ll leave first.
Ms. Ling,
don’t forget our appointment.
It seems
that Mr. Wu visits frequently.
Yes.
Even customers from Furong City
really enjoy the food I make.
My skills are really
top-notch.
Isn’t opening a branch store
just around the corner?
By the way,
what about my dough figurine?
You can't get over this, right?
I’ve been so busy recently.
When would I have the time to make it for you?
But you promised me.
I’ll make it when I have time.
Then
I want to drink milk tea.
The one you made for me last time,
which is called "Wish You Prosperity."
Did you find it good?
Should I add it
to the menu?
How did you make that ingredient?
I didn’t write it down at the time.
Let me think about
how I made that ingredient.
Wish You Prosperity…
What’s going on here?
My Lord.
Something’s gone wrong in Linchun.
Speak.
Tao Ziran bribed
Eunuch Zhou from Prince Xian's Mansion
getting Eunuch Zhou to transfer the order
to himself.
However, there was a mistake,
and Prince Xian found something wrong with the fragrance.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
My Lord. Don't worry.
The issue was resolved
by a twist of fate.
Xu Zilu stepped in
to save Tao Ziran,
And Prince Xian
didn’t pursue the matter further.
He even personally
sent the goods back to Furong City.
By the way,
My Lord.
Xu Zilu has successfully been appointed as the Imperial Merchant.
That was expected.
This matter won’t affect
you, will it?
It’s fine.
Prince Xian is benevolent
and generally
doesn’t hold grudges.
If he were that type,
Tao Ziran
would have lost his head by now.
By the way, My Lord,
we just received news from Linchun.
The head
of the Wu family from Lingnan, Wu Qi,
is currently in Linchun.
It looks like a trip back to Linchun is needed.
Mr. Qi has written
saying he is willing to take over the last batch of goods.
This will
help clear the accounts
and prevent Zilu from noticing anything.
Prepare the carriage.
Yes, My Lord.
This is freshly dried persimmon cake.
The best time to eat it is just after it’s dried.
Paired with
a warm drink,
it’s the best snack
for this season..
From what you’re saying,
it sounds even more delicious.
Let me try it.
Delicious.
You’re getting
more and more diligent.
Even checking the timber
in the mountains personally.
I’m quite pleased.
If I’m not diligent, who will pay you?
That’s true.
But after winter,
the scent of pine will be gone.
We need to prepare early
to ensure a smooth process
for making fragrance next spring.
I’m speaking.
Well. Look at that couple
over there.
Really. I wish you could
be as sweet to the Young Madam
as they are.
This is quite tasty.
Quite good.
Young Madam?
Who are you lying to?
Well Young Master.
Young... Young Madam.
Look.
I won't.
Look, it's right ahead.
Just ahead. Look.