[Debit Queen]
[Episode 23]
Eunuch,
don't just listen to his side of the story.
If this agreement were truly
written by my wife and me,
why would he possess it?
It was Ling Se who dropped it accidentally
when she came to the store.
And it's all clearly written
on the paper.
You still want to deny it?
You went to all that trouble to get close to us,
and this was your true purpose all along.
Wu Qi, you are so vicious.
Business is business.
I really
wanted to cooperate with you before.
However, I've discovered your crimes.
As an honest and upright
citizen of the Qing State,
I really can't be complicit
in any wrongdoing with you.
You?
Guards!
Take them down!
Wait!
Regarding the agreement,
my wife knew nothing about it
from start to finish.
It was all my doing.
Please let my wife go.
Xu Zilu.
Both of your names are written
on the agreement.
Of course, both of you are guilty!
Well...
Her Majesty has arrived!
Aunt?
What's all this commotion? What's going on?
Your Majesty,
today is the selection day for the Imperial Merchant of line incense.
Someone has reported
that Xu Zilu, a perfume materials merchant from Linchun City,
and his wife
pretended to be a couple
in order to qualify as the Imperial Merchant.
I was about to take them down
and interrogate them.
This is their
fake couple agreement.
If they are truly a fake couple,
how should we deal with them?
If this agreement is true,
Xu's Shop from Linchun City
will be disqualified as the Imperial Commercial Firm.
Both of them
also face severe punishment.
Mr. Xu, right?
I've used your incense.
I like it very much.
I can show you mercy today
and allow you to maintain your qualification as an Imperial Merchant.
However,
you two must divorce.
I can also grant each of you
a good marriage, respectively.
What do you think?
Your Majesty, your grace is boundless.
I... am willing to
relinquish the qualification as an Imperial Merchant.
I would rather go bankrupt
and be imprisoned
than lose Ling Se.
I will marry no other woman
in my life but her.
Madam Xu,
if the agreement is true,
you two will have committed the crime of deceiving the king.
If you divorce,
I can guarantee your safety.
I'll only marry
Xu Zilu in my lifetime.
Through life and death,
we'll share weal and woe together.
you'll share weal and woe together. Good.
Even when true couples face a great disaster,
they often go their separate ways.
If they're just a fake couple
bound by a contract,
how can they disregard their lives
during a time of crisis?
The agreement may be fake,
but true love can't be faked.
All of you, rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Come on.
What about our line incense?
It will begin
in one hour.
Even if we went back to get it, it would be too late.
Let them use the swift horse
from the palace to get it.
Yes.
Your Highness.
How is it?
Xu Zilu's incense
has been selected.
How could this happen?
Did Wu Qi
not do as I said?
Wu Qi did
do as you ordered
and submitted the agreement
you gave him.
But unexpectedly,
it was stopped by
the sudden appearance of the Empress.
The Empress?
Yes.
Her Majesty saved
Xu Zilu and Ling Se
and lent him a swift horse
from the palace
to get new incense.
That's why
Xu Zilu could make it in time.
Well, that's... surprising.
Since when did they have
such a powerful backer?
Ping'er...
Your Highness,
we also have news from Beiyun.
They said that they need a batch of goods urgently.
Got it.
Looks like we really can't
let Xu Zilu live anymore.
I have to find a better reason
to take care of him.
I was so scared just now.
You weren't delayed, right?
No.
How is our incense?
If it weren't for Her Majesty,
he wouldn't have the chance.
Wu Qi!
You scumbag! Bastard!
-Don’t go! I’ll kill you!
-Ling Se.
Calm down.
I think it was Prince Xian
who asked him to do it.
You mean he's siding with Prince Xian?
He has Prince Xian to support him.
We can't afford to mess with him.
I don't care whom he's siding with.
Anyway, I can't stand the fact
that he betrayed us.
What do you want to do?
I dare not provoke
Prince Xian,
but I can certainly deal with Wu Qi.
How would you like to do it? I'm with you in this.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Are you sure we need to paste that much?
Yes.
Turn around. Turn around.
One, two, three, go.
What about the cart?
Push it away.
You do it.
You...
Wait for me.
Arrogant bastard.
And then?
And then,
Her Majesty appeared out of nowhere
and helped us out.
Her Majesty even lent us a horse
so that we could come back to get the incense in time.
Her Majesty?
You all don't know that, do you?
It's all thanks to Ping'er.
Wang Zhujue,
let me tell you.
Ping'er's aunt is the Empress.
Then, am I not good enough for her?
Indeed.
I didn't expect Mr. Wu
to be such a cowardly
and vain person.
Don't worry, guys.
I've already gotten back at him about this.
Ling Se,
let's not mess with him anymore.
After all, he has the support of Prince Xian.
I know.
The most important thing now
is the sacrificial ceremony.
It's the most significant event
since our shop became the Imperial Commercial Firm.
We can't afford to make any mistakes.
Young Master, you've worked all night in the incense shop.
How about I make some ginseng soup for you
when I get back?
This...
Who did this?
Did you see who did this?
Did you see
who did this?
Xu Zilu.
Ling Se.
You're really something.
[Big Liar]
[Despicable; Shameless; Nasty]
What happened
to make you so angry?
The dishes are getting cold.
I was screwed by Ling Se and Xu Zilu.
What...
did they do to you?
They... actually
dumped a bunch of garbage in front of my house.
I didn't
see that coming.
This must be Ling Se's idea.
As the saying goes, women are the most vicious.
I don't know where they
got that garbage.
The servants have been
cleaning until now,
but it still stinks.
They won't last long.
Your Highness,
do you have any plans?
How could I let my own men
suffer?
Don't worry.
I have my own plans.
Thank you, Your Highness.
If you need anything
in the future, Your Highness,
just give the order.
If I can get that from you,
it's worth all the effort I have invested in you.
Let's eat.
Enjoy yourselves.
Come on. You're almost there.
Officers, officers.
What...
can I do for you?
I've been ordered to shut down this place.
Why?
I don't know either.
Go!
Go find Se.
I'll stay here and watch this place.
Go!
Something bad happened!
Just now, a group of soldiers
rushed into the Joy Game Shop,
saying that we were deceiving customers for money
under the pretense of games
and wanted to shut down our shop!
We opened the shop
with an official license.
How could they do that?
I guess this was Prince Xian's way
of taking revenge for Wu Qi.
Darn Wu Qi.
Seriously?
He even had my shop shut down.
He even has a stake
in my shop.
It's all your fault.
You didn't even try to stop me yesterday.
I was impulsive.
Anyway, let's just endure it for now.
Let it be, as the Joy Game Shop is already closed.
We can't afford to mess with Prince Xian.
You'd better behave
and don't cause any more trouble these days.
Xu Zilu,
what's wrong with you?
Why are you so cautious and timid
when you're here?
And Prince Xian.
Isn't he just a prince?
Why does he always meddle in others' business?
Exactly.
He first separated
Wang Zhujue and Ping'er.
Now he has my shop closed.
Now, we're sworn enemies.
Sworn enemies.
We can't let that old man off easily.
Then,
what should we do?
Since Prince Xian has made his move,
we'll be targeted
whether we act or not.
The only way we can protect ourselves
is
to fight back.
Fight back.
Then, how do we fight back?
To...
throw trash at the gate of Prince Xian's mansion.
Xu Zilu!
Meili,
ignore him.
Let's go to Wang Zhujue
to discuss it.
Let's go.
I don't believe that Prince Xian
can have everything his way.
Exactly.
I'd give up my life
for Ping'er.
There's no way I'll let her
marry that old bastard!
Right?
Yes.
For Wang,
for our sister,
and for our shop.
Isn't he just a prince?
We're not afraid of him.
Right, Se.
Prince Xian has really gone too far.
Se, let me help too.
Okay!
Wang!
Ping'er?
Good, you're all here.
Ping'er.
Why are you out?
Prince Xian has come again to force me to marry him.
My grandfather really couldn't bear it,
so he let me leave.
Your Lordship.
Your Lordship,
Prince Xian has sent a message
saying that he and Her Grace
have set a date for their marriage:
the eighth day of next month.
Yes.
My girl,
listen to me.
Go now.
Grandpa,
what did you say?
Go find
that rascal.
Go out of the city together
and leave here.
Find a place
where no one can find you,
and never come back!
I can't leave you here alone.
Don't worry about me.
My girl,
you are my beloved granddaughter, whom I raised.
I can't bear to see you
cry every day.
If you have made up your mind,
leave now.
Then...
What about Prince Xian?
Kid,
don't worry.
Even if the sky were to fall,
Grandpa is here for you.
Grandpa.
My granddaughter.
Ping'er,
since you're out,
how about this?
You go with Wang Zhujue first.
Go back to Linchun.
Leave Prince Xian to us.
Yes.
Se,
calm down.
Let me finish.
I just got some news.
For years, Prince Xian
has been making illegal deals
with Beiyun State.
If we can
find evidence of Prince Xian's smuggling activities,
we can really
bring him down.
And I don't have to hide anymore.
Smuggling? Really?
That's a serious offense that could cost your life.
It's true.
Ling Se.
Stop leading everyone into trouble.
I'm not.
Didn't you hear what Ping'er said?
Prince Xian has been smuggling.
He has committed a crime.
As long as we can find evidence against him,
Ping'er and Wang Zhujue
will be free,
and my shop can be reopened.
It's not as simple
as you think.
Do you know
what he has been smuggling?
What?
Fire lances.
What are those?
A special firearm from Qing state.
Beiyun and Qing
are now at war.
The fire lances are the most important
military equipment of our state.
Prince Xian is, indeed, an old bastard.
Isn't smuggling guns
a form of indirectly
killing our fellow citizens?
Xu Zilu,
how did you come to
know this?
Prince Xian
was using
my Third Uncle's caravan to smuggle.
After my uncle found out about it,
he was killed by Prince Xian.
It was Prince Xian who killed him.
How could you hide such a big thing
from me?
Because I wanted to keep you out of danger.
Then how can you
face danger alone?
Xu Zilu, we've talked about it.
Come what may,
we'll work together and share weal and woe.
Are you trying to leave me out of this again?
Enough.
It's not merely
a personal grudge.
The most important thing now
is to find evidence
of Prince Xian smuggling and colluding with the enemy.
-Yes.
It's fine
if we know nothing about this.
Now that we know about it,
we must find a way to stop him.
We mustn't be afraid of
Prince Xian.
That's right.
He's just a prince.
He's nothing!
Exactly.
If we allow him
to continue smuggling munitions,
won't
all our fellow citizens suffer?
Yes!
Xu Zilu,
let us do this with you.
I promise.
I'll listen to you.
Looks like
I can't talk you out of it.
Okay.
We can take action about it,
but we must follow the plan.
I've just
got some news too.
Beiyun is in a state of emergency.
It's very likely
that they'll have another deal soon.
So, our target
this time
[Missing Person]
is him.
The foreman of the Third Master's Chamber of Commerce.
He is fat
and speaks with a strong accent.
But we've investigated him.
He is actually
a mole planted around the Third Master
by Prince Xian.
Ever since the Third Master
was killed by Prince Xian,
he has also disappeared without a trace.
So, we believe
that as long as we can find him
and keep an eye on him,
we will find evidence
of Prince Xian smuggling.
Fat
and speaks with a strong accent.
But Furong City is so big.
Where can we find him?
I'm good at finding people.
How about this?
Tomorrow,
we'll look for him in four areas:
the eastern, western, southern, and northern parts of the city.
See if
he has passed by some places.
Be careful, everyone.
Report back to me if you learn anything.
Ling Se.
Take it.
Especially you.
You're nagging like an old man.
I know.
I will protect myself.
Okay.
Let me take another look.
Well.
Your Highness,
we have received news from Beiyun.
They hope that we can
deliver the goods as soon as possible.
Otherwise,
they will withdraw
the 30,000 elite soldiers that were sent to reinforce us.
Give it to them.
I'll deal with them
once I've achieved my goals.
Yes.
Have the arrangements for Xu Zilu
been made?
I've given the potassium nitrate to Foreman Wang
and asked him to find a chance
to add it to the line incense for the sacrificial ceremony.
Good.
Let's see how he can fight against me now.
Why do they get to
go out to search for the foreman
while we're stuck here
overseeing the incense-making?
After all, my brother-in-law is an Imperial Merchant.
The sacrificial ceremony is coming.
If anything goes wrong
with the incense,
we'll all face execution.
So,
our mission
is more important.
It better be.
Good morning.
You've seen Ping'er now.
Look how happy you are.
Of course.
If you're going to keep grinning like that,
you might as well move out and stay at an inn.
I've found a lead.
How can you treat a hero like this?
What lead?
Greetings, Master and Madam.
Yesterday, inspired
by your prank on Xu Zilu,
I had the beggars search for that man.
I didn't expect it to be this effective.
Within a day,
they found
the whereabouts of the foreman.
What are we waiting for?
Hurry up. Let's go find him.
Let's go.
Why does this road
seem more and more familiar?
That is the place.
[Xu's Incense Shop]
Isn't this your incense shop?
Are you sure this is the right place?
One of my men
spotted him nearby
just moments ago.
Grind it carefully.
I'll take over when I'm back.
Make way.
Well, Miss Tao,
would you mind watching over this place for me?
I... I need to use the restroom.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Fine, I could use some exercise anyway.
I'm sorry.
Go back to work.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. Just read your book.
What is this ingredient?
Why don't I remember that we need to use this
to make incense?
I'm sorry.
No.
He's that foreman!
Go after him!
I-I-It's him.
Let's go.
That foreman
put something in your incense!
Yes!
You stay here and watch.
We'll go after him.
You've done your job.
I've completed the task
that His Highness ordered.
Well done.
Tomorrow's sacrificial ceremony
will mark the end for Xu Zilu and the others.
His Highness said
that tomorrow's transaction with Beiyun at the dilapidated temple
on the eastern side of the city
must succeed; failure is not an option.
Let His Highness rest assured.
I will do my utmost
to carry out his orders.
Tao Meili,
you are really amazing.
We owe our thanks to Miss Tao
for discovering the tainted incense.
If
that incense had been used during the ceremony,
the consequences would have been catastrophic.
Of course.
Let's see
who dares to underestimate me in the future.
Yes.
Actually,
it's mostly my fault.
My ill-timed bathroom break
almost led to disaster.
But...
thanks to the leadership of
the beautiful, gorgeous, and fairy-like
Miss Tao,
we were able to avert this disaster.
She's simply
the modern female version of Di Renjie.
Awesome.
Tomorrow, the foreman
will conduct a trade with Beiyun
at the dilapidated temple on the eastern side of the city.
If we can catch them
and get
Prince Xian's secret letter,
we might be able to expose
his scheme to the world.
Let's
cheer for tomorrow's plans.
Okay.
For Xu's Shop!
For Ping'er!
For the people!
For the masses!
For Qing!
Let's do it!
Eunuch,
the line incense for the sacrificial ceremony
is all here.
Okay.
I'll take it with me.
Take care, Eunuch.
Let's go and get that foreman.
Let's prepare.
Young Master.
Why aren't they here yet?
Be patient.
The information should be correct.
They're coming.
This is the place.
Only three people?
That's easy.
Later, follow my instructions.
I'll distract them first,
and then, you circle behind and surround them.
No, that's too risky.
I've got a plan for it.
Be careful.
-Let’s go.
-Okay.
Here.
How long do we have to wait?
Yeah.
When will they come?
One.
Two.
Three.
They all
look fierce.
They definitely can't be someone good.
Ling Shuo.
Did you see them?
Yes. Yes.
Which one is in charge?
Come out!
I am.
May I help you, miss?
I planted these trees.
I made this road.
If you want to use this road,
you must pay a toll.
Toll?
We always take this route.
Why is there a toll now?
Because you've met
me!
My eyes!
Don't move!
Fuding, keep an eye on them.
Okay!
I'll kill anyone who moves!
How is it, Xu Zilu?
We've caught them.
Should we just wait for
the envoys from Beiyun State to come?
Why do I have a feeling this was too easy?
Don't you find it strange too?
No.
It's easy because
I have chili pepper.
Fuding, keep an eye on them!
Stop!
Don't get up!
What is this?
Oh no.
It's a signal bomb!
Stop!
Let's go!
Go!
Let's go after them!
Stop!
Why do you flee at the sight of me?
Why are you chasing me?
Why are you running?
You're chasing me, leaving me no choice but to run!
Stop running!
Stop chasing me!
The goods are fine.
Boss Wu,
be careful.
Xu Zilu and the others
won't find me out, right?
Don't worry.
His Highness has a brilliant plan.
They are
still chasing Foreman Wang.
What a feint!
His Highness is so wise.
But how did His Highness find out
Xu Zilu's plan?
That foreman
put something in your incense.
Yes!
You stay here and watch.
We'll go after them.
You have done your job.
Idiot.
See the men you used.
He didn't even know he was being followed.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
I'll get rid of Foreman Wang now.
Wait.
Let them go after him first.
They will not discover that I have already replaced the goods
until they catch up with him.
Let's take our time
to enjoy the good show.
Your Highness is wise.
Xu Zilu,
do you really think
you're one step ahead of me?
So childish.
Where do you think you can run?
Run if you dare!
I have no grudge against you.
You... You chased me and detained my workers.
I'm going to report this to the police!
You still dare to report it?
Help me up!
When we find the secret letter,
we'll send you to the police!
Hand over the secret letter.
Search me.
I don't have it.
Go!
Hurry up!
Get down!
How is it?
I've asked.
None of them are from Beiyun.
Oh no.
You're Xu Zilu?
Yes.
What's the matter?
Arrest him!
Wait.
You've got the wrong person.
They are the ones you should arrest.
The Ministry of Justice has issued an order.
There is something wrong with the incense
used in the sacrificial ceremony.
So we need to arrest Xu Zilu
and bring him back for interrogation.
It must be a misunderstanding.
Have you made a mistake?
No matter what the truth is,
Xu Zilu, the man in charge,
must be put into prison for interrogation.
No.
You can't arrest him.
This is not up to you.
Let go of him!
Fine.
I'll go back with you.
Zilu.
It's okay.
Wait for me.
I'll find a way.
You must protect yourself.
Got it?
Take him away.
Yes.
Let's go.
Don't touch her!
Go!
Hurry up!
Wang.
Hurry back and take Ping'er away.
Go as far away as you can.
-Okay.
-Hurry.
Wang.
You
come back so early.
Your Grace, have you heard
the news from the palace?
The incense used in the sacrificial ceremony
exploded.
Now, Xu Zilu
is as well dead.
How is that possible?
Yesterday...
This is the end of this matter.
Ping'er,
you've had your fun.
It's time to go back with me.
I can't go back with you.
I didn't mean
to make things difficult for you on purpose.
But you should know
that no matter how long you stay,
the result will be the same,
right?
Now, the Xu family
has such a big event.
I have something to tell Se.
I have something to discuss with her.
Please go back first, Your Highness.
I'll go back home tomorrow.
I know what you're thinking.
Ping'er.
At this point,
where can you escape to?
Who else
can take you away?
If you don't want me
to make things difficult for your grandpa,
just listen to me, okay?
Okay.
But please
let me stay here a little longer.
Okay.
I'll grant your wish
to have a proper goodbye to him.
Ping'er.
Pack up and come with me.
Wang,
are you alright?
Yes.
Where do you want to go?
Why is he here?
Ping'er won't
go with you today.
Ping'er.
Now that you've seen him,
we should go back.
You wish!
Ping'er, don't be afraid.
Even if I were to die today,
I wouldn't let you take Ping'er away.
Wang Zhujue, don't be so arrogant.
Later,
you will cry and beg me.
I beg you?
Nonsense!
Bring him over!
On your knees!
Look.
What did I say?
Dad!
Jue! Don't come over!
-Dad!
-Don't move!
Don't come over!
Let him go!
On what grounds can you arrest my father?
Because... he is a primary suspect
in colluding with
the merchant, Xu Zilu.
Nonsense!
My father is clean.
How is that possible?
I said he is,
and then he is.
I'll kill you!
Wang.
Jue!
Kill me first if you want to kill him!
Out of my way!
-Ping'er.
-Wang.
Ping'er.
This is all part of your trap.
Isn't it you who are
determined to challenge me?
You are so despicable!
I've warned you a long time ago.
It's you who are dreaming of taking down the bear.
You're overestimating yourselves.
Now, everyone's life
is in my hands.
Wang!
Ping'er.
I'll give you one last chance.
Will you marry me or not?
Fine.
I'll marry you,
but you have to
let my friends go.
As long as
even one of my friends is hurt,
I will never let you go, even when I'm dead.
Ping'er!
Wang Zhujue.
Okay.
I'll comply with all of your wishes.
Our wedding is near anyway.
You can
stay at my mansion now.
As for the Marquis,
I'll tell him about it in person later.
Take Her Highness back.
Yes! Take him away!
Go!
Father.
Don't worry.
I'm fine, Jue.
Move.
Wang.
I'll leave Wang Zhujue
in your care.
Ping'er!
Wang.