[Debit Queen]
[Episode 20]
[Xu Mansion]
Welcome, Your Highness.
Please forgive me for not greeting you in advance.
Mr. Xu.
I didn't expect
we'd meet again so soon.
Your Highness.
There's no need to be overly courteous, Your Grace.
These are
my friends in Linchun City
that I talked to you about yesterday.
So you are the ones
who took care of Her Grace in Linchun City.
I hereby
express my gratitude to you.
After Her Grace went missing,
I've been worried about her day and night.
Now, Her Grace came back to me
safe and sound.
It's all thanks to you.
Your Grace.
You haven't told them
about our engagement, have you?
I...
I haven't even told them
that I'm a princess.
Of course I wouldn't tell them that.
You're thoughtful, Your Grace.
Actually, to be honest with you,
Her Grace and I
have been engaged for a long time.
Ping'er.
You are already engaged?
I...
Who's this?
This is a friend of mine from Linchun,
Wang Zhujue.
He's here for the exam.
It seems Mr. Wang here
doesn't know the rules.
How can you call Her Grace
by her maiden name?
I'm used to it.
Your Highness.
It's because I asked them to call me that.
Why don't you sit down
and have some tea first?
No need.
I'm only here to pick Her Grace up
and take her back to the Marquis Mansion.
I still have something important
to discuss with Marquis Wei later.
I'll come visit you another day.
Your Grace.
I'll go back today.
See you, Your Highness.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Your Lordship.
Please have a seat, Your Highness.
Please.
I was discussing the sacrificial ceremony
with Grand Commandant,
so I'm back a bit late.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
It's okay.
I just arrived too.
I also picked Her Grace up on the way.
I thought since we were going to discuss the marriage,
Her Grace should be here.
Yes.
I ordered a fortune-teller to do another reading.
After the sacrificial ceremony,
it's an auspicious day.
You're really thoughtful, Your Highness.
But since marriage is such an important life event,
of course we should take it seriously.
As for the wedding date, I think
we should wait
until I go back and
set a date with her mother and uncle
through discussion.
After that, I'll come to...
What do you think?
Discussion...
Of course that's necessary.
However, Your Lordship,
my love for Her Grace
is sincere and clear.
Therefore, I'll forgive and forget
that Her Grace bailed on me at our wedding before.
But if
anything goes wrong again this time...
No, it won't.
At that time,
Ping'er was young and immature.
Please don't take it to heart, Your Highness.
Don't worry, Your Lordship.
Her Grace was young and playful.
How could I blame her?
Is it sweet?
It's sour.
Then eat all of it.
I was lying. It's sweet.
Try it.
Can't you two
be a bit observant?
Why do you have to rub salt into my wound?
I... I...
I can't watch it anymore.
Weren't you quite confident this afternoon?
"It's just Prince Xian. What's to be afraid of?"
Didn't you say that yourself?
I was just bluffing.
What do you think I should do?
Will I never
see Ping'er again?
Ping'er only went home. It's not like she became a nun.
If you want to see her,
just go see her.
Or,
you can ask her to come see you at the Xu Mansion.
Right.
I can go see her.
I won't stay here
and watch you two being lovey-dovey any longer.
I'll go back and study.
If I fall behind in my studies,
Ping'er will be angry.
I'll go see her first thing tomorrow morning.
Look at him.
He's quite pitiful.
What should we do
about Ping'er and him?
Wu Qi talked to me
about the situation in Furong.
It was all about Prince Xian.
After spending time with
Prince Xian these days,
I finally realized the ramifications of it.
If Prince Xian doesn't budge,
it's almost impossible for Ping'er
to break off the engagement with him.
But even if he is Prince Xian,
Ping'er is a princess herself.
It's exactly because they're well-matched
that this matter
is even harder to deal with.
So... What should we do?
[Marquis Wei's Mansion]
Did Her Grace agree to see me?
Young Master.
Please go back.
His Lordship said
Her Grace is waiting to be wedded.
She doesn't know any young master out there.
How is that possible?
Her Grace and I know each other.
We are... We're friends.
If His Lordship says she doesn't know you,
then she must not know you.
You might have mistaken her for someone else.
His Lordship is magnanimous.
He won't pursue this matter any further.
But if you come trouble us again,
we'll report it to the government office.
Why don't you let me in?
I'm really friends with her.
[Xu Mansion]
Ping'er.
Why is it you?
Wang.
Eat something.
I haven't seen Ping'er for two days.
I have no appetite.
You still have to eat something.
Get up.
It's not like when you were in Linchun,
you could see her
every day.
That's different.
When I went to the Wei Mansion today,
they wouldn't even let me in.
They said
we don't know each other at all.
We've known each other for so long.
How could they
identify us as strangers just like that?
Did they really say that?
What should you do?
I can only miss her by looking at this for now.
Wang.
Act normal, please.
Eat first.
Come on.
After dinner,
I have some good news for you.
Good news?
Good news.
Se said
she’s going to see Ping’er in the next couple of days.
Even if you can't see her,
you can ask Se
to help you give her a message.
Ling Se is going to see Ping'er?
I'll go see her now.
Wang.
Wang, have some more.
[Marquis Wei's Mansion]
Ping'er.
I didn't expect you
to be so good at playing games.
I almost lost.
Why aren't you smiling?
Se.
Be careful
on your way back.
Your dear Wang
asked me to say hello to you.
I couldn't tell you in there.
Also,
he has a lot to say to you.
I found it too cheesy,
so I asked him to write it down.
I can't read it anyway.
Thank you, Se.
Please tell Wang that
I've received it.
Actually,
I prepared a note
for Wang too.
I've been waiting to give it to you
when you come.
Rest assured.
I'll make sure he gets it.
You have no idea.
He's been so depressed these days.
This note
will definitely cheer him up.
But you guys can't
keep passing notes to each other
like this.
You still have to meet in person.
Se.
It's not my grandfather
who forbids me from seeing Wang.
It's Prince Xian.
He has many people
watching me at the gate of our mansion.
I can still see you,
but I'm afraid it'll be very hard
for me to see Wang.
Don't worry.
From now on,
I'll pass notes for you two.
How about this?
Ling Se.
I can't wait any longer.
Just tell me
whether I can
see Ping'er or not.
Should I put this here...
Just tell me.
I asked you
to wait for news at home.
Now that you came to my shop,
you need to give me some advice.
On what?
Help me think
what I should sell
in my shop.
I'm not in the mood to think about this.
How about
you tell me
Ping'er's news first?
And then,
I'll help you think about it carefully.
Okay?
Fine. Fine.
It's only because you look pitiful.
Look.
What is this?
Is this
from Ping'er?
Don't worry.
Ping'er is doing well.
It's just that
it's inconvenient for her to see you now that she's living in the mansion.
From now on, if you have something to say to her,
just write it down and give it to me.
I'll pass it to her for you.
Okay.
As long as Ping'er is doing well,
and as long as she still thinks about me,
everything will be fine.
Alright, Young Master Wang.
In a few days,
I'll find an excuse
to ask Ping'er out.
Then you two can meet at home.
Really?
That's great.
Ling Se.
You're doing me such a big favor.
Let me kowtow to you.
Don't do that. I can't accept it.
If you want to thank me,
help me think
what I should sell here in this shop.
But
I've never opened a shop before.
I really don't know anything about it.
But
there are many students
coming and going on this street.
As for bookstores alone, there are two.
Let me think.
Other than studying,
all students care about is eating and drinking.
But there's already enough catering service on this street.
If Ping'er and I
could have somewhere to go to play games,
that would be great.
Play games?
That's a great idea.
[Yushan Perfume Shop]
Miss, please pay your bill here.
Okay.
Young Master, are you here to buy incense?
Please have a look.
The seasonal incenses in our shop
are Auspicious Snow Incense and Refreshing Incense.
They've both come out.
You look like an extraordinary man, Young Master.
The Spirit-worshipping Incense and White-admiring Incense
suit you so well that it's like they're
customized for you.
If you're buying for a girl,
I recommend the Lotus Incense and the Jade Incense.
Girls love the smell of them.
How much is the incense?
Two taels of silver per box.
Two taels?
Are you selling incense or robbing money?
This is the level
of business we do.
If you think it's too expensive,
there are many stalls that sell incense for 3 or 5 coins
on the street.
What's with the arguing?
Young Master.
Mr. Luo.
It's been a year since we last met.
You truly look radiant.
Young Master is here.
Why didn't you inform me?
I... I didn't recognize him.
Third Uncle changed the name of the shop
to his name.
Isn't it understandable that
the shop boys don't know me?
Young Master, don't say that.
We're living off the Xu family,
and of course, the shop we're managing belongs to the Xu family.
You're the owner of the Xu family's shop.
Even if we are as blind as a bat,
we would recognize you.
Did Manager Wan tell you
when he came here that
Third Uncle is no longer a member of the Xu family?
He... He did.
So why didn't you cooperate
when he came to claim the shop?
Young Master.
Third Master
was right here in the shop at that time.
We wanted to cooperate,
but we didn't dare go against him.
My heart
is loyal to the Xu family.
Loyal to the Xu family?
How can you prove that?
Young Master, please wait a moment.
Here are the title deed, ledger,
and inventory details of the incense shop.
Everything is here.
Please take them all, Young Master.
You could have done this earlier.
Do I have to
come here in person?
[Xu's Incense Shop]
Young Master,
why don't you go in and have some tea?
I'll ask the kitchen
to cook some dishes for you.
Mr. Luo.
I have something else to do.
Okay.
If you have the time,
you might as well teach your subordinates
how to do service work right.
Yes.
You're absolutely right, Young Master.
Smell it.
This incense smells familiar.
It smells like Xu's incense,
but meanwhile, it smells a bit strange.
After smelling it for a while, it's a bit astringent.
Xu's
can never formulate such an incense.
Young Master.
You mean
there's something fishier in here?
This incense used
a total of 10 ingredients.
Nine of them
are in Xu's inventory.
But the last one
can't be found in the entire territory of Qing.
Young Master.
You mean...
I wonder
where Third Uncle got
this ingredient that only grows in Beiyun.
Go and check
who Third Uncle
has been friendly with recently.
Okay, I'm on it.
My Lord.
There's a message from Prince Xian,
asking you to hurry up and deliver the goods
to the other party.
This batch of goods needs urgent shipment.
I'm afraid we're short-handed.
Recruit more men
for the warehouse first.
Yes.
[Xu Mansion]
We agreed to meet here at this time.
Why isn't she here yet?
Ping'er!
Your Highness, Your Grace. Greetings.
No need to be overly courteous.
I happen to be free today,
so I thought I'd get some fresh air
out here with Her Grace.
We didn't have the chance to get to know each other better last time.
Today,
I brought some gifts.
Think of it as me making up for the welcome gifts last time.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Please come in.
Okay.
Your Grace.
Why is Prince Xian here too?
He has been following me.
We didn't know you'd come today,
Your Highness,
so the family banquet was prepared a bit hastily.
Your Highness, please take no offense.
You're too kind, Mr. Xu.
This table of delicacies is good enough.
I only get to enjoy this kind of cuisine
since I came with Her Grace.
As long as Her Grace is happy,
I'm happy.
I heard a lot about Madam Xu from Her Grace,
saying you are as close as sisters.
So why don't you change seats with him
and sit next to Her Grace
so that you can talk to her better?
Your Highness, there's something you don't know.
My husband and I love each other very much.
If we don't sit together
at dinner,
I'll lose my appetite.
You two
really love each other deeply.
I wonder what ranking
Candidate Wang got in this Provincial Examination.
I...
I was
supposed to fail.
I barely made the list
and only took last place
because I got guidance
from a master before the exam.
But being the last on the list now
doesn't necessarily mean
I'll always be the last.
By the time of the Metropolitan Examination,
perhaps my ranking
will be really high.
Even the person who gets first place in the Provincial Examination
may not be able to get a government job.
You are quite confident
as the last one.
I admire you.
Your Highness.
The early bird catches the worm, and diligence can make up for lack of intelligence.
With such ambition,
Wang's dream may actually come true,
right?
Then I wish you
pass the exam with a high ranking, Candidate Wang.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You're welcome.
You're Her Grace's friend.
I'm supposed to be nice to you.
How about this?
When Candidate Wang
becomes the Number One Scholar,
I will arrange a good marriage for you.
I remember Assistant Minister Liu
has a daughter who's not yet married.
She's a good match
for you, Candidate Wang.
Your Highness, you flatter me.
My biggest strength
is that I know my place.
I won't make
the Number One Scholar.
And some assistant minister's daughter
is way out of my league.
Besides,
I already have someone in my heart.
You haven't achieved anything in your career,
yet you already have someone in your heart.
Candidate Wang.
So what you care about is not career,
but romance.
I wonder which family
that charming girl comes from.
We were too busy talking.
The dishes are getting cold.
Please, Your Highness.
Please.
Here, Your Grace.
Thank you, Your Highness.
This shrimp was for Her Grace.
Sorry.
I've been studying too much lately.
I've got bad eyesight.
I really thought it was for me, Your Highness.
How dare you!
Please forgive him, Your Highness.
Wang didn't mean it.
Please don't blame him, Your Highness.
We're in the middle of eating.
Why did you all stand up?
Come on. Sit down.
Sit.
But
I do have something to make clear.
Back when you were in Linchun,
you didn't know Her Grace's identity.
No matter how you treated each other,
as the saying goes, those who don't know are innocent.
So, whatever happened will not be pursued.
But now, we're in Furong City,
and Her Grace is Marquis Wei's granddaughter.
She will also be my wife, Princess Xian, in the future.
So, please remember
your etiquette.
I won't pursue it
because I have a big heart.
But if this gets out,
it'll be embarrassing.
You're right, Your Highness.
We all got that.
It's an honor for the Xu Mansion
to have you here today, Your Highness.
I heard that you're good at
all the Four Arts, namely zither, Go, calligraphy, and painting, Your Highness.
I wonder
if I may have the honor to see that today.
Yes.
I've heard it before in Linchun
about how talented you are, Your Highness.
I really want to see it with my own eyes.
Did Her Grace mention this to you
yesterday?
Yes...
Yes.
In that case,
I won't let
Her Grace down,
and I won't let Her Grace lose face.
How about this? Let's eat first.
I'll play a song after dinner.
It's indeed my honor
to be able to hear a song
played by you, Your Highness.
Come on, Mr. Xu, Madam Xu.
To you, Your Highness.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Find a way
to let Ping'er
see Wang Zhujue alone.
You're really good at giving me challenges.
This family banquet was supposed to be
a chance for them to see each other.
Who knew Prince Xian would come?
Okay, I'll figure something out.
I did my best.
It was so good.
You're too modest, Your Highness.
I usually
make friends through incense,
and sometimes, I play the zither with my friends.
But today,
after hearing the song you played,
I feel that
all those I heard are unbearable to hear now.
I also like burning incense
to entertain myself when I play the zither.
It seems that the two of us
share the same interest.
Your Highness.
I developed a new incense recently.
It goes the best
with books and the zither.
I'm trying it out in my study right now.
Judging by the time,
the incense
should be best burned now.
Your Highness.
Do you want to come with me and take a look?
In that case,
I'm willing to be
the first one to eat crabs.
Mr. Xu.
Please lead the way.
I won't go with you
to my husband's study.
It so happens that Her Grace and I
have something intimate to talk about.
I'd like to invite Her Grace
to come to my room to catch up.
I also prepared
her favorite food and playthings.
Okay.
Go.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your Highness, please.
Let's go.
Ping'er.
Wait here.
Wang Zhujue will be here in a minute.
Take your time to talk.
I'll keep watch outside.
Xu Zilu will find a way
to stall Prince Xian.
Okay.
Thank you so much, Se.
Mr. Xu's study
is so nicely arranged.
It's both spacious and elegant.
If I didn't know
you were a businessman,
I would think
I've entered a scholar's study.
Thank you for your compliment, Your Highness.
Are these all your works?
Yes.
Furong doesn't have as many ingredients
as Linchun.
Your Highness, if you have time,
please visit Linchun.
I'll take you to
Xu's and show you
the ancient incense-making technique passed down in the Xu family.
Linchun is a great city.
I will definitely go there if I have a chance.
Okay.
Actually, I'm usually quite bored
in Furong City.
I only get to do the Four Arts
on a superficial level.
A few months ago,
I went to Lingnan
and collected a few sets of Four Treasures of the Study.
Next time we meet,
I will give you a set as a gift.
The Ink Pavilion in Lingnan
is indeed the best.
I wonder if you've been there, Your Highness.
That's exactly where I went.
Their inkstone is second to none
in the Qing State.
I heard that the orders
have been lined up to the year after next.
I had to take full advantage
of my status
to cut the queue and got three sets.
I've also heard a lot of nice things about Ink Pavilion.
But last month when I was there in Lingnan,
I didn't get a chance to visit it.
It's really a pity.
Last month?
I remember
there was a freeze disaster in Lingnan last month.
The road conditions were tough.
Mr. Xu.
Why did you go there at such a time?
Xu's has a Laurel Garden
in Lingnan.
It was severely affected by the disaster this year.
I was there to comfort the victims.
I wanted to go to Ink Pavilion
after I finished my work,
but I didn't expect that
I'd have an accident along the way.
Accident?
Yes.
There was an emergency at home.
On my way back,
I ran into a bunch of bandits.
I almost died.
There has been no report of bandits in Lingnan for years.
How come there were bandits out of the blue?
I also found it strange.
Those bandits were really fierce that day.
One of my companions was killed.
I was lucky
to have survived.
Someone got killed?
So what happened then?
Did you report it to the government office?
How did the government office deal with it?
I was saved by the villagers.
After I woke up, I went to report it to the government office.
But I was in a hurry to return to Linchun,
so I didn't pursue the outcome.
There have been many disasters in the south this year.
If natural disasters are met with man-made disasters,
the people will have
a even harder time.
Yes.
If the bandits are rampant,
I must report this to His Majesty
to pacify the bandits.
Mr. Xu.
Do you remember
the victim's name?
And where was that person from?
Go after them!
Young Master!
A bunch of people are after us!
Dear Young Master.
The stuff inside this parcel
is very important.
If anything happens to me,
please take it
to Furong City.
Furong City?
Well,
I don't know about that.
But
that person seemed to be
from Furong City.
Furong City?
Let's not talk about this.
After this ordeal,
you'll definitely have great luck
and have a bright future, Mr. Xu.
Thank you for your kind words, Your Highness.
Ping'er.
I saw that
you didn't eat much today,
so I brought some chicken drumsticks
from the kitchen.
Have some.
Wang.
How have you been these days?
I'm all right.
Everything is fine.
It's not that I didn't want to see you,
but my family...
Ping'er, you don't have to explain.
I understand.
We can figure something out together.
No matter how powerful Prince Xian is,
as long as you don't want to marry him,
we'll find a way to get you out of it.
There must be a way.
I only escaped back then
because I didn't want to marry him.
That's why I escaped from Furong City to Linchun.
I didn't even want to marry him back then,
not to mention now.
Wang,
will you wait for me?
I will.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll wait for you.
But Prince Xian
is nice on the outside and indifferent on the inside.
He's very cunning.
Wang.
Promise me.
Don't
provoke him again.
And pretend to be a coward?
That's what I'm best at.
At worst,
I'll avoid him from now on.
I won't let him
have anything on you.
From now on, I'll stay in the mansion and study.
I won't go anywhere.
I won't provoke him.
Okay.
I'm relieved then.
Ping'er.
Take good care of yourself.
Eat well.
I've understood
all the learning techniques you taught me.
I will work hard.
I'll pass the Metropolitan Examination.
I promise I won't let you down.
Wang.
Take good care of yourself too.
Eat well.
Ping'er.
It's a deal then.
Okay.
It's a deal.
Deal.
Young Master.
You don't know that person's name
or his facial characteristics.
There's no clue whatsoever.
How should I investigate it?
Isn't this a clue?
But isn't this
just a dark little box?
This is not an antique.
But the craftsmanship is quite delicate.
There's no logo
or pattern on it either.
This is obviously
from a rich family for home use.
Just follow this line of thought
and investigate.
Young Master, there are
countless families
that can afford this in Furong City.
If I were
that capable,
would I still be working here?
I would've been an official in the government office.
Chen Bin.
Young Master.
Investigate this item
for me.
Leave it to me, Young Master.
Not to mention you have this,
even without it,
I can
find out the truth.
Come here.
Put it down.
Didn't you ask me to investigate it?
Why do you have to take this with you
for investigation?
You're clumsy. What if you lose it?
I can do it without taking it with me.
Because I've seen
all the details.
Liufeng.
Yes, Your Highness. Any order?
Have you found Yetian and Mu?
Not yet.
So,
you haven't found that thing either?
I'm incompetent.
Go investigate Xu Zilu.
I want to know
if it's possible that
he has that thing.
Are you suspecting
Xu Zilu has something to do
with the spy sent by the Ministry of Justice, Your Highness?
During the freeze disaster in Lingnan last month,
Xu Zilu made a trip there.
I want to know
if he knows something.
Do we need to silence him?
Silence him?
What good would that do me
if we silence him now?
Killing him is not a big deal.
But what if you
ruin my plan because of it?
I was wrong.
Use your brain
when you work.
Follow him for the time being.
We'll make a plan after finding out what he's up to.
Yes.
Young Master.
Prince Xian sent someone to Lingnan.
Lingnan?
Why did he think of Lingnan all of a sudden?
I also find it strange.
This never happened before.
So what has he been doing these days?
Just as usual.
He's still been visiting the same shops.
Yesterday, Prince Xian went to the mansion of Imperial Merchant
Xu Zilu.
Mr. Xu is really something.
He's only been here a few days,
yet he got Prince Xian to visit him in person.
Did Xu Zilu
go to Lingnan last month?
Yes, he actually did.
All right.
Ask your men
to keep watching Prince Xian.
Empty the private room upstairs.
I have a guest to meet there.
Yes.
It's quite busy here.
Pardon me,
you two.
We have quite a lot of guests today.
You may have to wait
for two more hours.
We are friends of Wu Qi,
Mr. Wu.
He's booked a private room upstairs.
I see.
This way, please.
Thank you.
I prepared a simple meal
to welcome you to the capital.
You call this a simple meal?
Mr. Wu.
You gifted me a shop,
and now you're treating us
to dinner at such a nice place.
It must have cost you dear.
Thank you for your hospitality, Mr. Wu.
I will
treat you to dinner in turn another day.
It's a great time
to eat silver carp now.
One of the reasons why I invited you two here today
is to enjoy delicious food together.
The other reason is that
I'm really curious about
how the preparation
of Young Madam Xu's shop has been going.
I've thought about it.
Your shop
is quite close to the academies.
The students there have nowhere to go for fun
after school.
So I decided to
open a game shop.
Young Madam Xu.
You're even more imaginative
than before.
You flatter me, Mr. Wu.
But
the gaming equipment
will cost a lot of money.
Mr. Wu.
Are you interested in
making an investment?
Okay.
I'll pay for
all the gaming equipment
in the shop.
Thank you in advance then, Mr. Wu.
Here.
I look forward to working with you.
Happy cooperation.
Congratulations,
you three.
Your ordered
our signature set meal today.
So,
you got a lucky draw.
Besides, the winning rate is 100%.
You can send a representative
to try your luck downstairs.
Darling.
Go.
I'm not usually lucky.
Okay.
I'll go then.
Please.
I've already
sent my wife away for you.
Go ahead.
What is it?
Has Prince Xian
been to your mansion recently?
Did you arrange someone
to keep watch at my mansion?
Why do you know everything?
Given my relationship
with you two,
I don't need to arrange anyone there.
I could ask you directly.
I'm just curious about
why Prince Xian went to your mansion.
I think I can tell you.
Prince Xian
has some connections
with Ping'er, who's in my mansion.
Ping'er?
Just Ping'er?
Prince Xian didn't mention Lingnan?
You've been talking to me about Prince Xian the last couple of times we met.
Why is that?
Mr. Xu.
Given your connections with Prince Xian,
of course you'll take to business like a duck to water.
It's just that in business,
besides making money,
safety is the most important thing.
I wonder
if you think so too, Mr. Xu?
Yes.
My family's safety
and happiness
come first.
May
our wishes come true then.