[English subtitles are available]
[Debit Queen]
[Episode 1]
Excuse me.  Excuse me.
Who is it?
Stop running! Stop!
I'm Ling Se,
owner of the most popular food stall
in Linchun City.
I'm popular because
everyone knows
that I love money.
No haggling is allowed at my stall.
Know
that every copper coin
matters to me.
Little one,
where do you think you can run?
I'm famous
because
my shop is doing well.
The desserts and sweets I sell
are very delicious.
Whoever eats it knows.
True craftsmanship and careful cooking
bring out the best flavors!
Don't miss out.
18 coins per bowl.
Buy it for your wife,
and she'll treat you well every day!
Get it for your husband,
and your worries will melt away!
Here.
This is Ping'er,
whom I took in a few months ago.
I bought her a meal
and wanted to take her in to work for me.
She said she was a maid
who had escaped from a rich family.
But she can't do anything
that maids do.
She's always so mysterious.
And she eats a lot.
She can eat all day long.
I've really taken a big loss.
If I hadn't been able to make money,
she would have already drained me dry.
Every day after closing,
I turn into another girl.
The young lady from Ling's Silk Shop
in the city.
But I'm not at all like
what you might imagine of a young lady.
My mother passed away a long time ago.
I have a stepmother,
but she doesn't want me, no matter what.
She is determined
to raise me like a maid.
As the saying goes,
"When you have a stepmother, even your father becomes a stepfather."
My father's ambition
is the same as hers.
Look at yourself.
You don't look like a young lady at all.
Go outside
and ask around about your reputation.
If it weren't for me
protecting you
because you lost your mother when you were little,
your father would have long
beaten you up
and kicked you out.
Great!
Who are you?
You don't have a place to speak here.
Why haven't I seen
a maid like you in the house?
It's all my fault.
Listen carefully.
We'll have a noble guest today.
You
stay in your room
and behave yourself.
Okay.
Don't come out and cause trouble!
Do you hear me?
Behave yourself!
Just looking at you like this
makes me feel unlucky.
So annoying.
I'm already used to it.
I just need to put up with them for a little while longer,
and I can be free of them.
I love money, and I'm good at making it.
I want to fulfill my ambition,
which is to buy a shop,
expand my business,
move out on my own,
and live
my sweet life freely.
Today,
I've saved enough money to buy a shop,
and this is a big step
towards my dream.
The shop in my dream, I'm coming!
[Si's Rice Shop]
That's right.
This is it.
After months of searching,
we've found this shabby shop
with few customers.
What do you know?
When doing business,
you need to have a long-term perspective.
Besides,
I have some insider information.
In less than a year,
this street will be busier than the East Market.
You even know that?
Of course. Who am I?
I am...
I have my own clever plans, like that person.
Zhuge Liang.
Ladies,
you've been chatting here for hours.
Look at my shop.
It's not that big,
but not that small either.
What's wrong with it?
Your shop
is fine.
The problem
is the price.
A big shop like mine
on Peony Street
would sell you
at least 200 taels.
I sell it for only 100 taels.
It's already a good bargain.
I can only offer 50 taels.
How can you bargain like this?
The prices are
all determined by the location.
You have said it yourself.
Your shop is not
on Peony Street in the East Market.
There are not many customers coming here.
Of course, it can't be the same price, right?
Look at your cabinets.
They're all falling apart.
The door... the door is even broken.
See?
I have to
renovate this whole place.
80 taels.
50 taels.
70 taels?
60 taels.
Sell me the shop along with the rice.
Do you know how much rice
is in my shop?
50 taels then.
I'll only buy the shop.
Well...
It's okay. No rush.
Take your time.
I'll come back tomorrow.
Ping'er.
You are so stingy.
What do you know?
I know a lot.
[Ling Mansion]
Don't make much smoke.
Keep sweeping. Keep sweeping.
Here's the water.
Come here.
Young Master,
we've arrived.
Is this
about business or a wedding?
And didn't I say no maids?
Why are there still maids here?
You handle them.
I'll use the side door.
Miss Ling Se.
Don't go to the front.
It’s not appropriate for women there.
Butler!
Okay.
Someone is looking for you.
Butler!
Coming.
It's just down the road.
I won't listen to you.
My precious banknotes.
I'm counting on you to buy the shop.
Why isn't Fuding here yet?
Since when do we have such a handsome man in our family?
Why don't I remember him?
I thought
the maids at Ling's Mansion
were well-trained,
but you're no different
from the maids in other houses.
It's one thing not to help,
but do you have to add snide comments?
It's true that you men
are no good!
Today is definitely not my lucky day.
Maid, stop right there!
Are you calling me?
Get me a new pair of shoes and socks.
You don't have to bring them to me.
Let the servant do it.
Jackpot.
I'm not going.
Say that again.
I said,
"I'm not going."
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless you pay me.
Socks, 10 coins. Shoes, 3 taels.
Stay away from me.
Thank you for your kindness.
You're not a member
of our family,
and I'm not obligated to help you.
But if you pay me,
things are different.
As the saying goes,
"Take someone's money and resolve their troubles."
I have no other hobbies
besides making money.
How about this?
I'll give you a discount for the whole set,
3 taels.
Fine.
I'll pay you.
You don't have any money?
Then why are you so arrogant?
How about this?
I'm generous,
so I'll give you some free advice.
Didn't you step on dog's poop?
Just take it as a sign
that you're going to have some good luck!
I'm giving you this piece of advice
for free.
Being fussy
is unbecoming of a man.
Mr. Xu,
let's just forget what happened just now.
Let's get down to business.
I'm sure you know
that my Qifu Silk Shop is the largest silk shop
in Linchun City.
If you can
give me
this opportunity,
I will give you
another 10% discount
on the basis of offers from other merchants,
and I guarantee the quality is better.
Mr. Xu, what do you think?
If you want to become the new packaging supplier
for Xu's Perfume Shop...
you'll need to offer at least a 30% discount.
30%?
Mr. Xu,
my offer is already very low.
I will soon
become an imperial merchant.
The sachets made by my shop will be sent to the palace
in a steady stream.
This is a big deal.
Mr. Ling,
you need to take everything into account when doing business
and have a long-term vision.
Mr. Xu,
take care.
Young Master,
you were so cool
just now.
Did you see
Master Ling's face?
His face was all green.
Young Master, no wonder
you are a big profiteer.
No.
I mean, you are great!
Check if the people of Ling Mansion have left.
They left. Young Master, you...
What's wrong, Young Master?
Are you stupid?
Where did you find the shoes?
I-I-Impossible.
The shoes I found for you are new.
See for yourself. Are they small?
Are they small?
I'm asking you, are they small?
I...
Your salary for next month is gone.
No, no, no!
Come on, Young Master.
This way.
My clothes.
Isn't this Young Master Xu?
Why are you dressed so shabby?
Are you trying to experience the hardships of common people?
Fuding,
check the horoscope before going out in the future.
Why?
I don't want to run into some haunting ghosts
when I go out.
Wait!
You're scolding me?
Yes, you.
Wait.
Aren't these
the limited edition shoes with cloud embroidery
I ordered for 20 taels of silver?
Why are they on your feet?
Well...
Here...
I...
Here's the thing.
Master Ling
invited my young master here for a business meeting.
Then my young master
accidentally stepped on the dog...
What?
You stepped on my baby dog?
That’s Wealth!
If anything happens to it,
you're dead!
Wang,
let’s meet another day.
My Wealth!
Young Master,
the dog poop you stepped on is called Wealth?
And it seems to be his baby.
Wang Zhujue,
I didn't expect your friend
to be so different as well.
You're a genius.
He hasn't passed the Provincial Examination
for four years in a row.
Yeah.
At such an age,
he is still going to school.
Does your father know you're out, embarrassing your family?
Where did he go?
None of your business.
My father
is doing his best
for the city.
For the plan of the new market in the western part of the city,
he hasn't been home for days.
We, from official families,
really have no desire to
associate with people like you
who only care about business and making money.
Xu Zilu!
You ran away again!
My young master,
you're finally back.
I'll ask my men
to light up the candles now.
No need.
So as not to disturb my mother.
Fuding is enough to serve me.
Okay.
You still know you have a mother in the room?
Stop yelling
in the middle of the night!
Greetings, Mother.
Xu Zilu,
there's a limit to my patience
with you.
I can’t just sit back and watch
the Xu family fall into ruin
under your hands.
You're still not married.
How can I face
your late father?
Mother.
These are two different things.
How can you mix them up?
Fine.
Let me ask you.
What are the requirements
for becoming an imperial merchant in the Qing State?
You tell me!
Firstly, be the industry leader.
Secondly, have a clean family background.
Thirdly, have no direct relatives in official positions.
Fourthly...
F-F-Fourth...
Four...
Xu Zilu!
Fourthly,
the person in charge must be an adult
and have a family.
Mother.
Even if I'm to marry,
I should find a suitable partner.
Your childhood sweetheart
left you at the altar. So what?
For the past few years,
No maid can even enter
our mansion.
I asked you
to go on a blind date with the Eldest Miss of the Tao family.
Did you go?
No wonder...
No wonder the whole Linchun City
is saying my son is not interested in women.
Tell me,
do you have any hidden illness
or do you have some
peculiar preferences?
Mother,
what are you talking about?
The Imperial Merchant selection happens every four years.
It's not the only chance.
Please give me more time.
Within four years, I'll get married and have children.
Rest early.
Stop right there.
Xu Zilu,
do you think I arranged
for you to meet Miss Tao
just for a blind date?
How naive.
The Tao family
controls vital trade routes with
the Yanchen State.
And the ingredients
for our new fragrance
come from there.
Now that the palace has tripled their order,
if we can't deliver on time,
it will be
a serious crime.
I know.
If that's your concern,
Mother, don't worry.
I will cooperate with the Tao family
in my own way.
Mother, go to sleep.
You...
What's your way?
All you do is lying to me.
I...
Hello, here I am.
Have you been waiting?
You're already packing up for me.
Miss,
I've been waiting for you.
What took you so long?
My 50 taels aren't
a small amount, huh?
I was thinking of
selling it to you for 50 taels.
I don't care about that.
That's good.
But
I waited for you for a long time but you didn't come.
Another buyer came along
and bought here.
Look.
Wait.
I've been waiting for this day for six years.
This...
Who's trying to take this shop from me?
Who dares?
Me.
Do you have a problem with that?
You again.
What?
You know each other?
-Yes.
-No.
Sir,
you have a really bad memory,
already forgetting what happened yesterday.
Fine.
It doesn't matter.
But first come, first served.
Do you know the rules?
I chose this shop first.
First come, first served.
You first.
Do you have proof?
I...
The shopkeeper can testify.
I came here first yesterday, right?
Did she pay first
or sign the agreement first?
Or,
you sold the shop to two people?
No, no, no.
Since that's the case,
first come, first served.
Whoever pays first gets it.
You understand, right?
I...
I'll give you a suggestion for free.
What?
Go somewhere else.
Shopkeeper,
have you prepared the title deed?
Yes.
Here it is.
Wait,
we can talk about it.
Sir,
I'll pay the original price.
Could you give me the shop instead?
Young Master, are you alright?
Hey, you.
How could you
touch the Young Master?
Well,
I just slightly touched him.
Is he that delicate?
Of course.
Not just anyone
can touch the Young Master.
Alright.
If I touch him, will he jump into the river?
Let's go.
You...
Don't move.
What's wrong with you?
If you're sick, go see a doctor.
Shopkeeper, who is he?
The richest man in Linchun City, Xu Zilu.
The rich man
who became the head of his family at twelve
and rumour has it that he's afraid of women?
Yes.
How much did he pay for it?
One tael less than you.
49 taels.
Young Master,
so we've been
wandering here for such a long time
just for that shabby shop?
Why not?
No problem,
but it's just getting harder
to figure you out.
Come here.
Well, you've been
with me for so many years.
What have you learned?
Well...
Wang Zhujue said yesterday
that his father is planning to develop the west market.
Once the news is revealed,
the land prices there will surely rise.
This shop is in the center of the west market.
Not to mention 50 taels,
even 100 taels are worth it.
You're back so soon.
Looks like things went well today.
I'll leave this stall to you.
I gotta go.
What a bad day.
I think
we should just give him 20 taels.
In a few days,
we could set up our own shop.
It’s better than making trouble.
It's not a matter of
20 taels anymore.
We're
already
in trouble now.
So someone bought
the shop you wanted?
Just because you tried to save some money
and didn't pay the deposit,
now it's taken.
Forget it.
As long as we have money,
we will figure out a way.
Luckily,
we still have 100 taels.
Look at you.
What's wrong?
I exchanged the 100 taels
for a bank note
and put it in the liner.
It's gone.
This is weird. It must be in this room.
It can't be lost.
Think about it.
Have you checked the cabinet?
This room is just this big.
It must be
somewhere.
It must be...
Where is it?
Have you checked your clothes?
My Lady.
Oh no.
I left the bank note
in the dirty clothes.
But who would take
my dirty clothes?
The clothes are really hard to wash.
No matter how hard I wash it, it keeps shedding.
Well,
once I get paid next month,
I have to buy some
new clothes for my sister.
Young Master,
the young lady is back.
Back so early?
Hurry up.
Hurry. Let's go.
Okay.
Xiang, go take a look.
Have you seen
a green outfit?
Outfit?
What outfit?
An outfit exactly
like the one I'm wearing.
I think it was hanging in the courtyard.
The courtyard?
Let's go.
Is this it?
No.
This is your clothes.
No one has ever
washed her clothes.
When she sees this,
she'll definitely praise me.
Se.
Which bastard
washed my clothes?
How could you not check inside
before washing?
My 100 taels.
Ling Shuo, what did you say?
Did you see
who washed my clothes?
I don't know.
I didn't see it.
Who is so wicked?
Not only is the bank note gone,
but the clothes are ruined too.
Was it you who washed my clothes?
No,
I don't even know how to do it.
What is this?
I should have thought it was you.
It really wasn't me.
I'll kill you.
Otherwise, I won't be Ling Se.
Se.
It really wasn't me.
Stop right there!
Believe me, Se.
I must kill you today!
You have to believe me.
Young Master, stop running.
Se.
Stop!
Believe me.
I didn't do it.
100 taels.
I saved that money for six years.
Don't cry.
Actually,
if it's meant to be, it will be.
If it's not, you can't force it.
You still thinking
about the 100 taels of silver
won't help at all.
Stop with
the poetic nonsense.
It's giving me a headache.
What should we do now?
How much money do we have?
There are only three taels left.
What can we do then?
Should we go beg
that black-hearted guy?
Ping'er.
I was talking nonsense.
Don't take it seriously.
Yes.
I can go beg Xu Zilu.
I don't care.
As long as he's willing to
rent me the shop,
he's a good guy.
Se,
you always give up
so unexpectedly.
What about your bottom line?
No bottom line,
only a deadline.
I'll ask him tomorrow.
Just wait and see.
This one is pretty.
This one is good too.
Son, look.
Aren't they beautiful?
This booklet
took a lot of effort
to get.
That fat woman
is indeed the most popular matchmaker
in Linchun City.
She has the best resource.
Over 300 girls on it
are unmarried.
I've read them all.
Pretty good.
As merchants, we can't be
as picky as those
noble families.
Good character and looks
are enough for us.
I don't even
care about their background.
Zilu,
even if you
bring a courtesan back,
I'd be happy too.
Just
pick one today.
Pick one,
and I'll handle the rest for you.
I don't want to.
I don't care if you want to.
As long as I'm willing.
Also,
ever since Xie Wanrong
ran away from her wedding,
you've been dodging the idea
of marriage with every excuse.
Enough with all your
excuses.
Mother, what are you talking about?
I just don't want to
get married carelessly.
I'm telling you, Xu Zilu,
you have to pick one today.
If you don't,
I'll pick for you.
Mother,
there are still three months
until the Imperial Merchant selection.
Why are you
in such a rush for my marriage?
Who told you
there are three months?
Didn't your third uncle tell you?
Governor Wang has sent someone
to inform us.
The Imperial Merchant is being reformed.
This is the last selection.
It will be held on the first day of next month.
We have
barely ten days left.
Do you think I want to force you?
Forget it.
Madam.
I won't care about you anymore.
Whether you get married or not,
who you marry,
or if you even want to
marry a girl,
I don't care anymore.
Thank you, Mother.
Yushan.
Sister-in-law.
I have a favor to ask.
From today on,
you will take over as the head of the family...
I...
and join the Imperial Merchant selection for the Xu family.
Xu Zilu,
from today on, neither the Xu family
nor Xu's Perfume Shop
have anything to do with you.
Mother.
Ms. Jia.
Madam.
Inform the elders of our clan
to come here.
Yes.
I...
It's just getting married.
Three days.
I'll bring back a wife in three days.
Zilu,
what nonsense are you talking about?
I'm not talking nonsense.
Three days it is.
If you can't get married in three days,
I won't change my mind
no matter how hard you beg me.
Fine,
three days it is.