[English subtitles are available]
[Debit Queen]
[Episode 12]
How dare you run away?
Will you continue to run away?
Do you believe that
I'll still shoot you with a slingshot?
Are you scared?
You want to run away?
I'll still shoot you with a slingshot.
Catch him!
Yes!
Stand up!
Go!
Xu Zilu.
You still had to rely on me
at the critical time.
[Prefecture Office]
My Lady!
Ping'er!
You're finally back.
My Lady, I miss you so much.
Let me look at you.
How come you're fatter now?
Maybe it's because I had
nothing to do in prison,
and all that I could do was eating.
Anyway,
thank you very much this time.
You don't have to thank me.
But speaking of which,
you should thank Wang Zhujue.
He caught the culprit himself
this time.
However, don't compliment him too much.
He'll get carried away easily.
Okay.
When I see him another day,
I'll thank him sincerely.
It's good that you're back.
Come on. Let's go home and eat something delicious.
-Okay.
-Let's go home.
What crime did he commit?
Burglary.
Can't you see it? It's written here.
Don't forget to remind me of the thing
I've mentioned to you.
Okay.
Young Master.
Isn't that Mr. Wang?
Why is he here again?
And he's wearing such gaudy clothes.
His meaning is too obvious, Young Master.
Why are you
dressed like this?
It's none of your business.
This is my home.
Wang!
Ping'er?
I'm here to see you.
You suffered a lot in prison.
Look at you.
You've lost weight from hunger.
-Those bad guys.
-Really?
After I go back, I'll give each of them a slap on the face
to relieve your anger.
Wang,
actually, I didn't suffer much
in prison.
Everyone took good care of me.
What's more,
I don't seem to have lost weight.
By the way, Wang,
thank you.
Thank you for saving me.
From now on,
I'll owe you a favor as you saved my life.
Tell me what you want.
I will repay you.
You're welcome.
As long as I'm here,
no one will bully you.
Thank you, Wang.
How about I treat you to a meal?
How can I ask you to treat me to a meal?
I've already prepared it.
I've prepared Braised Meat Balls in Brown Sauce,
Braised Crucian Carp,
Scrambled Eggs with Tomatoes
and some of your favourite dishes.
Why does Mr. Wang
want to treat Ping'er to a meal?
And why didn't he invite us?
I wouldn't go even if he had invited me.
I would go.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
You know what?
I can't believe that my father actually commended me.
Isn't that good?
Wang,
haven't you always wanted
your father to commend you?
But I didn't expect that
he would be so happy.
He also said,
"Kid,
in the future,
you will definitely
bring glory to our family."
I always think that
you are very excellent.
It's just that Magistrate Wang
probably didn't notice it.
But in your opinion,
what achievement is considered as bringing glory to our family?
I can't always
go out to catch thieves every day, right?
I have an idea.
Have you signed up for the Provincial Examination?
Although you failed to pass the Provincial Examination
several times,
if you study hard this time,
you might be able to pass the exam.
If you pass the Provincial Examination,
your parents
will definitely be very happy.
Isn't this an achievement
which can bring glory to your family?
Yes.
I failed the exam because I didn't want to study hard.
What if I pass the exam after I
study hard this time?
Ping'er.
Can you be my teacher?
I can understand all that you've said.
But I just don't understand
what my teachers said.
Of course I can.
Of course you can't.
I don't have enough money now.
If I don't even have enough helpers,
my shop will be completely out of operation, won't it?
Where is the source
of our funds now?
Let me make it clear in advance.
I don't have money.
Don't count on me.
Don't worry.
I've never
counted on you.
But you just can't take her away from me, right?
My shop has just been opened.
There must be many customers.
Many customers?
But Sister,
even if I go,
I can't help much, either.
I... I have such a big appetite.
After your new shop has been opened,
don't make it go bankrupt because I eat too much.
How about
you just let me be Wang's teacher?
You silly girl.
How much money can it cost if you eat the food?
Right now,
your incident is just a trivial matter.
The point is that
we don't have
enough money now.
That's right.
Humans are not important, while money is important.
How about
we borrow some money?
Your friend, Liu Yeniang,
runs an inn, doesn't she?
She must have money.
I don't want to borrow money.
That's my principle.
As the saying goes,
if a person borrows money,
the more he borrows, the poorer he'll become.
Yeniang,
last time, I told you about
the investment...
and asked you to become a shareholder.
Have you made up your mind after consideration?
Let me tell you.
I've found a supplier that will
give me a 30% discount.
We only need 30 taels
to open the shop.
30 taels?
Do you think my money
was earned without efforts?
Ma'am, give me a pot of wine!
Wait a moment.
I usually don't even have enough money
to buy clothes, watch an opera and go shopping.
How would I have money for you?
Ma'am, hurry up and give me the wine.
I'll be right there.
You can buy
clothes anytime, can't you?
It's rare for several best friends
to make money together.
How about this?
I'll exert my capability
as the Stingy Girl
and open the shop with 20 taels.
My dear girl,
you can also sell your tea at the stall, can't you?
How can it be the same?
At the stall, I can only sell the tea
at the price of 20 coins per cup.
If I run a shop, the price can be 30 coins per cup.
Think about it.
Even if I sell
only 50 cups in a month,
then the net profits will be
20 taels a month
and 200 taels a year.
You'll earn a large amount of money, won't you?
You'll be the major shareholder.
You might even wake up from your laugh in your dream, huh?
Alright.
You're so shrewd.
I can't refute what you said.
Thirteen taels. I won't give you a penny more.
My good sister.
I know you're the best.
Don't worry.
I will definitely
regard every penny of your money
as my lifeline
when I spend it.
I will definitely enable our shop
to have a grand opening.
Opening a shop? What kind of shop are you going to open?
She's going to run
a weird shop.
She even asked her best friends to invest in it.
Yes, Miss Tao.
If there's a good project, as best friends,
we can make money together.
We can work together and spend money together.
Aren't you happy just thinking about it?
Miss Tao.
Do you have some spare money?
Will you consider investing in my shop?
Does that mean that
you'll work for me?
Sure.
But I don't have that much money.
Don't loathe it if I don't give you much money.
Of course I won't.
Even a copper coin is also money.
How would I loathe it if you don't give me much money?
100 taels.
This is all the money I have.
You said you didn't have much money.
How come it's not quite the same
as what I've imagined?
Are you busy?
The deadline of the Assessment of Imperial Merchants
is coming soon.
I need to pay more attention to the affairs
of the perfume workshop.
What's the matter?
Well, tomorrow,
it'll be the opening day of my tea shop.
I think
you must be quite busy recently,
so I've brought my new product here
to let you taste it.
It's a good thing that you'll open a tea shop.
If I have time,
I'll certainly go there.
Then I'll wait for you tomorrow.
Remember to eat it.
I won't disturb you any longer.
[Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop]
A happy opening!
Please support us.
Congratulations.
Big Boss Ling Se.
The same to you.
Manager Ping'er.
Ms. Ling.
Ms. Tao.
Ms. Ling, wish you a prosperous business.
Wish you prosperity!
Let's open a branch store!
Let's open ten branch stores next year!
Ten branch stores!
We've almost finished
discussing business.
As I have something else to do, I have to go now.
Xu,
it's still early.
Why are you in such a hurry to go back?
Are you going back home to be bullied?
Look at us.
We've finished talking about work.
Just listen to me talk about
my family affairs.
There's a promotion event for our opening.
Ladies,
if you buy one cup, you'll get another one cup for free.
If you buy three cups, you'll get another two cups for free.
What do you think?
Please enjoy yourselves.
Liu.
Give me ten cups of Aromatic Tea.
Little Young Master, each person can only buy five portions.
Otherwise, the people after them can't buy the tea.
Can't the shop owner's family buy ten cups?
Not even the family can do this.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here's your milk tea.
Please enjoy yourselves.
Be patient. Be patient.
Sorry to keep you waiting. The milk tea is ready.
Thank you.
What do you want?
Drink it while it's still hot.
It's delicious.
Really?
It's good. It's really good.
What are you looking at?
Nothing. Go give them to the customers now.
Hurry.
Yes, yes, yes.
Alright.
I really have something to do. I have to go now.
No, Xu!
I just want to
complain to you about this.
I'm just
trying to get drunk to relieve all my sorrows.
Come on, Xu.
Thank you for listening
to me talking about so many
sad things today.
Now that I have you here...
Come on. Let's drink. Okay?
Waiter!
Bring me two more pots of wine.
I'm so tired.
I've never done
so much work
all my life.
My legs are also
aching so badly.
How about we take a rest
for a day tomorrow?
No.
We sold all the goods
on the first day of the opening.
We have to go on working hard on it tomorrow.
Ordinary people can't stand this, can they?
Are you really not considering
hiring several people to help you?
I'm considering about it.
But it'll cost some money to hire
some people to help us, won't it?
We had a promotion event today.
After the costs are deducted,
we still have some losses.
We'll still need to save more money.
The saying of suffering losses only to earn some popularity can be used to describe you.
Anyway,
today,
we had a good start in a way.
Later, let's
go eat something delicious.
No, I'm exhausted.
I'm going back.
From tomorrow onwards,
just work hard to earn money for me.
Ling Se.
Okay, Ms. Tao.
Go back and have a good rest
I won't eat, either.
I haven't been in my inn for a day.
Except Da,
all the other waiters are newcomers in my inn.
I'm worried that these people
might make a mess in my inn.
I'm leaving.
Then just go now.
Ling Se.
Later, ask Ping'er
to eat at my place.
And she can also
tutor me in my studies.
Then you have to study hard.
Don't let Ping'er down.
Just go.
Then just wait for me.
Keep up the good work.
[Fulai Inn]
Come on. Be careful.
Xu!
Young Master.
Why are you so late?
Take him home safely.
Did you hear that?
Okay.
Young Master, what about you?
[Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop]
Xu Zilu.
You...
You didn't leave?
I thought you wouldn't come.
Why are you sweating?
You're even out of breath.
I... I just did some exercises.
Then let's do some exercises while going back.
Okay.
Ms. Ling, wish you a good opening.
Wish you good luck.
Thank you.
Let's go.
You eat first.
-It's so sweet.
This one.
Write it like this.
By the way, Ping'er,
my father bought many desserts today.
Do you want to taste them?
Wang.
I'd like to thank Magistrate Wang
and you for thinking about me.
But I'm really full now.
How about saving them for me next time?
I'll eat them next time.
Wang, write it like this.
By the way,
you haven't had the pear soup
which I made for you today.
I don't want to drink it, Mr. Wang.
I really can't drink it now.
Hurry up and write it.
I can't see anything.
Ping'er.
Ping'er, where are you?
Ping'er, is this you?
Ping'er!
Wang.
Don't try to play tricks in front of me.
That's impossible.
How come I suddenly can see things again?
It's so amazing.
What do you think is going on?
If you can't finish
writing it tonight,
you're not allowed to go to sleep.
Oh no.
I failed to muddle through again.
I'll
just write it.
[Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop]
Here are the Four Seasons Spring Milk Tea
and Rose Milk Tea for you two.
Drink them while they're still hot.
If you drink them within two hours,
they'll taste the best.
-Thank you, Ma'am.
Thank you.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Bye.
Sister.
Why is no one here?
I was going to help you today.
Yes.
I also thought that there would be many people.
How dare you say that?
Where did you go yesterday?
Don't mention it.
Yesterday, I tutored Wang
in the Book of Rites.
He performed the cross eyes
in front of me.
He even pretended to be bline
He was doing those trick for so long that
I really couldn't stay awake.
Then I fell asleep.
Forget it.
I don't have any customers here anyway.
If you are tired,
go back early and have a rest.
Even if there was
only one more customer coming, it would also be okay.
Young Master.
The goods that will be sent to Furong City
are all ready.
They can be transported there anytime.
Dispatch more
capable men to escort the goods.
Remember.
Send Jiuchongtian to
Prince Xian's Mansion as soon as possible.
Young Master, don't worry.
I travel on the road to Furong City
all year round.
There won't be any problems.
Just be more careful.
Don't be negligent.
Okay, Young Master.
I'll take a walk by myself. Don't follow me.
Are you admiring the moon?
I don't have the time or the mood
to do that like you, Mr. Xu.
Are you crying?
No, I'm not. You're the one who is crying.
Then...
Then what's the stuff on your face?
It's dew.
I'm so upset.
There have been no customers in my shop in the past few days.
Is it because
the food I made is not delicious?
Of course there's room for improvement.
It's quite delicious.
Really?
Of course.
Actually, the location of Wang Zhujue's shop
is really remote.
Plus, this is your first time doing business.
It's normal that
people don't know about a new shop.
Do you think that
I haven't comforted myself like this?
I've been thinking all kinds of ways
in the past few days.
But none of them was effective.
Although the beginning is always difficult no matter what we do,
when will it stop being difficult?
Actually, there are still two sentences
following this sentence.
The beginning is always difficult no matter what we do.
It'll still be difficult in the middle.
In the end...
It'll be the most difficult.
You've heard of this?
Actually, today,
I have something to tell you.
There will be a trade fair in the east of the city tomorrow.
Normally,
participants are supposed to take their family with them to go there.
With my current identity,
it's inappropriate for me to go alone.
Ms. Ling,
tomorrow, will you have time to
close your shop for a day
and go with me?
Okay.
I'll do that for the sake of the most difficult part.
Welcome, everyone.
Mr. Qiu.
Xu, you're finally here.
There are still many things
to be handled by you.
Come with me now.
Ling Se.
Later,
wait for me after you enter the inner court.
I'll get back to work.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hurry. Come with me now.
What's the matter?
Okay. Three people, right?
Okay.
Let me take records for it.
Sure. No problem. No problem.
Come on. Everyone, please come in. Please come in.
Miss.
Please stop.
Miss,
you look a bit unfamiliar to me.
Who are you?
I'm Ling Se.
What Ling Se?
Please show me your invitation letter.
Invitation letter?
Miss,
our club
is not open to outsiders.
You can't come in without an invitation letter.
So please show me your invitation letter.
Well...
I came in with someone else.
It seems that I've dropped my invitation letter.
I dropped it at my home.
How about letting me go in first?
I'll ask someone to send it to you later.
Why don't you come here again another day?
No. I'll continue to look for it.
That annoying Xu Zilu!
Miss, you dropped something.
Sir,
have you mistaken me for someone else?
I didn't drop anything.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You dropped
[Invitation Letter]
this thing, Miss.
You didn't notice it, did you?
Yes, it's mine.
Thank you.
Please come in, Miss.
I can come in now, right?
Please.
I'm going inside first.
My husband
bought a new piece of land in the southern suburbs.
He said he would take me to see it in two days.
I teased him.
Can there be gold
growing in this land?
There are quite many flavors.
Who is that?
Whose wife is this?
Who are you?
Are you asking me?
My name is Ling Se.
Whose wife are you?
I'm from Xu's Perfume Shop.
I'm a member of the Xu family.
You... So you are the Young Madam of the Xu Family?
Young Madam Xu,
did you not eat enough food at home?
Why are you eating these snacks here?
Well, these snacks are really delicious.
You can also taste them.
I won't eat the food here.
Take it away.
Mrs. Chen is used to being picky about food.
Since this food is placed there,
it's just for people to eat, isn't it?
Young Madam Xu.
Why are you wearing this dress?
Yes, your dress is so short.
It looks like a maid's dress.
Why... Why didn't you bring your wife along
when you came here?
I think
my wife is in the inner court now.
Did she go there alone?
Well... Young Madam Xu
is here for the first time.
You're supposed to take her there
and... and introduce her to those several
ladies inside.
You know what my wife is like.
The other ladies inside there
are also not to be trifled with.
Young Madam Xu is young.
I'm afraid that she can't
manage with it by herself.
You've thought too much.
I think it'll be fine.
I'll go take a look.
Don't you think he's just...
Let me tell you a secret skill.
When you cook rice, you need to put some oil in it.
In this way, the rice will be
both fragrant and soft.
The kids will all like eating it.
Really?
My child
doesn't like eating rice.
This is great.
Then do you know
how to make the egg custard delicious?
My husband always says that
the egg custard I made smells fishy.
Egg custard?
It's even easier to make egg custard.
Just put some
corn grains,
carrot granules, shelled shrimps,
peas and so on inside.
Just remember the most important thing is that
you need to add vinegar and cooking wine to remove the fishy smell.
Then
steam it with a bamboo tube.
After it's steamed,
I'm sure it will be
both fragrant and smooth.
Isn't this Mr. Xu
of Xu's Perfume Shop?
Why are you hiding there and listening to our conversations?
He must be worried about his wife,
so he's here to see his wife.
I... I'll go there first. You guys...
-Just go.
They are really close to each other.
I used to hear that Mr. Xu
was apathetic about the intimate relationship with women.
After I saw him today,
I can't believe that he cares about his wife so much.
That's right.
Mrs. Xu is good at controlling her husband.
She's so lucky.
I've really learned a lot.
It turns out that a party for rich married women
is like this.
Right?
You usually associate with the disciples of Hong Sect
and vendors in the market.
You should also learn about
the preferences of rich married women.
In this way, it'll be good
for your business.
I think
you get along well with them.
You must have talked a lot with them.
So you specially
brought me here?
I... just did it incidentally.
Incidentally?
No wonder
you didn't even give me the invitation letter.
I almost couldn't come inside just now.
Well...
Didn't they know you?
They said they would only recognize invitation letters, not people.
Who was that?
Just forget it.
We're leaving anyway.
But I still want to thank you.
Thanks for doing this for me.
When I look up to the sky, I have a clear conscience.
When I lower my head, I don't feel guilty as I haven't done anything disgraceful.
These are the two joys.
Wang,
what is the third joy?
Joy...
Alone...
It's better to enjoy something with others than to enjoy it alone.
Ping'er.
I'm sorry. I fell asleep again.
Why did you always doze off?
People tend to get sleepy in spring, get tired in autumn and doze off in summer.
During March in winter, it's hard to get totally awaken.
In such weather, I just can't help
dozing off.
Alright.
I have an idea.
Go out and do some exercises with me.
Ping'er.
Your idea is really good.
After running two laps, not only am I not sleepy anymore,
but my body is also warm.
In the future, if you are sleepy,
we can run more.
It's just that
the weather is cold now.
Even though our bodies are warm after running,
our hands are still quite cold.
The hands are cold?
By rubbing your hands, they'll get warm.
Look.
How about
you rub your hands by yourself?
Look at you.
You don't stay in your shop,
but you come to my inn every day instead.
Well...
What kind of mess is this?
There are no customers anyway.
Isn't it better to close it earlier?
Look at you.
I just don't know
what you guys are
worried about every day.
Ma'am, give me a pot of wine.
Wait a moment.
I know this woman.
Let me help you.
Mrs. Qiu.
You're here, too?
Why are you here
to have a drink alone?
Don't mention it.
It's due to my mother-in-law.
I really don't know what evil things I did
in my previous life.
Last time, I taught you the tactic of cooking for her.
Didn't you use this tactic?
Even my husband said that
the dishes I made were delicious.
But my mother-in-law
just didn't like this
and didn't like that.
I was furious when I heard it.
But I couldn't say anything.
I'm so angry.
It shouldn't be like that.
By the way,
your mother-in-law often
plays mahjong with my mother, doesn't she?
How about this?
Next time when she comes,
I'll sound her out for you.
Come on. Let me have a drink with you.
Mother.
What do you think is going on
between Mrs. Qiu
and Old Madam Qiu?
Why are you suddenly interested in
the gossip about their family?
The grudge between them
has lasted for a long time.
Since Mrs. Qiu
married into their family,
Old Madam Qiu has never liked her.
This afternoon,
I came across Mrs. Qiu.
She told me that she couldn't gain favor
from Old Madam Qiu all this time.
I feel sorry for her,
so I just want to help her.
No wonder
I just like you.
You are so soft-hearted.
But this is their family affair.
It's inconvenient for us to intervene.
How will you help her?
How about this?
Mother,
you can ask Old Madam Qiu
to play mahjong tomorrow.
It's okay to ask her to play mahjong.
But playing mahjong and helping her are two different things.
By that time,
we'll put on a show in front of her.
This is not okay. I'm not able to do it.
No, no, no.
Mother, you can do it.
By that time, I'll teach you how to say it.
You'll teach me?
Okay.
Just give it a try.
I'm so nervous.
You can do it.
[Xu's Mansion]
It's the same to do it earlier.
Mother.
Exactly.
Right?
Yes.
I've made some Furong Cakes for you.
Taste them.
What?
Furong Cakes.
What kind of weird name is that?
What kind of food did you make?
Its neither sweet nor spicy nor sour.
Fu... Furong Cakes?
Your cooking skills are really getting worse and worse.
Take them away.
Yes.
Have I asked you to leave now?
You have no insight at all.
What are the three of us doing?
We're waiting for you.
We need one more player. Let's play mahjong.
Sit down.
Come on. Sit down.
Se.
Give me that cake. Let me taste it.
Aren't you afraid of being poisoned?
It's quite delicious.
The cake you made is much better than
the one my daughter-in-law made.
You just
don't know how lucky you are.
I'll eat them all.
Who actually doesn't know how lucky she is?
Speaking of your daughter-in-law,
a few days ago,
she specially came to our mansion
and learned to make cakes from Se
in order to make you happy.
I even like your daughter-in-law.
She just faked sincerity.
My daughter-in-law
always makes my son and my grandson
stay with her.
My son always spends time with his wife.
I can hardly see my grandson every day.
Since she married into our family,
the three of them have been a family.
Wherever they go, the three of them always go together.
And I'm always left alone at home.
That's too much.
What did you say just now?
A family of three, right?
You have a son and a grandson.
Do I have a grandson?
How I wished that I could have a grandson.
Have you ever given birth to a grandson for me?
No, you haven't. You...
I don't think I have.
You... You can give it a try on this.
Mother, I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Look. I've married into the Xu Family
for so long.
But I haven't had a child yet.
If I could give birth to a child
for our family like Mrs. Qiu,
my mother wouldn't have been so worried.
Well...
Why are you crying?
Look. It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have talked about my grandson.
Calm down. Just calm down.
Every family has its own problems.
No one's life is easy.
Let's play mahjong.
Alright. Stop crying. Let's play mahjong.
Hello.
Is this the Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop?
Yes.
Please give me a portion of
each kind of tea in your shop.
I'll take them away.
Okay. Wait a moment.
Hello.
Do you have any speciality snacks here?
Yes.
Give me a portion of each kind of
snack in your shop.
Yes.
Give me a portion, too.
Okay.
Ladies, please have a seat.
-I'll bring them for you right now.
-Let's sit down.
What flavor of milk tea do you want to drink?
Here's your milk tea.
Thank you, Ma'am.
Bye.
Thank you.
Ping'er.
Sister.
I can't believe that there are so many customers.
You're really amazing.
I guess Mrs. Qiu
did some publicity for me.
People came here
just for her sake.
In a few days,
maybe the business will be bad.
It won't.
The milk tea you made is so delicious.
They will definitely come back
to buy your products again.
You're right.
Come and help me.
I'm so busy.
Let's go.
I've heard that
the desserts here
are very delicious.
Really?
Which one is good?
Green Bean Cakes and Red Bean Cakes.
And Furong Cakes, too.
This is their speciality.
It's very delicious.
Dear customers, please have a seat first.
I'll come serve you later.
Hurry up.
Okay.
Here are your desserts.
-Thank you.
This milk tea is our speciality.
Please taste it.
It smells so good.
I want a cup of
Mashed Taro Bubble Tea.
Why are you here?
I...
You came at the right time.
Help me take these cakes
to that table.
Be careful not to drop them.
Okay.
Hello, what milk tea would you like?
I want that Mashed Taro Bubble Tea.
Sir, here are your desserts.
Taste them to see if they're delicious.
If you think they're delicious,
recommend them to your relatives and friends.
Okay.
Enjoy yourselves.
Alright.
Take these two cups of milk tea to that table.
Be careful. They're a bit hot.
Tell them to drink the tea while it's still hot
as it'll taste good in this way.
Okay.
What would you like?
Come on, dear customers.
Drink the tea while it's still hot.
What is this?
This one is for you.
It's called "Wish You Prosperity".
Young Master Xu, thank you
for your guidance these days.
I didn't help much.
Ladies, your takeaway drinks are ready.
-Thank you.
-Enjoy yourselves.
I'm really so busy with the business
in my shop.
I really can't handle it.
I really need to hire one more person to help me.
I guess next year,
I can open another branch store.
I've even decided what its name should be.
I'll name it Scented Aromatic Tea Shop.
Then I'll hire some
versatile
and eloquent waiters.
Drink it while it's still hot.
I have to get back to work.
You should get back to work, too.
Here are your desserts.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Okay.
Here's your milk tea. Drink it while it's still hot.
[Fragrant Aromatic Tea Shop]