=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
=Episode 9=
(In order to know Li Wuyou's thought,)
I must first do what he likes)
(and find out
which type of girls he likes,)
(so he can fall in love more easily.)
(First, the most welcomed)
(gentle-and-virtuous type.)
Young Master.
I made your favorite osmanthus cake.
Try if you like it.
(Why did she change
her persona suddenly?)
Open.
How was it?
Not bad.
(Nothing is happening.)
What's going on?
Nothing.
(Perhaps he doesn't like this type.)
(Let's try the second type,)
(bold-and-open type.)
Young Master.
As the children of the underworld,
fate brought us together.
I shall toast this tea
instead of wine to you.
(What a smooth)
(personality switch.)
(Without a trace.)
You're welcome, Heroine Chuchu.
Nice one.
I wonder if you
need me to serve you tonight.
Of course.
You have an amazing massage skill.
I would love to have it.
(Why is it still not working?)
(It seems there's
another mystery in this red rope.)
(I must use my final trick now.)
(I'll try this one last time.)
(Sexy-and-charming type.)
Young Master.
Why aren't you eating?
Eat another piece with me.
What do you want me to do with you?
(What's going on?)
(Why is my heart beating so fast?)
(As if it's going to
jump out of my chest.)
I'm full now. I shall leave.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪The dream in my heart♪
♪Froze at the street
intersection in the morning♪
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪In my mind♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪