[English subtitles are available]
[Rival Love]
[EP12]
Mr. Su!
Due to multiple
murder cases occurred in town,
no one is allowed in
or out of the City.
We appreciate
your cooperation.
Deputy He,
I can't be
the murderer, right?
I have business to attend to in Yunjing.
Please
make an exception.
Sorry, I can't.
Report!
Sir,
we found the butler Li.
Mr. Su,
please go back.
No need to look.
He's already dead.
The soldiers said
he was screaming all night,
telling Biyun to stop talking.
He must have been hallucinating,
thinking Biyun was after him.
He couldn't bear it and killed himself.
He got off easy.
I'll
handle the rest.
You...
Alright,
let's go.
[Father,]
[Biyun,]
[the butler Li has confessed.]
[I hope your spirits]
[can rest in peace.]
General He,
since I started down this path,
I won't stop.
You know what I mean.
Just let me go with you.
May I ask you a question?
Of course.
Last night,
you took good care of me when I was drunk.
Today,
you helped capture Li.
Why are you willing
to help me like this?
Su Mei,
you've prepared
so much for revenge,
aren't you tired?
In these war-torn times,
many people struggle just to survive.
I can't complain about being tired.
I know
you're looking for the Necklace
to stay ahead in these
changing times.
That's right.
You're...
the leader of
the Eclipse, aren't you?
You seem to already know.
I'm sorry
for using false information to lure you.
The Necklace
isn't in the city, right?
Back then,
Su Qiping killed my dad
before the treasure was found.
Even if
he hadn't been called over for the proposal,
he'd have come for trade routes.
I know.
I had another reason
for calling you here.
Supported by the Eclipse,
I found out
his businesses are just a front.
He actually
has caused many murder cases
behind the scenes.
Miss Su,
what is your intention?
He Jingyao,
how about we make a deal?
Su Qiping likes to carry his dirty money
in banknotes with him.
When done,
you can have them all.
Then your trip here
won't be in vain.
Then,
what do you want me to do?
Get engaged to Luo.
General He,
this is...
The murderer of the brides.
Who is it?
Butler Li.
What?
How?
He burned himself to death in guilt.
No further discussion needed.
Mr. Su,
since he was your servant,
you can handle his body.
No wonder
he seemed off after the incident
at the dock days ago.
He always looked so honest.
Men indeed can't be judged by looks.
Sir,
since the murderer has been found,
can I leave the city now?
But you haven't agreed
to my marriage with Su Luo.
Why do you insist on marrying her?
No, I don't.
Then, what do you think
of me marrying Su Mei?
Mei,
ignore that madman.
The boat is ready,
You can leave tonight.
Now you're done using me,
you want to get rid of me.
Since I can find out
that you're Biyun's brother,
Su Qiping can do it too.
By then,
he'll definitely link
Biyun's connection with my father
and suspect you killed butler Li.
So you're worried
Su Qiping will come after me.
Live well from now on.
With your talents,
you don't need to be stuck here.
Leave
and do what you truly want to do.
Let me stay and help you.
[He Jingyao!]
I've made up my mind.
I'll marry you.
But even so,
you won't have my heart.
As you wish.
I know,
if I don't marry you,
my sister has to do it.
She and Wei Shiting are well-matched.
I don't want her to sacrifice for me again.
Well-matched?
Don't worry,
I won't mess with Luo again.
She's just childish,
being
curious about me.
But General He
seems to have fallen deeply for you.
Is that so?
Men understand men best,
and
love making
other men jealous the most.
Where are you going?
Behave yourself,
Wei Shiting.
Don't be rude
to disturb them.
Though I'll never love you,
since we're to be married,
I have to be by your side often.
From today on,
I will try to spend
more time with you.
Hopefully, we can become friends.
No need.
[Where are they?]
Sir,
the body has been examined.
He indeed died by suicide.
Many saw him acting suspiciously
at the dock,
so his suicide
makes sense.
No,
he had no reason to kill those brides,
and at the place
where Biyun died 10 years ago.
Is it possible
that Biyun was killed by him?
He told me that
he only killed Qi'an
and no one else was involved.
The shop on Greenstone Island
suddenly lost many orders to Zhen.
And Li died mysteriously.
I suspect someone
is targeting you.
For safety,
shouldn't you leave here for now?
What's the point of running?
Such being the case,
digging out the mastermind behind
makes it funnier.