=The Perfect Husband in the Mirror=
=Episode 22=
I'm not leaving.
You wanted to exchange your life.
But look at what you've done.
It's all your fault.
I cherish her and love her
more than you do.
Shut up.
You cheated on her.
You don't deserve to be her husband.
I'm not going back.
What are you doing?
Luo Weiqi,
didn't you say
we'll leave together?
Have you forgotten?
Have you forgotten all of it?
I need to be sure
if you would leave with me.
Of course I would.
You are much better than Meng Yingchao.
But if we leave,
my mother-in-law
will surely come looking for us.
I don't want to spend our future days
in fear or anxiety.
Trust me.
I will treat you well.
Haven't you realized it yet?
Stop daydreaming.
Meng Yingchao,
do you think
you can live in peace
after I leave?
You ungrateful bad guy.
It's none of your business.
Everyone,
you either are exchanging your lives
or have already exchanged your lives.
Do you really think
you can shirk all responsibilities
in this way?
The New Club is filthy.
What's behind it
is selfishness and cowardice.
Giving your lives to strangers.
You are truly pitiable,
detestable, and pathetic.
Ask yourselves.
How can you face yourselves
and those who love you?
Are you okay?
Yes.
How did it go?
The only way
to restore order in this world
is to shatter that mirror.
Meng Qi.
Let me go.
My name is...
I know.
You have been following me.
No.
I...
Actually, I've liked you...
I've liked you for a long time.
(We had a deal.)
(Come with me.)
(After the funeral,)
(we'll leave together.)
(Of course I would.)
(I'll make him
come back willingly soon.)
(I will also make him wish he was dead.)
(If I sign this,)
(you will leave with me, right?)
(I will)
(take care of Weiqi for you.)
(We're about to have our first child.)
(That's great.)
(Honey.)
(I miss you so much.)
(You have no idea)
(how long I've been waiting
for this day.)
(Well,)
(can't I be nice to my wife?)
(Weiqi,)
(let's start over.)
Honey.
Sorry.
If you want to pursue me,
I can only say sorry.
That one is fake.
And now the real one is back.
Hello, a cup of cappuccino, please.
Madam, I think the mirror is gone.
Retreat.
What?
I said, "Retreat".
Weiqi.
You saw what happened just now.
This is not AI technology.
They are not twins, either.
To shirk his responsibility
for the family,
my husband
found a substitute to live with me.
These fake husbands
come from a mirror of the New Club.
For her own interests,
the owner of the club
would help those who are cowardly
and afraid of facing the reality,
just like my husband.
That's right.
I am also one of the victims.
My ex, Shi, just wants a girlfriend.
He doesn't want to take responsibility.
So he went to the New Club
and found someone identical to him
to marry a rich woman.
And he used her money
to live a life of debauchery.
This club will disappear soon.
However,
it might reappear somewhere.
So I hope,
if one day you find out
the person beside you is fake,
do not be deceived by tenderness.
Please step forward.
Do not become a victim.
Let's go.
They ran away fast enough.
Maybe
they'll still show up somewhere.
I hope they'll never show up
to harm anyone again.