=The Perfect Husband in the Mirror=
=Episode 6=
Weiqi.
Why did you space out?
Do you suspect
he has multiple personality disorder?
Do you still suspect
he's cheating on you?
From what I've observed
this period of time,
Meng Yingchao has truly changed.
I think he only wants to treat you well.
That's too much.
Don't you think he's
like a different person?
You don't have a fever.
Isn't that the perfect husband
you've always wanted?
Hello.
Hello, honey. Come back home tonight.
We agreed
that I'd go straight to Li Ke's home.
Okay.
Well, don't forget to do the test.
Just be normal, okay?
Leave.
Do you miss me right after work?
Li Ke, I need you to see
if anyone's following me.
Is there?
Yes.
Can you see the face clearly?
No.
You send me a location
and I'll call the police.
You bad guy!
Honey, it's me.
Aren't you going to Li Ke's place?
Why are you alone?
You've been following me
from the clinic?
Why are you sneaking around?
And you even got hurt.
I'll do it myself.
What do you mean?
I remember
you have blood phobia.
I have to be strong
to protect you.
I will stay at Li Ke's place tonight.
You'd better go home.
Weiqi.
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
Were you the one
who's been following her?
How do you guard your husband
like he's a thief?
You two are really funny.
You'd come home with me.
Li Ke, didn't we agree I'll go to
your place for midnight snack?
Can't your wife
stay at my place for one night?
I will stay at Li Ke's place tonight.
Okay then.
Then I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Okay.
Then we're leaving.
Let's go.
Welcome home, honey.
Mom.
The man who ran away the other day
must be Yingchao, right?
You've recognized him?
I've recognized him at first glance.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
What have you done with my son?
What can I do to him?
He made me do it.
Impossible.
I know my son
well.
You really don't know.
Weiqi is pregnant now.
Whose child?
Child?
Impossible.
Did you forget what the contract said?
You don't belong to this world.
It's impossible to have a child.
I...
Even if there is one,
it won't be yours.
Your son's child.
Now,
you really need to help your son.
Dr. Luo, here's your parcel.
Thank you.
Weiqi.
Let's go and have a meal.
You just go. I've ordered takeout.
Amy just called and said
she left a stocking in my car.