=The Perfect Husband in the Mirror=
=Episode 24=
(Real Estate Sales Contract)
(The verdict is in.)
(I've sold the house.)
(I'm leaving half of the money to you.)
(Take care of yourself.)
Hello.
The number you've dialed
is not in service.
Please check the number and dial again.
The number you've dialed
is not in service.
Please check the number and dial again.
I want to resign.
So happy?
Planning to seek
a better position elsewhere?
Bye.
Adults should remember
to treat themselves to candies.
Thank you.
Dr. Jiang,
I'll supply all the sugar
you need for the rest of your life.
Then you'll have to take
good care of my teeth.
No problem.
We have a more important thing
to do today. Let's hurry.
When you return
after completing your studies,
I'll work with you, Director Luo.
You started calling me that now.
Of course.
You promised to offer me a job.
No regrets allowed.
Not just a job.
I'll give you a great job.
When my business grows big,
I'll invite Dr. Jiang
to work together too.
No problem.
It's already hard to focus on
and excel in one thing.
I support you.
Amy.
I heard you were leaving today.
You look well.
So do you.
You're getting married?
Yes.
To a man I love and who loves me.
It's quite nice.
I always thought
relationships were all about effort.
But after I met the right person,
everything seemed
to fall into place naturally.
Alright, enough chit-chat,
or Dr. Luo is going to miss the flight.
Hurry up.
Okay.
No need to see me off. I'm leaving.
Weiqi.