=Wise Woman=
After being the daughter of Gong Family,
you can no longer be Xue Wan'er.
Are you really giving up
the status of your child's mother?
Things in the world
are always hard to have both ways.
But this time,
I insist on having it both ways.
I will protect the Gong Family
and take back my child.
I will also make
those who have harmed me
pay the price they deserve.
(One month later)
=Episode 4=
The bride is stepping over the brazier.
Once she steps over the brazier,
she officially enters the Rong Family.
♪The cold tea was replaced♪
By following me,
will you regret it?
Never.
♪Another year of wind,
another year of sorrow♪
Miss Gong? Miss Gong?
♪The person I'm thinking of
isn't there after I turn around♪
♪The hurting heart
believes in tears after healing♪
♪Perhaps things go against wishes,
and love does not last♪
♪I have no regrets,
even if we can't be together♪
♪If we meet too late,
who will be touched♪
♪We feel torn as we fear
the passage of time and being apart♪
The newlyweds may stand upright.
Bow first to join in matrimony.
Bow second for eternal unity.
♪We feel torn as we fear
the passage of time and being apart♪
Bow third in respect.
♪I promise forever♪
Have you heard?
Matriarch had the daughter
of the Gong Family marry into our family
because she wanted her
to have a legitimate son
to inherit the general's title.
She is the legitimate grandmother
of the eldest son,
and the patriarch and the third son
have family ties.
They will inevitably
have secret competitions.
Who the benefit will fall to
remains to be seen.
When the clam and the snipe grapple,
it's the fisherman who profits.
If the water is stirred up,
maybe I'll also have a chance.
Where are you going?
I will curry favor with my new aunt.
You can't go.
Why?
It's almost night.
Don't you mind proper etiquette?
Honey,
are you even jealous of the marquise?
She is my aunt.
After the adoption,
she will be my legitimate mother.
Alright.
I won't go.
Just sit.
You must be tired.
I'm not going.
(Rong's Mansion)
Young lady, he is coming.
After all,
it's a hereditary title of marquis.
Who wouldn't be tempted?
My lady, please don't cry.
Marquise.
Heaven is helping me.
My lady.
Don't cry.
My lady, don't cry.
Aunt, what's making you sad?
Who are you?
Someone, help!
Aunt! Aunt!
Stop hitting.
I'm Rong Xiu from the fourth branch.
It's you?
It's you...
You suspected me of infidelity
without listening to my explanation,
and you drowned me.
(I can't hide.)
(She wouldn't dare kill me
as a weak woman.)
(For the title,
I have to bring her down.)
I misunderstood you.
I regret it every day,
wishing I could take my own life
to compensate you.
Kill me.
I don't deserve
to be the father of your child.
Child...
My child...
I can't
kill the father of my child.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
What on earth has happened
these days?
I was rescued by the Gong Family.
My sister asked me
to marry in place of Miss Gong.
Xue Lingyi knew it all along?
Then why did she keep it from me?
Maybe my sister
didn't want you to see me.
(This venomous woman...)
Now, you've married
into the Rong Family.
We can be together now.
I thought that was the case.
I'm already in the Rong Family,
yet my sister tried every means
to prevent me from seeing my child.
If I can't see my child,
what's the point of me staying here?
In fact...
I wish...
I wish that I can
keep my child by my side rightfully.
Actually, there is an opportunity now.
What opportunity?
Didn't the matriarch ask you
to pick someone
from my generation of the Rong Family
to adopt for the general?
You mean
you want to be my son?
Yes.
Right. In this way,
my child could also be included
in the general's lineage.
As the marquise,
I could take care of him rightfully.
But in this way,
won't my sister be unhappy?
After all,
she doesn't like us getting too close.
Why should we tell her
about what's between us?
♪Drunk in the twilight of the 38th year♪
♪Time paints the branches yellow.
Let's have our farewell♪
♪Awake in the height
of summer of the 38th year♪
♪The rain is ticking into my youth♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
The past still lingers♪
♪I am waiting for you
in the fall of the frost♪
♪Dye the silk with bright red♪
♪Memories have rusted♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
I'm looking at the Red Tower♪
♪You heave a slight sigh
for the lovers that kept forever apart♪
♪The moonlight has whitened the hair♪
♪In dreams, I have kissed your eyes♪