=Wise Woman=
Fish! Fresh fish!
Sir, how about a fish?
It's very fresh.
Mr. Wang, nice to see you.
Where is Mrs. Wang?
She's doing the laundry.
Give me one.
Have you heard?
There's quite a commotion
in the Rong family.
Yes, I have.
The new marquise, who married
into their family not long ago,
had a child with her stepson.
It's more than that.
They say that woman
has been married three times before.
She's really shameless.
It really fits the saying
that only the stone lions
in front of their mansion are clean.
Such a promiscuous woman
should be drowned
or bludgeoned to death.
Otherwise, who knows
how many more people she will harm?
Right?
Exactly.
Indeed.
Yes.
That's the fact.
I was victimized
by Rong Xiu and Xue Lingyi.
=Episode 22=
Matriarch,
don't listen to her nonsense.
It's not like that at all.
Shut up.
The facts are all here.
Please be fair, matriarch.
What do you mean the facts are all here?
Your words alone are the facts?
Xiu, tell us
what exactly the truth is.
Ancestors in heaven,
your unfilial descendant, Rong Xiu,
is kneeling in front of you.
I am naive,
and I was deceived
by Xue Wan'er and Xue Lingyi.
Xue Wan'er
seduced me before.
I fell into their trap
as I was considering
the issue of having an heir.
So,
it was the two sisters
who deceived you together,
and you didn't know at all.
I was also a victim.
In that case, Rong Xiu,
you really can't judge people.
Reflect in your room for three days.
From now on, think twice before you act.
Don't tarnish our family's reputation.
Yes.
Fine.
So today,
you are not here
to distinguish right from wrong.
You are here to put on
a show together, right?
What are you laughing at?
What am I laughing at?
I'm laughing at you guys
for not telling right from wrong.
I'm laughing at your lies
and covering up for each other.
You! You are not only licentious
but also spouting nonsense
and insulting ancestors.
Guards! Drag her down and deal with her
according to family law.
Who dares to touch me?
Don't you understand?
The truth is not important
to our family.
This whole thing started because of you.
It's been blown out of proportion.
Now, only by dealing with you
can we calm the storm
and restore our family's reputation.
Dealing with me? How?
You...
You want to kill me for my silence.
You want to kill me to bury the truth.
Matriarch,
you're also a mother.
Yu and I are mother and son
with a connected heart.
Is it wrong for me
to return to Rong's mansion for him?
Is it a crime that I just want
to protect my child at all costs?
Why does your Rong family
have to treat me this way?
Why do you treat a mother
who loves her son like this?
Matriarch,
don't you even care a bit
about blood and kinship?
You're not guilty.
And you didn't do anything wrong.
It's our family
that owes you.
But
this is for the dignity
and honor of the Rong family.
If the general becomes aware of this,
it will be troublesome.
I'll send someone to pass a message
to the royal concubine in the palace
and ask her for help
to let the general stay in the palace
for three days.
Okay.
Then we must take care
of Xue Wan'er within three days
without a trace.
(Enduring Virtuous Lineage)
(Great Virtue and High Manners)
(Humble But Genuine)
(Virtuous And Genuine)
(Ancestral Virtues)
Madam?
Du Juan,
I'm here.
They locked me up.
I tried my best to get out.
I heard...
I heard
you haven't eaten or drunk for two days.
I was so afraid...
I was so afraid I was too late.
I'm still alive.
Miss, what should I do?
The general hasn't returned.
They must have managed to delay him.
Go to the Gong family for help.
Master Gong loves his daughter, so he did wrong.
But Madam Gong is virtuous,
and I believe her.
But, Miss,
you haven't eaten for two days.
Don't worry.
For Yu,
I will survive.
Xue Wan'er is fine inside.
Madam Gong, don't slander us.
We haven't abused her.
But she, as the general's wife,
had improper conduct.
This issue relates
to the reputation of our family.
You can see her,
but you can't take her away.
My poor child!
I heard it all. You have suffered.
Miss.
- Quickly.
Take it easy.
Slow down.
I just took these from the kitchen.
I still have a lot here.
You took them from the kitchen?
Why are the leftover pastries
from the kitchen
still so warm?
The people of the Rong family
want me dead.
How could they just
let you stay in the same room with me?
It's poisonous.
The people of the Rong family
are determined to get me killed,
yet they're afraid
to take on the crime
of murdering the marquise.
So they came up with such an idea.
The pastries were brought by you.
Even if this gets to the officials,
they can escape the blame.
How malicious they are!
Don't eat these.
Mother,
if I don't eat these,
I'm afraid
I won't be able
to wait for the general to return.
But, my child, they are poisonous!
♪Drunk in the twilight of the 38th year♪
♪Time paints the branches yellow.
Let's have our farewell♪
♪Awake in the height
of summer of the 38th year♪
♪The rain is ticking into my youth♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
The past still lingers♪
♪I am waiting for you
in the fall of the frost♪
♪Dye the silk with bright red♪
♪Memories have rusted♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
I'm looking at the Red Tower♪
♪You heave a slight sigh
for the lovers that kept forever apart♪
♪The moonlight has whitened the hair♪
♪In dreams, I have kissed your eyes♪