=Wise Woman=
It's his fault.
He took our child away.
Don't come.
Young master.
Young master, please save the madam.
The madam has been locked in the manor.
She's very sick.
Tell her not to bother me.
Go away.
Wait.
Young master.
I will go see her now.
=Episode 20=
Lingyi.
You finally came to see me.
I thought you abandoned me.
We've been a couple for so long.
How could I possibly give you up?
My lord,
take me away.
I don't want to stay here anymore.
Take me away.
I can take you away,
but
you should sign this first.
(Confession Letter)
Confession letter?
All the above things
were done by me alone
and have nothing to do with others.
Rong Xiu.
So that's why you came to see me.
The general is back.
He is a ruthless killer
on the battlefield.
If he knows about this,
he won't let us off.
I am your husband.
Save me.
Please save me.
In the past,
you just thought of
your own glory and wealth.
Now you are only
thinking of your own safety.
Have you ever thought about me
for a bit?
I will not be so silly again.
Today,
you must sign it
whether you want to or not.
I will sign it.
Catch her!
Let me go!
Take her back.
General,
this is Xue Lingyi's confession letter.
All the crimes listed here
were committed by her alone.
She's your wife.
What does her wrongdoing
have to do with me?
She admitted it herself.
She maliciously plotted against
the biological mother of Yu.
What?
Yu's biological mother is so pitiful.
It was Xue Lingyi
who proposed to take
the child from his biological mother,
in order to secure
her position in this mansion.
It was she who drugged that woman.
And it was she who wanted that woman
to be dead.
All her crimes
are clearly listed in the paper.
She is the culprit.
The crimes were committed by her.
You are really venomous!
Evildoer!
You set me up!
Aunt,
with such a wife,
I am not worthy to raise Yu anymore.
Aunt, may I burden you
to raise
the child
for me?
Alright,
it will be done as you said.
But are you really going to let Yu
have such an evil mother nominally?
General.
You're right.
Xue Lingyi is
unforgivable.
Today, I will divorce her.
Get me
a divorce letter!
Bring me one!
Divorce letter!
Someone!
Someone, get her out of here.
From today on,
she no longer has any relationship
with our family.
(Divorce Letter)
♪Drunk in the twilight of the 38th year♪
♪Time paints the branches yellow.
Let's have our farewell♪
♪Awake in the height
of summer of the 38th year♪
♪The rain is ticking into my youth♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
The past still lingers♪
♪I am waiting for you
in the fall of the frost♪
♪Dye the silk with bright red♪
♪Memories have rusted♪
♪Years flow like a rainbow.
I'm looking at the Red Tower♪
♪You heave a slight sigh
for the lovers that kept forever apart♪
♪The moonlight has whitened the hair♪
♪In dreams, I have kissed your eyes♪