(Kaede) Because I want a divorce.
I would like to consult with you about this.
<From my sister Kaede
I received a request for divorce defense➡
Hatsu Otokita and Detective Umi Iseya➡
He was in charge of Kaede's daughter➡
There was a reason>
(Kaede) That girl
When you talk back a little ➡
Push it away and put your ear on the corner of the shelf
Hit it hard➡
I lost my hearing for a while.
(Owari) My educational policy is so
Don't you like it?
Who will decide the future path of my child?
It's a parent's responsibility!
(Kaede) Only for that person
Don't give Anna away.
＜Just then, at the beginning
From the Disciplinary Committee➡
Disposition of suspension of business>
(Anna) Mom!
mother!
mother….
(Owari) Anna I'm going home.
(first time)
Something that cannot be undone...
[whimper]
(Sea) Anzu-chan!
Umi-kun...?
I didn't have anything else to do...
I was wondering if you're okay.
I see.
I'm glad you contacted me.
Will you stop by as a family restaurant?
Shall we have some parfait?
My father
I'm keeping an eye on it with GPS.
I can't take a detour.
Is that so?
Eh, then
I can't even go on a date with Tomoki...
Ah, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
I don't feel like that.
sorry.
Hakkun, how are you?
yeah~….
Well, I'm fine.
I see.
But➡
In the life with An-chan
Because I'm used to it.
Me too, for the first time somehow➡
I guess it's a bit darker.
I see.
Yeah.
Umi-kun.
yeah?
It's nothing.
It's okay if you don't have anything special to do.
Please contact me again.
Me too for the first time➡
Always about Anzu-chan
Because I think so.
Yeah.
bye bye.
[Smartphone dial tone]
[Smartphone vibration sound]
(♪〜)
[Sound of knocking on door]
I met An-chan.
(♪〜)
I don't feel like doing anything
I understand, though➡
(♪〜)
I need to eat some.
Leave me alone.
(♪〜)
I'll leave it there.
(Kaede) First Yes.
Open it.
Isn't it nice?
I went to many shops.
Because I looked for it.
joy as always
You're the kind of person who doesn't show it to your face.
The tie, of course, by myself.
Now you can tighten it, right?
no.
Huh?
So today is special, right?
Huh? Why?
It's special!
yes.
The tie is
I can't tighten it properly➡
It's a popular point.
If I can find someone I like someday
Have it tightened.
Yeah.
yes.
Yes, yes.
yes!
Over there, over there.
Ah….
Yeah! Feels good.
first time.
I think being a lawyer is a calling.
picture?
can help people in need
What a job➡
It's so cool!
When my sister says something➡
It's light, isn't it? [laughs]
But➡
At first, it's easy to feel other people's pain➡
I'm a little worried though.
To those who asked me for the first time
Please answer honestly.
Even if you don't say that
I understand.
Okay.
(Kaede's voice) Congratulations on your opening!
(♪〜)
good morning.
Sorry about yesterday.
What do you mean?
(♪〜)
What happened when I opened my office?
Remember me.
I became independent in my mid-20s.
People around me say it's reckless➡
That's what I was told.
Yeah.
But at times like that➡
In my sister's words
I was supported.
I think being a lawyer is a calling.
Hey.
But my sister also has no basis for such a thing.
I don't think it was.
But at that time, like that
For what you said.
I thought that might be the case.
What are the words of a loved one➡
What gives me more power than words
Yes, there is.
That's why I will continue to be your sister.
I have to live my life without shame.
(♪〜)
Anzu-chan, are you okay?
I liked this➡
I'm trying to give it as a present
That's what I was thinking.
Radio) (Kaede's voice) First time.
Radio) I am➡
very soon
I will disappear from this world.
So➡
My only regret➡
About Anna➡
I would like to entrust it to you for the first time.
This is➡
Your sister's will?
Radio) After I’m gone ➡
Leaving Anna in Owari
I'm not worried.
That person is
If there's something you don't like➡
It can be high-pressure at times.
Every time, I protected Anna.
But even if I want to get divorced ➡
Because that person is an expert➡
It's difficult to get custody
I knew it➡
There was nothing I could do.
that's why….
I➡
The family I couldn't give to you➡
Could you make one for me?
To that child➡
Peace of mind for your family.
Warmth.
radio) give it to me
Can I have it?
radio) to the cloud
It will be advantageous for divorce➡
I have left evidence.
In case something happens to me➡
I want you to see that.
Your sister is➡
Anzu-chan
You wanted to ask us.
Yeah.
But I can't do anything as it is now.
Yeah….
If➡
While your sister is still alive➡
What if we were officially divorced?
Then the story will change.
After the divorce was finalized, the parent passed away➡
The other parent➡
I'm not suitable as a guardian.
If certified➡
It should be possible to move it away from Owari.
Not suitable as a guardian...
But to certify
It must be quite difficult.
Even if it's difficult➡
This is your first time being close to a client, right?
(♪〜)
What I can do for Anna...
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
Anzu-chan
Even though I was injured like this➡
Did you know the first time?
Ah, when I went to visit you at the hospital
I heard it.
Then more
I wish you would tell me sooner.
Listen, what are you going to do?
There's nothing you can do about it.
I'll protect An-chan.
Children are in a better position than me.
Raising your hand to the weak➡
no matter what the reason is
There's no way I'll forgive you.
I know that, but
Legally, you can't do anything.
They said it would be fine if I took custody away...
It's not easy.
Recently➡
Between parents and grandparents➡
fight for child custody
There was a precedent.
The high court also said that grandparents
I wish I could have been the custodian➡
The Supreme Court denied that
After that➡
This Supreme Court decision
It has become the standard.
Eh, that's it...
Well then, that's what it means, right?
Even relatives
Does that mean I can't become a guardian?
Ah.
[Intercom sound]
(Owari) You guys, Anna
It must be hiding!
yes?
You understand, right?
Something like taking someone away without permission...
Anna isn't there.
At a time like this
Haven't you come back?
Let me confirm.
(♪〜)
(Tomoki) Yes.
(Anna) Fine, eat it all by yourself.
If you don't eat, you won't feel well.
I'm not feeling well.
Good.
(First/Umi/Anna) Itadakimasu.
(First time) So-so I guess it's so-so.
(Umi/Anna) Yay!
You're Umi-kun's assistant today, right?
It's work.
(Sea) Hey!
hey~!
What's the point?
What method?
Hey, what kind of method?
Look behind the sea
Are you sure you're using the wrong garbage?
(♪〜)[Twinkle Twinkle Stars]
(♪〜)
Yay!
Mom died.
Do you feel lonely?➡
I don't really understand.
I'm still in the hospital➡
When you go to the hospital➡
I feel like I'll be able to meet you.
It's Tomokki.
Because my mother is not here➡
Even if I don't want to go home
No.
When I'm with my dad
It makes me nervous.
Isn't that so?
me and grandma
We live together, right?
And my grandma is kind➡
Have you ever been nervous?
That's right.
That's nice...
Mr. Lin!
(Hayashi) Ah!
My male classmates too
It seems like he hasn't come home.
Apparently the two are together
I wonder if there is.
Could that be?
Are you Tomoki-kun?
(Hayashi) Ah.
Is this a secret base?
What is a secret base?
Tomoki-kun's friend at the secret base
Could I ask you the location?
(Hayashi) It's a secret base. Yes.
Anzu-chan!
Anzu-chan?
Anzu-chan, are you there?
Anzu-chan!
Umi-kun?
Eh, An-chan?
Anzu-chan! ?
Huh, are you really okay?
Are you injured?
Good, really good.
Thank you for being by my side➡
Thank you.
Are you both okay?
Doesn't it really hurt?
Are you really okay?
(Owari) Anna!
(Owari) causing trouble to those around you
What were you thinking!
Look! Apologize to your teacher!
sorry….
(Owari) Hey, everyone!
I didn't have to apologize to you so violently
Okay! He himself is the best...
(Owari) Outsiders, shut up!
Mr. Owari!
(Owari) Who are that child's parents?
(Hayashi) With grandmother
We live together.
He's old, so I'll take him home.
I'm supposed to send it to you.
(Owari) Take care of your children properly
Because it is a family that cannot be managed➡
Become a child without common sense!
There's no way to say that!
(Owari) Let's go!
It's not possible...
Anzu-chan, I want to run away from home
You hated living with your father.
I was being assaulted like that.
Contact during this time
It was an SOS after all.
Somehow, An-chan was taken from Owari.
Can't you separate me?
Custody is in Owari➡
If Owari
Even if you file for divorce after death➡
Blood relationship with the child
It's impossible because it doesn't change.
Yeah…
I wonder what An-chan wants to do.
Tell your sister about Hatsu and Anzu.
He asked me to help him.
What do you think about that bow tie?
I guess it sent a message.
I'm going to see Owari.
It is difficult to appoint a guardian.
I know, but➡
There's no way things can stay like this.
(Owari) Last night you
I got involved.
(First time) No.
I can't believe you're coming to visit my office.
That's rare.
What are the requirements?
I'm talking about Anna.
Oh.
My sister asked me to do it.
Please protect Anna.
She said something strange.
I have a father, so why come to you?
I wonder if he said that?
My sister is.
Anna's future
I was worried.
that's why
When you can't take care of yourself ➡
He entrusted Anna to me.
Anna's designated guardian
I'm thinking of filing a complaint.
I was wondering what you were going to say.
Is that so?
Even though I am under restraint➡
If you are also a member of the legal profession➡
If you fight it in court
There is no way such a claim would hold true➡
You know.
My sister is➡
He was someone I could always rely on.
The only person who understands me➡
When things don't go well with those around you
My sister always helped me.
I am➡
I loved my sister.
I owe so much to you➡
As you know➡
My sister is patronizing about things like that.
That's not my personality.
And yet➡
When I realized I was dying ➡
Say you owe me something
It was my first time asking for a favor.
(♪〜)
What do you want to say?
To that extent➡
(♪〜)
About Anna
I was worried.
(♪〜)
I can't talk to my sister anymore.
But the feeling of regret
I am receiving it.
(♪〜)
I am aware that it is difficult➡
I'm going to fight you.
(♪〜)
“Delivering a delicious divorce”
I want to see you again.
Latest episode on TVer.
What on Hulu?
All episodes now available!