(First time) I am here for you.
I will protect you.
＜Partners both in public and private life＞
<To be legally bound
The two of us are incomparable➡
someone who suffers from a partner's betrayal
Let's be of help➡
team up
Undertook divorce defense
I will request 100 million yen in compensation.
<The behind-the-scenes look of the popular host➡
Revealed during live broadcast and released to the public>
(Aono) Everything is
It's for the client's happiness.
If you are disposed of for that reason➡
accept it patiently
I'm ready.
<That unconventional defense is
Controversial>
(Owari) Otokita's first.
He's an unrepentant man.
(Girl) Dad!
Huh?
(Sea) Huh?
<In front of those two invincible people
A girl appears>
[Train passing sound]
[Sound of car door opening and closing]
(Tatsuya) Okay.
Haa, I've arrived. I've arrived.
[Smartphone shutter sound]
(♪〜)
(Aono) What about Ayaka?
Did they know about us?
(Ayaka) Um... on TV...
I was a fan of Mao, so...
(Aono) TV broadcast! (Ayaka) Yes.
(Aono) That's pretty good.
It was impressive!
Hey?
(Aono) Hey
It's better not to get nervous➡
I think it will be difficult➡
My Otokita
This is normal operation➡
Don't worry about it.
(Aono) Well, Ayaka-san➡
From Miyagi on the occasion of marriage
So you came to Tokyo?
(Ayaka) Yes, three years ago.
(Aono) How do you like it? Tokyo.
(Ayaka) I can't get used to it... [laughs]
(Aono) That’s right!
Miyagi: That's a great place!
(Aono) Speaking of Miyagi?
Zunda!
(Aono) Hey.
Eh...I found out about my husband's affair➡
ask for compensation
Because I want to get a divorce➡
Is that okay?
(Ayaka) Yes.
(Aono) Currently with my husband
What about living separately?
(Ayaka) Huh? (Aono) Ah.
As soon as I found out about the act of infidelity
There are many people who are separated.
(Ayaka) Is that so?
No, we are.
(Aono) Well then, Ayaka-san.
In what situation?
your husband's infidelity
Did they know?
(Ayaka) That's...
(Ayaka) Somehow.
(Aono) Somehow?
Who is your partner?
(Ayaka) I'm a friend.
Someone who lives nearby.
(Aono) Ah, are you a friend?
Is that so?
Do you have any proof?
(Ayaka) Yes.
(Ayaka) Can this be evidence?
take a photo
I'm not very good at it.
(Aono) This is your husband.
This is my friend.
(Ayaka) Yes. (Aono) Ki~~!
(Aono) What happened?
home. I'll keep it here.
(Ayaka) Please.
(Aono) Huh...
(Aono) This time
It doesn't seem like it's complicated either➡
Please proceed slowly.
First time!
♪The beginning of the first Pyon Kichitaro~
yeah? Do you understand? First time.
Yellow card.
It's accumulating!
a little bit~!
Something that goes outside the rules
Please don't do that.
Actually yesterday...
no.
It'll come out for a while.
Sigh….
a little bit!
△○※△×！
[Phone ringtone]
Elder Sister….
Shit, no matter how much you spend, it won't come out.
(Anna) Mother
Because I'm in the hospital now.
hospitalization! ?
here you are.
Yeah.
So go to Hakkun's place➡
If you call me "dad"
He said he would let me into the room➡
That's what I said.
Hakkun. Hakkun?
Then I'll start too
Can I call you Hakkun?
Hey really. that….
Until mom leaves the hospital➡
At Hakkun's house
I told her to spend some time.
Even if your mother is in the hospital
Your father is there, right?
Well, that's fine!
Rely on Hakkun
Because you came.
Hey?
What about Anna? from everyone
What is it called?
My friends call me Anzu-chan.
Anzu-chan.
Then I'll call you An-chan too!
Because we're friends.
What is a friend?
nice to meet you!
[laughter]
[talking voice]
(Kaede) Ah, first time!
copper? Are you getting along well with him?
Is it Umi-kun?
We live together, right?
Ah.
That would be great.
Anna too, I'm going to meet Umi-kun.
I was looking forward to it.
cool!
There really are detectives out there.
Hehehe… [lol]
Hey, can I touch this?
Ah, okay. But.
Because those are special glasses.
Don't tell your friends.
special?
Yeah.
Jaja!
Wow, that's amazing!
yes.
Huh?
You can see it, right?
I feel like a detective!
Anzu-chan.
Do you want to be a detective?
Yeah!
Hehehe… [lol]
Before bringing Anna
I wish you could just contact me.
(Kaede) Then you'll probably refuse anyway.
Say you're busy with work.
It's not me.
You have a husband, right?
Ah! Hey, do you remember?
First bedwetting problem
Because it won't heal easily➡
I wake you up like every night
You took me to the bathroom.
Huh?
The same goes for school plays.
When I did North Wind and the Sun➡
The feeling of the north wind
Just because you don't understand, resist it➡
The play stopped➡
me on stage
Toward the traveler instead of the first time➡
Pew! hand
There were times when the wind blew.
What did you say?
First of all, I owe you something.
That's why even if you suddenly say that.
What about elementary school?
I'm contacting my homeroom teacher.
While I was in the hospital
My younger brother will take care of me➡
for a while
Please let me study at home.
Talk to me like that...
Later.
Is there one more thing I would like to ask you?
what?
Because I want a divorce
I would like to consult with you about this.
Huh?
Since when is things not going well?
Since when...
Well, maybe since I got married.
Then why sooner?
Didn't you consult me?
It's my problem.
Let's rely on the first time
Because I didn't think so.
Then why now...?
[Smartphone vibration sound]
when I have time
Come again.
I will explain in detail at that time.
When can I leave the hospital?
Hehehe...right away.
I heard it from my mother.
I've been saying Hakkun since I was little.
He loves keema curry.
Ah, that's right.
If you eat this
It makes me feel better.
And there aren't that many tomatoes.
Don't crush it too much➡
That seems to be the point.
Ha~ I heard good things!
Teach me that!
Okay.
Thank you.
Ah, welcome back.
welcome home!
I'm home.
Anzu-chan.
Yeah?
There are canned tomatoes on the shelf in the hallway.
It's in there➡
Can you bring it for me?
yes.
Thank you.
What about your sister? Did we meet?
Ah.
Even if it feels like I'm falling asleep
Because there wasn't ➡
You'll be discharged from the hospital soon.
various
It might cause trouble though.
There's no such thing.
Anzu-chan is a good girl.
Something suddenly happened to the child.
I'm glad it looks like it's done.
Who is your sister's husband?
What kind of person are you?
He's in the same industry as me...
The type you don't like?
Well.
I see.
Where is the sea?
Huh? Haven't you found it? Anzu-chan
Wait a minute.
Good luck.
(All) Itadakimasu.
copper?
Well, well… well, I guess.
Yay!
(Aono) Phew...
[Phone ringtone]
Yes, yes.
Yes yes.
This is from Ayaka Nimura.
Moshi Moshi has been replaced.
Phone) (Ayaka) I'm sorry, teacher.
Not the teacher, but Otokita.
(Ayaka) I'm sorry. that….
The photo I showed you yesterday
Will it serve as evidence?
yes?
Is the photo usable?
Please check...
"Check"?
What do you mean?
(Ayaka) Ah...no, I'm sorry.
It's nothing.
excuse me.
[Sound of phone being disconnected]
(Aono) What did you do?
"Please check if you can use photographic evidence."
Apparently someone told me that.
What do you mean?
It's just as the word says.
Ah, sure➡
At that time, I just felt nervous.
I thought so.
I felt like I couldn't see my true feelings.
Does she really want to break up with him?
Or...
Is there another reason?
Oh! It's a mystery.
[Door opening/closing sound]
(Tatsuya) I'm home.
(Ayaka) Welcome back, you were quick.
(Tatsuya) Huh...
I've been busy with work lately.
That's why I was late because I was working overtime all the time.
(Ayaka) Not that I...
sorry.
(Tatsuya) Huh.
I don't have to make dinner separately.
(Ayaka) Huh?
(Tatsuya) Ah, um...
I can't read when it's time to go home.
Having to wait is also a burden.
Yeah.
Okay, come on!
ray!
ray! nice!
Yes, will you call me?
Yeah!
Hey! Good.
Next time with a cute duvet cover
I guess I should buy it.
It's totally okay.
Because if you close your eyes, it's the same thing.
Don't say adult-like things.
But that's it
You don't have to hold back.
Yeah.
good night.
I'll erase it.
Thank you.
yeah?
No, I'm talking about Anna.
Hehe...[lol] Gratitude is watery.
But➡
Sleeping alone in a large bed
I feel sorry for her.
Ah, that's right
Lay out the futons here➡
Why don't you sleep like a river?
Anzu-chan was asked to sleep in the middle.
No, no, that's fine.
Just sleep between me
I think you'll feel safe.
Is that what it is?
That's how it is hahaha... [lol]
(Owari) Hatsu-kun.
Mr. Owari.
long time no see.
You...
Are you planning to quit? A lawyer.
my brother-in-law
If you're causing trouble again➡
Will report one by one
I hope you have friends.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
oh yeah
Isn't Anna causing trouble?
I'm here to take care of my daughter.
I can't believe I asked Hatsu-kun.
I sometimes think about my wife
There are times when I don't understand.
(Kaede) Because I want a divorce.
I would like to consult with you about this.
Anna is
I will take care of it responsibly➡
Don't worry.
Yeah.
You'll get caught after all, right?
what happened?
It's about work.
Don't look at it.
Go eat ice cream over there.
Well, well, well.
Anzu-chan.
yeah?
This is a photo I took secretly.
Yeah.
Is there something you are concerned about?
Hidden camera?
Yeah.
yeah~….
Yeah….
You don't understand. It's okay.
Isn't this person smiling?
Huh?
Oh...it might be worth looking into.
(Ocean) Change the saturation here.
If you stop by...
(First time) Oh, I'm sure you're smiling.
towards the camera
That means you're smiling➡
Looking at the camera wasn't a coincidence
It turns out to be true.
As expected! He's just my assistant.
(Anna) Hehehe… [lol]
Oh no!
This stinks.
Yeah.
So it's my turn.
Yeah yeah.
Eh, when did you become an assistant?
Boom!
For the first time, I was with An-chan.
I'm sure he'll get angry if he finds out.
it's okay
After all, he's Kai-kun's assistant.
good?
Anzu’s work today➡
Studying next to me.
yes! Boom!
Hahaha… [lol]
(Staff) Welcome.
Please take a seat that is available.
[Sound of door opening]
(Clerk) Welcome.
(Mika) At the meeting.
At this timing?
Meet a cheating partner.
What do you mean?
I wonder what they're talking about...
How about sitting closer?
That's it
The other person will see your face.
The detective should keep a low profile while being followed.
I have to.
Hmm.
The problem is➡
Where should I put this thing?
Eavesdropping device?
Ah! I had an idea.
Huh?
(Anna) Okay.
I'm coming.
this child
I seem to like this plant.
Radio) (Mika) It's bothering me.
Be bold...!
Radio) (Mika) means ➡
The lawyer is
That photo is proof➡
clearly
You mean you didn't say that?
(Ayaka) But
He accepted it➡
perhaps
I think it's okay...
Radio) (Mika) Maybe?
Radio) It's unreliable.
Umi-kun, are you bitter?
Radio) (Ayaka) I'm sorry.
Do you want to add sugar?
Are you okay.
(Radio) (Mika) If that photo isn't good enough.
(Mika) Do you have time after this?
There is, right? (Ayaka) Huh?
(Mika) More conclusive evidence
I'll let you take a picture.
I'll call you after this➡
Hide in the closet.
(Ayaka) Who are you calling?
[Smartphone vibration sound]
(Mika) That's already decided.
(Mika) He said he could come after this.
your husband.
Hehehe… [lol]
this is….
It's just a cheating investigation
I might not finish it.
Hahaha… [lol]
(♪〜)
(Aono) Yes, yes, ah~
Thank you for your help.
(♪〜)
Ha! Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa! ! !
First time!
Mr. Hatsu has finally arrived!
(♪〜)
"Delivering a delicious divorce"
The latest episode is available for free on TVer!
Be sure to add it to your favorites!