Keep up.
Come with me.
Come on.
Be careful here.
If we let Jiang Yuan take the mine,
and Mr. Yu Retires,
can the two of us even stay in Dongping?
Will we still have good days?
This is not betrayal.
It's finding a way for us to survive.
[In the Name of Justice]
[Episode 22]
See?
What did I tell you?
Uncle,
it's late,
what are you waiting for here?
For you, kid.
I knew you're gonna do this.
They just sealed this place
earlier today.
What, you're ripping it off again?
Yeah, I'm ripping it off.
How else do we make money?
How do we get back to work?
How do we pay off the loans
and interest?
That's none of your concern.
Just don't break the seal!
Listen to me,
if you tear it off again,
the cops will come for you.
Cops?
Then let them take me.
Our life is already miserable,
what's there to fear?
Let them take me in,
that'd make things easier.
I miss my father. I'll go see him.
Enough, stop this childish act.
Alright, now,
dismiss, go home.
We're not working today.
Chao,
keep what your uncle said
in mind.
Think about it.
Fine.
You two are the elders.
You're the grown-ups.
I'm just a kid.
I'll listen to you.
I'll go back to sleep.
Go on.
Uncle,
I haven't paid
Chen Hui and the others yet.
Can you take care of that?
Hui,
you saw what happened.
I can't pay you.
Ask my uncle for it.
Chao…
Ask my uncle!
Mr. Wan,
can you settle the wages
for us?
Yeah, we want our wages.
Settle what? Nonsense.
Then let us work,
or pay us.
Let us work!
Chao said
once work resumes, we can make money.
Work!
We'll earn it ourselves.
Okay?
Mr. Wan…
Fine, do whatever you want!
Okay, let's get to work!
Thank you, Mr. Wan.
You go down with them.
Go.
Stop!
Move.
Shine the light over here.
Okay.
[May 15
SEALED]
Slow down, Mr. Wan.
Go, let's go.
Go.
Keep up.
Come on…
Watch it.
What are you smacking your lips at?
Get that seal back on
exactly the way it was.
You are out of your mind.
Screw it.
For three years,
we've been working our asses off
for Jiang Yuan.
Isn't Wan Chao illegally mining?
If a mining accident happens…
Jiang Yuan can forget about
that judicial auction.
This could cost lives.
Haven't enough people died already?
I'd rather destroy this mine myself
than let it end up
in Jiang Yuan's hands.
Are you crazy?
Do you know what this would lead to?
What?
Can't think straight now?
My mind has never been
as clear as it is now.
Long.
This comes at too high a cost.
Yes, I know
that you want to stop the mine
from going to auction.
You don't want this mine
to end up in Jiang Yuan's hands.
I know all that.
But there are many ways to do it.
Not just this one.
If we do this,
the consequences can be really bad.
At that time,
how would Mr. Yu think?
Think about it.
Can we turn our backs
on him?
All these years,
we've followed his every word.
Whatever he told us to do, we did it.
Would Tianlong Company
be where it is today
without him?
Now you can have
all the food or drinks you want,
life's good, right?
True,
these three years,
he and Jiang Yuan were
secretly planning the whole mining deal,
this and that.
Didn't bring us in.
I believe
he must have his reasons.
Three years.
He plotted for three years.
And I've fought for him for three years.
Three years of crime.
You and I
did all the dirtiest, hardest jobs.
Now it's harvest time.
And then Jiang Yuan shows up,
and Mr. Yu Just lets him
take our fruits.
Do you think it's fair?
What we've done is capital crimes.
Do you understand?
Wan Hai is not guilty!
We're not a criminal organization!
- This is all slander!
- My father isn't a criminal!
We were framed!
Wang Yu!
Help!
Defendant Wan Hai,
for multiple crimes,
is sentenced to
ten years and ten months.
Right,
capital crime.
If Mr. Yu hadn't
taken me in back then,
who knows
where I'd have died by now?
So from that day on,
I swore
I'd follow him.
I'd do
whatever he says.
Whoever he tells me to mess with,
I'd do it.
If he asks me to die,
I'd still do it with no fear.
You really think so?
Yeah.
Bro,
I got on my knees and begged him
to let you stay.
Come help!
There's a coal thief!
Run!
[25 Years Ago]
I got you now!
Run…
Don't hit me!
I dare you…
- I'm sorry!
- Thief!
Thief!
You dare steal from us?
I… I'm sorry.
Now you're sorry?
Too late!
Where are you from?
Where's your family?
I don't have one.
Why not?
My dad's dead.
My mom…
I don't know where she went.
Enough.
Don't waste your breath on him.
Just take him to the police.
Make the call.
Didn't you hear me?
Mr. Yu,
can we let him stay?
Stay?
He's a thief.
You want him to stay?
Mr. Yu,
I'll watch him.
I'll make sure
he'll never
steal again.
Get him cleaned up.
Yes.
I keep that in my heart.
What do you mean?
You want me
to choose
between you
and Mr. Yu?
Is that what you mean?
Exactly.
Captain Liu…!
We're not mining!
The seal's still on!
Wan Chao.
Who are you?
You don't need to know.
You know this is illegal, right?
Stop it now!
Who do you think you are
to tell me what to do?
Wait a minute!
Wait!
Get down there and bring the workers up!
Yes!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm telling you,
I've already called the cops!
They'll be here any minute!
Get the hell out,
or you'll all go to jail!
Bro.
It'll be a mess if the cops come.
Calm down.
Chill out.
Bro…
Calm down.
- I dare you!
- Just go.
Go.
Chao.
Chao, are you okay?
Uncle,
you can't call the police.
We're illegally mining.
Silly boy, would I really call them?
If I hadn't said that,
would they have left?
It hurts.
Bro.
Think about it.
Don't you feel like
Mr. Yu's not thinking straight anymore?
Back then,
if I hadn't knocked him out,
let you carry him away,
and I went to jail for him instead,
would he even have had all this now?
Would he have had this mine?
This feels amazing!
Mr. Yu, I love you!
Slow down.
Mr. Yu!
Let's go!
Slow down.
It's really different
to drive after a few drinks.
He's totally drunk.
But you're not.
Speed up.
Pass him.
Slow down…
Brake!
Mr. Yu, feeling good?
Slow down…!
Mr. Yu…
what now?
Get off.
Go over there.
Hurry up.
Come, help him.
Get him over there.
Out.
Hurry up.
Stop crying!
Get in there.
Uncle Yu,
what do we do, Uncle Yu?
Don't cry.
Uncle Yu.
Stop crying! Stop!
Mr. Yu, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
She's dead. You'll go to jail!
Let me take the fall!
I'll do time for it!
Let me!
Get out of here!
Pull him out, quick!
Mr. Yu, you can't take the fall for this!
Go away!
Come with me!
Leave it!
Don't be angry.
Let go of me!
Are you crazy?
He won't blame us.
This means real prison time.
Stay out of it!
Let me take the fall!
I'll take it!
Get him in the car, hurry!
Hurry.
This phone
is my life.
Keep it safe for me
until I get out.
Give me your phone!
Go…
Are you serious…?
Go!
Hurry!
Pull yourself together!
I was the one driving,
not you!
Yes…
It was you. You hit her.
I didn't kill anyone.
You killed her.
I didn't kill her.
I didn't kill anyone.
I was in a car accident.
Did I go to jail for Mr. Yu?
I did it for Jiang Yuan, that bastard!
Haven't I done enough?
Long,
how did it come to this
between us and Mr. Yu?
If we really do it,
we're done with him.
It's over.
There's no going back.
We can't go back anyway.
I finally see it now.
We're just servants
to him.
We have been his loyal servants
for twenty years.
I want to be myself now.
You call that being yourself?
You're being an ingrate.
So what?
What else can I do?
Bro,
think about it.
If we let Jiang Yuan take the mine,
and Mr. Yu retires,
can the two of us even stay in Dongping?
You have a waste treatment plant.
I have Tianlong Company.
But will we still have good days?
This is not betrayal.
It's finding a way for us to survive.
[Serve the People]
[Dongping Municipal
People's Procuratorate]
Who are you here to see?
Prosecutor-general Li Renjun.
Okay.
Wang Yu, right?
This way, please.
Hello.
Hello…
Mr. Li.
Isn't this Mr. Li?
Our hero.
Thank you
for getting rid of a bully
for Dongping.
If it weren't for you,
that Freight Hub would've
been long gone from my hands.
So…
why do you
want to see me?
Let me introduce,
this is Prosecutor-General Li Renjun
of Dongping Municipal
People's Procuratorate.
I am Guan Wenbo.
You're Wang Yu, former manager
of Wanchuan
Storage & Transportation Group,
right?
Yes.
Wait, why are you recording this?
So formal.
Isn't the case closed already?
It's part of our procedure.
Which case?
Which one could it be?
The Wan Hai case.
We asked you here today
mainly to ask about your connection
with people from Tianlong Company.
Tianlong Company? Yeah.
Isn't their
general counsel Cheng Zijian?
Isn't he
your brother-in-law?
Are you close?
Sort of.
We've done business together.
Over time, of course we got familiar.
Besides, in Dongping,
if you don't know about the relationship
between Cheng Zijian
and the prosecutor-general,
how can you even survive
in this city, right?
Tell us about your interactions.
What…
what interactions?
We just…
do business.
He came to buy, and I sold.
Is that… is that a crime now?
When was it?
That was
years ago.
About three years.
At that time,
three years ago,
wasn't Wan Hai the owner
of the Freight Hub?
Why would they come to you
instead of the actual owner?
Well,
because I was the one
managing the hub.
I knew the business.
Isn't a buyout
just a deal?
If the price is right, it gets done.
That Freight Hub…
Wan Hai locked you up and beat you
until you agreed to sell it to him
at a low price.
So why did you
still choose to work for him?
Wait,
what are you getting at here?
Let me lay it out for you.
The first person who reported
Wan Hai's a gangster
was you.
The one who provided
the evidence against him,
also you.
Am I right?
And you testified in court.
After Wan Hai got convicted,
the biggest beneficiary was still you.
Now the Freight Hub
is back in your hands.
The facts are clear.
Here is the procuratorate.
You are not called in
for no reason.
We're already well aware
that you couldn't have done this alone.
Someone in the system helped you.
Someone made introductions.
Someone provided the money.
Someone did the dirty work.
So, Wang Yu, we called you in,
because we want you to come clean.
This is your chance.
But chances,
once missed, are gone for good.
If we find out everything ourselves,
you won't be sitting here
having a nice conversation like this.
Understand?
Understand what?
What do you want?
And you're filming this, for what?
Trying to overturn the case?
I'm the whistleblower.
I reported him for
being in organized crime.
Is this how you treat whistleblowers?
You're turning this back on me?
Accusing me?
Listen, Li…
Mr. Li,
can you say Wan Hai isn't a gangster?
Do you have evidence?
You can keep me here if you have proof.
Wang Yu.
If you don't, I'm leaving.
You're in the procuratorate,
watch your tone.
So what?
I'm in the procuratorate, so?
You wanna question me,
show me the proof.
Do you have any?
Bye-bye.
Can I go now?
Wang Yu!
Bye-bye.
Yang Guang.
Yes!
Zhou Haiyi
Tian Bazhao.
Yes!
- Li Ping.
- Yes!
Xiong Erqiang.
Song Weiqin.
Yes!
Get ready to go down.
Okay.
Come with me.
Come.
Be careful here.
Keep up…
Have some good food.
Chen Shenglong.
Get Xiong back here.
I can't cover for your mess this time.
Have you thought about the consequences?
You could kill someone!
He's not answering my calls.
You call him.
Tell him to stop right now.
"Three violations" refers to
unsafe operations,
unauthorized instructions,
and breaking labor rules.
Call him, or I'll kill you.
Xiong
It's already started.
Mr. Sun,
send it to Captain Jiang now,
tell him to move immediately.
Or it will be too late. Hurry.
You're unbelievable.
[May 16 19:35
Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
[May 16 19:36
[May 16 19:37
Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
Chao.
Something's wrong, Chao.
Wake up.
Something's wrong!
I was…. Who is it?
Me!
Uncle…
The lifting cage fell down.
The cage that takes workers down
into the mine just fell.
How did it happen?
I have no idea!
Anyone in it?
Yes, a dozen of them.
Then go rescue them!
Calm down. Listen to me.
I've called the cops,
they'll be here soon.
We still have to rescue them!
Calm down!
Listen to me!
You're the legal representative.
If anyone dies,
you'll be held responsible.
You might end up in prison!
I already told Wan Hong to come over.
We've got this.
You leave now.
Or when the police get here,
you won't be able to.
Go, hurry.
Hurry.
Hang on.
Take the back roads.
Don't go on the main road.
Go!
Officer, up there!
Hurry up.
Jin,
tell the Control Center
we've arrived at the scene.
Copy.
Yang Jing,
lead the team.
Take control of the scene.
Okay.
Keep up.
Hurry.
This way.
Officer,
hurry up, here.
- Police.
- Hurry up.
Hurry!
Over here.
Move!
Help rescue the injured.
Jin, Yang Jing,
find the person in charge.
Yes, sir.
Control Center…
Call 120 to the site immediately!
Hurry!
Come on.
Haven't had time to ask,
did you return that house?
What do you want to be when you grow up?
Study law. Become a prosecutor.
Renjun,
your son says he wants to study law
and be a prosecutor one day.
Hear that?
You can't study that.
Look at your dad, can't stop
thinking about cases even at home.
- Learn from Auntie.
- Go wash your hands.
Be a journalist.
Come on.
You seem distracted. What's wrong?
Ah…
nothing.
These two days,
I'm a bit out of it.
Keep thinking about
when I first joined
the Municipal Procuratorate.
Back then,
I swore
I'd become the prosecutor-general.
It's been over a decade,
now that it's finally happened,
I feel kind of empty inside.
You're just nervous.
You'll be fine in a bit.
Auntie, let's eat.
Okay.
Come on.
Please take your seat.
Here.
The seat of honor.
Sitting here makes me feel
ten years older.
Where's the kid?
Well, you're the head of the family.
Actually, we're just
having dinner together
as a family.
No need for this fancy title.
How could I not?
You've been promoted
to be prosecutor-general
and can't go out drinking
with your coworkers.
We should at least
celebrate properly at home.
Little rituals make life feel special.
Am I right, prosecutor-general's wife?
Stop it.
But it's been a while
since we got together.
Auntie,
say a few words,
then we'll raise our glasses.
Me again?
She always says I sound too official.
Today, I'm just here for the free food.
Um…
Renjun, you say something.
Why don't you return to the house
in Dadu Xishan?
Li Renjun, what's your problem?
Are you still going on about this?
Didn't I tell you?
It's not like we didn't pay for it.
What are you afraid of?
You oversee Tianlong Company
in the development zone.
And I just got promoted.
You can't take that house
at such a steep discount.
You just got appointed,
and you're already lecturing me?
Zijian, you tell him.
Was that price just for me?
Of course not, sister-in-law.
Ms. Lan, Renjun,
they dropped the price
to clear inventory.
Anyone would get the same price.
Hear that?
Same price for anyone,
why can't I buy it?
Anyone else can buy it,
just not us.
Why?
Renjun was right.
Anyone can buy it, except you.
Auntie…
Come on, let's eat.
We asked you to say something good.
Why'd you have to bring that up?
You don't understand. Don't interrupt.
I'm serious.
You've ruined the dinner.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Yes, let's drink.
Sister, don't be mad.
Come on.
Cheers, Renjun.
What's wrong with you?
So annoying.
Hello?
Everyone, make way!
The ambulance's here.
Make way!
Make way.
Everyone, step back.
Let the car through.
Everyone, back down.
Captain An.
How many of you are here?
Thirty people.
What's the situation inside the mine?
The cage fell down.
How many people are down there?
Fifteen, as far as we know.
How many ambulances are on site?
Five, so far.
Not enough. Dispatch more.
OK, Mr. Xu.
Where's the mine manager?
He's helping manage the situation.
- You go help.
- Can the rescue ladder be lowered?
Okay.
No, the mine's too deep.
Rope.
Can we send people down by rope?
Ropes won't reach either.
What's going on?
Wasn't this mine sealed?
They were mining in secret.
- Do you copy?
- Captain Wang.
Mr. Wang is here.
Mr. Wang.
Sir.
Where is the accident site?
Up there.
[Wang Jianning
Party Secretary and Mayor of Dongping]
Send a few people over.
We need more people here.
What's the casualty situation?
Sir,
Wanchuan Mining's
lifting cage at Mine No. 18
was old and poorly maintained,
and the brakes failed,
causing it to fall.
Now fifteen people are down there.
Casualty details are unclear.
But we have immediately
started rescue operations.
Mr. Sun…
The winch is repaired.
The cage's pulled up.
Okay, copy that.
The winch has been repaired.
And the cage has been pulled up.
What about the mine?
Any safety risks?
We've checked.
Everything else is safe,
except for the lifting cage.
Where's the legal representative?
We're still looking.
Find him!
Once found,
- Okay.
- Take immediate control.
OK.
Spare no effort to rescue the people.
Clear out a fast rescue passage.
Be careful.
Careful.
Tell the hospital to be prepared.
Make sure the injured
get treatment immediately.
Yanwu, while rescuing,
organize all departments
to investigate
the cause of the accident.
Gather leads and evidence ASAP.
Determine responsibility quickly.
Yes.
Liu Yun.
You're in charge of
treating and transferring the injured.
Okay.
Comfort the workers' families.
- Yes.
- Help them!
Rescue…
Sir!
Mr. Wang.
Rescue them, sir!
This is the mine's deputy manager,
Wan Hong.
Where's your legal representative?
I don't know.
Sir, please save them.
Go check down there.
They're in there…
Stop yelling here, control him!
Save them!
Director Liu,
what should we do?
What happened?
Why did you go down there secretly?
What should we do?
You've caused a big trouble,
you're going to jail for this.
Director Liu.
I'm currently outside
the gate of Wanchuan Mining,
where the accident happened.
[An Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
Rescue operations are underway…
Good.
What color is this?
Yellow.
Around 7:30 PM on May 16th,
at Wanchuan Mining
in the development zone,
a serious industrial accident occurred.
We've learned that…
Mom, what are you doing?
The blocks all fell over.
Workers were on the lifting cage
going down the mine for work
when the cage suddenly malfunctioned
and fell.
[An Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
Casualty numbers
are still being confirmed.
After the accident,
emergency, police, medical,
- 445310.
- fire departments
and other agencies…
Sit down.
immediately arrived at the scene.
[An Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
Rescue work
is underway in an orderly manner.
Our footage shows
injured people being carried out
one after another.
[An Accident at Wanchuan Mining]
The mine involved
belongs to Wanchuan Mining.
It is known that
before the accident,
the mine should have been shut down.
Bro, this is huge.
The person in charge
was mining without permission,
organizing workers to operate illegally.
How many people will die
because of this?
At the moment,
the cause of the accident
is still under investigation.
Now,
please follow our reporter for details.
Hello?
Mr. Chen.
There's an accident at the mine.
Have you heard?
Hello?
Mr. Chen?
Wan Chao was illegally mining.
It was bound to happen sooner or later.
Then…
who did it?
None of your concern.
Mind your own business.
♪Had it not been for you♪
♪I'd never have known how love feels♪
♪The darker the night,
the brighter the stars shine♪
♪If not for the words you let me hear♪
♪How could I break from chains of fear♪
♪To feel myself rise, then gently fall♪
♪No rest, no peace, no dare♪
♪No dreams, no thoughts,
no confusion or fear♪
♪No fight, no cry, no words to lend♪
♪I owed you nothing in the end♪
♪But still, I thank you♪
♪For blooming my midnights♪
♪Even through roads both rough and wide♪
♪You traced the shape of free inside♪
♪Someone will always hold that grace♪
♪A love that time cannot erase♪
♪And what I once clung to
with all my might♪
♪Now softly lands beyond the light♪
♪No sleep, no rest, no will to try♪
♪No dreams, no thoughts,
no confusion or fear♪
♪No fight, no cry, no words to lend♪
♪But love will bloom in me till the end♪