We've already submitted the application
for the land expropriation rights
in Hongjia Village.
We're planning to
build a battery plant there.
This land
was really allocated to us.
[Land Use Plan of Yuanli Group
New Energy Battery Plant Phase I]
Yuanli.
The boss's name is Jiang Yuan, right?
His father is Jiang Xudong,
Vice Chairman of
Provincial Committee of the CPPCC.
You can't touch the mine,
and definitely not the land.
Is Dongping going to build
two new energy battery factories?
But the only land suitable
for battery factories
is in Hongjia Village.
So I only want Hongjia Village.
We're gonna take
that land.
I want both the mine and the land,
no one can stop me.
[In the Name of Justice]
[Episode 26]
Jiang Hongjun,
no family business,
no rental properties.
Then where
did the 3.23 million in cash
and 28 gold bars come from?
My brother
does business abroad.
It's not safe over there,
so he stores his money in China.
All that money is his,
and it's in his house.
When did I ever say
it was found in your brother's house?
Look.
This is the
3.23 million cash
and 28 gold bars.
And look again.
Look.
Who is this?
My wife.
Your wife?
What is she doing here?
Don't know.
She's signing it.
She admitted
that all of this
belonged to your family.
No denial.
Do you understand?
No way.
That's not right.
We've got more, look.
What is this?
Look at this back view.
Familiar?
Who is it?
I don't know.
Too dark, can't tell.
Mr. Hong.
Who would recognize their own back?
Hold this for me.
I...
Hold it.
See?
Who is it?
It's... me.
Me...
So where is this?
At Wanchuan Mining.
It's... the winch room.
When was this?
It's...
the night
of the accident.
Here's the list of people
we rescued from the cage.
Can you confirm it for me?
Let me see.
The first one is me.
Wait,
there are sixteen people
in our shift going underground.
There are only fifteen on your list.
You sure it's sixteen?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I remember now.
The mute wasn't there.
Mute?
He's not really mute,
just doesn't talk much with us.
He's new here.
Name's Xiong Erqiang.
Do you remember what he looks like?
Thin and tall.
It's dark when we're down there,
I can't clearly see what he looks like.
Xiong Erqiang.
You got filmed, so you admit it.
I asked you many times earlier,
you just wouldn't talk.
What do you mean?
I...
I forgot…
I went to that winch room
to check
if there were any safety hazards.
How did you know
to check the winch room?
Well, we got a report
saying the cause of that accident was
the cage's
fall.
And there were casualties.
So you graduated in
mine electromechanics?
No, I didn't.
But with my experience...
In all your years in the Police,
how many mine accidents
have you handled?
None.
But this is a mining area,
it's common sense for us.
It's common sense for you.
Then that night,
why were you the only one
who went there,
while all the other officers
were at the primary scene?
Jiang Hongjun.
I'm asking you
to be honest with me
and tell me clearly
what exactly you were doing
alone
in that winch room
on the night of the mine accident.
I...
I went to the...
winch room,
took a wrench
and screwed the bolt
that caused the accident
back in place.
Was it your idea to go?
No, absolutely not.
The leader told me to do it.
Which leader?
Mr. Sun.
Full name of Mr. Sun, please.
Sun Fei,
Deputy Director
of the Development Zone Sub-Bureau
of Dongping
Public Security Bureau.
So, on the night of the mine accident,
under Sun Fei's instruction,
you went alone into the winch room,
restored the bolt,
tampered with the evidence,
and altered the facts,
causing the accident
to be categorized
as a work safety issue,
and thereby changing the nature
of the entire case?
Is all of that
true?
Yes.
True.
Mr. Sun, according to the results
of technical surveillance,
the last place Captain Jiang appeared
in Dongping
was near Anning Street,
close to his daughter's school.
After that, he went off the grid.
An hour later,
he resurfaced
near an old building on the outskirts
of Jiangnan City.
Send me the location.
[Pingshan Development Zone Sub-Bureau]
[Not connected
Boss, cut me some slack.]
[Loading...]
[Unable to start voice call.
The user hasn't added you as a friend.]
[Boss]
[Your message was sent
but declined by the recipient.]
What are you writing?
Just getting a little thrill out of it.
There is not enough evidence yet.
Mr. Xu.
What's wrong, Mr. Sun?
Coming to me this early
in the morning?
Let's talk inside.
Mr. Xu.
Something serious has happened.
Jiang Hongjun's been taken away.
He's...
currently being held in Jiangnan City,
and it's already been a full day.
Jiangnan?
Who took him?
People from the procuratorate.
And seems that
the police were involved too.
It's a joint operation,
and
a pretty high-level one.
How do you know all this?
His...
His family
was extremely upset.
And I
also wanted to understand
the situation,
so I used some 'means'.
Mr. Xu.
No matter what,
Jiang Hongjun is
the captain of
Criminal Investigation Unit.
But no one
has informed us
about this incident
or given us
any kind of explanation until now.
Don't you think
that's a bit inappropriate?
Look,
can you maybe
make a call to Jiangnan City,
or to the provincial level,
see what's really going on?
Make a call?
And what exactly should I say
in that call?
If he had done nothing wrong,
would he be in custody?
Tell me,
was Jiang Hongjun the person in charge
of investigating the mine accident?
Yes.
Was he also in charge of
the Qiao Zhenxing case?
Yes.
But Jiang Hongjun
is the backbone
in our Criminal Investigation Unit.
We assign major cases to him
all the time.
Then I'm curious.
How could such an outstanding officer
just get
taken into custody for no reason?
Indeed.
There are
still some things
I'm trying to understand.
Sun Fei.
At this point,
you're still not gonna tell me?
Does Jiang Hongjun
have a problem or not?
Tell me!
Yes or no?
His wife told me
they found
several million yuan in cash
at home yesterday.
Millions in cash?
Does he even realize who he is?
He's the captain
of Criminal Investigation Unit!
Do you understand
the implications of this?
Mr. Xu, please don't get upset.
I mean,
is there some kind of
misunderstanding here?
Even for an ordinary citizen,
having millions at home
is also a big deal!
Yes.
Tell me,
besides the mine accident
and the Qiao Zhenxing case,
was he involved in the Wan Hai case?
Yes...
Who assigned him to it?
Jiang Hongjun
definitely has issues.
So, is it possible that
the cases he handled
also have problems?
You were the ones
who fought to take on those cases.
I handed them over to you
because I trusted you,
because Ms. Lan trusted you.
Now you're asking me for an explanation?
How about you give me one first?
Sir...
Sorry...
Go.
Whatever happens,
report to me immediately.
Hello, Ms. Zheng.
I'm the director of Procuratorate Office
Stationed in Prison, Wang Huashan.
Hello.
Didn't expect your visit today.
You came for...?
The organization has made it very clear,
no asking, no leaking.
Please, come in.
How's Wan Hai doing lately?
You know prisoners.
Make a scene when they first get here,
but quiet down once they're inside.
Wan Hai's got coronary heart disease,
can't engage in heavy physical labor,
so we've been lenient.
We have him working in the kitchen.
Emotionally,
he's distant.
Doesn't talk to people much.
A while back,
he got into a dispute
because of the accident
at his family's mine.
We've talked to him seriously
about this.
Thank you.
Leaders,
why are you here again?
I told you
to believe in the law.
That hasn't changed.
We are the Task Force
under the supervision
of Haidong Anti-Crime Office,
coordinated by
Haidong Provincial Procuratorate,
and supported by
Haidong High People's Court
and Public Security Bureau.
We're here this time
to re-investigate
the Wan Hai case,
the Qiao Zhenxing case,
the Wanchuan Mining Accident,
and related matters.
We're digging deep into
the political and legal
protection networks behind these cases
and possible official misconduct.
We hope you'll cooperate.
Come on,
don't joke with me.
First, it was the Guidance Group,
now, the Task Force.
All this back and forth,
didn't I still end up in here?
Just forget it.
Let's just leave it at that.
In this regard,
you're not even as strong as your son.
What do you mean?
The reason we set up a Task Force
is because of Wan Chao's report.
He didn't give up.
But look at your attitude.
Wait, what?
He...
What did he report?
Wan Chao reported that
the mine accident wasn't an accident,
it was man-made.
He gave us the evidence he had.
That's great.
Then
where is he now?
Have you put him under protection?
He is currently wanted
by Dongping Police.
His whereabouts are unknown.
We're also looking for him.
Then what are we even
talking about here?
How about this,
you find him,
then we talk, okay?
We'll do our best to find him
and keep him safe.
Please believe me.
I believe.
You just said
a whole bunch of fancy words.
I can tell you're determined.
Digging into the protection networks
behind all this,
but can you really?
How do you dig?
How far can you go?
Uncle.
Chao.
[15 May SEALED
Mineral Resources Management Bureau]
Why did you come this late?
I'm starving.
You think I didn't want to come sooner?
I can't come here during the day.
Did you bring me hot food?
Yeah, look.
It's good stuff.
I never realized before
how delicious
these raisins and nuts are.
If you like it, eat more.
How did our life get like this?
Even eating a hot meal
has to wait until midnight.
Uncle.
I thought about it during the day.
I can't stay here.
Take a chance,
I've got to get out.
At least leave Dongping.
I'll leave tomorrow.
Are you crazy?
Where are you going?
Where would you even go?
The cops are looking for you.
Cameras on every street.
That red hair of yours
stands out everywhere.
Even if the police can't catch you,
what if they catch you?
Them again.
Can you tell me, uncle?
Who are they?
Didn't you say someone
besides the police
was chasing you that day?
Uncle,
can I trust you?
What do you mean?
If you don't trust me, who do you trust?
Then tell me,
have the cops come
looking for you the past few days?
Or anyone else?
Asking about the accident?
Why would the cops come to me for?
What's there to investigate?
The mine case has been determined.
It's a work safety issue.
- What else is there to check?
- Just tell me, has anyone come or not?
No.
Really?
Are you deaf? No.
Then let me be straight with you.
Uncle,
it wasn't just an accident.
It's man-made sabotage.
I have proof.
And I already gave it to someone.
What proof?
Who did you give it to?
You handed it over,
and then what?
Have you been contacted?
How can they contact me?
I'm now wanted by Dongping Police.
That's why I asked you,
has anyone come to see you?
Has anyone come to see you?
Chao.
You're so stupid.
Have you thought this through?
You really trust those people?
All they do is say nice things.
Which one of their promises
ever came true?
Zhang Wenjing.
Zhang Wenjing was released.
What about your father?
He still got sentenced.
What good did it do?
You said it yourself,
it was man-made.
Then think about it,
if they dare to kill someone,
what won't they do?
They want the mine.
Then who
are 'they'?
Tell me.
I don't know who they are!
Right now, I just want this thing
to be over safely as soon as possible.
Who is it?
Nobody.
Hello, please don't hang up.
The number you dialed is currently
on another call.
[Wan Hong]
Who called you?
Was it them?
You're in touch with them,
can't you just tell me who they are?
I just can't tell you!
If I tell you,
you'd be dead
before you even knew what happened.
If you had listened to me,
and sold the mine like I said,
would there have been a mine accident?
Would people have died?
Would you still be out here,
not being able to go home?
Wan Hong!
Have I not told you before,
don't bring up selling the mine?
You bring it up again,
I swear I'll kill you.
Who are you threatening, huh?
I'm your uncle!
You stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
Eat more walnuts,
help your brain work better.
[Wan Hong]
Mr. Chen.
Busy man, huh?
Can't even pick up the phone.
No, I wouldn't dare.
I just didn't hear it earlier...
No signal just now,
so I pressed decline.
It's been a few days.
We've missed you.
Mr. Chen,
did you need something?
Just checking in.
Did you speak to your brother
about what we discussed last time?
Yes, I did.
So what do you think?
Yes or no?
Give me a straight answer.
Look,
Mr. Chen,
I just think
this isn't something we can rush.
We have to take it slow.
There was just
that huge accident at the mine,
if I talk to him about selling now,
won't that set him off?
He'll definitely blow up.
So, Mr. Chen, you have to believe me.
Do it at my pace.
I'll find the right time,
and talk to him.
Mr. Chen?
Hello?
What did you talk about
with your brother?
Not much.
Just some small talk.
Did you mention the mine accident?
Yes.
But I didn't go into details.
And did your brother ask about Wan Chao?
He did. I told him not to worry.
I said Wan Chao's fine, very safe.
Mr. Chen.
Please, don't overthink it.
Don't get me wrong.
I really don't know
where Wan Chao is now.
I just said that
to reassure my brother.
Think about it,
he's locked up right now.
He can't do anything to help.
He'll just get worried.
Honestly,
if something really happens
to his precious son,
with my brother's temper,
he can do anything.
No one can stop him.
Then we can forget about
selling the mine.
So what I said to him
was all for your sake.
Am I right, Mr. Chen?
Right.
That makes sense.
Then I'll wait for your update.
Okay.
Don't worry, Mr. Chen.
I'll talk to him soon.
This deadbeat
is lying!
Go
find Chao.
Hello?
Dear auntie,
why do you call me
during work hours?
I've got something serious to tell you.
Do you remember Jiang Yuan?
Jiang Min's brother.
Old secretary's son.
I told him to come to you.
Isn't he abroad?
He's back.
Wants to start a business.
I looked into his company's credentials,
looks solid on all fronts.
If you can help, please do.
Oh, and his company's name,
let me have a look.
It's
Yuanli New Energy
Technology Group Co., Ltd.
Got that?
New energy?
He's doing new energy too?
Yes.
He says he wants to tap into
Dongping's copper and nickel resources
to produce new energy vehicles.
His factory site plan
has already been approved,
right in Hongjia Village
of your Development Zone.
So I told him to reach out to you.
Hongjia Village?
And the plan has been approved?
Auntie, are you sure?
I'm sure.
I saw the pre-approval document myself.
We've already submitted the application
for the land expropriation rights
in Hongjia Village.
If you have time,
please help move it along.
We're planning to
build a battery plant there.
Hello?
I am listening.
If you can support, then do it.
As long as
it doesn't violate
any rules or regulations.
Okay, I got it.
I have a meeting later.
I gotta go.
Hello, Mr. Chen, it's me.
Where are you?
[Land Use Plan of Yuanli Group
New Energy Battery Plant Phase I]
Auntie.
You are?
It's me, Yuan,
Jiang Yuan.
Oh, I remember.
You remember?
Yuan.
Aren't you abroad?
I'm back.
I just came to visit you.
Where's my uncle?
He's inside.
Inside.
Old man.
Hurry.
Uncle.
Look who's here.
Hurry.
This is?
Liang's brother-in-law.
Jiang Yuan.
Long time no see.
He just got back from overseas.
Come on.
Let's go.
Mr. Hong.
Got important guest today?
What a grand entrance, so impressive.
I can tell he's important right away.
He's Jiang Yuan,
Liang's brother-in-law.
Mr. Jiang.
Nice to meet you.
Very sharp-looking.
Du!
Quit dawdling, hurry up!
Help with the things.
Just having you here is enough,
you didn't have to bring anything.
Let's document the good life.
Enough.
- Come inside.
- Later,
share those things with our neighbors.
Okay.
Yuan, let's go in first.
You go inside.
Okay.
Stop that, Hong Yi.
Enough shooting.
How nice, look.
Everyone says it tastes great,
so I brought it for you.
Said it's good for older folks.
How is it?
How long are you staying this time?
This time,
I might not go back.
And we may
see each other a lot more often.
What do you mean?
Actually, I came back this time
for a project
in the new energy sector.
You know that piece of land
in our village
that got zoned for industrial use?
We're gonna take
that land.
So all this fuss
about the land expropriation
is related to your company?
Yes.
And I'm telling you,
if this goes through,
the village economy
will shoot right up.
It'll also create a lot of jobs.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
If I'd known...
You know what,
the village committee
asked me to give my opinion many times,
but I didn't go.
Really?
If I'd known you were involved in
this expropriation,
I would've shown up in full support.
That means a lot coming from you.
Let me be honest with you,
I'm here today
to ask you
for a favor.
Go on.
The thing is,
the land
has been approved for us.
But there are so many people
in the village,
and since we joined in
a bit late,
there might be some pushback.
I think
it's best if we can
sit down
and talk things through together.
So you're talking about
this matter?
Yes.
Xingzi,
Jiang Yuan came to the village.
I sent you the video.
Looks like he's here for the land.
Okay.
Got it.
You keep an eye on it.
Wait for my signal.
Okay...
I got it.
Uncle,
we're family.
I won't beat around the bush.
I know everyone wants
what's best for the village,
and wants to secure the interests.
You're highly respected around here,
so I was hoping you could
help talk to the others
when you have time.
If anyone has concerns or requests,
tell them to bring them to me.
I'll do my best to find solutions.
Okay.
Not a big ask.
A young man wants to start a business
and build up his hometown,
that's a good thing.
This old man should help,
I'll do my best.
Thank you so much.
Well,
let me toast you with tea first,
we'll drink properly in a bit. Okay?
Come on.
Okay.
I know
the land in Hongjia Village is good.
But there's nothing we can do.
The Planning Bureau
has approved it for them.
And
this Yuanli Group
does have some serious backing.
Mr. Chen,
I really tried my best.
In fact, you might want to consider
moving into new energy.
Global demand
for nickel in batteries keeps growing.
And
there's a copper-nickel mine
right here in our Development Zone.
Would you be interested, Mr. Chen?
You can't touch the mine,
and definitely not the land.
Chen Shenglong,
you can't
take this mine.
Forget about it.
Yuanli?
The boss's name is Jiang Yuan, right?
His sister is Jiang Min.
His father is Jiang Xudong,
Vice Chairman of
Provincial Committee of the CPPCC.
Is it right?
You knew each other?
Or
have you
been investigating them?
Would you consider working with them?
I can help connect you,
build that bridge.
Director Liu,
let's eat while we talk.
Mr. Chen,
take your time with your meal.
I've said what I came to say.
I have a meeting later.
I'll get going.
Director Liu.
Is Dongping going to build
two new energy battery factories?
What do you mean?
I asked,
is Dongping going to build
two new energy battery factories?
But the only land suitable
for battery factories
is in Hongjia Village.
So I only want Hongjia Village.
Mr. Chen,
I understand your feelings.
But I'm limited in what I can do.
And acquiring land
isn't as simple as you think.
Perhaps you can consider another site.
As long as it's
within the Development Zone,
I'll do everything I can to help.
I told you,
I only want Hongjia Village.
Chen Shenglong, what's with the banging?
Watch your attitude!
There's no point talking
if you're like this.
Just think about what I proposed.
If you can accept it,
we'll pick it up later.
What are you doing?
What do you wanna do?
Director Liu,
sit down.
I told you I have another meeting.
I also told you to sit down.
You trying to pull some
gangster move on me?
Fine,
let's talk.
The night
of the mine accident,
your whole family was celebrating
your husband's promotion
to prosecutor-general, right?
Lan Jingming was there too.
She even told you
to return the house to me,
right?
Did Cheng Zijian tell you that?
Funny.
While you were toasting and laughing,
the Wan family's mine...
What a coincidence.
Consider it a gift from me
to your whole family.
Partnership?
Not interested.
I'll buy the whole thing.
Only with full control
can I devote myself to it.
We still
want to buy the mine.
Wan Hong can't afford
compensation.
We can take that on too.
Dad!
As long as Director Liu
and the leaders of
the Development Zone Managing Committee
can support us,
we're willing to contribute.
You're welcome.
I'm calling the police.
I'm exposing you!
Give me back my phone!
Give it back!
I'm gonna expose you!
I'll make sure you rot in prison
for life!
Director Liu,
wasn't it you who brought it up first?
You asked me to
take over the mine
and the new energy project.
That's why I stepped in.
I didn't ask you to
stage a mine accident!
You should thank me.
If I hadn't stepped in,
how would the bank loans
have been repaid?
You killed someone, you know that?
And now you're telling me to back off?
Why?
You're insane!
Why do you think I sold you
the Dadu Xishan house
for half the price?
How did a house worth millions
end up under your name?
This is crime!
You wanna return it?
Absolutely impossible!
And copper and nickel mine.
Are you still human?
Jiang Yuan's behind this...
You have no bottom line!
You let him take over!
You're an animal!
I'm an animal!
To you,
to Jiang Yuan and the rest,
I'm an animal!
You used me,
exploited me,
stepped all over me to climb higher.
What do I get?
Nothing at all.
I had to claw my way up.
You left me no choice.
Jiang Yuan.
Yes, sir?
Sit down.
What have you been up to these days?
I told you.
Working on the new energy project.
Where exactly?
That is...
In Dongping, right?
What exactly have you been doing
using my name in Dongping?
Grabbing land? Buying mines?
Even getting into disputes?
Is there such a thing?
You're my son.
What would people think?
Jiang Yuan.
I get that
you want to come back
and make a name for yourself,
but you can't do it under my banner,
especially not where I used to work.
What would people think of you?
Or me?
But...
You need to leave Dongping.
I've planned this for three years,
and now you ask me to just leave.
H-How can I?
Three years?
Weren't you studying abroad
three years ago?
♪The sprout hides deep in the soil♪
♪Shrouded in darkness,
no light in sight♪
♪When will hope
break through the ground♪
♪The mist no longer hides♪
♪Always seeking, spreading♪
♪Until there's nothing left to shield♪
♪Be the bloom
that wildfire can't consume♪
♪When spring winds come,
it grows again♪
♪A flower blooming in the cold winter♪
♪Breaking free from the ashes♪
♪Seeking truth,
not withering in silence♪
♪Be the bloom unbent by howling wind♪
♪An undefeated cold winter flower
soaring through the clouds♪
♪Carrying sacred light♪
♪Scattering the dark clouds away♪
♪Be the bloom
that wildfire can't consume♪
♪When spring winds come,
it grows again♪
♪A flower blooming in the cold winter♪
♪Breaking free from the ashes♪
♪Seeking truth,
not withering in silence♪
♪Be the bloom unbent by howling wind♪
♪An undefeated cold winter flower
soaring through the clouds♪
♪Carrying sacred light♪
♪Scattering the dark clouds away♪
♪Shattering the darkness♪
♪Let the hidden fragrance bloom♪
♪Return this world to
one last blaze of brilliance♪
♪A blaze of brilliance♪