Are you guys blind?
Can't you see my car is parked here?
What's wrong with you?
Mr. Fu,
I heard you often
visit the detention center.
That place is bad luck.
This time it's a fake knife,
next time it'll be a real one.
[In the Name of Justice]
[Episode 6]
Come in.
Mr. Xu.
Yes?
I need to talk to you.
I just went to Yongqing River,
my brother's crime scene.
I noticed a lot of key evidence
doesn't add up…
Who sent you?
You went alone
or with someone else?
With that
Hong Liang from the Guidance Group.
[Official Document of
Dongping Municipal People's Government]
I dragged him there.
So what have you found?
We're nowhere near that yet.
The evidence just doesn't make sense.
Let me break it down for you.
First, the pickaxe…
Qiao Zhenxing's case has been closed.
It's suicide.
Suicide?
Mr. Xu.
How would my brother commit suicide?
It's not for you to consider.
We just lost a prosecutor.
Things are pretty tense lately.
I advise you,
don't get involved.
No, commander.
I have a request.
I'd like access
to my late brother's
call logs and location records.
Who wanted it?
You?
Or…
Me.
Something's wrong with this case.
I don't accept their…
What did I just tell you?
Don't get involved…
Don't you understand?
Just let me take a quick look.
Get out.
Get out!
Em…
How's Xie?
Xie Hongfei?
Yes.
He's fine.
Honestly,
Xie Hongfei is more qualified to be
the director of
the First Division than me.
And,
the Wan Hai case,
how much was Xie involved?
He…
He wasn't much involved.
You know,
I've been on this case for two years.
Well, Xie Hongfei is responsible
for all cases
in the First Division, but not this one.
He's dedicated.
So,
two years on Wan Hai case.
Have you,
like,
ever felt
so drained,
while stress just keeps piling on?
You must have, right?
So,
do you wanna
take a break?
What are you doing?
Trying to set me up here?
Li Renjun,
looks like your
acting prosecutor-general seat
is a little shaky.
Watch your mouth.
Why are you here?
Something's up.
A problem.
It feels off.
What is it?
I just came back from Yongqing River.
First,
next to the hole in the ice,
they said there was no fishing gear.
That means he did not
slip into it.
Second,
the mobile phone.
They found everything
except the phone.
Weird, huh?
Third,
the empty wine bottle in the car.
They said he drank it.
If he drinks,
one sip and he's in the hospital.
He'll never do that.
Sounds off, right?
That's why I came to you.
You
give the Dongping Police
a heads-up,
tell them to dig deeper.
What I just told…
Xu Yanwu called.
He told me.
What?
Dongping Police
have already
ruled out homicide.
They will give me
the final report soon.
Not a homicide,
definitely not an accident either.
Suicide.
Impossible!
Happy family,
and nothing's wrong with him,
he's healthy.
Then it must be the workplace.
Who did something to him,
and he couldn't get over this?
But I thought he has
a lot of friends at work.
You're his best friend,
you've had his back.
Director of First Division,
didn't you put him forward for the role
at the party meeting?
What could happen to him?
Hong Liang…
- Hong Liang.
- Impossible.
Tell me,
you've been away
from Dongping for over ten years,
do you think you know
Qiao Zhenxing well?
Of course, I know him well.
We were college classmates,
living in the same dorm for four years.
Then we worked together here.
Of course, I know him well.
I also went to college
with him for four years.
I've been his colleague
longer than you,
even I wouldn't say
I truly know him.
Have you ever reflected on yourself?
Because now you're
looking for a promotion,
and you're
the acting prosecutor-general.
Your future is bright.
Maybe you're starting to
look down on us grassroots folks.
Speak plainly.
Why are you so annoying?
What did I do to you?
I visited Qiao's place
to offer condolences,
and then,
you just had to make that call
right in front of
my team leader.
What's your deal?
I was protecting you.
Protect, you know that?
Oh my goodness.
You really opened my eyes.
Hong Liang, do you know
your role here?
You're a member of the Guidance Group.
We still haven't figured out
how Qiao Zhenxing died.
Do you think
it's appropriate to go there?
Listen to yourself,
you look exactly
like my team leader Zheng Yaping,
really.
Are you two incompatible?
Tell me the truth.
I went to Qiao's place
to express my condolences,
in terms of humanity,
that's not wrong.
But disciplinarily speaking,
I should've informed her.
She didn't give me the chance.
So, that night,
at the summary meeting,
I was properly chewed out.
Great.
You had it coming.
How about I chew you out?
Let me 'protect' you too.
Some people
should really try doing
something decent for once.
Don't disgrace their own name.
Li Renjun.
Be a decent man.
Qiao is gone,
we've been buddies for years,
and you don't wanna
pay your condolences?
I will do it.
But not now.
Then on the anniversary?
Isn't it a little late?
A kind reminder,
at least show up.
You keep hiding yourself,
Zhou Mei hates you now, you know that?
She said you took Qiao out.
Why did you do that?
I mean, why did you do that?
He was doing a good job.
Hong Liang, you're an insider,
don't talk like a layman.
You really think I,
as acting prosecutor-general,
can remove Qiao Zhenxing
from the lead position
on the Wan Hai case?
It's the result of the party meeting.
What does it have to do with me?
Do you know how Qiao Zhenxing scolded me
after that decision was made?
Everyone here heard it.
Li Renjun! Why pull me off the case?
Did I make a mistake or abuse my power?
Don't get so worked up.
It's fine, go back to work.
Come, sit down and talk.
You've been on the Wan Hai case
for over two years,
I bet you barely had time
for your family,
didn't pay much attention
to your kid's studies either.
You've lost so much weight,
take good care of yourself.
My health is none of your concern.
Do you believe what you just said?
Wan Hai not being prosecuted,
it's holding back your promotion,
blocking your achievements,
keeping you from
becoming the prosecutor-general!
Am I
blocking the entire
Dongping People's Procuratorate?
The Wan Hai case is huge,
you've been holding it up,
who do you think is
carrying this pressure for you?
It's me!
I've been taking the blame
from above and the public!
Yet, you're upset!
I don't need you.
I have the law to carry it for me.
Li Renjun, let me tell you,
no matter who handles this case,
as long as the facts are not clear
and the evidence is not conclusive,
it cannot be prosecuted.
If you have a problem,
take it to the provincial office.
Go talk to the higher-ups.
Your removal
was a decision made by the committee!
Don't act like a martyr here.
Fine,
I will report it.
I will definitely report it.
I will tell them
you remove a prosecutor at will,
and I'll accuse you
of dereliction of duty!
What would you do if it were you?
Two requests of
supplemental investigation,
both filed on the very last day.
It's not that I didn't
give him a chance.
But I can't do it forever.
Keep returning the case,
it'll never be prosecuted.
Wan Hai case took
two years in total,
we can't just abandon it.
Pressure from the society
and the higher-ups
is all on my shoulders.
Did I say anything?
No, not a word.
The case is retreated at his will.
Sometimes,
I can't even tell
if he's targeting me
or the case.
Everyone in the procuratorate
can criticize him,
only I can't.
I say one thing, he fires back with ten.
Caution is good,
but when you take it to the extreme,
caution turns into paranoia.
I don't know how to talk to him.
Forget it.
He's gone now.
But
if he really killed himself
because of depression,
part of that's on me.
[4 March
Day 6 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
[Day 7 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
Here, look at this.
Even if these devices are depreciated,
they should at least go for this price.
If it's lower than this,
we can't sell.
Problem is,
the price is not up to us.
Okay, I got it.
I'll try to find
a few more mining companies,
see if anyone's willing to pay more.
Brother,
does that sound like something
a brother would say?
You call this lending money?
Who charges interest that high?
Why don't you just go rob a bank?
At least that's faster.
What collateral?
What do I
even have left to put up as collateral?
Take me then.
Bro,
this mine,
do you dare to take it
if I give it to you?
You can have it.
Besides, this mine
belongs to the bank now.
What the…?
That path won't work.
Don't go down the loan shark route.
For our family, that's just
pouring gasoline on the fire.
What are they doing?
Take your feet off!
I'm eating.
Counting something?
I'm adding up
the devices in our mine.
They're useless to us now,
might as well sell them for some money.
Uncle,
are you crazy?
How many times have I told you
you can't sell them?
How are we supposed
to survive without them?
You think I want to?
The bank's been calling every other day.
We've got to show them something.
Come on, is that our problem?
That's the bank's problem.
The bank lent us the money
to buy equipment and start mining.
We bought the equipment,
now the Mining Bureau won't let us work.
Can you ask the bank
to talk to the Mining Bureau?
Can you make this right?
My prince,
owe money, pay it back.
That's how it works.
You think the bank
cares about your problems?
I've got the equipment,
now I need to mine!
So that I can pay them back, right?
Why did the Mining Bureau shut us down?
Because you were mining illegally.
Well, that's to make money
to pay the bank!
But the bureau won't let me do it.
Isn't it a giant paradox?
So I wanted to sell equipment
for some money.
How much money
can you make from that then?
Can you cover the interest?
- The equipment…
- It's better than nothing.
Better than nothing?
How much can you pay
with that little money?
And what about after that?
Stop arguing.
Just talk it through.
Hello?
Hello, Fu Bing?
This is the Guidance Group
of the provincial procuratorate.
If it's about Zhang Wenjing,
don't call me.
Your law firm…
Jing,
is this a good time?
Yeah.
Good, then.
I didn't get Qiao's location records
before his death.
Captain Jiang's guarding that
too tightly.
It's okay.
Oh, Jing,
I cooked you something.
I know you're very busy,
barely have time to eat dinner.
So I made you some hot food.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Oh, and…
I…
I got you
a thermos cup.
Figured you can drink
more hot water with it.
I don't usually drink much water.
That's not good.
You've got to drink more,
especially with your job,
always out on cases,
you should definitely drink more water.
[Beijing]
Have you been there?
Yes.
How was it?
How else could it be? Terrible.
Zhou Mei is so pitiful.
Did you give them the money?
I did.
Listen,
Dou's school stuff
is pretty much sorted.
[Dongping Hotel]
Start next semester,
they even agreed to put her
in an advanced class.
And the house thing.
I was going to rent one,
but I checked out three more places,
my legs nearly gave out.
And guess what,
Jiang Yuan helped us.
One of his friends
owns an apartment near the school.
He's abroad, so the place is empty.
Said we could use it for now,
just temporarily.
Once you're here,
we really need to thank him properly.
OK.
Something's off with you.
What's wrong? Tell me.
Nothing.
Just that…
I talked to Renjun
about Qiao today.
Then out of nowhere,
he asked me
"Hong Liang,
do you really know Qiao?"
It hit me hard.
I realized I didn't really know Qiao.
I don't seem to know Renjun either.
Pretty frustrating.
Now that you mention it,
I remember something
you told me before.
What?
Back in college,
they were both running
for student council president.
They were neck and neck,
either one of them could've won.
And in the end?
In the end,
they were tied,
then Qiao voted for Renjun.
And Li Renjun voted for himself.
So Li Renjun won.
So sneaky.
Right.
You three
lived together for four years,
you didn't even know
he was gonna vote for himself.
Totally.
So,
no one really knows anyone.
Just like now,
I don't even know
what's going on in your head.
I'm an open book in front of you.
You know exactly what I'm thinking.
People who claim they're an open book
usually aren't.
I'm serious,
wrap things up
and get back to Beijing.
You've got a pile of work
waiting for you.
Got it.
Don't get too tired.
Get some rest, don't stay up too late.
Bye now.
Good night.
Wan Hai not being prosecuted,
it's holding back your promotion,
keeping you from
becoming the prosecutor-general!
Am I
holding back the entire
Dongping People's Procuratorate?
The initial assumption is
something could be wrong
in his personal life
or maybe at work.
If we're saying his depression
led to the suicide,
then it must've been triggered
by his removal
from the Wan Hai case.
Why?
Happy family,
nothing's wrong with him,
he's healthy.
Then it must be the workplace.
I will tell them
you remove a prosecutor at will,
and I'll accuse you
of dereliction of duty!
What's wrong?
The Police have
ruled it.
Suicide.
Are you sure?
Pretty much.
What's the cause of suicide?
Why?
Did something happen to him?
Because…
Because of me.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean because of you?
Renjun,
you must not think like that.
Think about your office,
how many cases does
each prosecutor handle every year?
If everyone who got pulled off a case
couldn't handle it,
how many people would've died?
You just
take too much on yourself sometimes.
Most people would run from
this kind of responsibility.
But you…
what are you doing to yourself?
It's not like that.
Looking back now,
during the six months
after I pulled him off,
something changed in him.
He's already different.
If he committed suicide,
it's because of me.
If someone killed him,
it's still because of me.
No matter how he died,
it's all because of me.
- I killed him.
- Renjun.
Renjun…
Don't think like that.
That was a decision
made by the committee.
It wasn't on you.
Stop overthinking, OK?
I'm begging you.
Can you leave me alone for a while?
I want to be alone.
Then promise me,
don't overthink this.
[5 March
Day 7 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
[Day 8 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
Hello.
Zhang Wenjing, visitor.
What happened?
Someone hit you?
I've been threatened here, too.
They threatened me with my daughter.
I can't believe this, Fu.
How can Dongping be this lawless?
Do you know why Zhang Wenjing
is considered a gangster?
Because you want her to be!
Then do you believe
we could make you one too?
Forget it.
We can't beat them.
Our firm got trashed.
I'm being sued.
And my license is suspended.
Sorry.
I can't defend you anymore.
What do you mean?
You're quitting?
Are you afraid?
Qiao Zhenxing is dead.
What?
They can really do anything.
Really.
Sorry.
Don't blame me.
What do you want from me?
You…
how's your investigation?
What investigation?
That guy…
how did he die?
How would I know about that?
I wanna know too.
You're a cop.
I'm a cop. So?
You don't know what I do?
Let's drink this…
Here.
Take this
to my sister-in-law and Ran.
They haven't eaten all day.
See you.
Don't go, sit down.
What now?
I haven't finished yet.
Sit, just sit.
Listen to me, sit down.
Listen,
the day before your brother died,
he came to see me.
Look.
When was this photo taken?
Any idea?
Two days ago,
I took my sisters out to dinner.
Where did you get this?
Think about it.
Anyone suspicious
near you that night?
Oh my god.
Was this taken secretly?
What's going on?
Get off.
By the way, Zhou Biao,
don't tell Mei about this.
I won't.
If anything happens, call me.
The next day,
he's dead.
Have you told Jiang Hongjun about this?
I didn't.
Why?
Your information is very important.
You have to let the Police know.
I'm telling you now,
you're a policeman.
I'm in logistics.
I can't do anything from there,
you know that?
Bro?
Zhou Biao, you bastard!
Where have you been?
You owe people money,
and they're in our house now!
Are you trying to
get me and your son killed?
Come back here now!
I need to go.
Are you okay?
Yeah, just some people I know.
Remember what I told you.
What kind of driving is that?
Zhou Biao. Are you Mr. Zhou?
Our boss Mr. Zhang
wants to talk to you
about the construction payment.
What…
What Mr. Zhang?
I don't know him.
Bro, there must be some mistake.
You'll know when you see him.
I mean…
Get out of my way!
Go away!
Hands off!
Let go.
Let go,
hands off!
Get in the car.
Help!
Get in now.
Go, move.
Get in the car.
Get in.
Here you go.
Let's go.
Zhang Wenjing.
Are you okay?
The director asked if you were okay.
Do you want me to step out this time?
I plead guilty.
I'm a core member of Wan Hai's
criminal organization.
I am guilty.
Are you sure?
Zhang Wenjing.
I plead guilty.
I'm a core member of Wan Hai's
criminal organization.
I am guilty.
[Dongping New World
Environmental Recycling Energy Co., Ltd.]
Who's that?
Is it Mr. Zhang?
Mr. Zhang,
I really don't owe you any money.
I remember I paid you
the elevator fare last time.
Who is Mr. Zhang?
Who are you?
Who are you people?
It doesn't matter who we are.
What matters is
you're who we came for, Mr. Zhou.
Hungry?
Come on.
Eat something.
Hurry up…
Eat something first.
Eat it.
Slow down.
There's plenty, don't worry.
Don't choke yourself.
Here, have some water.
Mr. Zhou, I heard that
that prosecutor Hong
went to your sister's house.
What did you guys talk about? Tell me.
Nothing, really.
He just gave us a condolence envelope.
Then what did you say to Qin Feng?
I said nothing.
Nothing at all.
I really didn't say anything.
It'd better be nothing.
Is your brother-in-law a good person?
Does he take bribes?
Come, help Mr. Zhou think.
Mr. Zhou.
Let me
help you
think about it.
[Serve the People]
What's going on with Zhang Wenjing?
We're here to investigate
if her claims were true,
and now she just pleaded guilty.
Director,
what do we do next?
Are we going back?
Did the handwriting analysis
for Zhang Wenjing come out yet?
Not yet.
Did they give me a chance?
I didn't have any chance to speak up.
I want to state the facts.
If there is no trial,
no one will ever hear my side.
And the longer
they put the trial on hold,
they'll have more time
to fake evidence
and forge documents.
Shut up!
Who forged documents?
Who faked…?
Do you dare let a third-party agency
do the analysis?
The first time we met Zhang Wenjing,
she quarreled with Mr. Xie,
asked if we dared to let
a third-party agency verify it.
She didn't say it impulsively,
she said it to us.
We can't get in touch with Fu Bing now.
If we don't figure out
why Zhang Wenjing pleaded guilty,
our job as the Guidance Group
can't be done.
Come in.
Ms. Zheng.
Mr. Li, Mr. Wang.
I'm really sorry.
When you went to see Zhang Wenjing,
I had a meeting in the city,
so I didn't make it.
But I heard from Mr. Xie
it went well.
Zhang Wenjing pleaded guilty.
That's right.
Mr. Li, to be honest,
prosecutors from the provincial office
really are impressive.
We've been working on Zhang Wenjing
for so many years.
No matter how we talked to her,
nothing worked.
But once Ms. Zheng
and her team showed up,
Zhang Wenjing confessed right away.
That really helped us out, big time.
We actually think
it's a bit out of the blue.
Why?
Ms. Zheng,
your first round of questioning
worked.
Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
You helped us fill the gap
in the Wan Hai case.
Mr. Li.
Look,
the Guidance Group
has been working hard lately.
The job is almost done,
I wanna tell our canteen to
prepare a few local specialties
as a treat for them.
It's too early for that.
We're not
quite finished yet.
The Guidance Group is really thorough.
Well then, Ms. Zheng,
if you need us
to help with anything,
feel free to ask.
[6 March
Day 8 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
[Day 9 Since the Wan Hai Case Trial Began]
Captain Jiang,
we picked up a signal
from Qiao Zhenxing's phone.
Sorry, Police.
You the owner here?
Yes.
We're the Police.
Did you just take in a phone?
Yes, that's right.
Where is it?
Over there.
Yang Jing, check it.
Did you wipe it?
No, not yet.
I just got it,
just started charging it up.
Yes.
Who sold it to you?
Just now,
some guy said he picked it up somewhere.
So I bought it.
I didn't know it was a problem.
If I'd known, I wouldn't have taken it.
Your security cameras working?
Did you just sell a used mobile phone?
Yeah.
Is this you?
Yes.
Come to the station with us.
We need to question you.
Please cooperate.
[Pingshan Development Zone Sub-Bureau]
Can I help you?
I'm here
to file a report.
Go on.
What do you want to report?
My brother-in-law
took… took bribes.
Who's your brother-in-law?
What's his name?
Qiao… Qiao Zhenxing.
Say it clearly! Details!
Last year,
April last year,
I bribed Qiao Zhenxing on behalf of
Wan Hai.
Which day in April?
Be specific!
Start from the beginning!
The date…
I can't remember.
At that time, Wan Hai
was already locked up.
I received a letter,
it was
from one of Wan Hai's guys, telling me
to go to the Dream Paris suite
at Wanjia Denghuo KTV
and get a suitcase
for my brother-in-law.
I followed the instructions,
went to that room,
and picked up the suitcase.
[Dream Paris]
For you.
What is it?
Who gave me that?
Wan Hai.
It was packed full of cash.
Then I gave that suitcase
to my brother-in-law.
Are you done?
Yes.
How can you be sure
it was Wan Hai who asked you
to bribe Qiao Zhenxing?
Wan Hai's guy
gave me a letter.
Where's the letter?
I… threw it away.
But I took a picture.
Where is it?
In my phone.
This one.
Where did you get this phone?
I picked it up.
Where did you pick it up?
By the Yongqing River Reservoir.
Where by the reservoir exactly?
You know that path east of the reservoir
that leads onto the ice?
I picked it up there.
Why do you remember so clearly?
Habit, I'm a driver.
Can't remember much else,
but roads, I do remember.
When it comes to roads in Dongping,
I'm like a living map,
believe it or not.
Was there anything else
next to the phone?
No.
There was a car.
But no one inside.
What car?
I think…
It was a silver sedan.
Was there anyone around?
Not really.
If there was, I would've
asked about the phone.
What day did you find it?
Around 8 or 9 AM on the 27th, I think.
Did I ask you for the time?
It was 8 or 9 AM anyway.
Why didn't you sell it that day?
Didn't think much of it at the time.
But I lost some money
playing cards last night,
so I sold it for some cash today.
You said,
you're a driver?
Yeah.
What car do you drive?
Garbage truck.
How many people usually
work in the same car?
Three.
Me
and two cleaners.
So that day you were
driving the garbage truck?
Who else was with you?
Just myself.
Why did you drive a garbage truck
to that kind of place alone
so early that day?
Captain Jiang.
Yang Jing,
Mr. Sun wants you to head to
No.2 Middle School
and bring Zhou Mei over.
Mei,
we just got a report
saying that Qiao Zhenxing
accepted a huge bribe last year.
You know about that?
♪At the river's end,
bitter rain and brutal waves♪
♪A human life is strewn with hardship♪
♪Brother, there's a weight on my heart♪
♪Until I meet Old Lady Meng,
I can't let it go♪
♪Since ancient days,
black and white have stood apart♪
♪Don't preach
that letting go makes you a Buddha♪
♪Even good folk may die unrewarded♪
♪So why should the wicked live in ease?♪
♪For one last breath,
for one clear principle♪
♪For this single rite,
I'll see it through to the end♪
♪I will wear my life thin
just to glimpse the snow-orchid bloom♪
♪I will shred these shoes
and barefoot tame the wind-blown sands♪
♪I will face rosy clouds by day
and lift a torch by night♪
♪Beneath the bright firmament,
I want every deed bound by law♪
♪I want the ones who set out
to return home, no matter how late♪
♪I want the rain that falls from heaven
to rise back into heaven♪
♪I want to earn my daily bread
while guarding this wild land♪
♪I want every righteous path on earth
to stand beneath clear skies♪
♪I want the well-diggers' pockets
lined with salt♪
♪And I want the heartless cheats
to feel the justice in their eyes♪