[In the Name of Justice]
[Episode 10]
Mr. Chen,
thanks for your generosity,
but isn't giving away
such a huge place a little much?
Not at all.
Zijian is gifted.
Honestly, I'd do even more
to keep
someone like him on my team.
So Mr. Chen,
how did you spot his talent?
Thanks to me!
Come on.
We've done a ton of interviews
with Long's company before.
I knew he needed a legal advisor,
so I recommended Zijian.
They hit it off right away, right?
Isn't that right, Zijian?
Of course.
Renjun,
Yun,
here in Dongping,
besides you two,
Mr. Chen
also feels like family to me.
I see Zijian as my own brother.
Now that we're all here,
let's get a group photo, guys.
Sure!
Come on.
Hurry up!
Over here!
Honey,
did you notice
Yun seemed
really into
this place today.
You saw that too, huh?
You know,
she was practically glowing
the whole tour.
She couldn't stop raving about it.
For real?
Actually,
I have an idea.
What is it?
I was thinking,
just imagine,
if Renjun and his wife moved here,
they could
look after you when I'm tied up at work.
Oh, come on!
They're actually busier than you!
When would they ever have time?
Yeah, you're right.
But still,
if they ever did move nearby,
it'd be great
to have each other's backs.
Chen Youcai!
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
Chen Youcai, have you lost it?
Seriously, are you crazy?
Hit me, huh?
Come on.
Right here.
Hit me. Let's see!
You actually scared me for a second.
Chen Youcai, you punk!
What's going on here?
What's all the yelling about?
What are you staring at?
Mr. Wang,
Mr. Chen here is upset
about the rail car arrangement—
he threw a fit downstairs.
Look, I'm bleeding!
What are you doing?
Why'd you mess with my incense?
Now, for god's sake,
just tell me,
how can you hand
those cars over to someone else?
You promised me, in writing!
My goods are stuck here,
you're hitting me with storage fees,
and my clients
are on my back for penalties.
I'm broke, can't afford to pay!
Why are you doing this to me?
Put the incense back first,
now!
So,
whose goods are those?
Mine!
Say that again?
They're mine!
Okay.
Then come over here,
I'll show you something.
Still gonna play dumb?
Take a good look.
What's this then?
Go on,
look for yourself.
You really think Mr. Wang doesn't
know what you've been doing?
Answer me!
Didn't I tell you
I don't want anything
from the Wan family on my turf?
You know who they are?
They're gangsters!
Was I just talking to the wall?
Does what I say
mean nothing to you?
Mr. Wang,
if you don't let
their shipment out,
their ore will never
leave Dongping.
Mr. Wang,
the Wan family
is never coming back from this.
But we're all human,
we all have to make a living.
We can't just destroy
someone's livelihood like that.
Now you care about the Wan family?
Where were you before?
You've been playing both sides,
and now you want to act concerned?
What now?
Playing both sides, huh?
If I hadn't,
would you have this hub
back in your hands?
Would Wan Hai
have ended up as a gangster?
With the deity as our witness,
Mr. Wang,
remember how good Wan Hai was to you?
Don't push people too far;
or it could come back to haunt you.
Mr. Wang,
do me this one favor
for everything I've done for you,
let the Wan family ship this batch.
I let Wan Hong down.
I gave him my word.
Please, help me this one time.
Come on.
Help you?
Who do you think you are?
Come on, tell me!
You've never kept
a single promise to me!
Wanna kick down the ladder, huh?
Just so you know,
you pushed me to my limit today.
One day,
someone might push you even further!
Tell me,
what's written on that wall?
"Win-win cooperation."
Have you cooperated?
Did we both win here?
Chen, I'm done going easy on you.
Ms. Zheng, Mr. Wang,
this is the largest freight hub
in Dongping.
It handles not only bulk rail shipping
but also container transport.
There's also massive warehouse space
and logistics services.
The trains and trucks here
load and unload seamlessly,
connecting rail
and highway transport
for incredible efficiency.
Ms. Zheng.
Take it easy.
Mr. Wang, watch your step.
No worries.
This is really a huge place.
Back in the day,
this was just
a regular rail depot.
Its only job was
shipping coal and iron ore
from here and nearby mines.
Over time,
it grew into what it is today.
Now we got everything, fruit, veggies,
seafood, cold-chain, you name it.
It wasn't like this
before Wan Hai took over, huh?
As far as we know,
it really wasn't that big before,
just handling transfer
between trucks and trains,
no storage or logistics at all.
Just a basic cargo depot.
Exactly.
Wan Hai sure knew
how to grow a business.
This way.
Who is it?
Open up.
[Wanchuan Operations Office
General Manager's Office]
Looks like the boss lady's here.
The Guidance Group decided last minute
to drop by for a quick tour.
What,
you're not letting us in?
No!
Please, come on in!
After you.
Everyone, please come inside.
Sorry, it's a bit messy in here,
hope I got enough chairs.
Just make yourselves at home.
Youcai.
Look,
let's deal with our issue
another time.
We'll sort things out later—
the Guidance Group's here now.
Catch you later.
Now that Mr. Chen's here,
let's all sit down and talk together.
I actually have something urgent,
gotta go.
It won't take long.
Just a quick chat.
That alright with you, Mr. Wang?
Why not? No secrets here.
Let's all sit down.
Go take care of your business.
Come on, have a seat!
This way.
Have a seat.
It's fine,
just talk for a bit.
Hong,
I'm on Zhongxing Road.
Where exactly?
I'll send you my location.
Okay.
He sent the location.
Put it in the GPS.
Zhongxing Road.
What?
They're headed for Zhongxing Road?
Do something!
Do whatever it takes
to stop them.
Stall them
until I get there.
Run them off the road
if you have to!
Do not let them
beat us to Jinhai KTV.
Understood?
Got it, sir!
You guys hurry up.
Mr. Chen,
last time you said
you and Wan Hong were childhood friends,
and you've worked together for years.
So you two go way back, right?
When you testified for Mr. Wang,
did the cops ask you to,
or was it your call?
Better not lie,
we'll double-check it
with someone else.
I did it on my own.
You chose to testify
against your old friend?
Did you hesitate?
Come on, with the way things are now,
who really has 'friends' anymore?
Your 'friend' for now
can stab you in the back one day.
Someone like me,
I don't get the luxury of hesitation.
I'm just a
traitor anyway.
Hey, that's enough.
What's that supposed to mean?
I mean,
that's what I am, a traitor.
That's what they're all calling me now.
'They'?
You mean Wan Hong?
Not him.
Mr. Wang, maybe?
Definitely not!
It's just gossip,
nobody specific.
And your relationship with Mr. Wang?
Personally,
I think we're
as close as brothers.
He showed me the ropes,
taught me business,
helped me build everything.
I owe my success to him,
and he
owes his to me.
Mr. Wang always put me first.
Needed a yard?
Wanted rail cars?
No problem, right?
Chen,
I don't think I ever
gave you any special treatment.
Ma'am,
we are,
not that close.
He's still mad.
We'd just had a little fight
right before
you walked in.
Alright, let's all calm down.
That thing you wanted,
consider it done, okay?
How long have you
and Wan Hai known each other?
Well,
it's been so long
you can barely keep track?
Right,
it's definitely been quite a while.
Back when he and his brother
first started
at the mine,
they came here
to work in distribution.
After a while,
we got to know each other.
It's probably been
over
ten years or so.
Ten years or so?
Then you must be pretty close.
So why did he go through
Mr. Chen to buy the hub
instead of coming to you directly?
Actually, Chen and I,
we're closer!
We're like family, right?
So if Wan Hai
wanted my hub,
it had to
go through Chen,
right?
Without him,
I never would have met Wan Hai,
let alone
gone through all this mess.
Right, Chen?
So you don't blame him?
I used to, sure.
But then I figured,
Wan Hai's a gangster.
Chen
was forced into it.
When it came time to turn Wan Hai in,
Chen and I even talked it through.
Right, man?
Mr. Hong,
that car's been tailing us
this whole time.
You're always so paranoid.
You think you own the road?
I changed lanes to see
if they'd back off,
but they're still sticking to us.
There's a fork coming up.
[443 meters ahead
Turn onto Unnamed Road]
But that path's a dead end.
Got it.
See? Still on our tail.
Mr. Hong, no way out up ahead.
Huai'en,
we haven't done anything wrong,
no need to worry.
Mr. Hong!
Hurry!
Things must've really gotten ugly
between you and Wan Hai,
if he just took over your hub like that.
Of course, ma'am.
Why do you think I hated him?
Why else would I turn him in?
But he still kept you on as GM.
Why go along with that?
Ma'am,
the guy's a gangster!
He does whatever he wants,
simple as that.
He forced me!
What choice did I have?
That was rock bottom for me,
you know?
There was nothing I could do.
Wait, is this...
You didn't use this for gambling,
did you?
No...
You're right!
Mr. Wang
always says, "No risk, no gain.
Got to gamble to get ahead."
He loves to play games
wherever he is.
And at that time, if I recall,
you were seriously in debt, right?
Collectors were knocking at your door.
Chen, what are you talking about?
The inspectors are here!
What 'time' are you referring to?
Was it before or after
the deal with Wan Hai was made?
Just kidding.
Seriously, ma'am,
what exactly are you here for?
What do you want to know?
Check the records
if you've got questions!
I've already told you everything!
I've been fully cooperative.
So what more do you want?
Thanks for your time.
Sorry, officers.
I really am swamped,
one text after another.
Mr. Wang,
mind if I ask?
The hub is huge now—
what's it worth?
Over a hundred million, I assume.
You mentioned before
that when Wan Hai took it,
it was worth fifty million at best.
Once he's in prison,
you get your hub back.
You're coming out on top.
That's life, huh?
Take care.
See you.
Mr. Wang,
when can I get those rail cars?
Hong.
What's up?
Hurry up.
What's wrong?
Get in the car.
What's going on?
Quick!
What...
Wait...
Come on!
Drive!
Let's go!
Hurry!
- Where are we going?
- Just drive!
What's wrong, man?
I think we're good now.
Hong,
I just checked,
there are 18 shops here.
My brother was here
for six hours that day.
Someone must've seen him.
Not many shops are actually open.
Some are that way, and some over there.
And that side...
Hong,
got a minute?
Hello?
Hong?
Are you busy?
Hello?
Ms. Zheng,
that's it for today's agenda.
Would you like to go back to the hotel,
or to the office?
It's still early.
Let's stop by the detention center.
I want to see Wan Hai.
Right now, ma'am?
Is that okay?
Of course!
I'll set it up. This way, please.
[Jinhai KTV, Zhongxing Road]
You two, hurry up!
Hey, over here.
Seriously? Why is this so hard for you?
Smash it.
Hong,
no one's seen him.
Give it to me.
Hurry! They're coming this way!
Come on!
Move!
Leave it!
Anyone here?
Gosh.
Hong.
The fish tank's shattered.
That water outside
must've come from here.
What happened here?
No idea, honestly.
Did you find anyone?
Nope.
Let's go.
Alright.
What's wrong?
I can't live with the guilt anymore.
Because I was
the umbrella
shielding Wan Hai's criminal outfit.
I admit it:
I took Wan Hai's money
and promised to clear his name.
I've failed the Party
and the nation that trained me.
Every step that led me here
was my own mistake.
I brought this on myself,
and I deserve whatever punishment comes.
Death would not be too much.
My brother...
Zhenxing...
Brother...
Hong, if this water matches
what was in Zhenxing's lungs,
then the evidence was planted, right?
Right?
Yeah.
Exactly.
Who are you calling?
Forensics.
Wait!
Why are you calling them?
To have them come out
and test the water!
Test this?
Right!
Who ran the tests last time?
Same people.
Same...
Hong, what do I do now?
Who can I go to?
Who can help me now?
No one can help.
No one!
What do I do?
Hong!
Help me figure something out.
Mr. Hong,
we should report this to the higher-ups.
Let our people handle it.
Tell Commissioner Sun.
Leave it.
This has nothing to do with us.
Keep your mouth shut.
Hong,
can you send your team out here?
I can't.
Just this once, help me,
please.
He doesn't get how this works. Drop it.
Please, help me, Hong.
Feng,
we're here for Zhang Wenjing's case,
You know that.
I'm begging you.
Get up, come on!
Feng!
Please, Hong!
Come on, listen to me.
Please, I'm begging you.
Mei didn't deserve this...
And Zhenxing didn't
deserve to die like that!
Where is it?
Got it.
I'll inform the higher-ups right away.
Lock down the scene
until we arrive.
Ladies and gentlemen,
how much longer is this going to go on?
I've told you everything I know.
Wan Hai, watch your attitude.
Zhang Wenjing's case
can't be resolved
in just one or two talks.
The provincial leaders
are here again today.
Let's give them all the facts
about that case, okay?
Wan Hai,
what was your relationship with Wang Yu?
I thought it was about Zhang Wenjing.
Why bring up Wang Yu now?
Just answer the questions;
you don't need to know why.
What was your relationship with Wang Yu?
It was alright.
We weren't exactly close.
How long have Mr. Wang
and Wan Hai known each other?
Back when he and his brother
first started at the mine,
they came here to work in distribution.
After a while,
we got to know each other.
It's probably been
over ten years or so.
Why did you take over
his freight hub in the first place?
For the money.
At the time,
most ore from Dongping
went through his freight hub.
That Wang Yu
just sat back
and raked it in.
Naturally, I wanted a piece of that.
I tried to buy it.
Since you took...
bought the hub,
why keep him on
as manager?
Weren't you worried he'd try
to get back at you?
If you'd ever met Wang Yu,
you'd know that's not in his nature.
Why'd he agree so easily then?
Even if the hub was underpriced,
the contract says it sold for
over 20 million.
Why would he work for you?
How should I know?
Honestly,
you'll have to ask him yourself.
He loves to play games
wherever he is.
And at that time, if I recall,
you were seriously in debt, right?
Back then
Wang Yu owed a ton of gambling debts.
Collectors were on him day and night.
He was desperate,
so he sold the hub fast
for the cash.
That's how Wan Hai got the hub.
If,
I'm just saying, if,
Wang Yu
was drowning
in gambling debt,
and got roughed up by collectors,
maybe that's why
he let the hub go so cheap,
and you
got your bargain.
You're getting a 50 million freight hub
for 25? Seriously?
Wang Yu,
you made an urgent request, you know?
And you demanded all cash.
I scraped together whatever I could
to get 25 million in cash for you.
You're taking advantage
of me at my lowest.
Come on, that's not fair.
If I just cut out
your kidneys right now,
would I get 25 million for them?
If I invested the money anywhere else,
it'd make more.
If not for our history,
I wouldn't have bothered.
What 'history'?
I don't think so.
So, it's my fault?
You know what I heard?
You owed money all over,
to both Mr. Zhang and Mr. Li.
What, all the debts came due at once?
Yeah, that's why he...
Come on, stop it!
Took advantage of you?
I actually saved your skin.
If you really want it,
just name a fair price.
Here, you talk to him.
Wait, you...
What's going on, Mr. Wang?
We all came here to make a deal.
Youcai's here.
Go ask around,
who else in Dongping
could've raised 25 million
in cash overnight?
Think it over.
Surprisingly,
the business
took off over the years.
Wang Yu regretted selling it,
and wanted it back.
So,
he turned you in, called you a gangster,
and accused you
of forcing
a crooked deal.
That's how you wound up here.
Does that
make sense?
Ma'am,
are you saying
I was framed?
Ms. Zheng,
that's not really appropriate, is it?
Wan Hai,
if that's really the case,
then tell us
why did you admit it.
Who made you do that?
Are you hiding something?
Was there any
false accusation involved?
Think carefully.
Look, officers,
stop trying to catch me out.
The only reason I admitted to anything
was to try and get a lighter sentence.
Like I said before,
Wang Yu wouldn't sell,
so I tried everything to get it.
It's all on record...
Qiao Zhenxing is dead.
Did you know that?
Happened the same day as your hearing.
How would I know
in here?
Wan Hai,
this case just keeps getting bigger,
and the fallout is growing too.
It's no longer just
a local anti-gang case,
and it's not something
you can handle on your own.
If there's anything else
you need to say,
now's the time to be honest.
You have to fight for your rights,
and for your chance.
Wan Hai,
I don't know what you're so afraid of.
If the freight hub was yours,
and so was the club,
you should stand up
for them
and not let anyone take them from you.
Always remember,
the law is your weapon.
The justice system
has your back.
Ma'am,
thank you.
But I'm really not feeling well.
I need to rest.
Alright.
Wan Hai,
hope you feel better soon
Guard.
Thanks.
Thanks, Hong.
Don't mention this
to anyone,
not even your sister-in-law.
Got it.
Ran can keep them.
If
the water sample we sent tonight
matches the one
they got from Qiao,
the one from the reservoir...
Ma'am,
I just don't get it.
Where
was Qiao
actually killed?
It's not just about
where the crime happened.
If those samples match,
then the evidence was tampered with.
Those are your words, ma'am.
Hong Liang,
I think
we need to do a second autopsy
on Qiao Zhenxing's body.
Say something!
But there's a problem, ma'am.
The thing is,
Qiao's at the funeral home.
The farewell's tomorrow morning.
It'll wrap up
around ten,
and after that, he'll be cremated.
Once that happens,
a second autopsy won't be possible.
♪At the river's end,
bitter rain and brutal waves♪
♪A human life is strewn with hardship♪
♪Brother, there's a weight on my heart♪
♪Until I meet Old Lady Meng,
I can't let it go♪
♪Since ancient days,
black and white have stood apart♪
♪Don't preach
that letting go makes you a Buddha♪
♪Even good folk may die unrewarded♪
♪So why should the wicked live in ease?♪
♪For one last breath,
for one clear principle♪
♪For this single rite,
I'll see it through to the end♪
♪I will wear my life thin
just to glimpse the snow-orchid bloom♪
♪I will shred these shoes
and barefoot tame the wind-blown sands♪
♪I will face rosy clouds by day
and lift a torch by night♪
♪Beneath the bright firmament,
I want every deed bound by law♪
♪I want the ones who set out
to return home, no matter how late♪
♪I want the rain that falls from heaven
to rise back into heaven♪
♪I want to earn my daily bread
while guarding this wild land♪
♪I want every righteous path on earth
to stand beneath clear skies♪
♪I want the well-diggers' pockets
lined with salt♪
♪And I want the heartless cheats
to feel the justice in their eyes♪