[Choi Soo Young]
[Gong Myung]
[Kim Sung Ryung]
[Kim Sang Ho]
[Jo Yoon Hee]
[Second Shot at Love]
[Prevention and Treatment of Alcoholism]
Korea is very tolerant toward alcohol.
You can easily purchase alcohol
at any time of day.
You can drink anywhere.
[Who is an alcoholic?]
Which one is an alcoholic?
You might think it's the homeless man,
who is too drunk to even walk.
But that's not necessarily the case.
It may also be people
[Han Geum Ju / Senior Engineer]
who have enviable jobs, and
are seen as hard-working experts in their fields.
An alcohol abuse diagnosis
is not about societal status
or professional competency.
Cheers.
If you're losing the ability to control
how much you drink,
you might...
[Ju Yeop]
[15 Missed Calls from Ju Yeop]
already be an alcoholic.
Must be crazy.
She's drunk.
[Episode 1: A Very Rational Alcoholic]
When did you get here?
You weren't picking up my calls.
Do you know how many times I called?
I didn't know.
I was grabbing a drink with Mi Yeon.
Geum Ju.
Do you love booze that much?
Let me ask you something.
Alcohol or me. Which do you choose?
Alcohol.
- What?
- I prefer booze to you.
Let's forget about getting married.
Oh, Ju Yeop.
Oh, no. Here I go again.
Son-in-law, it's still lunch hour, right?
I brought some rice cakes for you
to share with your co-workers...
What?
What do you mean?
Seven, seven, seven...
Wait... What is this...
Geum Ju.
Han Geum Ju!
Wait...
Where did she go after making this mess?
Geum Ju...
Gosh...
Hey, Han Geum Ju.
Get up right now!
Mom!
How could you ambush me like this without warning?
Without warning, my foot.
You wanted to shop for furniture
for your newlywed home.
You said to pick out a fridge
and a washing machine.
I told you so many times I was coming today!
Speaking of, how could you ambush me like this?
Ju Yeop told me everything.
You told him you prefer alcohol to him?
You called off the engagement?
That blabbermouth. He wasted
no time ratting me out.
Aigoo.
It must be true, then.
Hey. Are you insane?
Drinking is a normal part of social life.
How can I marry a man who doesn't understand that?
What did you just say?
He loved my drinking when we were dating.
But he totally changed once we set the date.
He nags me every single day.
How can I live my whole life with a man like him?
Absolutely not.
Marriage is not a joke.
Go beg at his feet.
Tell him you'll quit drinking.
Leave it. Why would I quit drinking for him?
I'm not the kind of woman
who lives and dies for a man.
I must've slept in a weird position...
Aigoo...
Are you okay?
You think I'm okay?
You think I'm okay right now?
[Ad: Contact me if you need to borrow money fast]
Geez.
Ju Yeop, I'll make Geum Ju beg at your feet.
Please come to her apartment.
He did read the text,
but no reply. And he won't pick up his phone.
Aigoo, what am I supposed to do?
What do I do?
He must be here. Aigoo!
You're here, Ju Yeop.
A bonus item!
What are you doing right now?
You haven't eaten anything all day.
I ordered chicken stew with neungi mushroom.
You want me to eat the stew now?
When you deserve to be stewed alive?
Come on. Stop.
Stop what?
Ju Yeop won't pick up my calls now.
What will you do?
Gosh, stop calling.
I'm not getting married.
That's it? You won't get married?
Marriage is not like a pension reservation.
You think you can back out by changing your mind?
You can cancel a one-night stay at a pension.
Marriage is for the rest of your life.
You should cancel it if you're not feeling it.
You think you're all that?
Marriage or whatever,
I'm just going to focus on my work now.
Focus on your work?
I thought you got extended leave
for ten years of service.
Focus on work, my foot.
I asked to be reinstated.
[HR]
Speak of the devil, this is work.
Gosh, I'm sorry. It turned out that way.
The groom's mother was such a diva.
I could tell this marriage would
bring a lot of hardship.
So, I suggested they break it up.
I'll treat you to a meal sometime. Okay.
Must you do all that?
Then, should I say that my daughter
broke it off because she prefers alcohol?
Aren't you embarrassed of yourself?
Why would I be embarrassed?
Shut up.
I'm the one who called off this wedding.
You keep your mouth shut.
So, why did you have to drag me
all the way down here?
Why? Why?
Speak of the devil, this is work.
"Senior Engineer Han Geum Ju.
We regret to inform you that
reinstatement will not be possible
as a replacement has been hired during
your requested extended leave..."
"Reinstatement will not be possible"?
Aigoo.
Your marriage fell apart,
your reinstatement fell apart...
And your apartment lease ends this month.
You already put the newlywed home on the market.
The one you put the deposit and savings on.
Am I supposed to just leave you stranded?
Why would I be stranded?
I can just stay at student dorms
until the house sells.
Shut up.
Quit drinking, no excuses.
Become a new person and go back.
I have no intention of quitting drinking.
Oh, I see. Then, quit being my daughter.
Let's quit being mother and daughter.
What are you doing?
Go!
Fine...
All right...
Wow, I don't think I need to come anymore.
Really? Am I healed?
No. Not at all.
You haven't healed a bit.
You've gotten worse.
So, why won't you come anymore?
What's the point of me coming
all this way to see you?
You don't take your medicine.
And I bear the brunt.
I won't treat a patient who won't listen. I won't.
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I've been busy working in the fields.
Pardon? I told you to rest, and you worked?
Wow, this is too much.
- Head nurse.
- Yes.
I won't be coming here anymore.
I hope you live a long life.
Gosh, why did you do that?
What do you mean?
It's harvest. Everyone's busy helping each other.
I can't just slip out.
Unless someone were to take my place...
Doctor.
Me?
No way.
Doctor Seo, you're back.
You are!
You took my place last time.
And you're here instead
of Grandma Soon Ae this time.
Gosh, you're so sweet.
It's not an easy thing to help someone like this.
I'm helping myself, not someone else.
What do you mean?
If a sick person gets sicker while working,
they'll call me over,
and that means I need to travel all this way.
I am helping myself
because I don't want to go through that.
Okay, okay.
We got you. Why don't we take a break?
While we take a break,
what if the Doctor sings a song for us?
Love it!
Come on. The work is hard enough.
No way I'll sing.
Just one song.
Sing for us!
- Gosh, I said I won't.
- Sing for us!
♫ When rain pours ♫
♫ I will be the biggest umbrella
in the world for you ♫
♫ So you can walk in peace ♫
♫ If you grow tired on your walk ♫
- Good?
- No way!
You can't just end it there! Sing more!
Let's focus on work.
We need to harvest all the way to there today.
Let's hurry up.
Great work!
- You're amazing.
- Come again!
Come back.
Grandma Kim Jeong Ja has
severe rheumatoid arthritis.
I'm worried about her working in the field.
Grandma Park Mal Soon's gastritis
is not getting better,
so I think we should switch the medication.
The osteoporosis for Grandma Lee Jeong Rae...
Stop.
You just finished work.
Take a breather.
All right. Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Good job.
I got these precious gifts, thanks to you.
How nice.
You're so good at field work.
I used to help out
when I lived with my grandmother.
Oh, right.
You mentioned your grandmother's from here, Bochun.
Yes.
It's beautiful here.
It's healing just to look around.
So happy. Right?
[Welcome to Lake Bochun Pension]
Hurry up.
I'm coming...
Dad, cheers!
Who's this?
My precious baby daughter!
Oh, Dad. Long time no see. You, too, Unni.
What are you doing here?
Weren't you getting ready
for the wedding all week?
Yeah, I didn't even call
because I didn't want to bother you.
What are you doing? In bright daylight.
We cleaned up right after the guests left.
We just got started. Just a drink after work.
I thought I'd just have one drink
before the twins came home from school.
It's so delightfully breezy today.
Perfect for day-drinking.
Gosh, my baby daughter.
You have amazing food luck.
We made this plum wine last year, and it's amazing.
A welcome drink.
- Come here.
Welcome drink, my foot.
This is all because of you.
It's all because of you!
While everyone else fed their kids
black bean noodles.
you two fed her liquor
and set them on a track.
Cheers!
[Liquor immediately upon graduation]
That's not all.
You'd stay up all night to drink.
You showed them how to drink.
[Valedictorian alcoholic]
And you drilled into them
that drinking is the most important thing
once you start working.
That's how she became addicted to alcohol!
What are you talking about?
That girl.
She broke off the engagement for liquor.
What?
He broke up with her for drinking too much?
That bastard...
No, not bastard. Bitch.
He didn't break it off. She did.
Your daughter broke it off
because he nags her about drinking too much.
What?
Mark my words.
There will be no more alcohol in this house.
Put your life on the line
if you're going to drink.
I'll end you for good!
Honey.
I heard Geum Ju out,
and she does have a point.
Get out.
Should I?
I knew he'd be like that.
I didn't like how he acted at his first visit.
Remember? We offered him a tiny bit of liquor,
and he passed out in the living room.
Actually, I knew it then.
He's not cut out to join our family.
I know, right?
Gosh, all this wasted plum wine...
You'll get hurt.
Leave it. I'll take care of it.
Is Mom okay?
She's fine. You know her temper.
She gets fired up, and then she calms down.
She'll get over it. It's okay.
I'm sorry. Because of me...
Shut it. Don't talk like that.
He's right. How can you live with someone
who nags you for social drinking?
Breaking it off was the right thing to do.
You understand me, Unni.
Of course I do.
Marriages break apart even
if you're crazy about each other.
Look at me.
Calling the wedding off is way better
than getting divorced like me.
What? Getting divorced is nothing in today's world.
That's what I'm saying. Divorce means nothing.
Calling off a wedding is no big deal.
I completely agree.
Breaking off an engagement isn't
even news these days.
- Right?
- Totally.
What? Called off the wedding?
Out of the blue?
Yeah.
The mother-in-law was a major diva.
What is she like?
Gosh, I don't even want to talk about it.
It was obvious the mother would
make her life miserable.
How was I supposed to marry her off?
So, I broke it off.
Good job.
Geum Ju is your precious daughter.
And no one should have to suffer
under a mother-in-law.
You did the right thing.
What was she like?
I said I don't want to talk about it.
I thought she'd torture her if she stayed in Seoul,
so I dragged her here with me
since she's on vacation.
Gosh, seriously.
What in the world did she do that
you called off the wedding?
Hyungnim*, come on. W-What did she do?
(Same as "unni" among women)
Huh? What is it? Spill it.
Gosh, why, why, why did you do that?
Tell us!
How did it happen?
She's just like you!
She just won't stop arguing.
I couldn't bear it! Happy?
Why are you lashing out at me?
Wow, it's almost like
there's some other reason
the engagement broke off.
What do you mean I lashed out?
Young Woong's mom, you didn't make
your daily payment today.
Can I pay you tomorrow?
Again?
You've pulled this way too many times!
Hyungnim...
Every other time, you let it slide.
Why are you so sharp today?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I was just wondering if she knows
how many times it's been.
I don't know, either.
Let's not keep count.
That's what I meant.
You can pay tomorrow. Tomorrow.
Thank you, Hyungnim.
Sure.
Well, I...
I'd better get going.
See you all tomorrow.
Suddenly?
- You're leaving?
- Hyungnim...
You're still wearing our apron and bandana...
[This is Mirae Studio]
Pre-wedding video, my foot.
We're getting married!
[Ju Yeop and Geum Ju are getting married]
[We promise to live happily ever after]
We were so cringey.
Auntie! Woo Ri and Na Rah are here!
Auntie! Auntie Geum Ju!
Auntie!
Auntie, Auntie, Auntie!
We just got home.
Oh, yes, just a moment.
- How have you been? Did you miss me?
- How many?
We missed you!
So, so much!
Did you? Auntie, too!
Auntie, let's play outside.
I want to go to Bochun Lake
and ride the merry-go-round.
Shall we? Okay! Let's go.
Giddy up!
Auntie! Hi!
Auntie, I'm here!
Auntie!
When did they get so big? Woo Ri and Na Rah...
Hey, Yeong Rong.
Unni, did you really break off
your engagement and come to Bochun?
Just a second.
Yeah.
I broke off the engagement.
Why?
Keep this to yourself.
He constantly nagged me about my drinking.
He finally made me pick between him and alcohol.
And? What did you say?
What do you think?
Obviously, I picked alcohol.
And I called off the wedding.
What did you just say?
Are you happy now?
Are you happy now that you've told
everyone you're an alcoholic?
Mom, what do you mean I'm an alcoholic?
I'm just an alcohol connoisseur.
I should smack you in the mouth.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean for the word to get out.
She's wrong for eavesdropping.
Stop blabbering!
I'd better sew up your mouth
so you can't drink anymore.
What? Aigoo, connoisseur?
- Connoisseur, my foot.
- Come on!
- Mom, calm down.
- Please stop.
This is her first vacation
in a long time. Let her rest!
Let me go!
Geum Ju, split! Split!
Hey! Stop right there!
Seriously!
How did I end up in Bochun?
So annoying...
Hey, Geum Ju. Is it true?
You really called off your wedding for liquor?
I heard it with my own ears.
Geum Ju, why do you live like that?
Let me live the way I want.
Rumor spread like charcoal smoke in tiny Bochun.
Geum Ju, we've got drinks that are worth
calling off a wedding for.
Want a drink with a side of pollock?
The pride of Bochun,
hailed as a genius since childhood.
What became of the daughter of Bochun?
So upsetting.
I'm not your daughter.
I was a tastier drinking snack than pollack.
Geum Ju did always like to drink a little.
A little?
She likes it enough to call off her wedding.
That tells you everything.
I can hear everything.
I became gossip that's easier
to peel than an onion.
Your aunt can't get married
because she loves to drink too much?
- Yeah.
- Stop.
Kids, look here.
It's not that Auntie can't get married
because she likes drinking.
It's that she's not getting married
because she prefers drinking.
There's a major difference.
There's a clear distinction. Okay?
Good going.
Teaching kids great lessons, Han Geum Ju.
Gosh, this country town is the same as always.
How does a rumor spread so quickly?
Gi Beom's mother is Bochun's loudspeaker.
Let me through.
She's a part of so many group chats.
If she tapped all of them,
that means every newborn in Bochun knows.
Gosh, why did she have to catch me?
What's so bad about calling off a wedding?
Why is everyone making such a fuss?
It's not for calling off a wedding.
It's you breaking it off for liquor.
I mean, you know this.
I work in a very male-dominated industry.
I, Han Geum Ju, tried so very hard to survive
in a space where you can't build
relationships without liquor.
I thought of drinking occasions
as an extension of work.
And how am I supposed to marry a guy
who nags me about drinking?
Wow, excuses galore.
You always loved to drink.
That's what I'm saying.
I'm lucky to get to work in a field that suits me.
If it were me, I would've cheered him on
with a hangover remedy, instead of nagging.
You think you're all that.
Still, you've dated for a while.
How come you don't seem
to have any lingering feelings?
Lingering feelings? What's that?
Is that the name of a new berry wine?
By the way, what's taking him so long?
[Bochun Car Center]
Gosh, so stressful.
Hey, how long are you going
to wrestle with the car?
Yeah. I'm disappointed.
Your friend is here for the first time in forever.
I'm sorry. I promised I'd fix this by today.
They said it was a brake issue, so I fixed it
but it's still not working.
Look. The warning light is still on.
Gosh, so stressful.
Can I take a look?
I'd be grateful if you did.
Gosh, looks like I'll be working in a skirt today.
Got it.
- The light's gone now.
- Daebak.
I had no idea it'd be an electrical issue.
Han Geum Ju strikes again.
Here I am, back on the scene.
I fixed it.
Got it.
Are you friends with the car owner?
I'm friends with him, too.
This is Ui Jun's car.
Ui Jun? Seo Ui Jun?
You didn't know? Ui Jun works at the Bochun Clinic.
Darn.
It must be Seo Ui Jun that I saw.
You met up with him?
We brushed by each other.
I thought I mistook someone for him.
Why is he in Bochun right now?
We thought we saw wrong at first, too.
A hotshot doctor in Seoul came
to a countryside clinic.
There's a serious medical vacuum in small towns.
[Bochun Clinic, 1 Year Ago]
The clinic had closed over a year ago.
Then, Ui Jun arrived like a king.
The entire town broke out in a festival.
It was a bigger celebration than
if ancestors returned from the afterlife.
Anyway,
Ui Jun is considered Bochun's God.
The savior of the townspeople.
Someone came here with major fanfare, and...
What about me? What?
Aigoo...
You think...
Seo Ui Jun heard about my news already?
Why? Are you embarrassed?
Me?
Me? Hilarious.
Why would I be embarrassed?
What happened between you and Ui Jun, by the way?
You used to be super close.
By chance, did he...
- nag you about your drinking, too?
- Gosh!
I don't know. I don't want to talk about him.
I'm leaving.
Geum Ju, Ui Jun is on his way.
Say hi before you leave.
Are you crazy? Why would I?
I also have a lot to do, you know.
Why didn't anyone tell me Seo Ui Jun is in Bochun?
It's because you throw a fit
every time anyone brings him up.
Whatever. I bought soybean stew ingredients.
Don't worry. Bye.
[Year 2007]
Hey, transfer student.
What are you doing? Get on.
Can't you tell?
Gosh, let me see.
Leave it. Go your way.
What if I don't?
Hey, you mustn't have heard about me yet.
Here we go.
Why do you carry...
I'm the expert fixer in this town.
When I was little,
there was a genius discovery show,
and I was a young mechanic-
- You were on that show?
- Almost.
But I grew up too quickly.
- What?
- Hey, hang on.
This will only take three minutes.
Imagine you're heating up
instant curry and waiting.
You ungrateful bastard.
Why is he here?
Whatever. I'll just not see him.
I'll just make sure we don't run into each other.
Thank you...
Han Geum Ju?
Long time no see. It's good to see you.
Good to see me?
I don't think that's the nature of our relationship.
I heard the news about your wedding-
Yeah, I called off my wedding.
Because I didn't like him nagging me
about my drinking. Happy?
What are you talking about?
What? You said you heard the news.
I heard the news about your wedding recently.
I was about to congratulate you.
But you broke off your engagement?
Because of liquor?
Yeah.
But the nature of our relationship isn't one where
we make small talk and ask about personal matters.
I didn't ask you anything.
You volunteered the information.
Anyway, let's pretend we don't know each other,
even if we bump into each other.
Just like we've been doing,
let's pretend we don't know each other. Okay?
No way in hell I'm eating the soy bean stew...
Don't pick them up.
Leave it. I don't want your help-
I have no intention of helping you, either.
You told me to pretend we don't know each other.
Whatever. Forget it.
I erased you from my life, anyway.
You're out.
Doctor, Patient Kim Young Im is done
with physical therapy.
- I'll take her to the consultation room.
- Okay.
How's your shoulder?
How could she be okay?
I'm sure she's rotting inside.
All she has to boast about is her two daughters.
But the first daughter got divorced
and the second one called off the wedding.
Right? Who knew Geum Ju would turn out like that.
I'm sure she's mortified.
It's wild that she broke it off for a reason
no other than alcohol.
That's why she lied, which is so unlike her.
You happy? You sound giddy.
Now that she must understand what it means
to rot inside because of your children,
I feel like the ribs I ate last month are
finally getting digested.
[Bochun's Treasure!
Bochun's Pride! Hosu Rice Wine!]
This darn, good-for-nothing booze.
Try this, too.
I can't eat anymore.
I'm full.
Really? Then, go brush your teeth.
Okay!
Geum Ju, eat up.
Dad, I'm also done.
Why? Eat more.
Are you feeling anxious?
It's okay. The rumor will dissipate soon.
It's not that...
It's too fatty.
Same here. A glass of beer
would go great with this.
No.
Pork belly pairs best with soju.
Look.
Gosh, Dad.
Pork belly is best with a cold beer.
You're both wrong.
Pork belly is best with a soju and beer mix.
Shake the soju.
Three parts of soju
and seven parts of beer. This is a smooth one.
It's really smooth. Really smooth.
- Geum Ju.
- This is perfect.
- Geum Ju?
- So perfect. I thought...
What?
Oh, the tornado.
I forgot about the tornado.
I'm going, going, going...
One shot.
Why take away their food?
You make me want to drink more, Mom!
- Cheers!
The drinks taste so good.
So delicious.
I'll cook more meat later.
Oh, really?
Let's cheers to that.
What are you doing so late at night?
I can't go to sleep. Just can't sleep.
You have scissors here.
Just use the scissors.
Why are you using your teeth? Here.
Because I can't tear you apart with my teeth.
This is too much.
Why did you drag me down here?
How dare you yell at me?
Stop grilling me.
I'm human, too. I get hurt, too.
Get hurt?
You do whatever you want
with no regard for anyone else.
Get hurt?
Do whatever I want?
- Me?
- You don't?
Think about Ju Yeop, whom you hurt.
Don't you feel bad? At all?
No. I don't feel bad at all.
Not even a little.
That bitch...
Gosh, I raised her wrong.
Feel bad? Bullshit.
We fixed the problem.
The sensor data is back to normal.
As expected.
We couldn't have resolved it if it weren't for you.
Oh, right, today's your last day
before vacation, right?
- Yes.
- Want to get a drink?
I'm not sure...
Let's do drinks another time.
I'll go home from here.
I'll help you process the payment.
[Pregnancy Test]
5,500 won.
Don't worry.
I've been meaning to break off the engagement.
No, I'll just break up with her today.
- Really?
- Yes, of course.
So, don't cry.
Better not scare the baby in your tummy.
Okay?
Don't cry.
[Ju Yeop]
- Why aren't you picking up?
- He's in the way of our drinks.
All right. Persevere. Endure.
Bottoms up!
Alcohol or me. Which do you choose?
Alcohol.
Let's forget about getting married.
Han Geum Ju, what are you talking about?
Let me set this straight.
I broke off this engagement.
I broke up with you.
Because you're...
worse than booze to me, you bastard.
Where did you go so early in the morning?
I didn't want to be home.
Glad to hear that. Follow me.
What is this? Where are we going?
Shut your mouth and follow me.
Wait. Mom!
Mom!
Where are we going?
Mom! Mom?
Mom, Mom, Mom...
Do you want to go on a date with me?
Gosh, are we burying something?
I don't want to go.
I'm so tired.
I'm not going.
You won't even tell me where we're going.
Gosh, seriously...
This is perfect weather to get buried alive.
How did she come up with this?
She wants me to collect mountain spring water?
She sure comes up with all kinds
of methods of torture.
Yes, Monk.
I'd like to contribute a roof tile
in the name of Han Geum Ju.
I will offer 500,000...
No, I'll wire over one million won.
- One million won?
- Nongmin Bank...
- 3319...
What are you doing right now?
Can't you tell?
I'm praying to Buddha so that
you can quit drinking once and for all.
Excuse me.
Come here.
Stop it. Why are you doing this?
Why do you think?
I'm trying to enlist Buddha's help.
I don't need to quit drinking!
You still don't get it, do you?
Step aside.
Monk, I will wire the money right away.
Oh, my gosh. Hey!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Han Geum Ju, just wait till I catch you!
Hey! Stop!
You're done the moment I catch you.
That girl...
Hey!
Stop right there!
The moment I catch you...
Hey!
Hey! Geum Ju!
Aigoo!
Geum Ju!
I'm telling you, I'm not quitting booze.
I'm not quitting. So, give up.
Hey. Hey!
Seriously...
Are you okay?
Where did you come from?
Seriously...
- Ma'am.
- Thank you.
What do we do with Geum Ju?
After getting in trouble because of her drinking,
she still can't get her act together.
I heard you give talks about alcoholism.
Do you know of a good way?
I don't know what happened between you two,
but you used to be best friends.
Think of all the good times you shared.
With alcoholism,
recognizing you have a problem is the first step.
Just give it time.
Given your effort, I'm sure she'll come around.
If you trust and wait,
they say people are bound to change.
Will she really change
if I trust and wait?
Taste this.
It's hot! Hot! Hot!
- It's perfectly seasoned.
- Is it good?
Rice wine would go great with this.
Right?
What if we down some rice wine
before your mom gets back?
Except if she catches us, we're dead.
You're back.
Where's Geum Ju?
I'm sure she'll come sooner or later.
Will she be back in time for the ritual?
Did she run off because she doesn't want
to face the relatives?
Could that be?
[Eldest Daughter Hyeon Ju]
Mom must be throwing a fit again.
I feel like she'll get worse if I go home...
[Seon Uk: What's up? Want to grab food?]
They're not even here yet, and you start cooking?
We'll order more when they arrive.
Wait for it to cook fully before eating.
You can eat beef raw.
Sir, please calm down.
How come you always go mad for meat?
Are you an animal?
You're crossing the line here.
I'm your brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law, don't cross the line
with your eating.
- Slow down.
- Shut up.
- This is...
- You don't even need to cook this at all.
- You can eat it-
- Beef is expensive-
You made me come when I didn't even want to.
And you two are fighting?
I see. You wanted me to watch your fight?
We weren't fighting. He was just picking on me.
He was just picking on me.
You're the one who picked a fight.
- You keep...
- Nope.
- I'm not eating with you guys. Bye.
- Fine, fine. We won't.
Sit.
You always leave.
You promised we'd have an enjoyable dinner.
Yes.
Ui Jun, Geum Ju is coming, too.
You're fine with that, right?
What?
Sure. I guess.
Does she know I'm here?
Of course not.
We staged this surprise reunion,
so you two can make up.
Gosh, make up for what? That was so long ago.
What happened to you two?
- Why did you cut ties?
- No need to ask.
I'm sure Geum Ju messed up.
It's not that.
Great, then. You can extend an olive branch.
Yeah.
Geum Ju is so immature, anyway.
This way, please.
And even in this situation.
I can't believe she called off
her wedding for booze.
How dare he talk about me behind my back?
Ui Jun, you were baffled
when you heard that, right?
Sure. Yeah.
Why did they call him?
I thought she'd have become
a much better person if we ever met again.
Sure.
I wanted to become a better person, too.
Don't worry.
I've been meaning to break off the engagement.
No, I'll just break up with her today.
Alcohol or me. Which do you choose?
Alcohol.
I couldn't let a jerk like that ditch me.
Of course, I should ditch him first.
That way, I could at least save face.
You can't put spring water
on an ancestral ritual table
instead of alcohol.
Yes, you can.
- This is not right.
- It is right.
Oppa, you speak up.
- Well...
- He has nothing to say.
His daughter broke off her engagement for booze.
- What?
- Broke off her engagement?
- What do you mean over booze?
What do you mean by that?
She called off the wedding
because he nagged her about booze.
Incredible, right?
But...
who raised Geum Ju to be so incredible?
The eldest son of the family
who taught them how to drink from a young age.
And all of you,
who offered endless booze
at gatherings, played a part, too.
Am I wrong?
If you feel any morsel of responsibility,
don't mention alcohol again.
I will...
just trust and wait.
My Geum Ju is not a thoughtless kid,
so she'll quit drinking.
She'll never go near alcohol again-
I'm home!
Why do you keep running away?
Uncle!
Auntie!
You're here to see me?
Right, today's Grandpa's memorial...
Geum Ju.
Why the hell did you show up drunk?
We can't even put liquor
on the ceremony table because of you!
What did you say?
What? There's really no booze there.
Gosh, Grandpa loved to drink.
Gosh, no wonder.
I knew why I was pulled to...
buy this today when I saw this.
I...
Wait. Move over.
Here, have a glass.
- Grandpa, have a glass...
- Geum Ju...
your mom is mad. Stop.
- What?
- Your mom...
Unni.
Let go. Let go. What?
How can we leave liquor off
of our grandpa's ceremony table?
Look, look.
Grandpa is nodding. You saw, right?
- You crazy bitch.
- Let me pour you a glass.
Let me. Let me do it.
Let go of me.
Let go!
What's gotten into you?
I don't think...
you would come around with trust and time.
I told you.
Risk your life if you want to drink.
Why don't you pour your grandpa a glass
and follow in his steps?
Pour him as much as you want.
Mom, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
I'm not okay!
You crazy bitch!
Are you finally awake?
Seo Ui Jun?
Why are you here? Where am I?
What happened?
I asked you what happened, you bastard!
Hey, Han Geum Ju.
You really need to quit drinking.
[Epilogue]
This will only take three minutes.
Imagine you're heating up
instant curry and waiting.
Why isn't it working?
Hey, you said this will only take three minutes.
You said to imagine I'm heating up instant curry.
I could've gone to the market,
got the ingredients,
made curry at home, and did the dishes, too.
I could be in bed by now.
Just wait.
I now understand why the
genius discovery show didn't cast you.
Genius, my foot.
Hey.
I really am Bochun's genius.
Are you laughing at me right now?
Looking down on me right now?
How could I not?
You're not Bochun's genius. You're Bochun's goon.
La-di-da.
- What?
- Look at your face.
Geez.
Look.
Come on.
Let's just go. Your scooter is going
to run out of power.
No.
As Bochun's genius Han Geum Ju,
I will live up to my name and fix it.
It's almost done. Wait a little longer.
♫ My heart keeps beating ♫
♫ As I navigate the darkness
with nowhere to lean ♫
♫ Lonely, with no one to talk to ♫
There we go.
♫ Like spring that fought
the winter to arrive ♫
♫ It gives me butterflies ♫
Hey, since I fixed your bike,
you have to come with me
to get my scooter tomorrow.
You're Bochun's bully, not a genius.
What did you just say?
♫ No matter how brightly the world shines ♫
♫ I only see you ♫
Focus on steering straight.
Fine, just hold on tightly.
Just hurry up.
Are you a turtle?
You're just too heavy.
I'm just going to walk.
♫ I dream a new dream ♫
♫ Like my heart is empty ♫
[Second Shot at Love]
If you sell any of my family booze,
and I won't do business with you again!
It's driving me crazy that
I can't drink at home.
Now I can't even drink in town?
Do we all need to follow this order?
No way!
Everyone has joined forces to help you.
Geum Ju, quit drinking.
Live up to you name.
- What?
- Something bad must've happened.
She dashed away.
Damn it!
Hey, Geum Ju! Wake up!
Hyungnim, Geum Ju...
Geum Ju!
♫ Silently smiling ♫
Dramaday.me