Ein chol스템
Director of commander-in-chief Zhang was devastated
He had complaining with a enough eyes
The one who destroyed the former emperor died in the wild
The demon-slaying is true
It seems that there is a demon-slaying
The former emperor died, now it's Lord Zhang
Who will be the next emperor?
The next emperor is the one who will be the next emperor
One nose is not sharp, two eyes are not clear
One mouth is not clear, two ears are not clear
How do you know that the cat demon likes to eat these disgusting things?
This has happened before
That year, Lin Wude died without a clear reason
His heart was hollowed out
The people in the government did not find out the cause
Then the chief sealed the back mountain
Zhang Cheng, stop talking nonsense
I closed the back mountain for the safety of the students
Who told you it was because of the cat demon?
You are not allowed to cause trouble
Let's bring this matter to the level of threat
Then the murderer can be released
OK, according to what you said, it's not the cat demon
Then it can only be the emperor
It's true
The death of Duan Sheng
The emperor is the biggest evil person
Then the direction has been unclear
Yesterday, someone was at the academy
Found the evidence of the emperor
Then Lord Zhang died
What is it that he is not the cat demon?
Everything is a speculation before the emperor was found
The most important thing to investigate is evidence
You are empty-handed and slanderous
Who slanders?
You have to say something
Enough
Zhou Sheng
You saw Lord Zhang's body is well secured
Dare to send a case in the academy
So arrogant
Even if it's a demon
I have to get it out
One nose is not sharp
Two eyes are not clear
One mouth is not clear
Two ears are not loud
Little cat, little cat, come quickly
Eat this spirit heart
How can there be such a strange demon?
There is a little mystery in this life
Since the murderer used the demon to kill people
There will be more victims
Then we will get the murderer out
I also want to know
Who is it?
Dare to marry me to the cat demon god
Cat demon god
You also believe in the demon blood
How is it impossible to know the world?
The evil spirit said
Believe it or not
I will go to the cat demon god
I still don't understand
Who is Li Wude mentioned by Zhen Sheng?
Li Wude is famous among the students of the previous books
Is it because he is talented
Or good character
It's because he doesn't take the exam every year
But there are years to take the exam
So the students in the academy have a deep impression of him
Until that year
He fell into the trap again
Found the chief of the mountain to ask for mercy
Chief, please give me another chance
I can do it today, chief
I didn't expect you to do such a thing
Chief, please
You disappointed me too much
Chief
Chief, please
After seeing him again
He put down his body in the back hill
His face was completely burned
His heart was also dug away
There were also many cat claws on his body
Since then
The cat demon god's words are even more effective
The chief sealed the back hill
This murderer may be a model
Maybe he is the one who killed Li Wude
The murderer
Chief Zhou
Just say it
Zheng Sheng found the clue of the emperor
And brought people there
Why don't you stop him
What if he is a military snake
Let's go
Brother Zhou, can we go together
The back hill is desolate
You should stay in the academy
My brother and I are in close contact with the emperor
We may be of help if we go together
Okay
You go to report to the chief
Go
Say it
Where is your brother
You bad girl
Let me go
You
Enough
Zheng Sheng
You said you knew the clue of the emperor
Yes, brother Zhou
This bad girl
How do you know her brother
If it wasn't for Wang Sheng's stop
I can definitely ask
Ask what
You have to make a big claim to a child
Why do you talk about escaping
I can't
I have my own way
Stop
Make a move on a child
Do you have any pity
Child
Do you live here
You go back with Uncle Shan Zhe
Arrange a place for you
Wait for your brother to come back
Okay
Thank you, chief
Fan Shutong
Yes
You take care of the emperor and sister
Make sure it's arranged
Yes
Go back