The King's Avatar
Episode 1
What are you doing?
I've made it clear.
It's not me.
If you're not guilty,
why are you holding the dagger?
Why?
You're students,
yet you're so
I just found the broken pieces in the row of flowers.
Oh, yeah.
I was there that night.
It was too dark.
I slipped a little bit.
I didn't send the broken bowl to them.
Then why did you
change the cleaning time with Xiaosi?
He can't get up.
I helped him.
Is it wrong to help others?
You're lying.
The cleaning of the yard is fake.
Your real purpose
is to clean up the crime scene.
No, I didn't.
That day,
you met the worst cut
on your way to deliver soup to Zhou Sheng.
met the most powerful Duan Sheng.
Maybe he spilled your soup
or he was humiliated by you.
Because of the conflict,
in the quarrel,
your sleeve was cut by the coffin
and left this broken cloth.
You knocked Duan Sheng down.
You hate the evil-looking, bold and wild life
from the heart.
You kicked him down with one foot.
So he left
the ashes of your feet on him.
Duan Sheng fell into the flower pot.
You didn't do anything.
You grabbed his head
and hit the stone in the flower pot hard
until he died.
Right?
No.
It's not like that.
You were really scared.
But you quickly calmed down.
Because you knew
Duan Sheng was
fooled by the legend of the cat demon killer.
So you used a knife
to cut off his tongue
and framed his death
on the legend of the cat demon killer.
The evidence is clear.
How dare you say no?
No.
It's not like that.
Duan Sheng is a member of the cat demon killer.
He's a servant.
He deserves it.
Duan Sheng may be guilty,
but he's not guilty of death.
You should find an excuse for your behavior.
I didn't provoke him or offend him.
I used to hide from him when I saw him.
But that night,
I met a scoundrel like him.
He came up without saying a word
and broke my plate.
He beat me with his neck
and cursed me as a cat demon.
Mr. Duan.
Cat demon!
I almost got killed by him.
I used all my strength
to knock him down.
Mr. Duan.
I was so scared at that time.
I was afraid that he would die
and I was afraid that he would wake up and take revenge.
Mr. Duan.
Let go.
I was so scared after Duan Sheng died.
Luckily, fewer people came to the backyard.
But someone found out early in the morning.
You must clean it up as soon as possible
Brother Gou
Fan
You didn't sleep well this night, did you?
Yes
How about this?
I'll help you
You go back and rest
Thank you
Stop laughing
I thought I could do something without knowing if I transferred the body
As long as no one finds out the real crime scene
There will be no clue
But you forgot
There is a piece of cash in the flower bed
The cash in the flower bed is exposed
It's true
God is watching
Xiaoyun
Don't come here
Put down the knife
What are you doing?
Young master
I'm sorry
I killed them
But I still don't understand
Why did you kill Mr. Zhang and Huang Sheng?
Huang Sheng saw me kill people
I can only kill him
As for Mr. Zhang
He bought the students' strategy
And said otherwise, he would seal the moon
Let all the students lose the opportunity to be a official
My son's biggest wish is to be an official
Since I killed Duan Sheng
It doesn't matter if I kill another Mr. Zhang
Xiaoyun
Why are you so stupid?
It's just like this
Young master
We made the same mistake
I don't want to be a burden to more people
As long as I die
It's the best ending to fight with my life
Who wants to fight with his life?
Duan Sheng is the most capable
Even if the people from the government come
I can be your witness
All the students in our school can be your witness
Am I right?
Okay, young master
Don't say anymore
Mr. Tao is right
Duan Sheng shouldn't die
I should have this ending
Young master
I believe you
You can be promoted
Remember me
Come to my grave and tell me
It's a wish for me to end my life
Xiaoyun
No
The flower blooms and the world is re-enacted
Brother Tao
The case is solved
Why are you still so confused?
I always feel that the matter is not so simple
You mean the murderer has another person
No, he is the murderer
Duan Sheng should be killed by him
But Mr. Zhang is eight feet tall
He is a big monster
Fan Shutong is thin
How did he fall on the beam?
I suspect that the murderer is more than one
Fan Shutong committed suicide for the crime
The purpose is to protect this person
Zhou Shang