The
Brother
I saw the tears on your face
When?
Where?
Stop looking
Here
pigs
So there's someone else
Your chance
was this
The
먹을 거 핏
어나
Intelligent
I wanna know
Hi, so what
I want to ask you
The truth95
If I tell you everything
can you tell me why?
You were
I don't know
You don't believe me, do you?
What are you doing?
There's nothing written in the book.
The spiritual leader is a new person.
He's not old or injured.
I've lived like this for a thousand years.
This is the real person.
For a thousand years,
I've been changing my identity,
my address, my surname.
I don't have a family or friends.
I've lived countless false lives like this.
Aren't we friends?
A thousand years ago,
I had a silent family.
Do you remember
the time we first met?
We were always together.
We knew each other well.
We were like a perfect match.
But he died because of me.
Is this friend
the one you drew in your house?
So you think we look alike
and that's why you took me in and helped me,
right?
No.
You're not like him.
You are him.
So this time, I must protect you.
Tell me the truth.
Then I can help you.
I... I forgot.
What did I see in the first five years?
What I told you is different.
I really forgot.
I forgot.
Yes.
I came in 2005.
After I was pushed down from the cliff,
I finally got my life back.
Then I don't remember anything.
Then I went to 2025.
Then we met.
I...
I didn't tell you that time.
I was afraid I would scare you.
I was afraid you wouldn't believe me.
Someone wanted to hurt you.
Who is it?
I don't think
I can see your face clearly.
So you came to the library
to find a way to get through?
Yes.
But I haven't summed up the rules.
Since you came in 2005,
you must find a way to get through.
But the murderer didn't find it.
Even if you go back, you'll still be in danger.
Indeed.
So I want to go back this time
and find clues.
Then what did you find?
I found this.
I saw this on the crime scene.
The murderer must have left it.
But you lost all your memories.
Maybe this is yours.
Look at the carving and the carvings.
They are so detailed.
I'm a student.
I can't afford it.
I can find its source.
I have a way.
This pen is a limited edition
of the gold factory in your name.
There were five of them in total.
Four were bought by foreign buyers.
And there is one more.
Xinshan University.
But the information from 20 years ago
is not in the electronic file.
We can't find the whereabouts of the pen.
Then can you check it?
Is it a polite risk
to talk to your friend's sister?
Stop pretending.
I knew you weren't her sister.
Time has passed.
I haven't had the time to tell you.
Brother Wang knows everything.
Brother Wang.
Her ancestor is Huang Xiao Mei.
Huang Xiao Mei.
A thousand years ago,
her brother and I studied in Xinshan Academy.
Then we were in danger.
I took over her.
The Huang family has been
helping me with business.
How did she know?
We went through something
extraordinary together.
We...
You went through it.
You remember?
I didn't have the time to check it yesterday.
But today,
I suddenly have more memories.
I remember
you came back from your mom's funeral.
She was with you.
This is extraordinary.
I thought you wouldn't believe it.
After all,
I've seen some incredible people since I was a kid.
Is it possible to be a bad person?
We don't have much time.
Let's go check it.
Wait.
I have some important documents.
I need you to sign it.
Wait for me outside.
I'll come to you when I'm done.
What do you want to say?
July 12, 2005.
It's not the first time I've seen her.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry.