(Praomook)
If you will help me with my house,
I'm willing to be married to him
for a year.
And if he can't make me believe
that he can be a good executive,
I will not let him
take over this company.
A man had followed us on a bike.
I saw him about to shoot you,
so I turned the wheel.
This is the third time
he tried to shoot you.
- What do you want from him?
- It's none of your business.
Alright.
I'll find the answer myself.
You like women. We used to date.
How can you like men?
Our relationship ended.
He is the person
in my life right now.
I can't marry you.
I don't like women.
Be honest with me.
Why don't you want to marry her?
Because she is Praomook.
Her selfishness disgusts me.
I hate her more than
anything in my life.
I hate her and will never love her.
The date for the wedding.
It's two weeks away.
I think it's too soon.
The longer we wait,
the worse it will be for Lan.
He was shot and had a car accident.
We can't wait anymore.
I get it. You worry about your son.
But to be honest with you,
I don't want to
sell my daughter for money.
You're not selling your daughter.
You're helping my son.
Look, Da.
Don't take this the wrong way.
This is a win-win for all of us.
Since Mook is helping my son,
we want to help you
and your family in return.
But your offer is a lot of money.
Da, I understand you.
However,
Pethai has helped me many times.
One time I was close to bankruptcy
and he let me borrow his money.
Everything I am is because of him.
Now that his family
is having a tough time,
it's normal for me
to want to help him.
Please.
- I'm begging you.
- No, Pat.
I accept your offer.
If Pethai knew about this,
he would let Mook marry Lan.
Da, thank you so much.
So,
do we have your permission
to host the wedding?
Yes.
There's one more thing
that I need your help with.
What is it?
I want you to work for my company.
Just tell me what field
you want to work in,
your position, and expected salary.
And I'll arrange that for you.
But on one condition.
Within a year, you have to get
Lan to come to work.
If you can do that,
I will clear all of
your father's debts.
Okay. I will work for your company
and will get him to come to work.
It's time for him to grow up.
You can tell me
what position you want.
I'll tell Lak to arrange it for you.
Consider it is your company.
Hi.
According to Mook's resume,
she has a degree in interior design.
I think it's best to have her work
with Win in product development.
Keep an eye on her
and report to me on her every move.
Got it?
Alright.
What makes you distrust her?
I don't trust her. I'm afraid
she will try to steal from us.
Mook, what position
do you want to be in?
Do you want to be in management?
It will be a perfect position for
my future daughter-in-law.
She has no work experience though.
If she works outside her field,
she will be seen as privileged.
That will look bad on us.
Why would it look bad on us?
You and Danai don't have a degree
in your line of work either.
And you seem to be doing fine.
Everyone knows it's nepotism.
So what?
Danai and I are working
outside of our specialties
because the company
had issues with people back then.
I'm saying this
because I'm worried that
Mook won't get to do
what she is good at.
Win's team has
an available position.
If he has a graduate
with honors to help him,
it will be great.
I agree.
My team needs a fresh pair of eyes.
I think she may have
some nice ideas for our products.
Are you interested?
I'd like to work in design
like Lak has suggested.
That's great.
Design is one of the key components
of our company.
Then I'll have Win give her
a tour of the department.
Win, please take care of Mook.
Of course.
Please follow me.
Lan, they approved our proposal.
Let's get to work then.
Hey.
What's wrong? Don't be modest.
- What's up with you?
- What?
- Come on.
- Lan!
- Let's go.
- I know. I can walk.
- Just go.
- We can walk like normal people.
It really seems like
they love each other.
Is my sister going to be
the other woman?
This zone has furniture
for the family market.
These sofas are minimalistic
and made of mainly wood.
Look at these products. You might
get an idea for a new concept.
Okay.
- Can I talk to you about this?
- Sure.
Give me a moment.
You can look around the place.
Sure.
- Hello.
- It's me, Praomook.
Duckling, why are you calling me?
I'm at your father's company.
I agreed to work for him.
What are you trying to do?
Nothing.
I heard from your father
that you don't want to work here.
As your future wife,
I'll fill in for you.
When we're married,
the company will be mine.
You finally revealed your evil plan.
Are you a leech
trying to suck my father dry?
Stop calling me
a duckling or a leech.
My name is Prao.
Is your brain damaged?
Maybe it's better to have
a mindless, brain-damaged husband.
The denser he is, the better.
Now I will be able to take
everything that belongs to you.
The company belongs to my dad.
I don't care if he gives it to you.
You can do whatever you want.
Don't call me again. It's annoying.
Why did Mook call you?
Mook?
When did you become close to her?
Since I decided to go after her.
You're making a mistake.
The duckling called me,
saying she is at the company.
She is trying to take over
my father's company.
It's your father's company.
So why are you angry?
I'm not angry. I'm just frustrated
by the idea of being scammed.
She's willing to do anything
for money. No dignity at all.
Hey. You're being too harsh.
You said she went there to work.
She is being useful.
At least in your father's eyes,
she is reliable, unlike you,
who causes trouble every day
and refuses to go and work for him,
even after graduation.
He thinks you're
an uncommitted, immature,
stubborn, ungrateful son
who likes to fool around.
Rut, you don't have to
try to sound like him.
I'm your friend.
You should be on my side.
I'm neutral.
If I were your parent,
I would adore Mook more than you.
- You're unfair.
- Of course.
What is it, Poom?
I've got the video from
the security camera you asked for.
Mook.
- Hi.
I'm Natdanai,
Lak's husband
and Lan's brother-in-law.
Okay.
I heard you will be working here.
Do you want to be
an assistant manager?
I've been looking for
someone to help me.
I'm not good at management.
I'd rather work in design.
You can always tell me
if you change your mind.
As a daughter-in-law, it's good to
be knowledgeable about management.
So you can help Lan out
in the future.
I'll help him once he comes to work.
That's good.
Anyway, do you want to get
the general idea about management?
Sure.
Follow me.
I tried to get videos from different
angles, but they were low-quality.
The traffic cameras
don't use HD technology.
That bike was intentionally
following you.
This is...
Is that a gun?
A man had followed us on a bike.
I saw him about to shoot you,
so I turned the wheel.
And while you were unconscious,
he walked toward you with a gun.
So I called for help.
What Mook told you is true.
Someone did try to shoot you.
Being hunted down like this,
did you step on someone's toes?
- I don't know.
- Exactly. You had no idea.
How would I know?
I was fighting with Mook.
Mook is a key witness.
To me,
she is a suspect.
Lan.
Please sit here. I'll call you when
it's your turn to do an interview.
May I have your resume?
- Wait.
- What is it?
Can I have a minute with you?
Are these people applying for
the same position as I am?
Yes.
Why are there so many people?
Our company is one of the best
in the gaming industry.
Although this is a part-time job,
it's a way to advance your career.
That's why we do formal interviews
just like any other positions.
I'll call you when it's your turn.
Alright.
Peerapat.
It's your turn.
Boss.
What is it?
Will you interview the candidates?
- Nampetch?
- Here.
It's your turn.
- Please follow me.
- Okay.
Please go over there.
- Well...
- Please take a seat.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
You don't meet
our first qualification.
Why are you applying for the job?
Because I want to work here.
I don't want to
miss the opportunity.
In my opinion, age is just a number.
It can't determine how good
someone is at their job.
Are you saying you're good?
I'm confident in my skill set.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have applied.
Anybody can say that.
I can give you an example of
how age doesn't matter in work.
You.
Go on.
You started working at a young age.
You built this company
when you were 18 years old.
You became an influential person
when you were 20,
becoming an idol to many people.
If age did matter,
you would've waited until for
the right age to start your career.
That's why I think
age is just a number.
People's skills are more important.
Complimenting me
won't give you extra points.
I'm simply stating the facts.
I don't want anything in return.
I don't believe that Mook can
get Lan to come to work.
You saw it.
He doesn't want to marry her.
Bringing her here
will only push him away.
I don't think he will come here
because he wants to see her.
I think
Praomook will know a way
to get him to work here.
Exactly. I believe she can do it
because she knows him well.
That was when they were still young.
Since Lan went abroad,
we barely saw her.
I think she even avoided us.
Mook and Petch
didn't come to my wedding.
Lan and Mook are strangers
at this point.
Come on. With this matter,
they will know each other better
once they get married. Am I right?
That's right.
They will eventually become close.
If he doesn't want to work here,
just let him be for now.
You don't have to ask
an outsider for help.
Danai and I can run this company.
Lak,
it's time for Lan to do his duty
as the family's heir.
Your and Danai's job is to
take care of the company for him.
We all have our duties.
Alright.
Let's see how Mook is doing today.
Come on, dear. Let's go.
That's a good idea. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Alright.
Come on, Lak.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Dear, is that Lan?
I'm not hallucinating, right?
You're not hallucinating.
It's really him.
I can't believe
Mook got him to come here
on her first day of work.
Maybe
she knows a way
to get him to work here.
We're on the right track, dear.
We have to follow them now.
Lak, do you see? Lan's come to work.
- He is here. Let's go, Lak.
- Dear, let's go.
Hurry.
We're targeting Asian
and European markets.
That's why we use modern designs.
We want our products
to remain timeless.
Alright.
- Right.
- I like this design.
- This one has a European style.
- Okay.
It's a top-selling product.
I have to talk to you.
Lan.
I can't let you out of my sight. You
throw yourself at any man you see.
Are you mad?
You insulted me out of nowhere.
Leave Danai alone.
The more you say no,
the more I want in.
If you do it,
I will make you regret it.
Is that all you have to say?
Let go.
You said someone tried to ambush me.
I believe you now.
So? If you want to say
that you're grateful for my help,
go ahead. I'm listening.
You're behind everything.
What are you talking about?
You saved me several times.
It's too coincidental.
You walked into my life
at the same time the attacker did.
You made the fortuneteller tell
my parents that I have to marry you.
You've planned everything.
I didn't do it.
If I'd wanted to do that, I'd have
picked a richer and nicer guy.
You can't pick anyone else
because you're in love with me.
You're full of yourself.
Your actions speak volumes.
You've planned to marry me,
sleep with me,
and get pregnant so you can have me.
Your mind is dirty and disgusting.
I would never try to trap a jerk
like you by getting myself pregnant.
I can be worse.
Do you want to try me?
- Let go.
- You hurt me, I hurt you.
You wrong me, I wrong you.
Let go.
You sent someone to attack me,
didn't you?
- I didn't do it.
- Stop denying it.
I know a way to make you talk.
Lan, get off.
- Lan!
What do you think you're doing?
What's going on?
Here are the games I've played.
I play all kinds of games
and I'm at a high level in each.
Being good at playing games
doesn't mean
you will be good at your job.
I'm not showing you the video
to make you see my skill.
It's to show you
that I'm a serious person,
that I know each game's
strengths and weaknesses.
And being a player myself,
I know your customers' needs.
You wrote in the application form
that you can dance.
Can you show us your talent?
Sure.
Lan, even if you don't like women,
you can't touch her like that.
You disrespected her.
You have to take responsibility.
That's right.
You have to be a gentleman.
You have to take responsibility.
If you do this,
it will settle everything.
This is the wedding date.
The fortuneteller
set the date for us.
You will get married in two weeks.
Take it.
- Lan!
What are you doing?
I'm not marrying her. Don't take
advantage of the situation.
It's you who took advantage of her.
You're saying it like
I'm a bad person.
Aren't you curious why
I don't want to marry her?
Are you trying to say
that you're in love with Rut?
You don't have to repeat that.
That is one of the reasons.
The thing is, she has a boyfriend.
And I don't want to
steal someone's girlfriend
because I'm not as shameless
as your favorite girl.
Is this true, Mook?
This man isn't my boyfriend.
If you want a confirmation,
I can arrange it for you.
Boss, what is your decision?
Just say it if she is hired or not.
Don't keep quiet.
I'm on the edge of my seat.
When can you start?
I can start anytime.
I'm available every day.
Then I'll have human resources
let you know when you will start,
because you're under 18
and still in high school.
This is a summer break.
Plan your schedule
with your supervisor.
- Get the hiring process right.
- Yes, Boss.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
Deal.
Thank you so much, Marut.
- I will work hard.
- Hey.
Take it easy.
Okay.
I've got a job.
See you tomorrow. Bye.
Were you watching your girl?
She isn't my girl.
But you hired her.
Are you sure it isn't favoritism?
There is no favoritism
in our company.
I see. This means you hired her
because of her skill set.
I know you're
a forward-looking person.
It's normal.
I think she can be useful,
so I hired her.
How?
I guess I should look for
a new CEO's assistant too.
A client meeting
is next on your schedule.
My name is Oak. I'm her best friend
and her manager.
Her manager. Does this mean
she is a very busy person?
She is very busy, ma'am.
Let me show you.
She is a DJ with
hundreds of thousands of followers.
She has a lot of offers. My job is
to filter through things for her.
Are you sure you're just friends?
You are always with her.
If you're more than friends,
just say it. Don't lie.
As her manager, wherever she goes,
I have to accompany her.
She works at nightclubs.
You know it's dangerous for a woman
to be out alone at night.
- Yes, I know. It's very dangerous.
- I agree.
And because I'm worried about her,
I always accompany her
and keep men from bothering her.
- I see.
- You do the right thing.
He can say whatever he wants.
Lan, don't interrupt us.
We haven't finished talking.
I assure you that he is my friend.
There is nothing more,
despite what some people may think.
Besides, I love being a DJ.
I assure you that
she only works as a DJ.
She does this
because she wants to make money
and she loves music.
She makes music too.
I'll play one of her mixes.
She makes music.
Let's listen to it.
Oh dear. You're brilliant.
- Here you go.
- Did you make this?
- Oh.
- Wow.
Dear.
Take it easy.
This reminds me of when I was young.
Dad, Mom. This isn't the time
to entertain yourselves.
We're having a serious conversation.
Okay. I'll be serious.
Alright.
Now that I've heard everything,
I can conclude that she will be
the perfect daughter-in-law.
She is perfect in every way.
Wow.
You've known to make a living
since you were in school.
You're motivated and diligent.
You're much better than him.
Dear.
Alright. In short,
Mook is the perfect girl
to be my daughter-in-law.
I stand by my statement.
You have to marry her
no matter what.
Don't you suspect that
the car accident
might have been her and
the fortuneteller's plan?
It's too coincidental that he
specifically said it has to be her.
There are other women
who were born on that day.
I think there must be
something more to this.
There is nothing more to this.
Master is a man of virtue.
He wouldn't do a nonsensical
thing like that.
More importantly,
Mook doesn't know him.
Lan, this is temporary.
We'll be married for only a year.
I've given up many things for you,
why are you dismissing
everyone's concern for you?
I don't want to get married
because it's you.
If it were someone else,
I'd have said yes already.
What's wrong with me?
Or are you scared that
you will fall in love with me?
I'm scared that
you will drag me down.
Besides, I don't want to hurt Rut.
I can talk to him for you.
If he loves you and knows that
I'm marrying you
to save your life,
he will agree to this.
After everything I've said, you're
still insisting on marrying me?
What Mook told you is true.
Someone did try to shoot you.
Mook is a key witness.
To me, she is a suspect.
Alright. If you guys
want me to marry her,
I will do it.
Hold on, Lan.
Are you serious?
You gave me your word.
But we will be married
for only a year.
After that, I'll choose my own path.
You won't get to have a say
in anything I do with my life.
If you're okay with that,
you can set the wedding date.
Okay.
You must stay married
to her for a year.
After that, I don't care
what you do with your life.
However, if you don't
stay married for a year,
I will disinherit you.
Everything
will become your sister's.
And part of the inheritance
will go to Mook
as compensation.
Dad, you can't hand
your legacy to a stranger.
I agree.
Why can't I?
They are my possessions.
I can do anything with them.
One more thing,
if you stay married for a year,
I'm going to give you
everything you want.
If you want your sister
to run the company,
if you want to hire someone
to work for you, you can do it.
Go ahead. I won't get in your way.
What about me? Why do I get nothing?
No, Lak. You can have mine.
I will give you all my possessions.
It's still unfair.
Why does something that's
rightfully mine
have to be used
as a bargaining tool?
Lak, don't be hostile toward
your parents.
Shut up, Danai.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
Alright. Let's settle this first.
Lan, what do you say?
Alright.
I will marry this woman for a year.
You have my word.
Congratulations. You've successfully
convinced me to marry you.
- Lak, no.
- Let go.
Let go. I'll delete everything.
I don't care anymore.
- Let go.
- Lak.
Calm down.
I can't stay calm anymore.
Look at what he did to me.
It's like I'm not his kid.
Everything is about Lan.
What do I have to keep
working so hard for?
What for?
Dad just said it
to convince Lan to get married.
Mom said she will give you
all of her possessions.
I want the company shares
and she can't give me that.
I've sacrificed so much for this.
I have to have them.
Dad can't give them to
his unappreciative son.
Will I ever be worthy in his eyes?
You still have me.
You're always worthy to me.
You told me you were going to
investigate the shooter.
Instead, you gave your word
that would marry Mook.
Do you even think about me?
Rut, you...
This is frustrating.
I pretended to be your lover
in front of people.
I ruined my playboy reputation
to stop your wedding.
How could you abandon me like this?
I didn't abandon you.
I agreed because of the conditions.
I will be married to her for a year.
After that, it's over.
I get my freedom.
The duckling will be out of my life.
Everything is over.
Anything can happen in a year.
That's right. It's why you have to
pretend to be my boyfriend.
See? I didn't abandon you.
We're still lovers.
Lan, you!
Rut, that really hurt.
If I were the attacker,
you would be dead.
You're the worst.
Let's hear it for the bride.
What are you doing?
Let me hear you scream.
Aren't you happy
that he agreed to marry you?
Why would I be happy?
This isn't a marriage based on love.
Why? Do you want to marry for love?
It's not like that.
Forget about the reasons,
let's celebrate.
You're about to have a husband.
What's good about marrying
someone else's man?
Lan and Rut aren't lovers.
Everyone can tell they're lying.
I have proof.
Proof that they're lovers.
Woah.
Maybe they really are lovers.
No, I guess.
This is obvious.
Do you still want to marry him?
I will marry him no matter what.
Mook.
Wait. Let's calm down.
Petch, where did you
get this picture?
Right. Where did you get it?
Someone sent it to me.
- Really?
Anyway, I don't agree with
this marriage.
That's all I have to say.
Mook, maybe they really are lovers.
I'm not so sure anymore.
I have to prove it.
Lan, it's me.
Danai, you scared me.
It's me. Who did you think I was?
It's nothing.
Why are you still awake?
I was waiting for you.
Is there something urgent?
It's not urgent. But it's important.
I want to know about the ambush.
How did you find out about it?
I overheard
your conversation with Mook.
This is serious.
Why didn't you tell me?
Why did you say it was an accident?
The person who saw
the attacker was Mook.
When we were in the hospital,
I thought she was lying.
After I got the video from traffic
camera, I realized it was true.
Can you see the attacker's face
in those images?
Do you have any leads?
His face is covered.
The license plate number is blurry.
Are you saying you've got no leads?
Yes.
Lan, you have to go to the police.
I'll do that later.
I want to find out who is behind it
before I go to the police.
I want irrefutable evidence
to settle it once and for all.
What will you do
if he attacks you again?
It's good if he does,
I'll get my chance to catch him.
Don't worry. I won't die easily.
Alright then.
If you find out who he is
and want to go to the police,
you have to tell me.
I will.
Don't worry.
I can look after myself.
How can I not worry?
You're my brother.
Be careful.
I should clean myself up.
Congratulations. You successfully
convinced me to marry you.
Why are you calling me?
I miss you.
I want to hear your voice.
We'll be together in a few days.
In your dreams.
I will dream about you tonight.
Should I dream about
being in your arms
or having you in my arms?
Or
something else entirely?
Never touch me in your dreams.
You're modest.
You can do anything to me
in your dreams.
You can touch my hand,
caress my arm,
my shoulder,
from my shoulder to my neck,
and slide your hand down to...
Stop.
Why? I haven't finished.
Stop trying to seduce me.
I don't feel anything.
That's too bad.
I'm going to bed. Bye.
Good night, love.
I'm going to get you.
Lan, don't think.
Don't think about the duckling.
No.
Don't think.
If you stay married for a year,
I'm going to give you
everything you want.
Alright.
You have my word.
Darn it.
Lan, you must be dreaming.
Are you really going to get married?
This is ridiculous.
Darn it.
Why are you here?
Your parents asked me
to pick you up.
Where are we going?
We're going to try on
wedding dresses.
- I'm not going.
- You have to.
If you don't go, I will tell your
parents that you're not complying.
And I will tell them that you want
a big wedding with 500 guests.
I have another condition.
What is it?
I want a private wedding, just us
since we'll divorce
after a year anyway.
I agree with him.
I thought you wanted a big wedding
so you can announce to everyone
that you've finally caught me.
Or are you scared that
other men will find out?
That's right.
Alright.
But we're going to
do it according to customs.
More importantly,
you will have to
register the marriage.
Alright.
After a year, I'll get a divorce.
I'll give you one hour.
Pick your dress
and get it over with.
Do you see that?
I knew she could make him go.
Although this is a small wedding
based on superstition,
I want her to wear a beautiful gown.
He thinks it's just a marriage
based on superstition,
to me, this is the real thing.
I told him
it will be over after a year
just to make him agree with me.
- You're amazing.
- Oh.
- That's what I have in mind too.
- Right?
I think Mook is a lovely girl.
She can make him fall for her
so that he doesn't want a divorce.
She is perfect for him.
I won't let her slip through
my fingers.
You read my mind.
Give me a hug.
Come this way please.
You can try on any of the gowns
that you want to.
As for the groom...
I'll handle it.
- Of course. Please take your time.
- Okay.
Lan, what do you think
about this one?
It's average.
Well, looks like my groom
doesn't like this gown.
Where is my suit?
I'd like to try it on.
Your suit is over there.
Lan, you must not feel anything.
Control yourself.
Excuse me.
Could you attach the bow tie for me?
Let me help you.
No. I can do it myself.
If you could, it would've been done
a long time ago.
Why can't you attach
a simple bow tie? Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I can hear your heartbeat.
Or maybe it's my imagination.
Nonsense. My heart is fine.
You're right. You like men.
You wouldn't feel anything
when you're around me, right?
And if I get closer to you,
you wouldn't feel anything.
When we get married
and get closer,
will you stop loving Rut
and love me instead?
No.
Sorry. I can't let him fall for you.
(Lan: Rut, help me!)
Lan.
You have to help me right now.
If you don't,
your DJ Prao is going to get me.
Although I'm allowing you
to marry him,
it doesn't mean you can have him.
Did you hear that?
I won't stop loving him.
Even if you give yourself to me,
I won't have you.
When did I give myself to you?
I see. Was it earlier?
I just helped you get dressed
and asked some questions.
Your mind is probably
full of dirty thoughts.
I hope you don't misunderstand me.
I'm a calm, reasonable man.
I know that the purpose of
this marriage is to save his life.
It doesn't come from love.
However, you should
also remind yourself
not to fall for him.
Because if you do,
I won't be able to keep my cool.
Rut, I just realized
how much you love me.
If you want me,
you have to kill him first.
I'm not dying for you.
Don't be mad. I'm just joking.
Remember this, duckling.
Although we're getting married,
you will never get my heart.
Disgusting.
I know you spent
your childhood together.
But that is the past.
I'm the present.
I won't let him fall for you.
If you don't want to get hurt,
during your year together,
don't develop feelings for him,
don't fall for him,
because he will never love you.
I will keep that in mind.
But please tell your man
not to develop feelings for me
or fall for me either.
He might be the one who regrets it.
That day won't come.
That brat was clearly seducing me.
If you had been a second late,
I'd have tied her wrists and ankles.
What kind of woman is she?
That's duckling abuse.
I'm the victim here.
This is just the beginning.
I can't imagine what she will do
after the wedding.
Why are you complaining?
You agreed to marry her.
If I didn't, my parents would've
found another way to convince me.
Besides, I have my reasons.
Firstly, to stop my parents
from pestering me.
Secondly, I have to get close to her
to find out if the attacker
and Praomook are connected.
Thirdly, I will get my freedom
if I can fulfill the agreement.
Wouldn't you agree to that
if you were me?
I'd agree to the marriage the second
I found out she was my bride.
You're lost.
Giving up your freedom
for a worthless woman.
Lan, you shouldn't
judge her unfairly.
She is helping you
because you are childhood friends.
Or maybe she still loves you.
She loves my parents' money.
It's why she's sold herself to them.
- Lan.
- Enough. Stop trying to defend her.
To you, she is a pretty,
harmless woman.
To me,
Praomook is a sly, scheming woman.
Once I have proof that
she is behind the attacks on me,
I will throw it in your face
so you can finally wake up.
I'll wait and see
if you're right or wrong.
Alright.
Hello.
I'm free all day.
Alright. I'll see you soon.
I have a date.
Call me if there is
an update about work.
Alright.
Rut.
I want to talk to you
about something.
I want to talk to you about
something. Can we meet?
Don't be quiet. Reply to me.
We used to be friends.
I'll wait for you.
Why did you hit me?
You embarrassed me
in front of other people.
Look at me. I look awful.
No one has ever done
this to me before.
But your girl attacked me.
Mook isn't my girl.
I love only you.
I don't believe you.
You must have given her hope.
That's why she dared to do it.
My friends warned me to stay away
from you because you're taken.
But I didn't listen,
because you've always
treated me so well.
In the end, you showed me
that we aren't supposed
to be together.
Nuch, please give me another chance.
No.
Lan,
let's break up.
Nuch.
From now on,
we're strangers.
Nuch, wait.
You said you want to talk to me.
I'm listening.
I want to be your friend. Can I?
You want to be my friend.
Yes.
You seem like a good person.
I don't want to be your enemy.
But I don't want to be
friends with you.
I understand that you don't like me.
Anybody would be angry
to find out that another woman
is marrying their lover.
That's one reason why
I'm upset with you.
I don't see what good it will do
if we become friends.
It will only benefit you.
Am I right?
You're right. It will benefit me.
But you'll get something
out of this too.
If during this one year,
we don't fight with each other
and live in peace,
we won't have any
extramarital issues.
I don't think that will be an issue.
That's true.
You came first,
so I will let you be number one.
Let's live in peace.
When I fight with him,
I'll have you as my adviser.
You should know him best.
Interesting.
It's a deal.
We're friends now.
You can talk to me about anything.
You can ask my advice
about anything.
Really?
Really.
We're friends now.
You can always talk to me.
And I will listen.
Lan.
I'm glad you agreed to meet me.
- You should try this.
- Get to the point.
I don't have much time for you.
When we broke up,
I was young and passionate.
I didn't trust you.
I was angry at Praomook,
but I took it out on you.
I was wrong.
It's behind us now.
I don't even remember what happened.
I remember everything between us.
I searched for you
until I found you.
Please, Lan. Can we start over?
Alright. We'll start over
as friends.
We can't be more than that
because I have Rut.
Are you two really lovers?
I thought you lied about it
to avoid marrying her.
It's the truth. I'm dating him.
About the marriage,
I can't avoid it anyway.
Did you turn gay
because of me?
If that is the case,
I'd feel bad about it.
You don't have to feel anything.
My preference
has nothing to do with you.
It's unfortunate.
Had I put up with Praomook more,
we wouldn't have become strangers.
Lan,
if you don't want to marry her,
you can ask for my help.
I can deal with it on my own.
Alright.
Tell me if you need my help.
Here.
The brand owner wired us money.
They will send us a new collection.
Okay. Thank you.
Tell me what happened.
Can dress fitting dehydrate you?
Has a woman ever turned you on?
Why are you asking me that?
I tried to seduce Lan
to drive him crazy.
And he was clearly into it.
Lan and I are different.
I used my gaydar on Lan and Rut.
It didn't ping.
Right. That's why I was
trying to prove
if he was gay or not.
Answer the question first.
This is up to
each person's preference.
I like men,
only men can make me feel things.
With you, I don't feel anything.
Even if you tried to seduce me,
I wouldn't feel a thing.
Is it possible that Lan is bisexual?
It's possible.
But the way he came on to you in
Korea showed his sexual preference.
I think he is straight and created
the story to fool everyone.
However, just to be sure,
I can prove it for you.
They are both delightful.
Try it if you get a chance.
I'm curious about it too.
You've got it.
Be sure not to test him on a whim.
Or you might start feeling things.
And when you start feeling things,
you might get hooked.
Then it will be too late
to back out.
Silly. I won't feel anything.
I won't get ahead of myself.
Saying it is one thing,
doing it is a different story.
Lan is your first and only love.
He is the reason why
you've been single all this time.
Who said that?
I just haven't found the right man.
You haven't found the right man?
Or you haven't forgotten
the first man you ever loved?
I told you. I don't love him.
You keep saying that,
but does your heart really think so?
Remember, Mook.
Don't use your heart to play.
Because eventually, you will be
the one who gets hurt.
In this game, the first one
who falls in love loses.
He will be the loser, not me.
Duckling.
I will never love you.
I hate you.
Even if you were the only person
left in the world,
I'd rather be single
for the rest of my life.
You love me.
Admit that you love me.
I don't love you.
Mook.
You're strong.
Guys, if you need my help,
let me know.
I'll do my best.
Could you proofread this
and summarize what happened at
the meeting by noon?
- Sure thing.
- Thank you.
Review this game and note
its strengths and weaknesses.
- Get it done by today.
- Okay.
Summarize user comments
and make a presentation.
Can you handle it?
If you can't,
you don't have to do all the work.
I'll ask someone to help you.
This is nothing. I can handle it.
Aek, it's done.
Okay. Give this to Boss' assistant
so that Boss can approve it.
Make sure to get it back
in the evening.
Got it.
Hey, Poom.
If you're asking about Boss,
I'm afraid that he is away.
I'm not asking about him.
I'm delivering this to you.
When will Boss come to the office?
- I won't tell you.
- Come on, Poom
I'm warning you.
He gave you a chance,
so try not to ruin it.
If you want to fangirl over him,
do it outside of work hours.
When he is working, Boss is
a mean, serious, and headstrong man.
If somebody displeases him,
he cuts their pay.
he threatens to fire them.
Sometimes he gets on my nerves
and I want to quit.
Why don't you write your
resignation letter? I'll sign it.
Here are the documents
requiring your signature.
Is this your first day here?
Yes.
Why are you standing here
and not working?
Do you want to quit too?
No, I don't.
I'll get back to work.
Why does he always
have a mean look on his face?
He is so cool.
What?
Your resignation letter.
Give it to me so I can sign it.
Here are the reports on the new
part-time and full-time employees
that you asked each department head
to make. They're all here.
About the video from
the rescue vehicle's camera,
did you find anything?
I found nothing.
It's fine. Get back to work.
Okay.
You look like a good man.
I don't want to be your enemy.
Let's live in peace.
When I have a fight with him,
I'll have you as my adviser.
It's a deal.
We're friends now.
Fine. If I want to be more, I have
to start with being her friend.
Hello.
It's me, Laknara.
Lak.
What can I do for you?
I want to talk to you.
Alright.
Take it.
(Check)
Why are you giving this to me?
You can have that money
in exchange for Lan's freedom.
Cancel the wedding.
I have to decline your offer.
I will triple the offer.
In return,
you get out of Lan's life.
I acknowledge what you are saying.
But I won't cancel the wedding.
I guess you think that
you'll make more from my father.
Make your choice.
Get it now or get nothing at all.
It's not like that.
I'm marrying your brother
for your parents' sake.
I don't want your money.
Are you
hoping that he will fall for you?
This is based on superstition.
Stop clinging to hope.
If he liked you, he wouldn't try
so hard to get you out of his life.
Thanks for telling me.
Whatever reasons you have for
this marriage, remember my words.
Don't take anything
that doesn't belong to you,
be it fame, wealth, or love.
Otherwise, you will be unhappy
for the rest of your life.
If you change your mind,
cash that check.
Or just let me know
if you want more.
The offer is still on the table.
(One hundred million baht)
I may need money,
but I'm not a greedy person.
Don't use me and Mom as excuses.
You're doing this for yourself.
You're selfish.
Alright. I'm selfish.
I don't care how he feels
or if he has a lover.
I only care about my own interests.
I'm a bad person. Are you happy?
I will be happy
only if you cancel the wedding.
Praomook, you have a beautiful name,
but you're behaving like
a worthless, despicable person.
It's almost 09:09 a.m.
and Lan hasn't shown up.
If he doesn't show up,
you won't get the house back, right?
- Hello.
- Lan, help me.
What's wrong?