''Mortal World Diary'' - Zhang Jie
♫  Loneliness on the Immortal Island of Penglai is advising people from the mortal world  ♫
♫  That true love is hard to find  ♫
♫  What will happen if you give up on love?  ♫
♫  True love can only be enlightened by chance  ♫
♫  Fate played tricks on me, causing my tears to fall  ♫
♫  The sorrow of separation, and the butterflies in my dreams  ♫
♫  I'll never regret my decision, even if I have to suffer in the Six Paths  ♫
♫  I'm helpless against earthly rules and divine laws  ♫
♫  I made countless attempts to create my own fate  ♫
♫  Like the tree's burden of making flowers bloom, I've wasted years of my life  ♫
♫  An air of melancholy surrounds me as the Bodhi leaves fall  ♫
[Immortal Samsara Part 1]
[Episode 37]
It's you?
You already gave it to me.
Why are you taking it back?
What about you then?
Will you one day... also leave me?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Could it be...
Could it be that I'm in another dream?
That's good too.
So this is what it feels like when the characters in plays don't know what to do with love.
Yan Dan, calm down.
What on earth are you thinking about?
You're a demon. He's a demon catcher.
It's impossible between you two.
Moreover, that person already has someone in his heart.
In terms of how unforgettable his love is, you can't even compare.
No matter if it's the past, present, or when he returns to the Heaven Realm, you two will be separated eventually.
Calm down. Return to your right mind, okay?
This might be what Jiang Chen meant by a personal experience.
Anyway, you cannot behave like those silly girls who sacrifice everything for love.
Remember what you're feeling right now.
With this experience, I'm sure you can write a better and more touching story.
Ying Yuan...
In the past...
my happiest moment...
was when I became your attendant.
Even when I was a lowly attendant...
have you ever... even glanced at me?
From now on...
I will never bow down to you again.
Where is he?
He didn't drink the As Desired Wine.
He transformed into the person I saw in my dream.
Liu Weiyang is so strange.
Since he was suffering because of an unfulfilled dream, why didn't he drink any As Desired Wine, if he had it?
We shouldn't trust him.
I'm sure he's hidden parts of the truth.
Also, he only wanted to use us to obtain Paper and Ink.
He said all those words on purpose.
I'm afraid he's related to the Devil Clan, he's definitely a part of this.
I didn't expect to be able to see Heavenly Lord Zhao Sheng's divine tool in my lifetime.
The three of us are superior deities of the Heaven Realm.
We're making a private visit this time.
Hurry and show us the chronicle. Don't waste our time anymore.
But... Everyone said that the Four Divine Tools were lost in the Divine-Devil War.
How did the three of you get your hands on them?
How could His Supreme Majesty allow the emperors' divine tools stay in the Mortal Realm?
We've already found them. It's just that we haven't told anyone.
It's normal for you not to know.
I was ignorant before this.
The chronicle is right here. Please read it as you like.
We superior deities will hold a discussion. You should leave.
Oh right, get us a pot of excellent tea.
Go on.
I'll go right now.
What do you think?
Wasn't my acting great?
Let's take a look.
[Zhucui County Annals]
"In order to kill Devil King, Emperor Chang Sheng sealed away the Illusion of Devils with Paper and Ink"
"and cut off his power source."
Since this Liu Weiyang could draw the Power of Devils from the Illusion of Devils,
why did he steal Paper and Ink in the first place?
The divine official who saved me said that Paper and Ink could provide life to all things.
When we were in the Devil King Hall, we watched it restore withered plants to life.
I'm sure Liu Weiyang intends to use Paper and Ink to revive the Devil King.
He might also try to revive all of the devils that perished in the Divine-Devil War.
Look at this.
Do you see that?
The Eye of Infinite Devils is passed down from generation to generation.
It complements the Illusion of Devils.
It can absorb the Power of Devils and embed itself in the Devil King's body.
It is only removable after death. Only the blood of Devil King can dispel its power.
[Seal away the Illusion of Devils, the Devil King's power source, with Paper and Ink.]
[The revival of Devil King, Xuan Xiang, will create a new turning point.]
This is definitely the same the mark on Liu Weiyang's chest.
Look.
You're right. He's definitely the Devil King.
Superior deities, please have some tea.
Soil Guardian, I have a question for you.
Why does it only show half of the Devil King's face?
Do you have his complete portrait?
I don't. Before he was defeated in the war, he pretended to be a recluse. His disguise was perfect.
Only a few people have seen his face.
That's why we only have this incomplete portrait of him.
There's no need to ask any further.
I'm sure he doesn't want to be concerned with the past anymore.
Soil Guardian, could you please tell us everything you know about the Divine-Devil War?
All right.
The Divine-Devil War started because of the death of a fairy.
Her name was...
Her name was... Tao Ziqi!
She was a superior deity.
She was the envoy of the Heaven Realm.
She traversed regularly between the Divine and Devil Realms.
Therefore she got to know the Devil King.
The Devil Clan was always a cunning clan.
The Devil King made Tao Ziqi fall in love him.
He kept lying to her that the Devil Clan had no intention of staging a rebellion.
Love between a deity and a devil?
This is such an interesting story!
Continue. What happened after that?
How is that love?
It was obviously a plot.
When the time was right, the Devil King
announced to the world that Tao Ziqi was trying to assassinate him.
He said that the Divine Realm took the lead in braking the promise to maintain peace in the Six Realms.
That's why they retaliated.
That was the beginning of the Divine-Devil War.
Then did Tao Ziqi attempt to assassinate him or not?
That was what Devil King said.
Just an excuse to turn on the Divine Realm.
However, the entire Devil Clan watched him slay Tao Ziqi personally.
The Immortal Clan is fatuous and incompetent.
They have always feared our power.
For the sake of our clan, I've always endured and avoided them.
Even so, the Heavenly Emperor still wishes to eliminate our clan.
Using a peace negotiation as an excuse, he sent Tao Ziqi as a divine envoy to assassinate me.
In order to save me, Elder Shuo Hua was seriously wounded.
Backing off won't give us peace!
It'll only make the Deity Clan push their luck even further.
My generals, as all of you will see,
Today I'll slay the divine envoy and bid farewell to our past humiliations.
For the sake of our peace and glory, we'll eradicate the Deity Clan and rule over the Six Realms!
We won't cease until the Divine Realm is destroyed!
"We won't cease until the Divine Realm is destroyed!"
Tao Ziqi, what else do you have to say for yourself?
There's nothing...
left to say between us.
I heard that all devils that were involved in the war were banished into the Life and Death Arena after the war.
And they can't leave the Night Forgetting River. Is that true?
So many years have passed already.
All of their skeletons have formed Bone Mountain, whose peak can never be seen.
After the Devil Clan was defeated, they suffered a huge blow.
Although they have some territories left, they no longer pose a threat.
Who seeks the power of the dark forces?
The ex-curator of the Magical Pavilion of Heaven Realm.
I seek the Fire of the Flaming Heart and the power of the dark forces
to restore my divine object spirit.
You're half human and half spirit.
If you receive this power, will you be able to withstand the devouring of the dark forces?
I need to seek revenge.
I won't regret it even if I die.
I have no fear of being devoured.
You have a sincere heart.
However, you only have ordinary powers!
Do you have any worthy tools that you can use as your offering?
I'm here for His Majesty's immortal spirit.
If I succeed, I'm willing to offer half of my immortal power.
If I fail, you can devour my entire being.
I shall die with no regret.
Excellent!
Yan Dan, Ying Yuan,
I will make both of you suffer 100 times more than what I've suffered.
Eat up.
Such scrumptious dishes. What's the matter?
Are you worried that we might die when we face off against Liu Weiyang tomorrow?
Yan Dan, if Liu Weiyang is truly the Devil King, I'm sure he stole Paper and Ink in order
to gather the souls of the dead devils and attack the Heaven Realm once again.
Tang Zhou and I already discussed it.
This trip is perilous.
So you should stay here and wait for our news.
I was wondering what you two were up to this afternoon.
So, you two want to ditch me?
Listen up, that's not happening!
If we go, we go together. If we die, we die together.
Among the three of us, you have the weakest power.
If we get into a fight, you'll be the one to drag us down.
Hey, what are you saying!
I'm no longer the lowly follower that I used to be.
I'm training every day right now. I can already cast fire spells.
I'm much more powerful than before. Really!
Fine. You're the strongest, okay?
But of course.
Yan Dan, the Devil King is as powerful as a superior deity.
Yu Mo and I might not be able to defeat him even if we work together.
Since we're trying to stop him, it's highly likely that we won't return alive.
That's why we need your help to report this to the Heaven Realm.
If he starts another war... the Three Realms might be in great peril again.
I knew this was a farewell banquet.
But I'm just a mere lotus demon.
How can I ascend to the heavens?
What about the Soil Guardian? He's a deity.
You both should entrust the task to him. He can report it to them.
- Yan Dan.
- At least all the parts of my body are precious.
I can heal you two if you get injured.
Aren't we friends?
If we're friends, we go through thick and thin together.
If you don't want to bring me along, that's fine.
Just tell me that you don't think of me as your friend.
Yan Dan, we'll follow your will.
That's more like it. Let's eat until our heart's content today.
We can depart early tomorrow morning.
Here.
I gave you my flower friends already.
Here's some for you, too.
When she wakes up and finds out that we've gone, she's going to yell at people again.
As long as she's safe, she can do what she wants.
You suffered in the Night Forgetting River for eight centuries.
I won't let you return to that decrepit place again.
Yan Dan? Stop causing trouble.
I just knew you two scoundrels would team up and ditch me.
But I'm smart. If you want to ditch me, it won't be that easy.
How could you leave me out when you two are going to go save the world?
Buddies, let's go!
You actually used my magic against me?
Too cunning.
I'm only cunning towards despicable people like you two.
Once the evil spirits outside Yinyang Pass detect the living, they'll attack those who try to go through.
At this time, you must remember to hold your breath.
If not, they'll discover you.
Yu Mo, don't worry. You and I aren't human.
Those evil spirits won't attack us.
But you? Tang Zhou, you're a sitting duck. You better watch out.
- Who are you calling a sitting duck?
- You.
I...
- Yu Mo, I can subdue those evil spirits when we enter the pass.
- You mustn't.
Although these evil spirits are obstructing us, they're also obstructing
the evil forces that are trying to escape from the Night Forgetting River.
Therefore, we cannot subdue them.
Did you all hear me?
We heard.
Watch out!
Don't breathe! Hold it in!
Don't move!
Are you holding your breath?
Are you looking to die?
I told you not to breathe! Hold it in!
Don't move!
Wearing the magical bracelet will put a restriction on your heart.
From now on, you'll experience no love in life and practice celibacy.
Tang Zhou's magical bracelet is reacting to me?
Yu Mo, hurry, come and help us!
Bone Mountain should be up ahead.
The Soil Guardian once said that an emperor once split the mountain to save a fairy.
After the mountain was reattached, it left behind a faint scar.
I would guess that this is it.
They say deities aren't supposed to be in love.
I didn't expect this emperor to be that romantic.
I wonder what kind of soul-stirring love story they have?
The Heavenly Rules are strict. It was nothing more than a tragedy.
It's fine even if it remains unknown.
Our current priority is to save the world. Let's hurry and ascend the mountain.
Let's go.
I've been waiting here for a long time.
You all really didn't disappoint me. You came so quickly.
Since you all are here, I assume you know who I am.
Are you truly Devil King Xuan Xiang?
How I wish I wasn't.
After I left the Illusion of Devils, my powers as Devil King have completely awakened.
However, I don't want to be shackled by the past again.
Some people are born as deities.
However, some are born as devils.
My people revered me as the leader of my clan.
However, no one ever asked me if I was willing to be their leader.
Then why did you steal Paper and Ink?
I didn't steal it to revive my dead soldiers and restore my clan.
I'm just here to summon a certain girl's soul.
Is it Tao Ziqi?
You killed her and now, you're trying to revive her.
Do you want to threaten the Heaven Realm by using her as your hostage?
How could I possibly kill her?
She was the only person who didn't see me as the Devil King and only treated me as Xuan Xiang.
Your clan saw you slay her yourself.
Stop lying.
That's because Shuo Hua impersonated me using the puppet spell.
Puppet spell?
We might be able to lie with our words, but our memories cannot lie.
I inherited the throne due to my family's legacy.
However, I had no intention of declaring war against the other clans.
Eventually, the elders of the clan turned me into a figurehead.
I thought my own inaction could bring peace to my people.
In the end, it emboldened the elders and their ambitions instead.
There was internal strife in the Devil Clan.
- All the elders establish their own rules.
- What are you doing?
To build up their power to engage in war.
Let's go!
Why are you disfiguring the statue of your leader?
The Devil King is the leader of your clan. You must never destroy his statue.
I hate him!
My father was taken away to fight in a war! He never returned home!
Yesterday, my brother was also taken away!
My mother is terminally ill and my brother was worried about her.
That's why he came back to visit her in secret. However, they arrested him as a deserter.
Deserters are executed. I don't want my brother to die.
Disfiguring the Devil King's statue is a serious crime.
Wouldn't your mother be even more heartbroken if you were arrested because of this?
Miss, you're pretty bold, aren't you?
Who are you? How did you recognize me?
You come from the Divine Realm.
Why did you protect the statue of the Devil King?
I wasn't trying to protect the Devil King. I was taking pity on the children.
It's a serious crime to disfigure the statue of their leader.
I don't want him to be punished because of his recklessness.
He's a devil child. You're a divine deity.
Evil and good do not belong together, but you're here to save his brother.
All living beings in the Six Realms are equal. There were never any differences between us.
Good and evil were formed due to teachings.
The children are innocent.
In troubled times, all people suffer.
I will try to help every single person I can.
With that said, you're putting a devil like me to shame indeed.
You must be a virtuous man yourself if you're here to save him too.
You mustn't belittle yourself.
Saving him is our priority.
So, the envoy of the Divine Realm is here.
Why did you come here in secret to save people?
Could it be that the Divine Realm is itching to wage war against our clan?
Elder Shuo Hua, this is my private affair.
It has nothing to do with the Divine Realm.
For karma's sake, when it comes to this soldier who made a mistake,
I wonder if Elder Shuo Hua could do me a favor and let me take him away?
You don't have any evidence.
All these soldiers of mine have witnessed
that you were provoking the Devil Clan.
If that's the case, it seems like we cannot end this peacefully.
You all should leave quickly.
I've been the Devil King for 10,000 years.
I've never been protected by a girl before.
She wanted to save all the beings of the world.
I wanted to fulfill her wish for her.
No matter how much I plead for leniency for you,
His Supreme Majesty isn't willing to believe that the Devil Clan doesn't intend to rebel.
The Divine Realm is already preparing for war.
I'm caught in the middle.
Every day it feels like I'm walking on fire.
Xuan Xiang, if you aren't lying to me, you should prove your loyalty to the Divine Realm.
Even if you are just using me to deceive the Divine Realm,
I won't blame you.
Having been able to get to know you in this lifetime, I can die without any regrets.
Ziqi, I've never deceived you.
As long as I'm the Devil King, I won't let the two realms go to war or let you be caught in the middle.
If only you weren't the Devil King and I wasn't a superior deity,
we could've found a quiet spot in the Six Realms.
Never letting any trouble come into our home.
How nice would that be?
If the Devil King vanishes, if the Illusion of Devils loses its power,
Shuo Hua cannot wage war against them no matter what he does.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?!
The Eye of Infinite Devils is the source of the Devil Clan.
It can never be removed from the devil king.
If you remove it by force, not only will you lose most of your devil power,
you'll become like a mortal and only be able to use basic spells because of the backlash.
No one can use the Illusion of Devils without the complete Eye of Infinite Devils.
Ziqi, tomorrow, I will bring this necklace to the Nine Heavens and propose to you.
Divine envoy Tao Ziqi, are you willing to marry the devil Xuan Xiang
and establish a marriage alliance between the two clans?
We ming geese are the most loyal immortal beings.
We only love one person in our lifetime.
If we cannot be born together, we shall die together.
Our love shall last for an eternity.
Ziqi,
I will definitely protect you.
Ziqi?
I really have to thank that seductive Tao Ziqi.
Without her, I wouldn't have been able to get my hands on the Eye of Infinite Devils this easily.
What have you done to her?
You were the chosen Devil King.
However, you only have eyes for your petty relationship!
What a joke.
The Devil Clan will be destroyed if you continue to be our ruler!
Now, I have the Power of the Devils!
I shall be the next Devil King!
There's no need to fear the Divine Clan!
Since you like the position that much, you can take it if you like.
However, if you dare hurt Tao Ziqi,
I will never let you off.
Your Highness, you just need to be a good boy and stay here.
After I massacre the Deity Clan and unite the Six Realms,
I'll naturally let Your Highness and that divine deity
go as far away as you want.
After that, I was locked up in the Devil King Hall by Shuo Hua.
He impersonated me using the puppet spell and initiated the Divine-Devil War.
After a few months, I received news of the Devil Clan's defeat.
Emperor Chang Sheng used Paper and Ink to suppress the Illusion of Devils.
Most of the Devil Clan's territories became wastelands.
I looked with all my heart for Ziqi.
I was rescued by my clan members after nine deaths.
(T/N: nine deaths and still alive is an idiom for a narrow escape)
Right before I lost my memory,
I found out that Ziqi
was sacrificed as a tribute to our war flag.
Even until death, she didn't know that I wasn't the one who killed her.
I'm sure she was heartbroken before she died.
I must tell her personally that although I'd let down the Devil Clan,
I never let her down.
So, this was the truth behind the story of the heartless man.
What a touching and tragic story.
Although your story sounds logical, you deceived us many times before.
We can't determine if your memory is true or not.
I expected this to happen a long time ago.
What are you doing?
With my powers alone, I can't revive her by using Paper and Ink.
That's why I set up a sacrificial array awhile ago.
The array was already activated when all of you were watching my memories.
If you assist me, we can leave the array together.
If you stop me, we shall die together.
You must be out of your mind!
I even chose to believe your crazy story!
I truly only want to save my beloved.
I had no choice but to resort to such underhanded methods.
I think that we can trust him one last time.
Even if he was lying to us, if we stop assisting him, he won't be able to get what he wants.
If he was speaking the truth, we can fulfill his wish for him.
By then, the Devil Clan will fall into ruins as they lose their leader forever.
Fine then. I'll agree to it then.
When a deity perishes, if his or her immortal spirit doesn't perish completely,
Paper and Ink can be used to summon the soul and reconstruct the flesh.
To activate the revival array, the activator needs to offer their soul and spirit as tributes for Paper and Ink.
Besides that, it requires two highly-skilled individuals to use their immortal powers
to prevent the activator from losing himself completely.
This won't do.
I once read this in a book. The Three Souls and Seven Spirits form one's source.
If you remove them by force, you'll experience excruciating pain.
If your immortal power goes berserk, you will die from it.
If the person I'm trying to revive isn't Tao Ziqi, you may interrupt me at any time.
At that time I'll lose my soul and spirit.
You can do whatever you want to me.
Fine. We'll give it a try.
But if you deceive us, I'll immediately destroy Bone Mountain.
So, it's best if you don't deceive us. Otherwise, I'll do what I say.
However, Bone Mountain doesn't have a peak we can see.
There are countless bones here.
How are you going to locate her soul?
Ziqi always wore her Ziyan Hairpin.
It was a reward from the Heavenly Court.
The Ziyan Hairpin is made from the strongest and most beautiful materials.
It will never disappear.
The Ziyan Hairpin meant a lot to her.
She was always playing with it.
As long as we can find that hairpin, we can surely gather her soul and spirit.
Hurry, let go of me.
If not, your wound will worsen.
It doesn't matter.
Why would you risk your life for me time and time again if you don't have me in your heart?
''Agarwood'' - Zhang Jie | Jane Zhang
♫  My most bewildering memory is the moonlight falling like frost on the ground full of fallen leaves  ♫
♫  For a single teardrop, I'm drowning myself in sorrow, obsessing with forgetting you  ♫
♫  If we'd have to walk till we separate, to where would you want to go?  ♫
♫  Turn around and become the delusion of my life ♫
♫  The most beautiful destiny is hidden in the dark night, "love" is the word for everything  ♫
♫  My loneliness and longing for you leaves a mark like fragments of the moon  ♫
♫  I still have an image of you imprinted in my mind even after washing away the fine dust  ♫
♫  Life after life, this is the longing I missed the most ♫
♫  You are the breeze of a fallen flower in the world of flowers adding to the mound of fallen flowers  ♫
♫  Will you shed tears over the truth of the mortal world?  ♫
♫  You're like the unattainable Autumn Moon in the vast sky, don't dare to shine bright yet not hesitate to shine  ♫
♫  In my dream, the one I loved is with me  ♫
♫  After bidding farewell, when Spring becomes Autumn, where can I find my heart in this world?  ♫
♫  Several lifetimes will not be enough for our parting  ♫
♫ As I watch lovers enjoying fireworks on the riverbanks, my love and longing for you makes my pain unbearable ♫
♫  There will be a time when the world is beautiful  ♫
♫  When the lotus blossoms again, you and I will be together  ♫