''Mortal World Diary'' - Zhang Jie
♫  Loneliness on the Immortal Island of Penglai advises people from the mortal world  ♫
♫  That true love is hard to find  ♫
♫  What will happen if you give up on love?  ♫
♫  True love can only be enlightened by chance  ♫
♫  Fate played tricks on me, causing my tears to fall  ♫
♫  The sorrow of separation, and the butterflies in my dreams  ♫
♫  I'll never regret my decision, even if I have to suffer in the Six Paths  ♫
♫  I'm helpless against earthly rules and divine laws  ♫
♫  I made countless attempts to create my own fate  ♫
♫  Like the tree's burden of making flowers bloom, I've wasted years of my life  ♫
♫  An air of melancholy surrounds me as the Bodhi leaves fall  ♫
[Immortal Samsara Part 1]
[Episode 21]
Mountain Chief, what's wrong?
Let me take you back to the mountain.
I'm fine.
I'm guessing you were too busy and didn't look hard enough.
Promise me. Even if you have to turn the place upside down, you have to find her.
I beg you. Please.
Yes.
Yelan Mountain got a new chief, and Yu Mo found the love of his life.
This is one good thing after another!
For today's welcome dance, make sure you give it your all!
I am telling you,
that flower demon lady will be Mountain Chief's future wife.
Let her experience our hospitality!
- Do you hear me?
- Yes! We hear you!
The Mountain Chief is here!
Lovely flowers under a full moon, wishing you two happiness.
Two mandarin ducks playing in the water, hoping your love lasts forever.
We don't ask for money, because love is more solid than gold and the envy of the immortals!
What's wrong with Mountain Chief?
Did your bride run away?
Why do you look so weak?
Did you get ambushed?
No.
Your internal strength is weak. Your meridians are a mess.
Where's your Extraordinary Eye?
Quick! Use it to cure yourself.
I lost it.
When you were at the troupe, you took the Extraordinary Eye and gave it away as a dowry, didn't you?
How could you be so foolish?
Now you've lost two things at once!
I want to be alone for awhile.
What is the matter with Mountain Chief?
He's heartbroken.
He gave her the Extraordinary Eye and she still refused to come back with him.
Mountain Chief Zi Lin, Flower Spirit Clan is here to present a gift.
They are already at the foot of the mountain.
Other than elixirs and divine tools, they brought a lot of beautiful ladies too.
Mountain Chief Yu Mo is not looking well.
Do you think he wants to meet the beautiful ladies?
His former wife is from Flower Spirit Clan.
If we told him to pick another beauty right now, it'll only sadden him more.
I am afraid that it will make things worse.
But it is all right. We are good brothers.
When it comes to this, I can do it on his behalf!
Bai Piaoliang. How is it going?
Is Zi Teng done yet?
Leader, as the saying goes, people have three urgencies.
(T/N: to pee, poop, and fart)
Judging by how Miss Zi Teng is doing, I don't think she will be done soon.
We need to give her some time.
You...
If she doesn't come out soon, I'll hang myself on this crooked tree!
Please don't.
You'll be even more embarrassed if she came out now.
Don't you have seven other ladies from Flower Spirit Clan?
One less person won't affect anything.
There's still a glimmer of hope for Flower Spirit Clan!
How could we do that?
I submitted the gift list a long time ago!
Eight beauties. How am I supposed to explain this if there is one missing?
Leader, do not worry.
There's always a road in front of a mountain. Everything will be all right!
There is always a way out!
Mountain Chief Zi Lin has arrived!
Greetings, Mountain Chief.
I am sorry that you came at the wrong time today.
The other Mountain Chief is currently cultivating in seclusion.
I had no choice but to receive you on my own.
Enemies on a narrow road.
(T/N: encountering someone you don't want to see)
Isn't he the stupid tortoise who called me ugly?
Mountain Chief Zi Lin is too humble.
Prison Lizard harmed people inside and outside of the mountain.
We owe it to the two brave mountain chiefs, who brought peace to the Demon Clans.
It's for this reason that the entire Flower Spirit Clan is very grateful.
To celebrate the Mountain Chiefs' ascension to the throne, on behalf of Flower Spirit Clan,
I am here to present the treasure of our clan, the Yanbi Pill.
This pill has condensed demon power. It can eliminate the yin and enhance the qi.
It is the perfect pill for one who is cultivating.
Mountain Chief, these eight ladies are the most beautiful in Flower Spirit Clan.
If you like any of these ladies, you can keep them as your maid or servant.
It is their honor to be able to serve you.
This is Wan Yan, a chrysanthemum demon.
This is Zi'e, a plum demon.
The rose demon, Leng Xiang.
This is a lotus demon.
Bai Piaoliang, what are you doing?
I need to use the washroom. E-Excuse me.
The ugly woman who stole my horse! Stop!
How dare you steal my horse? Ugly woman!
Which part of her is ugly?
I think she's quite eye-catching.
Buddy, who are you?
The Water of Forgetfulness really did make you forget everything.
Yu Mo, are you blind?
Isn't this the young man who nearly knocked my carriage over?
You are being rude. He is the other mountain chief of Yelan Mountain.
Greetings, Mountain Chief.
Mountain Chief? He's the halfwit who stood in our way?
M-Mountain Chief?
I remember you. I was in the carriage that day.
You knocked our carriage over with your horse.
I almost returned to my real form because of you!
Really? What a coincidence. What should we do about it?
If that's true, I guess fate has brought us together. Why don't you let me stay here?
Then you can compensate me for the injury you caused. What do you think?
It would be my pleasure. Does that make you happy?
Then... do you want to stay in my arms for a little longer?
No need. No need.
Lotus Spirit Bai Piaoliang,
hurry and show your gratitude.
It's fine.
I do not like the name "Bai Piaoliang." It doesn't sound good.
Why don't we change it?
So close, yet so far... searching for my old love.
Only writing about my deep love.
"Yan Dan." What do you think?
"Yan Dan"?
"Yan," as in "cheeky". "Dan," as in "simple."
This name suits me pretty well!
I now understand why they say heartbroken people are desperate.
It feels nice having the right person to back you up.
What are you all doing? What are you doing?
Your skin is so thick and rough.
If we don't give you a proper scrub, how can you spend the first night with Mountain Chief?
No! No! No! Spend a night with him? What are you saying?
Your Mountain Chief said I am here to recuperate.
My body isn't for sale!
That's not up to you!
However, the Mountain Chief has been a little ill lately.
When you see him later, you have to remind him to take the Yanbi Pill the Flower Spirit Clan gave him.
Yanbi Pill?
We left it by his bed.
You mustn't forget!
Give Miss Yan Dan a good bath. Get to work!
No, no. Wait. Wait a minute.
Let's talk this out!
Keep scrubbing!
Stop pushing me. I can walk myself!
Mountain Chief？
He is just ill. He won't die from it, will he?
But ugliness will kill me.
However, I am just an attendant.
Is it too much for me to take my master's pill?
Mountain Chief.
Did you want to use this Yanbi Pill to cover the green spots on your face?
To be honest, you are pretty the way you are.
It is not that. Mountain Chief, this is a misunderstanding.
To me, being ugly isn't all that important.
I'm just afraid I might embarrass you when we go out together in the future.
I can tell that you are very weak right now, and you really need this pill.
I am not weak.
Of course, you are not. But I shouldn't just take advantage of you.
You are my concubine. Isn't it normal for me to give you a present?
About this concubine thing... You've misunderstood.
I was there to replace someone.
I am just a demon who recently arrived in Mortal Realm.
I know nothing about love.
In my current state, I can't marry anyone.
All right.
If you want to get out of this marriage arrangement, then the Yanbi Pill—
The Yanbi Pill... really is something I need.
Mountain Chief. Look.
You are a hero. You are always surrounded by beautiful women.
Instead of marrying an unwilling concubine like me, how about making me your loyal attendant? Does that sound good?
What?
I'm the Mountain Chief, and you are my attendant?
I can be a general, too!
Liu Bei was assisted by Zhu Geliang. You can have a sidekick too!
(T/N: Zhu Geliang was warlord Liu Bei’s war advisor and right hand man in the Three Kingdoms period)
But everyone on the mountain knows about our marriage.
How will we explain this to them?
That is easy to solve.
Only Heaven and Earth, and you and I will know.
If you still can't rest assured...
I can sign a contract with you.
Then how long will the contract last?
It'll make me look insincere if the time is too short, which would ruin the deal.
But if it's too high, I'll have promised too much of myself.
- What about a hundred years?
- It's a deal.
He agreed that quickly?
I must have made it too high!
[Contract]
You have signed the contract and left your fingerprint.
You have to listen to me from now on.
Otherwise, this Yanbi Pill—
Understood. Understood.
But I think you really do look kind of weak.
I'm not weak!
How strong?
I know of a way to recuperate. Are you interested?
What is it?
What are you doing?
All of Yelan Mountain belongs to me now. I am the Mountain Chief.
Do I really need to sneak around to eat some late-night snacks?
You don't understand. We are doing this for the excitement.
Let me, the attendant, teach you how to enjoy life.
Let's go!
Yan Dan, you had a tough time in Heavenly Realm. It isn't a bad thing to have forgotten all of it.
Now that you are in the Mortal Realm, whether you understand it or not, it's fine.
All I want is to protect you so that you can live a happy life.
Whatever happens, I will be there for you. You can always take shelter behind me.
No one will ever lay a finger on you.
All the eggs in the Nine Heavens are laid by divine chickens.
It's very good for your immortal spirit. Are you sure you don't want to eat it?
I still won't eat it. I said I won't eat—
Hesitating? Then we're doing it the hard way.
I told you...
This tastes great!
What's the matter? Don't you like it?
I like it.
The late night snacks you make are my favorite.
What is this? Is it a seal?
As long as I'm alive, it will glow.
I promise that I will always keep you safe, as long as I'm alive.
From now on, I will take care of you.
From now on, this mountain will be your home.
- All right?
- Of course!
It is a huge bargain for me!
From now on, you are my master.
And I am Lian, your dear attendant for 100 years.
(T/N "Lian" means "lotus")
All right.
During these 100 years, if there's anything you wish for, just tell me.
I can help you fulfill all of them.
I don't think you can fulfill my wishes.
My biggest dream is to be the best novelist in the world.
However, according to my friend, I haven't seen enough of the world.
I have to travel to all the corners of the world, experience the Five Sufferings of the mortal world,
the Six Delusions, Seven Emotions, and Eight Hardships.
(T/N: Six Delusions: desire , detestation , delusion , pride , doubt , and evil views)
When I finally understand what human nature is, I can write a moving story.
Although I can't be the pen in your hand,
showing you the mortal world and experiencing different events in life... that's not hard at all.
Are you really willing to do that?
Of course, I am.
This is what I want to do most, in my life.
When I recover from my injury, you and I will leave the mountain and travel the world.
We will do one good deed every day.
Then you'll always have new stories to write about in your books.
All right. Great!
"So close, yet so far, searching for my old love."
"Only writing about my deep love."
Yan Dan.
Do you understand?
I do.
"So close, yet so far, searching for my old love. Only writing about my deep love."
The old love he is talking about is definitely the flower demon who took the Extraordinary Eye from him.
He is the master of the mountain,
but he failed to win the heart of the girl he loves.
One of the Eight Hardships is not getting what you wish for.
It seems like demons are not spared from this either.
I understand!
You don't understand.
[Lingxiao Sect]
[Get Rid of the Evil Demons]
[Eliminate Demons and Devils]
It's the Lingxiao Sect's duty to get rid of demons and protect the people.
Madams, there is no need to thank us.
My daughter was possessed by a cat demon.
It's all thanks to Taoist Master Tang Zhou that our family was reunited.
If it wasn't for Taoist Master Tang Zhou, our family's field would probably still be occupied by rat demons.
I had to come here to thank you personally.
But where is Taoist Master Tang Zhou?
Madams, what has actually brought you here?
Why don't you be direct?
I am embarrassed by what my daughter has done.
After Taoist Master Tang got rid of the demon power in her, she fell in love with him at first sight.
She said she would only marry him and no one else!
It is the same thing with my daughter.
I know the rules of the Lingxiao Sect.
The chief must practice celibacy.
However, that rule doesn't apply to the other disciples of the sect.
I heard that Tang Zhou is approaching his twenties, but he isn't betrothed to anyone yet.
So I've brought my daughter's birth date with me.
(T/N: for zodiac compatibility)
I did so too. We must see Taoist Master Tang today.
We want to share our gratitude with him. Chief, please do not turn us away.
Despite Tang Zhou being in his current state, you are still so kind to him.
I am grateful beyond words. Why would I turn you away?
Taoist Master Tang Zhou, he...
Tang Zhou has been diagnosed with smallpox.
If there really is a woman who wants to marry him and take good care of him,
then I will honor my late senior brother.
Well...
Sect Leader.
Sect Leader, have the madams left?
They have.
You are approaching your twentieth birthday.
There are more and more people visiting us, hoping to marry their daughters to you.
According to the sect's rules, the sect leader's successor must practice celibacy.
Fortunately, all you want is to cultivate, instead of being in a romantic relationship.
I am very glad about that.
However, there is no need to lie about having smallpox or tuberculosis, jinxing yourself.
Sect Leader, Lingxiao Sect's duty is to eliminate demons and devils.
We fear nothing.
Since I am already lying, of course, I need to lie effectively.
Sect Leader...
There is something I want to ask you.
This year is the tenth anniversary of Master's passing. I will leave the mountain to travel the world.
I won't be able to visit his grave and pay respects.
I will ask you to burn this on my behalf, Sect Leader.
I will definitely take care of it.
Senior Brother didn't put his hopes on the wrong person. You also didn't let him down.
This is your first time leaving the mountain. Take good care of yourself.
I will.
By the way, Sect Leader...
I... I have another question to ask you.
I have no idea why, but I've often had the same dream over the past few years.
In my dream, there was a heartbroken woman.
She jumped off a bridge, right before I did.
Is the woman... someone you know?
I don't think so.
Her back is always to me. I've never managed to see her face.
Every time I wake up from that dream, my heart aches terribly,
and have a hard time breathing.
Could it be from my past life?
According to the Zhou Gong's Interpretation of Dreams, we see our weaknesses in our dreams.
Tang Zhou. You have always been a very talented person, and your skills are outstanding.
You are the most outstanding disciple the Lingxiao Sect has had over the years.
However, it is true that you are inexperienced and too soft-hearted.
Perhaps the dream is trying to remind you not to be too soft-hearted and get deceived by a woman.
Do not fall into a demon's trap.
Because your softhearted master trusted a demon,
he got himself killed.
I understand.
The Lingxiao Sect will eliminate all devils and demons without exception.
I don't dare to ever forget this.
Sect Leader, you can rest assured. I'll prove my determination when I complete my expedition.
I'm sure you will never let the Lingxiao Sect down.
Good.
"Kill All the Tortoise-Flipping Men in the World"?
Why does this tortoise look so familiar?
You... You are actually a little tortoise!
Stop mocking me!
Keep mocking me and I will kill you!
Hey! Stop right there!
Yu Mo! Yu Mo!
- What is the matter?
- Quickly, help me!
- Shut up!
- Are you trying to bully her?
- Yu Mo. Yu Mo, do you know what his real form is?
I'm guessing he is a dung beetle.
What do you mean, "dung beetle"?
In your heart, am I just a bug that rolls dung into balls?
He is not that much better than a dung beetle!
His real form is a big tortoise!
I am not just any tortoise.
- I am a divine tortoise.
- Please!
Why would a divine tortoise sleep in a coffin?
Would a divine tortoise be that insecure?
Fine. I'll tell you the truth. I was supposed to live in the divine lake, eating fish and prawns.
I was living an idle life...
but I had the worst luck. I met an immortal who would flip me over every day.
Later, a kind immortal turned me the right side up again.
However, all that flipping almost killed me.
If you were me, you... w-wouldn't you lay in a coffin to keep yourself safe?
That divine tortoise was you?
You really are that divine tortoise!
Don't you remember the two immortals who saved you?
I almost died of excessive puking after all that flipping.
I had no time to find out who they were!
Yu Mo, I am warning you. You better make sure she keeps this secret.
If you dare let this slip, I...
You, you, you... What will you do?
Demons of Yelan Mountain, listen to this!
Zi Lin's real form is a little tortoise!
- You...
- What are you doing?
Yu Mo, how can you put your wife before your brother? I will deal with you later!
Ugly woman!
Little Tortoise.
You darned lotus spirit!
Stop right there!
Stupid tortoise, stop chasing after me.
As a tortoise, you will never catch me!
Got it? Guess what this is?
I must kill you today!
- You...
- This... Catch it!
Sister Bai Ling, I bet you five dried fruits that
Yan Dan will get beaten up so badly, she'll return to her original form today.
I bet ten dried fruits that Yan Dan will surely win the fight.
Because she has Mountain Chief Yu Mo backing her.
Bai Ling is right.
I just dried that fruit!
You can do it again later.
Yan Dan, stay strong!
Understood!
Catch this!
Little Tortoise!
This is the good life. Nothing is better than this.
You are done for!
I'm going to kill you!
Help!
I will kill you!
Move. Move!
[Lingxiao Sect]
Senior Brother Tang Zhou. You're leaving the sect just to avoid meeting all those ladies.
However, I predict... that you will run into another love disaster during your trip.
Really?
Qin Qi.
All the best, Senior Brother.
We await your return.
[Lingxiao Sect]
We have subdued the Bear, Rat, and Cat clans.
Other than the Fox Clan, that refuses to surrender, we have subdued all demons!
Congratulations to the Mountain Chiefs for becoming the Kings of all Demons!
From now on, all will obey you!
Kings of All Demons.
We are ready to serve you!
Please rise.
Since you have bowed to me, I will let bygones be bygones.
Zi Lin and I will definitely find you a place to stay on this mountain.
A place for everyone to live.
I'm sure you understand the rules of Yelan Mountain.
There cannot be fighting between clans,
nor fights for power.
You are not allowed to wreak havoc in the mortal world when you leave the mountain.
If I find out that any of you are breaking these rules, I won't show any mercy and punish you myself.
We are so grateful for the Mountain Chiefs' kindness.
Henceforth, we will definitely change our ways.
However...
What? What do you want to say?
In the past few years, Miss Yan Dan has often led the mountain demons to rob our clans.
I beg your pardon.
- Can you repeat that?
- No, no.
I was just offering some advice, that's all.
We clan leaders have already sincerely repented.
Can we ask Miss Yan Dan for a favor?
Can she at least return our demonic essence pills to us?
Yan Dan told me about this before.
She said that your clans are very powerful.
You disturbed the mortal world and bullied innocent people.
If you have your demonic essence, you will keep causing more trouble.
I think she is right.
That is why she turned your demonic essence into dice to play with.
Mountain Chief, Yan Dan is looking for you.
Can't you see that I am in a serious meeting?
Tell her to wait.
She said that, if you don't come, there'll be no late-night snacks tonight.
I'm coming.
What...
- This—
- What is with the fuss?
Though he is the King of All Demons, he fell head over heels in love with a lotus demon.
You told her everything?
Didn't I say I wanted to surprise her?
I told you not to let her find out.
But you still told her.
Mountain Chief, others give surprises in the form of jewelry. They're easy to hide.
But you are building a pavilion of books.
How could she not notice such a huge pavilion? It's impossible.
I don't need you to tell me that.
Yan Dan!
Yu Mo! Look what I found.
Yan Dan.
[Third Chapter]
Master... I want to build a stage in the mountain.
I will do anything, as long as it makes you happy.
I really want to drink fish soup.
Fish soup with lotus seeds?
Sounds good.
We've subdued all Yelan Mountain demons, except for Three-tailed Snow Fox Clan, who would rather die than surrender.
We admire your confidence and won't force you to submit.
But why are you suddenly here today?
I am Lin Lang, the daughter of the Fox Clan leader.
Zi Yan.
Where is your greeting?
This is my brother, the future successor of the Fox Clan.
He was accidentally poisoned, and no one in our clan knows how to save him.
If the two Mountain Chiefs help us, the Fox Clan will surely submit to you.
I am willing to stay and serve the Mountain Chiefs for the rest of my life, as well.
There are two Mountain Chiefs here.
Which one are you looking for?
The one who killed Prison Lizard and unified the mountain clans.
The only man whom the Three-tailed Snow Fox would marry...
is naturally you.
I am sitting right here!
How could you just ignore me like that?
I heard that Mountain Chief Zi Lin was once severely injured.
The man behind you saved you with the Extraordinary Eye.
Isn't that right?
I will save him, but forget about marrying me.
The Fox Clan has our pride. We always repay kindness.
Please do not turn me down, Mountain Chief.
Our Mountain Chief Yu Mo has a heart of stone.
Moreover, he has more than enough wives and concubines already.
How about this?
Perhaps... you can consider marrying me.
All members of the Fox Clan are loyal to their partners.
Once we have made up our minds, we are never swayed.
Mountain Chief, please respect our clan's custom and divorce all your other concubines.
I will be your one and only wife, from now on.
I swear to give you my all and stay loyal to you forever.
Three-tailed Snow Foxes... They are a noble bunch...
If we can save their future leader, we will be able to bring peace to the mountain.
You have everything to gain and nothing to lose here.
Why don't you just go along with it?
Close the door. Bring Yan Dan here.
Sister, it hurts a lot.
Is it hurting you again?
Zi Yan, don't worry. Hold my hand.
Zi Yan, stay strong.
They will cure you very soon.
Zi Yan, don't worry.
If they can't heal you, I'll take you to Shenxiao Palace...
and we'll ask the Shenxiao Palace Chief for help.
He will definitely be able to cure you.
Hang in there for a while more. Okay?
Your Highness. Your Highness.
- Can I come in?
- Yes.
Good boy. You will be fine soon.
Your Highness, may I take a look at your brother's leg?
Zi Yan, please endure it.
Can you cure him?
Your Highness, the Fox Clan might not be grateful for what you've done for them.
Our Mountain Chief isn't the only person who can cure him.
Why don't you seek help somewhere else? What do you think?
Are you trying to tell me to leave? Are you Mountain Chief's concubine?
I am from Flower Spirit Clan.
When I first came here, I was made his concubine. However—
What is the matter?
Your Highness, I shouldn't be here.
I won't bother you further and leave.
I hate it when someone doesn't finish their sentence.
What are you trying to say?
Your Highness, it isn't actually a big deal...
How should I say this?
What is this?
- Did the Mountain Chief—
- No, no!
The Mountain Chief didn't do this to me!
H-He didn't do anything to me.
Your Highness, do not let anyone know that I was here.
Also, keep what you saw just now a secret. All right?
I'll leave now.
Mountain Chief, please have mercy! I won't do it again!
- How dare you meet with the Princess of the Fox Clan behind my back?
- I won't do it again!
Tell me! What did you say to her?
I did not say anything to her!
I said nothing, Mountain Chief!
Please don't hit me there! The wound hasn't healed yet!
It hurts!
I understand!
You're venting all your anger on me because you can't find the wicked demon who stole your Extraordinary Eye, right?
Come at me! Just kill me. Do it now!
You are right. I really am a heartless man. Say it again!
I will kill you. I will kill you now!
Help!
The Princess of the Fox Clan spent way too long hiding and eavesdropping on us.
My throat is so dry from all the shouting. I'm losing my voice.
She finally left.
Thank you, my dear Attendant Lian.
It's my honor.
Solving problems for my master is my duty.
What we did to avoid marriage is something worth writing down in my novels.
I'm curious to see if Lin Lang will leave tonight.
Master.
I can tell that Lin Lang is a beautiful lady just from her eyes.
She was born into a noble family.
She's a little arrogant, but she's also very straightforward and honest.
She is a rare, wonderful lady. Why do you want to reject her?
Have you still not gotten over the wicked demon who stole your Extraordinary Eye?
I'll have to kick you out if I marry her.
Why don't you marry Zi Lin and be his concubine?
No way. Never.
Although I'm just an attendant, if I have to find a backer, he needs to be good, right?
Taoist Master Brother, please spare my life.
If you let me go, I'll give you the primordial spirit that I've spent a hundred years building.
My spiritual pill is a rare treasure for people like you, who are cultivating.
Consuming it can effectively grow your cultivation base.
A mortal will only get an upset stomach from consuming a spiritual pill.
Enough of your nonsense.
Get inside.
Go on.
Good morning, Madam.
Good morning!
Yan Dan.
Princess Lin Lang! Why are you here?
Are you all right?
I overheard your conversation with Yu Mo last night.
I know that you can help others, but you're too scared because you're intimidated by his power. Right?
Yan Dan. If you save Zi Yan, I will help you get out of here.
Zi Yan?
Thank you! Thank you, Yan Dan!
Thank you very, very much!
You are welcome, very welcome.
Now that your brother's poison has been removed, you two should leave before Mountain Chief Yu Mo sees you.
We just met by chance, and you were willing to risk your life to save us.
The Fox Clan will definitely repay your kindness.
Yan Dan, let's leave together.
From now on, you will no longer be abused by that beast, Yu Mo.
You are welcome. It's not a big deal, really.
The Flower Spirit Clan sent me here to be his concubine.
If I leave now, the Flower Spirit Clan will be implicated.
You should just leave with your brother.
Don't worry about that.
When you marry a Fox Clan member someday, I will surely keep your family safe.
Then you won't have to worry about anything ever again.
"Marry a Fox Clan member"?
Don't tell me you want me to marry him!
That's not a good idea.
I still prefer someone older than me, a more mature man.
We Three-tailed Snow Foxes always keep our promises.
From now on, no one will bully you again!
You went overboard.
Looks like your little concubine is about to get kidnapped.
- That's not appropriate. It's really not appropriate.
- Let's go now.
Wait, but—
You..
She is mine. Let go of her.
But you don't love her. Why won't you let her leave with me?
Hitting and yelling at her is a form of love too. Don't you get it?
Nonsense! Yan Dan is leaving with me!
If you don't let her go, don't blame me for not showing you any mercy.
I won't let her go.
Yan Dan.
If you two want to talk, just talk! Stop pulling me. It hurts!
- Did I hurt you?
- Are you all right?
Yan Dan.
Lian, tell her you're mine and you're coming with me.
Princess Lin Lang. I...
Stop forcing her!
''Agarwood'' - Zhang Jie | Jane Zhang
♫  My most bewildering memory is the moonlight falling like frost on the ground full of fallen leaves  ♫
♫  For a single teardrop, I'm drowning myself in sorrow, obsessing with forgetting you  ♫
♫  If we'd have to walk till we separate, to where would you want to go?  ♫
♫  Turn around and become the delusion of my life ♫
♫  The most beautiful destiny is hidden in the dark night, "love" is the word for everything  ♫
♫  My loneliness and longing for you leaves a mark like fragments of the moon  ♫
♫  I still have an image of you imprinted in my mind even after washing away the fine dust  ♫
♫  Life after life, this is the longing I missed the most ♫
♫  You are the breeze of a fallen flower in the world of flowers adding to the mound of fallen flowers  ♫
♫  Will you shed tears over the truth of the mortal world?  ♫
♫  You're like the unattainable Autumn Moon in the vast sky; don't dare to shine bright yet not hesitate to shine  ♫
♫  In my dream, the one I loved is with me  ♫
♫  After bidding farewell, when Spring becomes Autumn, where can I find my heart in this world?  ♫
♫  Several lifetimes will not be enough for our parting  ♫
♫  As I watch lovers enjoying fireworks on the riverbanks, my love and longing for you makes my pain unbearable
♫  There will be a time when the world is beautiful  ♫
♫  When the lotus blossoms again, you and I will be together  ♫