[English subtitles are available]
[AiLongNhai The Series]
Ai speaking
Where are you?
Is that you Dad?
I'm at home
I'll ask you again, Where are you?
I'm at home Dad…
Let's go back and talk at home, Aiyaret.
You don't have to hurry, but during that you should think about what kind of mistakes you have done.
Did Jaonan come with you?
No, he didn't. Don't expect to depend on him. We have to talk about this matter on our own.
Wait. Dad! Dad!
What's this.
Where are you going?
Home.
Hey! What's going on?
How was it, Not fun?
What's Fun?
Last Night.
Last night…
Hey, look.
You're the best, but I got to go because my dad just arrived in Toronto
Seriously?
A little bit.
Good bye.
Bye.
Good morning Dad. Are you tired? Would you like anything to drink?
Silence.
Oh Dad.
You don't have to be serious. Can we just talk?
You went too far this time. You quarreled until being expelled from university.
He started first.
I have never taught you to use emotion as a solution.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
I don't know. Why did you bring so many luggage?
It's not mine,
all of these are yours.
What!! What do you mean dad?
It means that you have to go back to Thailand with me.
When?
Now!!
Right now!!
You have caused so many problems that I couldn't handle with you already.
Don't take it serious, Dad. Please Let me stay here!!!
No, I'm not allowing you to stay here.
Pack your bags now.
Your behavior is unacceptable.
And this time, don't expect that JaoNan could help you.
These are all my belonging and luggage
What do you want me to pack? You are going to force me to go back to Thailand anyway. It's terrible.
Swearing in any language couldn't make I change my mind.
Terrible. Such a terrible moment.
If you go back with me, the car that grandfather bought as a present
will only be confiscated and let you use another car instead. But if you refuse to go back with me,
I'll sell it.
Please don't do that! It's my gift.
One more thing, I will cancel all your credit cards.
Choose on your own. Go back with me, or you won't get anything.
Oh, dad, if you planned to punish me like this, hitting me will be less painful.
if I intense to hit you, it will be no mercy.
JaoNan won't let you hit me.
Because if you hit me one time, JaoNan will hit you back twice.
Aiyaret!
Where are you going?
I'm going to pack my belonging,
If I am stubborn, I can be famish.
You know that I can not handle with difficulties. I will go back  with you. Don't be so mean.
Just wonder when I was your age, Do I lose temper like you?
Maybe Not, because when you were my age,
You're probably writing a diary fantasizing about JaoNan most of the time.
I will reduce your salary. Is that OK?
Oh, that's not good. Just pretend that I never said that OK? I'll go get my stuff.
Why is the weather so hot?
Are you done, Dad?
Wait a minute.
Come and help me to find the gift that I'll bring to Professor Amnat, please.
What does it look like?
It's a pen box wrapped in white paper.
I remember putting it around here.
Dad, why do you always like a big car like this?
And you can't find anything.
Good luck that this time is just a pen box.
It's not a car key like last time.
It's normal to become forgetfulness because I'm old now.
It's not about getting old, Dad!
You've been forgetful since I can remember.
Why did you keep complaining all the time?
This is the university where you used to be a teacher, right?
By the way, where is the faculty that JaoNan used to study?
I want to see it.
Let's go and introduce yourself to the professor in the faculty first.
Then I will bring you to observe around the campus.
I'll come to observe on my own later. After this, you can rest. I will drive back to Nan by myself.
OK, So Can you come and help me find a pen now?
you're a really forgetful old man.
Aiyaret!
OK, Dad!!!
It should be here.
Dad, look over there.
Do you want that motorcycle?
If you live in Bangkok, You better use a car.
I think is it inconvenient when going travel for a long distance?
I'm not talking about the car, Dad.
Look at the rider,
he look like JaoNan.
There is no one in this world like my JaoNan, No way...
Hmm.
Look similar.
Dad,
stop looking with those eyes,
or else I will tell JaoNan.
You already have JaoNan
This guys is mine.
Not all the man will love the same sex, do you know?
My heart tells me,
My heart tells me that
he Must be mine.
Enough.
You used to say  when you first met Nan, you were mesmerized by his sight.
So I fell in love because of those legs too.
I'll be right back.
Hey, where are you going?
Ai, Aiyaret!
Yellow duck.
Oh! Mr. Ducky!!
You dropped it over there
Thank you.
- What is your name?
- Thank you so much.
if I lost Mr.Ducky, it would be a big problem.
OK.
Let's go Mr. Ducky we are late now.
Wait!
I didn't know his name yet.
Do you still want to go back to Nan?
Or today you want to go to study with him?
Dad,
can you tell me about the first time you met JaoNan?
Then how did you know it was love?
I can tell you
But I can't tell you what love is.
You have to learn it by yourself.
Then use the feeling to answer yourself whether it is love or not.
I think this time is right.
Will he say yes to you?
Do you know who he is? What's his name?
Umm. Umm...
Even asking the name is also ignored.
It looked like he had been heartbroken from the start.
Oh, Mr. Sippakorn, why don't you cheer me up?
Here we go. The professor is waiting.
Thank you.
Kahabodee.
Waranluck.
Chen Nhai is here!
You arrived on time. Always come to class ion the last minutes  from the first year until the second year.
I am puntual.
Please Learn to iron your shirt, Mr. Chen Nhai.
Hahaha, it's my style.
Alright, let's go to your seat.
Hi guys.
We'll start the lesson, everyone.
You're late again!
It's all your fault.
Nobody called me to wake me up.
I'm in a hurry
and almost lost my Mr. Ducky.
By the way, someone can pick it up for me.
So handsome.
Thank you. I have been handsome since I was born.
Not you,
I mean that guy who picks up my Mr. Ducky.
Nhai, That's my pen.
Can I Borrow it? I lost my pen yesterday.
Or you can give it to me.
What? If you borrow my pen, which one will I use?
Ummm…
Maybe you can borrow Nine???
No, you have to borrow him yourself.
- Nine…
- What?
Mr. honors.
Can I borrow your pen?
You can use my pen,
I'll find another pen for you.
Always borrow others nearly every day.
More is the trouble that other people have to take care of your Mr. Ducky.
There's a rule that I can't lose this duck.
If I lose it, my father will not give me any money.
You guys have to help me take care of my Mr.Ducky. OK?
Why does your Mr. Ducky is related to us?
You guys know I'm forgetful.
You guys have to help me take care of Mr. Ducky.
So who is the guy that picks up your Mr. Ducky?
I don't know too.
I never see him before.
But so handsome, very handsome,
handsome as the  main actor from BL series
So why don't you become his boyfriend?
Let him take care of you and your Mr. Ducky.
Shut up.
You know I already have someone in mind.
My goal is to win the heart of Kanliew, the prom queen from the faculty of Business.
Have you ever told your father about flirting with Kanliew?
Yes.
As soon as I told him,
my father gave me Mr. Ducky key chain.
Your father must have told you indirectly.
Before taking care of anyone, take care of the duck first.
Are you saying that Nhai can't take care of himself?
Oops.
It's all true.
OMG! Are you all my friends?
Yes, but now I'm going to study.
And if not silent, Don't even think about copying the Lecture.
OK, sir!
Quiet!!
You are the one who keeps talking.
Dad, do you think JaoNan will like it?
I miss my childhood,
when I make a mistake
I'll collect this flower and give it to JaoNan.
Jaonan will always smile.
Flattering.
Why are you jealous of your son?
It's supposed to.
Even bring flowers to JaoNan. It won't help to reduce.
Very nice smell.
He must like it.
JaoNan.
Welcome back
I miss JaoNan very much.
Acts like we haven't seen each other for a long time
even though we just met
JaoNan,
Dad took my car.
Huh, didn't he tell you that
that is my idea!!
I didn't tell him
because I waited him to hear from you.
I'm the one who told your dad to take your car as punishment
and told you to return to Thailand.
What!!!
We will not talk about the past.
While being punished,
you can't do anything wrong anymore.
I'm so sorry.
Are you angry at me?
I'm not angry; I can understand the anger of youth.
I chose to punish you first
because if it's your father, he will punished you more severely.
You should know that.
Be nice, OK?
because we are not that kind.
OK!
Let's go have lunch, JaoNan.
Dad and Mom must have waited a long time as well.
Ai, It's heavy.
I love JaoNan more than you, Dad.
OK, Up to you.
Maybe I think I gave you too much money.
Dad! I love you as same as JaoNan.
You are liar.
As same as you.
Wow!
Cutie pie!
Just woke up or haven't slept yet?
What's the reason that makes you play the fiddle?
and playing in bad rhythm.
I can't sleep.
I played in bad rhythm because I thought of something.
- What are you thinking about?
- Bangkok!!
Huh?
I've never seen you so excited about moving to the new university.
I'm not excited.
I miss someone there.
Dad hasn't woken up yet?
He is still sleeping! Maybe tired.
Busy for many days.
You have to stop being so stubborn.
Umm... this time, what the point of arguing is?
My life was too good, so they got upset and tried to harm me.
Well, I never asked. Do you have any friends there?
No. I like being alone.
It's really good to have friends.
So who do you thinking of?
Mr. Ducky.
Hmm?? Duck or people?
The man with the duck keychain.
The face is slender,
the hair is like this, and the eyes are small. The nose is like this.
Ummm… OK, OK.
Let's go get paper and pencil and draw for me to see, shall we?
Draw in the air like this. How do I know
that the person who can make Ai can't go to sleep? What does he look like?
This is how he looks like,
from a long distance, he looks like you.
But when I look closely, it's not.
I had a dream about him last night.
When I woke up, he was still in my mind
I can't sleep anymore.
I don't know what to do.
Are you fallen in love???
I think so.
Then you should approach him.
If he doesn't like me?
Play fiddle for him.
Haha, he could misunderstand and thought that I playing the fiddle for "Buffalo."
Then......just force him to love.
Is that OK?
Just kidding.
Don't do that.
If you like him, try to approach him and flirt.
But if he doesn't like you, don't bother him.
OK!! I understand.
I study at the same faculty with him; I still have a lot of time.
Well, I'm here for you, Ai.
Tomorrow you have to go back to Bangkok, right?
Yes, I have to go back to university.
Professor Amnat is afraid that I won't be able to catch up with my friends.
I just realized that Professor Amnat is teacher.
When he is in Canada, he's like the naughty pilot.
I don't know how I got close to dad.
Your dad is a player too.
I'm lucky that he loves me with all of his heart.
Oh, if my father came to hear this,
he would surely smile.
I have looked at the results of our studies in Canada.
Very good.
I doubt your father taught you well.
My father taught me my homework last time when I was eight years old.
After that,
I am completely dependent on myself.
OK! You are intelligent.
But that doesn't mean you have permission to get into a quarrel,
your dad tells me to keep an eyes on you.
Of course not!
If no one starts first…
What did you say???
I definitely don't.
It's time to study. Let's go to the classroom.
I just got my nails done. Beautiful?
Very nice.
Very annoying.
Everyone coming?
My class no one can miss!
Chen Nhai hasn't arrived yet, Master.
But wait a minute, he will show up.
Oh Chen Nhai, I like your friend Intha.
He arrived on time for every class.
Everyone wonders who is the handsome young man next to me.
His name is Aiyaret
and will be your classmate.
He just returned from Canada. So he joined us in the middle of the semester.
Chen Nhai is here!
Oh! My Mr. Ducky's picker?
Yellow ducky.
Very punctual, Mr. Chen Nhai,
but I haven't checked yet.
Did I come on time?
Master, don't be kidding.
Be quiet. The class next to us has already started.
Come and sit here. No one sits here.
Can I sit with Chen Nhai?
As you wish.
What a small world!
What's your name?
Master already introduce him already.
you're late, so you don't know.
Aiyaret right ?
I'm Ton.
he is Nine.
I'm Intha.
I'm Chen Nhai.
Nice to meet you.
Aiyaret!!
You can call me Just "AI."
I think it is a little bit too long.
"Called Me Ai Only."
Can we talk not politely? I'm not fluent to speak politely.
I'm OK.
So why did you come in the middle of the semester?
when I saw you, I thought that you were in  another faculty.
I'm just back from Canada.
Yesterday, Nhai told me that you picked up Mr.ducky for him, right?
Huh.
And Nhai said you very handsome.
Nine, Stop!!
See, he's really handsome, like I said.
Look at his face!!
Yes! He is handsome.
Why did you touch his face?
The handsome face will be all dirty.
Ton!!
After classes, let's go get something to eat. Nhai will treat us.
Why have to be me?
To celebrate that Ai is keeping your Mr.ducks for you.
Nhai, if Ai didn't pick your Mr. Ducky that day,
your father will kill you.
Just treat us a little bit. you won't die, right?
So let's pay half of it.
I pay because you pick my Mr. Ducky!
You pay because we're friends.
for the others, just thinks that it is for charity.
OK!
Did you ask him? It's he wants to be your friend or not?
In!!
We are no longer friend Because I got a new friend.
Right?, Mr.Aiyaret.
What do you want to eat?
Don't answer "anything".
I want to eat fried chicken.
And I'd like to try sitting on the back of your motorcycle too.
Sure!! Mr. Aiyaret.
Chen Nhai Bike is happy to serve you.
Near or far away. Will it be a price according to the distance?
Or a kilometer? What will you choose?
Choose one or both, I can pay for it all.
What? You've got a new friend.
What are you studying?
Hey.
What do you want to eat?
I want to eat fried chicken.
I didn't ask you.
But I want to answer!! Did you have a problem?
Stop, let's go to the mall behind the university, OK?
How will you go? Do you have your car?
I'm going to park the car here and go with Nhai.
- Ai, Please don't...
- What your problem, Ton ??
Shut up!!!
You can go with my car.
That's OK.
I want to try sitting on the back of Nhai's motorcycle.
Hey, you see?
My best friend Ai wants to go with me.
You guys just go
I'm cheering you on.
You know I'm the most handsome.
Boo, Brother Ton dared to post.
It must be you.
Let's waiting to see, Ton.
I will focus on studying and able to study at the same University as you do.
I already thought that Nhai would be late.
Is it he?
Finally.
Where did you take Ai around the world?
Oh, what? I brought him to a shortcut.
Where is my water?
Here she just got it for you because you came so late!!
Your shortcut way? Always lost..
So why did you come so fast?
we come in normal way,
but the guy who rides a motorcycle for you isn't normal.
If not lost, not detour, not Chen Nai.
It's true! There was a trip that we went to Phetchabun.
I'll go with Nine's car.
But  He said he wanted to go by himself.
He appeared at Prachinburi province
and he missed that trip.
Silence and eat.
Stop ruining my picture.
Picture?
Are you talking about a personal image?
Yes, Correct!
Congratulations!
You are the first person who understands Nhai's Joke.
Since I was born,
I don't see anyone understanding Nhai's joke
The last person just broke up with Nhai
because of his bad joke.
Alright.
Are all of you bullying me?
I will get revenge by revealing all of you guys' girls stories!
Do it. Come on!
Let's start with Ton.
Well, Ton
Urmm, Ton..
Ugh.
Why don't you guys have a "peak" story.
Because our behavior aren't like you.
Well, that's such a pity.
Don't you have a girlfriend?
Nope.
Single, so single
single like..I can't believe that a handsome guy like me will be single.
And these guys,
you don't have to care about them.
Ai,
don't you have a girlfriend?
Oh, Intha.
Look at his handsome face, he looks just like a superstar.
If he doesn't have a girlfriend, that is strange.
Um.. I don't have a girlfriend, I am single.
- Really!
- Huh!
Are you serious? I can't believe.
Well, I will find a lover around here.
I have something to ask you guys.
What kind of person do you guys like?
I like a nice person, cute,
and the one who only loves me.
I like the person who I like.
I have the same mindset as Intha.
How about you?
I already have the person that I like.
Kanliew.
The freshman prom queen of the Faculty of  Business.
She has a long hair with little arm hair.
You are a psychopath.
You don't understand Nine.
People with arm hair are so attractive.
Right, Ai?
I have no idea.
I don't have hair on my arm.
What's wrong with you? Even if you have hair on your arm, I still don't like you.
I feel giggle.
That's hurt.
Hey, just kidding.
I will share the straw with you.
The straw to commit our friendship.
Nhai!
Your straw is dirty.
Why are you still offering him?
I ordered all the beverages for everyone.
Ai.
It's OK. I don't mind.
Listen well, all of you.
From now on, my new best friend is Ai
and you guys are just common friends.
That's fine.
His hands were dirty, still hugging his neck.
My best friend.
Alright.
Ai!
Why are you daydreaming?
Isn't it delicious?
Nothing.
Let's eat.
This looks tasty.
Well, Kimji at this restaurant is so delicious.
Let's me try.
Yeah, delicious!
Yeah, right.
- Hey, Kimji is so delicious. Let's try.
- Yum.
That's French fries.
Why are you making that face?
You want to ride with Nhai, isn't it?
That's so funny; how was the biker feeling?
Don't you feel like you went through the war?
If you are not OK with my ride,
you can go back with these guys.
I didn't say anything.
Nhai.
See ya.
Let's go.
Let's go back.
What's wrong with those guys?
Where do you park the car?
So, I can send you to the car.
Did you get angry at me?
Nope.
So where is your car?
There.
Wow!
You drive BMW?!
Yes.
My dad wants me to drive this car.
You are so rich.
JaoNan has many cars.
If you like sports cars, you should visit my home in Nan province.
I have never been to Nan Province before.
We should ask our friends to go.
Why not? Let's go.
Well, you just talk to me...
Does that me you are OK with me now?
Nope.
I am not mad at you.
Well, on the weekend let's have the party at my place.
Anything that you want to eat, I will take care of you.
Deal?
Deal!
You promise to prepare anything that I want.
Yes, as you wish.
Where do you live?
Nearby the university.
How about you? Stay at the condo or go back home?
Condo.
My condo just opposite the university.
Take care then.
I will go back now.
Nhai,
how about we download the GPS and share information?
- What's that?
- It's a map.
Well, Intha
told me that you always lose the way.
If you have this application and lost the way, I can pick you up.
Hey.
That's a good idea, let's download it.
But you have to download it for me I am a kind of low-tech person.
Sure,
there you go.
OK, I am leaving. Bye.
Thank you, Chen Nhai
for giving me a ride to my car.
Why are you grooming yourself?
I thought that you had already left.
I am about to go back.
Where are you going?
I'll go to the dormitory.
Dormitory? Why are you going there?
I will go there to flirt with Kanliew.
Kanliew is always at the Dormitory common space with her friends.
I'll go with you.
Do you like Karn Liw as well?
Nah.
I will assist you.
No way. You are way too handsome. She might change her mind  and like you instead.
That's will not going to happen. Besides, I don't like the person who has arm hair.
Come on Chen Nhai.
Handsome Chen Nhai.
Please...
Please let me go with you.
Fine. Let's go.
Thank you.
Hey! Did you guys say you will come and read the book? Why don't you guys pay attention?
Right!! Don't even have book.
Who say they coming for study?
This building is a female dormitory.
But as you can see that it full of men.
They always claim likes comes to buy some food,
but actually flirt with girls.
Same as you right?
Yes. No!!
I don't claim.
I'm here to flirt 100%
Someone brought a guitar to play.
Next time I will bright the guitar here too.
Hmm, can you play as well?
I can play music before holding a pencil and pen..
Kanliew.
She is coming!!!
Your are overacting.
Ai did she go?? Am I still handsome?
What can I do????
Hi Nhai! Did you come and find something to eat again??
Hi!
Who is this guy??
Kanliew, you don't have to care about him.
Just care about me, OK? Do you want to take a seat?
You can come and sit here.
It's OK!! I can go and sit with my friends.
See you later. Bye!
Oh, just carrying a guitar and you look handsome.
I thought that you were lost.
Did you care about me?
What's wrong with you?
But what song will you play?
Can I have a nice song for Kanliew?
Where is she?
Over there!
Are you having a problem recognizing people face?
She is so cute!!!
You are cuter.
What did you say??
Nothing!!
OMG!! He is my type….
If a man sings and flirts with me like this, my heart is for him since he starts playing the guitar.
I think the person sitting next to him is much cuter, very cute.
Looks more like he's singing and flirting together.
OMG!!
Shut up.
Shut your mouth.
Even if you flirt with a girl or flirt with themselves, I don't care anyway.
I like it anyway.
Do you think like me? B1.
Let's go, B2!!
Yes right there.
You came to help me flirt her,
or come flirt for yourself?
Everyone's looking at you now.
So what? I don't care about them.