THE GOLDEN SPOON
-Honey.
-Dad.
-Honey, Cheol!
-Honey.
-Cheol. Honey.
-Dad!
Cheol!
Taeyong.
How injured is my husband?
It's not serious, is it? He's okay, right?
What is this?
Taeyong, why aren't you saying anything?
Answer me!
Taeyong, is my husband okay?
Taeyong.
Doctor.
My husband is okay, right?
Doctor, where is my husband?
Mom…
Dad…
Patient Lee Cheol passed away at 8:50 p.m.
Dad! Dad!
Mom! Mom!
Honey…
Honey!
Dad…
No…
No!
It can't be true. It just can't…
Honey, it's me.
Cheol.
Dad.
Say something.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why? Honey.
No…
No!
Honey.
Dad.
Who did this?
Tell me, you bastard!
You must know who did it!
Who was it?
Who did that to my dad?
Seo Juntae.
-What?
-Seo Juntae.
He just passed away at the hospital.
-What about Juntae?
-We're still looking for him.
You must find him before the police do.
Yes, sir.
-What about my wife?
-Well,
she's going to hold
the house concert as planned.
-What time?
-It begins in an hour.
EPISODE 15
BASED ON THE NAVER WEBTOON
THE GOLDEN SPOON BY HD3
Juntae, listen to me.
I'm going to go perform now.
If I suddenly cancel it,
people will wonder.
Get changed into these clothes first.
You're the safest here,
so don't leave this room, okay?
Thank you, Youngshin.
But why aren't you asking me anything?
Something must have come up.
Hyeondo says that you've killed people,
but I don't believe it.
You'd never kill anyone.
Right, Youngshin.
Don't ever believe Hyeondo.
It's his fault that I ended up like this.
Young master, are you okay?
What's all that blood?
Young master.
I'm going to kill Hwang Hyeondo.
Seo Juntae!
Why did you kill my dad?
Why? Why?
What are you saying, you crazy bastard?
Get off my son.
Father, let's report him to the police.
-I'll make the call.
-Take him.
What?
Father, Seo Juntae is a murderer!
You know that!
Father! Father!
Why don't we have a chat?
Let go of me!
Father! Father!
Let go!
Open up.
Open the door right now!
That bastard Seo Juntae must be arrested.
Open the door!
Seo Juntae is the culprit. He did it!
We're looking into it.
We have to check the CCTV camera footage
-and collect evidence.
-What is this?
Were you never going to stop him?
Because he's
Hwang Hyeondo's brother-in-law?
Maybe you were never planning
on catching him!
Calm down.
Do you remember this gun?
I had prepared this for you.
I didn't know
I would use this again
to aim at you.
You've always been like this.
You lie, deceive,
and betray others.
Shoot me if you want.
Shoot you?
Juntae.
I'm not going to shoot you.
You'll cover it up
so the stock price won't fall
and the group won't lose its reputation?
It's a pity that
Lee Seungcheon's father had to die,
but it's a good thing.
You did well.
He was going to keep getting in my way.
Juntae.
Let's take our time to think about
how we are going to
handle this situation.
I have a nice idea.
Thank you so much, Hyeondo.
But…
My sister once told me
that she'd never believe you.
I should have listened to her sooner.
Why did I believe you like a fool?
Because I was fond of you.
When others said that I resembled you,
I felt
good.
But you ruined my life!
If you want to shoot me,
now is your only chance.
But,
the one who ruined your life wasn't me,
but your mom.
My mom?
Shall I tell you the truth?
Your real mother
is Seo Youngshin,
your older sister.
Now, the choice is up to you.
Juntae?
Juntae left
with a gun just now.
Call in the security team.
Stop him before things get serious.
You were
my mom?
Juntae, what are you talking about?
My brother is a little sick.
So he was hospitalized.
Juntae, you should be
at the hospital, not here.
I'll take you back to the hospital.
Are you my mom?
Answer me!
Pull yourself together.
I'm your older sister!
Mom passed away a long time ago.
The medication
doesn't seem to work at all.
I'm sick and tired
of your rants about Mom.
You're sick of it?
Juntae, you shouldn't do this.
Put the gun down. I'm sorry.
I'll tell you everything.
Let's talk it out.
You believe me, don't you?
No, I don't believe you anymore.
Juntae.
Ta-da!
You look the best
when you smile like this.
Study hard in the States,
and I'll make sure to visit you soon.
You'll come, right?
Of course.
Let me ask you one last time.
Are you my mom?
Just answer that.
Juntae, that is not important right now.
I'm always by your side.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect you to the end.
I won't leave you.
Juntae, please put this down.
You won't admit it until the end.
If you were really my sister,
you'd tell me you were my mom
whether it was a lie or not.
-Juntae.
-Mom.
I hope you live in hell.
Juntae! No!
Young master!
LEE CHEOL
Goodness.
How could something like this happen?
I can't believe this happened
to our kind-hearted man…
This is just unbelievable.
Goodness, Cheol.
Let me do what I can to help.
Goodness.
Mom.
Juhee is here.
I'm here with Taeyong.
How dare you come here?
My dad died because of you!
Just leave.
Get out of here!
Go!
Sungah.
It's all right.
Taeyong, come in.
Pay your respects.
-Mom.
-It's okay.
Get off!
I know. It's not Taeyong's fault.
He probably
understands you.
Mr. Lee.
Hey, Seung… Taeyong.
-Father, what's going--
-Don't call me that!
Don't you dare come back here again.
Do you know what this is?
He wrote this poem
in third grade, and it's called…
"Free." That's the title.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
I don't care what your name is.
I will always love you.
Because you're my son.
It's not my fault.
I only let Mr. Lee know the truth.
SUCCESS AFTER SUCCESS
CLOSED FOR THE TIME BEING
DUE TO PERSONAL REASONS
Dad used it to draw webtoons.
Are you going to sell it?
No, I'm going to keep it.
Hmm?
What is this?
Huh?
I think Dad used my golden spoon.
He knew who I was.
I didn't know Dad had something like this.
Give it to me.
It belongs to Hwang Taeyong.
He should have bought some clothes.
Like you said, let's go out
and enjoy the change of seasons.
And with Sungah and Seungcheon…
Let's be happy together.
We never got to go and enjoy
the colored leaves in autumn.
It'll soon
be autumn.
You shouldn't have made a promise
you couldn't keep.
How could you leave us like this?
Honey…
What have I done?
At first,
I just wanted to become rich.
I wanted to become rich
and buy a house for my parents.
I just wanted to live a life
without having to worry about
making a living.
Where did it start to go wrong?
One of your employees
gave us your condolence money.
Are you trying to return the money?
Is that why you came?
What's so great about your money
that I would bother to return it?
I appreciate your condolences.
I came here to see the pencils
my husband wanted to have.
There it is.
My husband was the kind of person
who thought he was
the richest in the world
with his favorite pencil
and a glass of soju.
But you know what?
You look poor.
You're surrounded
by all this valuable and expensive stuff,
but strangely, you look so poor.
I see there are various ways
to express your inferiority complex.
I wonder what others will think
if they hear this.
I don't care about what others think.
What matters is what you think.
You probably think I'm right.
You've never been satisfied
with what you had.
This pencil suits a poor man like you.
I'd better pay for this pencil, right?
CASHIER'S CHECK
I think Dad used my golden spoon.
He knew who I was.
Give it to me.
It belongs to Hwang Taeyong.
HWANG TAEYONG
Hello?
Why did you want to see me here?
I made up my mind here
to become rich.
It's where I promised Jinseok
that I'd make it big.
I have something for you.
It's yours.
I want to sincerely
apologize to you, Taeyong.
Because of my greed, I stole your life
and even made Dad pass away.
Only after he passed away,
did I realize how wrong I was.
Do you regret it?
Do you want to be Lee Seungcheon again?
I have no right to say that.
I'll meet the golden spoon granny
and make the final choice soon.
Tell me if you want to go back
to being Hwang Taeyong.
I mean it.
Here, it's your golden spoon.
I found it among Dad's things.
Like I told you before,
I'll stay as Lee Seungcheon.
That doesn't mean
I've forgiven or understood you,
but I accept your apology.
Right. I think I found my real father.
His name is Gwon Yohan.
He was Hwang Hyeondo's friend.
Have you met him?
Gwon Yohan? You mean the old CEO?
He passed away a long time ago.
He passed away?
It's been more than 20 years.
The factory went bankrupt,
and he took his own life.
No.
He's already passed.
Bye.
Sir.
I'll stay as Lee Seungcheon.
You seem busy, so I'll make it short.
Should I say we're too different
or too busy to be more than friends?
What are you talking about?
I'm reporting our breakup to the press.
It'll say I dumped you.
That's okay, right?
Yeojin.
I didn't know
-such a thing would happen to Mr. Lee.
-Yeojin.
My dad's death isn't your fault.
Don't blame yourself.
Don't try to console me.
I actually started
to fall out of love with you.
It's true.
It's a lie.
I didn't want to lose
you.
But I know this is the end of us.
Thank you for everything, truly.
I told you. I'm dumping you.
You think I'm going to
shake your pitiful hand?
Why did you tell him?
If you hadn't told him,
Juntae wouldn't have died.
You killed him.
You killed my Juntae!
What?
Had you admitted that you were his mom,
Juntae wouldn't have died.
You know that yourself.
Don't make me laugh.
It's because of you.
It's all because of you, Hwang Hyeondo.
Yohan, it's not my fault
that our Juntae died, is it?
Please tell me it's not.
Rumor says that Seo Youngshin is
Seo Juntae's mom.
If that's true, who is his dad?
Could it be that rich ex-fiancé?
That's what you're so curious about?
Not the disappearance
of all those articles about Seo Juntae?
I mean,
a few articles said that Seo Juntae
hanged himself at the hospital,
but there's absolutely nothing these days.
Isn't it strange?
Because Dosin deleted them all.
-Yeojin.
-He didn't die at the hospital.
He shot himself in Hwang Hyeondo's house.
Bang.
Do you actually buy this?
How naive considering
you work for the broadcasting industry.
Na Juhee, let's talk for a moment.
Are you here for the program reshuffle?
No, I came to give an exclusive
to a director I know.
I'm calling off my engagement.
Don't be too excited though.
As long as Seungcheon
stays as Hwang Taeyong,
you can't be with him.
There's Hwang Hyeondo.
Thanks for your concern,
but I can take care of my life.
What you said about Seo Juntae…
You weren't joking, were you?
Right, it's true.
But it's not true anymore.
Dosin… Hwang Hyeondo
can do anything.
Everything can be fabricated, right?
Fabricated?
LAYOFF LIST OF ALL STRIKE LABORERS
SHUTDOWN OF ANSIN FACTORY
Don't forget this kind heart of his
as you become a competent businessman.
-Let's put this off for now.
-Sir?
But it's the president's direct orders.
You should approve it.
Real estate prices have risen, so if
the factory is moved to a third country,
the company will surely
make a lot of money.
But who will be responsible
for those who lose their jobs?
Small sacrifices are needed
for a greater purpose.
So the company will make a lot of money
while they deal with small sacrifices?
Don't be like this.
Everyone's already complaining
due to the short-selling.
-If you continue--
-Ah.
The short-selling.
Right, I should resolve that issue first.
But…
Mr. Hwang!
Look properly, you jobless fool.
You're jobless too.
I'm not jobless. I'm a streamer.
By the way,
I wonder if Seungcheon
and his mother are all right.
You know, it doesn't hit you at a funeral.
She's probably having it hard around now.
Right, I won't be able to stream online
at Seungcheon's place, will I?
What?
Come do it in my room.
Jeez.
Dosin Group is the problem.
They slipped through
with Seo Juntae's suicide,
but what about
innocent shareholders like me?
The stock price dropped like crazy.
Is Hightech's short-selling still going?
It's a playground for stock manipulators.
I should have sold all my shares.
Goodness, my subscribers!
HWANG TAEYONG
-Hey.
-What?
Why is Hwang Taeyong calling you?
Beats me.
Show him.
HWANG TAEYONG
What do you want?
What?
What is it?
What? What did he say?
If you still have Dosin Hightech shares,
he wants you to keep them.
What?
Gosh.
What does that mean?
This is crazy!
What do you mean, short covering?
If I withdraw now,
I'll suffer a huge loss!
-Seongwon, you'll lose more tomorrow.
-This is annoying.
Do it now.
You guys too. Do it.
Just who is this guy?
Who's covering for all these shares?
Am I the only one in the dark?
Do you know?
If you do, tell me!
Who are you, people?
The Financial Supervisory Service.
We've confirmed
your illegal naked short-selling attempts.
Please come with us.
Damn it!
Thank you for helping me
despite the urgent request.
No problem. It's actually good for me.
I get to buy more shares at a low price.
Don't tell me you're planning
a hostile takeover.
You know I always hold a long position
when it comes to you.
When I was younger,
I often held short positions.
I guess I've aged.
I want to bet my money on
what makes others successful, not plummet.
Is that why you're running
that 2,000-won diner?
Hmm, not exactly.
It's because of fear.
When I started to make money,
I thought I was lucky.
As I kept making lots of money,
I began to think
I was brilliant and smart.
But growing old, I got scared of money.
Then I came to think I should
earn less and share with others.
It may seem petty,
but that's why I run my diner.
It's the same for this museum.
Did you collect
all these pieces of artwork?
No, quite a lot of them
belong to my rich friends.
Things that are a hassle to keep
but a waste to throw out.
Some of them are from your father.
I'm having dinner with my father.
Yes, Father.
You suddenly wanted to treat me to a meal,
but this is very unexpected.
You've never had this before, have you?
I had it when I was a student.
This is a snack for rich people like us,
but some kids were so poor
that this is all they had to get by on.
Did you refuse to give your approval
thinking for those poor people?
Why did you hand
the Amikus kids over to the FSS?
Did you feel bad
that they were ripping off
those poor investors?
Father, I want to change.
All along,
I've neglected
something very important in life.
If I can… If that's really possible,
I want to change.
What made you want to change
all of a sudden?
Now that Lee Seungcheon's father is dead,
does the world seem different?
A few days ago, I heard something amusing.
Someone told me
that I looked poor.
Isn't that amusing?
But you know,
that person got me precisely right.
I'm a poor man.
The moment you think you're rich,
becoming poor for real
is all you're left with.
I'm poor. I don't have enough.
I'm still thirsty.
You need the desire to move forward.
That's my priority. What is your priority?
Family.
They used to be a burden to me.
But I realized that
family was my priority.
It was foolish of me.
I missed something that important in life.
Thank you for saying so.
Let me say one thing as your family.
Stop with your useless concerns
and come back to your old self.
Don't let anything distract or confuse you
because I won't tolerate it.
You eat this triangular gimbap
to change things up.
It can't be your everyday meal.
But I'll enjoy it today.
I wanted you to get over it.
But I guess you're still dwelling on it.
Then you leave me with no choice.
I'll have to get rid of your old self.
Two scoops, right?
I can do it myself.
I'd better do that one.
No. Mom, stay seated.
-No.
-No, I want you to rest.
All right.
-Rest here.
-I'll do it. It's heavy.
-It's not heavy.
-It's heavy.
-No.
-Put it here.
I won't take long.
Let's go out after I finish this.
I'm okay. Take your time.
Are you here for anything urgent?
I just feel a little uneasy.
I wanted to see you too.
What's making you feel uneasy?
You know,
I feel like I was mistaken
to think everything was settled.
Today, I met Yeojin
and heard how Seo Juntae died.
If…
Just what if
my dad's death was fabricated too?
It's just a silly idea, right?
Because Hyeondo told me to.
He said he'd bail me out.
I didn't kill President Na.
I didn't.
Munki, can you come in for a sec?
Why would you call me in
when you're on a date?
I asked you to check where my father was
regarding President Na.
Did you look into it?
It's just as you know.
I didn't find anything in particular.
Really?
And I looked into Gwon Yohan as you asked.
He committed suicide.
Suicide?
But the first person who found his body
was President Hwang.
Hey, Taeyong. I'm coming now.
Yes, be right there.
Why do you suddenly want to meet Taeyong?
And just who is Gwon Yohan?
Sir.
Let go of me!
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
-Sir.
-I'm okay.
Stop right there.
Stop!
They seemed to follow me from the store.
It's just too suspicious.
Munki. How did it go?
I lost them.
-They had accomplices.
-What?
They didn't seem like normal thugs.
They even had a car.
I think they were trying to abduct him.
Report this to the police and check
the security footage in the area.
Yes, sir.
Can you think of a reason?
Not really.
Who on earth did this?
Don't let anything distract or confuse you
because I won't tolerate it.
No way.
My father?
But there's no reason for him to…
His name is Gwon Yohan.
He was Hwang Hyeondo's friend.
His friend?
Does it mean they are the same age?
Go to the house of a boy your age.
Eat three meals with this spoon.
Then your life will be switched with his,
and his parents will become your parents.
-It was Gwon Yohan.
-What?
The one who hired those men just now
and murdered President Na.
It was all Gwon Yohan's doing.
He used the golden spoon
to become Hwang Hyeondo.
Don't go around alone for the time being.
I'll tell Munki to come right over.
Juhee, stay with him until then.
-Where are you going?
-I have something to do.
He even tried to hurt Taeyong.
I can't just sit here.
LIST OF 2021 DOMESTIC
REAL ESTATE SLUSH FUNDS
LIST OF DOSIN AFFILIATES
AND SUBCONTRACTORS' SLUSH FUNDS
A. DOSIN ELECTRONICS 2020-2021
LIST OF OVERSEAS BORROWED ACCOUNTS
LIST OF BRIBERY FOR POLITICS AND BUSINESS
Taeyong did?
No, leave him be.
Yes, good job.
Did you lop the tree today?
Yes.
Useless branches need to be cut off
for a tree to bear more fruit.
That's right.
But you wasted your effort.
This tree itself is useless now.
Cut it down.
It's 5:10 a.m.
Why are you out here?
What did you do until this hour?
It's better you don't know.
You have too many secrets.
Sometimes, I find it hard
to understand you.
You're overly attentive
to Lee Seungcheon's family too.
What on earth are your secrets?
I'm sorry, Munki.
Even if I tell you, you won't understand.
But let me tell you one thing.
I'm going to attack my father.
Pretend you didn't hear it for your sake.
That's upsetting.
Did you really think of me as a brother?
Maybe it's because I don't have parents,
but I don't really understand
why you want to attack your father.
But Taeyong.
Your choices weren't always right,
but I still think you're a good man.
Whatever your secrets are,
I'll help you.
I'm always on your side.
Munki.
Thanks.
Come and buy a golden spoon!
It's 30,000 won only for today!
Hold on a second.
Today marks ten years.
Just why isn't that Seungcheon coming?
Mm?
Wait here.
Just come in.
Why did you want
to see me here of all places?
Wait, there.
That's where
my friend died.
His name was Gwon Yohan.
He was a very close friend of mine.
I heard you looked into him and me lately.
You could have asked me directly.
Then I would have told you everything.
Even that you are Gwon Yohan,
not Hwang Hyeondo?
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Gwon Yohan.
At last,
we meet like this,
Lee Seungcheon.
Since when have you known
that I was Lee Seungcheon?
When you first came to my house.
Hey. You forgot to take your thing.
I hope you will never
bring something like this here.
I knew instinctively
when I saw that golden spoon in your hand.
That's right.
I was so poor
that I wanted to become rich.
But why did you use it?
You were already rich.
You had a lot of money.
You were well-off, so why?
I had a lot of money?
Have you ever read the Bible?
Even if you replaced the word
"God" with "money,"
it wouldn't make any difference
in this world.
Good and evil.
Life and death. Eternity and resurrection.
Even God's path.
Everything is managed by money.
A faith called "money."
I chose that path.
Then did you kill President Na
because he got in your way?
That's right.
He cost too much money.
And he wasn't going to change.
So I killed him, I guess.
Even so, how could you commit murder?
I didn't commit murder.
I just got rid of the uncertainty
which was hindering my plan.
What about Taeyong?
Were you going to kill him
because he got in your way?
Well…
Anyway, as long as that boy
had the golden spoon,
I couldn't be at ease.
Of course, it failed because of you.
Gwon Yohan.
You're a monster.
You are no different.
Son.
You're just like me.
I haven't given up on you yet.
Live as my son.
And if I say no?
The golden spoon granny said
that whoever uses the golden spoon
is bound to pay the price.
That applies only to those
with fragile hearts.
No, you will pay the price too.
They're here.
They're from the prosecution.
Dosin's secrets you told me.
I didn't think I'd use them this way.
Those secrets were to be kept between us.
Don't feel too wronged.
I'll go with you.
We stole other people's lives.
I need to pay the price too.
Let's go together,
Father.
What did I
do so wrong to deserve this?
Have you forgotten?
Paper companies,
embezzlement, tax evasion…
There are tons.
Every secret you shared with me.
I handed it all to the prosecution.
But did you think
I was clueless about it?
You alone will pay for all those sins,
including the murder of President Na.
You killed him.
No, you killed him.
Taeyong's jacket with President Na's
bloodstain on it…
I mean, your jacket.
I handed it to the prosecution.
Mr. Hwang Taeyong.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Na Sangguk.
You have the right to remain silent
and to consult an attorney.
Anything you say may be used
against you in a court of law.
You should pay the price for your sins.
I won't go easy on you
just because you're my son.
You can take him.
Damn it!
Get him!
JUNE 20, 2012
PRESIDENT NA SANGGUK
A NEW MESSAGE HAS ARRIVED
What do you think?
It's footage from 24 years ago,
but the quality is not bad.
I'm guessing you have something to say.
Meet me at 12 tomorrow.
I'll tell you where later.
BIBLE
We agreed to meet tomorrow.
President Hwang,
you must have been pretty shaken.
Was it Taeyong just now?
He stormed out half-dazed.
Did you talk about something interesting?
Nothing much.
Let's talk outside.
I helped you grow
your pathetic little cable TV.
But I guess it wasn't nearly enough.
Let me ask you.
What more do you want from me
that you sent such a thing?
I need to survive, you see.
Promise that you'll save my company.
Then I will give you
the original copy of the footage.
These are certificates of deposit.
This much
should be enough to save your company.
Thank you.
Give it to me first.
Yes, right.
Here.
I want the original.
This is all I have. This is the original.
Can I trust you?
Believe me, President Hwang.
This really is all I have.
All right, I'll believe you.
Thank you, President Hwang.
I will never forget your kindness.
I didn't want to go this far either.
But I've always wondered.
Why did you kill Gwon Yohan?
Because like you,
he got in my way.
So I killed him.
It wasn't Gwon Yohan that I killed.
It was Hwang Hyeondo.
President Na. It's me, Taeyong.
President Na.
President Na!
It's me, Taeyong.
Why aren't you answering?
President Na.
President Na?
Attorney Go, what should we do?
Taeyong seems to have caused trouble.
THE GOLDEN SPOON
SPECIAL THANKS TO NA INWOO
FOR HIS GUEST APPEARANCE