How do you feel right now?
Why did you kill him?
Why did you turn yourself in?
Any words for the bereaved family?
Seo Juntae claims
he turned himself in
due to feelings of guilt
and pressure from the request
to reinvestigate the case.
An emergency airing of Seo Juntae.
Nice.
You know our channel received
the highest ratings, right?
I can't believe DSTV actually aired that.
Dosin had already cut ties with him.
Plus, defending a murderer
would only taint their reputation.
It would have been even better
if Ms. Na had been interviewed.
Would it have hurt to say
that she had avenged her father
in front of the camera?
She doesn't know television.
And you don't know people at all.
Jeez.
Dad.
You've waited a long time.
I'm sorry.
It's all over now.
So now,
you can rest in peace.
He must be doing well there, right?
Taeyong.
I dreamed of my dad last night
for the first time in a long time.
Every time he appeared,
I bawled even in my dreams.
Maybe he didn't want to see that.
I saw him again for the first time
in a long time.
And I didn't cry.
I smiled at him.
Thanks.
I'm sorry about everything.
I'm truly sorry that I suspected you.
What matters is that
you know the truth now.
Does this mean
we can go back to how things were?
Of course.
We meet again, my childhood friend.
It really has been
a long time, Na Juhee.
I told President Hwang everything.
I thought you would need his help.
I knew it.
No wonder Seo Juntae turned himself in.
You're right.
It was too much for me to handle.
But why do you treat me so well?
I told you.
Your late mother
was the closest thing I had to a family.
In that case,
I guess I'm your one and only family now.
But what kind
of an older brother uses honorifics?
Just talk casually to me.
Should I, Taeyong?
-It's easier to speak formally.
-Right.
By the way, why do you look so gloomy?
Everything panned out.
It's just that things resolved so easily.
And…
You know the golden spoon granny,
don't you?
Have a drink.
Judging by the fact that you can see me,
you must be pretty desperate.
This…
GOLDEN SPOON THAT MAKES YOU RICH
30,000 WON
Granny, Hwang Taeyong
bought one of these, right?
That's how he became Hwang Taeyong
when he's actually Lee Seungcheon.
Hwang Taeyong? Lee Seungcheon?
Who are those people?
Jeez, I don't know who they are.
Will you buy that or not?
Can this really swap my parents?
Leave if you don't believe me.
The choice is up to you, anyway.
I only offer you the opportunity.
What do you say?
Would you like to seize this opportunity?
It was just as the notebook said.
The old woman
really exists.
That means…
I'm Hwang Taeyong.
SUCCESS AFTER SUCCESS
We'll order a few more dishes from now on.
Thank you.
Let me.
Right.
Do you have any leftovers?
I haven't had breakfast yet.
Uh…
Mr. Hwang, why do you want
to pursue a spin-off?
Are you intimidated
by the FSC's guidelines?
I think he just wants people to love him.
Don't be too concerned
about the small stockholders.
Protecting the small stockholders' rights.
Sure. That's meaningful.
Governance is crucial in this day and age,
so it's important to abide by ESG
and reconsider the shareholder value.
But what's even more important is
money.
All the more reason why
physical division is necessary, right?
Where will you get the R&D fund?
Bequest? Corporate bond?
Doing so could put our company at risk.
What if we could turn that risk
into an opportunity?
Physical division is wise
when it comes to risk hedging.
But on the downside,
we'd have to share our rights.
If we're confident in our new technology,
then we wouldn't need to share our rights.
Because we'd get more money that way.
In addition,
seven percent of Dosin Hightech's shares
are owned by Golden Money Investment.
And its CEO, Alex Boo
also owns shares of our rival,
TQ Electronics.
Since the physical division
would require him
to invest more in our company,
that would be too much for him?
Correct.
Considering everything,
we should be listed after the spin-off.
That is my take on this.
Enough with your gimmick.
Tell me
your real plan.
I want to dilute Uncle Juntae's shares.
It's true that there's nothing
he can do right now,
but he still has Mother.
While the new business
is up for public purchase,
I want to personally buy
the holding company's shares.
Simply put, you want me to spend my money
on your succession?
It'll benefit you eventually.
After all, I'm your son.
I'll think about it. You may go.
You're the reason
Seo Juntae turned himself in, right?
Thank you.
You should have told me everything
from the beginning.
I was afraid
that you wouldn't believe me.
That's just ridiculous.
I knew…
that you didn't murder anyone.
My son, Hwang Hyeondo's son
would never do such a thing.
He knew that Taeyong didn't kill anyone?
He must have meant that
he wanted to believe it, right?
DOCUMENTARY NOTE:
MOST LAB'S YOUNG CEO, HWANG TAEYONG
YOU CANNOT BELITTLE MY HARD-EARNED…
Does this mean
we can go back to how things were?
As in friends?
Juhee.
Mmm.
My work had piled up,
so I was going to skip lunch.
You're the best.
Why aren't you eating?
I already ate at a friend's house.
I see. Mm.
I was actually about to call you.
What for? To thank me?
Since everything panned out thanks to me?
How did you know?
Your perseverance for the past decade
is what helped you come this far.
I'm proud of you.
I'm pretty awesome, right?
Right. When's Taeyong's interview airing?
Ah. Let's see.
SEUNGCHEON'S BIRTHDAY
HWANG TAEYONG'S SPECIAL AIRING
It's on you and Taeyong's birthday.
Is that so?
Seungcheon, what do you want
as your birthday gift?
My birthday gift?
Can you forget everything?
Everything that I said to you.
As in, when I confessed to you.
I think I was burdening you.
So I've made up my mind.
Let's remain good friends.
Forget about Lee Seungcheon.
Eat up.
Juhee.
I'm going to return to my old self.
I'll become Hwang Taeyong once again
and confess my love to you.
Cheers!
Gosh, that's good.
Nothing tops makgeolli
when it comes to alcohol.
Why are you drinking so much
when everything worked out fine?
Is it because of Seungcheon?
A part of me is relieved
that he wants to remain friends.
But I also hate myself
for not being able to accept his feelings.
In the past, I liked him more.
You can't force yourself to fall in love.
You're just each other's first love.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Right, I visited that diner again today.
And apparently, the suitcase lady
hadn't been coming.
I think she's avoiding you.
You said you had 500 million won in there?
I wonder where she spent all that money.
Mmm.
You know what?
I think I'm really materialistic.
That money wasn't proper.
I try to tell myself
that it wasn't mine to begin with.
But it still pops into my head at times.
"Would things have turned out differently
if I had that money?"
It would have been.
Having that much money back then
would have gotten you
an apartment in Seoul, a car, and…
But what's the use now? Let's drink up.
Ma'am, one more bottle of makgeolli!
Huh?
What is it?
What?
Ah. Never mind. I thought I saw someone.
Never in my wildest dreams
did I think Juntae would do such a thing.
Aren't you shocked as well?
What are you doing?
Can't you see?
Guys pamper themselves too now.
Can I take one?
-Do as you wish.
-I like it.
Janggun.
Which one's better?
Doesn't this look better?
Pick either one. They all look the same.
Then this one.
Right. What should I prepare
as a thank you gift for the wedding?
Why are you asking me?
Discuss it with your groom.
It's his wedding too.
Taeyong is busy, so I should understand.
Yeojin, what happened to you?
Yeojin, you should be the one
reigning like a queen.
You should have the upper hand.
So what's all this?
Why do you let him walk all over you?
Park Janggun, that's enough.
No. Not even.
I was the one who accompanied your father
to pick your wedding date.
You know how shocked he was
after visiting the shaman, right?
What?
You have no idea, do you?
He was extremely shocked to hear that
you had died more than a decade ago.
Why do I have to comfort him
when I'm not even your fiancé?
Hold on.
What are you talking about?
Ten million won for one of these?
No. This will help my Yeojin
live a long life.
Money isn't the problem here.
This is the guy
that used to live at my place.
Why does she have these?
What are you doing?
Sweetie, you're home.
You see…
I bought a talisman for you.
Keep this with you,
and it'll grant you longevity.
Janggun told me.
You must've been shocked
to hear that I was dead.
It reminded me of that time
when you were very sick as a child.
Don't worry. I'm healthy now.
I'll live happily married to Taeyong
and have beautiful kids.
So you should live a long, healthy life.
I mean that.
Okay. I will, Yeojin.
Lee Seungcheon?
I was worried you had left already.
I'm glad you're still here.
What brings you here at this hour?
Well…
I thought long and hard about it,
and I think I owe you an apology.
I was talking nonsense last time
about a golden spoon.
I'm sorry about that.
As Oh Yeojin said, I must have said that
because I envied you.
Right. And come to think of it,
that was a storyline
that I had come up with in high school.
I wanted to become
a webtoon artist like my dad.
Sure.
That'd be a good story for a webtoon.
Right? So I'm going to do it.
Show it to me once you're done.
I can't wait.
I'd be grateful if you read it.
I'll be leaving now.
Lee Seungcheon.
You are
And I'm Hwang Taeyong.
Based on my webtoon's plot.
I'll show it to you once I'm done.
You bastard. How dare you steal my life?
-What time is it?
-It's 9 p.m., sir.
Hwang Hyeondo.
And he's my father?
Maybe that's why
I feel at peace whenever I come here.
Juhee.
Will I feel at peace here as well?
Why is there a ghost in a church?
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
I'll come by more often.
-Ah.
-Na Juhee?
Hwang Taeyong.
Hey, Juhee.
What are you doing here?
Juhee, get up.
We meet again.
Hey, how much did you drink?
Just a tiny bit of makgeolli.
You reek.
Hey.
-A kitty.
-What?
Kitty!
You're such a good kitty
for staying still.
Do you want a snack?
I don't give this to just anyone.
It's pomegranate flavor.
Here.
A bite for me.
And a bite for you.
Mm.
Here.
Hmm.
Open up. No?
It must be full.
Come on. I'm Hwang Taeyong.
Open up.
Mmm.
It's good. Let's go home now.
Aah!
Let me go.
No.
Right. I need to go home.
-Home.
-Let's go.
That one too.
-This?
-Yes, that.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Bye, kitty.
-Yes. Bye, kitty.
-Bye.
Feeling better now?
Yes.
-Do you want more water?
-Yes.
Why did you drink so much?
I missed my dad,
money,
and Seungcheon.
You have no idea
how big of a crush I had on him.
The day I first met him
at the convenience store,
my heart practically skipped a beat.
When will he turn around?
When will he talk to me?
When will he smile at me?
You should date him again
if you like him that much.
It seems like he likes you too.
Mm-mm.
The Seungcheon right now
isn't the one I fell in love with.
Lee Seungcheon has changed.
Of course, he's still such a great guy.
But he's not the same guy
I used to have a crush on.
Actually,
I was probably the one who changed.
BOOK OF SOLUTIONS
Hey.
What are those dogs for?
They're gifts for the police commissioner
regarding Seo Juntae's case.
How could they be considered gifts?
He enjoys hunting.
President Hwang
never sends people the same gift.
Pottery, jewelry,
or women.
He always sends gifts that befit them.
Gifts that fulfill their desires?
But how does he know?
That's enough. We're just errand boys.
Our duty is to deliver.
Don't try to understand.
Let's go.
Their desires
are only a disguise for what they lack.
Just like how people's appearances differ,
there are various ways
they show what they lack.
-They're handsome.
-Do you like them?
-Hunting dogs.
-I do.
Pottery.
Jewelry.
But in the end, only money
can satisfy what they lack.
This isn't what you truly want.
You want to pursue your long-lost dream
that you gave up because of money.
It's because of this pencil.
It's too low quality.
Honey, come eat.
Okay. I'm coming.
Seungcheon, you're having lunch
at home, right?
I'll make some kimchi stew.
That's okay.
I'm eating at a friend's house.
Really? Who?
It's not like you know them all.
Stop asking.
I was just curious.
Have some meat too.
-Aren't these from Taeyong's?
-Yes.
Mmm.
It's delicious.
Seungcheon, did you know?
Our sales doubled thanks to Taeyong.
-Seriously?
-Yes.
You should treat him well.
We should have befriended him sooner.
Have some.
Wrap some rice with it.
Why do you keep giving me that?
I can eat it myself.
I'm not a kid.
Darn it. I'm done eating.
What a rude prick!
Mom, just let him starve.
A scumbag like him deserves to.
How dare he?
Ignore him and just eat.
-Eat up.
-Okay.
Don't serve any meals?
No, not even a glass of water.
And no one is allowed
to enter this house without my permission.
Be it guests or friends.
Especially Lee Seungcheon.
He should never set foot in here.
Understood?
Yes, young master.
The last time I fed him
shouldn't be a problem, right?
You killed President Na? That's absurd.
You didn't.
It's true. I killed him.
Juntae, what's wrong with you?
Do you think I'd fall for your lie?
Don't you remember
Taeyong's jacket that I got?
Taeyong killed him,
so why are you saying that you did it?
I know you. You would never commit murder.
You always see the good in me.
But that always frustrated me.
Quite a lot.
-Juntae.
-I killed him.
So drop it already.
No way.
He couldn't have.
Ma'am, I have something to tell you.
I thought I had lost it. Thanks.
You shouldn't drink that much.
You always smile
when you're having a hard time.
I do? When?
And I'm not having a hard time.
Forget it.
Why were you at the church yesterday?
-What?
-You don't live nearby.
You're not a believer either.
I came to take you home.
You called me drunk.
I did?
Darn it. I must've been crazy.
I should stop drinking.
Do you not remember?
Then do you remember
talking about Lee Seungcheon?
Even at our age, you're still so naive.
You still seem to be lost
in your first love fantasy.
Let me just say this.
The Lee Seungcheon
you used to like back in the day,
is a real bastard.
A jerk who only cares about money.
That's Lee Seungcheon.
Thanks for the coffee.
But I'll be going now.
Or else, I might get upset.
Hwang Taeyong, you jerk.
You're the one
who only cares about money, not him.
I know you're only appearing on TV
for the Dosin Hightech spin-off.
I know you want more shares
for your succession.
I can totally see through you,
so who are you calling a bastard?
Get your facts straight.
He's just ridiculous.
I shouldn't see him for the time being.
Going up. Door closing.
Door opening.
What? What do you want?
Take good care of your stuff
if you don't want to see jerks like me.
-And Juhee.
-What is it this time?
Don't force a smile
when you're having a hard time.
You'll only exhaust yourself.
Door closing.
Seungcheon
used to say that.
-Hello?
-Hi, Taeyong.
I didn't get to say hi to you earlier.
Will you be coming home late?
What about dinner?
I'll eat outside.
Okay.
Goodbye.
What's with her?
I heard you ate at our place
last time as well.
Did you know?
Taeyong told them to never feed you.
Isn't that strange?
Why would he say such a thing?
I thought you were friends.
You can ask him yourself.
Ah.
Judging by your rudeness,
I guess you two are friends.
Eat up.
What? Did you bring that spoon again?
You also brought that years ago.
How's your father?
Goodness. Why are you home so early?
I forgot something.
Hello, sir. I just stopped by.
I see. Take your time and enjoy the food.
Taeyong told us never to feed him.
And that boy is determined to eat here.
Aren't they just hilarious?
So immature.
I detest that kid.
Lee Seungcheon, his family's side dishes,
and his family, they all disgust me. Why?
Because I can see through you.
You chose him over Juntae.
Do you think that worthless kid
could hold a candle to my Juntae?
I can see that
you have a lot on your mind.
However,
I do believe
I've already explained what you need to do
as Juntae's mother.
Goodness. I made a mistake.
After all, Juntae's fate is in your hands.
So of course, I should listen to you.
-The number you have dialed…
-I was told that
Lee Seungcheon ate at our house twice.
Why does he keep coming by
when you're away?
LEE SEUNGCHEON
HWANG TAEYONG
I knew it.
The interview plays the most crucial role
in their recruitment.
Right.
There are times
when you're arrogant for no reason.
You should drop that.
You should always be humble.
Dongkyung, I'm sorry to say this,
but I won't go to interviews anymore.
I see. Then what will you do?
Will you become an online streamer
or something?
I'm going to become rich.
Wealthier than you could ever imagine.
Don't bother job hunting.
I'll land you a position.
-A position?
-Yes.
My goodness.
What a bunch of nonsense.
Have you gone insane from being jobless?
Is that funny to you?
Jeez.
HWANG TAEYONG
The number you have dialed--
Hwang Taeyong.
So this is how you'll play?
SEUNGCHEON'S MOM
Uh…
Hello, ma'am. This is Taeyong.
Taeyong.
I'm sorry for coming all of a sudden.
Seungcheon wasn't picking up.
I see. It must be something important.
Come in.
He just left to see Dongkyung off.
He'll be back soon. Come in.
Okay.
Goodness.
It's a mess, right?
Do understand.
It's okay.
I was preparing dinner.
-Have a seat, Taeyong.
-Okay.
Taeyong, come and eat.
You didn't have to.
Mmm. It smells so good.
Sit down.
Dumpling soup.
Wow.
Thank you for the meal.
It's hot.
Mmm. Mom, your dumpling soup is the best.
How can it be this good?
What is it? Do you not like dumpling soup?
That's not why.
I…
I really like it.
Thank goodness.
Dumpling soup was Seungcheon's
favorite food growing up.
Then it suddenly changed to kimchi stew.
I made some
because he seemed to be troubled recently.
I'm glad you like it.
-Go on and eat.
-Okay.
Thank you for the meal.
-My pleasure.
-Mom, do we have a guest?
Yes, Seungcheon. It's Taeyong.
I came because you weren't picking up.
Mom, there's a new fritter joint nearby.
I know you like fritters.
Goodness. You're the best.
Don't give any to Dad or Sungah.
Have them all.
Thank you, my son. I'll enjoy them.
Gosh.
Taeyong. Are you leaving?
There's something I forgot to do.
I'm sorry I can't eat this.
Oh, dear.
Right. I heard you came by
our house to eat.
You should've told me.
Then I would've prepared
a nice meal for you.
I guess that didn't occur to me.
I'm free tomorrow. Do you want to come
and have lunch together?
Sure.
I should get going then.
All right.
What should I do with this?
That's strange.
There's no record
of me calling him that night.
MS. WANG SOOMIN
Yes, Soomin.
Are you serious?
My goodness.
Over here!
Gosh. Let go already.
Jeez. Here.
Is it there?
No?
Where did you get this suitcase?
Where's the money? Did you spend it all?
Of course, I did.
There was only 500 million won.
I'm Geum Sukja,
the district councilor of Gangnam!
I don't deserve to be humiliated
just for 500 million won.
Enough with your lies.
You'll be arrested
if the real Ms. Geum hears about this.
How many times must I repeat myself?
I'm the real Geum Sukja!
The one who's pretending to be me
was my former housekeeper!
Darn it. If only I had the golden spoon.
Golden spoon?
What do you mean by that?
You mean, a golden spoon that can
make you rich, or something like that?
Do you know about it?
Did you meet the golden spoon granny?
You're here.
Did you bring your golden spoon?
Of course.
Then let me see it. I'm curious.
You must desperately want to become rich.
If what you said is true,
by using that golden spoon,
you'll be abandoning your parents.
Will you be okay?
You're the one who abandoned your parents.
I'm only going back to my rightful place.
I see.
Is that right?
Then go on and eat.
But if you don't become Hwang Taeyong
by the end of this meal,
you'd better brace yourself.
Lee Seungcheon.
You're trying so hard.
I know it's killing you deep down
to think I might actually use this.
Not at all.
I'm just worried about your parents.
They trust you
and are proud of the man you've become.
-Don't you pity them?
-Shut up.
You have no right to talk about them.
Eat up.
Let's see if what you said is true.
Go on.
What was that? Why aren't you eating?
Why are you just leaving?
Let go, you bastard!
Go back in there and eat!
Why won't you eat?
Eat and become Hwang Taeyong!
Go eat.
No, I don't want to!
That's why you're here!
Then eat.
You can't just leave!
Why you…
Lee Seungcheon!
Don't be mistaken.
Do you know why I refuse to eat?
Because I don't want to lose
the best parents…
in the world.
Are you happy
that you abandoned them to become rich?
In that case,
you can be Hwang Taeyong.
And I'll live as Lee Seungcheon.
Mom.
Yes, it's me.
Seungcheon.
Thank you so much for being alive.
Seungcheon, you're okay.
Look at me.
Follow me.
Inhale.
Exhale.
-♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
-♪ Happy birthday, dear my son ♪
-♪ Happy birthday, dear Seungcheon ♪
-Happy birthday to you
-Salute!
I'd like to declare that
Sergeant Lee Seungcheon,
has been discharged
from the army on July 6, 2016.
This is my declaration. Salute!
Salute.
-Mom!
-My son!
-You worked so hard.
-I'm finally discharged!
MOM
Hi, Mom.
Seungcheon, what's with your voice?
Did you catch a cold?
No, I'm okay.
What is it?
Well, I just called to ask
if you were craving anything for dinner.
Mom, I'd like…
some kimchi stew.
I want some kimchi stew
with a lot of pork.
That's all I need, Mom.
Taeyong, what's wrong?
Taeyong.
Yeojin.
I lost.
I'm no match…
for Hwang Taeyong.
Did something happen?
Don't tell me he met the old woman too.
He had a golden spoon.
But Yeojin.
Do you know what I did to him today?
I stole his golden spoon…
and swapped it with a fake one.
I didn't want him to become Hwang Taeyong.
I…
I didn't want to return
to being Lee Seungcheon again.
But that punk…
chose
my parents instead.
I thought he'd use the golden spoon too.
I thought he'd choose money
over his parents.
I'm a piece of trash.
Let's say that you are. So what?
It wasn't our fault
that our families were poor.
We had no money,
so we wanted to become rich.
We only seized an opportunity.
Anyone would have done the same
had they met that old woman.
But…
But Hwang Taeyong chose not to.
Don't be in pain.
You're killing me.
I wasn't lonely
because I had you,
someone who was just like me.
I don't care if the world criticizes me.
You're all that I need.
So can't you do the same?
We have nowhere to return to.
No.
Yeojin.
This isn't right. I'm sorry.
Seungcheon.
The golden spoon lets you swap parents.
Haven't you heard the story
about a golden spoon
that can swap your parents?
It's the same golden spoon story
as Seungcheon's.
I picked it up.
In the classroom back in high school.
You still have what I got you.
Don't force a smile
when you're having a hard time.
You'll only exhaust yourself.
Door closing.
Could Taeyong be Seungcheon?
That's absurd.
Hwang Taeyong.
-Taeyong.
-I came because I missed you.
I missed you so much, Juhee.
Are you…
Seungcheon?
You are, aren't you?
No.
I'm Hwang Taeyong.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: JEONG EUINAM
"Jeong Euinam. Eight priors…"
Eight?
Theft, theft, theft.
Assault. Housebreaking.
"Incarcerated in Seoul Dongbu Penitentiary
for assault."
He's one heinous bastard.
So why has Yeojin been sending him money?
Mm?
Look at this lousy scumbag.
You look good in beige.
I can't believe I'm visiting you here.
This is one strong friendship.
Don't you think?
I'll make sure
to repay you for that.
So how can you possibly
help us make money behind bars?
Dosin Hightech.
They'll sell short.
I knew it. He's just full of lies.
Their stock price is soaring
due to the spin-off.
-That's impossible.
-It'll be a physical division.
-What?
-Really?
Taeyong doesn't know his father too well.
But I do.
Hwang Hyeondo…
will choose physical division instead.
Put the young master's birthday gifts
on the table.
The stocks keep dropping
with news of the physical division.
Did you check the loan balance?
The majority are short selling.
What should we do?
-Where's Father?
-He's in his study--
Get the car ready.
I'll go right after meeting Father.
Yes, sir.
Lee Seungcheon.
Why are you here?
To deliver the side dishes.
Side dishes?
I'll be making the deliveries here
from now on.
I don't want my parents
to meet you.
If you meet your real parents
on your birthday,
you'll go back
to being your original selves.
Hey, you shouldn't be here.
Leave right now.
What's wrong with you?
I need to drop these off.
Just put them down and leave.
What's with you?
SUCCESS AFTER SUCCESS
SIDE DISH STORE
Taeyong.
Do we have a guest?
Father.
Lee Seungcheon?
It was you,
Lee Seungcheon.
We didn't switch. What's going on?
Once you guys are done talking,
come see me, Taeyong.
Okay.
What went wrong?
We should've been switched.
Don't tell me the old woman lied.
Seungcheon.
Jeez. Why did you--
Hello, President Hwang.
My wife made some dumplings
for Taeyong's birthday. You forgot them.
Here, Seungcheon.
Let me be Hwang Taeyong again.
You're Taeyong, aren't you?
I can't believe it.
Are you back to being Lee Seungcheon?
I remember that scene.
President Hwang
isn't Taeyong's biological father?
Your last chance,
there isn't much time left, right?
Do you think I'll just sit here
and take it?
But aren't you curious
about what your son, Lee Seungcheon did?
I'm asking you, Seungcheon.
Please don't become Hwang Taeyong.