[Qingchuan's Veil of Vengeance]
Your Ladyship!
Please come down.
Be careful of the child in your belly.
Your Ladyship.
-To the left. Be careful.
-Your Ladyship.
Be careful.
-Come down, Your Ladyship.
-Your Ladyship.
Please come down, Your Ladyship.
Your Ladyship, please be careful.
General Feng,
Her Ladyship...
Why?
Why not kill me
but choose to kill our child?
My flesh and blood,
I have the final say.
As for you,
don't be in such a rush
Your time
has not yet come.
Let me tell you a story.
Once upon a time,
there was a divine maiden
who fell into the River of the Dead,
devoured by thousands of demons.
Day after day,
year after year.
Even when her bones were laid bare,
she survived.
Do you know why she lived?
Because someone
was waiting for her to return?
No.
Because
someone was hoping
she would never return.
So,
you want to go back?
The pain I've endured,
those who pushed me into the river
will suffer the same.
What did Your Highness say?
Mo Qingchuan refuses the marriage?
This is bad.
She's at the height
of her reputation in Xia.
If she refuses,
even the Empress Dowager can't force her.
Let alone
offer an extra thirty percent in tribute.
What now?
If the peace talks fail,
the Second Prince might seize the chance
to strike back at Your Highness.
Then
everything the King promised Your Highness
will be for nothing.
As for Empress Dowager
Cao, I'll handle her.
As for Qingchuan,
she's just looking for excuses to refuse
because she still
clings to thoughts of Xia.
Fine.
Let her see clearly
to Xia, Mo Qingchuan
is nothing but a bargaining chip.
It's been three years.
It's time she let go
and returned with me to Chu.
How troublesome!
No matter how high
she climbs in Xia,
To
Chu,
she's just
a plaything of Your Highness...
Show any more disrespect toward her,
and I'll take your life.
Get lost!
Yes.
I was wrong.
General Qingchuan has returned.
With her commanding the Mo Army,
why negotiate at all?
Exactly.
What good intentions
can Chu possibly have?
Is Xia's food
made for livestock or what?
It's disgusting.
What did you
mongrels just say?
Move aside.
Behave yourselves.
You...
General Li.
Think of the bigger picture.
Now that General Mo is back,
you think we fear the people of Chu?
Exactly.
You think Mo Qingchuan
is so great?
She's already His Highness's woman.
Even carrying his child.
Shut your mouth!
What a joke!
Let's go.
I heard General Mo
was defiled by Feng Shiye.
Impossible.
General Mo should
rather have died than surrendered.
What are you talking about
Mo Qingchuan
defiled by the Prince of Chu,
Feng Shiye.
Who started this rumor?
His deputy, Li Feng
said it himself at Wangyue House.
Lots of people heard it.
[Jinghua Post Station]
Feng Shiye!
What's the matter?
What did you do to my master?
She endured cruel torture in Chu.
Her inner power is ruined.
Did you
force her?
If yes,
so what?
What do you want?
Kill me?
I am an envoy of a sovereign nation.
Yes.
And I will kill you now.
Stop!
Master.
Go.
I...
You really think you can defeat him?
Some things in this world
are worth doing even if doomed to fail.
In that way can I...
Is it worth it
for me?
It is.
Go
I must kill him today.
Master.
You're protecting him?
Yes.
He can't die yet.
Why not?
You don't need to know.
Master.
Won't you even
listen to your master now?
Go.
You taught Xia Qiguang
the Mo family's sword technique?
Does he deserve it?
Do you?
Don't touch him.
You already killed his father.
Isn't that enough?
The one who sent
a secret letter to Mo Junyu
that made him kill Prince Jing by mistake
was you,
wasn't it?
Prince Jing's assassination
was because Mo Junyu was manipulated.
The only one
who could use Mo Qinglian against him
is you.
You're impressive.
You're the one who's impressive.
Qingchuan.
You know what I am.
A scoundrel.
A villain.
Trash.
In this world, aside from you,
everyone else is beneath my notice.
Try me if you dare.
I want this one.
Thank you, Sir.
Okay.
[Teahouse]
Why are you following me?
She wants my candied hawthorn?
It's sweet?
You've never had it?
Back in Chu,
they fed children with strange potions
to turn them
into assassins.
No wonder
taking all those bizarre drugs
since childhood
must've been painful.
It's okay.
From now on,
I will make sure you have
all the candied hawthorn you want.
This one's for you…
[Jinghua Post Station]
Tell me her movements these past few days.
Bought food.
Argued with a vendor.
Let the wind blow on her face.
-Hopped across rooftops.
-Enough.
You're following the wrong person.
Your Highness.
This drugged warrior,
though skilled in martial arts,
is not very bright.
Let me go instead.
I will surely
redeem myself.
You?
Mo Qingchuan has exceptional hearing.
Only she can barely manage this task.
Why else
do you think I sent her?
What're you holding?
What is that?
Mu Yun.
They are the enemy.
You cannot get close to them.
Then why must they be the enemy?
We were born into opposing camps,
destined to meet in conflict.
And who decided this opposition?
Was it you, Your Highness?
Without summons,
you must not act on your own.
Yes.
The birthday banquet is near.
If peace talks between
Chu and Xia succeed,
it will be a double celebration.
Your Majesty.
Regarding the marriage alliance,
what does General Qingchuan think?
I was just about to discuss it with her.
Keep a close eye
on the banquet matters
I've never fully trusted
Grand Commandant Cao's handling
I understand.
I take my leave.
Your Majesty.
General Mo has arrived.
Summon her.
General Qingchuan.
Now that rumors are flying everywhere.
I'm afraid
even if you refuse,
you will still be made to marry.
Then tell me, Your Majesty.
do you believe I should marry?
As a woman,
I don't wish to make things hard for you.
But as the Empress Dowager,
if a marriage contract
could bring about peace...
But Your Majesty,
is that kind
of peace real
or merely a dream?
Why draw such lines?
Even though
you've survived countless battles,
you still don't
understand this battlefield.
Your enemies
are foreign tribes.
But mine
are far more terrifying.
They wear the masks
of loyal ministers and upright officials
and wield the sword of law and ritual
against me, a mere woman.
So
I gave them a choice.
To die in noise
or live in silence.
And now
I can stand beside them
without difference.
The water that's too clear has no fish.
That's what it means.
I understand your words,
Empress Dowager.
But I
Only wish to live with clarity.
I, Mo Qingchuan,
would rather die under a horse's hooves
than become my enemy's plaything.
I know you care for the people.
But this marriage alliance
is also a way to save the country.
Take me, for example.
Though reviled by thousands,
if I weren't holding court here,
Xia might already be in chaos.
How can the people
be at peace?
In truth,
you and I
are very much alike.
I
am not worthy
to be compared to Your Majesty.
I cannot change your decision.
But this life
is still mine to decide.
General Mo.
Even if you had power
that reached the heavens,
you are still a woman.
And women
cannot escape marriage.
If you had a marriage contract,
I might be able
to help refuse on your behalf.
What a pity!
But don't forget, Empress Dowager.
To the people,
I am a general first,
and a woman second.
You said you had a way
to stop Feng Shiye from marrying me?
Yes.
What way?
I'll go to the Empress Dowager
and...
And offer her
Prince Jing's title.
She might agree...
Agree to...
Prince Jing's title?
You're willing to give up so much?
In exchange for what?
For...
Say it.
For what?
For marrying...
Looks like we won't
be having perch today
That Mo Qingchuan.
What kind of heroine is she?
No integrity at all.
Exactly.
She and Feng Shiye
already had a child together.
Just a disgraced woman.
Where are you going?
Master.
They're spouting nonsense.
But they're not wrong.
They are.
What's wrong then?
Wasn't it me who endured humiliation
in the enemy's camp?
Wasn't it me who got pregnant
with Feng Shiye's child?
Just a body.
Why all the fuss?
What chastity and purity?
What flawless virtue?
On the battlefield,
I've seen all kinds of mangled limbs.
I don't find them ugly.
I have all my limbs.
Why should I feel shame?
That set of hollow virtues,
you all treat as sacred law.
But don't try to bind me with them.
The world may not know you, Master.
But I do.
If you were truly different from others,
you wouldn't have thought of marrying me.
Rumors can shatter gold.
And slander can grind bones.
I just don't want you
to be hurt by gossip.
I, Mo Qingchuan,
did it, then I did it.
Why fear judgment?
Why care about whispers?
Do I need you to beg the Empress Dowager?
Does it work?
Do you think when your father
begged the assassin to spare his life,
it helped?
You're angry?
Good.
Don't ever let me hear
the word "beg" from your mouth.
Remember.
Nothing in this world
is obtained by begging.
It's not just for others' opinions,
it's also because
as a soldier of Xia,
I cannot stand by
and watch a helpless woman be humiliated.
A helpless woman?
Who?
Me?
In my eyes, Master,
you're still a woman.
Still someone who needs protection.
Xia Qiguang.
What are you thinking?
I mean to say...
Whatever he can help you with,
I can do it too.
Yes.
He is despicable and shameless.
But to deal with villains,
one must unleash a mad dog.
My agreement with him
has nothing to do with you.
From now on,
you need not walk this path with me.
I won't let him
sway your resolve.
Resolve?
What resolve do I have left?
Master.
Trust me just this once.
What you've lost,
I'll help you reclaim.
If the road ahead is hard,
I'll be your vanguard.
[Qingxin Cottage]
Master went fishing alone,
refused to let me go along.
So dull.
Maybe I should
wander around the palace?
Who's there?
[Master]
If I want sweets in the future,
can I come to you?
That depends on my mood.
I'm not someone
who gives kids
candied hawthorn for free.
I'm
the kind of person
who makes others tremble in fear.
Already bought the candied hawthorn.
But she won't come.
Did I scare her off?
At worst
I'll give it to some other kid.
Forget it.
About the marriage alliance,
have Your Majesty come to a decision?
If General Mo is unwilling to marry,
who can force her?
Waiving thirty percent
of the tribute isn't enough?
Mo Qingchuan is no ordinary woman.
With General Mo present,
the Mo Army remains intact.
Then perhaps
these peace talks are unnecessary.
If negotiations fail,
do Your Majesty truly believe
a mere woman like Mo Qingchuan
can defend the border?
If we can't supply your requested tribute,
then I have no
choice but to believe in her.
However,
if your country could
reduce another twenty percent,
this matter
might still be negotiable.
Why does Your Majesty
favor chrysanthemums?
Your Majesty.
If you grow too greedy,
this may be the last
season your chrysanthemums
bloom in the palace.
What do you mean?
Your Majesty, bad news.
Your...
Your golden chrysanthemum...
Among them,
who is truly Feng Shiye's man?
There are only three days left
until Mo Qingchuan's
departure for marriage
and the signing of the treaty.
This time,
you must give it serious
thought.