[Qingchuan's Veil of Vengeance]
Mo Qingchuan!
Uncle,
how was it?
Good girl.
You're truly accomplished
at such a young age.
I lost in the martial arts demonstration,
and I couldn't even
beat you in the individual competition.
Mo Qingchuan,
you are truly the pride of our Mo family.
I willingly
admit defeat.
Uncle,
I'm flattered.
I should win at least once.
I will definitely win.
Sir.
The enemy has indeed
brought many reinforcements.
Many reinforcements?
Yes.
But they've all run into the lowlands.
They're being shot down by our archers.
Good.
Kill them all.
Leave no one alive.
Yes.
We're on the same side!
Stop fighting!
Let’s go.
Stop!
Did you hear them say they're on our side?
I think so.
I heard it too.
What's going on?
Never mind.
Keep shooting.
Attack!
Shoot!
Kill! Kill!
Why did it go quiet?
The enemy must
have sent more than ten men.
We've been tricked.
Kill!
Run!
Sir!
The enemy troops are advancing towards us.
What did you say?
The enemy troops
have already broken through.
More than half of our men
are dead or wounded.
Many of our men
have fled in fear.
How many of them are there?
I don't know.
We have no idea how many there are.
They're everywhere.
If we're caught,
it's certain death.
Sir,
we should flee quickly.
No one is allowed to run away.
Don't run!
Impossible.
This can't be happening.
Sir,
if you're found in the mountains,
you'll never be able to clear your name.
Saving our lives is the priority.
I'm leaving first.
Mo Qingchuan.
Grand Commandant, you're climbing
the mountain at this hour.
could it be that you're in high spirits,
out for a morning exercise?
I heard last night that Xia Qiguang
wiped out Yunwu Village
up in the mountains.
Surprisingly,
the village wasn't
filled with ordinary bandits,
but rather what seemed like two thousand
well-armed soldiers.
Grand Commandant, why
do you look so displeased?
Could it be that these soldiers
were your private army?
What does it have to do with me?
Don't you dare slander me.
Back then, you seized
the title of leader of the Mo Army.
Now, two thousand elite
soldiers have completely
fallen apart because of just 20 enemies.
You
truly are a worthless military leader.
20 men?
Yes, 20.
Mo Qingchuan,
you've gone too far!
Compared to when you single-handedly cost
tens of thousands of soldiers their lives,
this is nothing.
You...
Mo Junyu,
those departed souls
are now
crossing deserts and mountains,
returning to their homeland.
They stand around you.
Can you hear it?
Hear what?
Hear
the breath of the dead.
They are watching you right now.
This time,
they will witness your death.
A death
as helpless as ants crushed by
a collapsing sky.
Farewell.
You...
Let me go?
In this mountain village,
there's actually
a hidden underground prison.
Who's locked up in there?
Are you
Mo Qinglian?
That's the entire plan.
But if
he decides to move you,
take this medicine.
It will quickly
restore your inner power.
Also,
do you remember how to perform Dawn Break?
I do.
We're almost down the mountain.
Let's rest for a while.
Yes.
I am Mo Qinglian.
Mo Qinglian?
Wasn't he killed by the Chu forces?
Look!
Is that Mo Qinglian?
I think it looks a bit like him.
It really seems to be him.
Wasn't he supposed
to have died in Qingchuan Town?
And who is that woman?
I don't know.
He wasn't
delivered to Luoying Court.
He disappeared.
Disappeared?
Where could he have gone?
Was he taken by Mo Qingchuan?
Go find him.
Go find him quickly.
Go find him right now.
Master Chen!
Great news!
The young master is still alive!
Many people have seen him.
He was seen riding
a horse through the market,
heading towards
the Grand Commandant's Mansion.
[Grand Commandant’s Mansion]
Father.
Mother.
I'm back.
Mo Qinglian is back.
Qingchuan,
you're back too.
Uncle Zhou,
should I now call you Chief Scribe Zhou
or Minister Zhou?
Just call me Zhou Zheng.
I bought some
soybean sticky rice cake from Li's,
and some braised beef from Huang's.
Let's have some together.
Alright.
Zhou Zheng.
Thank you for these years,
for taking care of my mother.
It's my duty.
Back then,
the old general treated me
well.
But I've always been puzzled,
why did you help Mo Junyu
conceal the truth?
Was it for her?
Your feelings for her run so deep,
but perhaps she
never cared.
Do you know?
I know.
I also know
Mo Junyu is not a good match for her.
But even though Mo Junyu
committed such a serious crime,
she's still willing to share the burden.
All I can do
is to keep her safe for life.
Zhou Zheng,
you're different from others.
You care about the people,
and have good intentions.
Your official career
should have been smooth,
living peacefully.
But now you're suffering like this.
Is it worth it?
Perhaps
I'll be cursed by millions,
but my lifelong wish
is just for her happiness alone.
So,
you won't give me
the real Qingchuan battle report,
will you?
Thank you.
Thank you
for giving me the chance to confess.
It was I
who willingly fell from grace
and failed to cherish what I had.
Be as cautious
as you were at the beginning.
Keep your heart true and righteous.
Zhou Zheng,
this opportunity for redemption
wasn't given by me,
but by the vast populace behind you
who pleaded on your behalf.
Mo Junyu...
Mo Junyu is not just her husband.
he's also a sharp blade
in the Empress Dowager's hand.
The Empress Dowager
only cares if the blade can kill,
not whether it's clean or dirty.
As long as the Empress Dowager
wants to protect him,
you can't touch him.
After all,
Mo Qingchuan
will never be the Empress Dowager's blade.
Qingchuan,
be very careful.
Thank you for the warning, Mr. Zhou.
Let me also remind
you of something, Mr. Zhou.
You only seek to please one person,
but you are not her.
How do you know
she's pleased?
The bandit suppression operation
went roughly like that.
I really didn't expect
that this insignificant Yunwu Village
would have two thousand fierce bandits.
Moreover, the map provided by the
military affairs officer was incorrect.
If it weren't for the help of Mo Wang,
the owner of the Cicada Agency,
who said she
was familiar with the terrain,
this mission
would have been unpredictable.
Mo Wang?
Yes.
However,
Empress Dowager, your
birthday gift has been recovered,
and the rabble of Yunwu Village
has been completely dispersed.
Please review, Empress Dowager.
To help me recover my birthday gift,
Your journey
must have been arduous.
I will surely reward you
generously in the future.
Thank you, Empress Dowager.
However,
I have concerns.
Why did you go to suppress the bandits
with only ten men?
The birthday gift is one thing,
but if something had happened to you,
how would the world view me?
General Cao has arrived.
Empress Dowager, please calm your anger.
The matter of suppressing
bandits at Yunwu Village
has its reasons.
Please,
allow me to explain.
A few days ago,
Commandant Gao lost
a martial arts match to the Young Lord.
So he suggested to me that
since the Young Lord's
martial skills are superior,
ten men would be
sufficient to suppress the bandits.
At that time, I didn't anticipate
that there would be so many
bandits at Yunwu Village.
It almost endangered the Young Lord.
Thinking about it now,
it was Commandant Gao
who took personal revenge.
Yes.
However,
I did not seek revenge.
If it were revenge,
I wouldn't have followed the Young Lord
and put myself in danger.
Reckless!
I acknowledge my guilt.
Empress Dowager,
since he shared life and death with me,
on the battlefield,
life knows no
distinction between noble and humble.
We are all comrades.
Please forgive him, Empress Dowager.
Rise.
Thank you, Empress Dowager.
You, child,
possess both
filial piety and righteousness.
It's truly rare.
Empress Dowager,
I
have another strange matter
that I wish to report.
In the mountains,
we discovered someone
who closely resembles
the Grand Commandant's son,
Mo Qinglian.
Is that so?
Yes,
we saw it with our own eyes.
Where is he now?
I'm ashamed to say...
I originally intended to
take him alone
to the Grand Commandant's Mansion
for confirmation,
but Mo Wang
took advantage of my inattention
and knocked me unconscious.
Both of them
have disappeared without a trace.
[Eternal Bliss]
Master.
You're back.
I'm back.
Master.
Were you waiting for me?
Yes.
I'm waiting for you.
Qiguang.
Do you know what Mo Qinglian's
appearance means?
It means
Mo Junyu's hypocritical mask
will be unveiled.
What else?
It means
the truth about the Battle of Qingchuan
will soon be revealed to the world.
What else?
That's all.
[Eternal Bliss]
Master.
Take your medicine.
It means
I,
Mo Qingchuan,
should return to the public eye.
Didn't you already know this?
Yes,
I knew.
Why did you pretend not to know?
I...
It's alright.
No need to say more.
Master,
do you remember
when we first met,
you asked me a question?
What if, one day, you meet her,
and she tells you herself that
she betrayed us?
Xia Qiguang,
answer me.
What if she really
has betrayed us?
I've been waiting,
waiting for Mo Qingchuan
to truly return.
I'll answer again.
I want to tell you, Master,
and Mo Qingchuan,
if she has betrayed us,
it's not her fault at all.
I
will follow my heart
and never turn back.
The moonlight is beautiful tonight.
Why don't I teach you
the Dawn Break Form III?
Master.
Fang Du's medicine is somewhat effective.
Don't worry.
You're all dirty.
Go clean yourself up.
Alright.
Dawn Break Form III,
the most difficult form.
The blade moves like wind
sweeping clouds and thunder roaring,
lightning tearing through the sky.
Its force surges like raging seas,
with crashing waves striking the shore.
One strike,
and mountains and rivers resonate.
This is Dawn Break.
If you want to unleash
the true power of Dawn Break Form III,
you need to diligently
cultivate your inner power.
Yes,
Master.
Come,
try it with me.
[Grand Commandant’s Mansion]
Someone's dead.
Let's go, let's go.
[Grand Commandant’s Mansion]
What a bad luck.
So scary.
Let's go.
[Grand Commandant’s Mansion]