[The 21st Seoul International Culinary Competition]
[Do Ye Seok]
- Hello?
- Yeon Du is injured.
You need to come here.
What?
I was dragging you down.
That's why I wanted to break up.
This is the best for us.
Hey, Ji Hyeon Ho!
Where are you going again? Hey!
[Best Mistake 3]
Kim Yeon Du!
I'm sorry.
He said she was at the nurse's office.
Hyeon Ho.
Are you okay? Are you hurt badly?
Where and how much did you get hurt?
It's just a minor bruise.
No need to worry.
How did you get injured?
Did something happen?
That was...
[A few hours ago]
What's wrong with you?
Let go of me.
The one who locked up Yeon Du that day. It was you, wasn't it?
What?
Did you think you'd never get caught?
Why? What did she do to you?
Yes, I did it.
So what? It's all in the past.
How low are you going?
This isn't like you.
What do you know about me?
Do you know who I really am?
What do you want to say?
You don't know who I really am.
I was busy hiding myself while I went out with you.
You were from a good family with a smart brain.
All the professors and students liked you.
I became so small next to you who had it all.
But I was too busy pretending I was okay.
And yet...
You felt upset that I went to the internship instead of you?
You already knew everything.
I had to work two to three part-time jobs and I was desperate to get the scholarship.
And I still worried I wasn't good enough to get a decent job.
You already knew.
You knew how much I wanted that internship.
Jin Se Hui.
Kim Yeon Du is just the same.
She doesn't have to try hard and yet she gets everything.
Everyone takes care of her and protects her.
It's annoying.
That's why I did it, because she was so annoying.
Why not? Can't I do that?
It was yours.
What?
The internship, it was yours anyway.
Even if you hadn't taken my application away,
you would've gotten it.
It was yours to begin with.
Se Hui?
[SEATTLE CASTLA Final Application for Overseas Internship:
Hwayang Univ. Year 1, Do Ye Seok]
Yes.
I'm on my way from Professor Park's office.
Se Hui, she really set her mind into it.
Her portfolio was no joke.
CASTLA also pointed her out and wanted her to come.
Wow, is that true?
Huh?
You like it?
So much?
If Se Hui gets it, you don't, and you still like it?
Of course.
Se Hui has worked so hard for this.
You're so nice, aren't you?
Hey, it's a secret.
So act natural. Okay?
Yes.
Stop smiling.
So please just stop.
You're not like this.
Stop hating yourself.
The person you hate is not Yeon Du, but yourself.
As I said before, I forgot about it all.
So you do, too.
Just forget it and live your life.
I'm speaking from my heart.
Unni Se Hui. Unni Se Hui!
Are you alright?
Unni Se Hui.
Why are you here, Hyeon Ho? What about the competition?
Well, I pulled out of it.
Hey! What do you mean, "Pulled out?"
Have you still lost your mind?
What are you going to do if you act like this again?
Why are you here? Have you really lost your mind?
Listen carefully, Kim Yeon Du.
My choice is always you, then and now.
That's why I wanted to enter the culinary competition.
What?
I wanted to transfer here.
I wanted to get closer in distance.
And I also wanted to become a better person to suit you.
But in order to transfer, I needed an award.
That's why I entered into the culinary competition.
That's not what I wanted from you.
What?
Hyeon Ho, I choose who suits me.
No matter what school you go to or what grades or awards you have.
That's not important to me at all.
Because it's you, I like you because you're Ji Hyeon Ho.
Same here.
Because it's you, Kim Yeon Du.
Even if the same thing happens 100 or 1,000 times, you always come first.
Hyeon Ho...
So stop getting injured.
It scares me.
All right.
- How is Yeon Du?
- Why did you do that?
You and Yeon Du might have been seriously injured.
You should've at least told me.
What's with those two?
So how is Yeon Du now?
Is she okay? She didn't get hurt?
I should go see her.
What are you going to tell her?
Tell her everything and say you're sorry?
Well...
Leaving her behind on the trip.
Locking her up in the darkroom and even this...
She would never think you're behind it all.
Jin Se Hui, that little...
She thinks of you as a good senior.
She'll get hurt when she finds out.
Thank you for your concern, Senior.
Yeon Du.
But you know I'll handle my pain.
Could I have a word with you?
Was it really all your doing?
The incidents on the trip, the darkroom,
even today. Was it really all your doing?
Why did you?
Why did you hate me so much?
You were annoying.
What?
Do Ye Seok and Ji Hyeon Ho both liked you.
Everyone in the department praised you.
It was so annoying.
What did you say?
I had to work so hard to hear such compliments.
But you did nothing—
No.
You just had it all from the start.
It was unfair and frustrating.
How can you be so sure?
What?
You're wrong to say I did nothing.
And I didn't have it all from the start.
You can't just take someone's heart even if you want to.
I don't know how hard you worked for it.
But I didn't get it easy either.
It all needed time and effort for such relationships.
So don't underestimate me.
My time and effort, you don't know them.
No, I don't know.
But you still had everything I didn't.
And you were so annoying.
Now, are you satisfied?
Then why did you save me?
- Well...
- Didn't you worry about me, too?
That's the truth.
You helped me on the first day we met.
That's the real you and the arm shows your true heart.
Isn't it?
Is that so important?
You were constantly in trouble because of me.
Even today, you nearly injured yourself seriously.
You're right.
That's why I'm upset.
So apologize.
Not just with words.
Show me your truth in person.
I'm still upset.
So slowly, with time,
apologize to me.
I'll be watching you by staying next to you.
I hope nothing goes wrong.
You don't have to worry.
Kim Yeon Du is stronger than you think.
Call it even with this.
What?
I'm not trying to stand on pride.
I'm too shy to say thanks or sorry.
So just call it even.
You just did.
Pardon?
Apologizing and being grateful. You just said it all.
Well I was just saying...
You don't have to apologize.
And no need to thank me.
I was just explaining...
I'm also grateful.
What's with him?
Senior.
What are you doing here alone?
Well, I was looking at Life4cuts from the festival.
We'll be awarding the best cut among these pictures.
But everything looks so good.
It's hard to choose.
It's really, your life in four cuts.
- Senior Ye Seok—
- I found.
The best one.
Senior Ye Seok, I have something to tell you.
I already know.
Excuse me?
What you're trying to say. I already know.
The answer to my confession.
You're trying to say it right now.
You're refusing me, of course.
Right?
I'm sorry.
[Hyeon Ho♥]
Go.
I'll take care of the rest.
Okay.
But...
I won't be rooting for you.
If you two break up again,
I don't know what I would do.
[Congrats on graduation, Ah Hun.]
[Kang Ah Hun, You're An Adult Now!]
Those two won't stop until Yeon Du comes.
I'll call her to see where she is.
Squirtle!
Yeon Du!
I thought you weren't coming.
Sorry, I had to stop by the school.
Hurry and sit.
There is a seat next to your boyfriend.
- You're here.
- Yes.
- Sorry, I'm late.
- It's alright.
Why is everyone so late?
- Look at them having fun.
- Yes.
Listen up.
As the president of the photo club, I can't just let go on a day like this.
The photograph...
Let's take it here. All good?
Of course. Come on out.
Okay, I'll shoot.
Everyone, get closer.
I'll shoot.
Ten, night.
Eight.
Kim Yeon Du.
Yes?
Is it you? My girlfriend?
Hey, what's with the kiss?
- Ji Hyeon Ho.
- Yes?
Is it you? My boyfriend?
Yes, correct. I'm your boyfriend.
Hold on!
I'm not used to this.
What's with you two!
Ah Hun.
Where's my baseball bat?
Over there.
It's been an insane semester.
Now, a new season is almost here on campus.
No, I don't.
Let's have lunch together first.
- When you think about it...
- Sure!
Time is very odd.
It is equally given to everyone.
But it passes by differently for everyone.
That's not even close.
I'm accepted!
Congratulations!
Some kinds of time end.
And other times start again.
It matures for some.
Here's the officer's notebook.
Is it you?
My vice president?
What are you saying?
Thanks in advance, Vice President.
Sure.
Hug me once?
- No.
- Yes? Okay?
Go away.
Hug me, hurry.
And for others, it gradually fades away.
In the midst of time passing, we change
or stay the same.
What's important is that through those times,
we are slowly maturing.
Love isn't just a heartbeat.
Now we understand.
Feeling sorry, grateful, hurt, and sad,
it was all love.
Little by little, we are learning different forms of love.
The past is meaningful and the future is exciting
because I was not alone through it all.
It was our time together.
Throughout my eighteenth, nineteenth and twentieth year.
Thanks for being with me.
Channel manager biolince!
Thanks to segmenters pilar_velasquez and sylbi_18_751!
A very special thanks to chief editor lazarini!
Very thanks to translator editor awesomeharry!
Thanks to general editor damiechan!
Thanks to page designer shyny!
Thanks to all language moderators, editors, and translators!
Can we go one more time?
I forgot it all.
♫ It gets back to the starting point ♫
Is it right?
♫ I'm going forward to you with steering helm ♫
Um... Jin...
♫ You know I'm getting closer ♫
I'll buy you a drink if you make it in one take.
♫ Run faster toward me ♫
Why did you two break up?
Um, can I do that over?
I'll do that again.
No... No way.
I don't think that's an okay cut.
Don't you have any pride?
I'm sorry. I'll do that over.
♫ Sometimes I know or don't know, it's strange ♫
I'm sorry.
♫ Even if it hurts, we still cross the lines ♫
Oh, then...
♫ Like being possessed by something ♫
♫ It's getting perfect again ♫
Oppa. I said, "Oppa instead of Senior."
The call isn't going through.
Are you really out of your mind?!
♫ I really wanna like you ♫
♫ Even though I don't expect it'll last forever ♫
♫ It's hard ♫
♫ It changes from 0 to 100 ♫
♫ More than several dozens times a day ♫
I'm sorry for being snobby.
Let's do again.
I'll do that over.
♫ I'm getting hot ♫
♫ I'm losing my mind again ♫
Yes, let's do again.
♫ Hold me, you know ♫
♫ As much as you believe me, I'm falling into you ♫
[Keum Dong Hyun as Kang Ah Hun]
[Joo Hyeon Young as An Yu Na]
[Lee Jeong Jun as Choi Seung Hyeon]
[Nana as Yun Ah Ra]
[Choi Chan Yi as Jeong Ji Seong]
[Yoon Hyeon Seok as Kim Dae Yeong]
[Yoon Jun Won as Seo Ju Ho]
[Park E Hyun as Yu Seol]
[Kang Hye Won as Jin Se Hui]
[Kim Won Pil as Do Ye Seok]
[Kang Yul as Ji Hyeon Ho]
[Lee Eun Jae as Kim Yeon Du]
♫ It's getting perfect again ♫
[Thank you for watching Best Mistake 3]
♫ I still don't know about you ♫
♫ The more I like you ♫
♫ Just doing so ♫
[Best Mistake 3]
♫ The more anxious and impetuous ♫