=Heavenly Secrets Bureau=
=Episode 7=
Nobody move.
You trespassed
into a government-sealed mine,
released the spirit of the Lady Gu,
and endangered the people,
causing chaos throughout Nandian.
Unforgivable crimes.
Seize them.
Careful!
Xiao Ye!
You've been poisoned by me.
If you use your inner force again,
you'll die instantly.
Inhale this.
It will neutralize the poison.
But it'll take an hour
for your inner strength to return.
Now,
Take Xiaojuzi and leave.
If we all stay here,
none of us will escape.
No, Princess.
- I'm your guard!
- Enough!
I am a princess.
They won't dare lay a finger on me.
I heard from my royal father
that Governor Cao
has already arrived in Nandian.
Go now and get reinforcements.
Hurry.
I am Princess Li Lingyue of the empire.
I'd like to see
which of you dares touch me.
Hmph.
The Ninth Princess is of noble blood.
She should be safe in the palace.
How could she possibly
be here in Nandian?
You're just a wicked woman,
lawless and wild.
And you dare impersonate
a princess? Arrest her!
Xiaojuzi.
Go find Governor Cao and call for help.
What about you?
I can't leave the princess. Go!
The court is trying
the Lady Gu's accomplices!
Everyone, come and watch!
This woman
has been impersonating a princess
and poisoning people in Nandian.
These two villains
are the Lady Gu's accomplices.
Now, they've finally been captured.
For the sake of public peace,
I will sentence them to death by fire.
- Yes!
- Burn them!
- From now on,
- Burn them all!
- you can finally live in peace.
Remember this.
If you discover any suspicious people,
Little Diviner.
you must report them to the authorities.
Aren't you supposed to be all-powerful
and able to tell fortunes?
Tell me, can we escape this?
We must eliminate these demons,
- Since we can't escape this fate,
- only then can the people
- we might as well face it.
- live a good life.
Everyone,
- only then can we truly live in peace.
- Do you regret it?
What's there to regret?
If any of you discover
these demons' accomplices,
You could have escaped with Xiao Ye.
or any suspicious people
You're no different.
ask you about
- If it weren't for us holding you back,
- other information
- you might've already gotten away.
- or anything strange,
- You're not like the rumors say.
- you can report it to the authorities.
If there really is reliable information,
Dying with you would be worth it.
- At least we'd have each other in the afterlife.
- the authorities will reward you accordingly.
- Though you usually act cold, aloof and unkind.
- Everyone understand now?
Still,
These devils...
Since you're not too bad-looking,
I suppose I'll settle for you.
Many thanks for the honor, Princess.
I too feel that being able to accompany
Your Highness on the road to the underworld
makes this trip worthwhile.
Time's up. Begin the execution.
Light the fire!
Xiao!
Princess!
I'm sorry I'm late.
Be careful of that official, Li Sen.
He's highly skilled in martial arts.
Perfect timing.
I'll send you all to hell together.
Seize them!
Useless.
A bunch of useless fools.
It's the Twin Fish.
That symbol again.
Arrest Li Sen and his accomplices!
Princess, are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Princess!
I arrived too late to protect you.
Please forgive me, Princess.
Rise.
Go.
Interrogate that official, Li Sen.
Thank you, Princess.
Bold Li Sen, how dare you
attempt to harm the Princess?
Do you not admit your guilt?
I didn't know she was the Princess.
Besides,
ignorance is
no crime.
You...
Then I'll make sure you confess.
Xiaojuzi.
Li Sen.
You've ruined my life.
You murdered Zhong Dagao
and framed Xiu for the crime.
You even fabricated
the entire Lady Gu tale.
Just your words?
That counts as evidence?
The way you killed Zhong Dagao
is exactly the same as
how you killed those soldiers just now.
That's right.
The fracture in Zhong Dagao's
neck was identical.
There were no signs
of poisoning in his remains.
He was killed by a powerful,
swift strike that crushed his bones.
This is a frame-up!
Then explain the poison found in your room,
the same one used to frame Xiu.
How do you explain that?
You.
You pretended
to help Lady Gu's spirit return.
And tricked those infected
with the Gu poison
into drinking
your so-called divine water,
and wearing your talismans.
Those all contained
the deadly poison Qianji Powder.
All of this
was your doing, wasn't it?
Have mercy, Princess!
It was him.
It was all Li Sen's idea.
He ordered me to do it.
It was him.
He made me sell the talismans
and the miracle water.
And collected money from the townsfolk.
I only took a tiny bit of silver.
The majority
was all taken by Li Sen!
If I didn't obey,
he said he'd kill me!
Well done, Li Sen.
You're just a petty
seventh-rank county magistrate,
earning only thirty taels a year,
yet you bought dozens
of estates in the capital!
And you still deny it?
He's corrupted
and murderous! Kill him!
- Kill him!
- Lord Cao!
Spare me.
Please, spare me!
I was just confused for a moment!
Were you really
just confused for a moment?
I don't know what you're talking about.
The incense burner in your study
and the cave on Tianling Mountain
that you wouldn't let anyone approach.
On the weapons inside,
they all bear the Twin Fish symbol.
Tell me.
What does
Twin Fish represent?
If you tell the truth,
I will spare your life.
Fine.
I'll tell.
I...
Watch out!
Catch the assassin!
Hurry, catch the assassin!
Qifeng greets Your Highness
the Noble Consort.
Prince Qifeng, what unfortunate timing.
Yue'er is not in the palace.
I came here specifically
to visit you, Your Highness.
In just over a month,
I'll be marrying Yue'er.
To thank Your Highness for raising her,
I've prepared a small gift.
Yun Cang's golden-thread orchid
promotes beauty and longevity.
Please accept it.
How thoughtful of you.
I'm glad Your Highness likes it.
The Emperor and I have
seen your devotion to Yue'er.
Having her marry you
puts our minds at ease.
I thank the Emperor
and Your Highness for your blessing.
That girl has been spoiled
by the Emperor and me.
Who knows where she's off
to playing around again?
I, Qifeng,
enjoy meeting people far and wide.
I've made some friends
in the martial world.
I believe finding
the Princess won't be too difficult.
Then I'll leave it to you.
However,
Yue'er has always been willful.
What if she refuses to return with you?
Does Your Highness have a solution?
Here, take this.
This is...
Yue'er was born
with a congenital poison.
This antidote was developed
by her master, Wan Nianqing.
Her condition
only improved because of it.
But it only alleviated the symptoms.
Every six months, it will still recur.
And that time is almost upon us.
You might find this useful.
Understood.
Thanks to Ninth Princess
and Young Master Gu
for uncovering
the witchcraft case in Nandian.
Justice has been served for the people.
This is truly satisfying.
Young Master.
Uncle Da?
I finally found you.
Uncle Da, why are you here?
You've been gone so long without word,
how could I not worry?
Sorry, I forgot
to send a letter to ease your mind.
Ninth Princess,
this matter of the tens of thousands
of missing weapons
from Tianling Mountain in Nandian
is of great importance.
I have already drafted a secret memorial
to report to His Majesty.
Good. Then I'll entrust
the investigation of the weapons
to you, Lord Cao.
Hmm.
Guards.
Mount a fast horse at once.
Deliver this memorial
to the imperial palace.
Yes.
Lord Cao, there's still one mystery left
in the Nandian witchcraft case.
Li Sen kept a memorial tablet
for Master Yang at home.
Who is this Master Yang?
Master Yang...
Could it be referring to Master Baiyang?
The former Crown Prince, Yang Wen,
known as Master Baiyang,
has been dead for thirty years.
When the former dynasty fell,
he set fire to himself
in the palace.
Master Baiyang?
Master Baiyang...
(Could it be that the Nandian case)
(is linked to the former dynasty?)
(The memorial)
(Leicheng)