(I know where you are. )
So this is your melody.
(Deliberately stating that you don't need to know that I understand)
Because you are my most beautiful song.
"Come on girl",
"Your floral skirt",
(The heart is like a parachute. Beautiful and lovely. )
We'll remember to watch the sea with you now. ),
(Bring you to the sky fly),
"Come on sweet",
"Your little accident",
"Your marshmallow" Your sample "So shy"?
"We will always depend on me. "
"Say good night with me. ",
♪ Let's watch the starry sea together.
♪ My heart beats so fast.
"We're sitting on the rooftop. "...
"We're talking sweetly.
♪ I like it when I say I love you all my life.
♪ But you and I won't wander around.
"Spit it out if you're unhappy. "
But let me guess at every turn?
♪ I like you, though you're often helpless. ♪ I'm not afraid of you. ♪ You're very
powerful.
♪ All the stories are changed according to you.
♪ You were an accident to me. ♪ I know you're
connected.
♪ Where are you? ♪
So this is your melody.
(Deliberately stating that you don't need to know that I understand)
(Because you are my most beautiful song)
(I know where you are. )
(So this is your melody. ),
(Deliberately stating that you don't need to know that I understand)
Because you are my most beautiful song.
[ Long Yi, what are you going to do? ]
[ Episode 5 ] Who
pissed you off again?
Your weight fan?
I made you unhappy again.
What's Zhang Jingmei's way?
So horizontal,
Who?
Zhang Jingmei,
isn't this unforgettable white moonlight?
Yu Haoqiu's man,
Yu Haoqiu,
What kind of money should I be?
So rude.
Did I piss you off?
Hey, what are you doing?
No,
this is what you call pure temperament,
There are so many beautiful women.
Or what?
You have a misunderstanding about pretty girls,
or you have prejudice against Jing Ba.
Ask him,
what's going on?
As groomsmen,
you two are obliged
to choose the wedding address for me,
Look!
Well,
if you get married,
Why are you pretending to be a cultural person?
Why did you choose this place?
Aren't you going to stop me?
The Spanish version.
Do you want to change it?
You can do it.
Director,
what's wrong?
are you going to use the RV?
This RV belongs to the owner,
so I can call Deng Man Fei for you
and ask him if he's in the car.
It's not good for her
to get into someone else's car like this.
You still can't do it?
She said it hurt her leg.
What's wrong with Man Fei?
She insisted that she was in a bad state today
and couldn't perform anymore.
Let's go outside and tell the owner,
can we rent it for one more day?
Zhang,
Look,
Director Director,
this is a new house,
You finally agreed to shoot for one day.
Man Fei told me to add more money,
but it's not about money.
Then what?
Aren't you friends with the owner?
You can discuss it with him,
and you can't break your promise even if you're friends.
Man Fei said,
she wants to see your owner,
Tell him in person,
Jing Mei,
Aren't you friends with him?
Can you give him a call?
Okay,
Where are you going?
Ask the owner to go.
This girl is not bad.
What are you doing here?
Is this the place where you can come?
Aren't you going to see the owner?
Owner,
do you really think you've bribed Long Yi?
Then you can be a sister-in-law.
How did you know all of this?
Stop pretending.
I know this is Long Yi's car,
and that's Long Yi's house.
You just
bribed Long Yi's little brother,
He acted in a scene with Director Liu,
and tried to seduce Long Yi by the way.
But to be honest,
you're quite smart.
But you shouldn't... You shouldn't
just steal from me,
So Long Yi is your man,
how about you think,
He agreed to film here
just for a little outreach to you,
To tell you the truth,
he's a fan of mine,
I have to ask him when I go back tonight.
evening
Are you talking about him?
(Marriage certificate)
You.
I didn't expect my husband
to be so lovable.
Sis,
Have a cup of herbal tea to reduce the heat.
Director,
is it my turn?
Here we are.
I'm waiting for you.
What kind of herbal tea
is made strangely.
Action. Action.
All units,
get ready. -I'm coming. -Okay,
There's something.
Turn it on!
Where did you go last night?
Didn't I tell you?
When you go out for dinner with your bestie,
do you have to turn off your phone?
Can I not turn it off
if you keep calling me?
Okay,
It's unnecessary for me to care about you, isn't it?
I didn't care about you before.
Stop it.
Are you done getting angry all day?
Stop,
Yes.
Good job.
That's great.
Okay,
Now that this scene is finished,
let's get ready for the transition.
Take it easy.
Look at him.
Don't lose anything.
Take it easy.
Be careful.
Take this.
-Take this, too. -Take this. Here
it comes.
Brother,
the film is finished,
The room has been set up.
Have you seen your sister-in-law?
Sister-in-law,
I think she hasn't seen anyone since this afternoon.
Why is there no one here again?
No one answered the phone.
Long Yi,
Where are you?
Why hasn't he come back yet?
You're back.
What's going on?
No, no, I don't know.
Did you get irritated?
Sister-in-law,
it's dangerous.
-Step back. -What's wrong, sister-in-law?
-Inside, inside, inside. -Be careful, go
inside. Hurry up,
It's so noisy.
What are you doing?
Your Russian herbal tea is delicious,
but it has too much stamina.
Silly wife,
that's the liquor of the fighting nation.
Just drink.
Honey.
You called me "husband",
"husband",
You don't know,
it's so great to be your wife.
That's why I found out.
♪ You ignored your meticulous concern for me.
♪
I didn't listen to what you said. ♪ Call me Mrs.
Long. ♪ But I regret being mad
at you. ♪ When I was so anxious, I didn't know where to hide.
♪ You'll hold me tight with a smile. ♪ Sweet
breath.
Mrs. Long,
happy wedding!
♪ Sweet Breathing ♪
♪ I've completely exposed my affection for you.
♪ I'm sure you're the only one. ]
Jingmei.
What's wrong?
Happy wedding!
♪ Although I feel wronged in my heart.
♪ But I regret being angry with you. ♪ When I was so anxious, I didn't know where
to hide.
♪ You'll hold me tight with a smile. ♪ Sweet
breath.
♪ I fell into your arms. ♪
You smiled and said it's okay to have you around. ♪
Sweet breath.
♪ I've completely exposed my affection for you.
♪ I'm sure you're the only one. ♪
I'm awake.
Call me Mrs. Long.
Now you know you're shy?
You weren't like this last night.
Zhang Jingmei,
I can leave everything else to you,
Is it appropriate
for you to do that?
Zhang Jingmei,
why are you panicking?
You are legally married.
Gosh,
this is so unique.
When did he buy it?
We're legally married.
You're still sneaking around when you change your clothes.
Well,
when did you
buy those clothes?
Well,
I bought it a long time ago.
Do you like it?
What are you doing?
What a coincidence.
I'll get changed, too.
Then … Wait a minute. That lady is
preferred,
Men first, women first.
Let's go together.
No way.
Zhang Jingmei,
This … This is also my home.
have you swelled up?
Madam Long,
are you wearing this?
What's wrong with wearing this?
It doesn't look good.
I've been looking for it for a long time,
so I'm wearing this.
Your clothes are comfortable.
Your clothes,
I'm not going to a party.
Mine.
Stingy.
Miss Jing Mei, please have a meal.
Thank you.
This is the first time I've prepared breakfast for you.
I don't know if it suits your taste.
-Yes, yes. -Try
it first.
Call me if you need anything?
Thank you.
It's just breakfast.
There's no need to exaggerate.
Breakfast needs balanced nutrition.
I didn't say nutrition.
Uncle,
Our chef?
You have a chef at home?
Is it not to your taste?
No,
I mean, just the two of us,
It's just breakfast.
Just a little casual.
You don't need to bother Uncle.
Who do you want to trouble?
That's what Uncle Wang does.
Do you want him to lose his job?
What if Uncle comes to your house?
And Uncle Li and Uncle Zhao
Eat more Honey,
I'm done.
I want to talk to you about a mysterious wedding address,
wedding,
Luo Beichen and Yu Lang chose it
ancient castle
What do you think?
Hello, bro.
I'm back.
You have a WeChat message.
(Hello, bro. )
(I'm back. )
Who is it?
How beautiful
a beautiful woman is.
Jealous.
No.
Don't worry.
I'm much more manly than you.
A female man.
You still have such an old photo?
This is your black history.
I have to keep it for the rest of my life.
You still haven't changed
your bad-hearted habit.
A woman changes eighteen times before reaching womanhood.
You put on your skirt.
I've braids my hair.
You look like a girl.
What do you mean by "like"?
I'm a girl, okay?
One more time.
Childish.
Don't go.
It's not over yet.
I'm sure I can make a comeback
in the next round with someone else.
Take me to the hotel.
The one on Chunqiu Road,
you work on your first day at home,
No way.
I don't have to take care of the hotel now.
I came back this time for another mission,
so I don't need to
ask more friends
to welcome you.
Aren't you afraid that I'll say yes?
No,
you always hate parties.
I don't think he's free.
But if Grandpa asks about it,
I'll give you a good reception.
What happened? Why are you in such a hurry
to manicure with me?
Hunian,
I asked for leave.
If you don't have anything else to do,
I'll leave.
Jing Mei
-Mom. -Mom, it's
your number.
Okay.
How is my son Hu Bowen?
Is he handsome?
Handsome is handsome,
but I haven't even met your husband,
I just want to see your son.
In this order,
Old Hu is such a big director,
He's so famous,
why do you need me
to introduce you?
Think of it as trying on a wedding dress with me today.
Okay?
What do you mean
by doing manicure is the same as trying on a wedding dress?
Where is he?
Old Hu said he wouldn't hold the wedding again.
Second marriage is low-key,
just a few people have dinner together,
But if the budget is approved,
I can spend whatever I want.
That is to say,
he is still afraid that others will know
about your relationship.
Don't talk about me.
What's wrong with you?
You didn't even tell me.
We're not friends
enough. We haven't done it yet, right?
There's no wedding.
It's not Long Yi's style.
Why is your ring so ordinary?
You must be married to Long Yi.
Except for that dragon.
Can you marry someone else?
I don't seem to want to do it.
Like you don't want to get married,
Yes,
That's more like it.
How do you feel?
Big or not?
What are you talking about?
Is the mansion big?
What does it feel like to marry into a rich family?
I don't think so.
I just feel like
I'm not alone all of a sudden.
There's someone who can vote for you.
I can advance and retreat with you.
After hearing what you said,
how do I feel,
It's like a fake marriage.
I didn't ask you to marry my dad.
He's old and ugly. And I
… Don't say that. Your
dad doesn't need to wrap it. I'm eating
here. I'm eating a cake and cutting off my beard.
Sorry, Mr. Si Luo,
Miss Chen has bought the cake.
Have you paid for it?
Since I'm not lucky enough
to eat such a beautiful cake,
Would you be honored
to pay a bill for this beautiful woman?
Put it on my account.
2045,
you'd better charge it to my account.
At four o'clock in the afternoon,
there should be another cake service in your hotel.
Please order one for this gentleman,
and thank him for his love for this cake
Okay Miss Chen,
Take care, Miss Chen.
2046,
looks like an expert
Hey, honey,
According to my map navigation,
there are ten minutes left,
You have the right cast position, right?
The location is right,
but you don't have to come if you're fine.
Forget it.
I have something else to do.
Hello.
You make it sound like I'm the only one in the world who has nothing to do.
Brother is really free recently.
Sister-in-law said it.
Brother Hao,
take a look at your movements,
Come and grab this position.
Remember,
don't hit at a 45-degree angle.
It's easy to hit the stand-in in the face.
Okay?
Come on, let's go again.
Come on.
What is
Meng Hao up to?
Step up,
fall over your shoulder,
Is that okay?
Sure,
you have to remember,
You're doing the moves for Man Fei,
but you can't show your face all the way, okay?
Okay,
get ready, brother.
Brother Lai,
come on.
Turn it on!
Put it forward. Put it forward.
That one?
Put it here, boss.
Lower your voice.
Are you filming
with your voice down?
Okay, okay.
Turn it on!
Get ready.
One, two, three.
Are you okay, honey?
Honey, why are you here?
What do you think?
It's okay.
I'll go. Who are you?
You're killing yourself.
Long Yi,
What else did you get?
"You are the warm heart of summer night. "
You are the letter of the evening breeze.
♪ The air is so sweet. ♪
I want to go on an adventure together.
♪ Let's see the world together.
♪ The night sky has become very special.
♪ It's so special that the sky is flickering. ♪ I can't even reach
you.
♪ The gleam of the starry river lights up your wish ♪
♪ It lights up the light in your eyes.
♪ Stretch the shadow longer.
♪ Collect romantic memories and put them there.
"You are the warm heart of summer night. "
You are the letter of the evening breeze.
♪ The air is so sweet. ♪
Walking hand in hand. ♪ Shaking with the
wind.
My imagination has come true.
(Please remember that if I keep silent. ) (Look at the stars and the Milky Way. )
(The wish I made is for you to appear by my
side. ) (I miss you so much that I can't say
it. ),
(Answer it with a mark. )
Looking up at the stars means I miss you.
♪ Walking hand in hand ♪
Shaking with the wind.
My imagination has come true.
♪ Look at the starry sky in silence.
♪ My wish is that you will come to me soon.
♪ I miss you so much that I can't say it.
♪ Answer me with action?
♪ Looking up at the stars means I miss you.
(La la la la la la)
Looking up at the stars means I miss you.
♪ Looking up at the stars means I miss you.
(The right to disseminate the drama information on the Internet and other needs for dissemination through the Internet),
(The legal rights and broadcasting rights are exclusively owned by Shenzhen Tencent Computer System Co., Ltd. ),