This is for Mrs. Long.
You must be careful.
Okay?
Can you do that?
All right.
You know it's a wedding gift.
It's very precious.
Why didn't you answer the phone again?
I spent a lot of money.
director
If we can't figure this out,
I can't go on working.
Yiyi.
You're the acting assistant director of the crew.
You have the whole team.
How much does it cost to waste a day?
I'll pay for the delay.
But if the police come,
There's evidence that I didn't do it.
Then she will pay.
To challenge me.
Zhang Yiyi.
You're an actress and assistant director.
It's only a few pounds.
You pay for it.
Who are you to compensate?
Mrs. Long.
Someone asked you something.
Don't you want to answer?
Anita is here.
I asked you to order a wedding dress.
I'm calling you.
Why didn't you answer it?
I finally understand the director.
Is this an interview with my wife?
director
Did my wife cause trouble for the crew?
Nothing.
Young Master Long.
Are you kidding me?
misunderstanding
It's all a misunderstanding.
That's right.
misunderstanding
Today,
Everyone is not working.
That's great.
Honey, leave.
director
Where are you going?
Let's go.
Go and have a look.
Let's go, Miss Meng.
go
Choose.
To choose here.
Correct!
This is Anita.
This is my wife.
Miss Anita insisted on seeing you.
These ones here
Are Miss Anita.
I picked it out for you.
Miss Lin,
This necklace
It's not the one you lost.
No
That's good.
This is for my engagement with my wife.
Fierce
What about
Let's go, honey.
With might redoubled
It's limitless.
Miss Meng.
President Chen.
You still have one and a half days off.
Cancel my leave.
It's late now.
Actually, these jobs are not that important.
Get off work early.
Correct!
Young Master Jin will return home next week.
Do you have time to see him?
not see
Ask him to arrange it.
to give to charity
Hello, Luo Beichen.
My phone is precious.
Can you save me some snacks?
Who told you to abandon me and run so far?
If you regret it,
Hurry back.
If you're late,
I ran away with someone else.
That's right.
Brother Beichen is so popular.
Brother Yu Lang.
When are you coming back?
We missed you.
Brother Yu Lang.
When are you coming back?
We missed you.
roll
It's okay. I'm hanging up.
Something's wrong.
If you need help,
I
I really hung up.
You don't need me?
It's been a few days.
Let's drink together.
Brother Beichen.
Drink with us.
Are you going to cry, Childe Luo?
You're here.
Do you remember who I am?
It's all gone.
I'm his girlfriend.
Girlfriend
What's wrong, ex-boyfriend?
You're lovelorn again?
Take revenge.
Can you walk?
I can't carry you.
Get up.
The water should be poured like this.
You can't water it too much.
Can't be too little.
Let them dry.
Did you hear that?
this
I'm afraid I can't.
How about Madam Long?
To look after them every day.
You have opened such a big shop.
Do you have two little grass to raise?
You should have confidence in yourself.
I have more confidence in Madam Long.
I'm telling you,
If you raise them to death,
I'm asking you.
wife
Let's go home.
I'm here to patrol the shop.
I'll be home in two minutes.
husband
The things in your shop
Hundreds of thousands at a time.
I'll only give you two blades of grass.
Isn't it a little inappropriate?
take
It's perfect.
Full of love.
Full of vigour
Thank you so much, wife.
Honey, you've been working hard.
I should thank you.
No,
Watch the road.
Chen Xuanyi
What Xuan Yi?
Okay, I'll hang up.
I see him. Go.
get home
Slow down.
Look at you.
Luo Beichen.
Ex-girlfriend
elephant
Yu Lang, wait for me.
Yu Lang.
Why are you running so fast?
Why?
Be careful. I'll tell Zhang Jingmei.
She's my classmate.
I said,
Zhang Jingmei is Long Yi's wife.
She's not my wife.
Why are you always following me?
Who told you to bump into me?
I
What?
It's my bad luck.
Let's go.
Lower your voice.
Don't disturb the elephant.
Where are my clothes?
What? You want to run again?
No
Give me the clothes.
Take it and wash it.
What should I wear?
Think of a way.
You can't wear dirty clothes.
I threw up last night.
sorry
I'm sorry I have too many things to do.
Which one do you want to talk about first?
Linda
When I was in danger,
To save him.
This kindness
And bear it in mind.
roll
Linda
Last night,
Don't blame me.
I didn't do anything to you.
Thank you, Linda.
Who is Chen Xuan Yi?
No one.
Who is it?
You called her for a whole night.
Take it easy.
Let me know if you need anything.
Sister, table three.
I'll do it.
Jingmei
Little lady.
What's wrong with Jing Mei?
It's like fighting chicken blood.
Any more? Which table?
What are you doing?
The store is so busy.
sit
What are you doing?
What happened between you and Long Yi?
Nothing's wrong.
Did he bully you?
No, don't guess.
What's wrong with your family?
wrong
If anything happens to your family,
Long Yi will help you solve it.
That's work.
Did someone bully you?
No,
I have nothing to do.
To help you?
If you don't tell me,
I called Su Jialin.
Don't.
I'm just a little confused.
vast and indistinct
Your love is sweet and you married into a rich man.
Your work will be smooth.
What are you confused about?
I just don't know who I am.
Sister, sister.
Have some water.
No, no. I'm not drinking water.
Thank you.
don't mention it
You can call me Zhang from now on.
I've been here for a long time.
I've been acting in this group.
That Xiao Zhang
Director, they are waiting for me.
I'll go first.
It's okay, sister. Go back to work.
I'll be at your service anytime.
My name is Zhang Jingwei.
Zhang Jingmei
Zhang Jingwei
Our relatives
you're welcome
Director, I'm here.
to regret leaving
Yiyi.
Get a chair for Yi.
good
No, no.
to regret leaving
director
How do you think this scene should be shot?
Do you have any idea?
The director
The coordinator said
Let me check the actors tomorrow.
I'll go first.
Okay, you go first.
Yiyi, have a seat.
No need.
Director, go back to work.
OK, Yiyi.
When you said that,
It seems that everyone treats you well.
They are good to Mrs. Long.
What's the difference?
Aren't you Mrs. Long?
But I'm also Zhang Jingmei.
Zhang Jingmei
Are you a little hypocritical?
I didn't.
Did I? I didn't.
That's you.
You can't accept the title of Mrs. Long.
Does Long Yi know?
Hello, welcome.
How much is this one?
This is 150,000 yuan.
Sir, you have a good taste.
These are our top jewelry.
Look at this.
You can have a look at the high-end jewelry here.
The price is also expensive.
Hello, welcome.
Take a look.
Let me see how much this is.
This is 100,000 yuan.
I'll have a look.
If you need it,
I'll take it out for you.
Try it on.
Thank you
Easy, easy.
Slow down.
Sister, I was looking for you.
I found you a comfortable chair.
I'll bring it to you.
No, no.
I was running around.
You don't need a chair.
Thank you.
Don't.
I specially prepared it for you.
Xiao Zhang.
We are the crew.
Attend to each one's own duties
Just mind your own business.
If I need anything,
I'll do it myself.
Okay, I'll listen to you.
Don't.
We all listen to the director.
Okay, I've passed.
director
Yiyi is here.
Yiyi.
Jingmei.
Are all called Jingmei. In the future,
I apologize to everyone.
My real name is Zhang Jingmei.
But working on the crew
I'm Zhang Yiyi, the actress and deputy director.
If you are used to it,
Just call me Yiyi.
It's Yiyi.
Yiyi.
director
I'm married to Long Yi.
And Mrs. Long.
But it's nothing.
Working on the crew.
We are colleagues.
How did you work before?
It's still the same now.
Don't do that.
Alright, I'll call you Jing Mei.
Sister Jing Mei.
The director
I'll go to work.
Okay, go back to work.
Everyone is here.
Sister Enqi is here.
Sister En Qi,
Coach Zhang.
I heard you're the assistant director here.
Why are you here?
Director Wang gave me a chance.
Let me be a guest.
Sister En Qi,
Are you scolding me?
Do you know each other?
Did you bully her?
No,
impossible
Our team takes good care of the actors.
Yes
yes
Zhang Jingmei
You can't be Zhang Yiyi anymore.
This report is wrong.
They gave you the data.
Why do you still have a problem?
Sorry, sister.
I'll change it again.
Mr. Luo,
President Chen is having a meeting.
Why don't you wait for her?
No need.
This is Long Mei Island Omei Box.
The game design
Give it to President Chen.
President Chen will finish the meeting soon.
Why don't you wait for her?
No need.
Let's go to this house.
This place should be good.
Hello, welcome.
Hello
This is nice.
It's pretty.
How come
And sighs every time.
You're so unlucky.
I lost, brother.
What did you lose?
love
A girl once told me
I will be punished sooner or later.
have to
The retribution will come.
Why do I like Chen Xuanyi so much?
Who told you that, Linda?
What does it have to do with her?
What are you talking about, Linda?
I'm telling you,
Langlang called me that day.
He said he was going to see the elephant that night.
Do you know who I saw?
Who is it?
Linda
I saw Linda holding you.
It's an accident.
That's right.
It's an accident again.
It's an accident for you and everyone.
I want to make it clear to you.
Chen Xuanyi
Although she looks like a female King Kong,
Actually, he's vulnerable.
What you did before,
She never blamed you.
But I'll put the ugly words in front of you.
If you mess with her,
And you're not responsible,
I'll be the first to forgive you.
You know her well and you want to protect her.
Why don't you marry her?
According to Uncle Long,
He bought the latest remote-controlled car this year.
I don't know which one it is.
When I'm 25,
I will marry you.
These things are mine.
Brother Long.
You should grow up.
Chen Xuanyi
This is the men's room.
Go away.
It's okay. Pee on you.
I won.
Chen Xuan Yi, you're amazing.
You're so bold.
You're too bold.
That's fine.
Or I'll marry her.
I only have Jingmei in my heart.
narrow-minded
I really envy you.
You and your Chen Xuanyi
You can be innocent since you were young.
I envy you.
You don't have to know the female King Kong since you were young.
Hello, welcome.
I want to see this.
OK
How many are you?
You just came in. You went there.
It's called potential client.
She looked inside, you know?
It's two.
Long Yi.
Is it interesting to lie to yourself?
Who lied to themselves?
Seek truth from facts
I know.
It's hard to fail.
Who failed?
eldest brother
I haven't failed yet.
a row
As long as you insist, you will succeed.
right or wrong?