(It's huge.)
(A special invigorating dish for the summertime)
(The king of crustaceans, king crabs)
(I want to take a look at them too.)
(Gosh, they look tasty.)
Oh, my. Give them to me.
(Twerking with excitement)
All right. Pay attention to the sound.
(But...)
(Jung Woo is only staring at them instead of eating them.)
(An anxious gaze)
Here. Look at this, Jung Woo.
(Ta-da. Look at this.)
Gosh, it looks scary. It looks like a monster.
(Gosh, it looks scary. It looks like a monster.)
The Return of Superman. Episode 578.
(Chapter 578: The Challenge of Superman Dad)
The Challenge of Superman Dad.
I'll drive the boat.
Come on and get on the boat here.
(The table transformed into a boat.)
Jung Woo, hurry up. Come and get on board.
(Eun Woo and Jung Woo are role-playing together.)
This is my boat.
(They are not at the DM Town.)
It's your boat?
You can use these stepping stones here.
(They use the stepping stones made of books.)
There's a path here too.
(Jung Woo gets on the table boat.)
I'll drive the boat.
(Captain Kim Eun Woo of Boat Eun Woo)
(Jung Woo uses the stepping stones made of books.)
Ding-dong.
Jung Woo, get on the boat.
Mister, where would you like to sit?
Right here.
Then I'll drive you to your destination.
(He successfully gets on Boat Eun Woo.)
(He's glue to his brother.)
(Hugging tightly)
(The Woo Brothers are full of love from the morning.)
Guys. Who wants to have a yogurt drink?
(A yogurt drink?)
Who wants to have a yogurt drink?
(Food Goblin reacts immediately.)
Jung Woo, would you like to go out together?
Yes.
(Wait for us, yogurt drinks!)
(What will the Woo Brothers have for their morning snack?)
Let's have your favourite yogurt drinks and some fruit.
I'm going to have yogurt.
(As Jun Ho is on a diet, he'll have a bowl of Greek yogurt.)
I prepared low-sugar yogurt drinks.
How many do you want to drink?
- A lot! - I want to drink...
five.
Five. What about you, Jung Woo?
I want three.
Three.
(His words and actions don't match.)
If you want 3, fold 2 fingers here.
Like this. Try it again. "Three!"
(I want 3 that's like 5.)
- Three. - Yes.
(An essential Danish probiotic snack for the Woo Brothers)
Have a yogurt drink.
I want another, please. I finished it.
I prepared them because I heard they were very nutritious.
Try it.
You guys really love yogurt drinks.
(His eyebrows show that he really loves it.)
- Say, "Thank you." - There.
- I want a straw. - Okay.
- Put it down. - A straw.
(I want to eat them already.)
Okay. You're so impatient.
- Thank you. - That's it.
(Thanking him right away)
(Sipping)
(Why won't it come out?)
(Inhaling)
(As he doesn't know the straw is out, he inhales air.)
(He finally sees that it's empty.)
(Grabbing one more)
(He acts before he speaks.)
Okay. Hold on a second.
- Give me more drinks. - Okay.
Jung Woo, grab the whole thing and drink them.
Here. Hold the entire thing.
This too. Put a straw in this too.
(He ends up drinking 4 at once.)
Thank you.
(Thank you, Dad!)
I knew that you guys would drink a lot of this.
(Gulping down)
So I got you the low-sugar drinks.
(It's low-sugar yogurt.)
It's okay to drink a lot of it.
(The best way to enjoy them is to drink them non-stop.)
(Jung Woo has a fun way of drinking them.)
I want the straws in my drinks like Jung Woo.
Wait. I'll give it to you. Don't move.
(When Jung Woo got up...)
(and ate the meat, )
No. Sit down.
(I see. I can eat standing up.)
(He followed Jung Woo and got up too.)
No. Sit down.
(When Jung Woo ordered his drink in English...)
- Orange juice. - Orange juice?
- I want to try too. - Yes.
(Eun Woo could order his drink in English too.)
Orange juice, please.
(Eun Woo became Jung Woo's copycat.)
- That was tasty. - That was tasty.
(He's drinking them the same way as Jung Woo.)
Here.
(In front of his favorite snack)
Thank you, Dad.
(Acting super cute)
What a surprise, Eun Woo.
I guess it is good indeed.
(The Woo Brothers know how to enjoy food.)
Isn't this the perfect snack?
I'm going to have some yogurt now.
(Greek yogurt has no artificial additives but is full of protein.)
Do you know what kind of food slows down our ageing?
- I don't know. - It's a trend now.
It's eating stuff like this.
Actually, as for food that slows down ageing,
Uncle Soo Hong should eat it, not me.
Hey. My gosh. Are you all right? Give me a second. Oh, my.
(Taking care of kids at the age of 50 is no joke.)
I feel dizzy. Don't you feel dizzy?
(Guys, don't you feel dizzy?)
- Please do it again. - Please do it again.
(Their energy never runs low.)
Hey, guys. Did you know some dinosaurs lie down?
(He only had a taste of what raising sons would be like.)
(He runs out of energy.)
Like this. There are dinosaurs like this.
(As kids grow up, it'll be harder to look after them.)
- Do it again. - My gosh. What are you doing?
(He's just getting started.)
Should we do it one more time?
(Should we do it one more time?)
(Make sure to have healthy food.)
Woo Brothers.
Do you remember Jae Yi?
(Do you remember Jae Yi and Uncle Soo Hong?)
The girl we met at Uncle Soo Hong's?
- We saw fish. - Yes.
- Then we saw a baby girl. - You saw a baby girl too.
- Then we saw a baby girl. - Yes.
(I remember seeing a cat.)
We saw a cat.
That's it.
(He's got a great memory.)
Woo Brothers, I planned a packed day for us.
(They'll have a special day today as well.)
Did you enjoy it?
Yes.
It's good.
Now that we finished it,
let's go out and have a new experience.
(Let's go and experience something new.)
(Full of colorful and fragrant flowers)
(We came to Hangang Park to ride a bicycle.)
(A rider sets out along the flower-lined path.)
Eun Woo, you're so good at that.
(It's a piece of cake for a kindergartener.)
Seriously. You're so good.
(The weather is great, and so is his mood.)
Eun Woo. We should let Jung Woo ride it too.
(Me? On a bicycle?)
Tell Eun Woo you want to try riding it.
Go ahead. Get on the bicycle.
(Jung Woo will try riding a bicycle for the first time.)
Get on it.
(He wears a helmet for safety.)
All right. Get ready. Go ahead.
Go.
(A balance bike)
Go ahead. Do you think you can move forward?
(A pedal-free bicycle designed to develop a sense of balance)
Go ahead. Come on, try it. I'll push you.
I'll push you. Go ahead.
(It's 24-month-old Jung Woo's 1st time riding a bicycle.)
Do you think you can do it? Go ahead. That's it.
(Wiggling along)
Hey, you're good at this.
(I'm Kim Jung Woo.)
Look.
You're so good at this.
(This is a piece of cake for me, Kim Jung Woo.)
I thought you couldn't do it.
(Jun Ho's hands are there to catch him just in case.)
(He hasn't even taught Jung Woo how to ride it yet.)
Who taught you to ride it like this?
(He naturally learns how to ride the bicycle on his own.)
You're good.
That's it. There you go.
(Don't forget who I am!)
(Jung Woo, is it fun?)
There you go.
(Why are you making Jung Woo practice riding the bicycle?)
We came to the Han River for a reason.
We participated in Hyo Marathon in Hwaseong a year ago.
(A year ago, 3 generations of the Kims...)
(participated in the Hyo Marathon.)
(He pushed the Woo Brother's stroller at the marathon...)
- You got this. - I got this.
(even though it was already tough without the boys.)
Dad. You take over. I'm tired.
(The 3 generations of the Kims relied on each other...)
Give it to me. Keep up with me.
(and finished the marathon.)
This time, we'll try out...
for the cycling event of the Hangang Triathlon Festival.
(There are about 30,000 participants.)
(Running)
(Cycling)
(Swimming)
(MY PACE Hangang Triathlon Festival)
(This festival is held in Seoul every year.)
It's the very first Hangang Triathlon Festival.
(It's a representative health-related festival in Seoul...)
I hope you can thoroughly enjoy the Han River today.
(where participants can enjoy other various cultural programs.)
(Let's go and enjoy the festival.)
(Ho Woo Father and Sons will participate in cycling.)
Get in the back.
I'll ride the bicycle and pull you guys.
Dad, you can do it
(Do you remember the Song Kook Train from 2014?)
You have us cheering for you
Let's go.
(It's been over 10 years, since it's 2025.)
- You can do this. - You can do this.
I'm going to ride 10km on my bicycle with my boys.
(He'll try out for the beginner's course...)
(which is a round trip of 10km.)
Great. Let's give it a try. Okay?
It's fine as long as we don't give up.
Put on the sunglasses just like me.
(The Woo Brothers put on the sunglasses too.)
It's too sunny for your eyes. Put them on.
If you're uncomfortable or want to stop,
shake this.
But only shake it when there's an emergency.
(They have bells to call their dad in case of an emergency.)
All right. I'm going to do my best.
- "An Unbreakable Heart." - "An Unbreakable Heart."
That's it. It's all about staying strong.
Go.
(The starting line of the 10km cycling)
Let's go now.
Yes, shall we get started now?
(Dad, you can do it!)
- You got this. - I got this.
(The cyclists set out at their own pace.)
(Filming took place after all the participants had left.)
Let's go.
Dad, hurry up. Let's go.
Go.
(Dad, let's go!)
Eun Woo. Jung Woo. Here's the thing.
We're not supposed to go fast. The key is to take it easy.
(It's not a competition.)
(You'll get hurt. Don't overdo it.)
(It's a festival meant to be enjoyed at their own relaxed pace.)
(People of all ages and genders can join and have fun.)
(Let's take it easy.)
Gosh, there's a boat.
(I'll enjoy the relaxing time.)
Dad, there's an ocean.
It's an ocean.
Gosh, it's an ocean.
(I love the ocean.)
Gosh, it's a butterfly.
(Nice to meet you, butterfly.)
(Spotting a butterfly)
It's a butterfly.
(Jung Woo kicks back and enjoys the festival to the fullest.)
(Exhaling)
Let me know if I'm going too fast.
(But the former national athlete can't take it easy.)
You can't stop me from going
Life is all about going straight
There are no U-turns
You look handsome.
- Hello, Eun Woo. Oh, my. - Hello.
Good luck, Superman.
Thank you.
- You can do this. - I can do this.
(Ho Woo Father and Sons are super popular.)
You got this.
(After seeing how popular they are...)
(Making fists)
(Vroom)
(Is Eun Woo driving?)
(Please move.)
Please move.
(Here I come.)
Here I come.
Turn it harder. Turn left. That's it.
(Gentle Kim is no stranger to the wheel.)
Use your power to turn it.
(I remember that day.)
(Making a left turn and a right turn)
(Honking)
(He even honks now.)
(He enjoys the remote driving from the backseat.)
(The three of them are enjoying the ride in their own ways.)
Gosh, it's an ocean.
What? This is an uphill path.
(He sees an incline 2km into the race.)
(Let's do this.)
(Doing his best)
(Song Kook Train was in Songdo.)
Let's go.
(Along the Han River, we have the Ho Woo Train.)
(Exhaling)
(The weight of the trailer: 10kg, Eun Woo's weight: 17kg, )
(Jung Woo's weight: 13kg)
(The head of the family must carry 40kg in total.)
Eun Woo. Jung Woo.
I'm doing a 10km race while pulling both of you.
(Feeling sentimental)
Don't forget this when you grow up.
There's a Tyrannosaurus.
(Roaring)
It's blocking the sun and the wind.
There's a Tyrannosaurus.
(A happy moment for the Woo Brothers without paying attention to Jun Ho)
(Feeling bitter)
There's a Tyrannosaurus.
(They are in two different worlds.)
(Eun Woo grabs the water bottle.)
If you're uncomfortable or want to stop,
shake this.
(Ringing)
(What's bothering you, Eun Woo?)
What is it? Should I go faster?
Should I go faster?
(Faster?)
(Sounds good! Ring Ring!)
Faster!
(Go faster!)
Go faster.
- Go faster. - Okay. I'll go faster.
It's getting faster.
- Faster? - You got this.
(Let's go, Dad!)
It's Seongsu Bridge.
(Seongsu Bridge comes into view in the distance.)
Seriously.
(As he cycles diligently, )
(he's already at the halfway point.)
This is the halfway point.
(He has completed 5km out of 10km course.)
(Halfway point: 5km)
(They head back to the starting point.)
We're turning back now.
(Once they make it back, their course is complete.)
You got this.
(He continues to cycle...)
Thank you.
(and cheers for his fellow participants.)
- You got this. - Okay.
(He easily crushes the uphill path.)
(Thanks to that, his mood improves.)
My gosh, the weather is amazing.
(He overtakes other participants again and again.)
Coming through.
(Dad wanted to say this too.)
I always wanted to say that. "Coming through."
(Showing his boyish side.)
When you guys grow up, I'll sit in the back...
(I'm pulling you guys now, )
(but you two must pull me later, okay?)
and you'll pull me along. Okay?
(Showing no response)
(Snoring)
(He's sleeping soundly as he snores away.)
(Feeling betrayed)
Jung Woo is sleeping.
(He treats the ringing bell as a lullaby.)
Sure. You guys can go in front of me.
(He can't keep his eyes open.)
(Coming to think of it, during the Hyo Marathon last year...)
(Gosh, I'm getting sleepy.)
(Even then, he slept deeply.)
We can do this.
I can't even breathe.
(Jung Woo fell asleep again.)
Sure. Go ahead.
(Sleeping soundly with the water bottle in his hands)
Bye.
(He sleeps like a log whenever he holds something.)
(An essential item for Jung Woo to get good-quality sleep)
(He's holding yet another water bottle today.)
Bye.
(This temperature, humidity, and wind...)
(are perfect for sleeping well.)
(Loosening his grip)
(Securing the water bottle)
(He grabs his favorite water bottle and goes back to sleep.)
(Jun Ho picks up the speed for the last section.)
(Should I push myself all the way now?)
(Dad, going fast is great and all.)
(Ringing)
Jung Woo, you're up?
(Glancing over)
(Pulling Jung Woo's face toward his shoulder)
(It's okay, Jung Woo.)
(Holding his hand tightly)
(I'm going to protect my brother.)
(He continues to look at Jung Woo.)
(Taking care of Jung Woo up close)
(Eun Woo is the best brother.)
(Everyone rode slowly at their pace, except for Jun Ho.)
We have 1km left to go.
Go, Unbreakable Heart.
(He completes the 10km cycling course!)
We're here.
Eun Woo. Jung Woo. How was this cycling race?
(They look like they had a good sleep.)
- It was fun. - It was fun?
(Great job, Dad.)
(Since they finished the course, they ought to get a medal.)
(The Woo Brothers receive medals for completing the course too.)
Eun Woo. You did it. You finished the course.
I'll give it to you too, Jung Woo. There's one for you too.
Jung Woo.
(It's a small, yet important moment of achievement.)
Who wants to put it around my neck?
- Me. - Why don't you do it for me?
Put it around my neck.
(Jung Woo gives a medal to Jun Ho.)
Mine.
(Wrapped around his head)
(Yellow is his personal color.)
Say, "Bring it on."
(Doesn't it look great on me?)
"Bring it on."
(Taking it off on his own)
(You put it on too.)
(Should I try it on too?)
(Any headband looks great on Eun Woo.)
(Baby Eun Woo used to be adorably chubby.)
(Eun Woo is all grown up now!)
Hold up the medal.
(Everyone holds up the medal.)
Hold up the medal like this.
(Look forward to our next challenge too!)
(After completing the Hangang Triathlon Festival...)
Eun Woo. Jung Woo.
Look.
Aren't you curious about what's in the pot?
(Ho Woo Father and Sons are in the kitchen.)
(There's a steaming pot on the table.)
Come here. Who wants to look?
(A mysterious large steamer)
Look.
We're going to look now.
I'll show you what's inside.
(What's in the first pot?)
- One. - Two,
- three. - Three.
Look at this, Eun Woo. There are so many shrimps in it.
(Steamed seafood with the fresh aroma of the ocean)
(Shrimps, mussels, corn, pine-cone-shaped squids, )
(razor shells, scallops, and more)
Look at this. It's a shrimp.
- The shrimp looks good. - Does it look good?
(I want to eat it now.)
It looks tasty.
(This time, they'll check out the other pot.)
All right. Let's check the other pot.
(There's more food?)
One,
- two... - Two.
(I can't be more patient.)
Let's see.
- Three. - Three.
(I wonder what's in it.)
- Three. - Look at this.
- Gosh, it's hot. - What is this?
- It's huge. - It's huge, isn't it?
(What's this big thing that's steaming in the pot?)
- Two, three. - Three.
- Three. - Look at this.
(The king of crustaceans, king crabs)
(Here's a king crab, loaded with juicy white meat...)
(and perfect for the Woo Brothers who love to eat.)
- Have you seen something like this? - Yes.
Where?
- Yes. - Yes.
(You've seen a king crab before?)
Right here.
(Jung Woo gives a wise answer.)
I see. Here?
(How adorable)
Look at this. I'll lift it.
It's too hot. I can't hold it.
Close it.
- Dad. - Yes?
Close the lid.
It's hot.
- Ji Woo... - Sit back down. It's hot.
(The two sit back at peace.)
- Ji Woo... - I'll sit down.
Look. I'll lift it for you.
- Look at this. - A blue crab?
(It's...)
A blue crab?
It's huge.
(humongous.)
- It smells... - How does it smell?
It smells like a blue crab.
How does this crab smell? Smell it.
- Does it smell tasty? - It smells tasty.
(It smells tasty too.)
It smells tasty, right? Look.
(Is this our dinner today?)
Does it look tasty?
But the corn...
(Twerking with excitement)
(Even his bottom can't hide how happy he is.)
Okay. I'll prepare the king crab, shrimps, and clams for you.
(I'll cook delicious dishes...)
(with the king crab and seafood.)
I'll make them tastier for you.
- Okay. - Who wants to eat that?
(Eun Woo and Jung Woo. The Woo Brothers want to eat.)
- Me. - Me too.
You too, Jung Woo? Okay.
Look at this. Check this out.
(Boys, wait for it. This will be legendary.)
Gosh, that's a lot of food.
- Jung Woo. - I...
You can stuff yourself with clams today.
I like clams.
I like corn.
Eun Woo, you like corn.
Jung Woo likes broccoli too.
(What kind of dish will seafood and hardy vegetables make?)
Hold on. I'll make them tastier for you.
(During their trip to Macau, )
During our trip in Macau,
(Jung Woo came to love clams.)
Jung Woo became hooked on clams.
- Give me more clams. - What? My gosh.
- I want more clams. - Clams?
(Jung Woo has become a seafood lover now.)
Look at Jung Woo. He can eat clams now.
He really likes clams. I think he likes seafood.
- What about you, Eun Woo? - Potatoes.
(Give me potatoes.)
Potatoes.
(On the other hand, Eun Woo prefers potatoes to meat.)
The meat is the main dish. You should have some meat.
(A potato lover)
How did you do that?
(Hardy vegetables are Eun Woo's favorite type of food.)
Today, I prepared potato and corn that Eun Woo likes...
(Potatoes and corn are Eun Woo's favorites.)
and seafood that Jung Woo likes.
(What is the seafood dish that they can all enjoy together?)
I made boiling crab which has all those ingredients they like.
(Boiling crab, the American-style braised seafood)
(Hawaii's specialty, boiling crab is a dish made by braising seafood...)
(such as lobster, crab, and shrimp with potato, corn, and sausage...)
(and mixing them with Cajun sauce.)
(The key point is to mix everything in a plastic bag.)
(Just like Eun Woo and Jung Woo, the ingredients harmonize greatly.)
Watch this. I'm going to pour the sauce now.
(Shall we make the sauce now?)
Eun Woo, you go first. Here. Squeeze it out. Go on.
(Eun Woo will add ketchup first.)
You should spin it in a circle. That's good. Keep going.
(Spinning it in a circle)
(He spreads it evenly to make it delicious.)
(He puts in a lot of sauce as a sauce lover.)
I want to try it too.
- I want to try squeezing it out. - Add just a little bit of this.
It's lemon juice.
(The sauce Jung Woo will add is lemon juice.)
- Lemon juice. - You're done, right?
I prepared this because you two like a refreshing flavour.
(Even when he tasted double-strength vinegar, )
I'll wash it for you.
(Eun Woo didn't even budge.)
What? My gosh. Eun Woo is incredible.
(Chef Jung Ji Sun from "Culinary Class Wars" approved.)
Even some adults can't eat lemon.
- He took me by surprise. - It's delicious.
(The sour taste prodigy, Kim Jung Woo)
- Jung Woo surprised me. - Really?
I saw Jung Woo eating the lemon, which surprised me even more.
(For the Woo Brothers, who love sour food...)
I prepared this because you two like a refreshing flavour.
(They add ketchup and lemon juice.)
(Sweet chili sauce is the cherry on top.)
You can stop now. You should put in just a bit at a time.
Make sure to put in just a little bit, okay?
Become delicious.
- Become delicious. - Right. Become delicious.
(Next, put everything in a plastic bag.)
(Then mix the ingredients with the sauce evenly.)
Eun Woo, this dish is called boiling crab.
(Actually, boiling crab...)
(is a nostalgic dish they enjoyed on their honeymoon.)
Your mom and I had this on our honeymoon.
It's really tasty.
I'll make it delicious.
(That's why I prepared this for the Woo Brothers.)
Eun Woo and Jung Woo, this is...
(And there's a man who's watching it.)
It's really tasty. I'll make it delicious.
(Sentimental)
Is it "I'll cut the rice cake while you write letters?"
(In front of food, )
(this man always waits.)
It's "While you draw." That's why I brought you this.
(I can wait.)
(As Dad works hard to cook, )
(I can wait while swallowing my saliva.)
Your mom and I had this on our honeymoon.
(I'm waiting for the food to be ready as always.)
It's really tasty.
(Meanwhile, Jung Woo...)
Oh, my. I have knives here.
(Here it comes! The double hand skill)
(I can't wait.)
- Dad! - Yes?
Wait just a little while. I'll hurry up and finish it.
(Adding the king crab to the mixture.)
It's done.
You saw the large crab, right? The king crab.
(The boiling king crab looks magnificent.)
That's the last ingredient to add to the dish.
I'm sorry,
(With a friendly tone, they said something that wasn't friendly.)
- but I'll enjoy eating you. - It has cooled down.
I'll enjoy eating you.
All right. We're sorry to the crab, but let's enjoy eating it.
(He goes for the shrimp first.)
Who wants to eat this shrimp?
I'll eat it.
It's good.
"It's good."
(Will the 24-month-old food lover open a clam by himself?)
Peel this for me, please.
(Shucking is Jun Ho's job.)
Where is your plate?
All right. I'll put this here.
(He keeps opening his mouth to eat.)
Move your hand.
(Jun Ho puts a single clam on his plate.)
(Is he drinking the clam?)
Why are you eating it in a hard way?
You have a fork here, and...
Jung Woo...
(How this man eats food)
Why are you eating it in a hard way? You have a fork here, and...
(Kissing his plate?)
Jung Woo...
Why didn't you use the fork? You only had one clam.
(Clams taste best when eaten this way.)
Were you drinking soup or something?
I want more clams. I want to eat clams.
(Jung Woo keeps showing his love for clams.)
- Here. Put this on. - Clams.
Sit straight.
(I'm ready.)
(Clams are delicious as always.)
- Watch this. With this hammer... - Peel another one, please.
What do you want to eat now? Another clam?
You should hit it hard.
(Next up is...)
(I want to eat it.)
Dad, show me a crab leg, please.
- Okay. I'll show you now. - A crab leg.
(Jung Woo looks curious. If you break a king crab leg, )
I broke it. Look at this.
Yes.
(you can pull the plump meat out.)
Try this.
- Dad, have this with the sauce. - Yes?
(Sweet Eun Woo)
- Can I try it first? - Yes.
(Touched)
Thank you.
(Eun Woo always gives his dad food before he starts eating.)
(And Jung Woo watched Eun Woo doing that up close.)
Jung Woo, are you giving it to me too?
- Dad, you have this. - Really?
(Maybe he touched Jun Ho's heart during their trip to Macau...)
Yes.
- Dad, have this with the sauce. - Yes?
(because he learned how to be considerate of others from Eun Woo.)
Thank you.
(Thanks to Eun Woo, Jun Ho finally has his first bite.)
- Yes. - Thank you.
(His mouth opens as his dad's opens.)
(Desperate)
(Jun Ho meets his eyes.)
(Give me that! Give it to me!)
I'll give you some.
- I want to try it too. - Do you want to try this?
- I'll eat this too. - I want it too.
(Jung Woo, look at the king crab.)
Here. Look at this, Jung Woo.
Oh, my.
It's scary. It looks like a monster.
(So aren't you going to eat it?)
Jung Woo.
Are you ready?
I'll enjoy eating you.
(Sweet and scary)
(Biting)
How does the monster taste?
It's delicious.
(His first impression of the king crab is good.)
The monster tastes good, right?
Do you want to hold it by yourself?
- Okay. - Here.
(Once again)
I'll enjoy eating you.
(Laughing)
Good. Enjoy.
(A frown of sincerity)
(He's eating it with gusto.)
All right.
(Munching on it while holding it with both hands)
It's too big. Please cut it for me.
You peeled it nicely.
(Jung Woo looks like a plump fish in season that's biting the bait.)
Oh, my. Jung Woo can eat a king crab now.
(I won't miss the crab meat on my chin either.)
Is it good?
(He eats the remaining crab meat using both hands.)
Jung Woo will probably eat all the king crab.
I want to eat some more.
All right. I'll give you some more.
Look at this.
(Out of the 8 legs, )
There's no leg left. You ate them all.
(he ate 7.)
(King crab legs are so delicious.)
(Paunchy belly)
Give me nothing else but the king crab.
(Clams are delicious too.)
(But King Jung Woo's choice is the king crab.)
(Glancing)
You're in your usual position now.
(Chairman Kim Jung Woo is here.)
- No, I'm not. - "No, I'm not."
(Swaying his heel back and forth)
(For Jung Woo, this is the paradise.)
(It's warm here, and I'm full. It feels good.)
(While Jung Woo is finishing the king crab...)
- We have no king crab left. - Okay.
- You ate it all. - Okay.
Eun Woo, will you eat the king crab or clams?
I want to eat corn...
- I want to eat corn... - Do you want to try this?
- with the sauce. I want corn. - Corn?
Here. Try this corn.
- I'll eat the corn with the sauce. - I'll do it for you.
I think I know how to do this now.
(Eun Woo dips the corn in a lot of ketchup.)
I've gotten the hang of it.
(He takes a big bite.)
(It's yummy.)
(Giggling)
(Ketchup)
(Corn with ketchup is irresistible.)
This soy sauce is 15 years old.
(A 15-year-old seed soy sauce)
(The saltiness of it surprised Jun Ho.)
Is it too salty?
(But when Eun Woo tasted the 15-year-old soy sauce...)
Try it.
It's delicious.
(He couldn't stop reaching for the soy sauce.)
- Did you dip it in the sauce? - Yes, I did.
(Sauce Prince Kim Eun Woo)
He must like the sauce.
Is it good?
(He finished the corn and the sauce.)
The corn is so good.
"The corn is so good."
Jung Woo, did you enjoy the food?
- I ate the king crab legs. - Yes.
- And I ate the white legs too. - What? Okay.
Did you? Did you enjoy the food?
(Anyway, I enjoyed the food.)
Yes!
During our trip to Macau,
Jung Woo fell in love with clams.
Now that he's tried king crab,
I'm thinking about what seafood I should prepare for him next time.
(He's already worried about the next seafood to serve.)
(What should we do after eating?)
Come here.
Let's do a facial using cucumbers.
On a hot day like this, you need to massage your face with soothing gel.
(Last summer, they hydrated their skin with a skincare product.)
There are red spots on your face.
You should cool your skin down with soothing gel.
(Today, they'll hydrate their skin with a cucumber.)
- Dad, the cucumber is too cold. - Yes?
We're not going to eat this.
We'll use it to soothe our skin.
(Don't eat it. Put it on your skin.)
Look at this. It slices the cucumber like a pencil sharpener, right?
I want to eat some.
(What?)
(He chewed...)
(and tore it.)
(The number of king crab legs he ate)
(Out of the 8 legs, )
(he ate 7.)
(It's only been 10 minutes since he ate the king crabs.)
(Paunchy belly)
I want to taste it.
(Just once. I'll just taste it.)
(Just eat it once then.)
Just once, then.
Okay.
(Opening his mouth)
(He becomes playful.)
(Acting cute for survival)
I love you. Heart.
I never told you to do that.
(I never told you to act cute.)
(Hurry up.)
(Just give it to me when I say, "I love you. Heart.")
I love you. Heart.
I never told you to do that.
(Being annoying)
(A hard-earned bite)
How is it?
(Eun Woo is eating behind his back.)
(I want to hold it and eat it.)
Jung Woo as well.
Stop eating, guys.
(I don't know what we're doing, but let's eat first.)
"Don't eat. Give it to the skin."
Don't you know that saying?
Look.
(Why are you sticking the cucumber on your face?)
What are you doing?
You're silly.
(I can't believe you're sticking the cucumber on your face!)
Why am I silly?
(This is how you take care of your skin.)
You stay like this.
How do I look, Jung Woo?
You're silly.
- I'm not silly. - You're silly.
(Lie down. Let me do it for you.)
Come here. I'll do it for you.
Lie down.
(Our dad is a bit weird.)
I don't want to stick it on my face.
(I'll give it to my stomach.)
(Only Jun Ho was happy with the cucumber pack.)
(Next up after the skincare)
This is how you do it.
That's right. That's how you do it.
(Would you massage me as well?)
Do it to me.
(The cards Eun Woo prepared with love)
Massage.
(The 5 coupons for Dad)
(5-minute massage)
I'm going to use it today. Okay?
(He's going to use it for the first time.)
This is how you do it.
(Oh, do you know how to do it?)
That's right. That's how you do it.
This is how you do it.
(I'm good at massaging, right?)
That's right. That's how you do it.
(Would you massage me as well?)
Do it to me.
Not you. Massage me.
(That's right! Dad worked hard today.)
(Exhaling)
(He carried 40kg on his own.)
(He went uphill.)
What's important is having an unbreakable heart!
(He cycled 10km in the heat.)
Passing through.
Lie down, Dad.
I'll do it for you.
I'll do it too.
- Do it. - This is how you do it.
(The Woo Brothers' massage place is open.)
That's right. Do it.
(He can't believe the Woo Brothers are massaging him.)
How nice. It's so nice.
I'm happy you're massaging me.
(Massage his left leg, Jung Woo!)
Massage this leg, Jung Woo.
That's right.
(They each massage one leg.)
You can massage one leg each.
- It's done! - Already?
It's done!
Already?
Like this.
(The massage ended as soon as it began.)
You can massage one leg each.
- It's done! - Already?
This time,
it's the tongs.
How do you use that?
(Feeling anxious)
Tongs.
(They massage his legs using a face massager.)
This time, it's the tongs.
(Eun Woo reinterpreted massaging in his own style.)
Keep going.
That's right.
(He's getting a facial massage.)
(Just what he learned from Dad)
Don't do that.
(From head...)
(to toe)
(I'm touched, Eun Woo.)
It's refreshing.
(Eun Woo isn't good but he does his best.)
That's right.
Eun Woo is the best.
(But where is Jung Woo?)
(Jung Woo is massaging the floor.)
It's going.
The back as well.
It was done.
Eun Woo is the best. There you go.
This is me.
(Is it my turn now?)
- Really? - Yes.
Hurry and go on. It's time for the neck.
- I'll cut your hair. - Okay.
(It suddenly became a hair salon.)
Snip.
(Jung Woo cuts Dad's hair.)
(Eun Woo does the styling.)
Close your eyes.
You don't need to do my hair.
(This isn't the hairdresser's.)
I couldn't tell if it was a massage...
or if I was playing with them.
(The Woo Brothers don't even know what a massage is.)
I don't think they know the purpose of massages,
but they tried to do something for me.
(He was just happy that they were trying it for him.)
That was cute, and I was thankful.
(The 5-minute massage doesn't end.)
Why are you so interested in my head?
This is for the calf.
(Let me massage your eye.)
I don't want this.
That's for the calf.
(Don't use the massager for other purposes.)
That's for the calf, Jung Woo.
(Stop now.)
This isn't for the head.
(He switches to coach mode when it's time to discipline.)
(When I hit you with it, does it hurt or not?)
Does this hurt or not?
(Pouting)
(Are you crying, Kim Jung Woo?)
Does this hurt or not?
(Sobbing)
(Kim Jung Woo, the gentle baby since birth)
(He didn't cry when he saw a tiger.)
Say hi.
(He was calm even at the sound of clippers.)
(Even when he fell down, )
(Jung Woo never lost his smile.)
Put this on.
Does this hurt or not?
(He's about to cry.)
- Here. - Wait. He's about to cry.
Wait. He's about to cry.
(I'm in trouble! Jung Woo is about to cry.)
Jung Woo is about to cry.
Go home, Dad.
- Dad. - That's for me?
(He shared his favorite food with him...)
- Eat this, Dad. - Really?
Yes.
(and kissed him on both cheeks.)
- This side too. - This side as well?
- Really? - Yes.
(The person who Jung Woo loved most)
Who is the person you love most in the world?
(Dad)
- Dad! - It's Dad, right?
Dad.
(I don't want to see you.)
Go home, Dad.
This is my home.
(If this is your home...)
- Home. - This is my home.
- Dad. - It's Dad's home.
Go outside, Dad.
(Laughing)
Okay, Jung Woo. I'm sorry.
Come here. I'm sorry.
Let's make up.
(Hug Dad.)
Come and hug me.
- I love you. - I love you.
Pat.
(They pat each other in reconciliation.)
Let's get along well.
(Let's get along well.)
Okay?
- I love you. Heart. - Kisses.
(Kissing)
That's right.
This side as well? Good.
(They make up after kissing on both cheeks.)
(Let's get along well this summer as well, Eun Woo and Jung Woo.)
Let's get along well too, Eun Woo.
Okay?
(The Return of Superman)
(Ji Woo's transformation is never a crime.)
(Where is she getting her hair done?)
(Rolling)
It's done.
(A vegetable garden?)
(Why is there a hair salon here?)
What's this?
(The director's recommended hairstyles)
- You have the hairstyle designs. - Of course.
We're a professional salon.
(The vegetable garden hair salon has everything you need.)
I'm a hairdresser!
This is a hair salon.
(A perfect site with mountains behind and water in front)
Congratulations on opening your salon.
(A vegetable garden hair salon opened in Wonju.)
(Hello. Thank you for visiting us.)
Hello.
This is a hair salon.
(Designer Jang, the director of the vegetable garden hair salon)
I'm the hairdresser, Jang Dong Min.
- Nice to meet you. - What's that necklace?
My mother sponsored it.
(Dong Min's mother sponsored the necklace.)
This is our shampoo room.
(Where is this place?)
It's a state-of-the-art shampoo room.
(A state-of-the-art rubber basin shampoo room)
What do you think?
(It'll be hard to rinse her hair.)
- A basin? - You won't be able to rinse it.
- You just have to put her head in. - How...
(I'll start shampooing your hair.)
It's old-fashioned. The analogue style.
- How is it? Is it warm? - Yes.
We have a good water heating system.
(The vegetable garden hair salon has an excellent hot water system.)
(She enjoys the time under the natural sunlight.)
It looks beautiful.
What does? The sky?
(You can see the sky in Wonju as well.)
She looked at the sky and said it looked beautiful?
A hair salon where you can see the sky. How nice is that?
Please don't make it sting my eyes.
Okay. I have skills, so your eyes won't sting.
(Fortunately, he didn't dunk her head.)
I'll rinse your hair now.
(He rinses her hair.)
(He's done shampooing her hair.)
Let's see.
(They're ready now.)
Well done.
(Patting her hair)
(Before he starts, )
Let me take you to the chair.
(he checks her hair.)
Miss.
It seems like you've never had a haircut until now.
What hairstyle is this?
(Since Ji Woo and Si Woo were born, )
Until now, Ji Woo and Si Woo...
have never had a haircut since birth.
(they've never had a haircut.)
(As the children grow up, )
As Ji Woo and Si Woo grow up,
they'll ride bicycles, swim,
(he wants to be there for all of their firsts.)
and go inline skating too.
I want to do everything with them...
(So he happily tries something new with Ji Woo and Si Woo.)
and make it more fun than doing it with other people.
I want to do everything with them.
It would be meaningful.
(What kind of hairstyle would you like?)
How do you want your hair done?
I want it to look pretty.
(Breathing)
- I was a bit nervous. - Of course.
(Why is he sighing from the start?)
Actually, you're my first customer.
(It's his first time doing a perm for someone.)
I hope that's all right.
Doing perms or haircuts...
without proper training...
- might go wrong. - That's right.
So I learned how to perm.
- You learned it? - Yes.
(How long have you been learning how to do perms?)
How much did you learn?
I learned it from the hairdresser at the hair salon I go to...
(I've learned it for a whole 30 minutes!)
for 30 minutes.
What?
What's that?
(Just for 30 minutes?)
You learned how to perm and cut...
- for 30 minutes? - Yes.
And you're giving your child a perm?
Yes.
In my life,
(In Dong Min's life)
I've never learned anything for more than five minutes.
So investing 30 minutes...
(For a genius, do-it-all dad, spending 30 minutes learning it...)
is equivalent to putting my entire life into the task.
(means he's basically put his whole life into it!)
(He put his entire life into the task for 30 minutes.)
There you go. Yes.
(Dad with Golden Hands rolls the perm rods for the first time.)
- It isn't an easy task, right? - Seriously.
- Oh, my. - How did he roll it?
That's right.
(Since it was his first time, he ended up rolling it too loosely.)
You can see how bumpy it is. Despite that,
you're doing very well.
(To give Ji Woo a pretty hairstyle, )
That's right.
Roll it like this as you pull it.
(Dong Min invested the longest amount of time.)
(It's time for the actual work.)
Now, I'll begin.
(It's time for his life-devoted training to bear fruit!)
A mannequin is different...
- from a real person. - You're right.
(Extremely nervous)
- A person moves. - A person moves.
Sir,
did you begin perming my hair?
(He finally applies the perming solution.)
Yes, I began perming your hair.
- Apply the perming solution. - Yes.
(After brushing her hair)
Brush the hair.
- Yes. - Yes.
Actual hair is very different from a wig.
(What's different?)
What? What are you talking about?
- How is it different? - A wig...
A child's hair is very thin.
- It's thin and weak. - Yes, it's weak.
So it was much harder.
(Will he be able to overcome the unexpected challenge?)
Stay still.
The first perm rod is going in.
(Will he succeed in perming her hair?)
(He slowly rolls the perm rod.)
The hair needs to be tight. You need to pull it.
I rolled the first perm rod.
He rolled it well.
(The first one is rolled nice and tight.)
- Yes. He used the perm rod well. - Yes.
(Thanks to the initial success, Dong Min becomes less nervous.)
They can hear the bird sound.
Yes.
- Sir. - Yes?
I can hear a cuckoo's cry.
- She speaks so cutely. - Yes.
There are many cuckoos in the area.
- There are many beasts. - Beasts.
Cuckoo, come on out.
(Cuckoo, where are you?)
This must be the first hair salon where you can hear a cuckoo.
(I'm somewhere around here.)
What?
Sir,
a cat came as a customer.
Is that so?
- A cat as well? - Did a cat come as a customer?
(Is the next customer a cat?)
- My goodness. - I see.
That's right.
- A reservation. - It made a reservation.
- All right. - A cat came as a customer.
(The cat is the 1st customer on the waiting list.)
(Who is the customer who visited the vegetable garden hair salon?)
Hello.
- Is she a neighbouring grandma? - Yes.
Is this a hair salon?
Yes.
She heard about the place.
Baby, do you like it?
Grandma, this hair salon is good.
- Oh, my. She's incredible. - My goodness.
Ji Woo even promoted the hair salon.
(Promotion Fairy)
She did it for her dad.
Ma'am, do you want to get your hair done?
- Of course. - All right.
(I'd like to get my hair done.)
Ma'am, if you make a reservation,
(The vegetable garden hair salon is a 1-person shop...)
I'll give you a call.
(with a strict appointment-only policy.)
Okay.
She's actually making a reservation.
The entire neighbourhood participates in a comedy skit.
(Pretending to make a reservation)
I always tell you that this is "The Truman Show."
(Only those who are good at role-playing can live in Wonju.)
- She's my mom's friend. - I see.
- Thank you. - All right.
(Thank you for making the appointment.)
I'll be back.
Okay, ma'am. I'll call you.
- Okay. - Gosh.
- Grandma, bye. - Okay.
(The customer leaves after booking the appointment.)
The way she pretended to write was so funny.
- I know. - She was so funny.
I'm nearly done.
No, you aren't.
(He has just begun.)
The hair at the front hasn't been rolled.
(That's how it is in the service industry.)
That's how it is. "It's nearly done."
Ji Woo didn't complain once.
(For the VIP who has been waiting patiently, )
(he speeds it up.)
(Although he's a talented dad, it takes a long time.)
It took one and a half hours...
- to two hours. - It's so exhausting.
Even for adults, it's hard to wait for the perm.
(Big Ji Woo is the only one worried about Little Ji Woo.)
I'm exhausted.
- Since it's so boring, - I'm exhausted.
Adults look at their phones or TVs.
(We respect her patience.)
Becoming pretty...
(Ma'am, becoming pretty...)
requires time of patience.
(requires a time of patience.)
(Time of patience?)
It's very hard to be pretty.
(It's hard to become pretty.)
Is that so?
What do you think? Do you like it?
(I like it.)
Yes.
Until we use the perm neutralizer,
you need to wait 40 minutes in this state.
(Time of patience is 40 minutes.)
(If 30 minutes is like an entire life, )
What will she do while she waits?
(what can she do for 40 minutes?)
(Brushing)
- A doll. - She's playing with a doll.
How old are you?
Oh, I see.
(Ma'am, do you have a boyfriend?)
Do you have a boyfriend?
My goodness.
Ma'am, do you have a boyfriend?
(Of course, I do.)
- Yes. - Does she have one?
- Does she have one? - What's your boyfriend's name?
(Does she have a boyfriend?)
- Ha Min. - Who's Ha Min?
- Ha Min? - Yes.
Is he in your class at the daycare center?
(Her boyfriend is her classmate in the daycare center.)
Yes.
- Really? - Ha Min is in trouble now.
You should stop going to the daycare center.
(Laughing)
(Dad is upset.)
She hadn't said anything to me.
(The next process involves neutralizing the perming solution.)
(After 10 more minutes)
He's focused.
(The perm will be complete!)
(Did her very first perm go well?)
Let's see the final result.
(Will it be a success or a failure?)
- All right. - When it comes to a perm,
- result trumps process. - I can take them out, right?
Let's see how pretty your hair looks.
(It's his first attempt, so he can't guarantee the result.)
Let's see the result.
- I'm curious. - My goodness.
(Her dad did the work.)
My goodness.
(What will be the result of the first attempt to perm?)
Was the perm a success?
(Tight curls)
- I think it came out well. - It's a success.
- The curls are bouncy. - Yes.
(Tight curls and shine)
- The curls are bouncy. Good. - My goodness.
Good.
Bouncy.
(Ji Woo likes it too.)
They're bouncy, right?
What do you think? Do you like it?
- Do you? - They're bouncy.
- They're bouncy and curly. - My goodness.
(The side hair is curled nicely.)
They're bouncy.
- He rolled them well. - He rolled them well.
(The back of the hair is perfectly curled.)
I didn't expect this.
I'm excited right now.
Same here.
- "Same here." - Really?
It came out well.
(From the moment she said her first hello in June last year)
- Ji Woo. Two years old. - Two years old.
- Ji Woo likes ribbons. - Yes.
(She wore a ribbon when farming.)
- I go... - Ji Woo is known for ribbons.
(She wore a ribbon even during a comedy skit.)
To a daycare center.
- From Ji Woo to Ji Woo. - Yes.
(She always wore a ribbon.)
The blue ribbon from Aunt Ji Woo is her favourite to this day.
(She has had the same hairstyle for 1 year.)
(What's the result of the transformation?)
How pretty!
- Her hair is wavy. - It came out well.
Dad is the best.
- She looks cute with her hair down. - I know.
(Cute and natural style)
- What? - It came out well.
- My goodness. - My goodness.
(Feeling good)
Are you serious? She looks so pretty.
You did a good job.
- Do I look pretty? - My goodness.
(Who's the next customer at the vegetable garden hair salon?)
Won't you get a haircut?
- Si Woo, will you get it or not? - Si Woo?
(Ji Woo's brother, Si Woo)
- It was my son's turn. - Si Woo?
I'll give you a haircut.
(Shaking his hand)
He doesn't want it. He really doesn't want it.
Your sister got her hair done.
It came out so well.
(Dong Min puts him on the chair in a natural way.)
(He puts the gown over him.)
(Si Woo doesn't like it.)
Si Woo, don't you want the gown?
- Let's not use it. - What?
Let's not use it. Let's cut your hair without it.
(It's not easy from the beginning.)
It's okay if the hair goes in.
(The hair clipper has loud whirring sounds.)
It'll make sounds.
May I cut your hair now?
- The hair clipper sound. - Kids are scared of hair clippers.
(Previously, the others were afraid of the sound of the hair clipper.)
(Crying)
They don't like the sound.
(Whining)
Seriously. Children become scared at a hair salon.
(Many babies cried in the hair salon.)
(Will Si Woo be able to do well?)
(Crying)
Let's turn it on.
(Is it my time to step up?)
Si Woo, look at this. It shines.
Isn't it cool?
You can have it.
I mean,
- there's no sister like her. - Seriously.
(Look at this.)
Isn't it cool?
Gosh, Ji Woo is cool.
(She succeeds in catching Si Woo's attention!)
Si Woo, press the tail.
Si Woo only likes Ji Woo.
(As Ji Woo plays with him, )
He sits still if Ji Woo plays with him.
(Si Woo stays calm.)
He dotes on his sister.
(Dad is cutting his hair in the meantime.)
Jang Si Woo, you're sitting still in a dependable way.
Look at this, Jang Si Woo.
I brought this.
(Ji Woo is the best.)
- How cute. - What?
Isn't Dad cool?
Si Woo, look in the mirror.
Customer, what do you think of your new hair?
(Let me see.)
- She's the best assistant. - I know.
(He looks like he's about to dive into the mirror.)
- He's sitting still. - My goodness.
(Thanks to Ji Woo's help, Si Woo's first haircut goes well.)
You're doing great.
(He had baby hair in its natural state.)
Good.
- What? - He's young.
(I'm Jang Si Woo in the wild.)
- My goodness. - What?
(Si Woo is nearly unstoppable.)
He's a manly man.
(He falls many times, )
Gosh, he doesn't even cry.
- He doesn't mind falling down. - That's right.
(but he stands up without a tear.)
He's manly.
(That's who I am!)
(I'm a manly man!)
"I'm a manly man!"
- Success! - Success!
(Ji Woo and Si Woo get. a new hairstyle!)
(Well done!)
(What will Dong Min do next with Ji Woo and Si Woo?)
Today, I wanted to cook proper Chinese food...
(Dad will also transform...)
(to captivate Ji Woo and Si Woo!)
for Ji Woo and Si Woo.
So I turned into a chef.
(The multi-talented dad is back.)
What's this today? Will he cook Chinese food?
(Which dish will the multi-talented dad make?)
For today,
I'll make something children can eat well.
The first one is white jjamppong.
(Today's dish is white jjamppong, )
It looks so good. I'll have white jjamppong today.
(which is not spicy and has a clean taste.)
The next one is a luxurious dish. It's sweet and sour rockfish.
(The other dish is fancy...)
(sweet and sour rockfish.)
I failed when I tried making that dish on TV.
- It isn't easy to make. - It's a proper dish.
- Right? - I know.
(Meanwhile, the Woo Siblings are in the living room.)
Jang Si Woo, sit on a chair.
(Ji Woo is teaching Si Woo English!)
Ji Woo is teaching English to Si Woo.
What's this?
(What is "cow" in English?)
It's nice to see the two of them play together.
What's this?
(Nya)
(Nya?)
(Let's pass it for now.)
There's a language only the two of them use.
(What's the next English word?)
(What's "turtle" in English?)
What's this?
(Nya)
(She skips it again?)
He keeps going, "Nya." Is she skipping that?
(She's showing him English words, not teaching them.)
What's this?
(What's "spider" in English?)
(He says "Nya" the loudest.)
Ji Woo, you should give him the correct answer.
- All done. - All done.
(Will that be the end of the lesson?)
All done.
(What did Si Woo learn in the end?)
I guess Ji Woo wants to teach Si Woo English.
(In English, "cow" is...)
("Nya.")
(In English, "turtle" is also "Nya.")
("Nya" can be used for anything.)
- Everything is correct. - All done.
(It's okay to begin by looking.)
(My sister is the best!)
Let me tell you what that gesture means.
When Ji Woo was little,
she couldn't give a thumbs up for the best.
(He put up his index finger instead of his thumb!)
She put up this finger.
(Dad, you're the best.)
You're the best.
- I see. - They have a connection.
(The siblings even have the same gesture.)
(After the lesson, they come out to find Dad.)
Dad. I miss Dad.
She wants to see him.
(What are you doing, Dad?)
Do you miss your dad?
Jang Ji Woo! Jang Si Woo!
(We're going to cook together now.)
We're going to cook now.
Shazam, turn into chefs! Boom!
(Boom!)
Turn into chefs! Boom!
(The Woo Siblings become chefs.)
Chefs Ji Woo and Si Woo.
(The little chefs' first task: Clean the abalones)
These are abalones.
Brush them as if you're brushing your teeth.
(You should scrub it clean, like you're brushing teeth.)
With a toothbrush.
Get rid of the black things.
- Watch. Like this. - Let's brush every part.
(She's scrubbing it thoroughly like her dad.)
- Every part. - Let's brush every part.
- Brush it well. - Why is it moving?
They're still alive.
I bought fresh ones.
(Youngest chef, please join us.)
Si Woo, come here as well.
Jang Si Woo.
Would you brush them like me?
(I want to give it a try too.)
Si Woo joined.
Si Woo did it for the first time.
Sit next to Ji Woo.
Here. Si Woo, brush them as well.
(They sit together to help their dad.)
The black parts need to be gone.
(The Woo Siblings prepare abalones by themselves.)
Si Woo, do it like your sister.
(I don't know how to do it.)
- It's his first time... - That's right.
(Looking at her nervously)
- being an assistant. - Yes.
Si Woo, do it like me.
Abalone, hello.
(She greets it in a friendly way first.)
Oh, my.
(Don't be scared.)
I'll brush you.
Let's become clean.
- It needs to be brushed... - Yes.
- to be consumed later. - Come on.
(Ji Woo does as she is told even when Dad isn't present.)
(Is she really 35 months old?)
- She did well. - She washed them well.
(She prepared the abalones perfectly.)
She washed them well.
Look at it carefully. It's a rockfish.
(It's nice to meet you, Rockfish.)
Rockfish, hello.
(It's time to clean a rockfish!)
It's called a fish head.
Hey.
(Shouting)
Of course, it's scary.
(It startled me.)
She's startled.
(Did it startle you?)
What's this called?
(There's tension in the air.)
Rockfish.
(The rockfish thrashes vigorously.)
All right.
(Despite being startled, she laughs.)
- She finds it fun. - She's unfazed.
Rockfish, dance.
(One child can't laugh.)
(Nervous)
(He flinches every time the fish thrashes.)
- Si Woo. - He's startled.
I didn't know that.
- Si Woo froze. - Rockfish, dance.
(Si Woo is scared.)
He froze due to fear.
(Flapping)
Gosh.
(Crying)
- He's scared. - Si Woo is scared.
It's scary. Of course.
(Are you okay, Si Woo?)
It's natural for children to be scared.
(How will Ji Woo react?)
(Ji Woo is scared as well, right?)
Gosh.
How cool.
I want to dance as well.
("The Day I Want to Dance with the Flapping Rockfish...")
(by Poet Jang Ji Woo)
- She's something else. - My goodness.
(35-month-old Ji Woo has a way with words.)
It keeps flapping.
- What was that? - I think it's dancing.
(She's indeed a minstrel in The Return of Superman.)
- Okay. - Flap.
Flap, flap.
(To Ji Woo, it looks like the rockfish is dancing.)
- How is she so expressive? - It's dying.
Do the Rockfish Dance.
(The Rockfish Dance?)
(Flapping)
She's flapping like the fish.
(Rockfish, look at me.)
- There you go. - It's like the techno dance.
(Please grow up well.)
You're good.
(Ji Woo's new specialty, the Rockfish Dance)
How are Ji Woo's expressions so beautiful?
(Same blood, different reactions)
(They look just alike, though.)
Si Woo is scared.
Sit down.
(Crying)
He's scared. He's startled.
(I'm not doing the Rockfish Dance.)
It's dancing.
(It's the safest when I'm next to Ji Woo.)
- He went to his sister. - He's sitting next to her.
It fell asleep.
(Flapping)
(He needs to clean the rockfish.)
Look over there. It fell asleep.
Look over there.
Look over there. There's a tiger in the mountain.
(Did a tiger come?)
See where the tiger is.
- Look over there. - Will you put it out?
(During that time, rockfish passes away.)
(There is no tiger.)
(Feigning ignorance)
Rockfish, dance!
No. It won't dance now.
(It can't dance anymore.)
Rockfish can't dance anymore. It needs to be undressed.
This is rockfish's liver.
- Liver? - Yes.
(Dong Min takes out the rockfish liver.)
Liver.
(Ji Woo, are you going to...)
What about the liver?
I want to touch the liver.
Really? Touch it.
The texture is like...
(Does she want to touch the liver?)
- that of jelly. - She has no fear.
How is Ji Woo like that?
(A fearless girl)
Here. It's a liver.
- Liver? - Yes.
She said that she wanted to become a doctor.
(Is she going to touch it?)
She should touch things like that.
- It's a liver. - She's unhesitant.
(With dreams of becoming a doctor, she touches it without hesitation.)
Gosh, it looks like jelly.
(Liver looks like jelly.)
(She even said hello to the Japanese amberjack's head.)
It's nice to meet you like this. Hello.
(Despite being a 35-month-old, she's unrivaled.)
It's so big.
(Raw chicken, cow blood, intestines, trotter, )
(loach, octopus, eel, and more.)
Why are there so many trotters?
Seriously.
(She can even wash her face...)
(with the collagen water from the jokbal.)
(The sweet and scary Ji Woo)
(Calm)
- Dad, here. - Okay.
(My sister is incredible.)
- Say goodbye. - Liver, goodbye.
Okay.
You should rinse the tail too.
(She even bathes it at the end.)
She doesn't feel uncomfortable at all.
You need to score it...
(He cut slits to allow the marinade to absorb thoroughly.)
so that it cooks thoroughly.
I think I'll like it.
(The rockfish is prepared.)
Really?
(They're going to knead the noodle dough.)
All right. Shall we make the noodles now?
(They're going to make noodles by hand.)
I made the dough in advance.
- Press it like this. - Here.
(Ji Woo, Si Woo, let's do it together.)
Ji Woo, it's yours.
(They're going to make noodles by hand.)
Are you making hand-pulled noodles?
Dad, what will you make?
I'll make noodles.
(When will you have dinner?)
When will you eat dinner? The sun set.
- No, it's the next day. - Every time...
(It's the next day.)
Since we cook together,
children go, "I made this."
(They enjoy the food more when they make it.)
- They eat it with gusto. - Really?
(He's making noodles with Ji Woo and Si Woo.)
Dad, I'll put some flour on it.
(A handful of flour)
(Dong Ji Father and Daughter have the best teamwork.)
Thank you.
Dad, do you want a bit more?
(The hand-pulled noodles are coming along.)
Thank you.
(Who is this?)
- How cute. - Gosh, he's so cute.
Gosh, he's so cute.
(Grinning)
(While Dong Ji Father and Daughter worked on the dough)
Ji Woo, you aren't eating flour because you've grown up.
You can do it with flour.
(Applying...)
He put it on his face.
(blush)
All done?
(Si Woo became a snowman.)
It's like a tactile play.
(Staring)
Si Woo, shall we dust off your face?
My goodness.
(Hitting)
Is she hitting him?
It looks like she's hitting him.
(Sweet words, but not-so-sweet actions)
My goodness.
She learned from her dad.
(She learned how to hit from her dad.)
- She knows how to hit. - Seriously.
(Hitting)
(Come here. I'll do it for you!)
- My goodness. - It's uncooked flour.
(Can I try it now?)
That's right.
"This taste is..."
(The flour tastes good.)
He likes it.
(If you like it, raise your hand.)
- He finds it tasty. - He loves it.
- Si Woo, is it tasty? - Yes.
Make some noise if it's tasty.
(Screaming)
He understood his dad's words.
(The flour is delicious.)
(Staring)
When I was little,
I ate flour nonstop.
(While Dad was kneading the noodle dough, )
Ji Woo, you're still little.
(Ji Woo ate flour repeatedly at the age of 22 months.)
That's right. She ate a lot of flour.
(It brings back memories.)
Si Woo, are you eating flour like your sister?
I want to try some flour.
Really? Try it as you think about the past.
(I'm the original creator of the flour eating show!)
How is it?
Dad, it's tasty.
(Laughing)
- Is that so? - Is it tasty?
(You can tell that they're siblings.)
It must be very tasty.
(My children must be hungry!)
Ji Woo, I'll deep fry the rockfish now.
Rockfish, be careful.
Gosh.
Make sure your flesh doesn't fall off.
(Full of worries)
Rockfish, my friend. Be careful.
(My friend, don't get hurt!)
I should be careful, not the rockfish.
(Should Dad be careful?)
Dad, make sure you don't get it on your hands.
- Okay. - I'll wipe it.
(Ji Woo worries about Dad, though it's a bit late.)
She uses such nice words.
(The multi-talented dad makes it look easy.)
He's good. He isn't putting it in there right away.
(It's a dish that requires advanced Chinese cuisine skills.)
It isn't easy to do that.
(Dong Min pulled it off nicely as always.)
- You need to cook it thoroughly. - That's right.
That way, there won't be any unpleasant odour.
It's sizzling.
My goodness.
Gosh, children will love it.
(You can cook this dish at home?)
Look at the colours.
(Homemade sweet and sour rockfish)
It looks tasty.
(Full of abalones, a whole squid, shrimps, and other seafood)
The jjamppong contains a lot of seafood. Seriously.
(White jjamppong made with hand-pulled noodles and seafood)
- I added a whole squid. - It looks so tasty.
A round of applause.
It's complete.
Your brother is about to fall asleep.
(Si Woo is becoming one with the sofa.)
He became exhausted from waiting for dinner.
(I can't wait any longer. The wait was too long.)
He filled his stomach with flour.
(It's already dark night...)
He ate flour earlier. That's right.
(when they finally get to eat some food.)
He's downing baby formula.
He should down it. Yes.
Now, shall we try...
(Will we eat rockfish, our friend?)
the rockfish first?
Shall we try the rockfish first?
(Are we going to eat...)
(rockfish, our friend?)
How will it taste?
(She said hello to it...)
- Rockfish, hello. - Si Woo, you too.
(and danced with it.)
Gosh, it's the Rockfish Dance. Begin the Rockfish Dance.
Rockfish, my friend. Be careful.
(She became attached to the rockfish in a short time.)
Rockfish.
(She refuses to eat it.)
(How can I eat the rockfish?)
It's a friend.
Rockfish is food. It isn't a friend anymore.
(Will that work?)
- It isn't a friend anymore. - It isn't a friend.
(She learns about the cold law of the jungle from her dad.)
- It's food. - My goodness.
Isn't it a friend?
(She understands it right away.)
- No. - Is it food?
You can eat it.
It's so tasty. Open wide.
(How is the taste of rockfish, the fish that used to be a friend?)
Open wide.
- How is it? - How is it?
Your eyes went wide.
(This taste is...)
How is it?
It's good.
(There's no need to say. It's good!)
- Really? - She said, "It's good."
Her friend... I mean, rockfish must be tasty.
(Rockfish wasn't only good at dancing.)
(While they are inhaling the food, )
(Si Woo wakes up.)
(Aren't those the noodles I made?)
(Heave-ho)
(Si Woo gets down from the sofa.)
Can I eat?
- Yes. - Okay.
(Dad, how are the hand-pulled noodles I made?)
(Staring intently)
(Grabbing his collar)
(Dad, is it tasty?)
(Humming in approval)
(I'm glad you enjoy them.)
I'll give you an abalone too.
It's the best food I like, abalone.
(Ji Woo uses her chopsticks.)
- Abalone. - That's right.
I see that she likes abalones.
Can you pick up a piece of abalone with chopsticks?
My goodness.
(Abalone is slippery, but Ji Woo picks it up with ease.)
Can you pick up a piece of abalone with chopsticks?
She has always been good at using chopsticks.
(She started using chopsticks when she was 27 months old.)
Really?
(This 35-month-old mastered how to use chopsticks.)
Ji Woo is very smart.
(She picks up a shrimp...)
How does she pick up food by herself?
(and puts it in her mouth.)
(It's time to taste the hand-pulled noodle they made themselves.)
She doesn't eat the food my wife or I pick up.
- She tells us to put it down. - She wants to do it herself.
(Slurping)
- She's slurping the noodles. - Gosh.
She can slurp the noodles.
She can slurp the noodles better than me.
(Ji Woo, you're amazing.)
You can slurp the noodles.
(She picks up a noodle strand...)
(and slurps it.)
The white jjamppong must be tasty.
(Dong Min is proud of his daughter's eating show, )
It was nice to watch her eat with gusto.
(which makes him want to cook for her even more.)
- She's really enjoying it. - Seriously.
(She's the master of slurping noodles at this rate.)
- She's eating with gusto. - Yes.
My goodness.
This restaurant makes good food.
Really?
I'll come often.
(It has become Ji Woo's favorite place to visit again.)
Please come often.
(Please come often.)
Today, I opened a hair salon...
a well as a Chinese restaurant.
(How was everything that you've tried for the first time today?)
How was it?
It was the best day.
My goodness.
(Happy)
It was the best day for me too.
(Si Woo enjoyed the day too!)
Yes. Si Woo also thinks that it was the best.
He loved it.
(Proud)
So that my children will have the most amount of fun with me,
(Dong Min wants the kids to have the most fun with him.)
I want to do everything with them.
The dad,
(Dad will do all of your firsts together!)
Jang Dong Min's challenges will continue on.
(Although it's exhausting, we should go before the rain comes.)
My goodness. Let's go.
(The 4-member family will enjoy their 1st camping trip!)
(They say that you struggle when you leave home.)
There's a lot of items.
(Loading...)
(and loading again)
All right.
Camping trips are hard.
(Camping trips are hard.)
(He hammers for 30 minutes.)
In some parts of the inland, the daytime heat...
will bring up the temperature to 30C.
I could just picture it. There will be many struggles.
(Struggling alone is the way of the loyal servant.)
(Meanwhile, the other members are having a happy time.)
My goodness.
(Will Dad cook as well?)
What should I do first?
Honey, it's still moving.
(It's still moving.)
(Dad to the rescue!)
- No, it isn't. - No. It moved just now.
- What? - See?
(What?)
- It's moving. - At the bottom...
(Who is he talking to?)
(The opponent is a live lobster.)
I don't think it's necessary.
(The worried Coach Nam versus The Russian lobster)
In Seo.