[English subtitles are available.]
Our priority
is to repair the center
to protect students.
I agree.
How long will the restoration take?
The center is severely damaged.
I’m afraid we need Headmaster Ling Xi
to fix it.
OK.
I’ll go find her.
My respects,
Headmaster.
The Protection Circle is broken.
We need your help
to repair it, Headmaster.
[Headmaster Ling Xi  Headmaster of North Sect]
Are you a student?
Why are you wandering about at this hour?
What's wrong with your eyes?
I’m on my way back to the dorm.
My eyes are injured
so I’m temporarily blind
and can’t walk too fast.
What's your name?
Mu Chen.
It's you!
The Great Ruler
Episode 17
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Good.
She’ll be proud of you.
Jiu...Jiuyou.
Jiuyou.
Where are we?
I don't know.
I can’t sense anything
Nothing at all?
How can you still sleep?
We're imprisoned.
Did Black Dragon’s men do this?
Had it been them,
we’d have been dead by now.
You have a big heart.
I’ve lost my vision.
Without a big heart,
I’d kill myself already.
What the hell is this place?
I’ve never been here before.
Why do I feel
it’s a space in the formation?
There’s no center anywhere here.
Without it,
how was the formation created?
Am I wrong?
No way.
There must be places I neglected.
It might be on the wall.
Mu Chen.
You're just like her.
So stubborn.
Who are you?
And who is she?
What is this place?
You’ve figured it out already.
I created this space with my formation.
Although you can’t see me,
I’m everywhere.
It’s real!
Formations can
teleport people
from one place to another.
Why can’t they
create a new place?
Teleporting is
similar to overlapping two places.
To create a new one
is to build one within another.
Don’t stand still.
I asked Ye Sun’er to set up this Wind Formation
not to train your body.
Physiques do matter
but skills matter more.
I’m giving you a chance to practice
not to have yourself killed.
Can’t you dodge?
Not bad.
Thanks for your instruction.
I’m still not your match.
You’re progressing rapidly.
After some time, you’ll be as good as me.
You’re flattering me.
I only have more skills.
You're extremely talented.
Let’s call it a day.
I need to go.
The formation is broken.
Although it’s been fixed,
it’s not half as powerful as before.
Headmaster is restoring it
but it’ll take a few days.
Dragons won’t let go of this chance.
I have to go.
I want to go with you.
Really?
It’s the least I should do.
The Sect can provide you with maximum protection.
Once you’re out, your life will be on the line.
You’d better think twice.
No need.
I've made up my mind.
Fine.
Headmaster Ling Xi gave me this.
The badge holder
will automatically become part of the formation
and have free access to the sect.
She gave me two of them.
I believe
she wanted me
to find the right partner.
This badge is of great importance.
I’ll keep it well.
I trust you.
Thank you.
With great power
comes great responsibility to uphold justice.
You've failed
over 20 times tonight.
I can barely look at you now.
I’m starving.
When can I get out?
Maybe you did it wrong.
The key to maintaining a space
is stability.
By destabilizing it, we can get out.
It should work.
You’re too weak.
Let me try it.
Fire won’t break it.
You've tried that many times.
Something needs to be changed.
I don’t have enough power
to reach the third formation.
Maybe my method is wrong.
No.
It’s correct.
Does the problem lie in the overlapping?
Triple overlapping formation
requires not only power,
but also careful calculations.
All formations need to be well connected,
or the power will slip away quickly
and it’ll affect the overall stability,
leading to an explosion.
If all formations
can overlap each other completely...
I got it.
I’m back.
Thank you for enlightening me, ma'am.
You...
should call me teacher.
Teacher.
Come here.
Let me see your eyes.
The crux
seems to be in your veins.
It’s OK.
There’s still hope.
I’ll cure you at all costs.
Thank you.
Mu Chen.
She locked you up for so long.
Why did you thank her?
Jiuyou.
She was helping me.
Thanks to her, I’ve mastered complex formations.
Whatever.
You think everyone is good.
Jiuyou,
please take me to see Luo Li, OK?
No.
I remember
the last time when we were together like this,
you were only ten.
That’s right.
We practiced together when we were young.
You said sparring was the best way to improve,
so you challenged me every day.
You've become much stronger.
But not strong enough to defeat Xue Lingzi.
He’s reached the supreme level.
If he makes a surprise attack,
even I won’t be his match,
not to mention you.
Supreme level?
Given my speed,
it’ll take forever to catch up with him.
If I can’t beat him,
how am I supposed to protect my people?
I must speed up,
or it’ll be too late.
I've told you already.
You’re injured
and should rest for now.
But...
Relax.
I’m here to help.
Jiuyou.
Aren’t we going to see Luo Li?
Where are we now?
Don’t you know
I can only sense things around you?
I’m going to
where I’m most familiar with.
Mu Chen!
Where were you?
I was looking for you everywhere.
What’s wrong?
What happened?
Luo Li almost got caught.
Got caught?
Where?
By whom?
Xue Lingzi of the Xue God Clan.
He damaged the Protection Circle
to take Luo Li away.
Luckily, Shen Cangsheng arrived in time.
How could it be damaged?
Xue Lingzi disguised as a student
and destroyed the center in Mr. Zhu Tian’s room.
I don’t remember
hearing your voice before.
I’m new here.
What’s on your mind?
I might've met him.
Where is Luo Li?
In the arena.
I’ll take you there.
Let’s go.
Let me.
However many points you need,
I’ll get them for you.
Be careful.
Luo Li.
Mu Chen.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
I’m sorry.
It’s all my fault.
I did it willingly.
Don’t feel pressured.
My sight will be recovered soon.
You don’t need to fight anymore.
Are you going to see He Yao again?
He’s promised
to cure me.
I’d like to have a try.
No.
Luo Li.
What about you?
Me?
You need to rest.
Promise me
that you won’t challenge others again.
OK?
If I do that,
will you stop seeing He Yao?
I won’t stop you from seeing him for treatment,
but if he fails,
you have to let me continue.
Fine.
I’ll go with you to see him.
Mu Chen!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Don’t worry.
I’ve found a way to cure you.
Is it risky?
I won’t
stake a student’s life.
If you have doubts,
you shouldn’t bring him here.
Sir,
don't take it to heart.
Luo Li is concerned about me.
Never mind.
You can go back.
I’ll inform you once I’m ready.
The formation now is harder to break.
Leader,
let’s go ask Wen Qingxuan for help.
I don’t want to owe her.
Besides,
if Evil Deity finds out
that I took the liberty to come here,
I’m afraid...
Leader,
allow me to finish.
The North Sect is on high alert.
It’s almost impossible
to get Goddess
out of there.
And if Wen Qingxuan learns about this,
she won’t let it slide.
I have an idea.
Why don’t we offer
to cooperate with her first?
Evil Deity
will raid the North Sect sooner or later.
Then we can go with the flow
and assist him.
Let’s go.
Did the Protection Circle
disappear for a moment?
Yes.
By the time I arrived,
it had been restored.
I failed you.
Why bother coming back?
Yes, my lord.
Do you have a better idea?
I’m not sure if it’s better,
but Dragons and the North Sect are always enemies.
We’ve lost the edge.
Launching an attack
will only end up in vain.
I’m simply
trying to help Evil Deity.
You're using his power
to eliminate your enemy.
It’s nothing shameful.
No need to hide it.
But if you fail in your duty,
you’d better think of a way to explain it.
You’re ordered
to assist me.
Wen Qingxuan,
don't tell me what to do.
Can’t I?
What do you want?
Lord,
I’m only here
to help you.
We're on the same boat.
I have no reason to harm you.
If we succeed,
you’ll get the credit,
but if we fail,
you’ll have to take the responsibility.
You better think carefully
before making your decision.
After all,
I can’t tell you what to do.
Am I right,
Lord?
I have something urgent to report.
Speak.
Humans and gods
are forming an alliance.
How did you know that?
I was looking for my fiancée,
so
I disguised myself as a human
and sneaked into the North Sect.
I meant to bring my fiancée
back to my clan
but those humans
stopped me.
I had no choice
but to reveal my real identity and leave.
Xue Lingzi,
I ordered you to stay in your clan
and finish your tasks
but you disobeyed my order
and almost ruined my entire plan.
Sorry, my lord.
Although I left
to bring back my fiancée,
I managed to break the Protection Circle
in the North Sect.
You think I’d care about
such a child’s play?
I said it wrong.
Please punish me.
Forget it.
I’m not afraid of it,
but it might pose a threat
to others.
You did well.
I’ll forgive you.
Thank you for your kindness.
I’ll cooperate with Wen Qingxuan
to take over
the North Sect.
My lady.
Yes?
There’s a contracted beast inside Mu Chen.
It’s likely that they live and die together.
That beast is a Jiuyou bird.
Jiuyou
is an ancient sacred being Phoenix's descendant.
If we refine it into a pill
and present it to godfather,
he’ll gain the power of nirvana
and recover earlier.
Congratulations!
May your wish come true sooner.
You did well.
But
their contract is integrated into their blood.
Only by extracting
all Jiuyou’s pure power
can the pill be made.
Once the contract is broken off,
Mu Chen and Jiuyou will both die.
So
we only have one chance
to gain its power.
That’s indeed tricky.
Take this.
This is the Soul Erasing Spell.
It can remove veins in humans,
not to mention
a beast.
Thank you, my lady.
Sir,
Mu Chen is here.
Let him in.
Mr. He Yao.
This is my student Huo Feng.
Before you came,
he was the only student close to me.
Hello.
Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure is mine.
Today’s treatment is crucial.
After I begin,
no interruption is allowed.
You two may leave.
Yes.
The last phase is also the most painful one.
Bear with it.
Mu Chen!
Luo Li,
be patient.
Mu Chun is still under treatment.
Move!
This skill...
Mu Chen!
I said no interruption!
If the treatment is interrupted,
his veins will be severely damaged.
Mu Chen!
How do you feel?
What did you do?
Mu Chen!
Are you alright?
Luo Li.
I can see you again!
You can see me?
Thank you, Mr. He Yao.
The poison
is still in his system.
It's deep
in his bones.
I suppressed it temporarily
to restore his sight.
It takes time
to remove it completely.
Mu Chen.
Let’s go.
Luo Li.
you should apologize to Mr. He Yao.
Save it.
I don’t need that.
You still need to come every day for examination.
Yes.
He won’t come again.
The spell you cast is abnormal
and aggressive.
The color of your power is unusually blue.
It’s unnatural.
It's a secret spell.
Of course it’s different from others.
Luo Li.
I can see you
and Mr. He Yao.
His treatment worked.
Don’t be so paranoid.
Mu Chen.
The way he treated you is peculiar.
You...
Enough.
He’s treated me so many times.
If he wanted to harm me,
I wouldn’t have still been here.
I saw it myself.
Why don’t you believe me?
You once lied to me, didn’t you?
But I've never hurt you.
Mr. He Yao did this to help me.
Can you be reasonable?
Luo Li.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t mean that.
It's OK.
I get it.
Mr. He Yao.
I apologize.
Mu Chen.
The poison is still in you.
Although your eyes are fine,
to protect your veins
from damage,
you'd better come every day.
Let's go.
Luo Li. I...
Your class is about to begin.
I didn’t...
Relax.
I've promised you to give up the sparring,
so I won’t do it again.
Go to your class.
Don’t keep Qingshan waiting any longer.
Luo Li.
Thank you.
That’s unnecessary.
Xuantong.
Goddess.
Given the way he moves,
have his eyes recovered?
The Dark Blood Spell is gone?
Not exactly.
And,
something doesn’t feel right.
Let’s go.
Where to?
Lei Territory.
Sir,
I failed to stop Luo Li.
You aren’t able to anyway.
Sir,
one thing is bothering me.
How come
Mu Chen
can see things again?
The Soul Erasing Spell was interrupted.
It could endanger me, too.
I used the spell
to suppress the Dark Blood Spell temporarily
so that he’d regain his vision
and Luo Li
would leave.
You're wise, sir.
Let him breathe for another day.
Do we have enough points to enter Lei Territory?
These two combined
are worth 4,370 points.
You’ll still need 13,630 points
in exchange for an entrance pass.
Goddess.
Why don’t we come back in a few months?
We’ll have enough points then.
Blood Demon Pill, the 13th on the Land List
is worth 300 points.
You got lucky.
Not as lucky as Shen Cangsheng.
A few years back,
he risked his life to acquire a wolf demon's core,
which was worth 5,000 points.
That was remarkable.
Thanks.
How much is this?
Goddess!
This sword represents your status as a Goddess
and it used to belong to Luo God.
You can’t
pawn it for points.
Are you stopping me?
I want an entrance pass to Lei Territory.
This sword is about one meter long,
as cold as blue ice.
A piece of blue ice bone
is visible
and it extends to the edge.
This is a halidom of the Luo God Clan
and is worth 16,000 points.
Are you sure to pawn it?
I want the entrance pass.
Lei Territory is a danger zone.
Are you sure?
This is a badge to access there.
[Lei Territory]
Let’s go.
Xuantong.
Thanks for your company.
Protecting you is my duty.
Let's go.
Careful!
Come!
What are you doing?
Mu Chen.
You can see me!
How did you recover?
Did Luo Li help you with it?
Where is she?
No sign of her.
Why aren’t you two together?
Stop bringing up her name!
Ms. Ye!
Mu Chen fainted.
Fainted?
What happened?
He’s no longer blind
but he was acting strange.
He seized me by the collar just now.
That wasn’t like him.
What happened?
I don't know.
Suddenly, he passed out.
I couldn’t wake him up.
Tan Qingshan.
Go find Headmaster Ling Xi.
I’ll go check on Mu Chen.
Yes.
The rest of you shall continue practicing.
Jiuyou.
What are you doing?
Who do you think you are?
Headmaster.
Come in.
Mu Chen is in trouble.
What?