[English subtitles are available.]
Protect North Sect!
Watch out.
Your opponent is here!
Xuantong,
thank you.
Goddess, it’s dangerous here.
Take care of yourself.
OK.
Mu Chen,
you ruined my plan again and again.
I won’t
let you go this time.
White Dragon’s power?
He gave such a sacred power
to a human?
Stupid!
Black Dragon,
I’ll also revenge to you for
Lord White Dragon today!
Insignificant trick!
White Dragon never defeated me once.
You got his power, so what?
You are still low human.
The Great Ruler
Episode 28
Black Dragon,
this is all you got?
It’s my turn now.
For Headmaster Ling Xi!
For Lord White Dragon!
And for the people of White Horse City.
And this
is for North Sect!
You think
you can beat me in that way?
What a joke.
I have to say,
you really got something
that you can make me use
the Sumeru Pillar for many times.
Since that,
don’t waste your power anymore.
My Sumeru Pillar just needs nourishment
to help revive my clan.
Don’t be sad.
It’s your honor to do that.
Black Dragon,
stop dreaming of taking
all our power away.
I will end your life today!
Save it!
Mu Chen!
Black Dragon is gaining strength.
We must lead him away.
Or we’ll all die.
Black Dragon!
Over here!
Luo Li,
you go that way.
OK.
Luo Li!
Leave now!
Black Dragon!
Come on!
Mu Chen, are you OK?
I’m fine.
My power.
Sumeru Power is absorbing power now.
At this rate of loss,
everyone will be sucked dry.
Only Dragon Clan
can control the Sumeru Pillar.
Mu Chen,
you have White Dragon’s power now.
Maybe
you can also control it.
I got an idea.
But I need everyone’s help.
Black Dragon,
I will use Dragon Clan’s power to fight with you.
Since you devoted yourself to darkness,
I will make you sacrifice for the darkness.
[Evil Deity]
No!
Don’t you escape?
Lord has died.
Where can I go?
This is how you end up
after taking refuge in evil.
You should have known it.
Cut the crap.
Just kill me
if you want to.
Our North Sect was destroyed
by Black Dragon like this.
We can
rebuild it.
At least we are still here.
Since we survived,
we must carry on the Sect with
the hopes of our departed companions.
As long as we are united,
we can restore the glory of the Five Sects.
That’s right.
As long as we are together,
we can rebuild our Sect.
But now Headmaster Ling Xi is not here.
Who else
can lead us to rebuild it?
I think
it’s time for us to select a new headmaster.
And
we should
choose among us.
The responsibilities of the headmaster are heavy.
Dragon Roc,
I’m not qualified.
Cangsheng, don’t refuse.
You are our senior fellow.
And you encouraged us
at the critical time.
That’s right.
Cangsheng, please be our new headmaster
and lead us
to rebuild North Sect.
Cangsheng,
please accept it.
Only you
can carry on this duty.
OK.
I, Shen Cangsheng,
will live up to your expectations
and revive North Sect!
Revive North Sect!
Black Dragon died.
Three Eyes have been destroyed.
How could a small Beiling
make me lose this much?
Father,
should we open the remaining six Eyes now?
The slow speed was to keep a low profile.
Now I have no need to hide.
It’s time to show them
what real power is!
Qingxuan.
Yes.
Go to North Sect in person
and take Mu Chen’s head to me.
Yes.
The successor of Great Futu Spell
has ruined my plan once.
We can’t let him go again.
Thanks for your gift, father.
I will not fail this time.
It was
so dangerous today.
When you gave all your power to Mu Chen,
have you ever think of that
if you fail,
you will be trapped in Mu Chen’s consciousness
and never come back?
Aren’t you afraid?
If
I were Mu Chen,
would you do the same thing to me?
Mu Chen!
Bai Tong,
what are you thinking of?
What’s wrong?
I didn’t expect that
we could defeat Black Dragon.
For a moment,
I was really afraid we were going to die here.
But you looked so sure,
then I was not afraid of anything.
You trust me so much.
I can’t let you down.
And Lord White Dragon.
I used his power
to unlock Sumeru Pillar
and defeat Black Dragon.
I think
he can rest
in peace now.
But all these things
are so brutal.
Mu Chen!
Where is Mubai?
Why didn’t he come back with you?
Mubai…
He…
He was worried that Evilness Clan would harm you.
So he went to White Horse City to help you.
What happened?
Didn’t you meet him?
We saw him.
We did.
Mubai was in a fight
with Evilness Clan.
To save me,
he died.
What did you say?
Sorry, Qian’er.
I failed to protect him.
No way.
Impossible!
He won’t die!
He can’t die!
Mu Chen,
let her go.
Are you going to tell her the truth?
Is it right for us to hide the truth
from her?
If she knows the truth,
she will feel even worse.
Seven days.
I will find you
within seven days.
The disaster is over.
Many things are waiting to be done.
Today, I’ll take the post of headmaster.
I will live up to everyone’s expectation,
lead by example
and revive North Sect.
Revive North Sect!
Headmaster.
Ruler Mu and Mr. Mo are here to visit.
Let them in.
Yes.
Last night,
I felt several abnormal movements
from all over the world.
At this point,
I’m afraid
it has something to do with Evil Eyes.
Evil Eyes?
The Nine Eyes of Evil Deity.
What is that?
The Nine Eyes
are made by Evil Deity’s power.
At the start of the war between Evil Deity
and the God of Heaven, he divided his territory
into nine parts,
and arranged nine eyes to govern them.
The Nine Eyes
are the Eye of Heaven,
the Eye of Flat,
the Eye of Source,
the Eye of Bliss,
the Eye of Desert,
the Eye of Cruelty,
the Eye of Expect, the Eye of Void…
What is the last one?
The Eye of Whisper.
The Nine Eyes
can absorb power for Evil Deity.
After he was sealed,
the Nine Eyes were gone as well.
But now they showed up again
with unknown reason.
In Beiling and White Horse City,
three of them have been destroyed.
Does that mean
that Evil Deity can’t revive?
I’m just wondering.
The purpose of the Eyes
is for Evil Deity to absorb the power.
The Eyes are powerful.
Destroying three of them
can only postpone
his revival.
If you want to exterminate Evil Deity,
you have to destroy
all of the Nine Eyes.
What are the remaining six Eyes?
Where are they?
Days ago,
when I fought with Black Dragon,
I used Sumeru Pillar
to destroy the Eye of Bliss
outside the White Horse City.
I didn’t know
that the Eye of Bliss was there.
Luckily, you destroyed it.
But the Sumeru Pillar
is the treasure of Dragon Clan.
Why can you use it?
When we were in White Horse City,
before Lord White Dragon died,
he gave me his power.
I guess he knew that this day would come.
It seems that
it is destined.
Where is the
Sumeru Pillar now?
Maybe in the sea.
Sea?
Chen,
you have to set off to there
and get it back right now.
Sumeru Pillar is powerful.
Evil Deity must want it as well.
We have to get ahead of him.
And,
you have the power of Dragon Clan.
Only you can
get it back.
OK.
I got it.
There is another thing.
Please go ahead.
Black Dragon is gone.
Now we will face the Evil Deity.
So we have to unite all the power
that can be united.
That’s right.
Other than Human Clan,
we also need to cooperate with God Clans.
But Tailing Ancient Clan
is already missing.
And after the last war, Futu Ancient Clan
has retired.
So,
the only one we can ask for help
is Luo God Clan.
Guys,
I planned to go back to
Luo God Clan tomorrow.
I’ll try my best
to persuade my grandpa about it.
But Luo God Clan is in a war
with Xue God Clan.
That’s why
I need to go back and fight together
with my people.
As soon as I resolve the crisis,
I’ll be back to join the fight
against Evil Deity.
Your grandfather entrusted you to me
just to keep you out of the war.
Mr. Mo,
I’m the goddess of Luo God Clan.
Now the enemy is in front,
and my clan is in trouble,
I can’t hide myself from it.
Luo Li,
what can we help you?
The first task is to destroy the Evil Eyes.
Thank you for your concern and care.
I’ll remember it forever.
Luo Li,
if there is any difficulty,
just tell us.
Thank you.
Mu Chen.
You’re here.
I just packed up.
Don’t go now.
I’ll go to Luo God Clan with you.
Aren’t you going to White Horse City?
So, I want you to wait for me.
This time is different.
I don’t need to hide.
I’ll be back soon.
But, after you come back,
you still got other things to do.
I thought about it.
Although something strange happened,
we still need a long time
to find the other six Eyes.
I will come back to you soon after
things are settled in my clan.
Luo Li…
Be good.
I want to go with you
not only because I don’t want to leave you.
In public,
I have the power of White Dragon now,
I can help your clan to solve the problem soon
and we can fight against Evil Deity earlier.
In private,
do you remember my father said that
Ancient God Clans have strict discipline that
you people can’t get married with human?
You mean,
if you can…
help Luo God Clan this time…
Then the next time I go to propose,
your grandfather won’t ask me away.
Mu Chen,
I know you are here.
You…
I’m here to remind you to go.
I’ll wait for you at the gate.
Jiuyou!
I’ll go to White Horse City
alone this time.
Alone?
You can wait for me here.
And,
after I come back,
I’ll go to Luo God Clan with Luo Li.
You won’t go with us either.
Mu Chen,
what do you mean?
You think I’m a burden?
No.
You are Jiuyou Bird.
Luo Li won’t take your Spirit Blood,
but the other people in Luo God Clan will.
Now Luo God Clan is in a mess.
If someone with bad intention
wants you,
Luo Li can’t protect you then.
I don’t need her protection!
I can take care of myself!
I’m doing this for you.
For me?
I think you are just afraid of death!
We both live and die together.
Are you afraid of me getting in your way?
This is for your good.
Why are you mad?
Save it.
I‘m glad to enjoy the quietness.
Jiuyou!
What?
What’s wrong?
It’s Mu Chen’s fault.
It’s driving me crazy!
He bullied you?
He didn’t bully you,
why are you so mad?
I won’t allow anyone to bully you.
Come back.
In fact,
he didn’t bully me.
It’s just
he will go to Luo God Clan with Luo Li.
He won’t go with me!
Then, you want to go with him?
No.
But it should be me
to make this decision.
Why should I listen to him?
Jiuyou,
are you
jealous?
What’s that?
Well…
You know vinegar?
It’s a seasoning the human will use.
I have never tasted it before.
It’s my first time to know it.
No,
I don’t mean that.
I mean,
vinegar is a sour seasoning.
Being jealous is like how you feel
when you eat too much vinegar.
It feels bad and annoyed.
If you say so,
I really feel like that.
It’s like that
I ate an under ripe berry.
It’s sour and bitter.
But why am I jealous?
Because
you love Mu Chen.
Father,
Before Headmaster Ling Xi died, she told me
she was mother’s adopted daughter.
She was my sister.
Have you always known this?
Yes.
These years,
I've actually been in touch with Ling Xi.
Will you blame me for that?
No.
Father,
I know you want to protect me.
Headmaster Shen
has told me what you have experienced.
Chen,
if your mother could be here
and know what you have achieved,
she would be so happy.
I’m not worthy of what you said.
Don’t say that.
You did a good job.
Father,
I have a request.
After I come back from White Horse City,
I want to go to Luo God Clan with Luo Li.
I know what
you are thinking.
Fine.
You can
help them when you go there.
But I have to remind you.
When you are in their place,
be polite and have manners.
And don’t be rude
to Luo Li.
I know.
I can judge the situation.
And I’m going there for serious business,
not for affections.
You have grown up.
You are like a real man
and mature now.
Mubai!
Mubai.
Hang in there.
I will help you out soon.
Are you jealous?
Why am I jealous?
Because
you love Mu Chen.
Love?
Jealous?
What are these?
Jiuyou,
you look bad now.
I didn’t sleep well last night.
Well…
You first.
I was not
mad at you just now.
I was mad at Mu Chen.
Don’t get me wrong.
I know.
Are you still mad at him?
He did that for you.
I hate to listen to this.
He always said he did this
or that for me.
But I don’t want him to do that for me.
He never did that for you.
Jiuyou,
you love Mu Chen?
I don’t know.
Do you?
Yes.
Then can you tell me
what is love?
I can’t explain it clearly.
Everyone has a
different understanding of love.
For me,
it’s that I always think of him.
If he is happy,
I will also be happy.
If he is sad,
I will be sad as well.
To save me, he lost his sight .
I even wanted to give my eyes to him.
Then you will be blind.
Even if I’ll be blind,
as long as he can get his sight back,
I will be happier.
I think
this is what love is.
What if it’s not eyes
but your life?
I’m also willing to do it.
Great.
I can’t do it.
If I die,
he can’t live as well.
Goddess,
I have something to tell you.
Luo Li is right.
No,
I don’t agree.
Goddess,
when you left Luo City,
everyone knew that
you were going to find Jiuyou Spirit Blood.
But you are going to go back without it.
I think the elders will
use this to pick on you.
What thing I did
has ever got their approval since childhood?
Since I was born to be goddess,
I learned Luo Spell at age of eight,
was awarded the Luo God Sword at age of fifteen,
and I left Luo City to find Jiuyou Spirit Blood.
Have they ever supported me in anything?
Xuantong,
unless I do become the Saintess,
their criticism of me
will never cease.
Goddess!
Xuantong,
what are you doing?
Stand up!
Goddess,
I’m slightly older than you.
It can be said that I watched you grow up.
I have sworn that
I won’t let anyone hurt you.
As long as it’s good to you,
I can do anything even if it’s against
the conscience.
What do you want to do?
I’m going to get
Jiuyou Spirit Blood.
Stand up.
Come with me.