Administration
[Episode 18]
Morning Clean
Oh! Are you perhaps... Bread Shuttle (errand boy to fetch bread for bullies)?
Oh! Are you Bok Soo's friend, Lee Kyeong Hyeon?
Wow! How did you also come here?
Wow. I heard you became a teacher but you really are!
- You've succeeded, Shuttle Ma.
- Oh, yeah.
Why are you calling him a shuttle?
What?
No. I just...
Look here. Excuse me, but if I said to you,
"Hey, services. Hey, cleaning." would you feel good?
Also, addressing him with something that's painful to him from his past as if it's a proper noun and not painful to him
is not what a mature adult should do.
Listen carefully.
This person's name is not Shuttle Ma but Ma Yeong Joon.
Teacher Ma Yeong Joon.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm just an alum from the same class, so I was just glad to see him.
Alum from the same class?
Our Teacher Ma, who looks so young for his age, and you?
No way.
♫  Who are you? Who, who, who, who? ♫
♫ Who are you? Who, who, who, who? ♫
♫ Tell me, who are you? Who are you? Who? ♫
♫ I really want to know. ♫
♫ C'mon, tell me, who are you? You? You? Wow! You! ♫
People don't know well
that someone can rummage through their trash.
List of consulting institutes for college entrance
As expected, you're qualified as a CEO.
The school had a list for consulting institutes.
College entrance consulting institute.
Friend, I just saw you act as a smart man.
So shocking.
I absolutely hate meaningless consulting.
Nowadays, without a connection to the school's foundation,
it's a bit hard to take care of a student's records.
I have a very special relationship with Seolsong High.
Especially, for the most important campus competition,
we are the only one that Seolsong High provides information to.
It's all been planned out before the start of the competition, huh?
But it isn't wrong to pay money for consulting service.
It's okay if the school didn't give out information to the consulting institute, but...
They did. That's true. That's corruption.
Hey, are you going to let this out right away?
No, we need to reveal all the people who are involved first.
Oh Se Ho is definitely involved.
People who paid money...
Of course. I knew they'd get caught.
Debate Topic: One's career choice is based on money
What are you doing here?
Ugh!
Hey, then what are you doing here?
Because of my punishment. I'm cleaning.
- Why, why?
- Hurry and go!
Hey, we're debating against the wildflower class.
Right? We uselessly paid the institute.
I feel like we'd win even without receiving the tip in advance.
Those kids, we'd be able to beat them just by opening our mouths.
Oh, I forgot to tell you. My mom said that we would have to pay double the price to get the materials after the debate starts.
Isn't the school crazy? They have to have a limit on getting extra money.
Watch your mouth.
Oh... Sorry.
Money?
Hello, Teacher Son Soo Jeong.
Yang Min Ji. What are you doing here?
Bok Soo and I have something to do at school. You know it, right?
No, I don't know.
Looks like Bok Soo didn't tell you about such things.
Seolsong's 15th Debate Contest Final
Wildflower VS Ivy
Oh, Teacher Son.
How did it turn out to be against the ivy class?
- Student Department Teacher?
- Yes?
You should buy lunch one time.
How did Ivy turn out to be against yours?
They must have passed the preliminaries due to having Yeong Min in that class.
Hey, at least you made it to the finals.
You should be satisfied with that. Don't make kids dream too big.
Teacher Son, you'll probably need to console the kids.
Who are the members again?
Oh Yeong Min, Yoon Seung Woo, and Kang Bok Soo, right?
Yes.
An idiot, a last place, and a returned student.
Wow. The wildflower class members sure are the Avengers.
Yes. They are the Avengers.
If our students do well, watch out.
Well, to be honest, no matter how well they do,
they can't be compared to my kids.
I was scared you guys weren't going to come.
Hey. What kind of contest is this for you to be like that?
Even so, this is my first contest as part of the wildflower class. I want to do well.
Fighting!
We will be starting the final round of Seolsong High's
15th debate contest.
The topic is: One's career choice is based on money.
The first speaker who agrees with statement, please arise.
I'm Oh Yeong Min from the wildflower class.
Oh. You made it to be the leader since going to the wildflower class?
You've succeeded, Oh Yeong Min.
The team formation sure is amazing.
The school's last place and the school's oldest student.
Student Lee Chae Min, please keep your manners during the debate.
Ah, okay, Teacher.
I listen well to a pretty person.
Money is an immediate issue, you see.
But the accomplishment or satisfaction you get through your job is a later thing.
People who don't have money nor study well always say that.
Did you leave the ivy class due to lack of money?
What kind of future do those types of kids have?
In my opinion, money is already an important value that's established in our society.
A flow that you can't go against.
Therefore, the wildflower class agrees with the idea that money is a criteria
in choosing a career.
Admission before choosing the career path has already ended before first semester.
Yes, that is why I came to see the school's principals in person.
I'd like to continue the transfer with the recommendations through the school's principals.
By the way, Seolsong High is well-established already.
Why do you have to intervene in matters pertaining to a student's transfer?
Of course, I should come here myself when it's for the students.
Because our school focuses on university admissions,
I feel bad that the students who rank low are being left out.
Ah, yes...
Because it's a favor regarding our students, we do plan on providing support funds.
Firstly, how about we sponsor Yoomin High by buying you training equipment?
Aigoo, you don't have to.
Well, I mean Yoomin High does have the highest employment rate in the country,
so it's an honor to do it.
I'll try to make it so that Seolsong High students can transfer to our school.
Thank you.
- Please eat.
- Okay.
Let's eat.
Next up: the first speaker from the opposite team, please arise.
We, the ivy class team, negate the claim that
job selections are based on money.
Richard Easterlin's paradox emphasized that the rich are not always happy.
As for the hypothesis that the more you earn, the happier you will be,
a lot of research from various countries has proven it to be false.
Firstly, according to data from Korea Industrial Development Institution,
when the young select their jobs,
the thing that they prioritize most is stability.
Unlike what you have stated, stability is of greatest priority, not income.
And the second is income, according to research.
Members of the wildflower class team,
it seems that you are unable to perform simple fact checks.
Please only comment on what's related to the debate.
If there is no special individual comment to be made, we will wrap it up by making a final remark.
According to a Gallup Research opinion poll,
in the last half-century, the country's total production percentage has been continually increasing.
And also individual earnings from jobs have increased as well.
However, the percentage of people's happiness has not increased at all.
So, therefore, money shouldn't be a standard for picking a career.
I will end the final statement for our ivy class team.
Wildflower class team, please make your final statement as well.
I think people get so embarrassed constantly talking about money.
Money is a thing that we all need to survive after all. Isn't that right?
Even if money can be petty and dirty,
some people are anxious about getting canned, so they hang in there with great patience.
And the reason to protect their job is money.
It's not...
It's nothing to be ashamed of at all.
Honestly, I'm scared that I might get canned.
I'm shaking in my boots because of that stupid thing called money, and it makes me feel miserable.
Some people never have even experienced working for money.
Those punks who were born with silver spoons in their mouths want to take care of everything with money,
but those kids despise money too.
So when you are not paid for your work, that's considered volunteering and not a job.
Someone once said this.
"If you can't buy happiness with money, check if you are lacking the money."
No, you are not able to receive adequate pay for your work, so what use is self-realization?
That materialistic jerk. He's so vulgar.
- What?
- A school won't pay you,
so why did you crawl back to here? I don't get it. At your old age.
So embarrassing. Right?
Hey...
Stop.
How is liking money a vulgar thing?
Chae Min, you are the one who is reaping the benefits of money more than anyone.
More than anyone else, you are studying and coming to school with money.
Perhaps, was the textbook-type logic you presented, like "self-realization and social volunteering,"
bought with money as well?
Why don't you put your hand on your conscience and swear to yourself.
Self-realization and social welfare volunteer work are also jobs,
but if it's a job where you can't even earn a cent for doing it,
would you select such a job for yourselves?
The measuring stick for picking out a career is based on money.
That is it. From wildflower class, my name is Yoon Seung Woo, the final commentator for the debate.
Debate Score Card
38.9
Teacher Park, didn't the score card get switched?
What's up with the scores for the ivy class?
I gave out the points honestly.
This is really important for college admissions.
You should be supporting some capable kids.
How wasteful giving high points to the wildflower class.
Teachers should be fair.
What are you trying to say, Assistant Principal?
We lost?
Why? What's the measuring stick for scoring?
The debating competition is about teaching to listen courteously to what others have to say and respect for others.
You mocked other people's opinions and acted as if you were superior in the debate.
You mistook it.
And just reading out loud from already printed sources has nothing to do with the art of debating.
The wildflower class team lacked in many areas and was also a bit clumsy,
but they expressed their own opinions from the heart and also minded their manners.
That's the reason for this particular result.
I'm going to make an official complaint about this.
You should ask yourself what that complaint is exactly.
See if you are ashamed of your own self.
The 15th Annual Seolsong High School Debate Competition
Teacher, you should lower your temper. You are leading a tiring life.
What, kid? I didn't say anything wrong over there.
Of course, you don't ever say anything that's wrong.
Either way, you did well.
You have to do things that are troublesome and the things that you don't like from time to time.
Even if you are not capable, do the best you can. That's what school should be about.
I know, right?
Teacher, you should still look out for yourself. Sometimes I think you are worse than I can ever be.
I bet you are going to hear an earful this time.
I'm not scared of any of that.
Oh, the smell of trash.
The nasty foul smell is wreaking all over the place.
Who's the one that got kicked in the ass by trash, eh?
What is the worst student of the whole school saying, huh?
You should try to do something about that dumb blockhead of yours.
Are you really that proud of doing so well in school?
You think you are some hotshot or what?
Hey, it seems like you have no idea at all, but Chae Min is number one in the whole school.
Oh, really?
Let's go.
Oh, Mr. Elder! It seems like this old man really does act his age.
Oppa, I'm falling in love with you today.
As expected, you're cool.
So annoying. Go away.
You know you like it.
- How does it feel to kick the ivy class in the butt?
- Don't do that.
Can you say a word?
Good.
Are you really that happy about winning the debate competition?
I just like seeing my students happy.
I wonder why I feel so good seeing all the kids smile like that.
I remember Teacher Park telling us that he felt full just by looking at us smile once.
I don't know about feeling full, but I do want to make the kids laugh more.
Me too.
I also want you to smile more.
I feel like we are back in high school being like this.
But I am currently a student, after all.
I like school, Soo Jeong.
Me too.
I like school because you are here.
No, I can't! We can't do this until you graduate!
What is it that you can't do?
- Huh?
- I want to know what can't you do.
I'm so curious now.
Seriously, man.
You go now. I said, go!
My goodness.
Oh yeah, that's right. Okay, let's see...
What is the thing that you need to do with Yang Min Ji at the school anyway?
Why aren't you telling me?
- Son Soo Jeong.
- Yeah?
Are you being jealous right now?
No, I'm not!
- Yes, you are.
- No, I'm not.
- Yeah, you are.
Yeah, you are.
Hey, Soo Jeong, related to that issue, there is something that you need to know.
What do you mean student record corruption? That doesn't make any sense.
That nonsense is happening at Seolsong High right now.
Starting an in-class competition is dealt with using money.
I overheard No Woo Hyeon and Lee Chae Min talking about it.
In-class competition has increased, but I had no idea that starting one had such a problem.
So are you saying that ivy class parents start such a competition by paying money? No way.
That's not all.
Also, private college admission consulting companies would pay the school
to get the theme ahead of time, and then they tip the students with the best answers.
You know the debate competition that we just had, right? The kids from the ivy class
had both the exemplary answers for opposing and approval questions. I verified and confirmed it.
Take a look.
Debate competition play-off
Selection
Wow, are they totally insane or what?!
This is so important to college entrance for goodness sake! How could they?!
- What?
- I love it when Son Soo Jeong swears.
You little! Get out and do your lovey-dovey thing.
You went to school to get revenge and just ended up doing nothing but dating. And now you have to do this at work?
As the CEO here, I would like to prohibit dating at work.
Get out.
Thank you. Let's go.
Alright.
CEO, are we not allowed to date a coworker?
It's prohibited.
Then what do we do?
Huh?
The issue of dealing with the debate contest is already causing a lot of fuss among ivy class' parents.
What did you do for the results to come out like this?
Teacher Park is just so uptight and hard to get around.
Nothing seems to work on him. I'm in a very difficult situation here.
Just modify the ivy class score report first.
Announce that there was a mistake in judging, and thus, there was a reevaluation.
Order Teacher Park Dong Joo to submit his suspension forms.
He won't stand by it.
That's what I wish for.
Correcting the winners of the debate competition
After reevaluating, we have concluded that some of the judges made an error in their scores.
The judge responsible for this is subject to suspension, and the winning team has been changed to the ivy class.
Ivy Class
Don't get worked up. You can't.
Revenge is about rationality and coldness.
You don't know that?
This is the evidence that we need.
Kang Bok Soo, do as planned.
Are you kidding? We totally beat the ivy kids!
We did. And that's why they don't like it!
I heard something from the elder yesterday.
The ivy kids give money to the school.
They give money?
What?
You scared me. When did you come?
Is that true?
This sort of thing is done just to write something on the ivy kids' transcripts.
I never paid.
Not you, but your mother probably.
Eat this and calm down.
Don't spit on your own face.
How could I have made a mistake?
I did it precisely and fairly.
How can the school overstep on a teacher's exclusive right?
So why would you give the points like that?
Your markings are wrong.
You don't know that you're not supposed to be giving points like that?
Are you doing this because you really don't know?
I, this... I will formally discuss this with the director.
Teacher Park, you're so exuberant even at your age.
How about you quit and just retire to be a farmer?
With the strength you use to hold on to this place, do something more worthwhile,
because this school will still do well without you!
Bok Soo, Teacher Park is in trouble.
Right now, he's going to argue with Oh Se Ho.
I will go inside the director's office.
No, Teacher Son, I will take care of this.
This is about my class.
The wildflower class students are my kids.
Instead of the one who judged, I think that it is right for me, the teacher in charge,
to complain officially.
Let's talk calmly.
With logic. Don't panic or get emotional.
You can do it, Son Soo Jeong.
You bast***!
Are you done? Shall I give you some tea?
Director, please correct your ridiculous decision.
You know the wildflower class won fair and square.
Is it really fair and square if the results changed due to one person's judging criteria?
But it's fair and just to change the results
in order to let the pre-decided kids win?
You're saying some dangerous words without any evidence.
You know it's the truth.
Is teaching about unfairness your educational philosophy?
You said you were going to establish justice at Seolsong High.
You told me to watch for it!
I'm going to catch everything that's wrong at Seolsong High.
Soo Jeong, are you in the position to be so confident in front of me?
What about Kim Myeong Ho? What'd you do that you're like this to me?
Okay, fine. What about you? Do you have no wrongs regarding Kim Myeong Ho?
Where did all the money go? Isn't it to you or your mother?
Yeah, that's why we're accomplices.
If we're on the same boat, do you think it's right for you to dislike me like this?
Don't mess with the kids.
Okay fine, because of that pathetic money,
I sold my conscience and am living without honor,
but if you mess with the kids, you and I both are going to die.
I will never die alone.
No.
You tell me to not mess with the kids nor Kang Bok Soo. Then...
What do I do?
I... I myself did wrong,
so I'm okay if things like this happen to me, but the kids did no wrong.
You know the most that Kang Bok Soo did nothing wrong, you evil jerk!
You should know that the more you do this, the more I want to make Kang Bok Soo...
disappear.
Try it, you psycho.
Because I'll show you who's crazier.
Counseling Room
What are you doing not going home at this time?
I came after hearing from Teacher Park.
Are you okay?
Our Bok Soo, you look so good in a uniform.
I want to help you graduate.
Don't worry.
I'm going to graduate with my own will.
So you have to give me that diploma.
What do I do?
I want to confidently confront Oh Se Ho,
but because of my wrongdoings, I can't proudly fight him.
I really lived wrongly.
Counseling Room
My Strange Hero
This isn't a school, it's a corporation.
Is this all true?
Teacher Park wrote a letter to the Board of Education?
Don't you dare ruin my school. Get out this instant!
This is my school right now.
If you're going to kick me out, wait.
What do I do? I'm a teacher, so what do I do?
Don't worry. I'll sort it out. Trust me.
Make him transfer by saying that he was violent.
All of a sudden, doing this...
I got rejected.
Since you've rejected our good will,
we'll have no choice but to go with the stronger method.
Umbrella. Don't you have an umbrella?
Are you crazy? This is a school. You're wearing a uniform right now—
Is the uniform the problem?
Are you confident you won't hurt her?
I will never leave her alone.
I want to become a teacher like you.
First, we need Teacher Park.
I am the evidence that your education philosophy is a failure, Teacher Park.
As the school's director, I am now firing Teacher Park Dong Joon.