Hey idiots, I guess you'll be separated soon.
Episode 22
Do you guys think studying is enough?
Just pack up your bags in advance.
And clean out your lockers, too.
If you cause a problem right now, it'll only hurt us. Don't do it.
Oh Yeong Min, did I say something wrong?
Don't try so hard with crappy brains.
Just disappear quietly.
I really hate that they're making us transfer because we're not good at studying.
I am getting sick of being belittled.
Yummy. Yum. Yum.
Right, you are poor at studying, but you look so adorable when you eat.
You surely are my baby.
Son, do you not want to transfer?
I heard about it, and it doesn't seem so bad.
You will be able to go to college, I heard.
- Transfer. Mom.
- Hm?
I just started to like the school.
And I won't have any friends if I transfer.
Right.
Okay.
Go transfer! You get to learn vocational skills. It sounds good.
You'll inherit my shop anyway.
Go learn skin care, makeup, and the technicals of this field—
I don't want to. All my friends are here, but you want only me to go to a different school?
Why are friends important?
You're so thoughtless.
Seriously.
Why are you deciding on the transfer yourself?
Then should I let you do what you want?
Listen to your mother. Listening to the director, there isn't anything wrong. Hm?
I don't want to.
Then what will you do with a high school diploma?! Just transfer!
All my friends are here! All my memories are here too!
Is it okay for my school life to be ruined just because I don't study well?!
They made it nasty. Our school's bul-burg is so much tastier.
Don't eat it. Give it to me. Give me a to-go box!
Leave it! You better not take a bite.
- My mom told me to transfer.
- Same here.
Listening to my mom made me want to study out of pettiness.
But do you really think that we can do this?
Why can't you?
Why not? Let's show our moms.
Let's do it.
We will be learning about tenses today.
Teacher, what's a tense?
Tenses pertain to the past, present, and future.
The most important thing about tenses is seen by knowing the "be" verbs (am, are, is).
What's a "be" verb?
A "be" verb is... That's right.
It's possible for you to not know.
I am happy. I am sleepy.
I am a son.
The basics of a "be" verb. Let's start with only one.
Bok Soo, do you want to go first?
This looks hard.
"I am happy." It means I am happy.
"I am sleepy" is I am sleepy.
"I am a son" is I am a sun.
Oh, Elder! You're unexpectedly skilled!
Teacher! So what's a "be" verb?
The next question. What are those suffixes for passive verb change (for Korean)?
I told you guys this a minute ago.
Answer!
Yi hee... hee...
(The right answer: 이 yi, 히 hee, 리 lee, 기 gi)
Answer! Yi hee lee...
- Gi!
- Correct!
Yi si lee gi.
That isn't it.
I was almost there. Next one.
I'm starting.
Three types of honorific expressions in Korean?
Answer! Using an honorific subject, using an honorific object in a sentence,
- and using relatively honorific words.
- Correct!
Next problem. What are the special words for the honorific object?
Escort, give, inquire, and meet.
- Incorrect!
- What's wrong with you? Escort, give, inquire, and pay a visit.
Correct!
Oh, that scared me!
- Sorry.
- Ah, Teacher.
My heart is racing already.
Seolsong High
Education Board Department
I know the director of Seolsong High, Im Sae Kyeong, very well.
It seems that you have a lot of misunderstandings about her.
She is not a person to commit this kind of corruption.
This is really happening at the school.
The school is running under the system to rank the students mainly by grade.
It's extremely discriminating and makes students feel an inferiority complex
and a sense of relative deprivation compared to those who have better grades.
This society is running based on that discrimination already
because it's efficient.
You should teach your students what the reality is.
School has to be that way as well?
As a member of the education board, how can you value education with efficiency?
Are the kids machines?
No, I spared some time for you, but you don't have the right mindset!
Kids, let's stop here. Hurry and go.
Let's go. I'll drop you off.
Goodbye.
- Son Soo Jeong.
- What?
Are you a person who carries debts? I'm the kind of person who can't live with debt.
Debt? What does that mean?
No, if you slept at my house...
Why... here... here... my girlfriend...
Why can't I sleep at my girlfriend's
house once?
Let's do that then.
As expected. Son Soo Jeong is a contemporary woman (with an open-mind).
- Don't be nervous. We can just hold hands and go to sleep.
- Huh?
Okay.
Kang Bok Soo, are you sleeping?
Are you really sleeping?
Are you sleeping in this situation?
Are you really sleeping while only holding hands?
Wow, I must be crazy.
Why did I teach him about platonic relationships
and make him too straight up?
Patience makes the soul stronger.
Makes a soul stronger, my ass.
Hey, Son Soo Jeong.
I tried really hard to endure it, but I'm not able to because of you.
♫ Take a look, take a look ♫
♫ I just wanna be your sky, my love  ♫
♫ Something I have in memory ♫
♫ Such an embracing blue sky  ♫
♫ I just wanna be your sky, my love  ♫
♫ Your warmth wrapped around me  ♫
♫ Such an embracing blue sky ♫
♫ Blue sky, blue sky  ♫
♫ You’re in my memory ♫
♫ You’re in my blue sky ♫
Seolsong High School should abolish extreme discrimination
What the?
Teacher, are you seriously protesting by yourself?
It just happened that way. Other methods just don't seem to work on them.
You should've told us. Let's do it together.
Hey! You should just go.
Teacher, you shouldn't do this alone. It's cold out here.
Teacher Son, you should go in and teach your students.
And you, Kang Bok Soo, should go in and study hard.
Then what about you, Teacher?
Well, I should stay out here and fight for justice.
I was dropped from teaching duties, so I should at least do something meaningful.
Please go and do your thing.
Hurry up and go.
This is humiliating to show the students and the media might smell something funny going on too.
And ever since the Oh Yeong Min and Kang Bok Soo incidents, the media seems to be looking into our school more often.
Don't worry since I took care of that already. Principal, you can leave now.
There's a meeting with the man in charge of the committee today, right?
That's right, it will be tonight.
You seem to be cool since you are a young man and all.
It ended up taking a lot of time since I wanted to proceed with things without it getting out of control.
I think it's time for you to start discussing with me the other matters you've been working on with my mother.
What do you mean by other things?
Of course, it's the student records book.
Don't you think we should come up with a solid collaboration on this
since it's the most important thing when it comes to college admissions?
You know how I always guarantee the sufficient donation, right?
Are you planning to change the name of the donation account to yours?
No, ma'am.
When it comes to the donation, you can deposit it to my mother's account as usual.
I will be able to help you and other students' parents by knowing better about how things are done.
The school has been filled with all kinds of commotion.
I heard that problematic teacher has started a one-person protest, am I right?
The problem with that teacher will be resolved soon, thanks to you writing up a complaint so promptly.
Seriously, what should we freaking do about this Oh Se Ho?
He's coming up with all kinds of schemes to destroy Teacher Park.
I guess the best way to go about it is to get the media in on it, right?
We should go for it right away, as soon as we gather up all the data.
We have to reveal it all at once so we can destroy them all at once too.
CLOSE CODE
CLOSE CODE OK
The door is open.
Seolsong High second-year class placement test. Ivy class. Korean Language.
Why did you come to see me at this hour when you should be going out on a date?
I can't keep still when my teacher here is suffering.
Here you are.
What is this?
Bank Statement: Deposit
Hey Bok Soo, this is...?
The people from 'My Favor for You' and Soo Jeong are also helping out with this investigation.
I haven't been able to gather up all the sources yet, but once I do, I'm going to reveal it right away.
This is my responsibility. I—
Teacher, this is my revenge as well.
So please hold out a bit longer, Teacher.
Soon, I'm going to be able to destroy the seeds of the corrupt people.
And then...
Here.
For you.
Bok Soo, I want you to be my son.
Seriously, you're grossing me out. What's wrong with you, Teacher?
And besides, my mom has high standards.
My mom is all about looks, so if you are not good looking, then she just won't care at all.
Teacher, can't you just tell by looking at my face?
Am I supposed to look decent like you?
Yes, sir.
First of all, let me explain it to you, sir.
First, it's about the corruption of the student records book case.
This here is the bribe.
This is the account here.
One person protest Park Dong Joon.
Seolsong High School's extreme discrimination.
- Hello, Teacher.
- Hi, kids.
Hello, Teacher.
Teacher, isn't it cold out here? Here you go, sir.
Thanks, kids.
I'm cheering you on, Teacher. Good luck, Teacher!
Thanks, kids. Hurry up and go in now.
It's cold.
Hello.
Thank you.
- I'm cheering you on.
- Thanks.
Hello.
It's cold. Hurry up and go in.
Hello there.
- Hello.
- Hi, kids.
Wildflowers! Let's go!
Alright kids, let's start the exam. Good luck.
How do I solve this?
Wildflowers, good work.
This is my first time ever solving problems on an exam.
Did you do well?
For some reason, there were a lot of number threes.
What about number two?
Man.
It was crazy.
That was tough.
I feel strange.
I know, right? I feel like I burnt something wild.
That's so true. I think this is my first time ever studying like this since I was born.
You did well.
We didn't really do all that well. We didn't get the grades we wanted after all.
Hey kids, this is what Celen Keller said.
If you do your best, nobody knows what kind of miracle it will bring.
Uncle, it's not Celen Keller. It's Helen Keller.
I wish that a miracle will happen.
Second-year student class standardized exam grade by class
Class 1 (ivy class) - 90.7 average
Class 2 (sky class) - 87.6 average
Class 3 (watermelon class) - 67.5 average
Class 4 (wildflower class) - 51.8 average
51.8
Seolsong High School second-year student ranking list
First place: Class 4 (wildflower class), Yoon Seung Woo
What kind of nonsense is this?!
Soo Jeong, I mean Teacher Son.
This is insane. This is so crazy.
No way.
Is this even right, huh?
Is this an error or what?
Second-year student class standardized exam.
The upper ranking student list.
Second place, Lee Chae Min
(Second year, class one, ivy class)
First place, Yoon Seung Woo
(Second year, class 4, wildflower class)
Yoon Seung Woo, wow!
Epic! Yoon Seung Woo, you are awesome!
What kind of guy are you, man?
This is so great!
No way.
Does this even make any sense?!
That stupid loser.
I wonder why he is destroying what belongs to the school.
Teacher, are you being serious?
That's what I'm saying. Our dear Seung Woo here is the number one student in the whole school?
Wow, you're incredible, Yoon Seung Woo. You are perfect to be a character in a novel.
From worst to best?
Should I tell you something even more amazing?
Gather up, kids.
Our class's average score was over 50 points!
Teacher, what about me?
Your rank dropped because of him.
- You were the one who raised it.
- Who cares, whatever.
You should treat us at the snack bar, man.
Awesome, a free bulgogi burger.
You should do some studying.
The overall class standardized exam for this week will be invalid.
Have them re-tested.
What do you mean, Director?
There is circumstantial evidence that the test papers were leaked.
By my class? What are you trying to pull right now?
The class average increased by thirty points in one week's time.
That is because the average of our class was originally so low—
The school's last place getting a hundred on the exam is abnormal.
You can't suspect students just because the student got a better grade than on his previous exams.
Teacher Park, you know very well
that you can't tutor a student for tuition outside of school property.
I swear to the teaching ethic that I never did such a thing.
How do you explain this?
This... has nothing to do with the exam.
Then what were you doing? Can you testify what was in that?
I suspect that you could have tutored the wildflower class students after school for tuition.
The day you and Kang Bok Soo met,
we found traces of someone opening the safe that had the exam questions.
The only ones who know the safe's password are the principal and you, Teacher Park, Chief of School Affairs.
I can swear on my life that there was no such incident.
There's no need for you to put your life at stake.
You can testify about the rest during the disciplinary committee.
With this, we will be expelling Kang Bok Soo.
Oh Se Ho, you're crazy.
Does what you're doing make sense? How could you, to Teacher Park—
Then, you can't reveal what was in that bag on the photo.
Teacher, we can't let Bok Soo get expelled like this.
We did nothing wrong so let's do an official investig—
With this incident, Bok Soo will again receive misunderstandings from people.
We can't hurt him in the same way even though we can't prove the truth.
Then what should we do?
It's my fault.
I'll take care of it.
Teacher.
I knew you were going to come.
But I am not sure if you're going to rant at me or beg me.
Or both of them?
I will take all responsibility and leave, so leave Bok Soo alone.
What a tearful sacrifice. Teacher, you're always just thinking about Kang Bok Soo till the end, making me sad.
Se Ho, you can't do this to Bok Soo.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Finish this up and sign this first.
Resignation Letter
I don't want to hear you out.
Signed: Park Dong Joon
Se Ho, making others suffer
doesn't mean your suffering will disappear.
You'll only be suffering more.
Just reprimand me like you want to!
Don't pretend to be a good person or teacher.
You're angry!
I am harassing you and your beloved Kang Bok Soo
to this degree.
I understand that you've been hurt a lot too.
How could I reprimand you?
Falling off the rooftop? I already recovered from that.
No, your heart is still hurt.
Se Ho, I'm sorry that
I couldn't help you.
What on earth is going on?
That's what I'm saying. The school is so scary. How can we live?
So why did you do that?
Notify students that the last placement test result
has been annulled.
Do well and keep your mouths closed so that rumors do not spread.
Hurry and go!
How must the students in the ivy class feel?
What's wrong?
What happened?
Teacher!
Give me this.
- Hurry and give it to me.
- What?
Hurry and give it to me!
What is all of this?
You becoming like this because of me. I'm going to quit this place.
I-I'm fine.
I'm not fine though!
Don't do it. You can't.
Let go of me now.
- You punk.
- Let go of me!
If something bad happens to you—
If I can't protect you this time...
then I won't be able to take it.
I won't be able to be resilient enough.
Bok Soo, this time, you definitely have to graduate.
Please.
My Strange Hero