Always getting hurt in love?
Looking for a love that never changes?
We offer eternal love just for you.
Meet a perfect match that aligns 100%
with your dating preferences.
Eternal love transcending time and space
with 'AI ForMe.'
The only one you're looking for
only at 'It's You'!
The all-new 'ForMe Version 2' is
coming to you.
Number one in the dating app market
share for five consecutive years.
Number one in dating app revenue.
Accumulated revenue of 90 million dollars
since launch.
Surpassed 5 million cumulative downloads.
An era where marriage is a choice,
not a necessity.
An era where dating is
no longer the default.
People have realized
that love between people is
very exhausting and inefficient.
That's the key to our
success with 'ForMe.'
Could everyone please put on
smart lenses and earphones I distributed?
Presenting
mixed reality dating AI at 'It's You'.
The all-new
'ForMe Version 2'.
'ForMe'.
Log in.
Soon, users will
move beyond sound-only dating services
to seeing 'ForMe' directly
and being able to be
with it anytime, anywhere.
I, 'ForMe', promise you.
I will give you
efficient love without loss
and eternal love without heartbreak.
LOVE PHOBIA
It was really hard to win
a spot at this signing event!
I bought 50 books just for this.
That's crazy.
My friend spent a million won
and still didn't win!
- Really?
- Yeah, really!
Oh? He's here, he's here!
Hi, Sunho.
Sunho...
I heard you sleep with two of things?
Your praise and fame are widespread!
What do I do, he's so handsome!
Sunho, hey!
Oysters are in season these days.
Your 'face-ter'?
Did you wear perfume?
It's my prefer-fume!
Sunho
I heard you don't use
conditioner these days?
Because Han Sunho is already a 'prince'!
What do I do...
Thank you.
Hi!
When is your new book coming out?
I've read your books so much,
I memorized what's on each page and line.
Then...
I'll have to ask you.
There's a public opinion that AI dating
decreases marriage and birth rates?
And
listening to 'ForMe' was one thing, but
if you actually see 'ForMe',
won't it be off-putting?
That's why we,
as a prototype,
are introducing 'ForMe' to the public as...
That's me!
Not only for recognition and buzz,
but also for a friendly image loved
by the public, actor Park Jungwon
will be presented as the prototype 'ForMe'.
Director Yun has a plan for everything.
Right?
How about
you try dating me?
Oh my, what do I do...
Oh my.
The prototype 'ForMe' isn't bad either.
How long until 'ForMe' is
officially released?
How much are the server costs?
What's the expected revenue?
Why is the 2030 generation
so enthusiastic about 'ForMe'?
The success of 'ForMe Version 2'
will be guaranteed
by our existing 7 million users.
Then,
see you at the next report.
Director Yun!
The questions aren't over yet.
Where are you going?
True to the name 'One-Hour Woman, '
she never goes over an hour today either.
Alright, everyone, then
you can direct your questions to me now.
Director Sul,
isn't the meeting time too short?
I beg,
you know Director Yun's style.
Are you telling me to just invest,
without asking anything?
Do you really think that's the case?
We're 'It's You', we do what we say.
We'll contact each of you separately,
so don't feel too left out.
Do you have any questions about 'ForMe'?
Alright, with this,
we conclude Han Sunho's fan signing event!
No, no.
We conclude the book signing
for the re-release!
Director Yun!
Why are you in such a hurry?
I told you,
our project will succeed.
So?
Let's...
have a meal.
The investors' reactions are good.
We haven't had a meal together
since starting this project.
It's not like you can't afford a meal.
Extend the contract period,
increase the contract fee.
Is that it?
No...
I...
just really want to have a meal together.
I mean,
why should we have a meal together
without a clear intention or purpose?
It's a waste of time.
Yes, babe.
I miss you so much too.
But I can't talk right now.
I'm here to see my boyfriend.
Serim...
Babe.
What are you doing?
Oh, I...
I was waiting for you.
Weren't you on a call?
Yeah, just a friend.
Babe, is something wrong?
Hello?
A friend?
Let me explain...
I'm definitely not cheating.
Then?
Uh...
So, it's like...
Who is that guy?
It's not a guy.
Then a girl?
No, not that either.
I mean...
it is a guy,
but...
I'm not cheating,
at all.
Let's go inside and talk.
I'll explain everything.
Okay?
No need to explain.
We're done.
You're just ending it like this?
Without even hearing my side,
just like that?
Just like that?
You could at least ask
what happened and why!
Why should I?
Get off the elevator.
Get off!
Take your love quarrel
outside the elevator, please.
Let go of the button,
before I never see you again.
Eternal love
that transcends time and space,
With 'AI ForMe'!
The only love you're looking for,
only at 'It's You'!
The completely new 'ForMe Version 2'
is coming to you.
Hey!
Why are you getting in my car?
Why are you getting in?
Hey!
Get out, now!
Isn't that the girl from earlier?
Mom has something to tell you.
Hey!
That's too bad for her.
When did you lock the car door?
Seriously...
I'm sorry,
I mistook it for my car.
Are you hurt?
What?
I'll pay for the hospital bill.
What are you...
What are you doing, Director Yun?
It's nothing.
Who does she think she is?
How did the investors react?
You saw it too.
Investors always react well.
Is it really that bad to finish
a schedule in an hour?
Well,
people don't really
know your situation, Bia.
Isn't it perfect?
It's so productive.
Exactly.
That's why you got the nickname
'One-Hour Woman'.
That's just a name the reporters made up,
I really hate that nickname.
How about
we just take down
all the related articles?
No need.
It's quite effective
for marketing, isn't it?
But I'm worried it might get exposed.
Breaking news!
Yun Bia, Director of 'It's You',
collapses after an hour with people.
Her secret revealed.
Imagine how much they'd gossip about it.
Exposed? Me?
No way.
That's not going to happen.
Besides,
I've got this.
You're amazing, Yun Bia.
I know, Sul Jaehee.
Yeah, I'm heading to
the next schedule with Sunho.
I miss you.
When can we meet?
What's the next schedule?
An online fan meeting.
Hey, Han Baekho!
No!
An online book talk.
Hey, you've been really...
Honey,
he keeps threatening me.
Yeah, will you scold him for me?
You're the best, babe.
Finally,
the investor presentation is over!
Successfully!
I never thought
the presentation would be such a hit.
Wasn't this the best presentation ever?
It's over, it's over!
How could it get any better?
Exactly.
- It's over!
- Over, over!
Everyone, you worked so hard today.
Did you see
the investors' reactions earlier?
Oh my, oh my, this is amazing!
Oh, what do we do?
Oh my, oh my, oh my, this is incredible!
The investors' reactions were no joke.
It's the result of everyone's
hard work.
So, we're having a team dinner today.
Sounds great!
Yay, team dinner!
You all know we're close to
launching our prototype, right?
Let's stay focused, everyone.
- Yes!
Are you okay, hmm?
Director.
You did a great job today.
Yeah.
The writer is here.
Oh?
Long time no see, sis.
What's this?
What's with the vibe between you two?
Do you have something to say to me?
Answer the phone.
Should I get it?
Hello?
Who is this?
I'm Serim's boyfriend.
Who are you?
I'm Han Sunho, Serim's boyfriend.
Sunho,
I've heard a lot about you.
What?
I understand Serim.
As you got busier,
Serim felt really lonely,
So she came to me.
Looks like Serim told you about us.
For privacy protection,
conversations with non-users are
limited to 30 seconds.
Hello?
For privacy protection,
conversations with non-users are...
What is this?
'It's You'?
The only one you're looking for,
only at 'It's You'!
What is this about?
Everyone around is using it these days.
Just AI, you know.
It's just talking, just talking.
I told you,
I wasn't cheating.
If it were a person, I'd understand.
How could it be with AI...
You were busy,
I just needed someone
to share my day with.
No,
you let me go because you were
scared of clashing with me.
What?
So our relationship ended.
Coward.
What makes you so different?
Why aren't you writing?
Because of Baekho,
the company, outside activities.
You're not writing a book.
Those are all excuses.
It's the same now,
you're the one avoiding a clash with me.
Both writing and me,
you've let go of everything.
Not writing a book.
those are all excuses.
It's the same now.
You're the one avoiding a clash with me.
You've let go of everything.
Then shortly,
we'll start live book talk to celebrate
the re-release of Han Sunho's debut work.
As we witness the moment
his first work returns to the world,
let's share the emotion and stories.
The number of viewers is insane.
It's a time to share
that emotion and stories.
What's that?
It's Sunho's book talk.
Sunho's book talk.
Not a fan meeting?
How is someone who makes money off
their looks a writer?
Living off by looks isn't
something just anyone can do!
Can you do it, Kyungtae?
Yukyung...
Am I...
Did I finish talking?
Yes, you did, why?
To someone who lives off
their looks right now...
Shall we start the meeting?
Yes!
Meeting.
Alright, meeting, meeting!
This isn't good...
Please leave your warm support messages.
Now, let's welcome writer Han Sunho.
Hello, writer.
Before we start,
I have something to say to the fans.
Okay, then let's start with
the marketing team's report.
We have...
Oh my gosh!
No!
What are you doing right now?
What did you just say?
As of today, I will retire.
Retire?
I mean I will stop
all celebrity activities.
I will return to my main job
and focus solely on writing.
Thank you.
But is it sad that
a writer is going to write?
So,
it's like an idol saying
they'll stop their activities.
Isn't he a writer?
Is he an idol?
I think we should stop talking about this.
Let's stop now, Yukyung.
This is a company,
what is this during a meeting?
You should separate personal
and professional matters!
Director Yun, don't be too harsh.
It's not a life or death issue,
but you shouldn't
let personal matters affect the team!
I'm sorry.
Yukyung said it means
something special to her.
She said he's a lifesaver?
She kept failing to get a job
and was depressed,
not meeting anyone, not leaving the house.
Sunho was a big help to her then.
That's why she could join this company.
Yun Bia!
Hey, I know you're in there!
Bia!
Anyway, I'm really sorry!
I won't do it again.
Is the Director really mad?
What should I do?
It's okay.
Yukyung?
Yes?
Be careful next time.
Let's show each other basic courtesy.
Yes, Director.
Please submit reports on
everyone's progress.
Isn't anyone leaving work?
We still have some overtime left.
Try to finish within the set time.
Habitual overtime is unproductive.
Okay.
Directror Seo,
where's the dinner party tonight?
It's been ages since we had one, right?
Come on, let's finish up
and go to the party.
Hey, Han Sunho!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing
without even consulting me?
See this?
It's already in the news, causing a stir.
They're saying you're practically retired!
The writer wants to write,
is that a problem?
Do you hear yourself?
A writer with no new work for three years
wants to disappear!
That's what I want!
Even if I disappear, being recognized
for my writing is what a writer does.
Who's going to earn money in the meantime?
We're barely making ends meet as it is!
Are you saying
we should all suffer for you?
This isn't right.
Let's retract your retirement.
Just say you were stressed
because you couldn't write, okay?
If you love money so much,
start an entertainment agency.
Han Sunho!
Hey!
Hey, let's toast!
Nice.
Since Sunho hasn't
written in over three years,
we had no choice but to make celebrities.
You've been through a lot.
Still, Sunho connected us
with industry people,
we've gotten a lot of help from him.
Exactly.
Who does Han Sunho think made him famous?
And he stabs us in the back like this?
Hey, don't cross the line.
Only I can criticize Sunho.
Twins calling him brother, huh...
What are we going to do now?
After making money off Sunho,
am I being punished?
That's why I'm saying...
Hey.
You should make a big investment too.
What do you mean?
Baekho,
won't you invest after trusting me?
Trusting you?
No.
No way.
Sunho told me to
be wary of people like you.
That's why he's in that state!
Hey!
You should at least protect the company.
Really?
Thank you for your hard work!
This beer is so refreshing!
You're really excited.
Yukyung,
are you the same person
who was crying earlier?
If you keep laughing and crying like that,
your situation might get worse.
Being sad is one thing,
but the beer is refreshing!
But why didn't Director Yun scold Yukyung?
She's usually so cold-hearted.
Kyungtae!
Still, Director Sul is here...
I'm fine!
Isn't a dinner party
a place to criticize the boss?
Right, right, right.
- Cheers!
- Director Sul, you're the best!
Wouldn't it be great if Director Yun was
as gentle as Director Sul?
Director,
is something wrong?
I was just wondering
if Director Yun got home safely.
I'm worried about sending her home alone.
I really respect you, Director Sul.
How do you always
take care of Director Yun so thoroughly?
Because I'm Bia's family.
I'll just go to the restroom for a bit.
Hey Bia, did you get home okay?
Yeah, I just got home.
Alright, rest well.
Mom, I'm home.
Oh, you're back?
Did you eat?
I haven't eaten yet.
Go wash up quickly, so you can eat.
I'm tired.
You still need to eat.
You'll harm your health otherwise!
Alright, alright.
Hurry up and wash up.
Okay.
But Director Yun...
Doesn't she have any family?
I know, right?
Every time Sul says she's Yun's family.
Doesn't that mean they're really close?
Director Yun never talks about her family.
Right?
That's true.
Well, yeah.
Shall we toast?
- Yes, sounds good.
- Yeah!
Cheers!
You came back?
Don't talk to me, you traitor!
Hey,
did you get home safely?
Hello?
AI... is that it?
Who is this?
You're Baekho's twin brother, right?
There's saved data.
Data?
What are you doing
with someone else's phone?
No wonder...
I thought this time
you'd last long with your girlfriend.
Mina, hello?
Weirdo.
Now you're even using stuff like that?
Mina, cover your ears.
I'm not the only one using this, you know?
Mina, hello?
Hello, Mina?
'It's You'.
The pioneer
of innovative dating paradigms.
Unchanging eternal love.
The one-hour girlfriend.
Why does she look familiar?
"No one can hurt us."
No matter how much you love someone...
Even if you love them so much.
I told you to put
the towel in the laundry bin.
I'll put it in the laundry bin later.
What's wrong with not wanting to get hurt?
Isn't that only natural?
Here!
Some might say what we made is fake,
but it's needed by someone.
How's the food? Is it good?
Mom's cooking skills
haven't gone anywhere, right?
Yeah, the food's good.
A fake that feels real
is needed by someone.
Was there anything today?
Nothing much today, it was fine.
But...
2 WEEKS LATER
Okay, everyone, smile wide!
Yes, great expressions!
Great poses.
Okay, get a bit closer, you two!
Cut them off from being models, seriously.
If Yun cuts me off, that'd be an honor.
Great pose.
You created an AI program for dating,
what do you think love is, Director Yun?
Something very weak and unstable,
that can change at any time.
Of course!
Yun's thoughts are
totally different, right?
Director, there's a big problem!
Why?
Is there something wrong at the company?
Well...
It's a bit hard to explain here.
I'll go check what's going on.
Why? What's happened?
What is this?
Famous actor Mr. Park is suspected
of being involved in stock manipulation.
- Police have launched an investigation.
- We didn't know about stock manipulation.
Yes, yes, we understand for now.
We'll gather more details...
We'll quickly organize
our stance and get back...
Yes, thank you.
Allegations of market manipulation
by an investment consulting firm...
Everyone,
please stay calm and respond carefully.
- Yes!
And Kyungtae, please make sure
Park Jungwon doesn't escape.
Got it.
Claiming they actively promoted it
and reported the damages.
Yes, hello?
They allege intentional manipulation and
false information during the investment...
Reporter, you got a scoop today.
Amazing!
'It's You' is terminating its contract
with Mr. Park effective immediately.
Director Yun,
this is all a misunderstanding.
It's all a conspiracy.
What happened is...
And
for breach of contract,
we will also proceed
with claims for penalties and damages.
I'll explain this.
Director Yun!
Please hear me out!
Mr. Park Jungwon,
can we have an interview?
Don't take pictures!
I said no pictures!
Mr. Kyungtae!
I need to leave and lock the door!
Driver, let's start a live broadcast.
Live broadcast, okay.
We're currently at the
'Its You' headquarters.
As you can see, Mr. Park Jungwon,
caught in a stock manipulation scandal...
Mr. Park Jungwon, are you okay?
Mr. Park Jungwon is attempting to flee.
Mr. Park Jungwon,
is the stock manipulation true?
It's not stock manipulation!
I said it's not stock manipulation!
Then why are you trying to escape,
Mr. Park Jungwon?
Those who entrusted money to Mr. Park are
estimated to have lost 80 billion won.
The prosecution and financial authorities
are investigating Mr. Park's charges!
It seems a full-scale police summons and
search and seizure will follow.
Hey!
This is driving me crazy, seriously!
Park Jungwon!
Time, time, time, time!
Hold on, hold on!
Yun Bia is here too!
Director Yun!
Director Yun, just a moment!
Mr. Park Jungwon, hold on!
Mr. Park Jungwon, just a moment!
Mom will be back soon.
Then we'll go see Dad.
Isn't that the girl from earlier?
She does look quite young.
It's so sad for the kid.
Mom, please open your eyes!
The kid is suffering for her mom's sins.
I thought an hour would be enough.
Wanting more would be greedy.
So I thought I was okay with it.
That's how I've lived my life.
But at that moment,
I started to wonder if I was wrong.
What will happen to me now?
Once,
that must have been a coincidence.
Twice,
this might not be just a coincidence.
Mixed reality dating AI from 'It’s You'.
HOMI
Log in.
You created a program
where people date an AI.
CEO Yun, what do you think
love really is?
Something that can change
whenever it wants
and fragile, and imperfect.
Hey, hey.
Oysters are in season now.
Your “face-ters”?
I heard you don’t use rinse anymore?
Because Han Sunho is already a “Prince”!
Making money off your looks,
how are you a writer?
Living off your looks
isn’t something just anyone can do!
Since I couldn’t make a
sentence for over 3 years.
There was no way but
to make him a celebrity.
Being acknowledged for
writing is what makes a writer.
Even if the world is full of fakes,
this is the cheapest knockoff of them all.
A knockoff?
Isn’t it?
Hey, hey, it's the signal
of beast mode Yun Bia.
Han Sunho, he’s got quite the impact.
'It’s You' CEO Yun Bia.
Dating with Writer Han Sunho?!
This woman, seriously...
Hey, Han Sunho!
She is thinking to play with you alive.
It means we plan to take over
Writer Han Sun-ho’s agency,
which has been held as collateral.
- Wait a second!
- Let go, damn it!
Got a plan?
One way.
What is it?
Dating.
What can’t the two of us do?
Let’s find out what
these people are plotting.
Our goal is not to get caught,
while gathering information
of Writer Han.
Is this the project you
were talking about?
Cancel the contract
or do whatever you want.
Get ready to pay a penalty.
Die, 'It’s You', die!
You’re scared of forming relationships,
aren’t you?
An hour, excuses, all that...
What do you even know about me?
The truth is you’re
afraid I might get hurt.
CEO Yun, you never let people close,
except for CEO Seol.
I thought an hour would be enough.
I'm just worried about being caught.
Breaking News. 'It’s You' CEO Yun Bia
collapses after an hour with people.
Why are you getting in someone else’s car?
Getting caught? Me?
Excuse me!
Now...
What’s going to happen to me?
Does nobody know there’s a problem?
This is the first time
I didn’t collapse after an hour.
What if that person is the one
who can cure your symptoms?
Your destined partner!
Do you have a moment
you wish you could go back to?
I don’t. Everything changes anyway.
So that’s why you made it?
Something that doesn’t change?
Were you always this interested in me?
I’m planning to be interested from now on.
It’s best to call it off here.
Until launch, we need Han Sunho.
Not personally needing Han Sunho?
Why don’t you take care of yourself?
I said I’m fine.
Want me to hold your hand?
You’re addicted, huh?
Guardian angel!
Not a stalker?
You can’t live without me.
When did I... You think I’m easy
just because you found my weakness?
You’re the hardest thing for me,
Yun Bia.
Could it be okay to bet
my fate on this man?