[FEUD]
[Episode 10]
Yue.
It's you.
Heavenly Lord.
Are you alright?
Long Yuan.
Wait!
What are you going to do now?
Your spiritual energy…
I've been sealed for centuries.
You think it's easy
to fight against you guys?
You're throwing your life away.
If it means sparing me from
the monthly torment of the evil energy,
I'd risk everything.
Li Mo, aren't you going to act?
If you hadn't been soft-hearted
and refused to kill her back then,
we wouldn't be in this mess now.
No need to do anything.
Her spiritual energy is exhausted.
She's no threat anymore.
I've heard too many men say they love me.
But it turned out…
they all lied.
Living is just suffering for me.
The only thing I've ever truly wanted
was to see you again
and hear you say
you love me.
I've done the first.
As for the second…
it doesn't matter anymore.
Kill me.
I'm done living with
the torment of the evil energy!
She's your destined tribulation.
No matter what you do,
you can't escape it.
You say you study healing arts,
that you were born to help others,
but you couldn't even save me.
How can you save anyone else?
There are countless forms
of love in this world,
not just romantic love.
So,
this is truly my tribulation.
I told you, I'll free you
from the evil energy.
How did you do that?
I love you.
But not the way lovers do.
Mine is the kind of love
that seeks to save all beings.
Think carefully.
Not all the men you met
were pretending to care.
So… you're saying yes?
They truly cared for you.
Wonderful!
The one who pretended to care…
Honglian.
was you.
I've come back to marry you.
You only wanted
to resolve the evil energy.
You never truly cared for them.
That's why their heart blood
couldn't resolve your evil energy.
The root of it lies in you,
not in them.
So,
it's not about being loved.
It's about learning to love.
Exactly.
As long as you have love in your heart,
no evil spirits or energy can touch you.
Actually, I should thank you.
You helped me understand my tribulation.
In the past, I only cared about
saving the world and helping others,
but I never truly understood
what it meant to help someone.
It means to feel their pain
so you can ease their suffering.
I see.
Now
I finally understand
what you meant by "sin."
I've heard
there's a Jade Pool in Empyrean.
Please, take me there
so I may begin cultivation anew.
I won't need long to regain my form.
This time, I won't go astray again.
Alright, I promise you.
Are you really okay?
Have you forgotten what I practice?
These minor injuries are nothing.
Good. Then let's get down to business.
Mountains in clouds; white clouds rise.
In the tranquil mountains, the Way
guides those destined to follow it.
Mountains in clouds; white clouds rise.
In the tranquil mountains, the Way
guides those destined to follow it.
Young man, are you getting on the boat?
Yes.
May I ask how much you charge?
I ferry people for pleasure alone.
I don't want
spiritual pills or magical tools.
I only ferry those destined to meet me.
In that case, I'll trouble you.
Come, get on the boat.
Hold on tight.
Mountains in clouds; white clouds rise.
Young man.
I sense the yin and yang
in your body are in conflict.
Did you use the demon clan's
sacred object, the Sky-Reaching Ladder?
I did.
Do you understand
how dangerous that thing is?
I do.
And yet you dared
to come to the Nine Heavens
as a mortal?
From what I can see, you don't seem like
the type to do whatever it takes
just to become immortal.
So, what is it you seek
in the Nine Heavens?
I'm looking for someone I knew.
The Nine Heavens are vast and boundless.
There are countless
immortals and cultivators here.
Do you know where the person
you're looking for resides?
Canglei Palace, Danxia Land.
Canglei Palace?
Yes.
That place
belongs to Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
You've heard of it?
Who hasn't heard of Heavenly Lord Dacheng?
Come on, sit down.
Heavenly Lord Dacheng has powerful magic.
In the Nine Heavens,
he's one of the most powerful immortals.
If he was really that powerful,
he'd have ascended to Empyrean long ago.
Why is he still here?
Sounds like
you've got a bone to pick
with Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
You're not here in the Danxia Land
to cause him trouble, are you?
If I say I am,
will you believe me?
Fate and karma
are beyond my comprehension.
Hold on tight.
Mountains in clouds; white clouds rise.
In the tranquil mountains, the Way
guides those destined to follow it.
Immortal Lord Li Mo.
Is this Immortal Lord Long Yuan?
What are you doing?
Heavenly Lord, Immortal Lord Li Mo.
Say something.
Long time no see,
Siling.
How dare you show yourself
around Master again?
You...
You've got the wrong person.
I'm Li Qingyue,
not Siling.
I saw you use the Blazing Fire just now.
That was the magic once used
by Divine Lord Siling.
I... I don't know why.
It… it just happened
in the heat of the moment…
Siling and Master are of the same origin.
When one falls, the other rises.
Master is severely injured,
and you've gained new power.
Can you explain that?
We were pulled into the Vortex of Stars
and ended up in the Land of Ruins.
From here on, you have to travel alone.
I ended up here by chance.
If any immortal resides here,
could you give me directions?
Is anyone here?
You work for the Heavenly Lord?
Heavenly Lord?
You mean Heavenly Lord Dacheng, Bai Jiusi?
So you're not with him.
Who are you?
Give it back!
This is yours?
Give it to me!
Who exactly are you?
Jingyun Sect.
Zhang Suan.
Zhang Suan?
You're Li Qingyue's senior brother?
Oh no.
Why are you following me?
You still have my pendant.
Give it back.
Where did you get that?
A family heirloom?
You seem very interested in it.
You mentioned Qingyue just now.
You know her?
Where is she?
Why are you looking for her?
She's in danger.
Master, your old injury
has affected your heart meridian.
Now with your spiritual energy drained,
a full recovery will be very difficult.
I've searched through
ancient texts and found a possible method
that might help.
But the required ingredients
are extremely rare.
What do you need?
Use snake slough as the base,
and combine it with aconite, cinnamon twig,
processed monkshood, and asarum.
Refine it with
the Chaos Fire for 49 days and nights.
Most of those ingredients
can be found in Danxia Land.
There's still a wisp
of the Chaos Fire left in Empyrean.
Immortal Lord Long Yuan
can go and borrow it.
That shouldn't be a problem.
The Chaos Fire is easy to obtain.
But getting the snake slough
is the real challenge.
Ordinary snake slough
won't do anything for Master's condition.
It must be from a flying snake.
And it should be the skin
it sheds at the moment of transformation.
Flying snake?
Humans have primordial spirits;
beasts have golden cores.
But a flying snake
is neither human nor beast.
With a primordial spirit in its head,
it's a born divine being.
As the primordial spirit
in its head grows stronger,
when the time is right,
heavenly lightning will strike,
shattering its shell
and freeing it from the physical body.
At that moment,
its primordial spirit
will be released from its head.
The snake will shed its skin
and gain wings, becoming a true flying snake.
And what if it hasn't transformed yet?
A flying snake that hasn't transformed
looks no different from an ordinary snake.
Its slough is also no different.
Why didn't you mention any of this before?
Because you'd never
been injured to the extent of…
From what I've found,
Siling's old mount, the White Snake,
has indeed perished.
And its primordial spirit?
That remains unknown.
How is she now?
Her Ladyship…
Li Qingyue
was taken by Immortal Lord Long Yuan
to the dungeon in the mountain.
While you were severely injured,
he temporarily took over everything.
You're still injured!
Pass through this formation,
and you can leave the Ruins.
Alright.
You're not coming?
Since you know the way out,
why are you still trapped here?
I have my reasons for staying.
You just need to focus on your own path.
Don't ask about anything else.
Sorry.
Wait.
Head east.
Ride the wind for 1,000 miles,
and you'll reach the place
you're looking for.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Zhang Suan?
[Xiao Jingshan]
So this is my fate.
So be it.
I've hated birds my whole life.
Guess luck
just wasn't on your side today.
Who goes there? Tell me your name.
As a human cultivator,
you dared to come to the Nine Heavens
but don't have the guts to meet me?
Boy.
Got any wine?
Brat, you actually tried
to fool me with water.
Don't leave yet.
Throw that dead bird somewhere far away.
You killed it?
So what if I did?
You killed it
but don't have the guts
to dispose of its body?
Just do as I say.
Spare me the lectures!
You… are hurt?
Nonsense.
Who could possibly hurt me?
You're severely injured.
I'm not injured.
Your spiritual platform is shattered,
and your power is fading.
You call that "not injured"?
You ask too many questions.
Get lost.
Someone just told me
if I ride the wind eastward
for 1,000 miles,
I'll reach Canglei Palace.
But I've flown for ages and seen nothing.
You've been
in the Nine Heavens for so long.
Do you know where Canglei Palace is?
That's Bai Jiusi's residence.
Why are you going there?
To find someone.
You mean Bai Jiusi?
I know a thing or two
about Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
He's an arrogant man—
temperamental
and ruthless.
You're just a lowly human cultivator.
Aren't you afraid
he'll kill you with a single strike?
It's fine if you don't want to tell me.
Three, two, one.
Drop.
Brat.
You want to get out of here?
I can help you.
But you must promise me one thing.
Are you here to save me?
Do you also believe
I'm Divine Lord Siling?
When did you and Honglian
start plotting together?
In the illusion?
At the Lanyue House?
Or had it all been arranged
when you were in the Hell Ruins?
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
I've played along with you
for long enough.
When are you going to stop pretending?
I'm not pretending.
Your power and mine shift in opposition.
I lost my fire magic
after the battle with Honglian.
But you became better
at controlling the Blazing Fire.
Clearly, you had joined forces with her.
You lured Li Mo out for her,
and she helped you wound me badly
so you could reclaim your power.
You say you're not Divine Lord Siling.
Then tell me—
where did you learn
to control fire like that?
Speak!
So when you called Yue,
you were never calling me.
I don't know how
I suddenly learned
the Fire-Parting Technique.
All I know is,
when I saw you frozen in ice,
there was only one thought in my mind—
to save you, no matter the cost.
I just didn't expect…
I didn't expect that in the end,
it would become my crime.
Heavenly Lord,
I wanted to save you.
Was that wrong?
So you've made up your mind
not to tell me the truth, huh?
If you've already
judged me guilty in your heart,
why bother questioning me at all?
For both of us,
it's just a waste of time.
A waste of time?
Indeed.
Tolerating you for so long
has indeed been a waste of time.
Yue, your magic and mine
counterbalance each other.
When one wanes, the other grows.
If one of us is badly wounded,
the other's magic surges.
I'll ask you one last time.
What exactly are you planning?
Confess,
and I'll stop.
Before I answer,
can you answer something for me first?
Go ahead.
All the kindness you showed me before—
was it because of me
or because of Yue?
Listen carefully.
My name is Li Qingyue.
I used to live
at the foot of Yufan Mountain.
My father's surname is Li,
and my mother's is Jiang.
I joined the Jingyun Sect
at the age of eight
and guarded the gate for 11 years.
At 19, I married into Canglei Palace
and became the wife
of Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
I have my own friends in the sect.
I have my own joys and sorrows.
I have my own life!
I am Li Qingyue.
Always,
just Li Qingyue.
You're still lying.
Must I verify it myself?
How dare I trouble
the Heavenly Lord to verify it personally?
You just want me to get hurt, right?
I'll do it myself.
♪ But you kept making it cry ♪
♪ Kept breaking it down ♪
♪ Kept letting it slowly shatter
from the inside out ♪
♪ With no light to guide the way ♪
♪ It turned cold and dark like a stone ♪
♪ And you threw it away,
left it to suffer alone ♪
♪ You made it feel it all ♪
♪ The torment of a living hell ♪
Heavenly Lord, do you know the answer now?
♪ The kind of pain that makes you
want to tear yourself apart ♪
♪ It looked around at all the others ♪
♪ But somehow, only it was wrong ♪
♪ As if love was just
its own foolish fantasy all along ♪
♪ In my world,
there's never been room for mercy ♪
Master.
Li Mo said you're badly injured.
This place is cold and damp.
You really didn't need to come in person.
Let me handle such trivial matters.
My Lord, has Her Ladyship
done anything wrong?
She's just recovered from a serious illness.
Her foundation is not yet stable.
The dungeon is cold and damp. Please…
Master, what's wrong?
Send her back to Yuewu House.
Thank you, My Lord.
-Let go of me!
-Don't move.
What are you doing?
Boy, fortune has smiled upon you.
From this moment on,
every word I say—
you must remember it by heart.
My name is Xiao Jingshan.
I'm from Nanwu in Ning.
My parents and brothers
were all ordinary folk.
At the age of 21,
I got married and had a son.
Unfortunately, I fell victim
to some scumbags.
My family was destroyed overnight.
So I started cultivation,
expecting to avenge their deaths one day.
But my fellow disciples were arrogant,
keeping making things hard for me.
By my fourth year,
they expelled me from the sect.
From then on, I trained alone.
I drew power from nature
and learned wisdom from life.
I gave up on the Way to find the Way
and saw truth through illusions.
Abandoning the righteous path,
I gained true power.
Why are you telling me all this?
You are to become my disciple.
Of course I must tell you my story.
Who said I want to be your disciple?
I…
Too noisy.
Life is like a dream,
a dream hard to wake from.
I'm nearing the end of my life.
Yet a disciple showed up out of nowhere.
It seems the heavens haven't forsaken me.
Time is short.
Let's hurry up.
First, kowtow to me.
Good, good.
Enough.
I'm at death's door.
These past few days, I've mastered
an extremely profound sword technique.
I've decided to pass it on to you.
Once your power has greatly increased,
you can leave Taiyi Peak.
Boy, I'll only demonstrate this once.
Watch carefully.
Qi gathers in the upper dantian;
spirit spring flows to qihai;
purple flame settles at shenque;
the sword bridges yin and yang.
Boy, did you see it clearly?
This sword technique is exquisite.
What's it called?
I haven't decided yet.
Do you have any enemies?
There is one person.
I suppose you could call him that.
Who?
Heavenly Lord Dacheng, Bai Jiusi.
Good!
Then let's call it
the Immortal-Slaying Sword Technique.
Stop yelling, brat!
I'm passing my life's cultivation to you.
You've hit the jackpot!
My Lord, I need to tell you something.
Even though you've permitted it,
Immortal Lord Long Yuan
refuses to release her.
As of now, Her Ladyship
is still locked up in the dungeon.
Go and release her.
Yes.
Don't do that!
Go out.
I have something to report to Master.
You have no right to stay here.
What happened?
I heard from Li Mo about the flying snake,
so I used
the Spirit-Seeking Spell to look for it.
The White Snake is not in Hell.
Either it has perished
from the Three Realms,
or it simply didn't die.
Between the two,
I'm inclined to believe the latter.
Master, Li Qingyue conjured
the Blazing Fire that day.
We all saw it with our own eyes.
There's no way we could be mistaken.
Siling harmed you
more than once in the past.
Now that she has reappeared,
she definitely has ulterior motives.
Master, you mustn't go soft again.