[FEUD]
[Episode 32]
Master.
These are... all that's left of
Jingyun Sect.
In this time of crisis,
I'm grateful for your loyalty.
I thank you all.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
Jingyun Sect has suffered
heavy casualties.
Divine Lord needs more people.
I should go over.
Alright.
I'll let you.
Go if you want to.
Remember to come visit Canglei Palace
when you have time.
Come and check on your father.
Previously, I was burdened with evil energy.
I only knew how to hurt others.
Now, I want to be like him.
I want to roam the Three Realms,
aiding and saving those in need.
We need to carefully consider
how to revive our Yinlian Sect.
Do you really want to go?
We need to reclaim what we've lost.
In the past, I always had reasons
to make her wait.
After this experience,
I've learned to cherish those around me.
So...
I will accompany Xingman back
to Yinlian Sect.
I'll help her revive the sect
and set it on the right course.
Our master has passed away.
If you stay,
you'll be the next Sect Leader.
You're more suitable than I am.
I have no cultivation to my name.
How could I...
Who says the Sect Leader
must be chosen based on cultivation?
Your unwavering conviction
puts me to shame.
Junior,
rest assured.
If Jingyun Sect ever needs me
in the future,
I'll come back anytime.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
I'm off.
Have a safe journey.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
You've reconciled with your father?
Not exactly.
Just trying to avoid trouble.
After all, hatred itself is exhausting.
You're more enlightened than I am.
Divine Lord.
Why did Xiao Jingshan's death
made the mortal realm's drought even worse?
Is the calamity still ongoing?
Xiao Jingshan wasn't the calamity itself.
He merely accelerated it.
The demonic energy leaked from
the Infinite Stele
has further intensified this calamity.
Birth, existence, decay, and void.
Everything seems unavoidable.
No.
There's still a way.
Divine Lord.
Are you planning to exhaust all your power?
I was able to slay the
Drought Dragon back then
and broke the calamity.
Now, I can also become the rain that
nurtures all things.
But Divine Lord—
I was born a god.
I’ve benefited enough from what the world
has bestowed upon me.
It's time to do something
to repay this world.
[Mercy Over All]
Back then, the Primordial God exhausted
all his spiritual energy
to create the primordial world,
forming the heaven and earth of today.
Though my virtue cannot compare to his,
I wish to follow his example
and restore joy and peace
to the mortal realm.
[Prosperity]
You are...
Xi E, the Goddess of Time.
Looks like Bai Jiusi has mentioned me to you.
What do you want?
I sensed a massive temporal disturbance,
so I came to investigate.
I didn't expect that an
ordinary human cultivator
could forge such a powerful magical artifact.
That's actually impressive.
Xiao Jingshan was
no ordinary human cultivator.
When we confronted him earlier,
why didn't you appear?
Xiao Jingshan was the karma binding you all.
I couldn't interfere.
I'm here to give you a heads-up.
This magical artifact can reverse time,
allowing you to return to the past.
Are you serious?
Of course it is.
However, I must first remind you.
Changing the past doesn't necessarily
change the future.
Every cycle of life has
its predetermined karma.
These two have some spiritual energy.
I'll take them with me.
Do you want to go with her?
She can not only save Sister Ning Yan,
but also conjure endless delicious food.
Until we meet again.
Husband.
Husband!
Mother.
Jingshan!
Father!
All of you are alright?
A young lady
suddenly called us out.
As long as you you're safe.
Has it really changed?
[Prosperity]
Where's Xiao Jingshan?
Didn't he die on
Tianmu Peak yesterday?
Zi Yang, Li Mo,
Lyu Suguan, Shangguan Riyue, and Cang Tu.
Are Bai Jiusi and the others... still alive?
What's wrong with you?
So that's what it means.
Nothing.
-Just…
-♪ Spirits, return home ♪
♪ Spirits, return home ♪
What is he doing?
He's guiding the souls of our...
♪ Spirits, return home ♪
departed brothers.
Are you willing to become the Sect Leader
of Jingyun Sect?
♪ Spirits, return home ♪
Qingyue.
Grandmaster.
What are you...
♪ Spirits, return home ♪
You should go back first.
I have something to discuss
with Grandmaster.
♪ Spirits, return home ♪
Yes.
[Prosperity]
Grandmaster.
I gave the Qiyue Sword to Xiao Jingshan.
Are you not mad at me?
You did it for our sect members,
so there's nothing wrong.
Xuan Wei.
In the past, it was my selfish desire.
I dragged you into dealing with Bai Jiusi.
Now I've long since come to my senses.
You should also follow your own path.
I sense that your cultivation is complete.
You're just one step away from
ascending to the Nine Heavens.
Don't hold yourself back anymore.
When I was young, I was unfortunate.
My mother lost her life giving birth to me.
During the year of the great drought,
my father also passed away due to famine.
As a child of just a few years old,
during the year of the great famine,
I couldn't avoid being bullied.
It was hard to make a living.
Fortunately,
I met you, Grandmaster.
You taught me righteousness and
imparted the Dao to me.
Your great kindness is like that of
a second parent to me.
I have no way to repay you in this life.
Why are you...
saying all of this suddenly?
[Mercy Over All]
In the past, I was always trapped
within myself.
There were some things I couldn't
think through clearly.
Now the time has come.
Only now have I attained wisdom,
and understood the Dao.
What is your Dao?
To repay my debts,
like a crow feeding its parents,
is my way of repaying your kindness.
What are you doing?
This is the Spirit Dulling Herb.
I added some to the water.
It's harmless to the body.
It will incapacitate you for
just half a day.
[Prosperity]
What are you trying to do?
Grandmaster.
The reason I gave the Qiyue Sword
to Xiao Jingshan
was not entirely for the sake of
our fellow sect members.
But rather...
I didn't want to die by his hand.
In the past few days when you
went around looking for people,
I sought guidance through several readings.
According to the hexagrams,
our Jingyun Sect won't be able
to stop Xiao Jingshan.
I wanted to make a final fight,
but none of it worked out.
It forced me to believe what
the hexagrams showed.
I...
must die.
Either I die by Xiao Jingshan's hand,
or...
I could die for you, Grandmaster.
I am choosing the latter.
What nonsense are you talking about?
For tens of thousands of years,
whenever there were floods or famines,
plagues or insect infestations,
mortals who were in the thick of it
always felt hopeless about the future,
and struggled to make a living.
But every time,
as long as they gritted their teeth
and persevered,
they could always get through it.
All this didn't come from
praying to gods or Buddha,
but from their own
persistence and endurance.
Grandmaster, you once said
[May your spirit shine across all realms]
that we, as human cultivators,
shouldn't just aim for
enlightenment and ascension.
To achieve the right results of cultivation,
we should also think about this land,
and what we can do
for all these living beings.
I do not wish to become an immortal,
because I've been waiting
for this opportunity.
You have a mortal body.
Your strength is not enough to
shake the heavens.
Even if you sacrifice yourself,
it won't make any difference.
Xuan Wei,
there's no need to push yourself.
As you know,
there's nothing holding me back.
Don’t sabotage this opportunity.
Grandmaster.
Before Xiao Jingshan died,
he gave this to you.
It means he knew
there were many things that
only you could answer.
The greatest blessing of this lifetime
is meeting you, Grandmaster.
Even if I could start over,
I would not regret
helping you with everything I've done.
[Prosperity]
Please, Grandmaster, bestow this destiny
upon your disciple.
[Mercy Over All]
Grandmaster,
I...
shall leave now.
Please take care of yourself.
Take meetings and partings lightly,
and let your heart guide your happiness.
Your great kindness, Grandmaster,
I'll repay in the next life.
[Mercy Over All]
This is the place, I suppose.
Divine Lord!
Divine Lord.
I'm so glad you're alright.
I saw the auspicious rain falling...
and thought you...
It's Xuan Wei.
Divine Lord.
This was his own choice,
just like mine.
From the moment we met you, Divine Lord,
we've decided to follow you till death.
The greatest blessing of this lifetime
is meeting you, Grandmaster.
Even if I could start over,
I would not regret
helping you with everything I've done.
All of you've taught me a lesson.
In this cycle,
we've made too many mistakes
and had too many regrets.
Since we have the chance,
we can help our other selves
in other cycles
experience fewer setbacks.
Before Xiao Jingshan died,
he gave this to you.
It means he knew
there were many things that
only you could answer.
I think I know how to use this now.
You...
Don't just hurt yourself.
I can help you eradicate the evil energy.
What... what are you doing?
This is all I can do for you now.
You'll have to explain the rest yourselves.
Hit him! Hit him!
Let me go!
Hit him hard!
Hit him where it hurts!
Let me go!
Hit him! Hit him!
Let's beat him to death!
Beat him to death! Beat him to death!
Punch him!
Hit him! Beat him to death!
Alright, let's go.
What a nuisance!
Who are you?
I am an immortal from the heavens.
I see that you have some spiritual energy.
So I've descended to help you.
Take this book.
Study and cultivate yourself diligently.
You will surely achieve great things.
Dear immortal,
what can I do for you?
Practice cultivation well.
One day, you will establish a great sect
that saves the world.
Oh, right.
In the future,
if you meet a girl who gives you flowers,
remember to cherish her.
A girl who gives me flowers?
I under—
Finally... I did it!
Who are you?
Be careful not to disturb the fetus.
What did you say?
I just want to tell you something.
Take a seat.
Let me heal you.
Hua Ruyue,
you didn't heed
a single word I said.
You once promised me to save
Meng Changqin only once.
That's why I agreed to go through
the love tribulation with you.
But you broke your promise.
Now,
you've violated the heavenly rules again.
I can't be tolerant of you anymore.
The Heavenly Emissary was not easy
to deal with, was he?
What did you say?
Alright.
I know everything now.
You helped me stop
the Heavenly Emissary just now.
Also,
don't think about secretly taking
the heavenly punishment for me.
Even if I agreed to let you bear it alone,
the child within me wouldn't agree.
♪ I wish I could ♪
♪ Travel back to the past ♪
What?
♪ Forget all the grudges and griefs ♪
♪ Lean against you, and watch us smile
in the glistening mirror ♪
♪ By the water, the moon's reflection
is faintly bright ♪
♪ Thin mist curls gently, light as smoke ♪
♪ Looking back at the old scenery
of days gone by ♪
♪ No trace in sight ♪
♪ Entangled with love ♪
♪ Mending and patching a broken heart ♪
♪ The kiss still lingers on my lips ♪
♪ Brilliant as the stars in the sky ♪
♪ I pretend to stroll with ease ♪
♪ Avoiding the gaze of your eyes ♪
♪ I'm already in tears, though ♪
♪ Wetting a dragonfly in mid-flight ♪
♪ I wish I could ♪
♪ Travel back to the past ♪
♪ Forget all the grudges and griefs ♪
♪ Lean against you, and watch us smile
in the glistening mirror ♪
♪ I wish I could ♪
♪ Travel back to the past ♪
♪ Forget all the grudges and griefs ♪
♪ Lean against you, and watch us smile
in the glistening mirror ♪
Jingyun Sect will be entrusted
to you from now on.
With you here,
I can rest assured.
Divine Lord,
why can't I leave with you?
Because I'm going to find someone
who has disappeared.
This search might take
tens of thousands of years.
You can live your own life
instead of revolving around me.
Will you come back?
Perhaps.
[Everlasting Grace and Legacy]
♪ I embrace the wind
and drink a jar of wine ♪
♪ The willow in my dream
has withered in autumn ♪
♪ I say everything is fine with a smile,
despite the shedding tears ♪
♪ Melancholy takes up half of my life ♪
♪ I wish tender love
can last more than a moment ♪
♪ Love cannot be retracted ♪
♪ Thoughts crowd up
my mind, but I can't say any ♪
♪ I'm not ashamed to be in
the prison of my own making ♪
♪ Only when I'm drunk
can I dream about my beloved one ♪
Bai Jiusi.
♪ Across the magpie bridge,
I see the bright river of stars ♪
I'm here to accompany you.
♪ As I look at the mountains,
your smile is everywhere ♪
♪ How can I easily let go? ♪
♪ Drink this up, for butterflies
shall keep us company ♪
♪ I'm missing you on
this breezy spring day ♪
♪ The moon rises above the willow tree ♪
♪ It is dusk again ♪
♪ I wish tender love
can last more than a moment ♪
♪ Love cannot be retracted ♪
♪ Thoughts crowd up
my mind, but I can't say any ♪
♪ I'm not ashamed to be in
the prison of my own making ♪
♪ Only when I'm drunk
can I dream about my beloved one ♪
♪ Across the magpie bridge,
I see the bright river of stars ♪
♪ As I look at the mountains,
your smile is everywhere ♪
♪ How can I easily let go? ♪
♪ Drink this up, for butterflies
shall keep us company ♪
♪ I'm missing you on
this breezy spring day ♪
♪ The moon rises above the willow tree ♪
♪ It is dusk again ♪
♪ Drink this up, for butterflies
shall keep us company ♪
♪ I'm missing you on
this breezy spring day ♪
♪ The moon rises above the willow tree ♪
♪ It is dusk again ♪
♪ Melancholy takes up half of my life ♪
Ruyue.
Why are you staring at me?
Are you expecting me to
take responsibility for you?
[Out of the primordial chaos rose two forces;
hatred is but love taken to its extreme.]
[The love tribulation is over.]
[From now on, we will never
be separated in this world.]
[The End]