[FEUD]
[Episode 26]
Why are you guarding the gate?
My juniors are all excited about
coming to the Nine Heavens
for the first time.
Forget the gate.
Go get some rest.
We're in for a brutal fight tomorrow.
Qingyue.
Do we really have to fight?
May I ask, are you Divine Lord Siling?
I am.
Greetings, Your Divinity.
I'm Lingshu,
the divine official
under Lord Yu Ya of the Wenxuan Palace.
I've come here
to register the immortals
who have ascended
to the Nine Heavens.
I've worked
at Wenxuan Palace for 1,000 years.
I've seen husbands and wives ascend,
brothers ascend,
but never an entire sect
ascend all at once.
You're all powerful and blessed.
Such destiny is rare even in 1,000 years.
Congratulations.
Let's start with this gentleman here.
May I have your name?
No need for registration.
Why not?
We didn't ascend to become immortals.
If not for immortality,
why did you come to the Nine Heavens?
To spill blood.
But the Nine Heavens hold no mortals,
only immortals.
Then we'll kill immortals.
Senior, just now Divine Lord Siling said
you killed
Master Qing Yang of Jingyun Sect.
What's that about?
She must be holding a grudge
over my earlier warning
and wants to get rid of me,
so she framed me to ruin my name.
But Siling has never
done anything like that before.
What?
You trust her more than me?
I'm just thinking
maybe there's been some misunderstanding.
I'm upright and honest.
If I did it, I'll own up to it.
But if I didn't,
no one's pinning it on me.
Tomorrow, I'll fight Siling myself.
Even if she kills me,
I won't let a false accusation
stain my name.
Don't worry, Senior Long Yuan.
We won't let you fight alone.
We'll fight by your side
till the very end.
till the very end!
We'll fight by your side
Calm down. Master will return soon.
Where's Fan Jiaojiao?
He seems to have gone
to pick up his daughter.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
Grandmaster, someone
from Canglei Palace is here
to take Celestial Attendant Fan back.
[Prosperity]
I-Immortal Lord Fan
sent me to bring Miss Ling'er home.
Master?
[Prosperity]
It figures.
The moment he fed Ling'er
the Nightmare Flower,
I should've known
he wouldn't come to fetch her himself.
Celestial Attendant Fan
has suffered enough.
I just hope that when she wakes up,
she won't hate me
for sending her back to her father.
Master, you only did that
for her safety.
Ling'er, don't blame me.
This is the only way to keep you still
and out of trouble.
Immortal Lord,
after Miss Ling'er wakes up,
she might end up hating you forever.
It's not like she ever liked me very much.
I'm protecting her.
You're getting more insolent by the day—
barging in uninvited.
You still haven't answered
the question I asked at the gate earlier.
What question?
Do we… have to fight tomorrow?
What do you think?
Why else have we
come all the way up here?
I don't like Bai Jiusi
or the people from Canglei Palace,
but there's something I want to ask.
Do you really believe Master Qing Yang
was killed by Long Yuan?
Who else could it have been?
Instead of overthinking,
you'd be better off getting some rest.
That's definitely…
It hurts, so he's real.
He's real?
Don't you believe me?
Stop.
Junior, I'll do it myself.
How is it?
How is it? Is that him?
His Lordship is back.
His Lordship is back!
He's back!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, Senior. I'm so sorry.
Master, Siling was the one
who started it this time.
She clearly wants to get back at me
for declaring war last time.
In my opinion,
we shouldn't have
let Jingyun Sect off the hook last time.
Master, why are you
looking at me like that?
Do you really believe Siling's
false accusation against me?
Master.
Long Yuan may have been a bit aggressive,
but I don't think
he'd have killed Qing Yang.
There has to be
some misunderstanding here.
Now that you've returned,
why don't you invite
Divine Lord Siling over for a talk?
No need.
My Lord, you mean…
Open the barrier tomorrow.
Let them in.
Master, you've finally made up your mind.
Tomorrow, allow me
to be the first to charge into battle.
It's about time we redecorated
Canglei Palace.
You're awake, Ling'er.
What have you done to me?
Where's my spiritual energy?
What the hell did you do to me?
Ling'er, don't blame me.
You kept ignoring my warnings,
so I had no choice
but to destroy your cultivation…
to make you a bit more obedient
and keep you from getting in danger again.
You wiped away over 200 years
of my cultivation?
It's nothing serious. Don't worry.
Even without your spiritual energy,
you're still immortal.
From now on, I'll protect you.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Siling is about to attack us soon.
I need to go help Master.
I can't stay with you now.
If you need anything, tell Zhu Li.
Tell Zhu Li.
Stop right there! I said stop!
Come on.
Once we leave,
you'll lead the outer disciples
to activate the protective formation.
After that,
not even a bird will get through,
and no magic can break it.
Yes, Grandmaster.
You all just stay in the sect.
No matter the danger,
I'll follow you without hesitation,
Grandmaster.
You three stay here as well.
Grandmaster…
When Grandmaster gives an order,
you follow it.
Yes.
Jiang Bian.
I'm here.
You'll stay behind to guard the gate too.
Yes, Grandmaster.
I...
Master, please be careful.
It's time. Let's go.
Farewell, Grandmaster.
Steward Cang?
Why are you the only one here to face us?
Is there no one else in Canglei Palace?
I've been ordered to welcome you.
His Lordship
has prepared a bridal palanquin for you.
Please come with me.
Bai Jiusi has returned?
What did you tell him?
I came here for a fight.
Why prepare a bridal palanquin for me?
His Lordship said that
if you're willing
to come in the palanquin,
you'll leave here today feeling satisfied.
Is he offering up
Long Yuan's head as a gift?
You'll see soon enough.
Fine. I'd like to see what trick
Bai Jiusi has up his sleeve this time.
Master has her reasons for doing things.
All we need to do is follow her lead.
What is Master thinking?
Why is Canglei Palace adorned this way?
I heard he even
sent a bridal palanquin to fetch Siling.
This place doesn't look prepared
for battle at all.
It looks more like a wedding.
Is he really offering up Senior Long Yuan
as an apology?
I don't think so.
Did you see that sword on the table?
That's the Qiyue Sword.
It's on par with Siling's Zhuri Sword.
It was refined for 10,000 years.
It can split the heavens
and slay immortals.
Forged from
10,000-year-old cold stone,
it's a natural counter
to Siling's fire-based power.
I think these festive decorations
are just bait to lower Siling's guard.
Once she's here,
she probably won't walk out.
Good.
Let's see how long
Siling can keep up that arrogant act.
Woman!
If it's you, come down!
Answer me, is it you?
Yes, it's me.
Have you opened your eyes?
I've opened my eyes.
Woman, you've lost!
Yes, I've lost.
-She's opened her eyes.
She's opened her eyes.
We've won!
We've won! We've won!
Form up!
If you've got the guts, let us out!
Don't play dirty tricks!
What a nuisance.
Master, are you injured?
I'm fine.
The palanquin is broken.
Please wait a moment, Divine Lord.
I'll have another one brought over.
No need. I didn't need it anyway.
I'll go there myself.
Divine Lord Siling is here.
You've come.
After hiding like a coward all this time,
you finally decided to show up.
How dare you speak to my master like that!
Bai Jiusi, what are you scheming now?
When we married last time,
we didn't have a proper wedding.
I've always regretted that.
Since we've got the chance today,
I thought I'd make it up to you.
Look around, so many honored guests.
Doesn't it feel like
I've held a wedding banquet for you?
Stop stalling.
Are you trying to protect Long Yuan?
Don't worry. You'll get what you came for.
Ruyue.
You look beautiful in red.
By my count, I've married you three times.
In the temple of the Primordial God,
Xiaoqiu Valley,
Tianmu Peak, and Jingyun Sect…
Unfortunately,
none of them ended well.
I'm truly sorry.
Enough of this nonsense.
Just answer me this.
I'm going to kill Long Yuan.
Will you let me or not?
Long Yuan, come here.
Long Yuan, I want you to swear an oath.
No matter what happens in the future,
you'll never harm Ruyue
or anyone from Jingyun Sect.
If you break this oath,
your body and soul will perish completely,
and you'll never find peace.
So you've decided to protect him?
Swear it!
I'll say it one last time—
swear it!
I, Long Yuan,
hereby swear
that no matter what happens in the future,
I'll never harm Siling
or anyone from Jingyun Sect.
If I break this oath,
my body and soul will perish completely!
Great.
Go back.
Bai Jiusi,
since you've made your decision,
what are you waiting for?
Draw your sword!
-What are you doing?
-You said it yourself.
A life for a life would be enough.
Your master's life…
I'll repay it for my disciple.
Master!
Don't move!
I made a terrible mistake…
that's beyond saving.
Ruyue.
I'm truly sorry.
Master!
Siling! Give my master back!
Kill them all!
Don't forget the oath
Master just made you swear.
Are you going to defy
Master's last order?
Avenge Master! Avenge Master!
Avenge Master!
Form up!
Grandmaster!
Zhang Suan, what are you doing?
How is Grandmaster?
Go find Zhang Suan.
But Grandmaster...
Do as I say. Go find him!
Find Zhang Suan!
-Yes.
You…
Long Yuan.
Something seems
to have happened among them.
Let them go.
[Lord Qing Xu, Yuan Chenghua]
Break!
Oh, no.
He's heading for the Infinite Stele.
After him!
Yes.
Sword, return!
Bai Jiusi, you didn't die?
You were putting on an act
to fool me just now.
For someone like you,
a coward hiding behind others,
if we hadn't staged that,
you never would've exposed yourself.
I didn't expect that
in the end, I actually helped bring
the two of you back together.
It seems you know a lot about our past.
To deal with me,
you went to such great lengths.
So I guess
I'd better play along.
Go ahead.
Kill me or torture me.
Do your worst.
Alright, but get off Zhang Suan first.
We really do need to have a good talk.
Xiao Jingshan.
How dare you come here?
I went digging into some old history.
Sorry I'm late.
What old history?
I met with Xi E, the Goddess of Time.
Now, I know everything
that happened in the past.
I don't care what you found out
or what you know.
All I know is, my master is dead now.
It was not Long Yuan who did it.
I know.
Bai Jiusi,
let's put our grudges aside for now.
I have something
more important to tell you.
In the illusion I created
in Songhe County
using the Great Wilderness Stele,
do you remember seeing Zhang Suan there?
I do.
The Great Wilderness Stele
was under my control.
Without my permission,
no one could enter
or disrupt the illusion it created.
Unless...
Unless it's the person
who created the Great Wilderness Stele.
A celestial artifact can recognize
its maker and won't resist them.
When I helped you repair the Zhuri Sword,
I read many books on artifact forging.
So that Zhang Suan,
who is he, really?
I watched Zhang Suan
join Jingyun Sect myself.
Nothing's wrong with him.
The problem is that when he came
to the Nine Heavens to find me,
he met someone.
That person, right before death,
passed all his cultivation to him.
Who was it?
An old acquaintance of yours.
Xiao Jingshan.
I remember him.
He was a highly gifted cultivator
in the mortal realm,
skilled in artifact forging.
After ascending to the Nine Heavens,
he repeatedly tried
to destroy the Infinite Stele.
I caught him
and handed him over
to the Heavenly Emissary,
who imprisoned him
on the Heavenly Punishment Platform.
Why did he want
to destroy the Infinite Stele?
The real reason remains unknown.
Looks like that's where the problem lies.
You protected the Infinite Stele,
while he wanted to destroy it.
That gave him the motive
to use me against you.
I'm afraid that's not the only reason.
He tried many times
to destroy the Infinite Stele,
but it remained intact.
To destroy the Infinite Stele completely,
you'd need ancient divine artifacts.
The Zhuri Sword and the Qiyue Sword?
Exactly.
In fact, that's why I came here today.
I went to Yu Ya to check the Book of Fate
for these two people.
They died over 600 years ago
during the battle
to eliminate the Lei Bird.
Whoever you encountered afterward
might've been people
disguising themselves as them.
If that's the case,
our falling out
really was orchestrated
by someone behind the scenes.
It's all my fault.
I realized it too late.
If someone's trying
to turn us against each other,
why don't we just stage a brutal fight
to give them what they want?
Whatever you say, I'll do it.
I only have one request.
What is it?
When you come to kill me,
could you wear red?
Bai Jiusi,
this isn't a reconciliation.
Shi'an, Meng Changqin, and my master
all died,
directly or indirectly, because of you.
Once this is over,
we'll settle our scores.
Someone is using me against Bai Jiusi,
likely to destroy the Infinite Stele.
Today, I brought the entire sect to ascend
to draw that person out.
I'm standing right in front of you.
Who else do you want to find?
You disguised yourself
as the Immortal of Amusements
to give me the Record of Artifacts, right?
After all that's been said,
you still don't dare show your face?
No wonder you've spent centuries
lurking and scheming
in the shadows.
You let me fool you for centuries.
You really are a pair of idiots.