[FEUD]
[Episode 24]
Bai Jiusi, this is what you wanted to see.
It's not over yet.
Villagers!
This woman is a sorceress of dark arts.
She caused
all our suffering!
Rid us of her,
and peace will return!
Get rid of her!
Burn her!
Burn her! Get rid of her!
Evil spirit!
Burn her!
With the evil spirit cast out,
fortune shall be restored.
Burn her!
Burn her! Kill the witch!
Kill this demon!
Burn her! Get rid of the evil spirit!
No!
Tie her up tight.
Don't worry. It's secure.
She really is a demoness.
Look at her,
not even flinching in the flames.
Come on, give me a hand.
Alright, let's go.
Okay.
She's got
a surprisingly tenacious life force.
[Resurrection Formation]
Everything in this world
follows the laws of nature.
Can't believe there's such
a heaven-defying formation.
That wandering immortal said
he stumbled upon the book.
The book records various divine artifacts.
After witnessing
the Hanlin Dagger's power,
I pinned all my hopes on this formation.
Does the Heavenly Lord Dacheng
know about this?
He only cares about the way of heaven.
What I'm doing defies that very order.
If he knew,
he'd definitely try to stop me.
So once I regained my spiritual energy,
I pretended to make peace with him
and used the Heaven-Turning Seal
to trap him,
ensuring he wouldn't interfere
with my plans.
That's his child too.
If he knew, he might even help you.
He wouldn't.
This is the last one.
Your son's primordial spirit
has already been bound into the formation.
Mother.
Mother!
It was you... who killed him.
Hua Ruyue!
You stole celestial artifacts
and seized the blessed land!
Do you plead guilty?
Bai Jiusi.
You're the guilty one!
♪ But you kept making it cry ♪
♪ Kept breaking it down ♪
♪ Kept letting it slowly shatter
from the inside out ♪
♪ With no light to guide the way ♪
Stop!
♪ It turned cold and dark like a stone ♪
♪ And you threw it away,
left it to suffer alone ♪
♪ In my world,
there's never been room for mercy ♪
He's cold-hearted by nature.
I've been with him for thousands of years,
yet he left me behind and returned to
the Nine Heavens without a second thought.
Let alone the fact
that he's never even seen Shi'an.
How could I possibly bet on him
caring about a child he's never even met?
Alright, we've talked all night.
That's enough.
Three days are up.
Are you really not leaving?
I'm your master, after all.
Even if everyone else leaves, I can't.
I'm still drinking.
I'm not going anywhere.
[Mercy Over All]
One more pot?
[Prosperity]
Bai Jiusi... is wounded.
Now do you see
why she wants you dead?
There's no such thing
as love without reason,
nor hatred without cause.
I've seen your past.
I know you honor karma and uphold the law.
Now, it's time for you
to face your own karma.
Divine Lord Siling sure is lucky.
Three hundred years ago,
she turned the Nine Heavens upside down,
causing chaos everywhere.
Back then, I was immersed in cultivation,
wandering across the lands,
far from the Nine Heavens.
Otherwise, how could I have possibly
let her run wild like that?
At that time, I was painting
The Twin Realms of Mountains and Rivers.
That painting captured all of nature
and the world's spiritual energy in one.
It was incredibly taxing.
It took me over a decade
to complete that painting.
By the time I came out of seclusion,
Siling had already been slain
by Heavenly Lord Dacheng,
and her primordial spirit had fled
to the mortal realm.
Had I been there,
I would've wiped her out completely.
Things would never have become
such a mess.
I was indeed in the Nine Heavens.
But Siling was
Heavenly Lord Dacheng's spiritual partner.
In the end, it was a matter
between the couple.
How could I interfere?
It seems that no matter
how powerful a god may be,
once they're entangled in love,
they lose all reason.
Lieyang, what were you doing back then?
It's a pity.
I was in seclusion at that time.
By the time I came out,
Heavenly Lord Dacheng had already
destroyed Siling's body.
I never got the chance to step in.
That incident is the reason
I haven't set foot in Canglei Palace
for the past 300 years.
After all, it was Bai Jiusi
who acted recklessly,
wasn't it?
How could he go ahead with
something that big without waiting for us?
He let that menace got away for nothing.
The Four Venerables are truly remarkable.
Not a single one showed up
when we needed them.
But now that Canglei Palace
has taken action,
suddenly they're all here.
As long as no one says it out loud,
we can still pretend to be allies.
Tomorrow, we'll descend
to the mortal realm to slay Siling.
I hope the Four Venerables
won't come up with another excuse.
Of course.
Why are you staring at me?
Next, I need you
to keep an eye on Zhang Suan.
Are you going to look for
the Divine Lord again?
I told you,
she already has someone in her heart.
You don't stand a chance.
That's my business.
It has nothing to do with you.
Of course it does.
Did you steal my jade pendant?
Have some manners.
Isn't your jade pendant
hanging right there on your waist?
Do you remember
when you got this jade pendant?
I don't remember.
It's always been on me
for as long as I can remember.
My family said it's my protective charm.
Then it must be you.
Me?
I once asked Lord Yu Ya
who oversees the Book of Fate.
She said the one who holds
the other half of my jade pendant
is my destined partner.
That guy can help me
survive my love tribulation.
Then go find someone else
to survive it with.
You're really just throwing away
something you've had since childhood?
Yes, I don't want it anymore.
What did you do to me?
This is my Thread of Destiny.
I just casted a spell
to make it visible to you.
Don't mess around with me.
Get rid of it quickly.
How can I possibly break it?
It's a union decreed by the heavens,
not something I can just undo on a whim.
Nonsense.
I'm telling the truth.
How's it going?
Master, the wheel's stuck.
The horse can't pull it out.
Then get more people to help pull.
Exactly.
Listen,
we must reach the Jingyun Sect today.
If we don't,
something terrible will happen.
Master,
it's pitch black out here
in the middle of nowhere.
Where am I supposed
to find anyone to help?
Aren't you a person?
Stop standing there spouting sarcasm!
Hurry up and help him lift!
Go!
Bian is still at the Jingyun Sect.
He's just a child.
If anything happens to him,
I don't want to live anymore.
I shouldn't have sent him there
in the first place.
Master, the young master
is already 23 this year.
He's already come of age,
not a child anymore.
Why are you so talkative?
Put some effort into it!
Do you need any help?
Is it a person or a ghost?
I don't know.
Um, who was just speaking?
Me.
What did you say?
I asked if you needed help.
Of course we need help.
Do you live nearby?
Do you have any father
or brothers at home?
We don't live nearby.
And we don't have any father or brothers.
Well, then do you have...
any strong sisters?
Aunts or grandmas work too.
As long as someone can help me
pull the cart out,
I'll offer a generous reward—
candied haws.
No need to go to such trouble.
I can do it by myself.
By yourself?
Does your sister
brag like this at home too?
This isn't the time for jokes.
I'm really in a hurry.
Watch me.
What a big hole!
I really didn't expect that.
Miss, you're so strong!
Thank you for your help.
No need to be so polite.
Are you also going to the Jingyun Sect?
That's great!
I'm also going to the Jingyun Sect.
Do you know the way there?
I want to go too!
-Let's go together—
-Master!
Master, the wheel is broken.
We can't move now.
We need to fix it before we can go.
What are you good for?
Hurry up and fix it!
Alright.
Gosh, everything's going wrong.
How about this, Miss?
After I fix the cart,
I'll take you both to the Jingyun Sect.
How's that?
That's too much trouble.
How about this? I'll fly you there.
Just point me in the right direction.
Fly?
Master, are we still fixing the cart?
Magic is banned here.
We can't fly anymore.
Let's walk there.
Glad to hear that.
Is there still no way
to wake up the Heavenly Lord?
His primordial spirit hasn't returned.
Naturally, he can't be awakened.
Dawn is breaking.
If the Heavenly Lord doesn't wake up soon,
no one will be able to stop
Long Yuan from descending
and going on a killing spree.
Master's primordial spirit
doesn't seem to have been taken,
it feels more like...
he doesn't want to wake up.
My Lord,
please wake up.
If you don't wake up,
Lady Qingyue will be in trouble.
Greetings, Grandmaster.
Where are the Four Venerables?
We've sent people
to invite them several times.
They keep saying
they're coming right away.
We won't wait for them anymore.
Let's descend and face the battle.
Master.
Master, you're alright now.
Withdraw the troops.
Go back.
Master, Siling—
Listen up, all of you!
From this moment on,
if anyone from Canglei Palace
dares lay a hand on
a member of the Jingyun Sect again,
their immortal bones will be stripped,
and they'll be expelled
from Canglei Palace.
Understood.
Are we still fighting or not?
Yeah, why's it gone all quiet now?
Master, it seems something's happened
at Canglei Palace.
-My Lady!
-Li Qingyue!
My Lady.
I've finally found you, My Lady.
Li Qingyue!
Father?
Bian.
Father!
My Lady!
I've finally found you.
Li Qingyue!
My Lady!
My Lady.
Li Qingyue, I'm so hungry.
Make me some food quickly.
Don't you dare touch Her Ladyship.
It seems the battle won't happen today.
Everyone, go back to your cultivation.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Bai Jiusi's primordial spirit
has left his body again?
Yes.
I knew it wasn't your doing.
But that Immortal Lord Long Yuan
insisted it was.
Not only did he mobilize
the forces of Danxia Land,
but he also summoned the Four Venerables.
[Prosperity]
Moreover, he used the Skyshade Mirror
to issue a challenge,
openly defying the Heavenly Lord's command
not to harm you.
He really gave such a command?
When did that happen?
Right after he woke from his last coma.
My Lady, the Heavenly Lord
surely holds you in his heart.
So even if you meant to kill him,
he still couldn't bring himself
to hurt you.
It's all because
Immortal Lord Long Yuan
acted on his own.
We all laugh at him behind his back,
saying if someone didn't know better,
they'd think he was the one
who'd been wronged.
My Lady, I'm not saying
you wronged the Heavenly Lord.
But with Long Yuan
going after the Divine Lord like that,
how did you manage
to escape from Canglei Palace?
I almost forgot
if you hadn't mentioned it.
On the day Immortal Lord Long Yuan issued
the challenge with the Skyshade Mirror,
I secretly slipped away.
Fortunately, I received help
from Immortal Lord Fan on the way.
That's how I was able to
successfully reach the mortal realm.
He entrusted me with a task.
It's to give you this box.
He also said
that although you're on different sides,
this is the last thing he can do for you
as your father.
What is this?
I don't know.
You'll have to see for yourself.
I don't want anything from him.
I'm just the deliveryman.
If you don't want it,
you tell him yourself.
You're from Canglei Palace.
Not only did you descend
to the mortal realm to find me,
but you also told me all this.
Aren't you afraid
Long Yuan will come after you?
I was just afraid you might
misunderstand the Heavenly Lord.
That's why I snuck out.
It's all my fault for not knowing the way.
I wasted quite a few days.
Fortunately,
you haven't started fighting yet.
I think the Heavenly Lord
must have woken up today
and stopped Immortal Lord Long Yuan.
Bai Jiusi actually
doesn't want to kill me?
Of course!
The Heavenly Lord loves you so much.
How could he ever think of killing you?
Now that you've come to Jingyun Sect,
I'm afraid you can't return
to Canglei Palace anymore.
That's not true.
When you make peace
with the Heavenly Lord,
I'll be able to return to Canglei Palace.
That's not possible.
[Prosperity]
Heavenly Lord, where are you going now?
There's something I need to look into.
But if you leave now,
I'm afraid Immortal Lord Long Yuan might—
This time,
he won't dare.
Lingshu is back?
Heavenly Lord Dacheng?
Lord Yu Ya,
help me check the Book of Fate
for two people.
What are their names?
I don't know.
If you don't know anything,
how do you expect me to check for you?
Can you check now?
Yes, I can.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
Take all of these.
Take this too.
Bring it back for a drink later.
We can't stay at
Jingyun Sect any longer.
Let's head back.
Bian, are you leaving?
Who said I'm leaving?
I'm not going anywhere.
Watch your words.
How could Bian be the kind of person
who fears death
and abandons his fellow disciples?
Exactly.
You're right.
Canglei Palace
now fears the unity of the Jingyun Sect.
Even their prior challenge
has been withdrawn.
I refuse to believe
Bian would choose to walk away now.
Exactly.
How could I possibly leave Jingyun Sect?
No.
Wait, Bian.
Didn't you write to me
asking me to take you back?
Father, I know.
You must have missed me so much
that you made up a lie just to see me.
I didn't make it up.
Once I'm a disciple of Jingyun Sect,
I'll always be one.
There's no way I'm leaving.
Father, please stop trying to persuade me.
Listen—
You must be thirsty.
Have some water, Father.
It's been a long journey.
Drink more water.
Drink more.
You guys go practice martial arts first.
I'll be there shortly.
-Let's go.
-Okay. We'll wait for you.
Wait, you need to supervise his training.
Father.
Stop talking.
You really don't want to leave, do you?
Father.
Now, Canglei Palace
doesn't even dare to attack Jingyun Sect.
Jingyun Sect is safe now.
I didn't leave when things were worse.
Why would I leave now?
If I stay
and weather the hardships
ith Jingyun Sect,
the rewards will come in time.
But, Bian,
people should know their own limitations.
Honestly,
I don't think you should keep going.
Father,
are you looking down on your own son?
Trust me.
One day,
I'll become
a leading figure of Jingyun Sect too.
Who is it?
Bian, is that you?
The last thing you can do for me?
I'd like to see what you've done.
You...
I... I told you to find someone else.
Don't come to me.
Divine Lord...
Find the Divine Lord.
Her last words were to tell me
to find you.
She didn't say what happened to her.
My Lady, were you looking for me?
You're a wood-element tree spirit.
Can you check what's wrong with her?
She's asleep.
What's wrong?
Isn't this what you brought for Ling'er?
I'm a tree spirit, so I'll be fine.
But My Lady, please stay back.
Don't let the scent reach you.
There's a scent of Nightmare Flower
in here.
Nightmare Flower?
The Nightmare Flower
is native to the Hell Ruins.
It grows from
the remains of demonic beasts,
needing tens of thousands
of corpses to bloom.
It's rare to see even one in 100 years.
Its scent causes both gods and mortals
to lose consciousness.
After seven days,
they will die in their dreams.
Only Immortal Lord Fan holds the cure.
A flower from the Hell Ruins?
It's strange. Immortal Lord Fan
asked me to give it to his daughter.
How could there
be a Nightmare Flower inside?
Could it be someone trying to use him
to kill Fan Ling'er?
No.
Fan Jiaojiao is forcing us
to hand over his daughter.
Otherwise, he'd rather let her die.
How is that even possible?
What kind of father
could do something so cruel
to his own daughter?
Do you know how to counter
the effects of this flower?
It takes great effort
for this flower to bloom.
I've only seen it once before
from afar in the Hell Ruins.
I don't know how to counter it.
If we were to return Fan Ling'er,
should we have her father
come to pick her up
or should we find someone
to send her back to Canglei Palace?
We still don't know
if this is a trap to lure you in.
So whatever happens,
you must not show yourself.
There's no one in Canglei Palace
who can defeat me.
One may be no match for you,
but what if ten come at you?
Or hundreds? Or thousands?
Moreover, we still don't know
what's happening with Bai Jiusi.
The Heavenly Lord won't harm Her Ladyship.
But we can't just stand by
and watch Ling'er die.
Don't we still have seven days?
Let's investigate the situation
at Canglei Palace further.
It's not too late to make a decision then.
Let's count how many buns
are in the plate.
When I finish counting,
I will eat them all.
One,
two,
three,
four...
The little one can eat quite a lot.
Five,
six,
seven,
eight...
Come on, call me Brother,
and I'll buy you more buns.
Sounds good?
Eight,
nine,
ten.
What a big mouth you have!
Uncle, Senior.
Weren't you supposed to be practicing?
Why are you drinking again?
No, you're looking for my disciple...
Why do you need to see the Grandmaster?
That's none of your concern.
She's also an elder of our sect.
She has the right to be involved
in these matters.
Let's go together.
[Everlasting Grace and Legacy]
When we see the Grandmaster later,
don't drink and speak less.
And don't doze off.
[Temple of the Primordial God]
Since Miss Ling
is now under Master's care,
[Prosperity]
we can't just stand by and do nothing.
Master should stay
to guard the Jingyun Sect.
As for me,
I might pay a visit to Canglei Palace.
It's a good chance to find out
why the battle halted yesterday.
I think there's no need to rush.
We still have seven days after all.
Senior is right.
Grandmaster, I can go back
and check the ancient records
to see if there's a way
to cure the Nightmare Flower poison.
If there really is no cure,
it's not too late
to go to Canglei Palace then.
Wait.
Have you considered
that you've all attacked
the Nine Heavens before
and have a grudge with Canglei Palace?
If you go,
wouldn't it cause more conflict?
So why not let me go instead?
Nonsense! Your power isn't skilled enough.
How could you go?
Well, any one of you could use your power
to help me get there, right?
I've never fought
with Canglei Palace before.
When they see me,
they surely won't be as hostile.
Besides, in a war between two countries,
isn't it the rule not to kill envoys?
The immortals
should follow the same rule, right?
We'll discuss this matter later.
Let's first look for a way
to cure the Nightmare Flower poison.
Yes.
[Cultivate the Mind]
Is there a master in this world
as pitiful as I am?
Having to sneak around
just to see my own disciple.
What are you doing here again?
To drink with you, of course.
Do you know why I volunteered
to go to Canglei Palace today?
Why?
For you.
Me?
Last time you told me
about the grudge
between you and Heavenly Lord Dacheng.
After hearing it,
I think there might be room
for reconciliation.
After all, I am your master.
I plan to be a mediator
between you and Bai Jiusi.
We don't need a mediator between us.
That may not be the case.
You're too close to the situation
to see it clearly.
As an outsider,
I can see things more clearly.
As you said,
Heavenly Lord Dacheng
is cold-hearted and born without emotions.
So when he found you back then,
he should've captured you on the spot
instead of marrying you
and taking you back to Canglei Palace.
He was just too arrogant.
You're really dense.
No wonder you haven't passed
your love tribulation all these years.
Everything you've said
is just your assumption.
You've never asked Heavenly Lord Dacheng
how he feels.
Given how you treated him,
the very fact
that Canglei Palace hasn't struck yet
proves he's not completely heartless.
I'm also confused about
why he hasn't made a move yet.
Perhaps he's planning
an even bigger counterattack.
You're totally a lost cause.
Never mind.
I am your master after all.
I should teach you a thing or two.
Alright. Stop being so stiff.
You're like a wooden block.
Come on.
Come here.
Sit down.
Here.
Tonight, let's have a good drink together.
Come on.
For centuries, you have schemed
for the sole purpose of killing him.
I understand all of that.
Everything you've suffered,
all the pain you've endured,
started with him.
Especially the agony
of losing your own child.
Intentional or not,
the harm is done,
and he's to blame.
But does that really make him
deserving of death?
I know you'll probably say
that I haven't been through what you have,
so who am I to speak a few words
and forgive on your behalf?
But my dear disciple,
every time you try to hurt him,
you're only hurting yourself
again and again.
Because deep down,
you still can't let it go.
You've hated him for hundreds of years,
and that only proves
you've loved him for just as long.
Without love,
where would the hatred come from?