Spill.
Everything.
Are you two together?
But you talked on the phone for an hour
and said you missed each other.
We just keep talking.
He hasn’t told me if he likes me or not.
Tell me what’s wrong.
You know I like you
but I don’t know how you feel at all.
You said you like me. Are you sure about that?
If I wasn’t sure, I wouldn’t have said it.
Let’s date.
Why did you choose Nine that day?
Why didn’t you choose me?
Ever since you didn’t choose me,
I’ve been too scared to dream of anything, you know?
We’re shooting an MV the day after tomorrow.
You’re almost 30, Jane.
Follow your heart already.
Whenever you’re ready to follow your dream,
you can start here.
No matter what I do, will things stay the same between us?
Jane, have you seen this?
(When a Gunman)
(Falls in Love With His Target)
Isn’t this our intern’s idea?
Why is it showing here?
What were you doing with Nine when you were on leave last week?
Hey, Mr. Jane.
Why did they do this?
This is your idea, isn’t it?
They copied the whole thing.
Hello, Mr. Baimon.
I brought Mr. Jo a gift.
Here.
Oh, do you like the MV teaser?
I heard Jane’s involved.
But since when did Jane become a director at Nine’s production house?
I just saw him last Friday.
What a shame that he moved.
How crazy.
Such a shame, isn’t it?
EP 12: INTERNSHIP DIARY
Eat a bit before the noodles get soggy.
Yeah.
If a customer waits too long and the noodles get soggy,
my dad won’t let them eat it.
He’d rather make a new one and lose money than serve them soggy noodles.
Wait, your family actually has a noodle shop?
I thought you were joking.
Of course, it’s true.
Why would I lie to you?
My sister is Kiam-Yi.
We’re all named after noodles.
Why is your name Pah, though?
Is your name actually not Pah?
What’s your name? Tell us.
I have a funny name.
You don’t need to know.
Just tell us.
The funnier, the better.
It’s Bak-Ue.
Huh? What’s your name again?
My name is Bak-Ue.
You guys are laughing so hard at this.
Stop it.
My name means pumpkin.
It’s my mom's favorite thing to eat.
You can smile now, huh?
Hi.
Hey, the whole office is gossiping about Jane.
What exactly is going on? Tell me now.
Did he really sell your work to another production house?
It’s his ex’s company, isn’t it?
And he’s been absent for a few days now, right?
I haven’t seen him around.
Is he back with Nine?
Whose work did he steal? Was it yours, Pie?
Or Ryan’s, or someone else’s?
Hot tea.
It’s about Jane.
I heard he stole the intern’s work.
Damn.
The audacity.
Will he be able to keep his job?
(I’m waiting to hear it from you only. I won’t listen to anyone else.)
(Please come back and explain.)
(Can you please answer? I’m waiting for you, Jane.)
You know, Jane is a very jealous guy.
He’s jealous that Nine was chosen as co-director in the past.
And he acts all high and mighty at work.
He thinks he can get away with anything just because he’s under Jo.
Yeah, if it weren’t for Jo, Ball would’ve punched him in the face a long time ago.
We don’t know the truth yet.
Let’s not talk nonsense.
Are you an intern in the directing department?
Oh, Jane is your mentor.
Don’t get too caught up in the idea of a mentor.
Jane is just doing his job.
If he doesn’t take care of you, he’ll be scolded.
Also, I heard that Jane quit.
HR told me.
Let’s go.
Yeah.
LAST DAY OF INTERNSHIP
(Your mentors appreciate your work this semester.)
Where’s Tae and Ba-Mhee?
You can go first.
I need to fix something quickly and I’ll be done.
It should not take more than half an hour.
It’s okay. I can wait.
Just keep going.
What? Are you done?
No.
Forget it.
I’ll continue working on it tonight.
You can keep working.
I’m really fine.
I know you can wait.
From now on, you can talk to me honestly about anything.
I want to do everything for you.
Let’s go.
Whenever you are hurt, just call
Uncle Moo, Pie was so fierce that day.
She didn’t know how to peel mangosteens,
but she kept squeezing them until her hands went purple.
I’m good at peeling them now.
Bring them to me and I’ll peel 10 kilos for you.
No take backs.
Call me, just call
Pah, are you going to keep the mic to yourself?
Let me sing too.
Hey!
Great job.
I don’t need anything more
Can I love you? How many scores do I get
What should I do to be with you? I will do it all
Your girlfriend is so crazy, Tae.
How can you two even be together?
Go dance with your friends.
Come on.
Just go.
She’s on fire. How many kilos is she peeling?
Tae, come dance with us.
Uh…
Come on.
Take responsibility for stealing my heart
I tried to ignore but you got me from the start
You’re so cute, that’s clear
But you’re quick to disappear
Hey.
I’ve never had a friend as genuine as you.
Thank you so much for being in my life.
Don’t cry.
Besides Tae, you’re the only person I’d die for.
I’d die for you too.
Don’t cry.
But you’re quick to disappear
Tell me if you’re into me
Don’t be so shady
The mic.
- Give me the mic. - Oh, sorry.
Alright.
Oops, sorry.
Oh, where’s Jo? Has anyone seen him?
Jo?
Has anyone seen Jo?
Jo!
Huh?
What are you doing, Jo?
Give us the honor and say something to the interns.
You say it.
- Go ahead. - Come on up, Jo.
You’re our leader.
You go ahead.
Come on up and get it over with!
Come on!
Let’s give it up for him.
Come on.
It’d be the same if you gave the speech.
Well, what should I say?
This year, we have a total of five interns, right?
I remember the first day we met.
I heard none of you were any good.
Why do you want to intern here?
Your main responsibility is to organize the footage and sync the sound.
When needed, key out green screen footage before showing it to the client.
Do you understand everything I’ve said?
I feel like it’s what I’m really good at.
When you scoop it out, do it like this and avoid touching the seed in the middle,
or the flesh will break.
If you scoop it out without touching the seed in the middle, it’ll look perfect.
This is from when I took a course in Japan.
Filming this scene was really challenging
because we had to plan how to climb the mountain.
This one is from when I was on a short film set in China.
And here's a project that’s really interesting.
It’s one I’m really proud of.
Honestly, I couldn’t tell if three months later, you’d all get any better.
I just wanted you to find your own path
and see your own worth.
From now on, if anyone tells you that you can’t do it
or you’re not right for the job,
don’t believe them.
You know yourself best.
Today, I can say you guys have done really well.
Thank you for the past three months.
Thank you so much.
Well done.
You’re amazing.
Hey.
Yes, you’re so amazing.
I’m not going!
Pah, walk properly. Our ride will be here soon.
Huh? Where?
Just a moment.
Pah.
Pah, wake up.
Pah, we’ve arrived.
Pah!
Which room are you in?
Is there anything you want to ask me?
Where have you been?
Did you really quit to work with Nine?
I only worked with Nine one day on the pitch.
I wasn’t planning to continue.
As for…
As for the MV, I think you’re misunderstanding me.
Nine!
How could you do this?
Why are you so mad?
You always have spare ideas on your laptop, don’t you?
It wasn’t my idea and you should’ve asked for permission.
He’s just an intern.
Why make a big deal?
Just give him some pocket money and move on.
He should be happy to see his ideas come to life.
You never change.
You do what you want without considering other people’s feelings.
I thought we could at least be friends after breaking up,
but seeing you now,
I don’t even want that.
Aren’t you going to explain this to others?
Are you just going to let them talk nonsense?
Or are you really not okay with Jo anymore?
Ever since you didn’t choose me,
I’ve been too scared to dream of anything, you know?
Is it because of me or yourself?
Think carefully.
Do you want to keep being in my shadow or become a real director?
Jo and I are not fighting.
Jo wants me to walk my own path.
Thank you.
It’s a reminder that I’m talented enough to step out of my comfort zone now.
Besides Jo, you’re the one who makes me want to pursue directing again.
Are you quitting to become a director?
(Application for Master’s Degree in Film Production)
I’m flying out the day after tomorrow.
You’re not mad that I’m leaving, right?
As I said, I’ll support you in every way.
Whether you stay or leave,
continue your studies or work elsewhere,
I’ll always cheer you on.
Thank you, Ryan,
for everything.
(Over the past three months,)
(I’ve really become a porridge with side dishes like I accidentally said on my first day.)
(I don’t know everything,)
(but I’m not stupid.)
(I’m not ready)
(but I’m getting ready.)
(I’m not talented)
(but I’m trying.)
(I’m still too young to have clear life goals.)
(I’m only just beginning to learn many different things.)
(From now on,)
(whether I achieve something big in my own way,)
(I’ll probably never forget these three months.)
(End of internship.)
5 YEARS LATER
How about we go over these boards one by one?
These two boards are telling the same story.
How?
I thought we’re going to shoot the same way since it’s the same scene.
It’s the same scene but the approach will be different.
We’ll need about three more hours.
How about we do this?
Let’s focus more on the product.
You’re so cool, Ryan.
How are you so knowledgeable?
Did you see his face earlier?
He was shocked when you talked about Day For Night and Night For Day.
(Day For Night (DFN): Use daylight to simulate a nighttime scene)
(Night For Day (NFD): Use night lighting to simulate a daytime scene)
You’re great. You’ve figured out what work you want to do early on.
I’m not that great.
Don’t be so modest, Ryan.
I ask my 4-year-old son what he wants to do in the future
and all he says is “I don’t know”.
There’s no need to rush.
There are so many things he can try.
Even if he knows what he wants to do today, that might change tomorrow.
Let him take his time exploring
and he’ll figure out what he wants to do eventually.
Hey, Ryan.
Could you check the printer for me?
Hey, Ryan is the creative, not IT support.
You always ask him for favors.
The IT guy is on leave today.
No worries. I’ll have a look.
The client is all about looking cool.
Whatever I present, he always asks to make it bigger and cooler.
Wow, you’ve upgraded.
You complain more about clients these days, you know that?
Well, it’s really annoying.
I’ve been here for three years and this project is the most chaotic.
Come on.
You’ve complained about every project, but you’ve always gotten through it.
Hey, I’ve got to go.
I’m in trouble.
Excuse me.
The client needs to leave early, so they want to shoot the product sooner.
I can move that up but we need to finish this scene first.
We need to give the art team time to set up the product shot.
I don’t want to rush them too much.
Got it.
How are the actors doing?
Please wait a moment for my boss to arrive and make a decision.
Sorry I’m late. I was stuck in traffic.
(5 Interns, Class of 24)
(I’m jealous! How did you guys meet?)
(I want to work with friends too.)
(I miss the food on Thai sets so much.)
(When I’m back, I’ll binge on beef noodles.)
(We’re meeting tomorrow. Don’t bail!)
(Okay.)
(Got it.)
The production house filming our commercial is here to introduce their new director.
He’s worked in Hong Kong for many years
and was an Assistant Director for a long time before that.
He’s talented.
Hi, everyone.
This is Mr. Jane, the director for this project.
The new slides you sent have been updated, right?
Yes.
Okay.
Ryan.
I’ll send you the new slides in a moment and the timeline later.
Wait.
Can I talk to you?
I look forward to your guidance, Mr. Creative.
I should be the one saying that, Jane.
You’re a director now.
You look much more grown-up.
You’ve changed a lot.
Is there anything that hasn’t changed?
What about you?
Is anything about you still the same?
Everything is the same.
Why did he ask to meet so early?
I missed you and wanted to see you as soon as I could.
I got used to waking up early when I was living abroad.
I got up early and hurried to see people
because I was so lonely being alone.
Then why didn’t you reach out?
I kept waiting for you.
I was scared I’d give in and come back early.
Whenever I thought of you, I wanted to come back.
Can I lean on you?
What kind of mood and tone would you like, Mr. Jane?
Black coffee without sugar, please.
Huh?
What did you just say?
Black coffee what?
I couldn’t think of a good answer in time.
What did you expect me to say?
Right?
For the waterfall scene, we can use a green screen
since it’s a close-up and the expressions won’t be visible anyway.
Are you okay with that, Mr. Ryan?
Good idea.
Let’s focus on the product presentation scene.
Okay, as for targeting teenagers,
I plan to focus on those who vacation at the beach.
Do you think that’s enough, Mr. Ryan?
I think targeting teenagers who vacation at the beach is enough.
Yes.
By the way, your ideas are so romantic, Mr. Jane.
You and your wife must be so sweet with each other.
I’m not married.
That’s unbelievable.
You’re so handsome and talented.
What’s your soulmate waiting for?
I know, right?
I have no idea what that person is waiting for either.
What? Baimon never told me Jane was coming back to Thailand.
Baimon didn’t know either.
Jane just suddenly came back.
I don’t know what he’s thinking.
Don’t act like you don’t know what he’s thinking.
I bet you ran to scream in the toilet after you saw him.
Hi, guys.
I got you souvenirs from Japan.
I was there for three months but only got to buy them on my last day.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ever since you became Art Director for foreign films, you’re never in Thailand.
Yeah, I fly all the time.
By the way, is Jane really back?
How many more times do I have to retell this story?
I want to know.
You don’t need to.
What?
Tell me.
Hey.
What’s wrong with you guys now?
Same old problem.
Jealousy.
Mhee, you’re probably the only one misguided enough to fall for Tae.
Stop being jealous.
Your friend is the jealous one, not me.
I went to lunch with my client and he’s been sulking until evening.
I’ll go get some stuff from the car.
Pah asked me to buy it for him.
Yeah.
By the way, guys, the brand Judy works with has a lot of money.
And everyone I told about interning with her is jealous of me.
You’ve been talking about Judy since you got here.
You’re not thinking about her that way again, are you?
Come on. What could I even think about?
I spend all my time fighting with Tae.
But fighting with him is the most fun.
Whoa, this song is so old.
I sent it to flirt with Tae when we were in school.
Wait, should I propose to Tae now?
What do you think?
Are you crazy?
You’re a girl. Tae should be the one proposing to you.
I don’t know.
Eyes connect briefly, can people fall in love?
Just a fleeting moment
Would that be enough?
If two people are alike and have things in common
Would they quickly form a strong bond?
Someone you meet on a day you feel vulnerable
Would it be easier and faster when you fall?
You wanna marry?
Marry who?
Finish the sentence.
What do you think?
Marry me, of course.
Will you marry me?
You make me want to explore
My eyes yearn to see you more
You got me lost in a distant land
Too far to reach or understand
No matter how near or far
I’d do anything to be there in youniverse
Why didn’t you let me in on your plan, Tae?
Congratulations!
How can I help you?
Is Jo here?
Yes.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Is Moo here?
Who?
Oh, sorry.
Sure. Is it 25,000 net?
Oh, okay.
Should I pay on set or…?
Jane!
When did you come back?
I’ve missed you.
Have you started your new job or are you still on a break?
I take on jobs here and there.
I’m working on a commercial right now.
When you want to come back here, just let me know.
You can get any role you want.
I’ve missed working with you.
You’re not in a rush to leave, are you?
You’re waiting for your internship interview, right?
I’m sorry.
I’m late because we had a test for the client’s product today.
You want to intern as an assistant.
You mean Assistant Director?
Yes.
Why do you want to intern as an Assistant Director?
Well, I want to work on set.
Oh, hey.
The art team was so good at badminton.
They took it very seriously.
I’m out of breath.
What are you doing?
Oh, you want to hand in your work?
Remove the picture on the bottom right.
Remove this one too.
Jo.
Hey.
Hi.
Jane.
Wow.
How are you?
I’m good.
How’s it going here?
I don’t do much each day.
All I do is build Lego.
If you enjoy it, just keep doing it.
I only discovered what I like to do when I’m old
but it’s better than being old and not knowing what I like.
Yes.
At least now I know that building Lego before I die will give me peace.
Good for you.
How have you been?
It’s been five years since you left this home.
Well, I’ve been so tired.
It’s like I had to start everything by myself
but it’s been good.
It’s made me see myself better.
Okay.
I matter more in my eyes now.
I think
I’m finally out of your shadow now.
I know what I want.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
I’m glad to see you today.
I’m glad to see you too.
Good.
Intern?
Yes.
The people are kind here.
There’s nothing to worry about.
Hey!
Pah!
Don’t come any closer!
Let me get another mic.
Hey!
Come back here.
No.
Can I get a piggyback ride?
Hey, Jane!
Where’s Jane?
You’re on top of him, you idiot.
Damn.
How romantic.
He used to be strict as hell.
Why didn’t they fall for each other sooner?
Jane!
Over here!
Jane, where have you been?
My friend was upset for a year.
If you leave him again, I’ll tell him to find someone else.
Yeah!
Someone more handsome than you.
More talented than you.
Yeah!
Don’t leave my friend again, understand?
Well done, Tae!
Jane is scared now.
I’m not going anywhere anymore.
I’ll stay with you.
Will there be someone?
Then I found you, the one I looked for all along
Excuse me, excuse me, can you teach me, please?
About love, about love, can you help me with these?
If you take me on, I promise I'll study hard
Please teach me the matters of the heart
(Ryan After Work)
(5 Interns, Class of 24)
(The group is quiet again.)
(We have work to do.)
(Guys, my intern has talent but zero self-confidence. What should I do?)
(Just share how you built your own confidence.)
(You’re right.)
(My intern is so scared of me. I don’t understand why.)
(You really don’t know, Pie?)
(My intern this year is so talented.)
(Mine still makes spelling mistakes!)
(Babe, you need to calm down and teach her patiently.)
(Alright, baby Tae.)
(We’ve come so far. I’m so proud!!!)
(Ryan changed the group name to “Mentors”)
(Okay.)
(Ryan.)
(Yes, Jane?)
(Are you coming yet? I’m waiting in front of your house.)
(What? Where are we going?)
(House hunting, of course.)
(You said you wanted to live with me.)
(Don’t you want to live together anymore?)
(I totally forgot we’re going today.)
(Never mind. Just hurry.)
(I’ll wait.)
(Good. You made me wait for you for so long.)
(Can you wait for me for a change?)
(You’re talking back these days.)
(You weren’t like this as an intern.)
(You’re acting like a mentor again.)
(Why? You don’t like it?)
(That’s not what I meant.)
(I like every version of you.)
(You crazy kid.)
(Just hurry up.)
(Okay.)
(Darling.)
(Ryan unsent a message.)
(What?)
(Darling.)
(Okay.)
Let’s hear some loud cheers and applause for The Trainee.
Excuse me, excuse me, can you teach me, please?
About love, about love, can you help me with these?
If you take me on, I promise I'll study hard
Excuse me, excuse me, please lend me a hand
This thing called love, can you help me understand?
I want to know what it feels like to be in love
Please teach me the matters of the heart