(Kong Jae-hyun as Kim Hyung-ki,
Chun Jae-young as Kim Pil-hyun)
(Jin-kwon as Baek Ho-min,
Han Ji-won as Lee Yoon-seul)
(Kim Kang-min as Han Ji-woo)
(Son Woo-hyun as Kang Seo-jun)
(To My Star)
I saw someone
hanging about the restaurant,
so I went and grabbed the camera.
So why are you showing me this?
My father's company went under.
They took our house.
I'm the only one
who has a job in my family.
So what?
I took out a loan with the restaurant
as collateral.
And I'm about to lose this restaurant.
And Kang Seo-jun has a lot of money.
He even said how
he fixes problems with money.
I'll take this picture to him
and ask him for money.
Are you
serious right now?
I'm sure you don't want
to lose this restaurant either.
You came up with all of the recipes.
If you start at a new restaurant,
you'll have to start from the bottom.
So you're asking me to join you,
extorting money out of him?
You're just taking the easy way out.
You don't mean it, right?
Come on,
you can't possibly want to do this.
You make me sound like
the worst person on Earth.
Hey, do you think you're some hotshot chef
because you're rolling with Kang Seo-jun?
Come to your senses, you scumbag.
If I didn't stop this,
people would have found out anyway.
Then, people would be shaming you.
And your life would be over
after you hit rock bottom. Got that?
Ji-woo.
We've known each other for a long time.
He doesn't mean anything to you.
Right?
How could you say that to me?
(When I thought about it,)
(it was disgusting.)
What?
What happened with you
disgusted me when I thought about it.
Wait.
That doesn't make sense.
Something happened, right?
If I stay with you,
I might find myself in trouble.
What? What's going on?
Can I get my deposit back?
Hey.
Are you okay, Seo-jun?
You know I take birthday parties
very seriously, right?
But I'm not in the mood to celebrate.
So go out and have fun without me.
What are you talking about? No.
We'll stay with you.
Do that for me.
And
I don't want to waste food.
Can you guys take the food with you?
(The person you have reached
is unavailable.)
(You'll be directed to a voicemail box.)
Who is it?
(Hello. This is So-yeon
from Vaspatch, USA.)
(I came here to apologize to you.)
(I just wanted to be updated
about how you're doing.)
But something happened.
Something bad happened, actually.
(Italian Restaurant)
Hello?
Why is the restaurant closed?
(Isn't Ji-woo there?)
No, he's not here.
You're here.
Hey.
What on earth happened?
Do you know anything?
Gosh. I'm sure something
happened between them.
I guess something bad happened.
Is Mr. Han Ji-woo
really going to move out?
Yes.
I guess something urgent came up.
He asked for his deposit,
so I wired it this morning.
I thought his parents asked you
to put him up in that house.
Gosh, whatever.
He hates owing people, so it was
hard to convince him to move in there.
Look at this mess now.
Where are you?
(Where are you?)
I can't promise you,
but I'll try to wire you 20 million won.
Do what you need to do with that.
Is it from Kang Seo-jun?
It doesn't matter
where the money came from.
I don't want your money.
Why not?
Because I'm poorer than you?
I'm doing this, so I can save
the restaurant and you.
Don't use me as an excuse.
If you want to do it, own it.
You can get a job
with your resume and career.
Am I wrong?
When will I pay back all the debt
with chicken feed salary?
I didn't want to do this either.
That's not an excuse.
Kang Seo-jun called me.
What?
He knew everything.
You didn't have to come.
You don't own a house.
But I do.
Being a villain requires a lot of work.
Good job with that.
As you know,
this isn't my first rodeo.
Where's the money?
Why would I bring that much money
in cash? I'm not some caveman.
Seo-jun.
What?
I'll handle this.
Done.
If you still leak the photo
after this payout,
I won't let this slide.
Hop on.
No.
Wait.
Please.
Let's talk at home.
Come home with me.
Where were you last night?
You didn't go to Ms. Lee's either.
Where's your stuff?
Give me the memory card.
I want to burn it.
You could have just told me.
Why did you leave like that?
I didn't want to
be some fodder for gossip.
I'm sorry.
I was doing fine before you came.
Why are you messing up my life?
I said I didn't want you
to toy with my life.
You're going to leave anyway.
You were just toying with me because
you were bored and I happened to be here.
Just stop it now. It's over.
Go find someone who suits you.
Don't play with me.
Everything is handled.
So you can move out now, right?
You can go back to your house.
I can't find a better house
than this with the rent I can afford.
I'm not playing around.
I'm serious.
Do you still want me to leave?
Yes.
Okay.
I thought about it, but I can't do it.
The thought of not having you in my life
breaks my heart.
I really don't want this to end.
Don't get me wrong. Just listen.
This all means
that you like me too?
That's what it sounds like to me.
Ji-woo.
If this is too hard for you,
I'll go to you.
(To My Star)