(10th day of 4th month
of 3rd year of Xuantong)
(Grain in Ear is 30 days away.)
(Jiexiu, Fenzhou)
Sir,
we're from out of town.
We would like to collect
some things around here.
Do you know where we can do that?
What are you going to collect?
Just some old objects.
Old items.
- Give it to me.
- I want it.
Just some old items.
Old items?
Trinkets.
I don't know.
You should ask around elsewhere.
I thought every family
here had a treasure.
I wish I had one.
Why don't you take a look
to see if there's anything you want?
(Ask and you shall receive)
Things from the tomb.
How can I get those?
Who around here can do so?
Shovel.
You don't know him?
This one?
No.
The one who digs graves.
Isn't a shovel for digging soil?
It can dig anything, can't it?
I spent all morning
asking around the whole village.
No one has heard about Shovel.
Seems like none have anything
to do with tomb robbing.
Muqing,
you're so relaxed.
What if Zhuo Bufan
finds the clue before us?
Take it easy.
Judging by the clues left
by Tan Xian in the hotel,
Zhuo Bufan only knows that much.
He doesn't have more cards
in hand than us.
And he doesn't have
the county yamen's assistance.
He can only sneak around
blindly digging graves.
But we have a helper.
A helper?
Muqing, Getai,
I've missed you so much.
Today my right eye has been twitching.
I knew there must be good luck.
Sure enough.
The opportunity to serve
the imperial court has come.
Muqing,
is there anything I can help you with?
No.
I can't have you serving me tea.
Thank you.
Take a look.
Look.
Look at what?
Have a look if there's anything amiss.
It's not good porcelain.
Nor is it a quality clay body.
As for the craftsmanship,
it's just ordinary.
This tea tastes pretty good.
I didn't expect in this small village,
I would find palatable tea.
I've been sitting in this shed
all morning.
I drank two pots of tea,
ate a bowl of multigrain congee
and a boiled egg.
That multigrain congee contained millet,
sweet potatoes, pumpkins,
cabbage, Chinese yam and soybeans.
Wasn't that a bit too rich?
Even in a tavern
in Fenzhou, Taiyuan,
such a bowl of multigrain congee
would be considered a luxury.
Such a breakfast
cost me a total of 13 wen.
Wasn't that a bit expensive?
Eating breakfast in Fenzhou
wouldn't cost more than that.
Here, Jiexiu County of Fenzhou.
Yesterday, when I examined
the local documents,
I took a glance
at the local tax collection situation.
It's clearly a poor place.
A peasant family works hard
and earns about 16 strings
of coins a year.
It's like making forty-something wen
per household per day.
Can the peasants of Jiexiu
afford a 13-wen breakfast?
This dilapidated tea hut
at the entrance of a poor village
is not on a main thoroughfare.
Not many people pass by.
Who are the customers?
A golden goblet of clear wine
costs ten thousand.
A jade plate of delicacies
is worth ten thousand.
Muqing, you are correct.
People from this village
must be quite rich.
Muqing,
there must be some in this village
who don't live off farming.
And they aren't a minority.
I've been sitting here since morning
and haven't seen a single person
come for breakfast.
But look.
Which restaurant would wash
a huge pile of bowls
before opening for business?
Yes.
And which farmers
can afford to eat an expensive breakfast
that costs 13 wen
and then go work the fields?
So these washed dishes and chopsticks
must have been used
by those who worked at night
and came to eat in the morning.
We've found the right place.
There must be many here
who work at night.
Muqing,
I will have our men go door to door.
Getai,
we are here to investigate a case
not to catch tomb robbers.
If the villagers see us officers coming,
and they're asked about tomb-robbing,
they certainly won't tell the truth.
What did I bring him here for?
How clever!
Muqing, how brilliant!
I'm gonna
take a stroll around the village now.
What are you going to do?
Getai,
haven't you understood yet?
What do I do?
I specialize in dealing with antiques.
I am an expert.
I'll ask around
under the pretense of collecting things.
If someone brings out something
from a grave,
that person must be a tomb robber.
I pretended to be
an antique collector this morning
but didn't find out anything
after asking around.
Isn't that obvious?
Getai,
they can tell from your tone
at once you're not a collector.
I guess you don't even know the lingo.
What lingo?
How was the haul last night?
Take me to see our godson.
I don't know any of that jargon you use.
Alright, Lucky.
Hurry and go check in the village.
Okay!
That little brat.
=Heroes=
=Episode 13=
Mr. Zhuo, Ms. Huo.
This morning, we found someone
in a village of Pingyao County.
The female bodyguard
who was with Tan Xian at Maiqi Road
in the French Concession in Shanghai.
Why is she here?
If she's here,
it means she definitely knows
the location
of the Bodhi inheritor's tomb.
Right.
I speculated
she might go to the Bodhi tomb,
so I didn't let her notice me.
I had two junior brothers follow her.
Then I hurried back to inform you.
Well done.
So
let's catch up
with that female bodyguard.
Then notify everyone
to meet up in Pingyao.
Pingyao?
Mr. Zhuo commanded us to leave at once.
You've found the Bodhi tomb?
We found
Tan Xian's female bodyguard in Pingyao.
She definitely knows
where the Bodhi tomb is.
By following her,
we'll definitely find it.
Got it.
I'll pack up and be right there.
Hurry up.
Pingyao.
What's this?
Taigu cake, a specialty of Shanxi.
A waiter just brought it over,
saying it was sent by Mr. Yu.
Mr. Yu?
Yu Huanjie from the Rongtian Ridge.
He's working for us too?
We hope so.
Mr. Yu told that waiter
Taigu cakes went well
with beef from Pingyao.
Yu Huanjie is not foolish at all.
It seems Zhuo Bufan
has already found it.
They've gone to Pingyao.
This one.
A wine cup.
This is not rare.
Just dig a hole and you'll get
a bunch of them.
But this one.
It's a Taotie carved on it.
[*Ancient Chinese mythological creature]
It's not even noon yet.
I just took such a small tour,
and I've already collected
so many things.
Muqing, Getai,
and sir.
There must be a secret
lurking around here.
Alright, let's move.
I'm going to deploy people
to seal off the village now.
Getai,
bring over their village chief first.
I'll ask him some questions.
Follow me.
Sir,
I'm the local village official.
I don't care
about your grave robbing
and I won't arrest you.
You just need to do one thing for me.
Sir, I'm all ears.
More than 40 years ago,
almost during the early years
of Tongzhi,
there was a tomb robber named Shovel.
Find his descendants for me.
Or take me to his grave.
Sir.
I'll only give you half an hour.
If you can't bring the person
or point out the grave,
I will seize all of you.
By the Qing Code,
tomb robbers
shall be executed.
Sir, spare me.
Sir,
more than 40 years ago,
I was just a little kid then.
The man you speak of.
I seem to have heard of him.
He was a master at obtaining treasures.
But I've never heard
about his descendants.
Let alone knowing
where his grave is located.
If you don't know,
hurry back to ask around.
You only have half an hour.
Do as you see fit.
Muqing,
don't you think
half an hour is a bit long?
I'll go ask right away.
- How is it going?
- Mr. Zhuo.
Go two and a half li
and then head west.
Where's that?
Zhaozhuang.
Okay.
You two continue to follow her.
Remember not to alert her.
- Yes.
It seems the Bodhi tomb is right here.
Correct.
But before she finds any clues
or discovers the tomb,
we must not act rashly.
Otherwise, among the thousands of graves
in the nine counties of Fenzhou,
when would we ever be able
to find it on our own?
Bufan,
eat something.
You're always attentive.
Qin Tuo,
distribute these.
Here they come.
He brought that person.
No, he invited that person.
That person is the head here.
Actually, the village chief
listens to him.
You have a keen eye.
Just like me when it comes
to recognizing antiques.
Sir,
greetings...
Cut the crap.
Just tell me what I want to hear.
What do you want me to say?
The things about Shovel.
Come on.
Shovel.
Shovel must be referring to Mr. Su.
Mr. Su?
The details.
Yes.
In the early years of Tongzhi,
nearly 40 years ago,
in the entire Fenzhou
and even the whole Shanxi,
the best tomb robber
was Su Yunzhi,
Mr. Su.
Mr. Su used nothing but a shovel.
And he was so skilled
in using it.
So those in the same line of work
all called him Shovel.
And later on,
the number of Mr. Su's disciples
kept growing,
and his status kept rising.
So fellow antiquities dealers
all revered him.
It seems that you are quite familiar
with Su Yunzhi.
No.
Sir, please do not think so.
It's all hearsay.
I'm just an honest farmer
who tills the soil.
I don't understand antiques at all,
let alone anything about tomb robbing.
All I know about him
is from my grandpa.
But he didn't know
about tomb robbing, either.
Our family for generations
has been farming.
That's all we know how to do.
I don't care whether you're a farmer
or a grave digger.
If you keep beating around the bush,
I will smash the jade
from the Southern Song on your waist.
This...
The Northern Song.
Sir,
when my grandfather was alive,
he would pay respects
at Su Yunzhi's grave every year.
But my grandfather
has been dead for many years,
and I have never been to Mr. Su's grave.
I just know the place.
It's in the wild graves
on the west end of Zhaozhuang.
How can I find it?
Mr. Su robbed countless tombs
in his lifetime,
and he didn't care about the afterlife.
He thought a fancy tomb would only tempt
more grave robbers.
A desolate grave would be safer,
and it would be more quiet.
Let's go.
Muqing,
there must be many secrets here.
Let me stay behind
and have a good look around
to see
if there are
any other suspicious things.
You want to pick up
some bargains, don't you?
How about I count you in?
I'll pick a valuable thing for you.
Come with me to Zhaozhuang first.
After that, you can take
whatever you want.
Yes.
I'll follow your lead.
Muqing,
do you think the Bodhi tomb
is in Zhaozhuang?
Getai,
I have a hunch
that we're about to find it.
It really is you.
You were the one
who was with Tan Xian on Maiqi Road.
Since you're here,
it means we're looking
for the same thing.
Tell us.
Which grave should we dig up?
I am asking you which tomb
the Bodhi inheritor's is!
Someone's coming.
And there are many of them.
Huang Xing.
Getai,
we've found the right place.
It's just that we have to battle.
Let me say something.
You two,
should we fight first
or dig the grave first?
So many graves.
Which one should we open?
Huang Xing.
Either point out which grave it is now
or I kill you right away.
Miss Liu.
You...
Why are you with them?
You might just kill me.
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
Everyone is here.
Actually, this matter
is already troublesome enough.
Even if we dig up
these graves one by one,
it can't be done in a day and a night.
Besides,
this thing
is unconscionable.
Taboo.
Too taboo.
Can you actually find
the grave I am looking for?
Muqing,
excavating graves is not my forte,
but this actually has
some connection with antiques.
What kind of tomb are you looking for?
If I know the approximate year
of burial,
it may be simpler.
6 years ago.
6 years.
Okay.
Dude,
lend me a tool.
Stubborn, huh?
This grave is at least 15 years old.
Not right.
Mr. Zhuo,
I've brought 11 people.
Each one of them is a top-notch master,
whereas there are only eight of you.
And you've brought a woman along.
You are already at a disadvantage.
Any five individuals from my sect
can easily deal
with you so-called masters.
Not to mention there are eight of us.
But Men Sandao,
you are a real master.
There are fewer and fewer masters
in the martial world.
How about this?
You take your men back.
Make up some excuse
to appease the court.
The court will punish you.
But they won't go
as far as to execute you.
But if you fight me,
I will.
Thank you, Mr. Zhuo,
for your kind words.
But I bear the Emperor's command.
I can only give it my all
to not fail the Emperor.
Mr. Zhuo,
I'll give you a word of caution too.
You have already
committed a grievous crime.
If you continue to be obstinate,
you cannot escape punishment.
How would you punish me?
Don't you find your words
ridiculous?
I found it!
A 6-year-old grave.
Someone, come dig it up and take a look.
Getai.
I found it!
Why does this coffin have no nails?
Get ready.
Wait for those imperial guards
and the Rongtian Sword Sect
to both be weakened.
Then we'll make our move.
Let's go.
Don't just stand here.
I'm afraid if we don't take action now,
we won't find
such a good opportunity again.
We've got the thing.
Let's go.
Zhuo Bufan!
Men Sandao,
if you're determined to die,
I'll grant your wish.
You're right.
It may be the best opportunity.
What a mess.
Even the Beiyang Army
has been drawn into this.
That leader.
Why does he look familiar?
Isn't that Mr. Wang?
Why is he leading Beiyang soldiers?
And in military uniform.
Impossible.
This is absolutely impossible.
He was clearly killed by Zhuo Bufan.
I personally touched his corpse.
Jialuo.
You are Wang Jialuo.
I didn't expect you to be able
to cheat death under my sword.
Zhuo Bufan,
put down the sword in your hand.
Otherwise,
your sect will cease to exist.
Jialuo,
snatch the jar in his hand!
That's the most important thing.
Zhuo Bufan,
if you do not want me to shoot,
drop your sword now
and hand that over.
Mr. Ding,
capture these from the Rongtian Ridge
who not only killed people
but also attempted
to steal the treasure of the Qing.
If there is any resistance,
show no mercy and kill them.
Huanjie,
take the others and leave.
Don't move.
Take one more step
and no one will get this thing.
Go.
Let's retreat.
Go!
You have guns after all.
I lost.
It's a trick!
Shoot!
Catch him!
- Yes!
Getai,
have someone collect
all these fragments.
Not a single bit can be missed.
This is the clue to the Altar Treasure.
You know about
the Altar Treasure?
I am currently pursuing Zhuo Bufan
and his fellows
not only for the Dagu case
but also to stop them from stealing
the treasure of the Qing.
If it weren't for you today,
Zhuo Bufan might have succeeded.
Thank you.
But he still got away.
Why do you...?
You lead the Beiyang troops,
and you're in Beiyang's uniform.
It's a long story.
I have to go now.
Mr. Muqing, I'll see you.
Jialuo,
where are you staying now?
In Fenzhou.
Me too.
How about we have
a drink at a tavern tonight?
You can tell me
that long story.
Good. I'll see you tonight.
Mr. Muqing,
I'm off now.
Alright.
Zhuo Bufan did it on purpose.
The jar has been chopped up so finely.
There must be clues on this.
We must find a way
to restore and piece these together.
Where is Lin Haohan?
Get him over.
He...
How could he disappear?
Find him.
Hurry up and find him.
So dangerous.
Miss Liu Lin.
If it weren't for my quick reaction,
we would have been in trouble.
Why were you captured
by those fierce and evil people?
Look.
You should have followed me.
What is it?
Where are you going?
You're not going back, are you?
Miss Liu Lin, have you gone mad?
If you don't run now,
you'll lose your life.
Why go back to face death?
This place is not safe.
Let's head back to Fenzhou.
Go.
(43rd Association, Shanxi Army)
We found Zhuo Bufan
in Zhaozhuang, Pingyao.
But he managed to escape.
We couldn't capture him.
What a pity.
Jialuo,
we made you a second lieutenant
in the Beiyang Army
and gave you command of troops
because we want you
to stop Zhuo Bufan's intention
to steal the treasure.
General Long,
I understand.
I will certainly do my utmost
to guard the treasure for the Emperor
and for the Great Qing.
I've already ordered a citywide alert
and had my men search
for Zhuo Bufan and his fellows.
We will prevent him.
Alright.
You've been toiling all day.
You must be tired.
Go back and rest.
I'm not tired.
I will continue the investigation.
How come Mr. Wang is so hard to kill?
He survived many times.
Who knows
what he found in the coffin?
Yu Huanjie hasn't sent
any messages until now.
Maybe we should find
a way to contact him.
No.
I promised him that I would not.
Besides, Huo Qin is adept
with poisonous insects,
which isn't just hearsay.
Wait a little longer.
Mr. Wang is a headache for us.
You must find a way to get back to him
for information.
Zhuo Bufan destroyed the porcelain jar
he found in the coffin
right in front of you all?
Yes.
Very suspicious.
Zhuo Bufan might already be aware
of the secret of the porcelain jar.
That's why he resorted to such a scheme.
I think so too.
Those from the Rongtian Ridge
are so skilled
in martial arts.
They escaped too fast.
We couldn't catch up with them.
Do you think Wang Jialuo
can find Zhuo Bufan?
He has meticulously arranged for his men
to scout for their traces.
I think he can do it.
Moreover, on our turf,
he can't manage
to come and go without leaving traces.
Draft a telegram
detailing the whole thing
about the Altar Treasure
involving the Rongtian Ridge,
Zhuo Bufan
and the Imperial Household Department
from the start.
Yes.
General, there's a visitor.
Who is it?
It's Mr. Xie.
Bring him to my office.
Who is it?
A secret envoy from Beiyang.
He is here to see me.
It must be a matter of importance.
Mr. Xie.
General Zhong, it has been many days.
I've missed you quite a bit.
Sit.
General, do you know
about a sect in Lingxi
named the Rongtian Ridge?
It seems to be
a martial arts sect, right?
This Rongtian Ridge
is a declining sword sect in Lingxi.
They suddenly left
their stronghold a few days ago.
They first went to Tianjin,
and then they showed up in Shanghai.
And most recently, they went to Shanxi.
Quite strange.
So we did some investigating,
and we've found out their purpose
is to search
for a legendary secret treasure.
Mr. Xie,
what does this matter
have to do with us?
It has nothing to do with us.
But it might have
something to do with you.
Sir, I don't quite understand
what you mean.
This martial arts sect
is actually under someone's command
to go all out to search
for this legendary fortune.
The mastermind behind this,
according to our deductions,
is most likely your father-in-law,
Prince Qi.
But I have never heard of this.
Really?
I'm absolutely telling the truth.
General Zhong, please stay calm.
Sit.
Previously, we had
an agreement with Prince Qi
to assist him in a coup
and then help him form a cabinet.
But we wanted to maintain
absolute control of it.
If it is true that Prince Qi
is hiring martial forces
to look for the legendary treasure.
It indicates that he's actually trying
to use our power to control us.
Mr. Xie,
I understand what you mean.
But don't worry.
Although I am Prince Qi's son-in-law,
at the end of the day,
I am a man of Beiyang.
The Beiyang Army nurtured me,
so I will never forget my roots,
no matter what.
Very good.
So, what should you do next?
General Zhong, are you clear on this?
I will go and check soon.
If Prince Qi really
has other intentions,
I won't hide anything from you
or Beiyang.
♪Blood refines the sword,
and wind forges the blade♪
♪I am still that person
with rough edges♪
♪My heart is vast like the sea,
and my soul doesn't want to fight♪
♪How long can I remain young♪
♪I sigh for the elusive destiny♪
♪I struggle half my life in destitution♪
♪Who can laugh in this fancy world♪
♪Don't squander your prime.
Don't squander your day♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪