(Constable from Dagu County Yamen)
Irgen-Gioro Muqing
intends to rebel.
He shall be executed.
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
I know I shouldn't beat you
when you're injured.
But I am also injured.
Moreover,
when you killed Zhuo Bufan,
his injuries were much more severe
than yours.
Unless
you kill me today,
I'm going
to capture you.
You can't die.
I still want your Dharma Seal.
Do you think I have the seal?
I really don't have it.
Good.
Great.
There is no Dharma Seal in this world.
You'll never get the secret treasure.
Those rebels from the Tongmenghui
also won't get it.
Heaven bless the court.
I haven't told you yet.
Wang Jialuo.
You have the seal.
You are the seal.
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
=Heroes=
=Episode 36=
Am I disrupting the Buddha?
Yes.
Well...
If even this cannot be tolerated,
can it be called Buddha?
Thank you, abbot.
May you endure hardships and bitterness
for your revolution.
May you fail soon
for the Qing Dynasty you serve loyally.
I wish you lose everything
due to the revolution.
I wish the court you so staunchly defend
meets its end in the revolution.
We said it while drinking.
Why did you take it seriously?
You are really something.
You're shot by a bullet
through your body.
Yet you stayed quiet,
driving all the way here.
Such a long ride.
It's so bumpy.
You really have a high pain tolerance.
I truly believe
you can definitely endure torture
while talking about your revolution.
Liu Lin.
Don't worry.
When you come back,
this country will
become what you wish it to be.
It will
become better than you wish.
By then, the nation will be so powerful
that no one will dare to challenge it.
The Forbidden City will be open
to the public.
So will the Hall of Supreme Harmony.
The common people can visit it.
If I'm still around,
I'll take you to eat delicious food
and to visit fun places.
I'll make you happy,
and you won't have to
risk your life anymore.
I didn't expect you to drive so well.
I almost forgot.
You used to like foreign gadgets.
Back when you were in the palace,
you just rided bicycles.
One has to
learn advanced things.
Yes.
Muqing.
Let me teach you how to drive.
Okay.
Is it dangerous for you to do this task?
No.
I will just send a telegram.
There's no danger in that.
And you?
What else do you have to do?
I...
There is one thing
I must do.
(Telegraph Office)
Remember this, both of you.
Phone number?
Telegram.
The station of Beiyang Army
has telegraphs, right?
Yes.
That's good.
If anything happens to me,
send a telegram.
It's sent to Hong Kong.
Our people are there.
He will pass it to my master.
My master will know what to do.
What will happen to you?
Nothing.
Comrades.
Though I'm particularly afraid of death,
we are indeed risking our lives, right?
Don't be discouraged.
All of us will be safe.
We must be alive.
Alright.
We do what you said.
Yes, princess.
(Telegraph Office)
Load the bullets in here.
Then close the magazine.
Pull the bolt to fire.
Pull the bolt again after each shot.
Put the gunstock against your shoulder.
Near your face.
Aim with one eye.
When you're aiming,
the notch at the back
should align with the front sight.
The three points form a straight line.
If the distance is far,
aim a bit above the target.
The further away, the higher you lift.
As to how much to lift,
you need to practice more
to get the feel.
All your teeth have been knocked out.
And you can still talk.
So annoying.
Where did I hit?
I was aiming at her mouth.
Did I hit her mouth?
It seems
I will have to practice more.
This thing is powerful.
If a martial artist
who has practiced kung fu for decades
meets a guy who doesn't know kung fu
but knows how to use a gun,
the martial artist won't win.
The world has changed.
If I don't learn this,
I will be beaten in the future.
Lucky.
Today isn't a lucky day.
Father.
What are you doing?
A major event is upon us.
The Beiyang Army should have sent troops
as agreed.
They suddenly changed their minds.
You already knew it?
Zhong Haichao.
In the end, you chose Beiyang Army
and betrayed me.
Was it ten years
or eleven years?
Ever since you just
joined the Beiyang Army,
I have been paving the way for you.
Your military rank has been rising
year by year.
Your actual power
has been increasing annually.
I promoted you to a position
of great power.
Now, you are fully-fledged.
And you don't need me anymore
and are unwilling to yield to others,
right?
So,
you betrayed me.
Father.
It sounds inappropriate.
Indeed,
I am aware that Beiyang Army
won't send troops tomorrow.
But it's not something I can control.
Of course, it's not.
But you did not tell me earlier.
Father.
Don't tell me
that you found out
after you were in Fujian.
Betrayal.
It's a betrayal.
Your Highness.
When you chose me as your son-in-law,
you must have already anticipated this.
You chose me
because of my wisdom and ability.
A truly intelligent person
can't make the wrong choices.
A truly capable person
can't be controlled by others.
I admit
that you have cultivated me
over the years.
But if I were an incompetent person,
I'm afraid
you would have already discarded me.
A young man should stay ambitious
instead of complaining when in trouble.
Besides, over these years,
I have worked so hard
without any defiance.
But you have always been wary of me.
Just like this time,
if the Beiyang Army had not noticed it,
I probably wouldn't have known
that you ordered the Rongtian Ridge
to secretly search for treasure.
Oh, right.
You haven't told me yet
that you also have worked
with the Japanese military.
You seem to know quite a bit.
You would rather trust the Japanese
than the Beiyang Army.
If I'm against foreign intruders,
I will trust the Beiyang Army.
But if I'm against rebels,
foreigners are more reliable.
So,
the Qing Imperial Court
established the Beiyang Army,
but it could never control it.
And by the same logic,
the court doesn't trust Beiyang Army,
just like you don't trust me.
You are ungrateful.
You think you're right?
It's not that I'm ungrateful.
You're too wary.
It's not that Beiyang Army
is ungrateful.
The Qing Imperial Court is too feeble.
Your wariness and the court's weakness
make me and Beiyang Army feel hopeless.
Your Highness.
Today,
do you really think
you can make me believe
that you can turn the situation around?
Right.
At this point,
I indeed have no way to change anything.
But the dignity of the imperial family
cannot be insulted.
No one insults you.
At this point,
you're humiliating yourself.
So is the court.
It sticks to its old ways,
so it's humiliated by the great powers.
What do you think you are?
You're nothing but a dog.
I fail to tame you.
But the Beiyang Army fails too.
Haichao.
Stop!
Let her stay.
Spare her life.
Let her see the future world.
Do what the princess said.
Don't kill her.
Take her away.
Go.
I killed Zhong Haichao.
You don't hate me?
When you made me marry Zhong Haichao,
I hated you then.
You are my daughter,
not a child from an ordinary family.
Born in an imperial family,
you have no choice.
You know my position.
And you should know the wishes
I want to fulfill.
You're a sensible girl
and can see the bigger picture.
Father.
You let me see the bigger picture?
It means you're unreasonable,
but you still push me.
I hate you
not because you forced me
to marry someone I didn't want to,
but because you forced me,
and you still pretended
to do it all for me.
Is it all for me?
You did it all for your wishes.
Or you did it all
for your desires.
You've grown up.
You have your own thoughts.
But your thinking is still not mature.
Idealism is wonderful,
but too unrealistic.
And it can't bear much weight.
Well,
if you can understand
how heavy the burden on my shoulders is,
I believe you will understand me.
Indeed, I can't understand
your thirst for power.
Alright.
I won't talk about it with you anymore.
Oh, right.
I know
you still have feelings
for Irgen-Gioro Muqing.
After returning to the capital,
you two get married.
Although he is not willing to follow me,
I am willing to accept him
as my son-in-law.
You just said I've grown up.
Yes.
I've grown up.
So, I don't need your approval
of my marriage.
Muqing can marry me
without your approval.
(The ninth day of the fifth month,
3th year of Xuantong era)
(two days before Mangzhong)
You're awake.
Where am I?
You're on the sea.
We're waiting for people.
Who?
Men Sandao.
Do you really betray the court?
Haven't I already told you before?
What about the Dharma Seal?
You got it?
Do you remember the day
when Liu Lin and I
could enter the Futu Temple
but you couldn't?
Liu Lin saw the letter left
by my master.
In 1851, Prajna, Bodhi,
and Dharma met for the thirty-year pact.
But the chief of Disciplinary Department
didn't appear.
So the three chiefs made a deal.
To avoid accidents,
they tattooed their respective patterns
on their disciples' bodies
to pass them down.
Wang Jialuo.
The Dharma Seal has been on you.
What about Lin Haohan?
He is Prajna's inheritor.
Though Lin Haohan has died,
Prajna's inheritors are about to arrive.
We are here
waiting for them.
The chief of the Prajna Hall
spread revolutionary ideas overseas.
He has many disciples.
Each of them
bears the Prajna Seal.
Hi, thank you for coming.
Hello.
I have already copied the tattoo on you.
Again,
I admire you.
Join us.
If you want to talk,
I'll talk to you about the revolution.
At first,
you may be reluctant to listen.
If you listen more,
you will gradually accept it.
I'd rather die.
Men Sandao.
Let's fight.
Why?
You haven't eaten for days.
You can't even stand steady.
Can you be my opponent?
Let's fight.
Alright.
Let's see what you can do.
I'm telling you.
I'm not in a hurry.
I can wait.
I can gradually influence you.
When I'm tired,
I will tie you up
and throw you into the Futu Temple.
After some years,
you will understand
why we need a revolution
and why we must change the nation.
The ancients have made it clear.
Once rules are established,
why should they be changed?
I do my best to chase the criminal
not only to uphold the law
and regulations
but also to motivate myself.
I, Wang Jialuo,
fail the court.
(A nation needs a ruler.)
I let down the people.
(A court needs rules.)
I fail the emperor.
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
The law needs to be upheld.
I fail to fulfill my duty.
(A minister cannot be
without integrity.)
Do I have a reason
to live in this world?
Wang Jialuo.
Can you read it?
Lin Haohan has told me the way
to decode the seal.
The Discipline Seal appears
like mountains and waters.
In fact, it refers to Mount Huangmei
and Caoxi.
The Dharma Seal is a field of reeds,
suggesting the story
of crossing the river by a reed.
Therefore, the message conveyed
by the seal
is two places, Guangzhou
and Songshan Shaolin Temple.
The Bodhi Seal signifies the starting
and ending points of the treasure.
Tianzhu is the starting point.
And the Southern Shaolin burnt down
300 years ago
is the end.
Therefore, the three seals
indicate six locations.
Tianzhu,
Southern Shaolin,
Guangzhou,
Songshan Shaolin Temple,
Mount Huangmei,
and Baolin Temple of Caoxi.
The Prajna Seal is an amulet,
implying guardianship.
So the central point
of the six locations...
Tianzhu and Baolin Temple of Caoxi,
Songshan Shaolin Temple
and Southern Shaolin,
Mount Huangmei and Southern Shaolin,
Baolin Temple of Caoxi
and Southern Shaolin.
So, that's how this works.
Here.
Master asked us to guard this place.
I never thought
that we'd been guarding the entrance
to the Altar Treasure.
It's been guarded for generations.
What we've been guarding
is the secret treasure.
(The 11th day of the 5th month,
3th year of Xuantong era, Mangzhong)
♪The wind howls softly♪
♪I am strolling through the wind♪
It's finally about to end.
♪The waves wash fervently♪
♪I am feeling the surge♪
♪In the east sea♪
Give it a try.
Delicious.
It tastes good.
The heat control for each dish is good.
Oh, my.
This is so good.
Guess what?
It's crispy and tender.
Good.
Have some soup.
This soup is fresh.
Let me try.
♪Cloaked in autumn frost♪
♪Gazing far into the heavens♪
♪Yellow sand flies high♪
♪Dyed by the winter snow♪
♪We wander♪
♪Ten thousand miles in the world♪
Higher.
♪Bathed in the spring breeze♪
- Democracy.
- Freedom.
- Democracy. Freedom.
♪Cloaked in autumn frost♪
♪Gazing far into the heavens♪
(One month later)
♪Dyed by the winter snow♪
♪We wander♪
♪Ten thousand miles in the world♪
Be careful.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You don't write anymore?
No, I don't.
Anyway, no one sees them.
Just keep them in mind.
Will you come here again?
No, I will not.
You don't write.
I can understand.
Two more gravestones.
No.
One is for Zhuo Bufan.
The other is for Wang Jialuo.
Without them,
we wouldn't have the chance
to open the Altar Treasure.
The number of tombstones
doesn't matter.
So many have died.
We don't even know who they are.
By the way,
where are you two heading next?
Are you returning to the capital?
No.
My place is just a birdcage
made of gold.
I finally flew out of it.
Why do I fly back?
And you?
Before leaving the capital,
I was a fourth-ranked imperial guard.
Now I have become an accomplice
of rebels.
Can I go back?
To be precise,
you are definitely a rebel now.
How can you see yourself
as an accomplice?
Where are we two going?
I'll go to Hong Kong.
Lin Haohan's fellows
are transporting the treasures.
I am responsible for supervising.
If I go with you,
I won't be of much help, right?
You go to Wuchang.
My friends
and comrades are there.
When I come back from Hong Kong,
I will come to find you.
Okay.
I will wait for you.
You find a place
for us to stay.
I prefer a western-style house.
Okay.
I will plant flowers in the yard.
Red spider lilies.
Can I go with you?
I'm tired of slaughtering pigs.
I might as well join you
in the revolution.
After all, I'm good at killing beasts.
(December 30, 1911)
Is it especially lively in your place?
It's especially chaotic.
I think everyone is at a loss.
After so many years,
the Wuchang Uprising succeeded.
I'll be at a loss too.
Succeeded?
Isn't it a victory?
I think it is just the beginning.
Now it depends on the power of the army
to change the situation.
This is just one city.
To change a country,
it takes more people to wake up.
Hello?
The revolution in Wuchang will ignite.
I'm not sure if it can spread
throughout the country
or can truly change the nation.
I hope it can.
But given the experiences
over the past years, I think
we have to change
by completely
overthrowing the feudal dynasty.
Hello?
We can't be timid.
Hello, Muqing?
We can't give up.
Muqing.
If you think we have already won,
there will be a harder road ahead.
Anyway,
it's already started.
I believe in this.
I am willing to go on.
Muqing, what are you saying?
Hello, can you hear me?
I can hear now.
I'm saying the day
when we change the nation
will come.
The day when I marry you
will come too.
Wait for me.
(August 29, 1913)
(Men Sandao died
in the Second Revolution in Nanjing.)
(October 10, 1926)
(Wulan Shan followed the Fourth Army
of the Northern Expedition)
(and was shot by a stray bullet
during the general attack in Wuchang,)
(and died in Guangzhou one year later.)
(Since they parted in Fujian,
they've never met again)
(The End)
♪Blood refines the sword,
and wind forges the blade♪
♪I am still that person
with rough edges♪
♪My heart is vast like the sea,
and my soul doesn't want to fight♪
♪How long can I remain young♪
♪I sigh for the elusive destiny♪
♪I struggle half my life in destitution♪
♪Who can laugh in this fancy world♪
♪Don't squander your prime.
Don't squander your day♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪