(During the Kangxi era,)
(the Eight Banners
besieged Southern Shaolin)
(and burnt down the temple completely.)
(The reasons behind this are varied.)
(But most people)
(in the Imperial Household Department
believe)
(that destroying Southern Shaolin
was to seize the Altar Treasure.)
(The last abbot of Southern Shaolin)
(coexisted with the temple.)
(Before passing away,)
(he handed over the treasure map
of Southern Shaolin's Altar Treasure)
(to the chief
of the Disciplinary Department.)
(He told him to live in seclusion)
(and keep the secret.)
(By the 28th year of the Daoguang era,)
(before the second-generation chief
of Disciplinary Department passed away,)
(he passed on his mantle
to his eldest disciple.)
(But his second disciple
overheard the secret.)
(This second disciple is Xu He.)
(He secretly killed the elder disciple,)
(who's the third-generation
chief inheritor.)
(Then Xu He took the treasure map
and defected to the imperial court.)
(By the 7th year of Tongzhi era,)
(Xu He reported to Qing Imperial Court)
(that a person)
(who proclaimed himself
to be an inheritor of Southern Shaolin)
(came to him.)
(He wanted to take this man down
with imperial guards)
(of the Imperial Household Department.)
(But unexpectedly,
his plan was exposed,)
(and he got killed by this man.)
(All the clues are gone.)
(Therefore, documents
about the Altar Treasure)
(became confidential)
(and was locked up in Wenyuan Pavilion
by Imperial Household Department.)
This all happened a long time ago.
Even Mr. Cunqing said
that this secret treasure
is merely a legend to him.
It may not even exist.
Then Southern Shaolin
has no other inheritors, right?
Xu He was not
the inheritor at all.
So he didn't know most of the secrets.
But he vaguely remembered
that his master had
some mysterious friends.
But he had no idea who they were,
nor where they would be.
Xu He is dead?
Right.
He deserved it.
So no one
ever mentioned this again.
Now Tan Xian appeared.
Could Tan Xian be
another inheritor
of the Southern Shaolin?
Perhaps.
If he really is,
with Zhuo Bufan
who has the treasure map,
and Tan Xian,
maybe we can find the Altar Treasure.
Well,
Tan Xian is even
more crucial than Zhuo Bufan.
Getai.
Don't let Tan Xian get away.
He can't.
=Heroes=
=Episode 5=
The scallion oil noodles
are still best made in Shanghai.
There's an old shop in City God Temple.
They make them even more delicious.
After we settle the case,
I'll accompany you
to stroll around there.
Okay.
(Maiqi Road, Shanghai)
We need over 2,600 steps
to walk down the Maiqi Road,
about
25 yin 14 zhang and one chi.
There are 11 shops
on the east side of the street.
Three clothing stores,
two grocery stores,
two fruit stores,
two restaurants,
(Book Store)
one book store,
(Bama Tea House)
and one tea house.
There are nine shops
on the west side of the street.
One large restaurant,
(Bogu Store)
two foreigners' stores,
one fruit store, one jewelry store,
one gold shop,
and one shop that sells foreign bread.
The one above is
the foreign coffee shop.
Muqing, you are perceptive.
Trying to intercept people
on a street like this
only requires 15
capable guards,
even for a master.
Then we have enough manpower.
Muqing.
Maybe we should
get our men to wear these western suits.
We don't even know
where the contact person is.
Disguise ourselves
as members of the Tongmenghui
might give us away.
Just keep an eye on this street.
For his intersection, corner,
and this street,
we need to send more men to stand guard.
Understood.
What are you looking for?
I am wondering
where Zhuo Bufan will appear tomorrow.
I guess
he will definitely have his men
hide among these merchants.
Then we should deploy our men
all over the street.
So, we need
to have them disguise
themselves as passersby.
Merchants, tourists, peddlers, porters,
beggars, and vagrants as well.
Don't all disguise as the same type.
Got it.
This road isn't very long.
We've got enough men
to lock down the front.
No way.
If we do so,
Tan Xian and the others won't come in.
Position soldiers around Maiqi Road
and tell them to disguise.
Yes.
Did you take down
that county yamen's constable?
He can work on a case
with the Imperial Household Department.
It means that he must
be a master of stealth.
His martial arts are indeed
superior to those
of many Japanese samurais.
But I have already
knocked him off the cliff
and he is impossible to survive.
Did you
go down the cliff to look for his body?
You didn't?
There was no way
I could get down there.
Then how can you be sure
that he is impossible to survive?
Based on my judgment,
I think he must have been dead.
I hope so.
I hope you're right.
You're awake.
You saved me?
I can't.
You made it.
Eat some?
Take it.
Thank you.
You are a monk,
so why are you eating meat
and drinking wine?
What about the precepts?
Who told you I am a monk?
There's not a temple here,
let alone the precepts.
Furthermore,
following Buddhism is
all about the mind,
not related to the words
or the food.
You make sense.
You flattered me.
How much money do you owe?
Why were you attacked like this?
(Bama Tea House)
I want braised eel,
eight-treasure duck,
stir-fried herbage,
Yanduxian,
and stir-fried rice cake with crab.
Alright!
Sounds delicious.
Muqing, you are also
familiar with local dishes?
This is a nice place.
The whole street is in full view.
We'll observe any changes
here tomorrow.
This position should
be left for Zhuo Bufan.
Tomorrow we'll go upstairs for tea.
We have to be patient tomorrow.
We can't make any action
until Zhuo Bufan helps us
recognize Tan Xian.
At your disposal.
If these patrolmen meddled,
I'm afraid it would ruin our plan.
Go and notify the Patrol Yamen
to have all these patrolmen
transferred away tomorrow.
Muqing.
These are the patrolmen
from the Concession.
The Patrol Yamen can't control them.
Then who can?
It should be
the Concession's Public Council.
But it is controlled by foreigners.
Ask the Patrol Yamen
to tell those foreigners
the court has a case to handle.
No matter what,
let us do our things.
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
I can't believe you
chased all the way from Dagu County.
Are you going to
keep chasing to Shanghai?
Yes.
What are you after?
You are a mere local constable.
Is it worth it?
To ordain conscience
for Heaven and Earth.
To secure life and fortune
for the people.
To continue lost teachings
for past sages.
To establish peace
for all future generations.
You really dream big.
Can't I?
You are persistent.
But you are too persistent.
Do you think you can bring justice
on your own?
You don't know
how much it takes
to bring justice.
You're never going
to accomplish this in your life.
Your life is short,
but the dynasty lives long.
It existed before you were born.
Maybe it still exists when you're dead.
You can't even live longer than it.
Why do you care about it?
I just think...
The Qing Dynasty has been around
for nearly 300 years.
You are only a young man.
You know nothing at all.
When you're dead,
your flesh will rot away.
What's left?
Fame lasts forever?
That's a lie.
There is no fame in a pile of bones.
Not just fame,
even notoriety can't last.
Being notorious
is not an ordinary thing as well.
I managed to survive.
And yet you say such words,
so why didn't you kill me
in the first place?
As a merely
a county yamen constable,
you can quote Zhuang Zhou's maxims.
Impressive.
Really impressive.
What's so hard about reading
books by sages?
The hard part is
to convey the idea
of the sages to others.
You can achieve great things.
Anyone who can achieve great things
must go through hardships.
You've got a tough road ahead of you.
What great things can I achieve?
I'm a merely yamen constable.
All I think about is
being able to catch those murderers
and bring them back.
Because you are persistent,
so you will surely achieve great things.
Local constable,
fate has brought you this far.
You have no choice.
It's so hard to get drunk.
Local constable,
I have to go get some wine.
From here to Shanghai,
it takes half a day to walk.
You'd better get on the road.
Thank you for saving me.
If I...
If you can accomplish great things,
then I did a wise choice
to save you today.
(Shanghai Management Department)
Sir, I've been talking to the foreigners
at the Public Council
of French Concession all afternoon.
I have been exhausted.
And the foreigners finally agreed
to turn a blind eye,
and wouldn't hinder us.
From 8 AM
to 6 PM tomorrow,
there are 10 hours!
All the police forces on Maiqi Road
and the surrounding three streets
will be withdrawn.
It's a huge gesture.
What did he say?
From the hour of Chen
to the hour of You,
they can make things easier for us.
That's all?
You call it a huge gesture?
Of course.
Those are foreigners.
They also made
some requests.
Requests?
Right.
They want us to promise
not to create chaos,
not to fire guns,
or harm any innocent.
I have to give face to them
when we do our things in our own place.
Mr. Mu.
This is not our own place.
This is the Concession.
Mr. Mu.
This is the foreigners' territory.
Just bear it.
Flowers for sale!
Would you like to buy some flowers?
(Menxing Hotel)
Flowers! Flowers!
Would you like to buy some flowers?
Excuse me, kid.
What?
Sir,
may I ask...
This is a hotel.
You either sleep or eat here.
What do you want to ask?
Why are you like this?
I'm talking to you nicely.
What do you mean?
Look at you.
Hick!
Hick?
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
I am the constable of Dagu County Yamen,
and I come here to investigate a case.
Check it.
Constable of Dagu County Yamen.
Did you frighten me?
Dagu County of Tianjin.
What are you doing in Shanghai?
Look at you.
I think you picked this up.
You should pick a token
of a bigger city.
Laugh at me?
Laugh again, if you dare.
Sir!
Please don't be angry.
You are generous.
He's young and naive.
Let me ask you.
On the first day of the fourth month,
were there a group of people
in Lingxi costumes here?
Yes.
But they all left yesterday afternoon.
How many of them?
They've split up.
There were about 20 people.
They planned to book rooms
for three days,
but I don't know why
they all left yesterday afternoon.
Where did they go?
I don't know.
Did they mention any place?
Well...
Did they mention or not?
What did they say?
Where will they go or what will they do?
Think hard.
- Okay.
This is a confidential document
from the military department.
(Confidential)
(The third day of the fourth month,
3th year of Xuantong era)
(37 days before Mangzhong)
Cigarettes!
Muqing.
I've just made a round of checks.
The Concession's Public Council
have transferred
all the patrolmen away from here.
This street
and the surrounding three streets
are completely undefended.
And our people are also all in position,
from one end of the street to the other.
Setting up defenses.
What kind of defense is this?
These two beggars
just put mud on their faces,
but didn't even beg for money.
I wonder if these two vendors
are out of mind.
They don't even sell things.
Cigarettes!
Not for selling.
And those with shoulder poles...
They should be
walking the streets calling out.
But they are just sitting in the shade.
They just look like
imperial guards in disguise.
And these two...
They've even painted the lamps.
They don't even look like painters.
Who are they ambushing?
Muqing, you are right.
I'm sorry about that.
I'll go warn them.
They are already in position.
(Bama Tea House)
It's better not to move now.
Making any move might expose them.
Maybe the opponents don't see it
like you do.
I don't see anything unusual outside.
People
from Imperial Household Department
and the Japanese
might not know
we are waiting here for Tan Xian.
An ambush is not something you can see.
If it can be seen,
then it won't be an ambush.
Zhuo Bufan is here.
Just as you predicted,
they're sitting at
the same table we sat at yesterday.
Three people in total.
Zhuo Bufan, one man and one woman.
Right.
We found nine sets of clothes
at Tang Yu's place earlier.
So, I'm afraid
there are nine men
from Rongtian Ridge hiding out here.
Not nine,
but eleven.
Eleven?
Look at that clothes store.
There are four men inside.
From the way they dress,
they seem like reform-minded students.
But that store is for tailoring suits.
And they keep getting
close to the window,
and they are surely
observing the outside.
Those two standing
and chatting by the street
have been talking ever since I arrived.
There's not that much to talk about.
Three men who look like students
are sitting beside the bookshelf.
They picked the right place.
However,
I've already had a pot of tea
and he hasn't turned
a single page of his book.
That makes nine.
I am not that observant.
What about the rest two?
They are strolling,
from the street corner
to the center of the street,
and then they walk back.
They went back and forth three times.
Indeed, there are eleven.
Getai, have you noticed anything?
Please advise me.
The clothes store and the book stall
are on the east side of the street.
The people inside keep
looking across the street.
Those two people who are chatting
are standing near
the intersection on the east side.
Those two men who are strolling
keep walking south along the road.
So that's where...
Correct.
All of them
are focusing on that coffee shop.
Zhuo Bufan's men have revealed
that Tan Xian will show up there.
That coffee shop
is the key location for today.
Alright.
You guys sit here.
I'm going for a stroll.
Look at it clearly.
This is Tan Xian.
Yes.
(Bogu Store)
Boss.
Is business doing well?
Thank you for asking.
Not bad.
Sir, what would you like to buy?
Good stuff.
I only want good stuff.
Everything in my store is good stuff.
That's what I do.
Whether it's good or not
is not for you to say.
This is nice.
This jade cabbage is made
from a single piece of jade.
That Buddha statue is far inferior.
I'm
discerning.
Amazing!
Expert.
You are an expert.
Sure enough, an expert
is so discerning.
Take a look.
This is not simple.
It appears to be from Ru kiln,
but it's not.
It is from Bianjing official kiln.
This kiln has much
in common with Ru kiln.
Many are in antique style.
The main part is in deep gray or purple.
The glaze includes light greenish blue
and bluish white.
It's crystal-clear
with streaks.
Purple rim and iron foot.
You can't tell it
if you are not an expert.
Among a bunch of Ru kiln stuff,
but you...
You picked this one up.
You are discerning!
You are an expert,
and you have sharp eyes.
Sir.
It seems we are all experts.
We should communicate more.
I come from the South Asia,
specifically dealing in
antiques and treasures.
Let's get to know each other.
I am Lin Haohan.
(Lin Haohan)
Secluded groves
amidst the endless immensity.
Of course.
You can call me
by my English name if you like.
Lucky.
In Chinese,
it means good luck
and blessings for a prosperous start.
A good friend is hard to find.
Sir, you have arrived.
Is that him?
I think so.
Can I help you?
Coffee, please.
Alright.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
Sugar, please.
Any problem?
I just gave him
a gesture to verify identity.
But he had no reaction at all.
So what do we do?
It isn't him?
That man wants to say hello to me.
He's coming for us.
Stay calm.
Don't panic.
Let's wait a bit longer.
Fine porcelain
is truly more precious than gold.
Like you,
I just can't put
such a fine thing down.
Touching it feels
so satisfying
and amazing.
Let's go.
Those people
are very likely to come at us.
We have to leave right away.
But how can we meet them up?
If we don't leave now,
I'm afraid we can't get away.
Alright, as you say.
Let's go.
Sir,
what's the rush to leave?
The Japanese are here.
Sir.
Muqing.
The Japanese are here.
What's so surprising?
It would be odd if they don't come.
But they have many people.
There is no fear of the mob in numbers.
Looks like we will have a tough day.
No matter what,
don't waste your energy.
We have only one target.
The man in the coffee shop
must be Tan Xian.
There are too many people.
Don't go out now.
Qin Tuo.
Sect Leader.
Go in and capture the man.
Stop them.
Let's see who dares to stop me.
The murderers
of the Dagu Inn case in Tianjin,
the men from Lingxi Rongtian Ridge,
surrender now.
(Constable of Dagu County Yamen)
I am Wang Jialuo, the constable
of the Dagu County Yamen.
I have chased the murderers
for 1,000 miles.
Rongtian Ridge's men,
Yu Huanjie and Qin Tuo,
have committed the crime of murder.
Zhuo Bufan, Sect Leader of Rongtian
Ridge, has to take the responsibility.
Put down your weapons
and come with me
to the Dagu County Yamen for trial.
Should you not surrender
and confess your crime,
according to the laws
of the Qing Dynasty,
you shall be executed.
♪Blood refines the sword,
and wind forges the blade♪
♪I am still that person
with rough edges♪
♪My heart is vast like the sea,
and my soul doesn't want to fight♪
♪How long can I remain young♪
♪I sigh for the elusive destiny♪
♪I struggle half my life in destitution♪
♪Who can laugh in this fancy world♪
♪Don't squander your prime.
Don't squander your day♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪
♪When beauty fades,
dreams will never come true♪
♪I am willing to shed my blood♪
♪To be a part of the history♪
♪My ambition is hard to fulfill,
for it is in vain till the end♪
♪I've been concerned for the country
for a decade♪
♪My passion never fades♪
♪Life is too short,
just like plants all year round♪
♪What am I always on the way for♪
♪I am like a swan goose
stepping into the snow♪
♪The ship sails against the wind,
through scorching heat and biting cold♪
♪The insects that only exist in summer
will never know how the ice tastes♪