Let's go! This is for you, Jay-jay!
[roaring]
Let's go!
- Let's go!
- Go, Keifer!
[Cheering]
Yes!
Beat it! Beat it! Beat it!
Hello, I'm Andres Muhlach.
I'm Rabin Angeles.
And now we will do the...
Section E Olympics!
[cheering]
The first game that
we will be playing is...
Break the plate!
Dancer!
MK is tired. He's sweating.
[laughing]
So the mechanics of the game is
they should hit him.
He's thee target.
So we need two balls.
You can see two balls, right?
So you need to...
the plate and the balls...
Boom!
So if you get two...
Huh! Congratulations!
You'll have a prize.
And if you get one,
[Yanyan whimpers]
So let's start the game!
Ashtine, give us a sample.
How do you throw?
Throw it hard!
Whoa!
Wow!
You hit something.
Round one.
Go!
Game!
I'll go first?
Yes! You.
[chattering]
Oh my God!
That was hard!
Don't be mad!
[laughing]
Ooh!
Let's go!
Go Yuri!
- Go Rabin!
Whoa!
That counts as one?
One, one, one!
There, the one in black!
Ooh!
That's a shame.
Buji's next.
Martin.
Mic on Martin.
He's gonna win.
He is in dire need.
He'll score. He's in dire need.
Let's go!
Let's go, young father!
Whoa!
Head shot!
One more? One more?
One more!
That's enough.
I got you, boy!
Let's go!
[incoherent]
Ooh!
[chattering]
Whoa!
That's two!
Michael!
So Yuri wins. Congratulations!
Choose the toy!
You?
Pick a toy.
I'll get the brown one.
Ma'am, can you get it please?
The brown one.
There you go.
I'll come back.
So this is your prize.
Thank you for playing with us.
Welcome to Enchanted Kingdom, Ma'am!
And for our next game...
High striker!
[cheering]
Okay, stop. Stop.
Stop the car.
For our mechanics...
This.
The bat.
The bell.
Ring.
Win!
Yes sir!
Let's go!
[sorry, headphone users]
Yuri!
Where's my boy?
Let's go!
Yuri and Keifer!
Support! Support!
Let's go, Yuri!
Let's go! Let's go!
[cheering]
That's my boy!
This is for you, Jay-jay!
[chattering]
That's my boy!
Show them who you are.
[roaring]
Okay, okay! Let's go!
You can! You can.
But before 17.
That's 17.
Here, Keifer.
[chattering]
Okay!
Thor's hammer!
You'll beat the world record.
Believe in yourself!
So I'm supposed to beat 1700.
But...
I don't know. Let's see.
You must...
Again and again and again!
Go, Keifer!
[screaming]
It's a tie.
They're the same!
So guys, I lost.
It's a tie!
Oh its a tie?
That means we won!
We won, Keifer!
We won!
Round two! Round two!
No!
[chattering]
Okay, okay.
Okay go.
Game?
Game!
Go hard!
Go, lumberjack!
Go!
[grunting]
Let's go, baby!
No! You can't do it!
[incoherent]
Oh!
Oh 100?
It's lower.
There.
[chattering]
Let's go!
Guys, I have to beat-
What's the score? 16?
You should be 17 again or 18.
That's gonna be enough.
Yes!
We'll win this!
We'll win!
You can let them lose.
Go, Keifer!
Let's go!
Come on, Keif!
There you go!
Yeah!
Let's go, Keifer!
I love you, Keify!
Now what?
Who wants to go?
Keagan, Keagan!
You got this?
You want me to make a turn?
Okay.
Now...
1700 is AJ's
score to beat.
Beat it! Beat it!
Watch!
Watch me miss this.
I'm nervous.
Okay!
AJ Abejar!
One more, one more! Practice.
No, no, no! Did you see?
So did you see 1300?
Practice!
Like his height.
Okay, since Rory scored 1300...
Now, this is my boy.
Okay. We're gonna win this, right?
Am I right or not?
Yes.
So he said yes.
Now beat that!
Let's go!
Oh! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Do it for the girls, man!
[screaming]
Oh!
Let's go, Rory!
Come here, baby!
Game?
[chattering]
Let's go.
Ooh!
Nice try.
Last turn.
What about you? How do you feel?
I was told to say that I was gonna beat 18.
Wow! He's building momentum!
Whoa!
It rings!
That's tough!
[makes ringing sounds]
There.
Twenty? We got 20.
[screaming]
Yey!
Jay-jay!
So Jay-jay...
You choose.
I want the same color as your hair.
Wow!
Okay. Now we're going to our last game.
We'll see if Keifer can catch up.
We'll see.
And for our last game...
Can Smash!
There you go.
[cheering]
So for the game mechanics...
We have two balls.
They just have to knock them down.
To win...
a huge prize!
[cheering]
I'll go first.
Yeah.
And yeah.
- This is Andres Muhlach.
- And yeah!
Hi, guys! This is Andres Muhlach.
Two tries to knock down...
Six cans.
Okay. Ready, guys?
Go! Go! Let's go, Keifer!
I'll go first.
Focus!
[laughing]
Okay.
Oh!
Focus!
Focus.
You thought.
Yeah!
Wow!
All one! All one!
- One-one.
- Tiebreaker.
One!
One-one!
Yes, Sir!
Yes, Red Rabin!
Four to go.
Wow!
We lost. We lost.
[cheering]
So you can hear the screams here in EK!
The winner for this round is...
Keifer!
[cheering]
Let's go!
Since Keifer won...
which stuffed toy do you want?
Ma'am, I want...
The whole stall?
Can I have that one?
Why pick the one hanging?
So how do we do this?
Can you reach it?
The pig one.
So here's your prize, Ma'am.
- 1, 500 only.
- Thank you!
That's 1, 500.
I don't have [money].
Alright, she has none.
Congratulations!
Congratulations to me!
I'm the winner!
Yes, Sir!
What can you say, Ash?
What can you say?
I'm in tears!
Why?
Because I have so much to carry.
Because?
Because...
[stuttering]
You made me win.
And?
And...
I'm happy?
Because?
Because...
You made me win.
Ash, what's your favorite color?
My favorite color is blue.
Whoa!
What is your favorite number?
My favorite number is 19.
Whoa!
I hope you guys enjoyed and...
Yeah.
That's it. That's it.
I hope you guys enjoyed and...
Don't forget to watch
Ang Mutya ng Section E only on...
Viva One!
At Viva One.
You're the star!
Section E Olympics!