I like you.
I like you too.
Oh! Why was I dreaming like this?
I better go showering.
9.00 AM. step with the left foot, right?
There must be something wrong. You’re here early today.
I’m hungry. / You’re here early for eating?
Oh! You both came together today?
No. I came across with her at the gate.
Ah I see.
What?
It sounds weird.
. Look! There are people wearing shirt with the same color.
Why?
Here!
Enough of both of them. Today the auspicious color is black.
I didn’t even say anything.
Hello everyone.
You guys are ready, right?
Yes. / Yes, sir.
Have you been tired?
Pretty tired…
I am tired. Really tired. Is there any chance to get a bonus this month?
Saimai. You can’t talk like this to him.
Enough. No need to be arguing.
Just do your best today. Keep going!
Sir,
Oh. Khun Cindy.
Sir, the client has arrived./ Okay.
Here we go.
Hold on. The shirt seems not very neat.
Thank you.
You look good now
Okay. Everyone please goes to the meeting room.
Yes, sir.
How is it? Is it okay?
Well, it looks nice. I like it so much.
Your company is great as people say.
I have to give credit to Khun Weala and her team.
I love it.
Hmm…
Then, you don’t want to add any more things, right?
No. I like it like this. I’ll take this one.
Well, I probably must leave now.
Okay. I’ll take Khun Ray to the car
See you, Khun Ray.
Thank you everyone.
Goodbye.
How is it now?
What…
Look! That was so clear. Don’t refuse to admit it.
Because there’s nothing.
Or… you fell in love with her.
No way.
You know it. I don’t love anyone.
Khun Wea. If you find the right one. That one will get rid of your fear,
if the one is not right. May I take that one?
You should leave now.
I’m your client. You’re telling me to leave?
There you go.
and don’t forget, okay?
Forget about what? / about If you don’t take that one.
You should leave. There you go! / Okay. I’m going…
Everyone has been working very well.
. Today, I’d like to bring to you all to
Wow… of course!
Khun Nabdao.
Yes, sir
See you in the evening
Yes
Hey Cindy, what are you doing?
Cindy's secret to a good figure
No wonder Miss Cindy always has a good figure.
I'll have to find some to eat soon.
You can do it.
Want to be beautiful?
Oh! Nabdao and Boss!
Thank you, sis. No cheers?
You’re good as people say.
Hmm… nah. I only meant to do it my best.
Beautiful and smart! Do you have a boyfriend?
No, I don’t.
Same here. I don’t have a girlfriend.
I get drunk now.
Let’s cheers and have fun together!
Sure!!!
Cheers!
Come on, sis.
Khun Nabdao…
Yes, boss?
Yes,
I have something to tell you.
What about it?
I think you’re the one who makes my time runs faster.
Yes? What is it?
Everytime I’m near you. I’m so happy. I want to stop time.
You’re what I want to see every day.
I’ve been trying to find out about this,
and the answer is… I like you.
Is it possible if we try to…
Boss, I’m so drunk.
I have headache too.
Cindy. You’re too drunk now.
Hey, boss. Cheers!
Saimai.
Where should we go next? It’s so fun now!
Take care!
Saimai. Don’t be too noisy.
I’ll take her out now. I’m leaving
You go with Khun Ve, Okay?
Boss. I have a severe headache. We should leave now.
Okay. Take care of Nabdao for me, Khun Weala.
Let’s go. Hurry up, boss.
Are you okay?
Hmm… Khun Wea
Nabdao
Khun Wea
is so cute.
Let’s go home!
Going home? Take me there!
Yes.
It’s hot!
It’s hot! Khun Wea
Ouch!!
What are you doing?
I just…
Heat it again once you’re awake.
Sis. / What's wrong?
Why did you have such a strange hairstyle today?
It's the same.
Where is it like?
My hair is very long
I rode a motorcycle just now.
I don't know when the wig fell out.
So I had to wear a headband.
Should have expected that from the moment they left the house it wouldn't be blown away.
You're really good at knowing about other people.
I'm damaged.
Stop it, I have something to say.
I saw Nabdao coming down from Khun Wea's condo.
I saw them at the coffee shop.
They come together every day.
I thought I was the only one who knew.
I know.
Hey, I have something to say.
What's up?
You, do you know?
Nabdao with Khun Wea They have Something.
Nabdao, aren't you a fan of Boss Peam ?
doesn't know anything at all.
Tell me, you know everything.
You're the one who told me this.
Tell me where?
Tell me about it.
That day, they met in front of the office.
Many people saw each other.
They always come together.
I can't remember, there were too many things.
You're the one who told me.
Nooo… What happened to me.
I actually like Khun Wea…
What about Boss Peam.
I think you’re the one who makes my time runs faster.
Yes? What is it?
I like you.
Oh, what is this?