[The White Olive Tree]
[Episode 31]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.]
Captain.
Sasin.
You were supposed to handle the artillery,
not go onto the battlefield.
Why did you…
Lock me up if you want.
The war is over.
Why would I lock you up?
Forget it.
Since you just helped me out,
I'll let it slide this time.
Don't let it slide.
I don't want to be your scapegoat
and used as your excuse.
You know nothing.
Paying for drinks is not a big deal,
but freedom is.
Jerk.
What did you say?
At such a young age,
do you even know what a jerk is?
Where is your star?
Your star.
Stop.
Where are you going?
I need to find my star.
I'll go with you.
I don't need your help.
I can find it myself.
It's an order!
That bastard Ark escaped again.
We just took back the Holy Temple.
The battlefield hasn't been cleared yet.
You may be caught off guard and get shot.
And strictly speaking,
the star you lost is mine.
Take this.
Stop looking.
Let's go back.
I've given the star to you.
Why are you still looking?
The lost one is yours, but I still need to find it.
It's none of your business!
How can you find it in such a big place?
I'm talking to you!
Can you stop being so childish?
No.
Otherwise, Rina would blame me.
Cut the crap.
Come here!
Get down!
You got shot?
It hurts so much.
Zan.
The Holy Temple at Matuman
is still so beautiful.
Song.
Dr. Pei needs your help.
Just keep pressing on it.
Benjamin?
Why is it you?
Saline and gauze may not be enough.
Go get some for me.
Okay.
What happened to you?
An enemy shot at us.
He saved me.
I didn't take the bullet for you.
It was for…
For this.
You found it?
Don't move!
Do you want to have a limp for the rest of your life?
Dr. Pei, don't worry.
Even if I had a limp,
I'd still make it
to our Vinyl date.
No need for that.
You want to look at it, don't you?
Keep it to yourself.
I'm not looking at it.
I found the star,
but as Dr. Pei said,
I'll have to
walk with a limp in the future.
You'll need to provide for me.
Your leg is fine.
The bullet didn't hurt any bones or nerves.
You'll be fine after going to the hospital for some stitches.
Dr. Pei.
We got a patient here who needs your attention.
Okay.
You're in charge.
Just like this.
Okay.
Thank you.
For what?
I want to thank Zan too.
And him.
Eastern Country is like a big tree.
Thank you all for watering it.
Without you,
this tree
might never bear fruit again.
I…
I can't tell you
how grateful I am.
Sasin.
I always believe
Eastern Country and its people will make it through.
One day, you'll put down your gun
and pick up your pen again.
Song Ran.
That adjutant's injury
needs to be treated in the hospital.
Come with me.
Okay.
Take care of him.
♫Butterflies♫
♫Flying free♫
♫Tell the story♫
♫Dancing in the rain♫
♫Butterflies♫
♫Hiding from the world♫
♫Never feel alone♫
♫Never let her go♫
You're brave and brilliant.
Instructor Li.
It's me.
Sorry.
You're actually so fast
and so strong.
Sorry to scare you.
Here, wipe your face.
I'm good.
I'll clean it later.
There are so many bruises on your face.
And you did a lot for my country,
so I need to do something good for you as well.
You're welcome.
There are some basic medicines in the camp.
I'd better go back and clean my wounds first.
Well.
What is it? Did something go red?
It's okay.
Is it a gift from your family?
Yeah.
It's from my girlfriend
for safety and love.
Zan.
Song and the injured went to the hospital.
She asked me to tell you.
Did she just…
What?
Nothing.
Sasin.
I gotta go.
Ran, was that you?
♫Don't know where this road♫
The Holy Temple at Matuman
♫Takes me to♫
is still so beautiful.
♫Don't know where to restart♫
♫Feeling a fool♫
Zan.
♫I'm staring out the night♫
Where are you?
♫Bury deep my pain♫
It's been a long day.
♫To the place feeling good♫
I have a lot to tell you.
♫Don't cost a thing♫
♫This is not what I want♫
♫I'm not running from♫
We won! We won!
♫Where your love♫
♫Always been enough for me♫
♫Goodbye, my friend♫
♫To the laughter♫
♫And pain we had♫
Look, these are Matuman's heroes!
♫Saying goodbye to the endless nights in the rain♫
♫So long, my friend♫
♫Should have known you'd♫
♫Bring me this way♫
♫Saying goodbye to the place where I call home♫
Is Instructor Li here?
No. He's not here.
We won! We won!
We won!
We took Matuman back?
We took Matuman back!
God bless.
We won!
♫Goodbye, my friend♫
♫To the laughter♫
♫And pain we had♫
♫Saying goodbye to the endless nights in the rain♫
♫So long, my friend♫
♫Should have known you'd♫
♫Bring me this way♫
♫Saying goodbye to the place where I call home♫
Thank you so much. You're my hero.
♫In the land of Matuman♫
♫From the sea to desert lands♫
♫All the beautiful souls♫
♫Forever friends♫
♫We sing our oath to you♫
♫In the land of Matuman♫
♫There's a place where heroes stand♫
♫Through the ages♫
♫Your story aligns♫
♫We sing our oath to the sky♫
♫In the land of Matuman♫
This song is dedicated to the heroes
who bravely fought for Matuman Hill today!
♫From the sea to desert lands♫
We won!
We got Matuman Hill back!
♫All the beautiful souls♫
Long live Matuman Hill!
Great!
♫Forever friends♫
We got Matuman Hill back!
Let's go celebrate.
♫We sing our oath to you♫
Let's go to the square.
♫Have you ever found someone♫
♫Who sees right through your smile♫
♫Your eyes♫
♫You're sick from the miles♫
♫Tires are low♫
♫But in his heart♫
♫There's a place to go♫
♫He will be the light and the darkness♫
♫In your highs and lows♫
♫And say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know love♫
♫But I feel strong♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel loved♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know love♫
♫But I feel strong♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel loved♫
♫Te Amo♫
Zan.
I regret it now.
♫Still we don't know love♫
I regret breaking up with you.
♫But I feel strong♫
♫When I'm with you♫
I regret it.
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel loved♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Te Amo♫
I didn't think too much back then.
I thought you would…
But so much time has passed.
Ran.
Back then…
I know.
There was something on your mind.
Me too.
So you don't have to…
[Paroxetine hydrochloride]
Ran.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's not because we broke up.
I had this disease before.
The 926 Explosion…
Ran.
Why didn't you tell me about it?
I thought I had recovered.
Later, my mom got sick, and I…
Anyway, I'm fine now.
I haven't taken that medicine in a long time.
Don't… Don't…
Sorry.
I shouldn't have gone abroad when you
needed me the most.
No.
Don't say sorry to me.
You have nothing to apologize for.
I was…
I was in a bad mood.
I…
I shouldn't have said
I didn't want to hear from you anymore.
I was wrong.
I really regret it.
I wanted you to come back.
But
I didn't want you to change your mind
because I was ill.
Zan.
Things couldn't be like that.
I understand.
Ran.
It's not because of that.
I…
I've never thought about
cutting ties with you.
I just…
I said sorry
not because of that medicine.
I apologized because I knew it was very dangerous,
but I still came.
I knew you would find out
but still didn't tell you immediately.
I knew after I came here this time, I might…
I might die,
but I still kept moving forward.
Ran.
You're the person
who I owe the most in this world.
Because I knew I'd make you
endure a lot of pain…
but I still fell for you.
I still want to be with you.
I'm too selfish.
I let you bear
all the possible consequences. Sorry.
Sorry.
No.
Zan.
It was my choice.
I chose to be with you.
I fell for you.
♫She is a white island♫
Zan.
I couldn't bring myself to leave you,
♫The colorful wind rushes past♫
nor did I want to leave you.
But I still said those words.
♫Lonely waves, starlit glow♫
When I saw you at Matuman,
♫Quietly leaning together♫
♫Autumn reflects in the water♫
you were dismantling a bomb.
I saw you walking through bullets.
♫He is a blue sailboat♫
I was so scared.
♫Sailing alone♫
♫Through the boundless night♫
I was scared that
if something happened to you,
♫His sails dancing in the wind♫
I'd regret it…
♫Silently by her side♫
I'd regret it forever.
♫Heading toward her shore♫
I'd hate myself so much.
♫The sky turns a deeper blue♫
♫The brilliant night♫
♫Has never shone so bright♫
♫A white island♫
♫Blooms in the vast sea♫
♫I wish I could pick it♫
♫And give it to you♫
♫A white island♫
♫A blue sailboat♫
♫Heading toward her shore♫
♫The sky turns a deeper blue♫
♫The night has never been so dazzling♫
♫A white island♫
♫Blooms in the vast sea♫
♫I wish I could pick it♫
♫And give it to you♫
♫And she will remember you and me♫
Ran.
When I fell asleep at Matuman,
was it you?
So it wasn't a dream.
At that moment,
I smelled you.
But I was too tired
to wake up.
I could only snuggle up to you
as a response.
Zan.
You did respond to me.
It wasn't in your dream.
Otherwise,
maybe I wouldn't have...
I wouldn't have tried so hard to find you.
Luckily, I responded to you.
Zan.
Actually,
I'm a nice person.
Back then,
I was a bit weird because I was ill.
But I'm actually very nice.
I mean it.
I know.
Don't worry.
It's okay to be ill.
I don't mind.
Actually, there are many things I can't get over either.
Just like you.
Then,
tell me about them when you want to.
We have plenty of time ahead of us.
Okay.
Zan.
I want to tell you
a story about a tree and a bird.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Once upon a time,
there was a little bird.
It got injured
and fell from the sky.
A big tree caught it
and protected it from the wind and rain.
After the bird recovered,
it built a home in the tree,
sang for the tree every day,
and told the tree stories outside.
Then winter came.
The bird had to go to the south.
Before it left, it told the tree,
"I'll come back to you next spring."
But when the bird came back,
the tree
had been cut down.
Only a stump was left.
Then what happened?
The bird asked the grass nearby,
"Where is my tree?"
The grass answered,
"Your tree was cut down by a lumber mill.
You may find it in the lumber mill."
♫When the moonlight♫
The bird flew to the lumber mill
♫Glows on you♫
and saw tall piles of logs.
♫Each step is singing in the light♫
♫The song of snowing the white♫
But none of them were its tree.
♫Moonlight♫
So it asked a log,
"Have you seen my tree?"
♫Touch your face♫
♫All the shine of a thousand spotlights♫
The log said,
"Your tree has been sent to the match factory."
♫All the feelings♫
♫I can't deny♫
Then the bird flew to the match factory.
The production line was full of boxes of matches.
♫As you're moving close to me♫
It asked the matches,
♫My heart will never believe♫
"Have you seen my tree?"
The matches answered, "Your tree has been made into matches
and sold to a store."
The bird then flew to the store.
It was bought?
The last box of matches was sold a few days ago.
The bird was too tired.
It couldn't fly anymore.
On a stormy night,
its wings got all wet.
When it was about to fall into the mud,
it saw light from a cabin in the forest.
It flew in and fell on the table.
There was a lit candle and an empty matchbox
on the table.
The flame of the candle warmed the bird.
It finally woke up.
The bird asked the candle,
"Have you seen my tree?"
The candle said,
"Yes.
The last match
♫Cause you're so beautiful♫
that lit me to keep you warm
was your tree."
♫This love will never change♫
♫Halo on your side♫
It's a good story.
♫You are so beautiful♫
What's good about it?
I felt sad when I read it as a young girl.
♫Like angel from the stars♫
♫Over in the sky, tonight♫
But after thinking about it,
I think it might not be a love story.
The tree
might embody some kind of faith or belief.
The bird never gave up pursuing it.
Despite all the hardships in the process,
there would still be a warm ending.
You're trying to comfort me.
Zan.
Just go your way.
Everything will be fine.
Okay.
But I still think it's a love story.
Ran.
I don't want you to get too tired flying
or look for too long.
But if you can't fly anymore,
I promise to be the match that warms you.
Sasin.
Sasin!
It's getting dark.
Push me to the bar next to the hospital.
You want to drink in this condition?
I'm just going to the bar.
I don't plan to drink.
Why go to the bar if you're not drinking?
I have a date with Dr. Pei.
Usually, it's fine
to just cancel it.
But when I met her on the front lines this time…
I said something women hate to hear.
I need to make it up to her tonight.
Besides,
I bought a three-month
membership to Vinyl.
It'd be a waste not to go.
That's your business.
Why do you always like to sabotage
the relationship between Dr. Pei and me?
Is it because you don't have love in your life,
so you're worried that once I find true love,
there won't be anyone to take care of you?
-If that's the case…
-Shut up, Benjamin.
When have I ever sabotaged
your relationship with Dr. Pei?
You're doing it right now by not pushing me
to Vinyl.
Climb onto it.
I'll push you there now.
My leg is injured.
Why did you sit down?
This is not a place you should be.
You think I want to be here watching you?
If you could walk,
I wouldn't want to stay a minute longer.
Dr. Pei will push me back later.
You don't need to wait for me at the hospital.
Go back to camp and get some sleep…
He has a really bad temper these days.