[The White Olive Tree]
[Episode 33]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.]
Today,
I finally understand what domestic harmony means.
Instructor Li,
hurry up and get Ms. Song out of here.
If you stay any longer,
I'm going to be very angry.
Okay.
I'll take Ran for a meal first.
If you still have things to do later,
I'll bring Ran back.
No need.
I don't want to be a bad guy.
Song Ran, let's get in touch tomorrow.
Okay.
Shen Bei,
help me tell Jose
to put my luggage and bag
in the hotel.
I'm staying at the same hotel as last time.
Okay, got it.
Let's go.
Are you tired?
Why didn't you come earlier?
I was worried my girlfriend would get jealous.
I'm not that petty.
Besides,
Shen Bei doesn't like you anymore.
It doesn't matter.
As long as you like me.
Before I came to Eastern Country,
I went to Li Zan.
I asked him why he chose you
and how you outshine me.
He said...
-a landmine stepped on by accident.
-A landmine stepped on by accident,
an old elevator,
an apple,
a comb,
and a dance together in the moonlight.
It seems all these are the reason,
yet it seems none of them is.
I can't really explain why.
Maybe it's a matter of fate
or a feeling of heart-pounding excitement.
What do you want to eat?
Barbecue.
Just as I guessed.
Let's go.
Here.
Wait a second.
Let's celebrate first.
Celebrate what?
Celebrate that I've figured out your secret.
♫When the moonlight♫
♫Glows on you♫
My secret?
♫A soft glowing ring♫
♫You're dancing in the grace♫
Zan,
when...
♫Moonlight, touch your face♫
when exactly did you
fall in love with me?
♫Weave their dreams away♫
♫Let the stars fall in space♫
Since that landmine?
That comb?
♫As you're moving close to me♫
That old elevator?
♫My heart will never believe♫
Or that apple?
♫Cause you're so beautiful♫
♫This love will never change♫
You must be thirsty.
I'm going to buy you a bottle of water.
♫Halo on your side♫
Wait for me.
♫You are so beautiful♫
Hurry back!
♫Like angel from the stars♫
♫Over in the sky, tonight♫
You came to the north too?
A journalist
indeed goes wherever is dangerous
or where death occurs.
Madam,
if you want it,
I can give it to you.
We're also journalists.
Where does your patronizing tone come from?
Catching a hot spot
and become famous, isn't that what we're all after?
It seems that we're different,
not only in courage,
but also in consciousness.
I know you.
The Chinese journalist
who won a prize with Candy, right?
You're the one who benefited most
from the country's disaster.
Who are you to criticize me?
You are called a vulture on the web, aren't you?
We're the same.
Please don't include me in your category.
I'm different from you.
You, a journalist, who profits from the suffering of others,
have tarnished the reputation of our entire profession.
You are the true vulture.
Let me tell you,
I've won the Boshi Prize,
something you'll never achieve,
no matter how much suffering you witness.
Is there any problem?
She's my girlfriend.
Even in this country,
I won't allow anyone to bully her.
So you'd better be a gentleman,
and don't get yourself into trouble.
Don't be angry.
You shouldn't be angry.
Zan,
you acted... like a ruffian just now.
I really don't know if you're praising me
or mocking me.
Sir, we are ready to order.
We don't have anything you want.
Get out of here!
You rude people!
Get out!
What?
Are you crazy?
Damn it!
What a nutcase!
Shit!
I'm sorry.
Only for you.
You're so welcome.
Zan.
Are we really not going to pay?
You don't want to pay for your meal?
I think you're like a ruffian.
I'm not.
I'm worried if we pay,
the boss might be unhappy.
Then we can secretly put the money
under the plate.
Smart guy.
Come on,
eat.
You know those journalists?
I met them in Uglai,
when we
bumped into each other in the stairwell.
You treated me harshly that time.
This thing is dangerous.
It's not something you should play with.
So he gave you the knife.
He insisted on giving it to me.
I didn't...
Anyway, you threw it away in the end.
I should have treated him
more harshly just now.
As long as you don't treat me harshly.
That day...
I treated you harshly?
Okay, I'll be more careful next time.
I won't treat you harshly anymore.
Okay.
I have a demining mission early tomorrow morning.
Do you want to come and watch?
Sure.
I'll go help at the orphanage in the morning.
I'll go to you in the afternoon.
Send me the address.
Sasin?
That's Sasin.
Where's Zan?
Why are you running around?
Straying into a minefield is extremely dangerous.
I'm not running around.
I'm outside the warning line, right?
Besides,
even if I accidentally step on a landmine,
my boyfriend would come to save me.
Correct.
How did you know I'm here?
You came out for me?
I'm not that capable.
The demining work is already over.
They're cleaning up now.
I came out to get some fresh air.
Zan.
You must be very tired.
A little.
The demining work requires intense concentration.
Maybe I've been tense for too long.
It's okay.
I'm out here resting, right?
Come and sit.
Zan,
do you want to lie down and rest for a while?
This is fine.
How's it going at the orphanage?
It's going very well.
Almost done.
I really admire Shen Bei.
Rebuilding an orphanage in Eastern Country
shows she's perseverant
and very dedicated.
She's indeed changed a lot.
Last night, Shen Bei told me
if the present version of her
were to compete with me,
you might not choose me.
She was wrong.
I would still choose you.
Aren't you going to ask me why?
Any reason is fine,
as long as that's the answer.
Hey!
There's a dungeon here!
Let's go take a look.
What's going on?
We found a dungeon here.
But it seems all of them escaped.
Sasin is cleaning it up with the others right now.
Dungeon?
I want to go in and take some photos.
Be careful.
Sasin.
Zan.
Song.
Why did you come down here?
What's wrong?
This family
was taken here by insurgents.
The guards
knew we were on a demining mission nearby,
so they ran away first.
They activated the bomb before leaving.
But now it's too late to call
bomb disposers here.
I was just about to go find you
and see if there's anything you could do.
Zan.
I know you're scared,
but please calm down
for the sake of your children.
Try to soothe them,
and don't let them cry
or make big moves.
That would be a great help.
Okay.
We will remove those awful things
bound on your bodies.
Defeating these bastards' plan
is the best way to fight back.
Sorry, sir.
What do you need us to do?
We will try our best.
You don't need to apologize.
You're all being brave enough.
The bomb's setup
makes me unable
to save any of them first.
But fortunately, there's only one detonator.
Once the detonator is removed,
they can be saved.
But it's still not safe here.
Sasin.
You get them out of the dungeon first.
Ran,
wait for me outside.
Trust me. It won't take long.
Zan,
I'll go get you a protective suit.
No need for that.
There's not enough time.
You get them out of the dungeon first.
Your presence here will distract me.
Zan.
I'll wait for you outside.
Trust me, Ran.
They are too noisy around.
I let them out.
That's more secure.
Song.
Let's go.
You go first.
Sir,
are you okay?
Please, save us!
Trust me, please.
We'll... save you.
Please... trust me.
Trust me.
What happened, sir?
Are you okay?
Sir,
please help us!
Let me help you.
Help us! Help us!
Trust me, please.
I can help you.
Let me save you.
Zan,
what's wrong?
Is the bomb too complicated?
Sorry.
Zan,
-you did your best.
-Get lost!
Let me save them.
Sasin,
go.
You alone can't get the two of us out.
You! You almost got us killed!
You almost killed us!
Zan,
everything will be alright.
Everything will be alright.
Zan.
Sir, are you okay?
Please.
Please save us.
Zan.
♫A fire burning deep inside♫
You can save me,
♫Can you hear it?♫
just like the first time.
♫In this desert of silence♫
You can save me.
♫Ready to fly, yeah♫
♫I'm breaking all the rules♫
♫I'm tearing down the walls♫
♫An explosion of sound♫
♫As your voices drop and call♫
♫I'm going wild♫
♫And their energy is high♫
♫Wrack it to the beat♫
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫Igniting me on fire♫
♫Now we're unstoppable♫
♫On fire, on fire♫
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫And now we take it higher♫
♫This is our revolution, yeah♫
♫On fire, on fire♫
♫I'm breaking all the rules♫
♫I'm tearing down the walls♫
♫An explosion of sound♫
♫As your voices drop and call♫
♫I'm going wild♫
♫And their energy is high♫
♫Wrack it to the beat♫
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫Igniting me on fire♫
♫Now we're unstoppable♫
We're saved.
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫And now we take it higher♫
♫This is our revolution, yeah♫
Zan.
♫You set me on fire♫
Zan!
♫Searing desire♫
♫Fueled by the burning hot blood♫
♫Shout it out like a euphoria choir♫
♫On fire, on fire♫
Zan.
♫I got a feeling burning♫
♫Superhuman going straight to my brain♫
♫I've got regrets♫
♫I admit it♫
♫But I'm willing to change♫
♫I'm burning brighter than the sun♫
♫No I can't be contained♫
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫Igniting me on fire♫
♫Now we're unstoppable♫
♫On fire, on fire♫
♫Reaching for the sky♫
♫And now we take it higher♫
♫This is our revolution, yeah♫
Ran.
Now I want to tell you
what's been weighing on my mind.
Do you still want to hear it?
Yes.
On September 26,
the woman I originally wanted
to save
was actually
a suicidal insurgent.
This is a trait of someone who has practiced
pulling triggers for a long time.
I saw the walls of the nearby room were thick,
and it could minimize the explosion damage,
so I wanted to push her into that room.
But when I rushed towards her,
Jiang Lin knocked me down
and held her, rolling to the other side.
Then,
the bomb went off.
Just when I thought
Jiang Lin sacrificed himself
in order to save me,
the door of the room
I had planned to push the insurgent into
was blasted open.
Someone was...
in that room?
A family of four
was huddling together,
just like the family we saw today.
The shock and fear in their eyes
were just like those of the family today.
They just
stared at me,
like they knew
it was me
who almost got them killed.
And I
was the executioner.
It was my incompetence,
recklessness,
and self-righteousness
that ultimately cost
Jiang Lin's life,
so that that family didn't die.
Just like when I pressed the shutter
to take the photo of Candy,
I thought I was capturing the children's smiling faces,
but actually,
I was capturing
the last moment of their lives.
And I...
was the photographer who just stood there
and did nothing.
You're not like that.
Neither are you.
In situations like that,
what we could do was limited.
You know this better than anyone.
Blaming ourselves
or hating ourselves like enemies
is another kind of harm caused by war.
That is what I learned
from Candy.
Zan,
if we don't focus
on what we can do and what we
can change in a disaster,
who would have the perseverance to carry on?
I'm sorry, Ran.
I've let this barrier
exist between us for too long.
I'm sorry, Ran.
Zan.
Zan!
That family is waiting to thank you.
They won't leave.
Okay.
Ran, let's go over there.
Zan.
Bu.
We've arrived?
Zan.
Sleep in the hotel where I stay tonight, okay?
The hotel is more comfortable than the campsite.
I want you to get a good night's sleep.
Okay.
I'm so sleepy.
Ran.
We should never break up.
We won't.
What happened last time doesn't count.
We've never been apart.
No matter what happens,
whether we get moody,
or have a quarrel,
or give each other the silent treatment,
we can't break up.
We won't.
We'll never be apart again.
You...
Why can't you just
stay in your own tent?
Why did you come out?
I came to check on Zan.
It was too dangerous during the day.
I'm a bit worried,
so I came to see
if he's okay.
Zan has Song
to take care of him.
It's not your concern.
But how are you?
You encountered an unexpected situation today.
Are you okay?
Of course I'm...
I should have gone with you.
Forget it.
You didn't see what Zan was like today.
It was terrifying.
If you were there,
with your temper,
I'm afraid you two might fight first.
Is that so?
If we were to fight,
who would you help?
You.
You wish.
Your leg is injured.
Can't you behave yourself?
Be serious.
I have something to ask you.
Go ahead.
When Rina...
just passed away,
was my behavior also terrifying?
Not really.
You didn't scare others.
You scared me.
But it was okay.
So was it terrifying or not?
Of course.
I don't know how terrifying Zan's behavior was today,
but your behavior was no less terrifying than his.
If I hadn't tried
my best to keep an eye on you,
who knows what trouble you might have caused.
You're ungrateful,
and you even act like you want to eat me every day.
It's hard to be a good person.
I'm sorry.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
Did I say anything?
I'm going to bed.
Stop right there!
What did you just say?
Say it again!
I'm talking to you!
Who is making noise this late?
Captain!
What? Are you that delicate?
You can't even handle a little noise?
How are you going to manage on the battlefield?
W-What do you mean?
I don't understand.
Go back to sleep,
and don't come out again!
Yes, sir!
Jiang Yu did well in the midterm exam.
He took all the postcards you sent
to the school this time.
I think he'll compromise soon.
Thank you, Ms. Fu.
I hope when I return to China,
he'll have forgiven me.
No need to wait until you come back.
He's already stopped blaming you.
The essay topic for the midterm exam was
My Family.
I guess
he wrote about you.