[The White Olive Tree]
[Episode 7]
[This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance to reality is purely coincidental.]
Li Zan.
What's the situation over there?
Reporter Song and I are on the No. 7 Highway.
What about you?
The battle is over.
We've wiped them out.
Let's meet up at the garrison
outside Happo.
I happen to be going to Happo for interviews too.
Okay.
Zan.
Is our beauty reporter alright?
Yes.
Is she hurt?
No.
Was she scared?
Why do you ask so many questions?
Can't I care about her?
No.
What's wrong?
Why are you blushing?
Were you scared?
No.
It's too hot here.
It's hotter than an in Uglai.
Also, I ran so much just now.
I was too nervous.
The might have rushed up my face.
Why are you here?
Jiang Lin and his team
received a mission
to head to Happo
so I followed them.
I'm sorry I didn't have time to tell you.
There was no signal on my phone.
But when I passing the checkpoint,
I heard that you were on your way there too.
How did you know I came to this town?
Fortunately, you drew a circle on the map.
Otherwise...
Otherwise, I would be a corpse now.
That's not funny at all.
What about you?
Why were you there?
I applied to do interviews
at Happo.
I thought I was being smart by taking a shortcut.
Actually, I went to the barracks to look for you today.
But you weren't there.
I asked them to send you a message.
At that time,
we should have left already the barracks.
We were going to the warehouse outside the city to get equipment.
So we left early.
I guess I'm not the only one who stood someone up.
What?
Nothing.
What's wrong?
I think there's a small wound on your neck.
I don't think so.
There's one. Stop the car. Let me have a look.
Stop the car. Hey!
You're bleeding.
I'm fine.
Don't touch it with your hands.
Your hands are dirty.
It must be from a glass shard that flew
♫Have you ever found someone♫
when the window was shot by a bullet.
♫Who sees right through your smile♫
♫Your eyes♫
♫You're sick from the miles♫
♫Tires are low♫
I have erythromycin.
♫But in his heart♫
♫There's a place to go♫
♫He will be the light and the darkness♫
♫In your highs and lows♫
♫And say, Te Amo♫
Isn't erythromycin for treating eyes?
♫Still we don't know love♫
♫But I feel strong♫
That's the eye ointment you're referring to.
♫When I'm with you♫
Either way, it is an antibiotic that can kill bacteria.
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel strong♫
♫When I'm with you♫
Does it hurt?
No.
♫Have you ever felt so close♫
♫To touch a dream you can't define♫
♫Have you ever felt this way?♫
Done.
♫Are we♫
♫Lost in time again♫
Be careful.
♫Would you take the lead♫
Make sure the collar doesn't touch the medication.
♫When it starts?♫
Okay.
♫And say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know love♫
Why are you laughing?
♫But I feel strong when I'm with you♫
Nothing.
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know love♫
I just suddenly realized
that you're quite naggy.
♫When I'm with you♫
I didn't realize this previously.
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
There are still many of my
shortcomings that you don't know.
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel loved♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Te Amo♫
Mom.
My baby.
They're coming!
They got food! Come on, get up!
Reporter Song.
We need food.
Hurry up.
Give me some food.
Wait a minute.
I have more in my car. I'll go get it.
Here.
Sorry.
That can't be it.
I'll go look for food again.
Why is there none left?
There has to be some.
Reporter Song.
This can't be.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Reporter Song.
It's not your fault.
Let's share. Give me some for mine.
These people from Eastern Country
have gone through a lot of hardships.
Even at the brink of death,
they can still maintain order,
manners,
and the kindness in their hearts.
This is their dignity.
What we should give them
is not just water and bread,
but also respect.
From the bottom of our hearts.
Song Ran.
Look.
What is that?
That's...
A white olive tree.
I know what you want.
It will help you.
If you can plant it,
the white olive tree
makes your wishes come true.
That's a white olive tree.
This is a mirage.
A mirage?
Can I make a wish to it?
You can make a wish to any thing the nature gives us.
♫In this desert♫
♫Let every wish fly with strength♫
♫Fly to every corner of the world♫
♫Let love take root freely♫
♫Sprout and grow♫
-I wish for world peace.
♫Can I make a wish?♫
♫That there's no sadness under every ray of sunshine♫
♫That every tear reflects the lighthouse♫
♫In this world♫
♫Let every wish fly freely♫
♫Listen to the sound of peace♫
♫Sing gently♫
♫Filled with love and hope♫
♫When a mirage♫
♫Disappear quietly♫
♫The olive tree heard it♫
♫The wish we made♫
We can stay here to watch this for a little longer.
Sure.
Now that I think about it,
it's fascinating.
A few years ago,
I couldn't have imagined myself
driving and walking
on the tattered path
of a turbulent country.
While running for my life,
I'd be sitting here watchign the mirage.
You didn't think
you would become a reporter?
No.
You know
I don't like to deal with people.
I thought
I would work in a history museum.
But now,
I think it's good to be a reporter too.
I can record many things.
Maybe one day
I would record history
without myself knowing.
I don't think
you have to wait for that one day.
Every day in this world
for anyone
is a part of history.
You...
Me...
Same goes for everyone here.
Even if it's not written in black and white,
this land will remember it.
What about you?
Why did you volunteer?
There's no special reason.
If I have to say one,
it may have something to do with a childhood experience of mine.
I was naughty when I was a kid.
One time, I accidentally fell into a dried well.
The well was dark.
I was very scared.
I kept crying.
I felt like I was crying for a century.
My throat was hoarse.
But it probably wasn't that long.
Anyway, when I thought
I was going to die in that well,
a passerby heard my cry
and saved me.
I still remember those big hands
holding me now.
They were warm
and reliable.
I think
that's the feeling of hope.
Maybe I became a volunteer
because I want to spread that feeling.
Don't be afraid.
I won't leave you.
It's new.
Not dirty.
♫Have you ever found someone♫
Reporter Song.
♫Who sees right through your smile♫
♫Your eyes♫
It's not your fault.
♫You're sick from the miles♫
♫Tires are low♫
♫But in his heart♫
Zan.
♫There's a place to go♫
You've long become someone like this.
♫He will be the light and the darkness♫
♫In your highs and lows♫
Warm
and reliable.
♫And say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know love♫
♫But I feel strong♫
♫When I'm with you♫
♫Just say, Te Amo♫
♫Still we don't know how♫
♫But I feel loved♫
♫When I'm with you♫
Captain Jiang.
Please answer if you hear me.
Copy that.
Zan.
Where are you?
We met a groupof
homeless villages
on our way just now.
That delayed us a little.
We are still on the No. 7 Highway now.
We can reach the barracks in about an hour and a half.
Villagers?
Please be more specific.
There are about 30 to 40 of them.
Majority of them are elderly, women, and children.
Most of them have malnutrition.
Zan telling Jiang Lin these...
Reporter Song and I...
-Is to...
-Distributed all the food we had
to them.
Unfortunately, we didn't have many on us
and it wasn't of big help.
Can Jiang Lin...
help?
Tell me their exact location.
We met these villagers
on the No. 7 Highway
about 150 KM
southeast of Happo.
There is an abandoned village.
It should be their temporary shelter.
Got it.
Jiang Lin will find a way to help those villagers.
Look.
The wish we just made
is starting to come true.
How nice.
Are you sleepy?
When people relax after being nervous,
they tend to get sleepy.
There's still some distance from the barracks.
Get some sleep.
Isn't it the same for you?
I won't sleep.
I'll talk to you
as you drive.
No need.
Look!
A white olive tree.
It's real this time.
Check.
Kid!
Who said that you could play here?
This is the barracks.
No!
Run! Run!
How did you come inside?
Hey, kid!
Don't go away, stay there!
Let me down!
There's a hole.
Come.
Go.
It's hard to be a good person.
I have to do manual labor too.
Hey, soldier.
Could you do me a favor?
That's my luck.
Only time I try to be nice.
Pei Xiaonan?
Dr. Pei.
You seem to be a blessing for me today.
It's you.
This is for you.
Let's officially get to know each other.
My name is Benjamin.
Where did you steal the flowers?
Don't talk nonsense.
I saved a life in exchange for this.
Whether you stole
or exchanged for it,
we can't waste such beautiful flowers.
Since
you've accepted the flowers,
will you go on a date with me?
Sure.
Help me move these things in.
Then you can ask me to go on a date.
I'll go discuss the takeover with the doctor here.
Thank you,
soldier.
Sasin.
You can come in!
What's going on?
Why do you look unhappy
when you see me flirting with girls?
You like Dr. Pei too?
She doesn't suit you.
You're too young.
Do you think everyone
has nothing better to do like you?
I'm in Happo to do interviews.
I don't have time to listen to your nonsense.
Stop there.
They sent a little boy
like you to interview in Happo?
There's no one better in your TV station?
Don't you know it's dangerous here?
Am I going to be your babysitter again?
You're flirting with girls
while on a mission.
That's more dangerous.
He's so small-sized
but so full of anger.
In order to get a beauty,
let's do my best.
We are here.
Instructor Li.
Reporter Song.
Dr. Pei?
Dr. Pei.
What a coincidence.
You're here too?
Yes.
I heard you had an accident on the way here.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Thankfully Instructor Li arrived on time.
Instructor Li.
You're injured.
Do you want me to take a look?
It's all right.
It's just a scratch.
Besides,
I've applied some erythromycin ointment to it.
Erythromycin ointment?
I heard that
it's an antibiotic that can kill bacteria anyway.
Is that right, Dr. Pei?
Reporter Song.
Sorry.
I have an interview scheduled.
I have to go.
Bye.
Here.
Thank you.
Instructor Li.
How did you save
Reporter Song?
Tell me about it.
It's nothin.
I just brought Reporter Song to the barracks.
It was Captain Jiang
and Benjamin who saved her.
You're here?
Do you need help?
No.
Don't ruin my date.
Dr. Pei.
Don't break your promise.
Of course I won't/
There are still many things left.
Hurry up.
I won't disturb you then.
Instructor Li.
Wait for me.
Come on!
That's it.
Today's drink is worth it.
It's thrilling, exciting, and romantic.
Thank god.
What are you talking about?
Thank god, nothing happened between you two.
Otherwise, I won’t have a chance anymore.
Instructor Li is handsome
and righteous.
He's good at martial arts too.
He's my type.
You're not bad either.
You survived a great disaster.
It's worth celebrating.
Celebrate!
There's no more?
There is.
That's really it.
I have another bottle.
Wait for me.
I'll get it.
Let's finish it today.
Survived a great disaster...
That should be followed
with a blessing then.
Why are you so slow?
You took so long to get the wine.
Come and watch cartoons with me.
But don't tell others
I like watching cartoons.
People will laugh at me for being childish.
That'd ruin my reputation.
Hurry up–
Why were you eavesdropping?
Sorry.
I was just passing by.
I didn't mean to hear that
you like to watch cartoons.
But...
I don't think it's childish to like cartoons.
I think it's cute.