Senior,
you still
have a choice now.
[Once I repair the manuscript,]
[will I uncover]
[the truth about what happened back then?]
[Why did Great-Grandparents]
[end up parting ways?]
[I'll stop Yamazaki Hideo from returning to Japan.]
[You stay in the puppet government]
[and fulfill your mission.]
Jin'an,
be careful.
I'll wait for you.
Chi Hui,
if one of us has to sacrifice,
let it be me.
So Great-Grandma
deliberately stabbed Great-Grandpa
to take his place on the mission.
Shexian,
Jin'an has obtained Yamazaki's route back to Japan.
[I have a plan]
[to keep her safe.]
Shexuan.
Chi Hui.
Jin'an.
I failed to save Mr. Wu.
It's all my fault.
The situation is urgent.
The Japanese are coming.
You should go now.
Don't let them find you.
Go.
But what about you?
What will happen to you?
Don't worry about me.
Go.
The further, the better.
Don't worry about me.
Go.
Chi Hui,
we are not meant to be together in this life.
Let's meet in the next life.
Where are you?
Rongzhou.
Museum.
Have you ever seen Jiang Xun and Shen Shutu
paint together before?
I want to take this with me.
k
Okay.
Why do you ask?
It's none of your business.
Check if the sketchbook
is in the studio.
What's up?
Shutu,
I wish we could always be like this.
Of course we can.
Shutu, let's go to Sweden together.
Why do you say that?
I...
I'm just a little tired.
It doesn't matter.
If you're tired, just take a good rest.
Then we'll consider what to do next.
Okay?
Okay.
How's it going?
Shen Shutu said
the cryptographic key is in the museum in Rongzhou.
But I'm not sure if it's his conspiracy.
You only have 12 hours to hesitate.
If you can't help us get Jiaotu No.1,
you will lose your value.
You can't run away.
No matter where you go,
we can find you.
There are national security people in the museum.
Shen Shutu's amnesia is fake.
If you don't fear death,
the album is in the studio.
Go get it yourself.
[Ke Yu'ang,]
[we're in the same boat.]
[If you keep dragging your feet,]
[we'll both die.]
[What do you want me to do?]
[Abduct Jiang Xun when they're unprepared.]
[I'll be]
[at the dock to meet you.]
[You want to turn the tables?]
[Fine,]
[but I have a condition.]
Don't hurt Jiang Xun.
After the job's done,
I'll take her away.
Dinner's ready.
Come on.
I made you something tasty.
Shutu,
I've made up my mind.
I'm going back to Rongzhou with you
to get engaged.
Right now.
Are you sure
I'm the one you want to marry?
I'm sure.
I feel
we are destined to be together.
[Ke Yu'ang,]
[I will arrive in Rongzhou this afternoon.]
[Find out where the comic book is placed.]
Jiang Xun is avoiding me.
The comic book is in the office.
Go get it yourself.
Ke Yu'ang,
you know who you are.
We hope you can redeem yourself.
[In the drama,]
[Ke Yu'ang]
[is an agent of a foreign espionage and intelligence agency.]
[He participated in espionage activities,]
[which is a serious criminal offense.]
[He should be severely punished according to the law.]
[But under Jiang Xun's guidance,]
he realized
the shameless nature of the foreign espionage and intelligence agency.
He suddenly woke up
and stopped just in time.
He assisted in foiling the enemy's plot.
In the end, he redeemed himself.
According to Article 68
of the Criminal Law of the People's Republic of China,
if a criminal makes significant contributions after committing a crime,
the punishment can be reduced or exempted.