How did you ambush in the museum?
Xue Li went missing.
It was Jiang Xun who found him dead in the corridor.
Even the museum curator didn't know about the corridor.
How did she know?
Obviously, she's not telling the truth.
I suspect she's in cahoots with the spy.
They're working together to put on this act.
A thief crying 'stop thief'.
Where is Jiang Xun?
The doctor said she's fine.
and went home.
That's all?
That's all.
Feng,
I trust her.
Don't be emotional.
You need to use facts to reason.
The fact is she was with me at that time.
When Xue Li got into trouble,
I was with her.
I even took a picture of her at that time.
The time on the photo can prove this.
I heard that you confessed your love to her.
What do you mean by that?
Look.
There are obvious puncture marks
on Xue Li's neck.
There are signs of a fight at the scene.
It's obvious that she was killed
to silence her after the deal failed.
The museum was closed that day.
There weren't many staff who could get in.
The ones who are familiar with the museum
and have access to it are even fewer.
Who do you think is the most suspicious?
The curator manager,
Ke Yu'ang.
Right, Shen.
According to Wei Chuan,
when you entered the alley,
Ke Yu'ang had already left the museum.
So it was set up before he left.
Here's the situation.
Jiaotu No.1 is missing,
and Xue Li is dead.
We need to search the entire museum.
Jiang Xun is the first witness.
She's the most suspicious.
Keep an eye on her.
She just came to me.
I'll keep an eye on her.
You and Wei Chuan keep an eye on them.
Okay.
Next is Ke Yu'ang
and other staff.
You must remember
to investigate carefully.
Don't miss any detail.
Got it?
Roger that.
Work.
Coming.
Hello, auntie.
Shen Yu.
Yes.
You rushed off yesterday
after dropping Xun home.
I didn't even get to talk to you.
How's your dad?
He's doing well.
How about you?
I'm fine.
How's work treating you?
It's going smoothly.
I brought you a gift.
Have you eaten yet?
I'm not hungry.
It's okay, ma'am.
Is Jiang Xun in the room?
Yes,
he's in the room,
reading.
Reading.
He really loves studying.
I scared you.
Are you feeling better?
Not really.
I'm a bit scared.
I'm a bit scared too.
What? Trying to comfort me?
Who can handle
finding a body in a dark passage?
My heart
is still racing.
Shen Shutu,
I didn't kill anyone.
It's just a dream.
Jiang Xun,
I believe you.
I want you
to trust me.
I've been wearing
this jade pendant since I was a child.
It has become
a part of me.
It means a lot to you.
I can't take it.
It originally belonged to your ancestor.
So it should be returned to you.
And I'm very relieved that
you value cultural relics.
You will cherish it.
You gave me the pendant
to show your trust.
I should be honest with you.
Indeed,
I've been hiding something from you.
Can you
come to the museum tomorrow?
Okay.
I won't bother you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Come here often, Shen.
Okay.
Take care.
Hello, senior.
I'm at home.
Okay.
My senior called.
Who are you?
Hello, I'm Jiang Xun's senior.
I'm here to see her.
You're looking for Xunxun?
Come in.
Xunxun, your senior is here to see you.
Xunxun, sorry for scaring you yesterday.
I brought you some snacks.
Thank you, senior.
Yesterday,
how did you find that corridor?
Who is that person inside?
I stumbled upon it by accident.
It was pitch dark inside.
I didn't see clearly.
That corridor was really, really long.
I ran for a long time and still couldn't get out.
It was too scary.
It's okay.
You should rest well today.
Master, Ke Yu'ang is out.
I see him.
I'll go around from the left.
Keep a safe distance.
Master is going to see his wife.
What does it have to do with Ke Yu'ang?
He obviously wants to compete with you.
He has a deep hostility towards me now.
Not just because of Jiang Xun.
Maybe he has sensed
that we are watching him.
The Cultural Relics Group
will be wrapping up soon and heading back to Hong Kong.
You, keep an eye on him.
If he's taken the Jiaotu No.1,
how would he get it out?
Ke Yu'ang's team handles cultural relics exhibitions.
If
they want to smuggle the chip out,
they'd likely use the same methods for relics.
So I suspect
they would mix the chip
with the artifacts
and smuggle it out of the country.
What should we do now?
Let Feifei keep an eye on Ke Yu'ang.
We'll check out the museum.
If it comes to a search and seizure,
we'll request a joint operation with customs
to conduct a secondary inspection
on the artifacts.
But this process is very tedious
and requires a complete evidence chain.
I'll organize it, Master.
If we catch Ke Yu'ang,
remember to give me a long vacation.
Alright, your vacation is approved.
The current approach is fine,
but I always feel
something is still off.
I know what's wrong.
My future mother-in-law is in the Cultural Relics Group,
with Ke Yu'ang in the relics team,
suspected of being an accomplice.
But you keep defending her
in front of Feng.
You're also wondering
how she knew about that corridor.
What are you talking about?
She's very sincere to me now,
even invited me to a frank talk tomorrow.
Don't talk nonsense.
Fine.
Article 28 of the Law on Guarding State Secrets
stipulates that
any organization or individual
shall not illegally obtain or hold
state secret carriers.
Without the approval of the relevant authorities,
No state secret carriers abroad.
In this case, the cultural relics exhibition process is proper,
and customs clearance procedures are complete.
Foreign spies may take this opportunity
to hide the illegally obtained Jiaotu No.1
within legally transported cultural relics
and smuggle it out of the country,
getting through customs.
Be vigilant against those who attempt to smuggle in secret.