70,000.
100,000.
100,000, good.
This gentleman, 100,000.
200,000.
200,000 once.
200,000 twice.
Congratulations to Young Master Shen
for obtaining this Jordan-worn jersey.
Thank you, Young Master Shen.
Okay, next up is the next auction item.
The next auction item is
a villa in the 3D metaverse.
Is there any boss who wants to have
their own villa in the 3D metaverse?
The starting bid is 350,000.
Come and try our newly arrived cigars.
350,000.
Okay, 350,000.
350,000 once.
Playboy.
400,000 yuan.
This lady, 400,000 yuan.
Any higher bids?
500,000 yuan.
500,000 yuan, this lady, 500,000 yuan.
Any higher bids?
Okay, 500,000 yuan first.
It smells good.
500,000 twice.
500,000 three times.
Okay, congratulations to this lady.
Xue Li, is there any movement?
He went into the office and never came out.
No one went in.
The fourth auction item
is this beautiful jade.
It's an ancient jade with a slight blemish and subtle staining.
Master
Slight blemish with subtle staining
The code name appears.
I'll keep an eye on the auction.
Whoever bought that piece of jade
is the suspect.
Come on, everyone can take a look, bosses.
Beautiful jade.
Come on, bosses.
Come.
Come, boss, take a look.
Beautiful jade with slight flaws.
60,000.
Okay, 60,000 from this gentleman.
Any higher bids?
Take a closer look.
Miss, these inclusions are rare.
Isn't 60,000 for a fine Da Kai Men piece a good deal?
I'm not looking for a flawless stone,
but a jade that tells a story.
Naturally stained jades are the most lively.
The more you polish,
the more interesting it becomes.
You're an expert.
70,000.
This lady offers 70,000.
Any higher bids?
80,000.
Alright, this lady offers 80,000.
Any higher bids?
One hundred thousand.
Okay, any more bids?
One hundred thousand once.
Got it.
One hundred thousand twice.
One hundred and fifty thousand.
Okay, one hundred and fifty thousand.
This lady has bid up to one hundred and fifty thousand.
Ladies and gentlemen,
are there any further bids?
150,000 once.
150,000 twice.
150,000 three times.
Congratulations to this lady for winning this beautiful jade.
Bring her up.
Next is our last auction item.
It's a classic model of Patek Philippe watch.
Miss,
congratulations on winning this beautiful jade.
Please come with me to inspect and pay for the goods.
This watch
is one of only five
remaining in existence.
Please take a look.
Miss Jiang.
Mr. Shen.
Shouldn't Miss Jiang be
restoring artifacts at the studio?
A client stood me up,
so I came out to buy some trinkets.
You're a busy man.
How do you find time to hang out?
It's my family business.
I'm just doing some field research.
Our hobbies are quite a coincidence.
Did you just
buy a flawed piece of jade?
Let's talk later.
You've got dust on your shoe.
You're so thoughtful.
Thanks.
I'll go pay now.
See you later.
Master,
isn't she my future mother-in-law?
She's the suspect dealing with Xue Li.
Bring it over here.
Turn on the eavesdropping.
Roger that.
Have a seat.
Your shoe is dusty.
Those vulgar people
don't know jade.
You have a good taste.
You got the price I expected.
This is for you.
Thank you.
Master, we have the evidence.
Do you apply for arrest?
Wait a minute.
Xue Li's superior hasn't appeared yet.
Boss Xue is a jade industry big shot.
Please help me check
this jade pendant
and the broken jade I just bought,
are they a match?
Follow the rules.
Didn't we agree
I'd pay an extra consulting fee?
During the Republic of China period,
many noble families in Rongzhou
liked using dragon and phoenix pendants as love tokens.
May I ask,
where did you get this?
Let's be frank.
I won't ask you where the stone is from,
and you won't ask me where the pendant is from.
A Rongzhou Republic of China era craftsman carved it.
But the raw material of the jade
comes from Hokkaido.
The unique magnetic field of volcanoes and the sea
makes it have unique properties.
And this raw material is extremely rare.
If I'm not mistaken,
The pendant is from the stone's yin side.
So there's also a Yang side.
The material you've photographed
is the best choice
for this repair.
But even with the material,
you might not be able to repair it well.
Because the best tools for jade repair
are all in the museum.
Which museum?
Rongzhou Folk Museum.
It was built on the site of Jiang Mansion.
It's here.
It has a history with me.
You have a history with Jiang Family?
Thank you,
Boss Xue.
Miss,
the jade is in the shade.
It's unlucky.
Mom,
Is this jade from our family?
I've never seen it before.
What is this?
Let me see.
How did it break?
This is
the token of love your great-grandfather
gave to your great-grandmother.
Tomorrow is your big day to meet Young Master Shen.
Don't bring bad luck on yourself.
How can a love token be bad luck?
Just because Great-Grandparents divorced,
doesn't mean it's unlucky.
How about
you wear this necklace
for your blind date tomorrow?
You always do this.
Why can't we contact
our relatives in Jiang Family after we return to Rongzhou?
It's a family rule set by your grandfather.
We can't have any contact with relatives,
especially not mentioning
that ominous woman.
Unfortunately,
I specialize in dealing with the ominous.
Master,
Jiang Xun has appeared.
Should we proceed with the capture?
I didn't expect it to be her.
[Human genetic resources]
[are a crucial strategic resource,]
They hide important information
about human evolution,
racial characteristics,
the secret of longevity, and the root cause of diseases.
Like a double-edged sword,
if used properly,
they can bring breakthroughs in disease treatment.
If abused,
they could become a lethal weapon
that harms national security.
Just as the gene bank in the play
holds an important strategic position,
guarding our genetic resources
is guarding national security.
It's everyone's responsibility
to maintain the security of our genetic resources.
It is prohibited to illegally provide human genetic resources
to foreign individuals, organizations, and institutions.