♫ Almost paradise ♫
♫ Warmer even than the sun ♫
♫ The way you look at me ♫
♫ Feels like I have the whole world ♫
[Boys over Flowers]
Who do you think you are?
Who are you to say those things?
Who asked you to make that kind of request?
No, not a request... to beg?
Don't you have any pride?
It's not because I don't have any pride.
It's because you're in such agony.
Because you looked like you would die of sadness.
What's it to you?
It has nothing to do with you!
Get lost.
♫ I'm not too smart  ♫
♫ I only know you ♫
♫ I only have eyes for you ♫
♫ Tears keep coming down my face ♫
♫ I'm happy even if I have to see you walk away ♫
♫ Even if you don't know how I feel yet ♫
♫ Even if you walk right by me ♫
♫ Some days when I miss you so much ♫
♫ When it's too hard for me to bear ♫
♫ The words "I love you" keep circling in my mouth ♫
♫ I'm alone again crying for you ♫
There's a dark cloud over your head.
What's the use of the self-luminosity of the F4?
She's such a black hole...
Goo Joon Pyo.
Can I ask you something?
If I said no, would you keep it to yourself?
Just act like you usually do. This doesn't suit you.
When you like someone...
because you like them too much, considering their feelings,
holding back your own feelings without expressing them.
Is that good?
What's good about that?!
What's with that?
That's the same thing as ignoring them. What is there as to "liking" them?
If the world were to fall to pieces tomorrow, then you'd probably die of regret.
Goo Joon Pyo.
What?
You might not be completely stupid.
You're just figuring that out now?
It's better to regret after you act, instead of regretting after having done nothing. That's my philosophy.
It looks as if Ji Hoo isn't going to show up after all.
Everyone, be well. Stay out of trouble.
Have a good trip. I'll come to visit.
Not just to visit but to hold an exhibition.
Take care of your health.
Oh, the kindness disease.
If you're too kind, the wound lasts just as long, Mr. Casanova.
Must you do that lawyer or NGO crap, Noona?
I just don't understand you women.
Do you know it's been ten years since you've sincerely called me Noona?
It seems you've become cool, so I decided to acknowledge you as my noona.
Are you complaining?
Jan Di,
please remember my request.
Please take care of yourself.
Take care, everyone.
I'm leaving.
Go. Take care of yourself.
Stubborn bastard. How could he not come to see her off?
What did I tell you?
Say what you want about me, but Ji Hoo is the real cruel one among us.
He looks so serene, but once he turns his back, he's the scariest.
Isn't talking behind my back a little too harsh?
You—
- What is this?
- When did you get here?
Three hours ago.
What?
Then you got here before us
What are you going to do now?
Are you just going to stand around here?
Go after her!
If she can't stay here, you should go to her.
Didn't you say you loved her?
Hiding behind posts, is that how you show your love?
How can you say you love her behaving like that?
I'm on the next flight. All my luggage has already been checked in.
Yoon Ji Hoo!
Rascal. He has a knack for surprising people.
When did you get the guts to do something like this?
Thanks to
this little lady.
- What?
Rascal.
- Get over here!
- Cute rascal!
Cute!
I'm proud of you.
Thank you.
You were the one who made me realize that I have to face reality and be honest with myself.
You were the one who taught me that we need the courage to keep going at times.
I'm glad to have met a girl like you.
I'm leaving now.
Geum Jan Di...
What? What do you want?
Listen to what I have to say.
I'm only going to say this once, so listen very carefully.
Geum Jan Di... You and I...
(should start dating).
What did he say?
You're not getting in?
Saturday at 4 o'clock. In front of the Nam San Tower.
If you're late by even one minute, you're dead.
We need to get it, no matter what.
Come quickly!
Hurry!
As soon as it opens at 4 o'clock, run for this.
And if you find something that you think will fit, just stuff it in the cart.
Wouldn't it be better if we just go together?
Mom needs to go to the cabbage blowout sale.
If the clothes shop were the civil war, this cabbage shop is
- World War II.
- Right.
You know, last time the lady standing next to me got her teeth knocked out.
Really?
Three months' worth of our shop profits is in our hands. Got it?
- Do your best!
Oh, it's snowing.
We should get going. Dad must be waiting.
Saturday. 4 o'clock. In front of the Namsan Tower.
It can't be!
No, no, no way!
Why are you mumbling like a crazy girl?
- Mom.
- Yes?
One wouldn't wait outside for four hours in this snow on a promise that wasn't really made, would he?
No way, unless that person is crazy. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Hang on.
That crazy jerk.
Mom, hold this.
What?
Mom, go home first!
Yah, Jan Di! Where are you going?
I need to go somewhere!
Ahh, that girl!
♫ Come to me now ♫
♫ In the excitement that I myself don't know of ♫
♫ Today too I, like this I ♫
♫ Am pacing in front of you ♫
♫ Does love have to be said to know? ♫
♫ I've been wanting it so badly ♫
♫ One person with whom I'll promise forever ♫
♫ That's you, dear ♫
What time is it?
Shouldn't I be the one asking that?
Don't you know what time it is right now? Are you that jobless?
Didn't I tell you that you'd be dead if you were late?
Did I ever promise that I would come?
You came.
Well, that is...
I came to check if you were here.
What would've happened if I hadn't come?!
You showed up anyway, didn't you?
Also, whose fault is it that I'm in this state?
So stop getting angry like you have any reason to be.
Ah, it's cold.
Get up.
I'll buy you a nice hot drink.
Or you'll get sick.
Get up.
Hurry!
Do you want to drink tea or just go?
[Entrance]
Here.
This is 30,000 won coffee (about $30).
What a thug. Are you trying to scam me?
I don't drink this kind of stuff anyway.
Just give it a try first.
This coffee is the best.
Should I tell you why it costs $30?
Follow me.
How is it? I was right, wasn't I?
It's the same as drinking coffee in the sky-lounge.
Tsk tsk. You'd never be able to run a business, not even a small store.
What?!
36,300 won (about $36.30).
You need to include tax and service tips.
Wow, so even the rich know how to calculate those kinds of things!
I just pretend not to know.
There's no way you could become rich without knowing those things, could you?
Wow, there are so many stars.
Hey, those aren't stars. They're satellites, you stupid girl!
Geez, are you stupid? Are there that many satellites?
Are you kiding? They're satellites.
I don't want to hear that from you!
- What, "stupid girl"?
- What, you stupid boy!
You're dumb!
You're dumber!
Hello?
You're at the restaurant?
Okay. Stay right there. I'll be right over.
- What happened?
- What's that?
Why is so dark?
Mister! Mister! There are people still in here!!
Hey! Hey! The door is locked!
Really? Is it really locked?
Mister!!
Why are you shaking like a weirdo? Hold on, I'll just call someone.
I have to get going! My mom is going to kill me!
Where's my cellphone?
- You don't have your phone?
- How about you?
I never had a cell phone.
How can you not even have a cell phone?
It's your fault we're trapped in like this!
How is it my fault?!
Who was the one that waited like an idiot for hours outside?
I got excited, that's why.
I've never gotten to wait for someone like that.
What?!
What are we going to do?
Mister!
What are you doing?
Shall we wait in there?
Hey... Move over.
No.
Sorry.
What?
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
You've finally realized it.
But why did a rich boy like you do something like this?
Waiting in the snow for 4 hours... isn't your family worried?
Butler, bodyguard, drivers... What are they doing right now?
- I sent them home.
- Why?
I wanted to try to do things the way someone like you, a commoner, would.
How hard that must be for you!
Hey, Jan Di baht (lawn grass).
What?!
Can I tell you the truth?
Truthfully... what?
What is it?
Hey. You can say it from right there.
I uh... now...
What?
You bastard! You pervert!
Do you really want to do this in this kind of situation?
Shoot, stay away from me!
Get off of me!
You...
If you don't get off of me by the count of three, I don't care what happens next.
One...
Two...
Two and a half...
Three!
This jerk...
Why is he so warm?
Hey... Goo Joon Pyo, are you okay?
I'm sick...
You're sick?
Right, you must be sick to be so feverish.
It's cold.
Cold...
♫ Only for you ♫
♫ For you, I love you only you ♫
♫ Filled with excitement ♫
♫ Softer than a coffee with good fragrance ♫
♫ I look at you with my breath ♫
What are you doing?
If you wrap your head with a shawl, then you'll get warmer.
♫ You feel this too, right? ♫
♫ Whatever your heart is telling you is love ♫
♫ Hear it now ♫
♫ See it now, more beautiful than flowers ♫
♫ Innocent feelings ♫
♫ Look at me ♫
♫ Hold my hand tightly ♫
♫ Happy feeling, right? ♫
♫ Flattering destiny, right? ♫
♫ I smile at the fragrance of love ♫
♫ Happy feeling, right? ♫
♫ Flattering destiny, right? ♫
♫ Let's get drunk on the fragrance of love ♫
♫ Forever ♫
♫ Do you know this? ♫
♫ You feel this too, right? ♫
♫ Whatever your heart is telling you is love ♫
♫ Hear it now ♫
♫ See it now, more beautiful than flowers ♫
♫ Innocent feelings ♫
♫ I love only you ♫
Get in, I'll take you home.
No thanks.
Anyway, I have to think about what I have to say to my mom.
I'll just walk and take the bus.
I could help you out. Help you think of an excuse.
[Jan Di Dry Cleaners]
I'm sorry, mom and dad.
I'll never do this again. I have sinned greatly!
One, Two, Three!
Who sinned greatly? It seems you saved a pretty important person last night, huh?
The successor to the Shinhwa Group!
Then, Shinhwa group is what kind of group?
The number one group in Korea, of course!
Then, having saved the successor of Shinhwa Group is as good as saving the Korean economy.
How would it be a sin? It's not even enough for you to get a decoration!
That's why these came instead of decorations!
It looks good, huh?
Where did all this come from? And how did you know that?
What do you mean, "How did you know"?
Young Master... wait...
Young Master, Young Master... What was the Young Master's name?
Joon Pyo! Goo Joon Pyo!
Goo Joon Pyo.
I know, I know.
Young Master Joon Pyo sent all this.
He told us that you were with him and told us not to scold you,
and all this is to repay your kindness.
Maybe because he is a young master of the supreme Chaebol Group,
how polite he was!
He said next time he will visit us in person to see how we're doing.
It's so touching. My tears keep welling up.
Mom, don't cry.
Honey, how could you cry on such a good day?
Tell them that since you spent the night with me,
I'll take responsibility for you.
[Hey! Joon Pyo Sunbae is going out with Geum Jan Di!!!]
[Geum Jan Di's boyfriend is Joon Pyo Sunbae!!!!]
[Geum Jan Di ascends to become Joon Pyo's girlfriend.]
[Commoner, Geum Jan Di's upward social mobility. Ascends to be Goo Joon Pyo's girlfriend.]
[Geum Jan Di becomes Goo Joon Pyo's girlfriend.]
I'm so jealous!
- Oh, isn't she Jan Di?
- Jan Di i coming.
Jan Di! Hi!
You're so pretty today!
Geum Jan Di, hi!
Jan Di, hi! Nice to meet you!
- Jan Di! Jan Di!
- Good morning!
Oh! Oh! Good morning!
- Jan Di! Jan Di!
- Don't you want to go shopping together?
Geum Jan Di. Come to my birthday party next week.
Here, have this.
Thank you. Thank you.
Bye!
Geum Jan Di.
Evil.
This must be some kind of plot.
Joon Pyo, is this really true?
It's not! It's not!
It's not what you guys think! This is...
Yeah.
It's true.
No! No!
It must be true!
♪ A long time ago, on a golden
lawn (Geum Jan Di) hill where Magi ♪
♪ The place where they used to play together ♪
♪ The sound of watermills is heard ♪
Are you okay?
♪ My lovely Magi ♪
Yeah.
Just a little lightheaded.
I'm fine now.
That's a relief.
Nobody knows that I came here, so it's okay.
Jan Di...
F4 Goo Joon Pyo, is it true?
It can't be...
No way. It's just a rumor.
But it seems that he really likes you.
No, no way.
He's just joking around and making fun of me.
How could Goo Joon Pyo...?!
Don't you know how he is? Especially with the incident last time...
How could the so called "Great Goo Joon Pyo" like me?
That does seem impossible, right?
R... right.
Are you going somewhere?
Yeah, I think I'm all better now.
Jan Di, wanna go somewhere and have some fun?
Wait one second...
[Shinhwa Kindergarten]
Shinhwa Kindergarten?
No!
Why are you touching other people's stuff?!
What is it that you are so curious about?!
Sorry.
It's because I wrote some weird things in it.
It's a bit embarrassing.
I'm sorry for getting mad.
No, I'm sorry for touching it without your permission.
Come with me to change.
Joon Pyo, are you serious?
- About what?
- I'm talking about Geum Jan Di.
If it's not real, what else would it be?
For us, it isn't easy to call many things "real."
Our freedom only extends as far as dating.
You haven't forgotten that it's your parents who make the final decision, right?
Was it just talk when you guys said you were men?
What is this? You mean to say that it was all just a show?
What is your meaning of a real man then?
A man who is responsible from the beginning to the end.
Till the end?
That's right! Till the end.
♪ Let's go, baby ♪
♪ I'm your man ♪
♪ Keeping down the phone again ♪
♪ Burying the flowers in my heart ♪
♪ The letter I wrote all night long gets ruined in the rain ♪
♪ Even if I open your window again, and call your name ♪
♪ Only your bell sound with no reply rings in my ears ♪
♪ It's a shame. I miss everything ♪
♪ It's a shame. Everything hurts me. ♪
♪ It's a shame, I don't know any woman other than you ♪
♪ I am your man. Darling. ♪
♪ Today too, I... ♪
♪ Today too, I think of you only ♪
♪ I am your man. Darling. ♪
♪ Today too ♪
♪ You don't leave ♪
♪ I'm your man, I roam the streets more ♪
♪ I don't even know where I am ♪
♪ If perhaps you show up again ♪
♪ I'm your man, even if it's in your dreams ♪
♪ Will you greet me with a smile? ♪
- Don't you want to dance?
- What?
Don't you want to dance?
This is my first time at a place like this. I'm just going to watch.
Okay. Then wait here for a minute.
♪ I think more after you leave, I know now that you are gone ♪
♪ Is this probably love? My darling who left ♪
♪ It's a shame I miss everything ♪
♪ It's a shame. Everything hurts me. ♪
♪ It's a shame, I think about you who left me ♪
♪ I am your man. Darling. ♪
♪ Today too, I... ♪
♪ Today too, I think of you only ♪
♪ I am your man. Darling. ♪
♪ Today too, I... ♪
♪ Today too, I think of you only ♪
♪ I'm your man, I roam the streets more ♪
♪ I don't even know where I am ♪
♪ If perhaps you show up again ♪
♪ I'm your man, even if it's in your dreams ♪
♪ Will you greet me with a smile?
I don't know if you will find me again ♪
I'm so sorry.
What? You think it's unfair?
If you're ugly, you should at least know how to dance.
With a figure like that, there's no way you'd fit into a place like this.
Try not to make an ass of yourself!
Ga Eul, you're not going anywhere right?
Where would I go?
Don't go! You can't leave me alone, okay?
Geez... what in the world is he rambling about?
Hurry, go and make porridge or something!
Welcome—
Isn't Geum Jan Di here?
Yes, she is.
I don't see her though.
It's her day off.
You... you're Jan Di's friend?
-Nod-
Since when?
Since kindergarten.
Then you're her best friend, right?
Let's go!
To where?
See! I was right.
I'm telling you this out of consideration for Geum Jan Di, because I don't want her to get hurt.
So, please advise her well while by her side.
You know, how things like that are important to women.
What kind of advice?
Things like "Don't even look at a tree that you can't climb"?
Or "You are a toy to pass the time of Young Masters of the Chaebol. So when you are thrown away, just accept it."
Hey, calm down.
I get scared when a cute girl like you gets upset.
Ga Eul, you are Jan Di's friend, huh?
You may think that every girl would fall for your sweet talk with that cute face of yours,
but I'm not like that.
I'm going to pretend that I didn't hear you.
The more I think about it, it's infuriating!
The one who started this was not Jan Di, but him.
Our Jan Di never even dreamed of climbing up that kind of tree. Got that?
Yo, Yi Jung... What are you up to now?
What would I do?
When a girl dashes out of here in anger, there could be only one reason.
Whatever.
She's not my type. I don't care for that genre.
What genre is that?
The kind that whether it's a comedy or romance, always ends up as a tear-jerking soap opera.
I really don't like tacky things like that.
♪ Why not me? I am your person, right? ♪
♪ I'm your man, I roam the streets more ♪
♪ Today too, I... ♪
♪ Today too, I think of you only ♪
♪ I am your man. Darling. ♪
♪ Today too, you... ♪
You didn't have to go after that so desperately.
♪ I'm your man, I roam the streets more ♪
♪ I don't even know where I am ♪
♪ If perhaps you show up again ♪
♪ I'm your man, even if it's in your dreams ♪
But still, it's an important thing. I shouldn't knock it over. I'm sorry.
It's not really that big a deal.
It's suffocating in here, isn't it?
Thank you.
Let's go down after one more song.
Ah, I'm thirsty.
[Thanks for last night]
No.
No! This can't be!!!
Why did you make a fuss asking us to come in a school uniform like this?
Isn't it nice to feel like students from time to time?
Your hair... does it even get straight?
It's already been two hours. You're not going to do this every morning, are you?
I'm sure we can come up with a solution soon.
- Straighten it out properly.
- Okay.
What don't you like about me?
What do you hate?
Your gross face, I hate the way you talk! Including your curly hair!
You're totally annoying!
It's also annoying that you all don't wear the uniforms.
That whole Red Card thing, bullying others is what I hate the most of all.
Let's go!!
No! No way!
No way... no, no! How could I not remember anything at all?
Calm down. Let's calm down, Geum Jan Di.
If something had happened, there's no way I'd feel perfectly fine like this.
Could there be? No!
Could there be?
Ah, I'm going crazy! Seriously!
What the heck are you guys doing? Let go of me! Let go of me when I ask you nicely!
Why? When did you get so cheeky?
My goodness... how rude of you.
This is why they say poor people are the scariest.
I knew that you were pretending to be innocent. But you've gone too far.
Ya! I don't understand a thing of what you're saying!
There's no reason for you to be treating me like this, okay?
Let go! Are you going to let go?
- Let go!
- Let's teach her a lesson!
What? Why? Let go!
Hey! Let's get you dead now!
Hurry!
Hey! Stop it.
Let go of me!
No reason for this?
You cheating on Joon Pyo sunbae, is the same as cheating on all of us.
Insulting F4, is the same as insulting all of us!
A dirty rag like you... Did you really think we'd let you
disgrace the Shinwha School like this?
You bitch!
[Commoner Geum Jan Di, the truth of her is?]
What are you guys doing?
Who the hell are you to bother her like that?
Joon Pyo sunbae, don't be fooled by her!
Please come to your senses once you see this!
No, Goo Joon Pyo. This isn't true!
They're wrong.
How and where did things go so wrong
that you are in a photo like this?
I don't know.
I think someone tricked me.
So this is who you are?
Is this the type of woman you are?
You were fooled, were you?
Are you really the type of woman who can be tricked so easily?
Goo Joon Pyo, it doesn't matter whether you believe me or not.
I don't know why I'm defending myself over something so ridiculous.
Anyway, this isn't the truth.
I really don't know anything about this.
I'll ask you just one thing.
The woman in the picture...
is it you, Geum Jan Di?
You said you don't care whether I believe you or not, right?
Yes, you're right.
Geum Jan Di,
from now on, I want nothing to do with you.
Hey, you rag!
Transfer!
Take off your uniform! Get lost!
Take it off, hurry!
♫ Although I ask it to stop, to stop wherever it is ♫
♫ My heart keeps going to you ♫
♫ You don't even listen, or give in ♫
♫ Why is my love like this? ♫
♫ Counting each memory, one by one ♫
♫ My heart can't rest for even a moment ♫
♫ It must be a tough burden to handle ♫
Hey, this isn't good. In his condition, it won't be strange at all if someone gets killed.
I haven't seen him act like this since Joon Hee noona got married.
Quick, let's go.
♫ Because I love you too much ♫
♫ Just this one thing, just your feelings ♫
♫ Can't you share it with me? ♫
Please let me off the hook once.
We have to find that guy first and foremost.
You said you met him in a nightclub, right?
I went to ask, but they said they don't know him.
When you first woke up in the morning, was there anything that stuck out in the bedroom?
Like a business card or personal belongings.
There was a memo written on the mirror.
It said, "Thank you for last night." in red lipstick.
Wait, lipstick?
Yeah.
Was it yours?
Uh... No.
Then it must belong to that guy!
There are three people.
Seriously... Stop rambling nonsense and go away.
Wait a minute! Could it be?
Look, these photos don't look like selfies.
There must've been another person in the room because someone else took the photos.
The owner of the lipstick?
What are you doing?
It looked like there was some dust here. But it won't rub off. Is it not dust?
Look at that!
Let's go.
Leave it to us. Thanks.
Uhhh... sure.
With looks like that... they're definitely from Andromeda.
I don't recognize it.
[₩1,000,000]
It's a bit complicated.
Complicated? I hear he's the head honcho here.
I guess, if we take away the head honcho that would be a big blow to you.
Thank you for understanding.
But...
if you don't hand over that guy, we might have to close down this place.
- How about that?
- What?
Within a fortnight?
We have to save our face as F4.
- We need to wrap this up in a week.
- What?
The building next door... it's yours, right?
We'll be able to start as soon as tomorrow.
Shall I practice? I need a bit of warming up.
What was that name?
♫ Although I ask it to stop, to stop wherever it is ♫
♫ My heart keeps going to you ♫
♫ You don't even listen, or give in ♫
♫ Why is my love like this? ♫
♫ Something must have happened to my heart ♫
♫ I must have become a fool blinded by love ♫
♫ Just one place, everyday one place ♫
♫ Can't you love me? ♫
Or... when it's lesser than 33...
f(x) is equal to or greater than 0.
When it is so, f(x) is greater than 0.
[Everyone is invited to the Tomato party for the commoner Geum Jan Di]
Thank you, Sir.
Going first?
Jan Di, Jan Di.
I...
have something important to take care of, so I'm going to go first, okay?
Jan Di!
Oh, nothing.
Later.
(one, two, three)
There's no need to be in such pain.
Why are you acting like this over a lowly commoner like her?
It doesn't make sense.
Please come to your senses! This isn't right.
How could Goo Joon Pyo be this way?
This is so unfair!
You...
Weren't you her friend?
If you're her friend, why would you say those things?
Because she stole you from me.
Don't go, please.
Take your hands off me.
Why Geum Jan Di and not me?
What is the reason that it has to be Jan Di?!
No, Goo Joon Pyo! This isn't true.
There's something wrong with this.
How and where did things go wrong that you are in a photo like this?
I don't know.
I think someone's trying to set me up.
Let's go!
This is it?
C'mon. Go for it!
Attack!!
♫ I know I shouldn't feel this way ♫
♫ A lie... If I said it was a lie ♫
♫ Will my heart come back to me? ♫
♫ Tears are falling ♫
♫ I can't look at you because I feel sorry ♫
♫ My heart aches ♫
♫ What should my first words be? I can't think ♫
- F4!
- What's that?
- Shinhwa Group's successor Goo Joon Pyo!
- What?
Ah, so noisy!
♫ You make me have bad feelings ♫
What are you doing?
Except for your uniform and shoes, everything that you used
has been replaced overnight.
As of today, I announce officially that 2nd year, B class' Geum Jan Di
is Goo Joon Pyo's girlfriend.
I object to that decision!
Ji Hoo!
Where is this again?
New Caledonia. It's an island where just our resort is there. It's Shinhwa Group's.
♫ It's a very bad feeling, it's a very bad feeling ♫
Lo-love?
♫ Say something and hold me back, please ♫
♫ Don't try to make me feel better ♫
♫ Be like before, ♫
♫ Affectionately, just look at me well ♫
♫ Warmly, if you say a word ♫
♫ I have no other wish ♫
♫ You keep making me ♫
♫ Have bad feelings ♫
♫ Isn't a good feeling for me ♫
♫ Forgetting you ♫
♫ It's a bad feeling, it's a bad feeling ♫
♫ Our love won't disappear forever ♫