♫ Almost paradise ♫
♫ Warmer even than the sun ♫
♫ The way you look at me ♫
♫ Feels like I have the whole world ♫
[Boys Over Flowers]
[Episode 14]
♫ O madre di bontade ♫
♫ O madre pia ♫
♫  madre pia  ♫
♫ Ascolta, dolce Maria ♫
♫ La voce del peccator ♫
♫ Il pianto  ♫
♫ Il pianto suo ti muova ♫
♫ Giungano a te ♫
♫  i suoi lamenti  ♫
♫ Sul mare luccica ♫
What's this noise?
♫ Placida è l'onda ♫
Wow, it sounds like she is going to be fired.
How could a tone deaf person like that...
That person...
♫  l'astro d'argento ♫
♫  Placida è l'onda ♫
♫ prospero è il vento. Venite all'agile ♫
Do you know her?
No way. She's not Korean is she?
What an embarrassment to our nation.
That's right, she's Korean.
She's really cool though.
How do you know her?
She saved my life.
What? Didn't we save your life?
♫ Santa Lucia ♫
Hello.
Welcome.
It's such a pleasure to finally meet you.
Hello.
You must be very happy with such a good son.
I was also very excited to meet Jae Kyung. It's unfortunate we won't be able to meet her today.
She's playing around by herself in Macau right now.
We already gave up because she really likes to do everything her way.
I've heard that she's extraordinary. I'm looking forward to seeing her more and more.
Please don't anticipate too much.
Madam, the preparations are ready.
Then, shall we go?
Shinhwa Group's long-cherished ambition for 2020 is
to build a 2nd Cotai resort district in Incheon, in Korea.
It will be the ultimate resort city in Asia, complete with extravagant hotels and additional facilities.
In order to complete this project we absolutely need the cooperation of JK,
which has achieved many successes in constructing new resorts in cities
such as Las Vegas, Macau and Dubai.
If we combine Shinhwa's infrastructure as Korea's No. 1 group and JK's knowledge and skills in the field,
this blue print will become a reality much faster and
it will create a new history for Korea.
Wow, I'm so hungry. Let's go get something to eat.
Okay! Jan Di, you can count on it.
There's a killer restaurant here.
Let's go!
Welcome.
What's wrong?
Don't worry buddies. As long as we mention Joon Pyo's name, it's automatically "okay".
Let's go somewhere else.
Why? Now that you feel like you're in Venice, you want some Italian food?
You're right. There's a killer Italian chef here too, right?
Come on, guys.
There are many seats...
[Connecting...]
[A photo has arrived. Do you want to check it out?
Connect.]
Let's have a toast.
For the cooperation between Shinhwa Group and JK Group.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Are you okay?
About what?
Coming here,
do you regret it?
When would I ever get the chance to come here again?
It was my dream to go on a vacation alone.
What's your plan?
I don't have anything planned.
I just wanted to see his face and say,
"How have you been? I've been well."
Just saying hello would be nice.
Isn't it strange?
What?
It feels like our relationship is something of the past.
If Joon Pyo is really pretending not to know me,
then I wonder if I've just been dreaming.
It's not a dream.
If it was all a dream, it wouldn't be so hard.
Huh?
After letting you leave, I realized
that I was unable to do anything all day.
When I came to my senses, I was on the plane.
So, it's not a dream.
Since right now,
you're right here in front of me.
Sleep well.
["J"]
Okay! That's enough.
Go. Stop!
Seriously, if you weren't the chief manager, I'd cut you instantly.
Keep it up.
At 10 a.m., there's an inspection at the construction site.
At 11 a.m., you'll have to take the jet to the Singapore office.
At 5 p.m., you have a private meeting with the mayor of Macau.
And...
And . . .
And what? Why did you stop in the middle of a sentence?
If you could make some time to meet your F4 friends...
If you could make some time to meet your F4 friends . . . There is no time.
They've been waiting since yesterday.
Do I have that much free time?
Should I just put aside my schedule for today and hang out with them?
I'll see them if that is alright. Is it?
No.
Sheesh! What kind of lawn is this?
(T/N: Jan Di's name means "lawn", so it's a play on words)
Nothing's going right.
[Master Yi Jung]
Yes? It's me.
What kind of mayor wants to meet at a place like this?
Did he used to be an athlete?
I'm sorry.
It's not something you should have to apologize for.
Hey yo! Have you been well?
Long time no see.
You guys came?
If we want to meet Shinhwa Group's heir, the busiest man in the world,
we have to come to you, otherwise we'd never be able to see you.
It's nice to see you.
Really?
Because it doesn't seem like you're all that glad.
What's wrong? We haven't seen each other in so long.
Geum Jan Di came with us too.
Actually, that's not quite right.
She came before us, to see you.
You haven't seen her, have you?
Why should I see her?
What?
That kid has nothing more to do with me.
So then, Goo Joon Pyo,
are you saying you purposely didn't contact Geum Jan Di?
Whether it was on purpose or not, I don't have time to think about things like that.
- Things like that?
- Are you serious, Joon Pyo?
We finally meet and all you guys want to talk about are childish things like that?
How can you still call yourself a man?
What do you mean?
You guys meet and break up with girls too.
So, what's wrong with me doing the same thing?
Am I not allowed to do so too?
Even if I meet and break up twenty times, I don't do it the way you did!
- Yi Jung, calm down!
- Let go!
You! What did you say when we tried to stop you in the past?
You said a real man is someone that's responsible from the beginning to the end.
You really believed that?
By chance, did you guys think that she and I would be together forever?
That jerk.
Whose fault is it that Geum Jan Di can't swim anymore?!
- Stand up!
- Yi Jung, calm down.
Does it look like I can calm down? Do you hear what this jerk is saying?
You!
Did you start that relationship thinking something like this wouldn't happen?
I warned you not to be so rash, you cowardly bastard!
What's with you guys?
- Did you guys quit being my friends so you could become a group of Jan Di's protectors?
- Goo Joon Pyo.
If you came here as my friends, then play and go.
But if you came to just to talk about Geum Jan Di, then leave immediately.
How is it that you've changed so much?
- 700,000.
- What?
In Shinhwa Corporation,
those families I have to take responsibility for,
are about 700,000.
Try having 700,000 families' lives resting on your shoulders.
And see if you don't change.
An invaluable challenge. An unimaginable reality.
Asia's Venice. Shinhwa stands for the legend.
[Shinhwa]
Is Joon Pyo alright?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
It's okay. Except for the fact that he's become strange.
Hey!
Geum Jan Di has to know too.
As you know, a lot of things have happened.
Stress is no joke too.
He says he won't see me?
You, how did you?
You knew about it?
You don't have to worry too much.
No matter what it is, I came to hear it from Goo Joon Pyo himself.
I have to face it.
You really are Geum Jan Di!
Wow, the night air is so nice.
- Do you remember?
- What?
What we used to do here when we were younger?
Here.
Rock, paper, scissors!
- Rock, paper, scissors!
- Nice!
Ji Hoo, you go that way. Jan Di you go that way, and I'll go this way!
Ten...Nine...Eight...
Seven. Six. Five.
Four. Three. Two.
ONE!
I'm coming to find you guys!
Awaiting you in Venice,
The city of Lovers.
As a friend, I have a favor to ask.
Say it.
Just meet with her once.
Why should I do that?
I told you, it's a favor for a friend.
And if I ask why you're asking that?
Because right now, that's all I can do.
I'm going.
♫ Although I ask it to stop, to stop wherever it is ♫
♫ My heart keeps going to you ♫
♫ You don't even listen, or give in ♫
♫ Why is my love like this? ♫
♫ Counting each memory one by one ♫
♫ My heart can't rest for even a moment ♫
♫ It will only become a burden that's too much to handle ♫
♫ Why can't I just throw it away? ♫
♫ Something must have happened to my heart ♫
♫ I must have become a fool blinded by love ♫
♫ Just one place, everyday one place ♫
♫ Looking at the sad light called you ♫
♫ Can't you love me? ♫
What's wrong?
I was just about to go to the airport.
I decided to just say farewell here.
Before I leave, I have one thing I need to say.
After today, I don't think I'll be able to say it again.
I think it's really fortunate I got to know you, Senior.
I'll come back soon.
Sunbae?
Sorry for waking you up.
What's wrong?
There's somewhere we need to go.
Right now, at this time?
I've heard of gymnastics at midnight, but a walk at the break of dawn?
We're here.
What?
From here, you have to go by yourself.
It should be there on that bridge.
The reason you came here.
Wait...
Hi. I came to see you.
Yeah. What brings you all the way here?
I was worried after hearing the news about your father.
Thanks.
So...
You came all this way for that?
I guess you're getting along well now.
What?
As you can see, I'm doing great.
And as you know, I'm very busy.
Now that you know, you can go.
No need to worry about how I'm doing.
What? Do you have anything more left to say?
Really, is this how you feel?
What did you expect?
Perhaps "I'm sorry",
"Forgive me,"
"I'll be back, so just wait for me".
Were you expecting those words?
Why are you being like this?
I've started to come to terms with reality.
I get it.
Now, I finally get it.
You pretending not to know me, not wanting to see me.
It was all real.
So what I am to you is... I am...
A stain I want to erase.
You're cruel, Goo JoonPyo.
Really cruel.
No.
I was always like this.
I was only pretending I wasn't.
I'm going. Take care.
Just worry about yourself.
Hey pretty girl, are you okay?
Excuse me...
You are my special lucky lady, because you are my first today.
Lucky lady?
Excuse me...
Song. Please sing a song for me.
No, No. It's my treat.
♫ Vergin, tutto amor ♫
♫ O madre di bontade ♫
♫ O madre pia, madre pia ♫
♫ Ascolta, dolce Maria ♫
♫ La voce  ♫
♫  del peccator ♫
♫ It's really hard, from a step back ♫
From today on, Geum Jan Di from Grade 11B Class
is officially my girlfriend.
♫ Because of my tears, because of my longing for you ♫
♫ You are fading ♫
Can you see it? My heart?
♫ Can I go back to before ♫
♫ when I didn't even know your name ♫
♫ A little longer ♫
♫ I'll just look at you ♫
♫ I see nothing but you ♫
♫ Just for today ♫
♫ I'll just look at you ♫
♫ Tomorrow, I'll forget you ♫
♫ I promise ♫
Let go!
Young master.
Please leave us alone for a while.
Are you satisfied?
Now that you've gotten your way, are you satisfied?
Well, it's not pleasant
that we still have to talk about such an insignificant girl.
She is not just any girl.
She's the first girl that I,
your own son!
ever loved in my entire life.
Yes, that's right.
Then what do you plan to do?
You want to abandon everything and run to her?
You want to abandon Shinhwa Group's employees and your future?
Fine.
Have you ever thought about your father?
Stop.
You may have no issue with throwing Shinhwa Group away in a blink,
but your father, someone who tried his best for this company until the very end,
do you plan on throwing him away, too?
Stop it.
What are you going to do about that Jan Di girl?
Should I make her not be able to live anywhere in Korea?
Shut up.
Didn't I tell you to stop?
Jan Di...
Don't mess with her.
If you break your promise,
I'll destroy everything.
Can this pretty lady buy an ice cream from me please?
I'm sorry, but I'm not very good at Chinese, so...
What did you just say?
Ugly girl over there, please buy some ice cream.
Do you really think you can sell anything like that?
But you would still buy it, wouldn't you?
How much is it?
Your day?
That's the fee for the ice cream. Give me your time today.
♫ Because I'm stupid ♫
♫ I know no one but you ♫
♫ But you are looking at someone else ♫
♫ You wouldn't know how I feel ♫
♫ I wouldn't be in your day ♫
♫ I wouldn't even be in your memory ♫
♫ I still keep looking at you only ♫
♫ My tears keep rolling ♫
♫ Your backside ♫
♫ Looking at that is also a happiness ♫
♫ If you still don't know how I feel ♫
♫ If I stop this and go too ♫
♫ On the days that I miss you too much ♫
♫ On the days that it's too hard to handle ♫
♫ "I love you" plays on my mouth ♫
♫ Alone again, crying for you ♫
♫ Alone again, missing for you ♫
♫ Baby, I love you, I'm waiting for you ♫
Jan Di must be doing well, right?
Don't worry. No news is good news.
As soon as she meets Joon Pyo, she'll be dying of happiness.
Kang San.
If your stomach hurts, hurry up and go to the bathroom. Don't hold it in.
Kang San, what's wrong? Kang San.
Kang San, where does it hurt?
- Kang San!
- What's wrong?
- Why is he like this?
- Oh gosh!
- This is strange.
- Kang San! Look here!
Put him on my back.
Kang San!
- She eats well, right?
- Yes.
- She's sleeping well?
Your blood pressure is good.
- Hye Na.
- Yes.
Should I give you candy?
Alright.
You're so pretty. Handshake.
See you later.
Yes.
Good bye. Thank you.
Doctor!
Is there anyone here?
- Doctor!
- Is there a doctor here?
- Please save my son!
Something's very wrong. Please look at him!
♫ I know I shouldn't feel this way ♫
♫ A lie... If I said it was a lie ♫
This is nice.
♫ Tears are falling ♫
♫ I can't look at you because I feel sorry ♫
♫ My heart aches ♫
♫ What should my first words be? ♫
♫ I can't think ♫
♫ You keep ♫
♫ making me have bad feelings ♫
♫ Forgetting you isn't a good feeling for me ♫
♫ It's a very bad feeling ♫
♫ It's a bad feeling, it's a bad feeling ♫
It's time. Let's go.
That's mine.
I selected this first!
I saw this first!
It'd be better if you'd let go now.
- I can't let go!
- I said let go!
Miss, I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry, but, can you just give in this once?
Wh-What did you say?
Do you know the size?
Size?
Hey, wear this for a second.
Hey! Hey! What the heck are you doing?!
Perfect fit.
- Now take them off.
- I don't want to.
You're not taking them off?
Come here, come here!
Who the heck is he? Is he crazy?
Are you okay?
How is it you're just getting here now?!
They had some business so they left first.
What are you going to do?
It's time that we went back too.
Let's go on tomorrow morning's plane.
What is that girl doing?
Are you talking about Geum Jan Di?
Yi Jung and Woo Bin have already left.
Ji Hoo and Geum Jan Di are leaving tomorrow morning.
It looks like she's finally learned her place.
Where is Joon Pyo?
He's been in the conference room all night.
It looks like he's found his place, too.
♫ I keep smelling a familiar fragrance in the air ♫
♫ The breeze that brushed off you ♫
♫ Is passing by me now ♫
♫ In my heart ♫
♫ Perhaps there's only the sunlight that shines you ♫
♫ Even pain and wounds are embraced ♫
♫ Love you, I think of you now ♫
♫ I close my eyes again ♫
♫ I love you, if I could fill your two eyes ♫
♫ I love you, if you show me your smile ♫
♫ Even the starlight there ♫
♫ I will bring everything and give it to you ♫
Goo Joon Pyo!
Can you hear me?
While you've been gone, I've been thinking of you every day.
How is it the only memories I can recall are of the times we fought?
But isn't it strange?
The only memories I have are of us being angry and fighting, but
when I think about you, I can only smile.
Goo Joon Pyo,
you are doing well right?
When are you coming back to fight with me again?
Joon Pyo! Let's go together.
Have you seen this plane before?
- Isn't it a beauty?
- Yes!
See this. This is where the propeller is.
Later, you'll need to fly this.
Take a seat here.
- This is the handle.
- Okay.
Aren't there a lot of buttons?
When you learn how to fly a plane, you must fly this one.
- Who are you?
- I'm Goo Joon Pyo.
- Joon Pyo is?
- Of course I am Dad's son!
What will you do when dad is not here?
I must take care of Mom, Sister and Shinhwa Group!
Goo Joon Pyo!
Can you promise me, man to man?
Yes, sir!
I promise!
Ji Hoo, Yoon Ji Hoo!
- Min!
- Ji Hoo! What brings you here? When did you come?
Um, I came a few days ago. It's been a really long time.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming to Macau?
I missed you so much.
How long are you staying?
- We're about to go.
- You can't!
You can't. I can't let you go like this.
Ji Hoo, let's go to my house!
I can't. I'm with company, so...
Who... It can't be.
She isn't Ji Hoo's girlfriend, is she?
What if she says yes, will you stay?
I'm J iHoo's friend. We went to the same school.
Oh, really? Nice to meet you.
I'm really sick, right now.
It's very serious.
So, grant me this one favor.
Let's go to my house. Just one day.
Uh? Eh? Well, Yeah , okay.
Let's go!
It's no big deal to leave one day later, right?
Oh right.
It's really been a long time, right?
Let's go!
Oh, it looks delicious.
I cook so well, eh?
You even know how to say things like that?
You speak Korean really well.
Ji Hoo is Korean.
Did you learn Korean because of Ji Hoo sunbae?
No!
This is only for Ji Hoo's use.
It looks delicious.
Let's enjoy our meal.
Ji Hoo, eat up.
(Eat!)
That girl isn't pretty.
She's short, and she doesn't have any bosom.
And she eats way too much.
What do you want to hear?
That girl... Ji Hoo, is she your girlfriend?
What do you think?
Ji Hoo, that girl, you like her.
What?
Whenever you look at her, you smile.
Like before.
Before?
Whenever you saw Seo Hyun. Like that.
Find out Geum JanDi's room number.
What?
She checked out?
I got it.
Young master. It's time for us to leave.
When did Ji Hoo leave?
He is still in Macau.
Is that so? Didn't he check out?
He went with Geum Jan Di to his friend's house.
Friend? Which friend?
Should I find out?
No. Forget it.
♫ Shout to the world, "I love you..." ♫
♫ "...be my woman" ♫
♫ You are blinding. Always you're my star ♫
♫ I'll protect you ♫
♫ I can always do waiting for you ♫
♫ Towards the end of a tiring day ♫
♫ Towards the end of my exhausting life ♫
♫ You are the only one who welcomes me ♫
♫ I start another day ♫
♫ I recall your pretty smile ♫
♫ I will be happier than anyone ♫
♫ If you are by my side ♫
♫ On the sky I promise you ♫
♫ I'll give you my everything ♫
♫ Shout to the world, "I love you..." ♫
♫ "...be my woman" ♫
♫ You are blinding. Always you're my star ♫
♫ I'll protect you ♫
♫ I can always be waiting for you ♫
♫ Why did you come only now? ♫
♫ Feels like I have the whole world ♫
♫ Thank you my angel ♫
♫ I love you just like the first time ♫
♫ On the sky I promise you ♫
♫ I want to have everything of yours ♫
♫ Shout to the world, "I love you..." ♫
♫ "...be my woman" ♫
♫ You are blinding. Always you're my star ♫
♫ I'll protect you ♫
♫ I can always do waiting for you ♫
♫ Let's make one promise ♫
♫ Let's swear on the sky ♫
♫ Till the day that the sun runs out of light ♫
♫ I love you. Oh my love ♫
♫ Bye bye never say good bye ♫
♫ I can't hold you like this ♫
♫ I need you, I can't say anything ♫
♫ I want you, even if I hope again and again ♫
You need to take this off.
♫ On the days that I miss you too much ♫
You little brat.
Call me.
♫ Alone again, crying for you ♫
♫ On the days that I think of you too much ♫
♫ On the days that my chest hurts and it's sad ♫
♫ "I miss you" plays on my mouth ♫
More! Just a little more!
Alright, let's end it!