=My Rich Little Brother=
=Episode 23=
Help.
Help!
Zhengzheng.
I'm back.
Never leave me again.
I will always be by your side,
protecting you.
Believe me,
okay?
It was all just a dream.
Zhengzheng,
this is the 360th day since you left.
I've been thinking about you
every single one of those days.
You will come back to me, right?
I always feel like
that day is coming.
Maybe
you are outside my door right now.
And I can see you as soon as I open it.
Yingying,
you should learn to adjust.
Don't make us worry about you all the time.
Let's go to work.
Zhengzheng
loves this milk brand. It's his favorite.
When I first met him,
he asked me to buy it for him,
which cost me half my salary back then.
I felt so bad.
Yingying,
you should learn to accept reality.
Zhengzheng has been gone
for too long without any news.
Maybe he has...
No way.
Zhengzheng will be fine.
He promised to protect me.
He never lies to me.
And I can always feel
that he is still out there.
Yingying.
Zhengzheng can't be here.
But you still have me.
I really feel bad
seeing you like this.
Mr. Wei,
I want to be by myself for a while.
Just leave it on the desk.
I'll take a call.
Hello, Mr. Wei.
I'm outside your building now.
Let's go to the company together.
Sure.
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
(Next episode)
Forgive me.
I will find out the truth soon
and get back to you.
♪We grow up wildly holding hands together♪
♪The shadows get stretched over time♪
♪We can't let go♪