=My Rich Little Brother=
=Episode 8=
This is our factory's car.
Hello.
Your grandpa is sick
and he asked me to call you back.
Hurry up.
Just come.
Alright.
Wait for me downstairs.
I'll pass my work
to someone else before coming down.
It's my bad. It's my bad.
I shocked you.
Huanxi,
I've told you many times
that we are not a good fit.
I don't see it that way.
I will return the money
to you as soon as possible.
Search the frequent locations of this car.
Find the area it stays for the longest time.
Got it.
Why are you drinking tea, Grandpa?
This is the towel to wipe feet!
Grandpa.
Grandpa, how are you?
Is it serious?
Before I leave this world,
I want you to have a family.
That way, I'll rest in peace
when I die.
What are you talking about, Grandpa?
Just rest well.
Grandpa,
rest assured.
You can count on me for this.
I'm getting the marriage certificate
with Yingying tomorrow.
Such good luck
will make your sickness
go away.
Grandpa.
Just rest and get better.
I don't like Huanxi.
I'm not marrying him.
Yingying.
Huanxi has been so nice to you
all these years.
Don't be ungrateful.
Who are you marrying,
if not him?
Marry me.
Who are you?
Xin Zhengzheng.
Nice to meet you, Grandpa.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Please.
Stealing my wife...
Zhengzheng,
what are you doing here?
I was worried about you,
so I followed you here.
Yingying,
you had a boyfriend all along?
No.
Zhengzheng, you shouldn't have said that.
I was helping you out.
Sister.
Are you sure you don't need me here with you?
Just go back.
I'll go back to work
after Grandpa gets better.
Just go.
Alright.
Whatever you want.
You head on in first, Sister.
I'll watch you go
to reassure myself.
Xin Zhengzheng.
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
(Next episode)
♪When I start to lose my confidence♪
♪Under the sunset♪
♪We grow up wildly holding hands together♪
♪The shadows stretch long over time♪
Yingying is mine.
♪We can't let go♪