=My Rich Little Brother=
=Episode 7=
Let's buy Baoman company.
You're usually
not interested in the business.
Where has this idea come from?
Hand all of these out.
(Baoman Biotechnology)
Mr. Xin.
Ahh!
We dare not do it again!
I personally
conducted an on-the-spot investigation
of this company.
It's not bad at all.
It has a lot of potential.
It's not a big deal.
Before Dad left the country,
he had intended to purchase
some internet biotech companies anyway.
And can I run it
after we purchase it?
Sure.
I'll talk to Dad.
Wait,
you're not falling
for some girl in that company,
are you?
Dad said it before leaving
that you should study hard
and not waste time on romance.
Rest assured, Brother.
I'm doing it
just for my studies.
Here.
Studies...
Nice.
Do another pose.
Here.
Make it pretty.
(Good Luck on Bao Bei'er's New Starring Role)
If we hit the headlines,
then you'll get big fat bonuses.
The second young master
of Xin Family is down the hall.
Hurry, let's go!
We're not done yet!
How can you leave!
I didn't expect
that the second young master
of Xin family would be cured.
We shouldn't have canceled your engagement.
You're not as popular anymore.
If you can get engaged
to Xin Zhengzheng again,
then overnight
you would become a sensation again.
Zhengzheng,
Yifan told me you are here.
I know you don't want to see me.
But
I've talked to my father
and he agreed to allow our engagement again.
Since you chose to cancel it,
I don't think there is any need to do that.
I didn't want to cancel it.
I was not following my heart, Zhengzheng.
I know that.
I don't blame you anymore.
Besides, from now on,
don't call me Zhengzheng, call me Mr. Xin.
I have things to do.
Be seeing you.
Zhengzheng,
just give me one more chance.
I really have things to do.
Zhengzheng.
Zhengzheng, don't go!
Xin Zhengzheng.
I won't give up!
Bro.
(The richest man in Liu Village, Liu Huanxi)
Are you waiting for your girlfriend?
Yeah.
What about you?
Waiting for my wife.
Yingying.
Zhengzheng.
What are you doing here?
Huanxi.
We're running late.
Come on, let's go.
My wife is so pretty, isn't she?
Wife?
♪I worry if you'd get nervous♪
(Next episode)
Grandpa.
Rest assured.
You can count on me for this.
I'm getting the marriage certificate
with Yingying tomorrow.
Who are you marrying, if not him?
Marry me.
♪We can't let go♪