[The Auditors]
Mr. Assistant Manager.
Hey. What brings you here?
Why did you do that?
What are you talking about?
Why did you…
post the picture?
Hey…
What do you mean by that suddenly?
You posted
Seo Jin's pictures.
I discovered the IP address that
left a comment on the anonymous bulletin.
[Moon Sang Ho]
The IP address indicates this neighborhood.
It's near our company
and there are many studios.
Many of the company's employees live here.
Several employees live
in the small apartment building where I live.
You've got the wrong person.
Then why did you come to my house on that day?
Seo Jin…
Sir…
Mr. Assistant Manager
why did you set her up?
That is because…
[The Auditors]
- Excuse me.
- Please wait a minute.
Hello.
[Application form]
I think communication skills
and the ability to gather information
are the most important.
Okay.
Hey.
What? Did you go to Daesung University?
- Yes, sir.
- We went to the same University.
It was a long time ago.
You remind me of my old days.
That was a hopeless experience.
I had high grades and great qualifications.
My educational background was
why I failed to get hired
so I wanted to prove it.
[2020 JU Construction
New employee recruitment]
[Submit]
[Your application form
has been submitted completely]
If I had failed again, I would've considered
the reason to be my insufficient ability.
But I passed.
This is Moon Sang Ho
who will work with us starting today.
I'll work hard.
I felt guilty about it.
So I worked harder than anyone.
This is what you've asked.
And I realized that...
Good job.
I'm a skilled worker.
- You did a good job.
- Thank you.
I just didn't have a chance to prove it.
Unfair employment?
I was afraid when I saw the post.
Based on the post, he's expected to be…
But, I was relieved by the fact that
the target was employees
hired in 2022.
That's why I tried hard
to find Han Soo's test results.
I've found it.
I cared about Han Soo because I thought
we were similar in many ways.
Isn't it too much
to examine four years of documents?
We must find the 2020's documents.
Yes, sir. I'll find it.
When I was included in the audit scope
I couldn't stand the anxiety.
Finding the fact that the diploma
was fabricated was a matter of time.
She may be complaining.
That was when I saw
Seo Jin and the Vice President.
I'll go first. See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
She and the Vice President were like a family.
But I couldn't come up with another plan.
I'm sorry for Seo Jin
but I thought the post would turn
people's attention to her
and change the audit object.
But…
We'll keep investigating unfair employment.
I found something suspicious
in the post about Mrs. Yoon Seo Jin.
As you kept investigating.
Hey, Isn't it this?
My mind was possessed by the thought
of stealing the documents.
The documents are gone.
You drive a car and take Mr. Shin
and Vice President to the company.
I'll follow you.
Hey. Thugs took…
the documents away.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
I must've been out of my mind.
Where's the document?
It's at my home.
I couldn't burn it.
I knew it would be an irreparable mistake
if I burned it.
Sir, I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
You've violated the personnel regulations.
- You'll get disciplinary action and dismissal.
- I see.
Seo Jin.
I don't even deserve
to ask for your forgiveness.
I'm very sorry.
I'm sorry.
Go get the documents.
Let's go.
I've found it.
Only Ms. Jeong's score was changed.
[Interview scorecards for new employees]
[Jeong Hye Young]
Excuse me.
You've violated the Act
on Procedure for Employment.
Let's have an interview.
What… You have no proof.
Do you want proof? Here you are.
[Report of audit]
Weren't you confident
you would find her corrupt?
There wasn't anything wrong
with her recruitment process.
Didn't you say there was a financial dealing?
You said that the Vice President bought
an apartment for her.
I've also investigated it.
Tell me in detail.
I used to live in poor residential conditions.
The house was worn out
and flooded once.
The Vice President saw it
and bought an apartment for us.
But I couldn't get it
so I wrote him an IOU.
I'm still paying back
the principal and interest.
I've checked the IOU out.
So, isn't there anything wrong?
No, there wasn't.
The result is shocking.
Right. I didn't expect it to be like this.
Assistant Manager Jeong Hye Young
and Moon Sang Ho were dismissed.
Yoon Seo Jin was doing nothing wrong.
I heard she got hired on her own.
Are Assistant Manager Jeong's father
and Director Seo friends?
I heard that her father is a big player
in Jongnam City.
He also has the power.
They must've known each other while
participating in a redevelopment business.
So, he hired thugs to steal the documents.
It's a bit scary.
Don't you know who is really scary?
It's Moon Sang Ho.
How dare he set the Vice President up?
I didn't know he was like that.
Anyway, your team did a nice job.
They made up for their mistake
although it didn't help that much.
I have no idea what's going on.
Don't you get it?
Mr. Shin pulled the rug
from under the president.
You've got an eye for the Audit Team leader.
He's excellent.
Don't pretend you don't care.
Come in.
Sir.
We have good news.
I already cleared Seo Jin of false rumors.
You're late to the party.
I have other good news.
We've won a contract for the construction
of the Cheongyang Sports Complex.
- Really?
- Yes.
I've got a call from Cheongyang City Hall.
So, I've written a press release like this.
Why don't you read this?
This is the headline.
It's like the Vice President is a hero
for winning the contract.
It's a new breakthrough for the company
which was damaged hard
by the J-BIMS leakage accident.
What do you think?
You've done a good job after a long time.
Thank you.
You have a good future ahead of you.
It won't take long for you
to take the chair of the presidency.
Yes.
What?
When was it?
I see.
Sir.
Did something happen?
[Moon Sang Ho]
Are you out of your mind?
Do you want to cause harm to others
until the end?
I'm finished.
I'm really finished.
Then, I'm finished.
You're not finished.
You can start again.
Start from the beginning.
If you really expiate your wrong
you can start from the beginning.
I believe you can do it.
Sir.
I'm very sorry.
This is Shin Cha Il.
Sir, we have a problem.
Did Ms. Jeong Hye Young try to kill herself?
Sir.
We also heard it from the personnel department.
They found her fell on the floor
after taking pills.
How is she?
She looked unconscious.
Where is she now?
They said they'd go to Nasun General Hospital.
[Nasun General Hospital]
You're here.
Has he recovered his consciousness?
Hey.
It's me.
Can you recognize me?
Still, he hasn't recovered
his consciousness perfectly.
His condition will be stabilized soon.
What a relief.
When he regains his consciousness
we can kick that one out of the company.
Who do you want to kick out?
What brings you here?
I should come. Aren't I a family member?
You've never visited before.
Why did you come today?
You wanted him to be dead.
Are you sad that
he's recovered his consciousness?
It's not a problem that a younger brother
comes to see his older brother.
You must've had happy days
because you were like a king at the company.
Hey.
I'm happy that he's returned to himself.
You can see that I'm smiling.
Laugh as much as you want
because the days you can laugh are numbered.
When my husband returns to the company
you'll be damned.
I knew that I wouldn't be welcomed.
But you always treat me as a stranger.
I see that he's okay. So, I'll go off.
Take care of yourself.
I'll wait for you at the company.
Isn't the Audit Team leader incompetent
enough not to kick him out?
When the knife becomes blunt
you should throw it.
There are plenty of knives you can use.
Wait a minute, please.
Hey.
I don't want to hear more nitpicking.
What's your purpose?
What do you mean?
If you were me, could you believe my word?
Right. We aren't close enough
to care for each other.
But I sometimes mistake us for a family.
I won't mistake our relationship again.
You must be impatient.
You must've thought you were ahead of me.
But Brother regained consciousness.
You're totally boggled
because you're alone.
Are you happy that you have your side again?
You must be happy with the thought
of stamping on me with your brother again.
Suit yourself.
But you'd better brace yourself.
Who are you?
We're JU's Audit Team.
We want to see
Assistant Manager Jeong Hye Young.
The Audit Team?
Is it you?
Are you the one
who made our daughter like that?
I'm Shin Cha Il, the Audit Team leader.
- Is she all right?
- All right?
She tried to kill herself at the company.
I heard you bullied
and forced her into making a false confession.
It's a good place.
I'll kill you and hold a funeral for you here.
What's wrong with you?
Please calm down.
It's your daughter who committed a crime.
A crime? What crime?
You requested Director Seo
for unfair employment.
Then, our daughter deserved to die?
Tell me. Does she deserve to die?
No. I mean…
We also want to figure out
the truth of the case.
Please don't act recklessly.
Recklessly?
Isn't the audit
by this kind of murderer reckless?
I don't want to talk with them
so tell them to leave.
Did you hear her?
I don't want to talk with you. So get lost!
I see.
I'll be back when she calms down.
Is everything okay?
Is there someone who dropped by?
There's no need to worry about it.
Something will happen soon.
So, please stand by.
I'll contact you again.
Tell Mr. Shin to come to me.
Assistant Manager Jeong's family
complained that
you had forcefully investigated her
while auditing.
I can't admit that.
I'll talk to them about it.
They don't want to meet you in person.
That's not important now.
I barely persuaded them
not to report it to the press.
So
I'll start an audit.
I'll start to investigate to
discover the truth.
No. It's an audit about you.
They want me to discipline you.
You'll be excluded from
your duties for a while.
Don't you forget the special provision
of the contract?
It's an audit as a mere formality.
Isn't it you who forget that
there's a condition for that provision?
Who's going to take charge of the audit?
You have already met her before.
I wanted to meet you again
but I didn't expect you to be an audit object.
Let's start.
Yes. I'll start right away.
Why did you order thugs to steal
the recruitment-related documents?
I can bring the person
who appeared on the recording
and make you and him confront each other.
It must be your dad.
Please show me your phone.
You pushed her to answer the question
without proof.
Do you admit it?
The situation pointed out that
she was the suspect.
And it turned out to be true.
What did you do from 11 to 12
on the 21st of March?
Why did you post
Ms. Yoon Seon Jin's pictures?
So, you took pictures secretly
and uploaded them, right?
You pushed her to confess what she didn't do.
Do you admit it?
At that time…
The situation was like she was the suspect.
Well.
The investigation relying only on a situation
could be pushy and violent.
Don't you think so?
I knew he would be in trouble one day.
He was too pushy.
You're going too far.
Are you on Ms. Jeong's side?
I mean. Mr. Shin must've lashed out at her
too much to make her try to kill herself.
She didn't admit her guilt.
I don't think Mr. Shin was pushy enough
to get audited.
There's no one who did well this time.
You got it?
Submit all audit materials that
Mr. Shin was in charge of.
What? All the materials?
Please be hurry.
I want to check them at least in the evening.
You'll be excluded from
your duties for a while.
I know.
See you tomorrow.
Prepare the materials Ms. Seo requested.
And please prepare the quarterly audit well.
I'll go off first.
Sir.
Is it true?
Yes.
My dad has already made
a secret investigation into him.
Someone was dead due to him.
How could a person like him
be an audit team leader?
I'm a victim, too.
It's okay.
I'm about to wrap it up.
Yes.
Hello. I'm Gong Chae Yeon.
Ah, you found Ms. Jeong first when she fell.
Have you come here to see Ms. Jeong?
Yes. I want to see if she's okay.
And to give her her items.
Are you done?
I want to take a rest a bit.
I'm done. Take care of yourself.
I'm happy that Mr. Shin is in trouble.
He's been acting snobbish.
Sir.
Who will be happy
if the ex-president regains consciousness?
Is Mr. President's presidency on the line?
Or is the Vice President's position
on the line?
Both of them are doing all the best they can.
But the Vice President was a pain
in their family's neck.
Particularly
the ex-president's wife is crazy
about kicking him out of the company.
What's the reason?
She hates his family tree.
Then, Mr. Vice President could be kicked out.
Shouldn't we stand on Mr. President's side?
Use your brain.
Listen carefully.
The ex-president can't come back
to the company soon
although he has regained consciousness.
The chance is low.
Then what should he do?
I think he will nominate someone
and support him for his own good.
Isn't it a bad situation
for Mr. Vice President?
Hey. Put yourself in the ex-president's shoes.
One failed a 50 billion won project
and to win a contract.
But the other one won a contract
of 400 billion for construction
and is about to win a redevelopment contract.
Who will you nominate?
Yeah, I understand now.
So
In times like this, we should be far-sighted
and show which side we're on.
It's a tip.
As you know, I've gone through many hardships.
Keep it in mind.
Sir.
You're so sure of yourself.
Do you have secret information?
I don't have it, but I'll check it out today.
I can see
who gets the leverage.
Mr. President.
Director Lee isn't available today
because he plans
to meet up with the Vice President.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'll reconstruct the JU Construction
that is in crisis.
So, please have faith in me
and work hard for more time.
Cheers to JU!
Cheers!
Please give a round of applause.
I'll pour a drink for you.
- Thank you for your hard work.
- It's all thanks to you.
- You did a good job.
- Thank you.
- Go for it!
Sir.
If you win this redevelopment contract
the presidency is yours.
Right.
Let's burn the bull's horn this time.
And pull it completely.
We should get it done before the ex-president
comes back to the company.
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm sorry.
- Just drink.
- Yes, sir.
[Meeting room]
On March 5, 2024
you tried to forcefully take the laptop away
from Mr. Bae,
and he fell from the third floor. Right?
It happened because
he ran away with the laptop.
Did you go to a cocktail bar on March 14th
with Director Yoo, who was an audit object?
Yes, I did.
Then, you went to her apartment
where she lived alone
and faced a charge of harassment.
That already turned out to be a false charge.
I know.
On April 10th
you admitted that you had gone too far
and apologized
to Mr. Pyeon and Director Yang, right?
Yes.
You investigated Chief Park
at 4 a.m. on May 9th.
Was there an unavoidable reason
for that late investigation?
J-BIMS presentation was impending.
The chance of information leakage was high
and I didn't have enough time.
Why do you keep asking about past incidents?
Don't you get it?
You're pushing yourself.
You're urging yourself too hard
with a sense of duty to capture suspects.
So, you didn't realize
your oppressive investigation
harassed the audit objects.
Don't you think so?
Those who try to hide their crimes
are brazen and shrewd.
You also know that we need
to make a bold decision
to fight with that kind of person, don't you?
Even so
I think your way is too pushy
and drives people to a dead end.
You and I have different investigation styles.
Well.
What about this one?
[Kim Man Soo, Baeon Construction]
Deputy Director Kim Man Soo
from Baeon Construction.
Do you remember him?
[Two years ago]
Do you have a company?
Excuse me.
Who is he?
Who the hell is he?
What the heck!
Mr. Shin…
Do you admit you've used
the company credit card for pleasure?
No. It's just for…
I'll tell you for you.
Aren't the people you entertained the executives
from Moo San and Bong Sun companies?
I'm suspicious that they gave you
a higher subcontracted work amount
than the actual amount
to get back the difference.
It's an act of illegal fundraising.
It can be qualified as embezzlement
and breach of trust.
You have two options.
First. Admit that you set up a secret fund
and be fired and charged.
Second. Disclose who ordered this
and receive leniency.
Which one are you going to choose?
I'm sorry the house is a mess.
Why don't you come inside for a minute?
No, it's okay.
Where is Deputy Director Kim Man Soo?
What?
He went to work in the morning.
Isn't he at the office?
What do you think you're doing?
I know you're the Audit Team leader
but isn't it too much to drop by
my house without permission?
Do you know what my wife's condition is?
Let's talk in person.
Your wife didn't know you were excluded
from your duties and took time off.
I didn't tell her
because I didn't want to worry her.
Is it a problem?
Why are you trying to take all the guilt?
I know you're covering up for
Director Bae Hyung Kyu and the Vice President.
Please stop it.
It is really not.
Even though you keep silent
nothing will be solved.
I will never give up.
Everything will be discovered.
I said I did it alone.
If you keep doing it, I'll be finished.
You pushed him, who had already confessed
what he did, to tell the truth.
Was that why he committed suicide?
Is the case of Ms. Jeong the same
as that of Deputy Director Kim Man Soo?
I'm so worried.
A similar incident can happen again
if you keep auditing like this.
Let's
call it a day.
I think what Mr. Shin said is right.
What do you mean?
He said we shouldn't trust anyone.
Mr. Bae, Assistant Manager Moon
and even Mr. Shin betrayed my trust.
I can't believe
he audited someone until the one died.
Did he really do that?
You also heard the story
about Deputy Director Kim Man Soo.
I didn't think he was that brutal.
When you told me you believed in me
I was glad.
You were reliable.
I was encouraged a lot
when I had someone who trusted me.
So, I want to trust him.
I'm sure there was a reason we don't know.
If you'll keep working with the Audit Team
you'd better not trust someone easily.
You're right.
I feel like you've influenced me.
Right.
Mr. Shin Cha Il.
Do you remember me?
I'm Deputy Director Kim Man Soo's wife.
I know.
Please tell me.
Why should my husband have to die?
No one told me the truth about it
including the company.
You didn't tell me
what happened to him even at his funeral.
I need to know now.
I'm sorry.
I will never give up this time.
Isn't the audit
by this kind of murderer reckless?
So you killed a person?
While auditing?
I'm so worried.
A similar incident can happen again
if you keep auditing like this.
[Dismiss Shin Cha Il who did a murder audit
Discover the truth of my husband's miserable death]
Isn't it a golden opportunity?
We can fire him through this chance.
I'm sure it's your plan, right?
It's such an excellent strategy.
It's the best.
Are you excited?
Well…
Aren't you excited?
I know you have an acquaintance
at Baeon Construction.
Baeon Construction?
Ah, I can see your intention.
You're going to plan to fire him, right?
Yeah, I have an acquaintance.
I'll contact him right now.
[Dismiss Shin Cha Il who did a murder audit
Discover the truth of my husband's miserable death]
I'll come every day.
Don't push yourself too hard.
If you want me to stop it
please tell the truth.
Mr. Shin and I have agreed
to a special provision.
That's a provision that I can't dismiss him
within two years.
Two years?
He demanded two years for a decent audit.
But, there's a condition to that provision.
If he causes harm to the company
I can dismiss him.
Is the picketing one such thing?
If it becomes the focus of the public attention
you can call it into question.
Is it what you want?
I don't have any intention.
I just wanted to figure out what's going on.
Thank you. You can go.
This is a will Ms. Jeong wrote.
She wrote that it was such a violent
and oppressive audit that she felt shame
and couldn't stand the pressure.
The bereaved of Mr. Kim Man Soo
visited the company
and there was a gossip about you.
The issue has become complicated.
Is there something you want to say?
'I couldn't say anything because I was daunted.
You'll know if you listen to the recording.
She wasn't daunted at all.
Rather, she was confident and brazen.
The will contains her impure intention.
She tried to kill herself.
Are you saying she lied
at the risk of her life?
Don't let anything cloud your judgment.
You should be careful the most
not to lose the insight.
Figure out the situation with an open mind.
And do not jump to conclusions.
I'll report the audit result tomorrow.
If you don't have anything to say
I'll wrap it up.
What is this?
Go and figure out what happened to Mr. Shin.
Baeon Construction?
Why are you suddenly giving it to me?
Do you want me to find something
that can harm Mr. Shin?
You want to die?
I mean, it's weird.
Why are you suddenly trying to help Mr. Shini?
I do whatever to get back at the enemy.
It's the same
when it comes to returning the favor.
You go and find out what happened exactly.
This is all I can help.
- You got it?
- Yes.
By the way, may I tell Mr. Shin
- that you're helping?
- Yes.
Tell him if you want to die.
Thank you.
- Mr. Vice President?
- Yes.
So, I'll go to see him.
Why don't we go together?
- Did you hear that?
- What do you mean?
The audit result of Mr. Shin
will come out tomorrow.
It seems like disciplinary action
will be taken against him.
There's a picketing in front of the company.
The president definitely wants to show
he's paying attention to this case.
In times like this, we'd better play it safe.
Let's go to see him now.
We'll work outside of the office.
We'll be back.
I told you to play it safe.
Where are you going?
Hello.
Do you have a business with the Audit Team?
No.
Hey. Let's go.
Okay.
I'm not sure
whether it's okay to say it to you.
We want to know
what happened to Mr Shin exactly.
You also don't want him
to get an unfair punishment.
Please help us.
It's me. Where are you?
Don't worry. I will never tell.
But
you should keep your word.
You should save.
I see.
Did he say
'You should save.'?
Yes.
Please stop it. It is really not.
Even though you keep silent
nothing will be solved.
I will never give up.
Everything will be discovered.
I said I did it alone.
If you keep doing it, I'll be finished.
Your wife has
triple-negative breast cancer, right?
I heard you moved to a new house
because of the hospital fee.
Excuse me.
Is a huge amount of medical expense the reason
you're covering up for
Director Bae and the Vice President?
Please stop it.
You're so mean.
Did they guarantee you
the expense after the surgery?
Is that why you keep silent like this?
Do you really have to investigate like this?
You're just aggravating the situation.
I don't give up investigating it.
[The late Kim Man Soo]
I'm so very sorry for your loss.
Is it true?
Did my husband really commit a breach of trust
and embezzlement?
Is that why he died?
We need to investigate more.
No.
That's not true.
He liked to go to work.
He was strongly devoted to the company.
This is unfair.
It must be a false charge.
We couldn't receive his statement
and failed to leave a record
that it was due to a hospital fee.
We also couldn't tell the truth to his wife.
Mr. Shin couldn't tell her that
her husband committed a crime to save her life.
- Thank you for your time.
- Thank you.
We should let Ms. Seo know about it.
It wasn't an oppressive investigation.
He did that for his wife's hospital fee.
Yes. Let's go.
Okay.
Please wait.
Isn't it coincidental?
What do you mean?
I don't understand
why his wife suddenly came up.
I think Ms. Jeong already knew
about the case with Deputy Director Kim.
Isn't the audit
by this kind of murderer reckless?
I need to check this out.
- Hello.
I'm Goo Han Soo
a team member of JU's Audit Team.
I want to ask you something.
Who told you that
Mr. Shin is working at this company?
Why are you asking that?
Please answer it.
If you tell us
[Discover the truth
of my husband's miserable death]
I'll tell you the truth you wanted to know.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Please trust us
and tell us who told you about it.
He said his name is CEO Jeong.
He told me
that his daughter was also Mr. Shin's victim.
By any chance, is the phone number
you got this one?
Yes.
If she intentionally spread the story
of Deputy Director Kim
I doubt if she really tried to kill herself.
Are you saying that she pretended to suicide?
Is she trustworthy?
Wait a moment.
Look at this.
This is a post she uploaded
in the morning she tried to kill herself.
I want to quit work and go to Europe.
A person who is determined to die
wouldn't write a post like this.
I think there's a way to check this out.
[I don't want to open my eyes this morning
I want to quit work and go to Europe]
Please tell us the truth.
You came to the Audit Team a bit ago
because you had something to say, right?
Our team leader is in trouble due to this case.
Please help us.
Please
tell us the truth.
Well…
I'll take a few of these pills.
So call 911 right away, right?
Do you really have to do this?
You can't imagine
how shameful I was due to him.
I'm not just going to take it lying down.
Get your head on straight.
If you do it well
I'll give you the money you asked for.
I see.
Let's start.
Someone fell down. Please help me.
Is what you said now true?
Yes.
She had no intention to kill herself.
I needed money urgently.
So, I did what she asked on an impulse.
But I regretted what I did.
Have you secured her testimony?
I'll take care of the case.
You did a good job.
Thank you.
I'm…
jealous of Mr. Shin.
He has reliable team members who trust him.
By the way
will you tell Deputy Director's wife the truth?
She'll be shocked by the truth.
But I think she should know it.
If we don't tell her
her anguish will be bigger.
I'm surprised.
You should learn manners.
Did you pretend to kill yourself
to set Mr. Shin up?
What a bullshit is this?
What did you tell her?
Tell me what you told her.
Hey. Ms. Jeong Hye Young.
You'll be accused of
slandering and libeling Mr. Shin.
You'd better appoint a great lawyer.
Hey. Come here.
Hey! Tell me what you told her.
No.
Damn it.
[Report of audit]
[It turned out that Mr. Shin wasn't violent
and oppressive while auditing]
I see.
You can go.
Isn't the president upset?
He didn't say much.
Wait.
I realize today that I'm a wolf.
What?
I'm curious about one thing.
Are you a hunting dog or a wolf?
Aha.
I knew you were a wolf from the beginning.
Be careful that talking down
can be within the audit scope.
I heard the truth.
He did that for me.
I've blamed the wrong person.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's me who feels sorry for you.
Actually, I knew it.
I knew that your husband
had come to a dead end.
But, I pushed him more because I thought…
I could get more information.
That was my fault.
I'm sorry.
You just did what you should do.
By the way, what happened to them?
Those who took advantage of my husband.
I found other evidence.
They were disciplined and dismissed.
They're now in prison.
I see.
That's good news.
I'm relieved.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry.
Good morning.
- Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Do you have something to say?
No.
I'm just happy to see you.
I heard you helped me. Thank you.
You did a good job.
What did you say just now?
I said I heard about you.
I mean, the next sentence.
You did a good job.
No. The sentence before it.
Thank…
Be ready to work.
Yes, sir.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Goo Han Soo.
Do you have any good news?
I think something good will happen today.
You're so lame.
Honey.
It's me. Can you recognize me?
What did you say?
Se Woong? All right.
I'll call him to come.
Excuse me!
I'm sure. He wanted to see you.
He must've regained his consciousness.
He's fallen asleep now.
Please come early tomorrow morning.
I'll go to my house tonight
and come early tomorrow morning.
Thank God.
Sir. Here you go.
We've solved one thing
and now a bunch of work is waiting for us.
It's too much. I see no end to it.
The regular audit is a piece of work
compared to other incidents.
You're right.
May this peace continue.
[Benjamin Lee]
I have a hunch right now.
What kind of hunch?
I have a hunch that
something serious will happen.
Don't say that.
Don't say a word that like.
Let's work. We have a lot of stuff to do.
You're right.
Sir.
Have you heard that the ex-president
regained his consciousness?
I heard.
Yes. I didn't expect him
to regain his consciousness this fast.
What should we do?
I didn't expect to see you here.
I even hate seeing you in my dreams.
What brings you here?
Attempted manslaughter and dumping of a body
embezzlement, and breach of trust.
And a special request for a job position.
You'll be staying in prison for a long.
You bastard.
Are you here to rub salt into my wound?
I came to see you because you would know
a lot of embarrassing matters of the company.
Are you planning
to stab somebody in the back again?
It is not yet too late
to be a help to the company.
Get lost, you bastard!
Have you heard of Archcle-design?
Well…
Your look says you know about it.
Tell me as much as you know.
Let's say I know about it.
But why should I tell it to you?
Don't ever come to see me.
Just seeing your face turns my stomach.
[The Auditors]
The ex-president was on the gain
but suddenly died.
What are you suspicious of?
There's someone who keeps
siphoning secret funds and embezzling.
I look forward to working with you.
Since when have you been
on friendly terms with him?
The guy next to Mr. President
is Undersecretary Ahn, right?
Can the vice president be the real owner
of Archcle and secret funds?
I won't let personal feelings come into play
because I'm an Audit Team member.
Secrecy is necessary for this audit.
I'll catch a bad guy who's been extorting
JU Construction for a long time.