[The Auditors]
Is it because of the President?
Is that so?
How about this?
What if someone is trying to
leak company's important technology?
Yoon Woo.
You are also an important member of the team.
No matter how capable they are,
people who bully others…
should be penalized properly.
Don't you think so?
Thanks.
But.
Have you always had a bad relationship
with Mr. Park?
Or was there some kind of trigger?
We need to look at the context…
so try to remember anything.
That's not really the case.
In fact, Mr. Park and I even did
pair programming together.
Pair programming.
Does that mean you wrote code
on one computer with him?
Then, there can be a lot of conflicts.
Is that why your relationship got worse?
No. We had no conflicts.
Oh, yes.
Did you remember something?
That's right.
You have to break this down.
This looks good.
Good job. I'll finish the rest.
- Can you get me a cup of coffee?
- Okay.
[GUARANTEED 500% WINNING ODDS!
LAST OPPORTUNITY!]
[7aqwxuNET723E0g77.onion
Accessible only through a dedicated browser.]
Isn't this a spam?
Maybe the security for the emails
isn't updated yet.
I guess so. Thank you.
Sure.
I'm sorry.
Yoon Woo.
Did you report about the spam email
to the General Manager?
Yes, I thought the security system
needed a check.
Why did you report that directly to him?
I thought you were busy.
I wanted to act quickly for security reasons.
Yoon Woo…
don't you even know
about the reporting system here?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
After that incident,
I stopped pair programming.
Thinking about it…
it seems like he bullied me more
and more since that day.
Just for not following
the reporting system once?
That's harsh.
Maybe he was actually involved
in illegal gambling.
That's why he was upset with you.
I don't think he entered the website.
Thinking back, I find it odd…
that he replied to that spam email.
[YOUR EMAIL HAS BEEN SENT]
He replied to that spam e-mail?
Back then, I didn't consider it weird
since I was busy getting scolded.
Don't you think it's suspicious?
Can I see that spam email?
I moved it to my spam folder
because of the security system.
It should be still be in my mailbox.
This one.
[FRESH ONION]
Why? What is it?
This link is for the dark web.
But, why would Mr. Park enter here?
This is a place where illegally
leaked information…
is traded.
What?
Does that mean he illegally leaks information?
What kind of information?
Could it be?
Yes. J-BIMS.
[The Auditors]
You're suspecting that Mr. Park
is leaking information on J-BIMS?
Yes. I found a trace of trade
about J-BIMS on the dark web.
[FRESH ONION}
This one.
JJBM5…
JU Construction.
J-BIMS?
What do the numbers mean?
I have no idea.
Should we run the password generation program?
No need. Since this is basically
just something put up for sale.
He intentionally wanted to attract people.
He couldn't have used a difficult password.
JBIMS504090809
[ERROR]
[504090809]
[0513-500-550-DD]
0513 matches the date of the demonstration.
The numbers following that
seem to be the price.
Maximum of 55 billion won
to a minimum of 50 billion won
Finally, DD seems to stand for Direct Dealing.
It means you deal personally with him.
What are these numbers?
[0513]
I'm not sure about this one.
But it's definitely to trade about J-BIMS.
Leaking technical information on J-BIMS
is a serious criminal offense.
Are you sure that Mr. Park
committed such a crime?
Is there any other evidence?
Not yet.
Do you at least have a proof
that he entered the website?
I don't. But…
But it's weird that he replied
to a spam email.
Are you sure that he replied?
Yoon Woo said he saw it.
Are you sure that the bully victim
did not make up the story out of resentment?
He isn't the kind of person who would do that.
He wasn't bullied without a reason.
It was because he might have known
about the technology leak!
You are still judging with personal emotions
towards the informant…
and viewing things with a biased perspective.
Goo Han Soo.
We need evidence.
It might be too late late by then.
We need to investigate Mr. Park immediately!
Don't let your emotions blind you, Mr. Goo!
I repeat.
We need…
evidence.
Deal with this matter quietly after the event.
Workplace bullying is a serious issue.
It must be thoroughly investigated.
Did I say not to do it?
Do it after the event.
No disruptions should occur that would
interfere with the J-BIMS demonstration.
Even if that involves you, Mr. Shin.
J-BIMS, which will change
the future of JU Construction…
will be unveiled through
a demonstration next week.
It has already shown promising results
even in its incomplete test version.
J-BIMS is an AI-based
construction process managing program.
We will apply the demo version
to the Goo Young Building construction site…
that cost of 70 billion won.
It is expected to reduce construction costs
by approximately 1.4 billion won.
In the future, it will drastically
reduce construction costs.
It sounds impressive in theory…
but it seems like it's just about
reducing schedules, cutting costs, …
and ultimately reducing staff.
Through J-BIMS,
unnecessary manpower can be reduced…
There is no such thing
as unnecessary manpower in construction.
We hire them because we need them.
It seems like once this is completed…
management will talk about cost savings
and subsequent layoffs.
Is laying off the staff who have built the company
together while sharing the same meal…
the future the CEO envisions for JU?
If it's necessary for the company, yes.
Especially…
we will start by removing executives
who are hindering the company's growth.
By the way…
how many times have you visited
the construction site while working here?
Well…
If you have something to say, be specific.
How many people are needed for the pouring?
Do you not know what pouring means?
I'm talking about concrete placement.
For concrete placing boom…
the number of staff needed is…
0.49 person per 10 cubic meters
for reinforced structures.
0.49 person?
That's wild.
So you just cut a person in half?
Is this for winter or summer?
How about in rainy days?
- Sorry?
- When pouring concrete in an apartment setting…
you need two people for
the discharge area and hose…
one for the vibrator…
and two to three for finishing and
cleaning the surface.
That's at least 6 people.
In addition, if it's cold,
you'll need extra workers to heat the mix.
When it rains, you'll need additional
workers to cover the surface with plastic.
Understand?
Such factors can be taken into account
and reflected in the program.
There are many variables
in the construction site.
Are you going to rewrite the program
every time something changes?
Let's adjourn the meeting.
He may seem sophisticated,
but I can't trust someone
who relies only on machines.
You're right.
General Manager Ji Hoon looks like a person
who would stab people in the back.
He has the face of a traitor.
What kind of face do I have?
You have the face of a dragon.
It's a good sign.
You look like someone who will be king.
Mr. Yang, you're very transparent.
That's why I like you.
Ah well…
I'm loyal to the company.
No, I mean…
My priority is to be loyal,
loyal and loyal to you.
Speaking of which..
Shin Cha Il doesn't really
have the right look either.
His words are so harsh and
he seems to be rambling about a lot today.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
It seems like something interesting
happened at the Audit Office today.
Something interesting?
Someone from the Audit Office…
reportedly confronted Mr. Shin,
alleging that there was a suspicion…
- of J-BIMS information leakage.
- Why?
Mr. Shin dismissed it,
saying there was no evidence.
I heard that the CEO ordered…
not to create any disturbances
before the event.
So, he probably covered it up.
Se Woong and Cha Il only seem
to work together to bully me.
But still…
Are you saying Cha Il covered it up?
I will go ahead first.
He must be in a hurry.
I don't think so. He's just upset.
Everyone is dismissed for the day.
- Let's go home.
- Yes.
- Okay.
We'll leave first.
Goodbye.
Mr. Shin's expression didn't change at all
even after Han Soo left like that.
There may be suspicions,
but there's no evidence.
Why do you think he's so certain?
He's frustrated because
things aren't going well for his friend.
So he exaggerated his suspicions.
It wasn't that big of a deal anyway.
Geez.
Seo Jin, you should call and look after him.
I'll get going.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Bye, Seo Jin.
- Goodbye.
- Get home safe.
[Park Jae Hwan]
[Graduated Kyungseo University
with a degree in Computer Engineering]
[- Intern at Jeoksong R&D in 2012
- Working at JU Construction since 2014]
Director Yang was right.
You don't have the right look.
Thanks for the compliment.
You have a face of someone…
with blood on their hands.
Someone who pushes people
to their very limit…
is just simply ruthless.
It seems you've done some research on my past.
But I'm good.
You see it a lot on TV.
Cold-blooded.
I will get going.
It's quite disgusting…
when someone treats human lives…
insignificant and yet
keeps criticizing corruption.
You have a face of someone
with blood on their hands.
It's quite disgusting…
when someone treats human lives…
insignificant and yet
keeps criticizing corruption.
Mr. Shin Cha Il,
do you really have to go all this way?
I will fight till the end.
Mr. Shin, why do you keep doing this?
Why?
The CEO is focused
on the J-BIMS demonstration event.
That's why your team leader
can't do anything without evidence.
No.
He isn't someone
who would overlook suspicions.
But how could he ignore the CEO's orders?
[0513-500-550-DD]
Then, I'll have to make him ignore it.
What's up with you?
I think I found out
what these numbers mean.
For real? What is it?
This is an ASCII code.
It's converted it to decimal…
We just need to reverse it.
[judevelop@ju.com invitation]
This is my team's email address.
If you send an email here,
you'll receive an invitation in reply.
There will probably be detailed
contact information in it.
I'm going to try sending an email.
Will we get a reply?
We'll have to wait and see.
Hello, sir.
[National Intelligence Service Report
on Industrial Technology Leakage]
Here you go.
You printed this, right?
Thank you.
Hello.
The team leader doesn't seem
to be associated with the CEO.
But why is my uncle…
It's regarding the error check update.
I was worried since
it was my first time doing it…
but Yoon Woo had recorded everything in detail
so I was able to resolve it quickly.
Okay, thank you.
Yoon Woo worked so hard on this project.
Shouldn't we watch the demonstration together?
What's with the long face?
Sorry?
Don't you feel good?
You've been separated from Yun Woo,
who was like a pain in the neck.
Was it me that felt as such about him?
He'll be sent to another department.
You don't have to worry about him anymore.
Let's talk about work.
Change the order of the video
for the demonstration.
Some of them will need to be rendered again.
Finalizing the tuning
of the prediction model itself is challenging.
There's no way we can manage that as well.
We need help from other departments…
You do it.
Others aren't as reliable.
I have other works to do,
so I'll be out in the afternoon.
Yes, sir.
Hello.
- Hi.
- You're here.
You've been busy since the morning?
Mr. Shin is out on fieldwork.
Han Soo is on sick leave…
but I wonder if he's really sick
or just being rebellious.
He's too kind to be rebellious.
Did he get sick because he was upset
about what happened yesterday?
Even if Han Soo was being unreasonable…
Mr. Shin could have at least tried
to smooth things over.
But he's being just as childish.
You're more childish than them.
Being childish is part of my charm.
Are you Kim Jong Won?
Yes, I'm Kim Jong Won.
I'm the one who called. My name is Shin Cha Il.
I'm the Audit Team Leader at JU Construction.
Thank you for your time.
As I've mentioned,
I requested to meet…
because I have some questions
related to your work at Tree System.
Mr. Park.
You need to submit
the statement of reason by today.
Okay.
Yoon Woo could you write…
I don't think we'll get a reply.
Yoon Woo, you said Mr. Park
replied to that email.
That must've been the invitation.
Won't that be in his PC?
I guess so.
But how do you plan to check his PC?
Don't tell me…
Yes. That's the only way.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Are you sure there's no one here?
Yes, I asked.
They need to stay overnight tomorrow…
so they said they'll leave before 10pm.
All right. Let's go.
- Hello.
- Yes.
I am Oh Yoon Woo
from the Technology Development Team
What are you doing here at this hour?
That's because…
Mr. Oh is a victim of workplace harassment
and he's on leave.
He's under the audit team's protection.
We came to retrieve some personal belongings
that he left behind.
Okay. You may go in.
Staff from other departments…
are not allowed to enter
outside of working hours.
I'm from the audit team.
Mr. Oh is currently in a very unstable state,
both mentally and physically.
If we leave him alone and something happens,
will you take responsibility?
You need to be quick.
Okay.
Wait.
You need to put a security sticker
over you phone's camera.
Oh, right. Okay.
This is his desk.
Wait.
If the power is turned on,
an alert will go directly to Mr. Park.
Then he'll call the security office.
They'll come in immediately.
Two minutes?
No, it probably won't even take a minute.
I'll be as quick as possible.
Here I go.
JU protect Security System App
Yes, I'll check.
I found it.
It's a sample of J-BIMS demonstration version.
He showed it to the buyers as a sample
to make them want to purchase it.
Mr. Park seriously…
Okay, I will go and check.
What are you doing here?
I received a report that Mr. Park's computer
has been turned on.
Why did you touch his computer?
It was a mistake.
I thought it was my computer…
because we used the same computer
during pair coding.
I got everything.
We'll leave now.
Please wait here.
Mr. Park is on his way.
You may leave after he checks.
No, we can't.
Mr. Park is the perpetrator who harassed him.
They aren't allowed to meet. We will leave now.
- Let's go.
- You can't leave.
We'll let you go after we have checked.
Please stay still.
Can I at least make one phone call?
Who the hell was it?
Stop!
What is going on?
That computer is an important evidence.
Don't touch it until my team leader arrives.
- What are you talking about?
- Take another step…
and we will consider it as an attempt
to erase the evidence.
Mr. Shin. I found the evidence.
I received a call from Mr. Park
regarding an issue in the R&D office
What's all this about?
We figured why Mr. Park bullied Yoon Woo.
What are you talking about when you tried
to snoop on someone else's computer?
Let's see if you can say that
after seeing this.
What are you doing?!
You must be scared to see this, right?
The evidence is all right here.
What are you talking about?
Leave it.
Mr. Lee?
I'm not sure what this is about but be quick.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Park started bullying Yoon Woo
because he thought he saw his email.
What's that email about?
This is the email.
[Download permission is not available]
Give me a second.
This…
It was definitely here a minute ago, Mr. Shin.
Is it okay…
for the audit team
to search the R&D office recklessly?
I will report this matter directly to the CEO.
No. Wait.
No. I saw it.
The email was definitely here.
Mr. Goo, from this moment on
you will be excluded from this case.
- But Mr. Shin…
- I saw it too.
Mr. Oh, keep in mind that
this will only be detrimental to you.
Please go home immediately.
We will contact you later.
Come out.
Mr. Shin, I saw it.
Mr. Shin, I swear I saw it.
Sorry for the trouble.
Mr. Shin!
Why did you hack into Mr. Park's computer
in the R&D office?
To search for the evidence.
You said we needed proof.
I specifically told you yesterday…
to investigate discreetly.
We need evidence.
It might be too late late by then.
We need to investigate Mr. Park immediately!
Don't let your emotions blind you, Mr. Goo!
Mr. Goo Han Soo.
Is there something you want to say?
I couldn't talk about it
since it was a sensitive issue.
What do you mean?
I suspect there is information leakage
from the R&D department.
I knew it.
You also think Mr. Park is
trying to leak about J-BIMS.
No.
What?
The person I suspect is not Mr. Park.
Then who?
General Manager Lee Ji Hoon.
Hold on a second.
What is this about?
I need to take this
to the General Affairs team.
Go on.
Does the R&D Department use special paper?
Yes. Due to the nature the department…
their document management is more stringent
than in other departments.
Only paper containing sensors
is allowed to be used.
If an internal document is taken out,
it will be detected at the checkpoint.
May I have a look?
It looks like a normal paper.
Please excuse the mess.
I'm not really good at organizing.
But I have…
- Can I use this?
- Wait a second.
That one is probably crumpled.
Here's a new one.
Please wait.
I am here to interview
General Manager Lee Ji Hoon.
You may enter.
According to security regulations,
the R&D Department…
must use special paper
with a weight of 100 grams.
But the paper I found
on General Manager Lee Ji Hoon's sofa…
was lighter and thinner than the special paper.
It was likely the common 80-gram regular paper.
Then…
if he printed something confidential
on that paper and took it out,
it wouldn't have been detected
at the checkpoint.
He is outwardly very sensitive
about the security of the R&D Department…
and has always advocated
for strengthening the system.
However, he himself was engaging in actions
that violate the regulations.
It doesn't add up.
I agree…
but I'm still suspicious of Mr. Park.
It makes sense if Mr. Lee was attempting
to leak information with Mr. Park's help.
The problem is finding evidence.
Mr. Goo, I want you to
secretly investigate about Mr. Park.
Okay. I will find the evidence.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It is very important…
that the fact that we are investigating
must not be revealed.
I'm sorry. I should've been more careful.
What did you find?
A sample of the J-BIMS demo version…
was posted on the dark web
to show to potential buyers.
However…
it was deleted, perhaps because
they realized we were investigating.
That would have been definitive evidence.
He wasn't surprised.
What?
What are you doing?!
You must be scared to see this, right?
The evidence is all right here.
- What are you talking about?
- Leave it.
Mr. Lee?
I'm not sure what this is about but be quick.
It seems certain that Mr. Lee is involved.
He must have realized
that I accessed the dark web…
and deleted the demo version.
Mr. Park is an accomplice.
J-BIMS couldn't be stolen yet, right?
Some parts might have been
handed over to brokers.
However, since J-BIMS is not completed yet…
So the deal may not have been finalized yet.
That's right.
But we don't have much time left.
What should we do?
We need to closely monitor General Manager Lee.
I'll take care of that.
They must have caught on
to our investigation by now.
Be careful.
Yes, sir.
Why did you search through
the R&D Department's computers?
What were you looking for?
Or were you trying to steal something?
I hope you're not going
to make excuses…
like "We're trying to find evidence
of workplace bullying."
The issue is not related to workplace bullying.
Then what is it?
There were signs of an attempt to leak…
J-BIMS's core technology…
among the employees in the R&D Department.
What did you say?
Leaking about J-BIMS?
Do you have evidence?
There is no physical evidence yet.
We only have suspicions
about the attempt to leak the technology.
Is the owner of the computer that
the audit team secretly searched a suspect?
There is a high probability
that he's an accomplice.
So there's another main suspect.
It's General Manager Lee Ji Hoon.
Honestly, I can't believe it.
He oversees J-BIMS…
and has previously reported
about two external brokers' attempts…
at leaking information.
Still, an investigation is necessary.
Variables can always arise.
We need to determine if a leak attempt
actually occurred.
Handle it discreetly.
Most importantly…
the preparation for the demonstration
must not be disrupted.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Shin.
J-BIMS is crucial not only
for our company's future revenue…
but also for the management rights.
If the suspicions turn out to be false,
both you and the audit team…
will be held responsible for causing trouble.
I heard Han Soo is on vacation again.
People say…
No. Never mind.
What is it? Spill it.
Are you curious?
What is it? Tell us.
Well…
I heard someone caused trouble
at the R&D department.
I have a feeling that…
Was it Han Soo?
Yes.
He was eager to find evidence.
I guess he caused trouble.
It's just my gut feeling.
He went against Mr. Shin once,
he must think he's the Team Leader now.
He's probably going through puberty.
Mr. Shin…
I have something to tell you.
You haven't given up
on the R&D department case, right?
If you're hesitant to move forward
due to lack of evidence, I can help.
I'm also concerned because he's my colleague.
What Han Soo said did make sense.
For now, I will go to the Information
Security Team to check…
if there are any issues with our company's
network and technology security systems.
Is that alright?
Go ahead.
Make sure to investigate thoroughly,
but it should appear as a routine check
given the upcoming demonstration.
Yes, sir.
Come in.
- Mr. Park, come here. Take a look at this.
- Yes, sir.
Why was the timeline
for the demonstration changed?
While revising, it turned out that
changing it this way made the flow more natural
Restore it to its original state.
Then we'll need to adjust the simulation
for the latter part and rerun the calculations.
Yes, do that.
I'm currently fixing an error
with the material inventory calculations…
so I don't have enough time
to make this adjustment as well.
Is there anyone just lounging around?
Everyone's short on time.
Don't underestimate yourself.
You can definitely handle it all.
Mr. Park…
the demonstration is just around the corner.
We need to show them how much effort we put in.
Once we get through this
demonstration successfully…
you know
what will happen next, right?
Mr. Park…
No. General Manager Park.
I want to do everything too,
but realistically, there's not enough time.
Please edit it as you wish.
Just make sure to match
the presentation timeline.
This exact scene must be shown
exactly 12 minutes…
after I start the presentation.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
The demonstration is coming up soon.
I'm just asking as a precaution.
Our R&D department's information
protection system is intact, right?
Of course. The system is regularly upgraded.
It's rare for anyone in the R&D department
to violate security regulations, right?
There might be minor mistakes occasionally…
but with the demonstration so close…
Yes. There used to be one person
who occasionally made mistakes…
but there haven't been any in recent days.
Speaking of which…
I haven't received the statement of reason
about the security sticker removal.
Is that so?
Who is it?
That's…
Yes, I understand.
Mr. Shin, it looks like the transaction
is happening tonight.
He made an appointment with the broker.
When and where?
That's right. I have to follow the evidence.
Where did he go?
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
- Well…
- Well what, you brat?
Who are you?
Hand over what you received from Lee Ji Hoon.
What nonsense are you talking about?
- Hand it over.
- Hand over what?
I have nothing.
Stop lying. I saw everything.
Is this it?
Why are you doing this to me?
- Whose passport is this?
- My younger sister.
She left it at home.
I was bringing it to her.
Why did you meet Lee Ji Hoon?
Who is that?
The one you met under the bridge.
Let me go. This is a crime.
Call the police.
What should I report?
Assault and battery.
Yes, sir.
Hello. I want to report an assault incident.
Did you already know
that he is a passport forger.
I didn't believe his story entirely.
How so?
His sister didn't resemble him.
Is that all?
Suspicious location, suspicious money,
and a suspicious passport.
It was enough to raise doubts.
General Manager Lee bought a fake passport.
If the forger confesses, it's all over, right?
We might not have time
to wait for a confession.
Why?
This is Shin Cha Il.
I understand. I'm on my way.
We're going back to the office.
Yes, sir.
You get off from work quite late.
I'm going down.
Let's have an interview at the audit room.
What are you doing?
- Do you know what time it is now?
- It will be quick.
Please get off.
Is this about Oh Yoon Woo?
Let's talk tomorrow. Let me go home.
Don't misunderstand.
This is not a request.
Let's go.
Isn't Oh Yoon Woo's case over now?
The investigation about workplace bullying
is still ongoing.
I didn't bully him.
Mr. Park, have you ever been bullied?
What are you talking about?
Have you ever been bullied…
by General Manager Lee Ji Hoon?
Compliments and motivation
disguised as gaslighting.
That is his tactic.
[Lee Ji Hoon.]
I worked with Lee Ji Hoon,
before he joined JU Construction
It was a startup company.
He worked as a technical team leader
for about a year.
It wasn't just me.
There were a few others too.
The people who were bullied by him.
Let's end the meeting here.
Before joining JU Construction,
Lee Ji Hoon worked as a technical team leader
at a startup for a year.
Jung Ho.
Is this how you want to work?
I wouldn't be like this
if you take responsibility for your mistakes.
An employee who worked under him
resigned after only three months.
The reason being…
You have a brain.
Shouldn't you be putting that to good use?
Is it that hard?
Covert bullying.
[JU Construction Shin Cha Il]
I'm not sure where to start.
You fix this.
I can't handle it anymore.
Are you Mr. Shin Cha Il?
Yes, I am.
That wasn't the end.
Within less than six months, two more
employees resigned from the company.
Are you sure
you won't regret this?
Their reasons for leaving were the same…
which was bullying by Mr. Lee.
He used the same bullying style.
Hang in there just a little bit more.
We're almost finished with the project.
You can do it.
When it was just the two of them…
the bullying was intense and discreet,
unnoticed by other team members.
Finish it by tomorrow.
- To everyone else, he was Dr. Jekyll…
- But this…
but to the victim, he was Mr. Hyde.
Doesn't it sound familiar to you?
But from now on, this is not an interrogation
on the workplace bullying.
Then, what is it?
We'll being the investigation of Mr. Park,
the manager of R&D department…
for involvement in attempting
to leak the core technology of J-BIMS.
What…?
What are you talking about?
Leaking J-BIMS?
What do you mean I'm the accomplice?
We discovered that Mr. Lee Ji Hoon,
the General Manager of R&D department,
was involved in leaking
the core technology of J-BIMS…
to a multinational broker organization.
He had also agreed to receive
approximately 50 billion won in exchange.
Wait…
Is that true?
During this process, we have captured evidence
indicating that you assisted him.
No way. I've never done such thing.
Here.
According to the list of security
regulation violations in the R&D department…
you brought in standard A4 paper,
which is prohibited
within the development area.
Additionally, you removed
the security stickers four times…
and you submitted
statement of reason for these.
Wait but that's…
Above all, you replied
to an email from a broker…
disguised as an advertisement spam.
No. I've done all that
because Mr. Lee ordered me to.
You did all this
because your superior asked you to?
My position is low compared to my age.
I started working quite late
due to personal reasons…
so I didn't get promoted on time.
2 years ago…
I was sure that I would be promoted
as the General Manager of the R&D Department.
But then Mr. Lee, who's younger than me came.
But Mr. Lee said he would soon
become an executive.
So as long as I follow his orders…
he would promote me as the head of the team.
Then…
why did you excluded Yoon Woo
from the J-BIMS project?
I didn't expect that either.
Mr. Lee suddenly told me
not to ask questions…
and just respond to a specific spam email.
I did as I was told, but then Yoon Woo saw it.
After realizing this, he insisted
on sending Yoon Woo…
to another department
by any means necessary.
So, I ended up bullying him.
But I just followed his orders.
Do you think that makes sense?
But, I really didn't know
that it was about a leaking information.
I swear.
Mr. Lee promised you a promotion.
He also used your computer IP address…
to upload and promote the J-BIMS
demo version sample…
on the dark web.
He intended to pin
all the technology leakage on you.
What?
Mr. Park.
Answer me properly.
Depending in your answer…
we will either believe
your claim of innocence…
or decide to report you to the police…
immediately after this investigation.
I understand.
- There will be no problem at all.
- Welcome, sir.
What is going on?
I heard there was an error
in the cost estimation program.
Yes, thank you.
The CEO has allowed us to upload
the cost estimation program to the cloud…
only during the demonstration.
Then we can fix the error immediately…
and make real-time updates
to the demonstration files.
But won't there be a security risk?
It's only a part of the whole program,
not the entire system anyway.
Since it will only be for about
an hour during the demonstration.
It should be fine.
I'm using a secure cloud service…
and we can set a new password for access.
The password will only
be shared with Mr. Park…
since only the two of us
can fix the error right now.
The rest of you…
can just re-check the errors…
so that the demonstration
goes smoothly without any problem.
Yes, sir.
I uploaded the copied file in the cloud.
Please set the password.
I'm lazy to think. Let's just use this.
Then, I will modify the program from now on…
so please accept it and mark it as an error.
Yes, sir. I got that.
Mr. Lee will hand over
the core technology of J-BIMS…
to the broker at the demonstration event.
From the start to the end
of the demonstration…
please share with us all
notable activities of him.
If he becomes aware of what we know,
and tries to sabotage the situation…
we will assume that you leaked
the information to him…
and will immediately report you
as a technology theft accomplice.
While preparing for the demonstration…
were there any special requests made by him…
aside from violating security protocols?
People say AI will lead
to the extinction of humanity.
Do you know that you're contributing to that?
This way, sir.
Mr. Shin. Do you remember what I said?
Yes, I do.
I heard there was an error.
How did it go?
Rest assured.
The demonstration go on without a flaw.
The broker should be one of them.
How do you think he'll communicate
with the broker?
Using his phone would be best.
He's taking photos and
writing articles all by himself.
The working class are all suffering everywhere.
You must have been having a hard time lately.
Why? Do you want to blame it on Mr. Shin again?
No I wasn't.
I'm just getting emotional watching that.
- Are you getting attached to us?
- That's disgusting!
You're always thinking about nonsense.
Hello.
I am the CEO of JU Construction,
Hwang Se Woong.
Finally, the moment we've been
waiting for has arrived.
I am proud to introduce…
the innovative program…
that will propel JU Construction
to become a leading…
global construction company.
It is none other than J-BIMS.
He left his phone behind.
Hello. I am Lee Ji Hoon,
the lead developer of J-BIMS.
J-BIMS automatically
calculates the amount of materials…
costs required and the duration needed
for a construction site.
It has already achieved remarkable results
with its demo version.
At the current progress rate of 60%,
we have successfully reduced…
the total estimated construction cost
of 70 billion won by 2%.
Amounting to up to 1.4 billion won of savings.
At first glance, this figure
might seem insignificant.
But let's consider our annual average
order volume valued at 8 trillion won.
What does 2% of that makes?
It's 160 billion won.
There are two elements that are necessary
on the path to reaching our goal.
Passion and perseverance.
While it's okay to take a break,
we must never stop moving forward.
We proudly present the destination
of the journey we've embarked on.
The fully completed J-BIMS.
[Five W's and one H]
Who, when, where, what, how, and why.
We refer to this as the 'Five Ws and One H.'
Please remember this Five Ws and One H well.
It is the key keyword to experience
the fully completed J-BIMS.
That I will introduce to you.
Someone just accessed the cloud!
If you input the design blueprint like this…
the system provides a 3D rendering
of the completed building.
Additionally, it calculates maintenance
information for the post-construction phase…
and supports VR functionality…
offering a system that is…
What are you doing!
I have a question.
Here he goes again.
What do you think…
are you doing?
[The Auditors]
You are a broker who came to buy J-BIMS
that Lee Ji Hoon leaked.
Is it okay for someone to do this
with no evidence?
I am the CEO yet I am being
treated as a variable?
J Construction.
It's obviously talking about our company.
This is weird. Why is it not here?
Of course I took the aptitude test.
How would I pass if I didn't?
But there was no record of it.
Your asses will get fired soon.
I will look forward to that.
If the media obtains evidence
of hiring corruptions first…
the company will receive a bigger blow.