Yes, Dad.
I saw the article. You said you were okay, but are you sick again?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
How can I not worry about you when you're sick?
Do you have to make your parents worry when we live far away?
This is nothing to me, so please don't worry.
Don't you know people will come at you crazy when there's an issue?
You know we got harassed so much that we had to move this far away without you.
Dad.
Yes?
Did you eat?
Your mom and I ate something.
You should go to see the doctor, Seo Joon.
And be careful not to have more weird rumors.
Can't you ask me if I ate anything—
If we knew things would go this way, we wouldn't have let you become an actor.
I'm really regretting it right now.
At least I made a lot of money.
What? How can you talk about money at this moment?
When did we ask you for that?
I have to go filming, so I'll hang up now. Don't worry about me too much.
Seo Joon. Kang Seo Joon!
[To My Star 2]
Yes, Ji Woo?
Yes.
Seo Joon is not picking up his phone. Is he there?
He has an interview to do.
Didn't he go up to Seoul?
He told us that he'd come up tomorrow.
[Exclusive | Kang Seo Joon had an on-site attitude controversy, "A burdensome actor. We've always had to put him on a pedestal."]
[Dad: Don't forget to go to the hospital! Please let your mom and dad live peacefully.]
- What are you doing over there?
- What are you doing outside? It's cold!
Did you see Kang Seo Joon by any chance?
I saw him earlier.
When? Did he say anything about where he was going?
He didn't say anything about that, but he asked me if I went hiking with you.
He asked if you went hiking with Han Ji Woo?
Yes. So I told him we usually went to Yongjin Mountain.
What's going on? His car is also not here, so he must have gone to Seoul.
Do you want some fried chicken—
It would've been a problem if Han Ji Woo had come to eat this with us.
There's only one chicken.
Please! Why are you saying it like that?
I mean, if he agreed to come earlier, I would've bought two chickens.
But it's too late now.
So I'm saying my baby can eat as much as you want!
This cartilage part is delicious! So don't forget to eat this part, too.
Yes, sure.
But I wonder what happened for his eyes to look that scary?
Da Kyeong...
Da Kyeong!
It's okay. It's okay.
Since it has been five years,
I thought I would win.
I thought old memories would win...
But I lost.
Because of Han Ji Woo,
I studied hard and did my best to excel...
I tried so much to come back in perfect shape!
Doing because of someone is not important.
What's important is that we came all this way.
You did great. Okay?
So please don't cry.
You cooked this completely.
I told you to make the pan hot first,
close the lid, and turn off the heat. Then it'll come out half-cooked yolks—
Forget about it. Please don't say it anymore.
You promised not to criticize me anymore.
Okay, I won't do it.
Are you done cooking now?
It's healthier to eat this way.
Okay, D chord.
Try it. I taught you this before.
This is the D chord.
And G chord.
Let's try it now.
Get ready.
Let's play!
♪  When you look at my eyes  ♪
♪ Your eyes are shining more ♪
♪  When you touch my cheeks  ♪
♪  Your cheeks are getting blushed ♪
♪  When our fingers touched  ♪
♪  You are biting your lips  ♪
You are pretty stubborn.
- If you decide on clothing and wear it accordingly, it's easy.
- ♪ You are already falling asleep ♪
Ji Woo, stay right there.
It's perfect right now.
I think it'll pop out immediately.
Please stop it.
♪  It means I love you  ♪
♫ At this moment, when I'm looking at you ♫
♫ I hope every day that's touching you ♫
♪  Happy birthday to you!  ♪
♪  Happy birthday to my dear Han Ji Woo  ♪
Happy birthday!
When did you prepare all this?
Look over there.
Ta-da!
♫  It means I love you  ♫
Make a wish. You have to blow out the candles at once.
♫  The feelings that I can't hide  ♫
You can wear this on your finger,
and sometimes you can put it on a necklace like this.
Also, I have one more gift for you.
- Another one?
- Come out with me. It's outside.
♫  Will you look into my eyes?  ♫
♫  At this moment, when I'm looking at you  ♫
Let me not wear it for once!
I think it'll look great on you. Just try it once.
Just once. Please!
♫  The way you are looking at me  ♫
It really looks good on you!
It really does.
♫  I don't want to let them go  ♫
♫  You, you, I love you  ♫
♫  When I look up at the night sky  ♫
♫  You and I are twinkling  ♫
I want to try it.
So...
what is it you want to say?
So what I want to say is–
Say it. Look into my eyes and say it.
Ji Woo, you're so charming.
Was I really bad?
You think that was good? Let's just eat.
That's why I said I don't want to do it.
I'll save this.
No. I said no.
Please... It's just so cute.
- Don't do this.
- You look really good on the screen.
Ji Woo, I think you should be an actor.
You said I can't act.
I think you'd be good in campus genres.
Don't tease me. You said I suck.
It looks like you're wearing a school uniform.
You tape it.
I'll record.
From now on, you practice alone.
Don't.
Kang Seo Joon!
Yoo Ha, eat a lot.
My favorite food is chicken.
She's always asking me to buy chicken.
Excuse me.
- Yes, Seong Yoon.
- Yes, Reporter Kim.
I checked the IP address of where the rumor post originated, and it's Dacham Village.
Then it means the possibility of the person being one of the villagers is likely.
Yes. I think you could make the matter worse by pressing charges.
[Controversy on Kang Seon Joon's attitude on location, "Stressful actor... always had to be at his beck and call"]
I said no. Kang Seo Joon isn't like that.
We'll conduct an interview soon–
So, I'm saying, we'll make our statement.
It's late right now! Don't we get to rest at night?
What?
I said you can go home.
Hurry up and go home.
Hurry up and go. It's okay.
That's not it...
CEO, I'm sorry to say this in the middle of all this, but
I have something to say.
What? What's wrong now?
What is it?
I must tell you this by tomorrow.
Actually, I got an offer to be an idol.
Two months ago.
What?
D. C. H.
Could it be a person's initials?
Which last name starts with a "D"? Surname Do?
But no one in our village has the surname of Do.
Or CH could be one syllable.
Do Choon?
But I don't think the elders would've used the internet, though.
Isn't it like this?
DCH is Dacham Elementary ID.
My ID is also dch280102.
There are so many similar IDs, though.
Then what does this "28" mean?
(T/N: The way she said it sounded like a curse word)
2-8. What does 28 mean?
The year you enter the school.
The year you enter school?
Then what's this "shin-con-dot-con"?
Yoo Ha, you said there aren't that many classmates in your class, right?
There are five of us.
But none of my friends would do that.
But we should still let them know about this clue. You never know.
It could be someone who works at Dacham Elementary or someone connected to the school.
Give me a hair tie.
Well, fine. You're...
pretty handsome, and you look like an idol.
But did you always want to do it?
I was actually interested in it.
You were always clubbing. No wonder...
I see.
You were dancing your heart out at Seo Joon's birthday party. Your moves were different.
Fine. I see. That's what happened.
You've been missing a lot lately, saying you're busy with something.
That's right. That's what happened.
- I'm sorry–
- No, no, no.
Why should you be sorry?
It's fine.
I'll be fine. I'm just a little disappointed.
It's such an important matter.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Never mind. I feel bad that I couldn't pay more attention to you.
Right.
Hello.
I'm just calling to discuss Ji Woo's incident.
Rather than us handling it on our own, you said you know people in the press.
Dot-con. What's sin-con-dot-con?
Sin-con-dot-con is...
So, you know sin-con-dot-con?
That's a phrase used in video games.
"Sin''s control, got control."
(T/N: Sin here, pronounced "shin," means god/deity)
Sin's control, got control...
- Scared me.
- Geez...
No way!
- Yoo Ha, what is it? What is it?
- What?
Kang Seo Joon!
Geez...
What the heck?
What?
Han Ji Woo!
Hey!
Hey, Han Ji Woo!
Wh-What's going on?
Han Ji Woo, are you pulling my leg?
I don't have a cell phone.
911...
I'm okay.
Call other people.
They think you went missing. They're all worried about you.
They could've already called the police.
DCH!
Come on out.
Hey, sweetie. I'm just calling to tell you about what the reporter said.
Yeah, yeah. I'm not bothering you, am I?
So, you knew about it already?
Yeah.
By chance, do you have time next week? No, huh?
No, huh?
I keep asking while you're so busy, huh?
It's all soggy.
Why did you bother coming out all the way here?
- I–
- I'm sorry, but...
I'd like you to leave.
I want to be alone.
I didn't toss the ring and the necklace.
I couldn't. I didn't toss them but buried them over there.
So...
I threw them away already, though.
We're finished.
You're not going to say you realized everything now, so to take you back. Right?
No way...
And what else? Just because you came here,
you're not thinking that I'd take you back. Right?
There's got to be an end to being so pathetic, you know.
Well, people who put in their best don't have any regrets.
You have nothing to say, huh?
Leave then. Don't disrupt my rest.
Sorry.
[Apple Popcorn]
Geez... what time is it?
10:00 a.m.
Oh, it's Saturday today. Right?
Yeah, don't worry.
I got so scared.
But shouldn't we tell Han Ji Woo that we caught the culprit?
Where is he...
Han Ji Woo...
The phone is turned off. You'll be connected to voicemail after the beep.
What the heck?
[Ti Aspetto | Italian Restaurant | Closed]
My break is over.
Ji Woo, I told you to come in and wait.
Where the hell were you?
So, first of all, did you see the article?
I saw it. We can just ignore it.
Let it go. It's not the first time.
What?
Can't you see how tired I am? Hurry up and leave.
Let's talk later.
You said not to sit back.
Why are you sitting back when it's not true?
I'm sorry, but it's true.
Let's do an interview.
I don't want to.
Kang Seo Joon, let's do an interview.
I said I don't want to!
Leave, both of you.
Leave. I mean it.
Did you decide to be a baby now?
Who was that? Yoo Ha?
She wouldn't even be acting like you, Bro!
Do you know this?
Baek Ho Min! That jerk is...
Forget it! Forget it! I'm leaving.
How about you?
I'll stay for now.
It's the end of the world.
Going back and forth from Gyeongsang-do to Seoul.
Why all the trouble?
- Hello, CEO.
- Get in.
Did your audition go well?
Yes.
It feels strange sitting in here, CEO.
Why? You'll soon be sitting in the back.
Open the glove compartment.
The white one.
- This?
- Yeah.
Your severance pay will be paid separately. You'll have trouble making money in the future. Take that for now.
Don't get scared, man.
CEO.
Let's just be on equal footing.
Call me Jack.
My English name is Jack.
I'm sorry I couldn't pay attention to you all this time.
No. I should've done a better job.
Hey, you did a really great job.
Seo Joon's previous manager went home in three hours and 45 minutes.
Let's go.
Let's eat something yummy. I'm feeling down.
Good luck, Ho Min...
wherever you go.
Sorry.
I didn't know the door would open.
I think I stunk, so I went and took a shower.
We didn't get to eat, so I was going to cook for you with this.
Who do you think you are?
Why would you cook?
I went so far away, but...
if I typed in your name on the internet, I could find out what you were up to right away.
I kept seeing you around Seoul, so I ran away.
But it was the same in the end.
I'll stop running away now.
As for me,
if you keep pushing me away,
I can't...
continue after you as you did.
To where you are.
What? Is this a threat?
No.
It's a request.
Please hug me.
♫  The night has come. Still, like a habit  ♫
♫  I look up to the sky with a sigh  ♫
♫  The dark night sky that's like my heart  ♫
♫  And you are still there  ♫
♫ Are you looking at me? ♫
[Epilogue]
[To My Stars 2]
♫ So that I can't lose you ♫
♫ Please shine even brighter for me ♫
♫  The reason why I wait for the night  ♫
♫  The reason why I am waiting for you  ♫
♫  Even if the morning comes  ♫
♫  You are still there at the same place  ♫
♫  The reason why I wait for the night  ♫