AI generated
AI generated F
I AI generated
AI generated
3,000 light cavalry
will divide into two forces,
AI generated
flanking the enemy,
and attack.
AI generated
Divide and attack.
| AI generated
AI generated
Qianyu was ordered to go to the southeast corner of the supply camp.
Captain Han and the others who were about to leave the camp have all been shot dead.
AI generated.
A detailed map of our camp's weak points,
and General Gu's daily schedule.
AI generated.
You failed to discipline your subordinates.
What is the penalty according to the law?
I am only the army supervisor.
Captain Han is actually under General Gu Shanhe's command.
AI generated.
How can you say I failed to discipline my subordinates?
Mr. Xue, your plan is brilliant.
AI generated.
I admire you.
But you accuse me of colluding with the enemy.
AI generated.
Based on a forged silk letter by someone unknown,
and a few corpses that can no longer speak?
AI generated.
Today you can kill Captain Han for colluding with the enemy. Tomorrow,
whoever doesn't listen to your orders as the acting general.
Is it me, Wang Huiyue, who wants to defect to the enemy in this camp,
AI generated.
or is there someone who wants to borrow the Canglang army's sword
to seize sole power?
AI generated.
And I cannot help but suspect,
did you also kill General Gu?
AI generated.
Did you also kill General Gu?
Now that General Gu is not here,
AI generated.
as generals of Dasheng, you all should know.
Not to mention that the generals in this tent were all promoted by General Gu,
AI generated.
even according to military law,
the army honors the commander's orders above all else.
The body of your colluding deployment, which you just confessed to, is not yet cold.
[AI generated]
How dare you twist the truth here?
Report! The Golden Wolf Banner of the Azure Wolf King's headquarters has divided into two groups.
[AI generated]
Thousands of light cavalry each
are detouring along the riverbed towards the southwest and southeast,
[AI generated]
intending to flank us from behind
and surround our army.
[AI generated]
To the southeast, the Feiyu Camp!
The remaining 300 crossbowmen
[AI generated]
abandon the fort immediately!
Travel light, take all the arrows, and secure the pass.
[AI generated]
Block the riverbed from a high vantage point.
Do not retreat a single step until the arrows run out.
Hear my order! Feiyu Camp, follow me to secure the pass!
[AI generated]
Hurry!
Hurry! Ignore everything, just charge through!
[AI generated]
AI-generated
The enemy has already seized the pass.
We can't get through.
AI-generated
We can't break through.
Hmph, this time,
you must have run out of ko threats, right?
AI-generated
You forgot about Chen Gan.
If we can start this fire one more time,
our army will have a chance to turn the tide.
Our army will have a chance to turn the tide.
AI-generated
Take this lamp oil and saltpeter, detour to
the cliff, and attack with fire from above.
AI-generated
Attack with fire from above the cliff.
.AI generated.
Rest assured, Captain Chen.
AI generated.
After this battle,
you'll be the God of Fire in the army.
.AI generated.
You'll be the God of Fire in the army.
AI generated.
You have high EQ.
| AI generated L
AI generated
You have high EQ.
What's your name?
AI generated.
.AI generated.
What's your name?
He said it for me.
AI generated.
I saw you take a sip of kerosene just now.
.AI generated.
.AI generated
AI generated.
How did you know I drank kerosene?
The rest of you follow me and sneak in through the trail. Let's go!
AI generated.
.AI generated.
I heard the King
AI generated.
.AI generated.
I heard the King
let a Han dancer go.
.AI generated.
AI generated.
let a Han dancer go.
Yeah, and apparently she's an assassin.
AI generated.
Attempted to assassinate the King.
.AI generated.
AI generated.
How could he let her go?
.AI generated
.AI generated.
How could he let her go?
She should have been sent to the rear for us to enjoy.
.AI generated.
AI generated.
She should have been sent to the rear for us to enjoy.
They should be sent to the rear for us to enjoy.
[AI Generated]
Hahaha.
AI Generated
Words.
Damn it, watch where you throw that!
AI Generated
AI-generated
Lang
Are we staying here to die? Retreat!
AI-generated
Do you trust Chen Gan that much?
Do you know why I trust Chen Gan?
AI-generated
Because he is someone written in the history books.
History books? What history books?
AI-generated
Never mind, you wouldn't understand even if I told you.
Then tell me something I would understand.
AI-generated
Supervisor Wang, actually, you guessed right.
I am Shen Wenyuan, the Grand Astrologer of the current dynasty.
AI-generated
[AI Generated]
Why aren't you writing your Qing history at the Shiqu Pavilion in Shangjing,
why are you here in this desperate place in the Northern Desert wielding weapons
[AI Generated]
and commanding the army?
It's a long story.
[AI Generated]
Besides, you wouldn't understand even if I told you.
Because here,
to you,
[AI Generated]
the name Shen Wenyuan
is more lethal than Xue Gai or any other identity,
[AI Generated]
and more useless.
What do you mean?
Because the Grand Astrologer should be in Shangjing,
[AI Generated]
but is posing as an alchemist at the front lines,
holding the commander's seal.
[AI Generated]
This is a serious crime.
I, Gu Shanhe, and those who recommended me will be doomed eternally.
[AI Generated]
Therefore, telling you this secret
means you will never leave this camp alive
[AI Generated]
to report to anyone as Army Inspector Wang,
whether it's the imperial court
or your brother-in-law, Tie Xiangquan.
[AI Generated]
You...
You're going to silence me?
[AI Generated]
If I wanted to kill you, I would have done it already.
AI generated.
Five thousand against eighty thousand.
What difference does it make if I kill you or not?
AI generated.
Compared to this,
I care more about how Gu Shanhe is doing right now.
AI generated.
Gu
Alas.
AI generated.
Can we win this war?
General, it is indeed a sandstorm.
AI generated.
Under these conditions, we cannot proceed.
The best plan is to corral the horses and tie them up.
AI generated.
Tie up.
Never speak of wasted ambitions.
AI generated.
Throw down the pen and pierce through the smoke of war.
Chu sky is vast.
AI generated.
Dying on the battlefield is common,
just say I was here.
AI generated.
Fighting only to keep our homeland free of evil.
In this mortal world, drink wine with courage.
AI generated.
Let me sing a song for you from the beginning,
let's sing the Song of the Great Wind together.
Copyright Hainan Jiangxing Film and Television Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
AI generated.