[One Percent of Something]
[Ha Seok Jin]
[Jeon So Min]
Joo Jin Mo / Jo Jae Ryong
Kim Heong Min / Lim Do Yoon
Kim Seon Hyeok / Seo Eun Chae / Choi Seong Jae
Lee Hae In / Baek Seung Heon
[One Percent of Something]
She's clearly here for a marriage meeting.
Wow, their staff is really well trained!
It's my heart.
Then I won't decline your offer and I'll enjoy this.
I actually really like apples.
I wonder what kind of woman she is that the Chairman fell for her so hard?
Probably a nine-tailed fox.
(Korean legend: fox that assumes woman's form to prey on men)
Hello.
People like you are the absolute worst.
I feel the exact same way!
If he marries you, Teacher Kim Da Hyeon—
- Stop spouting nonsense!
- No way!
Then the contract has been made.
Congratulations, Grandfather.
This time you seem to have won. It’s not over yet.
It’ll probably still be that way in the future.
Like why? Why does it have to be this woman? What is this?
She looks so innocent... how did she get my grandpa to fall for her? What is she?
New type of gold digger?
With this face?
Ah... It'd be nice if he really was the grandson of Seong Hyeon Group's chairman.
That way, he could make Ji Su their main model and help him out.
Grandpa, since I came here, I've done as much as I could.
It shows that we aren’t meant to be.
This is just a coincidence. It’s not fate.
My grandfather wants us to get married.
The woman you introduced to me wants the three of us to talk.
The three of us to talk? Why should I participate?
Then who else would she talk to? This woman says she really doesn’t know you.
Take care of it yourself. That’s your mission, too.
Do you want me to carry you inside instead?
♫ Just thinking about it tells me it’s right ♫
Isn't he here yet?
I'm here.
Oh no!
But why do you keep asking me to meet you?
He said he would bear it even if we didn't marry.
In return, if we have a serious relationship as a male and a female for the next six months—
E-Excuse me.
I don't know what your grandfather thinks, but I have no intention of dating you.
But even so, would all of that money be mine?
Who knows what they are up to, when you know what kind of people they are?
Do you... call your aunt in Canada often?
Uh... No Hyeon Wu?
Ah, yes.
Hello, Miss Da Hyeon.
You know?
Mother,
Yes, yes.
I think I need to leave first today.
Is there a problem?
Yes.
A very big problem.
Are you close to the broadcasting station's PD?
Yes. He is my schoolmate, so we're in touch once in a while.
Teacher Kim Da Hyeon?
Oh my!
There's a small misunderstanding when a woman and a man date...
Anyway, it's really hard to date.
Why do you have to meet other guys even through a blind date?
It will all be resolved if you just date me.
That's complicated and suspicious.
We don't have to make it complicated.
What is there to be suspicious about? It seems like you need a man, Teach—
—er, and I need you.
We need an indoor gym so the kids can play indoors when it's raining, and I'd like to have a school bus.
Oh, and I'd like to have a big mirror in the multipurpose room.
I'm in charge of the dance club.
Contract complete. Don't change your mind later.
Great. Let's write a contract.
Keep your promise.
Of course.
But a promise is meaningful when both of us keep it.
I'm not sure if I can trust that guy.
Ji Su? Who is that?
That woman. No, I mean,
the thing that teacher wants.
♫ I can't help but feel regret ♫
♫ To meet you more politely ♫
♫ I talk with you even without you there all night ♫
♫ The words surround me ♫
Oh yeah, do you want to go eat pork belly?
♫ even though those words are foreign now ♫
You're worrying about the next two hours,
but I'm worried about the next six months.
Get out now.
Don’t hold it...
Pretend not to know me if possible. Don't even turn your face this way.
What, what...?
Stay still.
Doze off one more time if you want to know what I'm going to do next.
What... what are you going to do?
Close your eyes and I will kiss you.
Don't even touch me.
I didn't think about it back then, but there's something missing in that contract.
What is missing?
Physical contact.
Da Da? Why Da Da?
Is it because you run around saying "dadada"?
Da Da... it suits you.
Do I have to call him? He’s going to talk about ramen again.
By chance, are you looking for this?
I thought you were gone. Thank you.
No way I would just leave. It's not like I lack the sense.
We’re moving a little fast for a first date. Well, if that’s what Da Da really wants...
What are you doing?
Hey...
Come on!
Oh, really!
Give it to me.
Oh, my.
♫ Beautiful, oh you are beautiful ♫
♫ Beautiful, beautiful ♫
♫ You are beautiful ♫
Lee Jae In? A beautiful woman?
[SH Alpenzia CEO Lee Jae In Accompanied by Beautiful Woman at Concert]
Ah, this guy really...
Well... "beautiful woman..."
That's true.
True... but...
Is this because of that kiss? I'm sure that it must have felt nice for you too, though.
Are teachers supposed to be this violent?
We teach the students to do this when they encounter a shameless pervert.
I know how to kick a vital spot as well. Shall I try?
Let's rewrite the contract.
What would you rewrite?
No two-timing. None. No putting on an innocent act only to stab me in the back later. None.
You will not see any other man besides me.
So you're not going to see women like Lee Su Jin, Gang Mi Ra, or Yeon Seo Hee anymore?
You've never dated a guy before, have you?
That's not true!
Then did you only ever date eunuchs?
What a relief.
What?
You haven't fallen for me.
There isn't a single person on this planet who tries to be frugal with their time while seeing someone they like.
- Did you borrow that?
- Yeah.
You should've borrowed another one!
What for?
♫ Love with you, like early morning sunshine ♫
♫ It spreads within me ♫
I'll leave.
What are you doing?
Kissing.
♫ Falling in love with you, like the scent of flowers in the spring ♫
♫ That keeps tickling me, I want to see you ♫
♫ whenever I want ♫
♫ Please stay inside my heart, my love ♫
♫ I'll open leave it open for you, I will only listen to you ♫
♫ I will be where you can rest ♫
♫ Oh boy, you're so sweet, so pure, my therapy ♫
♫ I'm in love with you, like the first snowfall
♫ You fall into my arms, so I can hold you ♫
Episode 8 - A Confession of Sorts
Stay Here, at My House, by My Side
CEO.
See me for a moment, Team Leader Gang.
W-Why does he want to see me?
Man, I'm so scared.
Me too.
Make sure to come back alive.
Can you look into this for me, please?
I'm sure Grandfather has noticed this as well.
I think we'll have to take some countermeasures.
Actually, I've been bothered by many things since the fake bomb threat last time.
Why are you entrusting this to me, sir?
Because you're the only one I can trust.
You'll have to really pick a side and stick to it now.
My grandfather may be strong-willed right now,
but I'm planning to be even stronger-willed than him for the next 30 years or so.
I-I-I'm with you, sir...
Yes, of course.
You can leave now.
I feel like our school has a lot of demo classes.
I know, right.
[Health Education/ Experience Study/ Community Training/ Field Study/ Educational Programs to Prevent School Violence / Disaster Safety Training]
♫ That I love you and you are the only one ♫
♫ Hug me sweetly ya, ya, ya ♫
♫ Everything will change, ya ya ya ♫
Yes.
I'm sorry, but I don't think I'll be able to see you today.
Are you going to keep doing this to me? You canceled on me last time, too!
That's why we took a walk!
I'm busy too, you know! I have to prepare for my demo classes,
and my girls are competing in a dance contest next month.
So...
Are you saying that that's more important than me?
Of course.
Let's forget about today and meet up on the weekend instead.
This isn't a favor I'm asking of you, this is a request.
Oh, right... Isn't it your turn to come down this time? That makes it fair.
Kick the ball to us!
Yes, then do so.
Thank you.
Here you go.
Anyone that doesn't have one?
All right, guys. Today, we'll be reading a biography book and writing a book report about it.
I want you to write about what you think, feel, and get impressed, okay?
Yes!
What are you doing here?
I'm here to study. You told me to come. To be fair.
Even so, who told you to come in here—
This is a classroom.
I'm visiting a class. The Vice Principal said it would be okay.
You're not a parent.
Then tell him I'm not a parent.
Goodbye!
Goodbye.
Mister, why aren't you leaving? Class is over.
Oh, I'm waiting for your teacher.
There she is.
Mister, are you our teacher's boyfriend?
Oh, that's not it, guys!
Yes, I'm her boyfriend.
You shouldn't lie to the kids.
He's teacher's boyfriend.
Dong Wu, let's go. You too, Dong In. What did I tell you?
I told you to beware of strangers. Don't ever talk to strangers, understand?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Goodbye.
Yes, bye!
What? What's wrong now?
Rumors will go all around the school now! What are you going to do about it?
What do you want me to do? Take responsibility? You don't want to marry me, though.
Marriage, yeah right. I'll meet you at the hotel next time.
I'm going to hold a big sign with your name highlighted over there!
Try it if you want. The reporters would love that. Would it be okay with you?
Oh, really. How cunning he is!
This area is really quiet. I like it.
It's because the kids are all gone.
Transportation links might be a little inconvenient, but I think this place is good for the kids.
I'd love to build a resort here.
What the...This place is good for the kids. Don't even think about it!
This land belongs to the Department of Education.
Oh, my!
What?
You're not getting on?
You like doing everything kids do.
You've never been on one of these, have you?
I haven't either since I've grown up.
When I was a kid, it was really fun.
My dad pushed me so high.
♫ I’ll only whisper to you ♫
Oh, you're so heavy!
You're really heavy.
Come here.
I'm sorry! Don't come!
I'm coming up.
Do whatever you want. Whether you're coming up— Oh, no!
You're up here. Wait a minute. Oh my!
♫ I’m in love with you ♫
Where are you running away?
♫ Like sunshine early in the morning ♫
♫ You spread inside me ♫
♫ My heart is filled with the color of you ♫
♫ Isn’t it about time to confess ♫
♫ I think it's about time for you to be able to say yes ♫
♫ It's not as easy as I thought ♫
♫ Looking into your clear eyes, my heart flutters ♫
♫ How should I start over? ♫
♫ Whether it would be awkward or not ♫
♫ My head is such a mess ♫
You have to come to me next time.
Well...
You can also come to the hotel.
You didn't lock the door?
Of course I did. What is that?
Stay here.
Oh my!
Thief...
It must have been a thief!
Oh no, how could this be?
Are you okay?
It's okay, as long as no one got hurt.
There wasn't much to steal here.
Yeah.
Let's leave now.
Leave where? I need to clean this place up.
Then, you're thinking of sleeping here tonight?
Just pack up some of your clothes.
Your house...
What?
It's a bit empty.
Ah, I don't like being crowded with things.
Do you want to drink anything?
What do you have?
Alcohol, water... Do you want it?
Where is the bathroom? I want to wash my hands.
Ah, over there...
You're safe here, so take it easy and don't worry too much.
Something is off.
No, it didn't seem like there was anything expensive there.
Still, even if it were a petty theft... almost nothing was stolen.
Yes, I heard the police came too.
But please investigate further separately.
Yes.
What else is here except Zenga (a game)?
Acting all innocent.
What are you up to?
You are not changing?
It's a bit big since it's mine, but it should be more comfortable.
You are not leaving? I thought you were going to the hotel, since you have a lot of stuff to do.
I mean, I don't have to.
Wouldn't it be better to stay together
than be alone?
You're not going to leave, are you?
My house is pretty big and there are no bad guys here.
Well, good for you with this big house.
But are you sure there are no bad guys here?
What?
I didn't see it.
Did anyone say anything?
Ah, I really didn't see anything.
You want to sleep together here?
Can't we?
You seem like such a player.
So?
Speaking honestly, I'm swaying a little bit...
I don't think I can do this.
Why not?
Tomorrow morning,
one of us might regret it.
I don't think I will be the one to regret it.
Anyway, fine.
You go to bed first. I'm going to work some more and then go to bed.
I'm not going to the hotel now, though.
Oh, it's me, Da Da!
How has he not moved at all since he got there?
Am I not so attractive? Is this good or bad?
You work on your hotel stuff.
I'm going to build a hotel.
You are not sleeping?
I need to rebuild this hotel. It fell down...
Then you should have called me. It's my specialty.
Oh, and this is not for building, it's for taking pieces out.
How many bottles did you have?
It's against the rules to do this all alone.
What rules?
Do you want a sip?
It's raining outside.
I don't think it's quick shower this time.
Yeah, guess not.
Don't touch me.
Don't even think about "it," either.
I got it.
But really, can't I?
A guy who touches a drunk woman
is not even human.
So that's why you drank all this?
No.
I was wondering what I'm doing at a man's house.
Why did I come here?
What?
Because your house got robbed.
That's why I invited you.
Perhaps...
I've...
fallen for you.
I like having kisses with you.
Just sleep for today
You can sleep like this
after confessing your love to me?
♫ Like that, we went a few days without contact ♫
♫ but instead of feeling hurt, I worried more ♫
♫ Wondering if you were sick or not ♫
♫ Have something bad going on ♫
♫ What do I do about this fleeting feeling? ♫
♫ Did I make you sad? ♫
Tomorrow morning
I'll probably be the one to regret.
Perhaps...
I've...
fallen for you.
Ah, what do I do?
I like having kisses with you.
Alcohol is an enemy! Are you crazy, Kim Da Da?
Aigoo.
Puppy! Oh! Hey!
Hold on...
Baby... baby!
What is she doing?
Hey! Come here!
Aigoo, good boy... oh no, I'm in trouble!
Oh, Jae In!
Jae In, are you okay?
Jae In? Are you... dead?
No, I'm not dead.
But what the heck were you doing?
Well... thank you.
Take care of yourself, not the puppy!
Did you see it?
Since I saw it, you ended up hurting this much. Why would you dive from up there, being so ignorant?
If you're that uncoordinated, you should really at least try to be careful.
Who are you calling uncoordinated? I'm quick on my feet.
Yeah, right, I saw how quick on your feet you were. Get up.
Oh no! What do I do... are you okay?
- Shoes, shoes... - Oh, it hurts.
Go inside.
You came early?
Yes, something feels off lately.
What?
SH Mall stocks have been jumping up too much.
Well, you know how stocks can go up and down.
Don't worry. It's good for us anyways.
Don't think about that and keep your focus on that school teacher.
Oh, it smarts.
I'm fine, but your shoulder... Shouldn't you see a doctor?
Just stay put, I'm irritated from lack of sleep last night.
Why didn't you sleep well—
You're always irritated though.
Ouch, ow... it hurts!
Of course.
Would you be human if you didn't hurt like this after falling?
What?
Nothing.
But Jae In.
Don't change all of a sudden.
They say you'll die if you do that. (Korean proverb)
Really.
Why isn't he reacting?
Oh, it smarts.
Knock-knock. Does it hurt a lot?
It's a minor sprain. It'll get better soon.
Oh, no, what should I do?
Come on, let me see.
I don't think it's minor. It hurts, right? You can't even raise your arm.
Let's go see a doctor.
I don't know how to do this.
You would still be better than me now though.
You might regret this.
♫ I'll only shine for you, I'll only whisper to you ♫
♫ I will be the smile that spreads on your lips ♫
♫ Oh girl, you're soft, you are so fragrant, my therapy ♫
♫  I'm in love with you like sunshine early in the morning ♫
♫  You spread inside me  ♫
♫  My heart is filled with the color of you, falling in love with you ♫
It says that the first opportunity would be given to Jae In.
That means if Jae In fails, there will be another alternative plan.
That would be you, Tae Ha.
Where is the contract?
Some kinds of problems occurred, right?
Is that why you were going to sleep at the hotel yesterday?
Do you feel like you're going to fall for me?
I think I'll grow attached to you.
Then you can come together. Everyone is curious about you anyway.
Jae In!