Sung Hoon...
was Number 11?
(Calls, My Brother)
(My Brother)
The person you have called can't come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Hey, Seok Gu.
Can you track my brother's current location?
Yes, right now.
(Episode 11: The Ultimate Suspicion)
The controversial appointment...
of the Minister of Health and Welfare has finally ended.
Candidate Na Guk Hee, who received criticism because of her son,
has become the new Minister of Health and Welfare.
Newly appointed Minister Na started as a civil servant...
worked at the Ministry of Health and Welfare...
to become an expert in welfare administration.
She constructed welfare systems to help the socially weak...
What kind of nonsense is that?
What do you mean by adoption?
I don't know what you heard from where, but it's not true.
You and your brother...
are both my biological sons whom I gave birth to.
This photo is of Sung Hoon in front of the orphanage he lived in.
Are you still going to deny it?
Where...
did you get this?
Why are you lying to me?
Is there a reason why you must hide that Sung Hoon was adopted?
Well...
That's because...
Mom!
It was all for your brother's sake.
Even if the world has changed,
if people hear that he was adopted, people will become prejudiced.
That's still how it is here.
Your mom and I didn't want people to see Sung Hoon like that.
We wanted to raise him well.
There's nothing more to it.
How did you find out about Hope Welfare Center?
I don't know. How did we find out about it?
Well...
We found out about it purely by chance.
The director got arrested,
so they didn't have anyone to run it any longer.
We heard there were older kids there that had nowhere to go.
To be honest,
I was hesitant because Sung Hoon was an older kid.
But...
But, Sung Jun...
Do you know...
why I decided to adopt your brother?
It was because of you.
I felt bad for you because you were always alone.
So you wouldn't have to be lonely.
Sung Jun.
This may come as a big shock to you.
But just forget about all of it, okay?
At this point, what does it matter that Sung Hoon is adopted?
For 20 years, we've been a family.
And we will continue being a family in the future.
Just forget about it?
What does it matter? We're a family?
For the past 20 years, I...
For the past 20 years? What?
I thought...
you two weren't my biological parents.
I thought I was the one who was adopted!
What do you mean?
Why would you think such a thing?
I know, right? I also wonder...
why I came to think that way.
I don't know who I am.
My goodness.
About the adoption... Sung Jun doesn't know yet, right?
- My goodness. - It's so funny.
- Right, honey? - Gosh, cut it out.
Sung Jun.
Just don't do anything and sit still, okay?
That's how you can help your mom.
Because you always cause trouble.
How long must we be worried about you?
If Sung Hoon said you did good, that means you did.
Right?
Aren't you embarrassed about making Mom and Dad worry...
at your age?
Behave yourself.
Hey, Seok Gu.
Judge Ryu's phone is turned off,
so we can't trace it.
But we did confirm the last location it was used in.
Where is the last location?
It's the Children's Center.
And Sung Jun.
We found traces of blood in the yard of the Children's Center.
- Traces of blood? - Yes.
Let me talk to him.
Hold on. I'll put Captain on the line.
Thanks.
Hey, Sung Jun.
There's not a lot of blood. It's only a little.
It's near the front doors.
There's a security camera near the entrance,
but someone has damaged it on purpose.
I think the culprit targeted Eun Ki from the beginning and broke in.
The streets that lead from the main road to the center...
are here and here.
They're the only two.
There was only one car that came out of this street around 9pm.
Should I look into the car?
No, I know whose car this is.
Please track the direction this car went in.
Oh, okay.
I can't track it any further.
It seems the car entered an area that doesn't have security cameras.
That's the last location where the suspected car was caught on camera.
Where's Eun Ki?
Where is Eun Ki?
Why?
Do you think I might've abducted her...
and buried her in the ground?
I found it dead on the road.
I couldn't just pass by it.
Detective Ryu.
Yes, Captain.
I found Jo Eun Ki.
Yes, I'll tell you the details later.
- What happened? - Well, the thing is...
If something like that happened,
you should've called me or gone to the police.
I told her not to tell you.
I can't trust the police.
What?
And what about you? Why did you go to the center?
I had something to discuss with Eun Ki.
About what?
Why?
Is it a secret I'm not supposed to know?
Who on earth are you?
Why do you have so many secrets?
So what is it you want to say?
Hope Welfare Center.
Number 11.
That's you.
Why did you hide it?
I asked why you hid it!
Why did I hide it?
What would happen if I revealed that I was Number 11?
It's obvious everyone will suspect me.
If you had been me, would you have been able to say it?
Can you really not trust me?
Even you are suspicious that I might be the culprit.
Fine. I'm Number 11.
If I could erase it, I'd erase all of it.
That's how terrible those memories are.
Sure, Hope Welfare Center.
I was there.
But...
I'm not the culprit. Whether you believe it or not,
that choice is up to you.
(Caller ID Restricted)
(It's because of you.)
(Caller ID Restricted, May 22, 12:44am)
Kwon Yu Na.
She's in danger.
- What about her? - Where did you last see her?
She was at the center. We talked and she left...
Darn it.
Keep calling Yu Na.
- I'll go that way. - Okay.
Yu Na!
Eun Ki.
No.
(Muyeong Police Station)
Why did the culprit send you that text?
He must've been angry.
I'd thwarted him.
Why did you go to the center?
I was going to apply to be Kwon Yu Na's patron.
Eun Ki would know better than anyone what kind of help Yu Na needed.
So you went to the center...
and happened to see the culprit?
Did you see their face?
- No. - You can't even guess who it was?
Not at all.
When did you find out Yoon Jae was dead?
Shortly after I was adopted.
You went to Hope Welfare Center with Yoon Jae's older sister.
Where is she now?
I don't know.
We parted as soon as we reached the welfare center,
and I never heard from her since.
What about Number 12?
Do you know anything about him?
No.
In that place,
we were forbidden to talk about ourselves.
(Learn and Enlighten Yourself to Serve Your True Purpose)
The place was a huge prison.
We were small, powerless prisoners serving a life sentence.
Every day, morning to night,
we were put to work at an incineration plant.
Whether you were young or sick, there was no exception.
All we got to eat was doenjang broth with rotten vegetables...
and a ball of rice.
We were always hungry.
Kids who died of an illness or a beating...
disappeared before anyone knew.
The lucky ones got buried in the mountain.
(Muyeong University School of Medicine)
The unlucky ones...
got donated to the university to be dissected, we were told.
(Thank you for giving way.)
Why was I stupid enough...
to put up with it?
Of course,
we tried to escape.
We failed each time.
The last time we tried, An Tae Ho betrayed us, as you know.
I totally get why he did.
He was beaten the most out of us all.
They knew very well what the most efficient way...
to tame us was.
But the real reason we had no choice but to live like that...
wasn't the physical violence.
What was the real reason, then?
At first, I thought we were being treated that way...
because of a few evil people.
I was wrong.
Other people thought exactly the same.
That's when I realized...
we were just...
a pack of dogs...
they didn't know what to do with.
People didn't care how bad the situation was in there.
They didn't care...
who was in there and whether they ended up...
getting killed illegally.
The despair that I was completely cut off from the world...
made me accept that inhumane treatment as if it were fate.
I'm not Ryu Sung Hoon, the human being.
I'm Boy Number 11.
Like that.
Who is that?
Hello, sir.
Who's that man sitting in front of Ryu Sung Jun?
It's Judge Ryu Sung Hoon.
- Sung Jun's older brother. - Ryu Sung Jun's brother?
Yes, sir.
(In Seong's Place)
(Please help me find In Seong.)
(Age 10 at the time of disappearance)
(Name: Jung In Seong, Boy, Age 10)
- Is that true? - Yes.
I just found out.
The boy that couple adopted wasn't Ryu Sung Jun.
It was his brother.
I was fooled by the necklace.
He admitted to it himself,
so I'm sure of it.
So?
Why are you telling me that?
You don't know?
We need to get rid of him before he says anything more.
If you're afraid of your past coming out,
you should take care of him yourself.
As you can see, I'm behind bars,
so I can't even kill a rat.
Mr. Baek.
What if I do something that you want?
After I do this,
who will you get to kill me this time?
I don't what that sneaky punk, Detective Kang said,
but it's all a bold-faced lie.
Mr. Baek.
Did you already forget how your daughter died?
Think about it.
The only person who can get you out of here...
is me.
How do I look?
Hurry up.
Look at the camera.
Make a face you've never made before.
You have to look really silly.
One, two, three.
(Math Mom)
If I want to become a good person, do I have to go to college?
Why? Do you not want to go to school?
I wanted to focus and go,
but I might get expelled tomorrow.
I got into a fight with the rich girl in my class.
Why did you get into a fight?
That rude brat called my mom a tramp.
I really hate my mom,
but I hate it more when people talk badly about her.
How dare she talk about my mom like that?
If you need legal advice, let me know.
Advice?
Gosh, you're so handsome!
Thank you.
Okay. I'll get going.
- Come again. - I will.
Excuse me.
- Ms. Kwon. - Can't you see I'm working?
Just get to the point and leave.
I...
Well...
Yu Na...
That she's dead?
Did you know?
I got a call from the police earlier today...
and went to the morgue.
They say if you're born unlucky,
you can break your nose falling backward.
How could she die like that?
At times like this,
shouldn't the country do something for the bereaved?
For emotional compensation.
They give you all sorts of support funds,
so why don't they have compensation for those who were murdered?
No.
Maybe there is, but I don't know about it.
Miss, do you know anything?
Do you think you were her guardian or something?
Are you going to hit me?
(La Karaoke)
- Open it. - Okay.
(Jo Eun...)
Is it a dying message?
I have so many regrets.
She had no connections to me in her life,
but I...
wanted to act like a good adult, so I kept her close.
If...
If I could go back in time,
I wouldn't have acted like I knew her.
Yu Na really liked you.
She said you were the first person...
who helped her unconditionally.
She said...
she wanted to become...
a good person like you.
Whenever I was with Yu Na...
I felt at ease somehow.
Maybe, it was like I knew the pain she was going through.
And I felt bad for her too.
I also wanted to help her.
But I couldn't do anything for her in the end.
I'm back.
Eun Ki, why are you...
I told her she could stay here for the time being.
I thought it would be hard for her to stay at the center right now.
I'll only stay for tonight.
No, stay here until the culprit is caught.
You can use my room.
No, I can just sleep on the sofa.
No.
Use my room.
Go ahead.
Gosh, this is...
My room is usually clean.
I've been so busy lately. I'm usually very tidy.
You don't have to clean.
No, I'll be done quickly.
- The blanket is clean. - Okay.
Get some rest.
Eun Ki, so...
When I'm not around, keep the door locked.
And...
From now on, a security detail will follow you whenever you go out.
Is that necessary?
It wasn't a coincidence that the culprit targeted you.
All the jurors, including you,
were related to Hope Welfare Center.
In other words, you are also a target of the culprit's revenge.
What are you doing?
Darn it. Officer Lee!
Hurry up.
Come here.
Mr. Baek, calm down. Come here.
Sir, calm down. Let's sit down and talk.
Apparently, he went totally insane.
If that's true, what will happen to Baek Moon Kang now?
I guess they'll send him to a mental institution, at least.
If he ends up committing suicide, they'll all be questioned.
Would the chief let that happen?
Are all the jurors under protective watch?
Oh, right.
I assigned a security detail to Eun Ki.
And I gave the rest of the jurors a smartwatch.
- And Producer Bae? - We checked if he left the country.
It looks like he didn't.
And his phone hasn't been used.
There's no credit card usage.
This means there are no signs of life.
This is just my own theory,
but what if the culprit already got to him?
That can't be.
Recently, the culprit hasn't been hiding his crimes at all.
If Producer Bae had been killed, we would've found the body.
If he's still alive, then did he get abducted?
Let's declare Producer Bae missing.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
(National Forensic Service Muyeong Institute)
(Kwon Yu Na, 17, attended Hosu Girls' Commercial High School)
Cause of death was excessive bleeding.
The murder weapon is the same as...
with Baek Ji Eun, Yeom Hye Jin, and Kang Ha Na.
What about the trace of blood in the hallway?
Oh, that was a match to this girl.
They're defensive wounds.
She fought for her life.
You're not hurt, are you?
There was a nurse at Hope Welfare Center.
- That nurse is your mother. - Goodness.
Why did you lie...
about Hope Welfare Center?
I...
couldn't help it.
I wanted to help those kids too, but...
You wanted to help,
but why couldn't you?
As far as I know, you're the most tender and warm-hearted person.
There is no way that you would ignore it...
when kids were being abused and killed in a place like that.
I've always been grateful and proud that you were my mom.
But not anymore.
It's not too late, Mom.
You reveal it to the world yourself.
What they did to those kids there...
I can't see you before you do that.
Do you think it was easy for me?
It was painful for me too.
So I called the TV station.
That producer came to the welfare center...
and secretly filmed it.
He said he would reveal everything on TV.
But no matter how long I waited...
Who was that producer?
(Number 13, Jung Yoon Jae)
(Deceased)
(Number 11, brother)
(Survived)
(Number 12)
Sung Jun.
The forensic results of Kwon Yu Na's phone are out.
Is that so?
But it seems like Yu Na was quite close with Judge Ryu.
(Analysis report)
This is Mr. Choi's house.
Why did he go there?
If this was May 15, it was the day of the An Tae Ho case.
Manager An is at Mr. Choi's place now.
How can you be so sure that he's at Mr. Choi's place?
I'll go there and find out whether I'm right or not.
It's a waste of time.
An Tae Ho will die if you keep barking up the wrong tree.
Sung Hoon already knew that An Tae Ho...
wasn't at Mr. Choi's place.
That's why he told me not to go there.
But how come he didn't tell me about going there himself?
Sung Jun, where are you going?
Sung Jun!
(We Design, Make, and Install Signage)
Did this man come here to pick up the footage?
Yes, it was this guy.
He came and took the footage from that day.
May I see the drone you used that day?
Drone?
It wasn't a drone.
It was from a camera on an advertising balloon.
- An advertising balloon? - Yes.
One moment, please.
Here, I'll show you.
This is the advertising balloon we used that day.
(Join Muyeong's anti-smoking campaign for your healthy future.)
Right before Jung Man Chun fell,
I was waiting at the crosswalk in front of the hospital.
At that time, there was a drone in the air.
(Join Muyeong's anti-smoking campaign for your healthy future.)
Do you remember when he stopped by to pick up the footage?
About 3 to 4 days after we floated the advertising balloon.
So even back then, Sung Hoon knew...
who killed Jung Man Chun.
Why did he hide the evidence and pretend not to know about it?
What for?
(Social Worker Jo Eun Ki)
(The lack of evidence invalidates the prosecutor's argument.)
(Reasons for Sentencing)
(The accused embezzled over 300,000 dollars...)
(Judge)
What brings you to my courtroom?
I wanted to watch your last trial.
The last one isn't any different.
I just do what I always do.
But knowing that you were watching me in the audience...
made me a little nervous.
How do you feel to be leaving the court?
Well, it's bittersweet.
Do you have regrets...
about any of the rulings you've made over the years?
Regrets?
Yes, of course. I'm human too, after all.
I just...
did my best not to repeat the same mistake.
What's wrong?
Is something bothering you?
No.
This is boring. Come on, let's go.
You're free this evening, right?
Let's grab a drink together. It's been too long.
I've got plans. I'm sorry.
Oh, really?
Well, don't worry about it then.
(Court)
Eun Ki, why are you looking for Bae Chul Ho?
He worked on a story on the welfare center.
He might still have the footage.
That footage...
will help reveal the truth behind Hope Welfare Center.
(Muyeong Police Station)
To tell you the truth,
we're looking for him too.
Why?
Sung Jun!
We received a tip-off from a witness.
He was spotted at the terminal.
Let's talk later, Eun Ki.
- Let's go. - Okay.
(Missing Person, Bae Chul Ho)
It was this man.
Over there.
I think he put something in one of the lockers and left.
Do you happen to remember the locker number?
It was...
It was 17. Number 17.
Darn it.
(Gwangju, Jeonju, Gangneung)
We were right.
Producer Bae staged his own disappearance.
He faked his own disappearance.
We were worried for nothing.
(Gwangju, Jeonju, Gangneung)
Could we find out when it was picked up from the locker?
One moment, please.
Here.
It was picked up the next day.
Sung Jun.
That guy with a black hat...
Isn't he the suspect in Kang Ha Na's murder?
The one who impersonated Yoon Jae.
Sung Jun!
It's your first time here, right?
Yes.
Are you meeting someone here?
No.
If you want company, just let me know.
- When did you get here? - Just now.
Where were you?
The court. Where else?
Are you looking for something?
No.
Sung Hoon.
You know,
I have to write a report on Mr. Baek's case.
What day was it when you found the drone?
It was an advertising balloon, not a drone.
Really?
I guess I was mistaken.
So when did you find the advertising balloon?
I'm pretty sure I already told Captain Oh...
that I found it the day when I dropped off the footage.
Do you remember when he stopped by to pick up the footage?
About 3 to 4 days after we floated the advertising balloon.
I see.
Okay.
Darn it.
Sung Hoon!
He just left.
What's going on with Producer Bae? Did you find him?
I'll fill you in later.
Shoot.
Sung Hoon!
Sung Hoon.
Darn it.
Hey, stay with me. Sung Hoon!
(Our priority is to protect child actors...)
(and animals and the dangerous scenes...)
(were not shot with real children or animals...)
(but with doubles and dummies.)
(Blind)
I think I've figured out who the killer is.
Who is it?
It was a sashimi knife.
He's hiding something.
You bought me vanilla ice cream, my favorite.
What are you doing?
Impersonating Jung Yoon Jae...
Where is your brother?
What if Yu Na's dying message wasn't a name?
Jung Yoon Jae?