(This drama is fiction and people, places, organizations,)
(incidents, groups, and settings...)
(are not based on reality.)
- An escape? - Yes, sir.
When?
At dawn on the morning of Routine Inspection Day.
Who's involved in this plan?
Number 11, Number 12,
Number 13, Number 24, and me.
It's the five of us.
- Is that all? - Yes, sir.
Okay.
I'll pretend not to know, so just do what they say.
What are you going to do?
Have you tried hare coursing?
No, sir.
If you want to catch a rabbit,
you have to go from the top of the mountain down.
The thing with rabbits...
is their back legs are longer than their front legs.
So they're really bad at going down things.
When a rabbit escapes its cage...
and hops its way to the top of the mountain,
it'll be happy and relieved that it's safe.
Then at that moment...
you show up and drive them down.
Then the flustered rabbit will flounder about...
and get caught in a snare or get eaten by a wolf.
What do you think? Doesn't it sound fun?
You'll be okay since you're a good kid.
Are you...
going to let me go?
Of course I will.
Okay. You can go now.
Before the other kids get suspicious.
(Episode 6: Your Enemy is Closest to You)
Sung Hoon.
(6 hours earlier)
What are you planning to do?
I have to meet Sung Jun.
I'll know who the real culprit is once I meet him.
I got a call from Sung Jun.
Detective Ryu was right.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Do as I say from now on.
We're going to fool everyone. Including Sung Jun.
That's the only way I could help him.
(A fair and trustworthy court house)
(Sundae Soup, Grilled Fish)
(Grilled fish)
(Original Nam Nam House)
(Hansin Manufactures)
What do you want?
I'm sorry. I overreacted.
You shouldn't have done something so out of character.
When I saw our detectives all over that place earlier,
I thought, "I guess that's just who he is,"
and gave up.
I have to speak to my brother about something in private.
Yes, take your time. I'll be outside.
Let me make this clear so you don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't come here for your sake.
I want to catch the culprit...
who ruined my trial with my own hands.
Even if that culprit is you.
Explain this first.
(Jung Man Chun Case Autopsy Report)
(Autopsy Result)
(Photo of fallen victim's body)
(Button found near the railing of the rooftop)
What is...
When did this come off?
It's not like that.
I don't know why this button was on that rooftop,
but nothing happened between me and Jung Man Chun that day.
Then what about the evidence left at the motel murder case?
Do you not know anything about those either?
(Test Results, Comparison)
(Evidence 2, hair)
I realize you have enough reasons to suspect me.
But it's really not me, Sung Hoon.
Why did you meet Jung Man Chun?
That jerk called me to the rooftop, saying he had something to tell me.
And what did you talk about?
He said that Baek Ji Eun's murderer...
paid him to pretend to be the perp.
Does that make any sense?
So I thought he was messing with me,
and I almost smacked him on the head.
But...
he said his son had a brain tumor.
He did what he did because of the money,
but he was afraid that the real culprit might kill his son.
How did you know his family was at the motel?
Jung Man Chun told me.
He said the recording was there.
A recording?
What recording?
The recorded call of Jung Man Chun and Baek Ji Eun's killer.
So, did you find it?
No.
When I got to the motel...
Won Woong!
Please breathe.
Come on.
Thank goodness.
Help...
Won Woong.
My Won Woong...
- Won Woong. - Are you okay?
Hang in there a little longer.
My Won Woong...
Save him.
Ma'am.
Darn it.
Ryu Sung Jun!
But right then, Detective Kang arrived at the scene.
Hold on.
- The boy was alive? - Yes, he was.
He must've been murdered after I left.
If what you're saying is true, this means you're innocent.
- Then why did you run? - I didn't run.
I just hid for safety.
Detective Kang shot a live round out of nowhere.
And after that, I was abducted, and I lost consciousness.
Abducted?
By whom?
Mr. Baek.
He believes I'm the culprit who killed his daughter.
Look.
I was tortured.
I almost died, Sung Hoon.
Why did I hide if I was innocent?
You know better than anyone...
what kind of power evidence can have.
I'm a rat in a trap.
So please, help me.
I'll help you under one condition.
What is it?
Discuss everything with me from now on...
and get my permission.
Okay.
- Are you done talking? - Yes.
You're headed to the courthouse, right? I'll give you a ride.
I'd like the know the reason.
Why would you take on such a risk to help Sung Jun?
I was trying to repay his kindness and ended up like this.
And if Sung Jun gets arrested,
you might face legal consequences too.
I know that much too.
You must believe Sung Jun is innocent.
Do you not trust your brother, Judge Ryu?
(Photo of the scene where the body was found)
(Hypodermal bleeding confirmed around nose and mouth)
(Muyeong Police Station)
You idiots!
It wasn't just one of you,
but the entire Violent Crimes Unit,
that failed to catch Ryu Sung Jun?
This is exactly why the people call you dogs, not cops!
All of you. Tell the truth.
You did this on purpose, didn't you?
You let him go because he was one of your own!
- Isn't that true? - We would never do that, Chief.
Captain Oh.
Do you think I'm a joke?
Do you think I don't know what goes on outside since I'm stuck in here?
Do you think I don't know...
that you dropped the cell phone on purpose...
to ruin the arrest?
You. Turn in your ID.
Get lost.
A guy like you who only protects his own...
doesn't deserve to serve the people!
- Got anything? - Hello? Hey.
Gosh, this is torture.
No, I'm still waiting.
Did you hear anything?
What?
If you heard from Sung Jun,
you should've let us know first.
Why did you let the police know...
and make things even more complicated?
I'm sorry.
Sung Hoon must've thought he was doing what was best for Sung Jun.
If he cares so much about Sung Jun,
how does he not know what his brother is up to?
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You must be in a tough spot because of Sung Jun too.
I've been on edge.
Don't say that.
Like you said,
I didn't pay close enough attention to Sung Jun.
Since then, have you not heard from Sung Jun again?
No.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
- Here she comes! - She's here!
- Here she is! - She just stepped outside.
Ms. Na, have you gotten in touch with your son?
Is your son a serial killer?
Do you have any intention of stepping down?
- Please give us a statement. - Please answer the question.
Perhaps, if you're thinking of giving up your nomination,
don't do it, Mother.
Sung Jun isn't the culprit, right?
I can't say for sure at the moment,
but I will take care of the matter with Sung Jun.
So please continue on your own path, Mother.
Just like you have until now.
- Please say something. - Over here!
My son risked his own life...
in the recent hostage situation to save a woman's life.
He is a righteous police officer.
I don't know why he was framed for murder,
but I believe and trust my son.
The truth will come out when he returns.
Please bear with us.
Will you not step down from your minister candidacy?
Why should I resign when I'm ashamed of nothing?
No.
Hey.
Help me.
Brother.
Please.
Hey.
Brother.
- What are you doing? - Standing by.
If you're awake, sit up so I can clean your wound.
No, wait.
Do you have a doctor or nurse license?
My mom's a nurse.
You must've had a dream. It didn't sound like a romance.
It was horror.
I'm a kid being chased by a monster.
However hard I try to get away, I just can't.
I always get caught in the end,
and wake right before I'm eaten.
I see.
Not bad for a horror flick.
At least you're with your brother.
How do you know I was with my brother?
You kept calling for him.
Did I say anything else?
No.
You just called for your brother.
How much taller will you get...
if you're having scary dreams at your age?
Do you feel very anxious?
I don't feel anxious at all.
I have a completely safe hideout...
and a dedicated caregiver.
I'm not anxious at all.
I'll wash your bloody clothes. Change into this.
Did you buy clothes for me?
You can't.
If the cops run your credit card transactions and see...
you bought men's clothing, they'll suspect you right away.
This is why I should've taught you...
how to dupe the police.
What should we do?
They're my clothes.
Oh, okay.
They're unisex clothing.
Try them on.
Get changed.
But...
Eun Ki lent me a shirt.
It suits you.
Change into this.
Okay.
Wow, handcuffs.
I haven't seen these in ages. I missed them so much.
Cash to spend for now.
Eun Ki. The food, medicine, and other expenses I incurred,
I'll pay in full from here.
Great, thanks.
Transport.
- Where is it? - Mall parking, across the street.
B13, basement level two. You'll find a motorcycle parked.
A bike?
And these are phones we'll use to contact each other.
- You use this from now on too. - Me too?
Back out if you want to. There's still time.
I can't back out now.
Eun Ki. Isn't my brother incredible?
He isn't just meticulous at work.
He's like that in everyday life too.
The sight of our fridge would shock you.
Everything's in a line.
He has robotic organization skills.
You're in no position to crack jokes.
Right.
Jung's recording of his talk with Baek's killer was at the motel?
- Yes. - Did Jung say exactly where?
No. He said if I went to the motel his wife would give it to me.
If his wife had it, it's likely the police found it.
Shall I find out if the police have it?
(Girlfriend)
(Detective Kim Seok Gu)
Hey, honey. What's up?
Are you on your own?
I'm on a stakeout with a senior detective.
Then answer yes or no to my question.
Among the evidence from the motel, was there a recording?
The killer's voice is on it.
No, miss.
Nope, it wasn't there.
Okay, thanks. Bye.
(Detective Kim Seok Gu)
If the police don't have it, the killer does.
Why else would he have gone to the motel?
Is there nothing left to prove who the real killer is?
Right.
There's one left.
Do you want to know who I am?
My name is Yoon Jae. Jung Yoon Jae.
Why did you ask to see me?
You know Sung Jun appeared a few days ago, don't you?
Yes. I saw it on the news.
He passed me a note that day with surprising information.
That you abducted and tortured him and even...
tried to kill him.
That can't be.
There's also talk that you heard the killer's voice.
Could I hear it as well?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Sung Jun said he was framed.
And you believe him?
Why are you so convinced that Sung Jun's the killer?
- Yes? - Honey.
Do you know who just came over?
Ji Eun's boyfriend.
Ji Eun's boyfriend?
Where could it be?
Darn it.
Honey. What are you doing?
Hurry up. The candles are all melting.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Ji Eun
No. Stop!
No, don't take it down!
No! Honey.
No.
Ji Eun's coming home soon. She's coming after.
- Let go! - Stop it.
Ji Eun's cake!
No!
I didn't find anything.
- You didn't? - I didn't.
I looked in the living room, the big room, and the small room,
but I couldn't find anything.
What if it was never there to begin with?
If that's not it,
maybe the culprit got there before me.
Don't resent me.
This is all Yoon Jae's fault.
(Baek Ji Eun Murder Case)
Okay. Let's start from square one.
You're the prime suspect in these three cases.
Under the pretense...
that the murderer behind Baek Ji Eun, Yeom Hye Jin,
and Jung Man Chun's family is the same person,
if we can get evidence regarding even one of these cases,
we can clear your name from the serial murder charges.
First, this.
(Muyeong Hospital Rooftop Fall)
There's a piece of evidence from the rooftop...
where Jung Man Chun fell from that the police haven't figured out.
What is it?
Right after Jung Man Chun fell,
there was a man on the roof.
How can we find a man...
that the police couldn't find?
Right before Jung Man Chun fell,
I was waiting at the crosswalk in front of the hospital.
At that time, there was a drone in the air.
That drone might've filmed something on the roof.
It's illegal to fly drones inside the city,
so if we ask the police, we can find out who was flying it.
Should I call Seok Gu?
No. I'll look into the drone.
Sung Jun,
go over everything on Baek Ji Eun and Yeom Hye Jin's murders...
and try to see if we missed anything.
Sung Hoon.
You just want me to sit here and go over everything?
What else can you do right now?
I'm sure I can find something.
Why are you guys fighting? We're on the same team.
Let's cheer up. Okay?
Come on.
Eun Ki. Keep an eye on him,
so he doesn't do anything stupid.
(Reserved)
(Vacant)
(Taxi)
Welcome. Where can I take you?
Are we there?
(Yu Na)
You told me to mind my own business.
What is it?
Save me.
Yu Na.
What do you mean? Yu Na?
I...
Ms. Jo...
Please save me...
Yu Na, where are you?
Yu Na.
Where are you now? I'll come get you. Just tell me...
I'm sorry.
All right. Everyone, check the batteries on your flashlights.
You each have your batons, right?
This is the current situation.
We tracked Kwon Yu Na's phone and the signal...
was last pinged in this vicinity.
- Once we get backup... - Yu Na!
- Hey, wait. - Yu Na!
Kwon Yu Na!
- Darn it. - Yu Na!
- Kwon Yu Na! - Come on, we should all go.
- Let's go. - Kwon Yu Na!
- Officers go that way! - Kwon Yu Na!
Yu Na!
You there, go up that way.
- Yu Na! - Kwon Yu Na!
- Kwon Yu Na! - Yu Na!
Kwon Yu Na!
- Yu Na! - Kwon Yu Na!
This way. Kwon Yu Na!
Officer Park. Get over here.
Go farther up.
Yu Na!
Hey, what are you doing here?
Why are you sleeping out here?
Get up, now.
Get up. Let's go.
Let's go.
Get up.
Let's go buy you some shoes.
I'll empty out my bank account and get you a really nice pair.
Yu Na. You can't do this.
You can't go like this.
Poor Yu Na. What am I supposed to do?
Yu Na!
Gosh, you're so loud.
So, to summarize,
you left the club and got in a taxi.
You dozed off, and when you woke up...
the taxi driver suddenly dragged you to the forest and did this, right?
Darn it. How many times do I have to tell you?
We just have to be sure.
Do you remember the license plate or the cab company?
I don't even remember the driver's face.
Would I remember something like that?
I'm curious about one thing. Why are you so angry?
You're making me angry, that's why.
You're not out there catching the culprit.
Why are you bothering me when I'm hurt?
Okay, Yu Na. Get some rest.
Detective, let's stop here for now.
I'll let you know if Yu Na remembers anything.
Yes, I think that would be the best.
I can't say anything.
- Let's go, Seok Gu. - Okay.
A tattoo.
That jerk had a tattoo on his arm.
Darn it.
Look at you. Did you just dodge?
I'm going to kill you.
Darn this thing.
Darn...
Darn it!
(Hoonyoung Driver's Diner)
But this really is unexpected.
Ryu Sung Jun being Yoon Jae, I mean.
I had no idea.
Wasn't the guy you saw in court Yoon Jae?
No, the guy I saw wasn't Yoon Jae. It was number seven.
Number seven?
You know, the rat with the burn mark.
Moon Kang. There must be a reason...
these guys showed up at once.
You mean they colluded and killed Ji Eun and Chief Yeom's daughter?
They're definitely capable of it.
I'll look into number seven.
(Taxi)
It's been a while.
It's me, Mr. Choi.
Crazy Dog is looking for you.
But should I hand you over to him or not? I'm not sure.
The thing is, I need some money.
I'll decide after I see what you do.
Let me know when you're ready.
(Rat)
Darn it!
He had this tattoo on his arm.
Is she sure it's this tattoo?
Seok Gu was also surprised to see this tattoo earlier.
Why is that?
I saw it on Mr. Choi's arm before.
Could I see a photo of Yu Na's current state?
This was how she looked this morning.
Sung Hoon. Look at this.
She was hit in the face and torso the most.
It's similar to Yeom Hye Jin.
Then are you saying Yeom Hye Jin's killer is Mr. Choi?
Mr. Choi used to beat his wife habitually.
When she ran away, he would've needed an outlet for his anger.
And maybe that outlet was to beat up women like Yeom Hye Jin and Yu Na...
who were going home alone late at night.
It's a plausible theory.
But these photos and his record aren't enough to make a case.
I know that.
We need foolproof evidence like a witness or DNA.
(Yeom Hye Jin Murder Case, Victim: Yeom Hye Jin, 33 years old)
(Found in a flower bed at Muyeong Park by a guard)
Right.
Didn't she say the guy had a wound on his arm as well as the tattoo?
Yes, she said he had scratch marks on his arm.
(Victim: Yeom Hye Jin, 33 years old)
Sung Hoon. What if the person who gave him that wound...
(Yeom Hye Jin)
was Yeom Hye Jin?
Then Mr. Choi's DNA would've been found during the autopsy.
What if they couldn't find any because her nails were broken?
Don't you think it's too late to find the broken nails?
No, it's not too late.
Because...
I've already found it.
(April 19, 2022, The day after Yeom Hye Jin's body was found)
As fast as you can. I'm asking you as a friend.
Hey, come on. Just take a look.
It's Yeom Hye Jin's fingernail.
Yeom Hye Jin's fingernail?
You're right. It's the same nail gel as Yeom Hye Jin's...
But where did you get this?
At the park where Yeom Hye Jin's body was found.
I scoured the entire trail to find it.
You see this bloodstain, right?
Don't you think something might be in there?
Are you a pheasant?
Hey, Ryu Sung Jun.
Will you turn me in? If so, then I'm leaving.
You crazy jerk! Where have you been?
What... Are you okay?
Gosh, I never thought I'd hear you say that.
How do you think I feel...
watching you go on the run when you used to chase suspects?
- What happened? - It's a long story.
It's a 2.5-hour long blockbuster. I'll tell you when we have the time.
Yeom Hye Jin's fingernail that I brought in that day.
Do you have the test results?
Gosh, seriously... Of course, I have them.
We found an unknown person's DNA from her fingernail.
- "Unidentified?" - That's right.
It means they ran it...
in the police's DNA database and didn't find a match,
which means I'm no longer a suspect...
in the murder of Yeom Hye Jin.
Do the police know about this?
Yes. Of course, they know.
All clear.
(National Forensic Service)
(To Senior Police Officer Ryu Sung Jun)
(DNA Test Report)
(Victim's nail found at the scene)
(Interpretation)
(Victim Yeom Hye Jin's DNA sample was analyzed...)
(in comparison with the nail found at the scene.)
(Victim's nail found at the scene)
Ryu Sung Jun brought this nail?
Yes.
He asked them to analyze the evidence behind our backs,
which is certainly suspicious.
He may be trying...
to misdirect the investigation by manipulating evidence.
(Victim's nail found at the scene)
Who else knows about this nail?
The medical examiner...
and those who work in the lab. That's it.
Like you said,
this could cause confusion in the investigation,
so don't tell anyone about this for the time being.
Yes, sir.
(Chief Yeom Ki Nam)
What is going on?
Yoon Jae...
wasn't the one who killed Hye Jin?
(In Seong's Place)
I'm picking up Muyeong Police's order.
- They didn't order anything. - They did. One gukbap.
Oh, you're right. Just a moment.
Hello, I'd like one bowl of gukbap.
Okay, sure.
The judge gave me this.
The report on the jurors' texts and locations at the time.
What about the DNA analysis of the nail? How did that go?
Well, I haven't seen the report yet.
What are you talking about?
The medical examiner sent it over to the team.
The thing is, Detective Kang...
came in early and took an envelope from Captain Oh's desk.
That was probably the report.
What?
(In Seong's Place)
Hello.
Here you go.
Watch out for cars.
We need another bowl of gukbap here.
Sure.
(Location Tracking Report)
(Choi Soon Gil)
(April 14, 2022, SMS received at 11:42pm)
(Soho 2-gil, Dong-gu, Muyeong)
Come in.
I thought it might be you.
I was right.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
- Here, Eun Ki. - Thank you.
Here, Ms. Kwon.
No pressure.
But I'd love it if you could all come and enjoy the meal.
Oh, my. This is an expensive venue.
This must've cost you quite a bit.
She's my only daughter, so I went a little overboard.
Anyway, I'm worried.
You really should marry your children off...
while you're still working.
Now that I'm retired,
even sending out these invitations is a struggle.
Most wedding guests...
are invited by the parents.
What if no one comes? I'm worried.
Gosh, no way.
You have so many friends.
Everyone is free that day, right?
I'm a freelancer, so I can certainly be there.
But it'll be hard for him because of the restaurant.
I'll have someone fill in for me.
Saturday is my day off, so I can be there too.
My gosh! Thank you all.
Anyway, where is Mr. Jung?
I'm sorry I'm late.
- There he is. - Come and sit here.
Which road did you take?
There was no traffic on my way here.
The Olympic Blvd. There was an accident on the way.
Oh, no. Who caused an accident...
during the rush hour?
Oh, thank you.
Congratulations, Mr. Kang.
Thanks.
All right.
Are we just waiting for Mr. An and Mr. Choi now?
What happened?
Hello?
Mr. Choi. It's me, In Seong. We were on the jury together.
Mr. Choi?
Isn't this Mr. Choi's number?
All good?
Let's go.
Captain, I don't think anyone is here.
Hold on.
He's still breathing. Call an ambulance now.
- Yes, sir. - Hurry.
(Detective)
This crazy punk.
Ryu Sung Jun. What are you doing?
Mr. Choi got whacked.
- What? - He's been hit in the head.
He seemed to be in critical condition.
- You went to Mr. Choi's place? - Yes.
I clearly told you not to go anywhere without my permission.
What's with you? You little...
No, you've always been like this.
All your life, you never cared about others...
and always did whatever you wanted.
Do you know what the family is going through because of you?
Of course, you won't know.
You only care about yourself, you selfish jerk.
I had no choice.
Why is that your excuse every time?
Detective Kang hid the report from the National Forensic Service.
My colleagues aren't investigating the case,
and you want me to do nothing?
Look.
It's from the day when Yeom Hye Jin died.
It shows the jurors' texts and their locations at the time.
(Choi Soon Gil, Yeom Hye Jin)
Choi Soon Gil was the only one...
who was at the park when she was murdered.
If he really is the one who killed her,
the DNA under her nail must belong to him.
So I wanted to get his toothbrush or something.
I feel bad that you're going through this because of me,
so I wanted to clear my name. That's why I did it. Happy now?
Sit down.
Other than Mr. Choi, was there anyone else at the scene?
I didn't see anyone else.
Did you see anything suspicious?
I found this hidden on top of his wall clock.
(Recording 001)
What is it?
There's a recording.
It's from today.
(Recording 001)
Come in.
I thought it might be you.
I was right.
That day...
Was it in the courtroom?
I happened to glance at you during the trial,
and it looked like you recognized him.
Back then, you guys called him Crazy Dog.
You were glaring at Crazy Dog.
The moment I saw the burn scar...
on the back of your hand,
I realized that you were there that day.
You're Number Seven.
Don't tell me you came here empty-handed.
I warned you that Crazy Dog was looking for you.
- Number 24. - Number 24?
You're making all this fuss because of Number 24?
Come on.
Let's be honest. Number 24 died because of you.
Had you not been such a tattletale,
Number 24 would still be alive.
Number 24...
He said the culprit was in the courtroom that day.
Where was Mr. Choi sitting that day?
He was sitting in the back.
The second seat from the end.
How many people's hands could you see from that seat?
You can probably see almost everyone...
except for those sitting in the last row of the audience.
If we exclude women and elderly people...
The culprit was in that room that day.
(Recording 001)
Come in.
(Do Not Cross)
This man walked slowly.
Was it intentional?
(Recording 001)
I thought it might be you.
I was right.
The left and right footsteps sound different.
A difference in stride means...
Hey, Sung Hoon.
Go down the stairs in time with the recording.
Okay.
(Muyeong Local Court)
You won't come to the dinner?
You go ahead. I'll follow.
Promise.
I found the killer.
(Our priority is to protect child actors...)
(and animals and the dangerous scenes...)
(were not shot with real children or animals...)
(but with doubles and dummies.)
(Blind)
Don't trust anyone.
Not even Sung Jun.
Or me.
If you don't hand over Yoon Jae,
The son you really cherish will get hurt.
In the container...
was a wedding invitation with blood on it.
These three have some sort of connection.
The truth about who the killer is.
Do you know who I am?
Number 13, Jung Yoon Jae.