♪ Come watch me ♪
[opening theme music playing]
[coins jingling]
[whooshes]
-[whirring]
-[chiming]
[whooshing]
[chimes]
[coins jingling]
♪ Come watch me ♪
[A-ri] Have you ever
found yourself thinking,
"This online world
is a little exhausting"?
I mean, it's true.
There are just so many things
to buy, to eat, and to do.
Wouldn't you agree?
And there's a daily onslaught of people
trying to tell you
what you should eat, buy, and do.
It is exhausting.
And aren't you tired of it?
Don't you wonder if these things
are really necessary?
You know, I used to feel that way myself.
"I don't get what all the fuss is about.
They aren't even that pretty."
"I don't understand
why everyone is buying them,
wearing them, and posting about them.
-But you know what?
-[chimes]
Yes, the sheet masks
are made of natural materials
and don't cause any skin irritation.
Right! You'll notice how comfortable
and refreshing they are for your skin.
And of course, you'll be collaborating
with The Hue Cosmetics again.
They're known to be the best.
Yes, so I can vouch for their quality
working with such titans in this industry.
Oh, and I'm getting word
that we're about to sell out right now.
We ask that you please stay on the line…
[A-ri] Sadly, once we're used to seeing
the constant stream of products
coming at us from every direction,
we consciously start doubting
our own choices.
We think to ourselves,
"Everyone else has one.
Shouldn't I have one too?"
Or we say,
"Everyone else is doing it.
Shouldn't I try it?"
We compare ourselves to other people.
Worrying,
"What do I do if I get left behind?"
[Mrs. A-ri] Oh, come in, come in. Uh-huh.
This way. Come in.
[chuckles] Over there.
To the left, right there.
This place is insane!
Whoa!
So you're paying
20 million won a month for this?
A-ri makes so much that 20 million
is just nothing to her!
Mom, oh my God.
This is all natural marble.
Of course it is. [chuckles]
Look there! [gasps]
[Du-seong]
There's a swimming pool out there?
[Jeong-sun] Really?
[A-ri] It's true.
I leveraged all of your wants,
and worries, and doubts to make money
and found more success
than I even imagined.
-♪ Hey! ♪
-♪ Sh-- Sh-- Sh-- Shake! ♪
♪ Sh-- Sh-- Sh-- Shake! ♪
♪ You think you can afford me?
You better think again ♪
-♪ Hey! ♪
-♪ Sh-- Sh-- Sh-- Shake! ♪
♪ Sh-- Sh-- Sh-- Shake! ♪
-[Jeong-sun] Hi.
-Hi.
-So, just take a look at this.
-[gasps]
[chuckles]
[A-ri] I think this one
has a better feel to it.
Oh, I really like it.
[upbeat music playing]
CEO IN THE LIMELIGHT
POWER ROOKIE CEO SEO A-RI
[clamoring]
[A-ri] But once I reached the top,
was that really all?
Was this where my journey ends?
[dramatic music playing]
No. Of course not.
Because, if that had been the case,
then we wouldn't be here now
in this thrilling livestream together.
[scribbling]
TAEGANG DIRECTOR
JIN TAE-JEON
We can't just allow people
to delude themselves, hmm?
Letting them believe
they're a somebody now.
This is exactly what's wrong
with the press, you know?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. [chuckles]
Oh, no.
Seo A-ri will cost you more
than an average influencer.
Right.
It's ten million
for a 30-minute livestream endorsement
and five million for ads on her feed.
That's right. Yes.
But the thing is,
she's completely booked out until October.
Yes.
-The ad sponsorship proposals for Ari.&.
-Yeah.
Right.
Yes, well, uh… [sighs]
…this deal might still be on the table
if we raise the price a little.
That's right.
[chuckles] Of course.
1.3M FOLLOWERS
Ah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[chuckles]
-Well, then…
-[knocks on window]
Sir, Ms. Seo A-ri is here.
Right. I've told you all there is to know.
Let's continue this another time.
Great.
[chuckles] God.
That was another inquiry about Ari.&.
Things have been so hectic.
I know we're late,
but our meetings dragged on.
Ah, don't worry.
I don't mind a little waiting.
Ms. Seo has another appointment soon,
so let's make this quick.
I'll be done in five minutes.
Oh God, this isn't the one!
[sucks teeth, sighs]
This one. I want to get this new release.
But that one went to Seo A-ri
for sponsorship.
-[scoffs]
-What?
-I have to go.
-[Ji-na] Wait, where?
You need to get clothes too.
You want me to pick through A-ri's castoff
from shit she doesn't want?
Really?
I'm Jin Chae-hee!
[Chae-hee grunts]
You're fucking pathetic, you traitors.
Not that long ago,
you were begging me to wear your clothes.
But now you've picked Seo A-ri over me?
Seriously?
[Chae-hee breathing heavily]
Chae-hee! Shit.
Chae-hee!
So what you're suggesting is we change
how I run my account?
Yes.
[inhales]
-You have 1.3 million followers now.
-[A-ri sighs]
Things have changed.
You realize
that you're the first and only e-celeb
to break a million so fast? Hmm?
And besides,
the rumors about you and Han Jun-kyoung
are really making you
the talk of the town.
Problem is, offers are pouring in,
but your need to personally vet
each product you advertise
is extremely inefficient.
Going forward, we'll provide everything
from product selections, to PR lines,
and we'll upload straight to the feed.
Oh! You're busy enough as is.
Let's definitely do this.
That's not
how I do things, okay?
We'll be keeping my feed as is right now.
I'll go over the proposal in detail,
but I won't change
how I manage my account.
[Jun-kyoung] A-ri, please. Uh…
I'm sorry, Miss Seo.
[Jun-kyoung sucks teeth]
All of this is… [chuckles]
…good. It's easy money.
-We should rake it in while we can.
-[A-ri] Business is good.
Isn't that right, Mr. Ju?
All because I have an M
in my follower count.
I told you I'd make it big
and that you'd get your reward.
I've kept that promise.
So I'll tell you again
that I'll manage my account my way.
[pensive music playing]
Look, it's already been 20 minutes.
I have another appointment.
[Jeong-sun exhales shakily]
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[exhales]
[A-ri] Should we drop by the shop
before the event?
A-ri, I, uh… Why don't we do what he says?
Huh?
I mean, it just seems like
there's a lot of money on the line.
I'll pass. I just want to work
on the brand right now.
Is it because you don't want to pay Mr. Ju
a commission or something?
I could try taking it on.
Why would I give you that job?
It's not even something
you could really do.
-What?
-Let's drop this, okay?
I'm gonna cut back on ads anyway.
I've not been comfortable
doing sponsorships since the beginning
because I don't believe in them, so…
-You get it, right?
-[chuckles] Yeah. Yeah, I do.
We need to use our energy
on Ari.& for now.
Let's focus on making this thing huge.
-[elevator chimes]
-Great.
[button chimes]
[upbeat music playing faintly]
The goal was fusing
this breast cancer awareness campaign
with the type of parties
that Gen Z and millennials have at clubs.
We've invited a lot of A-list celebrities,
as well as online influencers,
and rest assured that all the entry fees
will be donated to charity.
That sounds pretty unique.
It'll be great
for raising public awareness.
Picketing campaigns were getting
a little stale, I must admit.
Oh, I wondered why you chose this venue.
Why did we change it?
I thought that we originally planned
to go with the Richen Hotel.
Yes, we did, but we were trying
to adhere with current trends.
Aragon is picky with its clientele,
but they agreed to it
because of Haeum's involvement.
We're grateful.
This is all thanks to you, Ms. Yoon.
[dramatic music plays]
[upbeat music playing]
♪ No time to check out
All the petty things that boys tell me ♪
♪ So don't be such a cling ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't want to hang out
With guys like you ♪
♪ Hey, don't let me down ♪
♪ No doubt the whole world
Revolves around me ♪
♪ I'm not sure you can take it ♪
♪ But good luck keeping up with me ♪
♪ Good luck keeping up with me ♪
♪ But get up out our way, girl ♪
[Du-seong] Whoa,
look at these insane lines.
[A-ri] Why did it have to be here.
Oh, let's fix up your face a little.
Uh, no. I'm good.
You're a public figure now, A-ri.
You have to look perfect.
I… I'm not a public figure.
Influencers are public figures
in the modern world.
Maybe the modern world
is wrong about that.
Celebrities are public figures?
We should reserve that
for people who help people.
What? Don't be so weird about this.
Oh, a pic! Let's snap a pic before we go.
-Wait, Du-seong, there's someone--
-[both gasp]
[both breathing heavily]
Is that girl fucking crazy?
Oh my God. Hey, are you okay?
-Did you get hurt?
-No.
I'm okay.
Oh, wait. Come on, you can't just go.
-We should take you to a hospital--
-Just leave me alone!
I just have to go now. [breathing heavily]
I'm sorry about this.
Sorry. I'm so sorry. [exhales]
[Jeong-sun] Does she plan
on wearing that to the party?
-[cheering]
-[camera shutters clicking]
[upbeat music playing]
[attendee] Whoo!
Min-hye, please,
can we get a word with you?
Um, it's such an honor to be invited
to an important
and meaningful event like this.
And I think tonight's gonna
be a lot of fun. [chuckles]
-And also, I'd like to--
-[all gasp]
[cheering]
Camera. Camera, over here. Hurry!
Oh! Oh!
Wait, why would they just run off?
[cheering intensifies]
[upbeat music playing]
[woman] Miss Seo A-ri,
thank you for attending this event
despite your busy schedule.
It's such an honor
to have you with us today.
I'm honored to just be invited
to such a meaningful event.
I think I'm gonna have
an amazing time tonight.
God, you asshole!
Why the hell did you let
that bitch in here, you idiot?
I didn't know, sir.
The organization hosting
was in charge of admitting--
-[sighs] Jesus!
-[man grunts]
[breathing shakily]
[sighs]
[woman] Are you the owner of this place?
You know my brother, don't you?
He used to work here.
[chuckles] Jesus fucking Christ!
What the fuck is this shit?
♪ Just move ♪
-[upbeat music playing]
-[cheering]
[chuckles]
♪ Just move ♪
[cheering]
Yeah!
[all cheering]
God, this sucks.
You made it here. I know you're busy.
I have to head out soon.
Just water tonight.
I figured I'd make an appearance
since you're hosting this.
Well, thank you for making the time.
Have fun tonight.
[Jun-kyoung] Si-hyeon.
We have to talk, don't we?
We have something to discuss.
I've been thinking about
what you said the other day.
What should I have known back then?
And what should we have said?
I told you that it doesn't matter now.
Understand?
There really isn't anything more
to say at this point.
The reason that you left me,
was it something I did?
If it wasn't just a change of heart,
was it…
'cause of everything that happened
that day in New York?
-[upbeat music playing faintly]
-[muffled cheering]
[upbeat music intensifies]
[cheering intensifies]
[Min-hye scoffs]
It's so boring here tonight. [sighs]
Ah, give me five! [chuckles]
[gasps] Oh my God, Choi Bom is here.
Choi Bom just got here. It's Choi Bom.
-Choi Bom is here?
-[Yu-rang gasps]
[Yu-rang] She's so pretty.
-Oh my God. Look, that's Choi Bom!
-[Choi Bom] Hi, A-ri.
Ah, you're here!
-[Choi Bom] How have you been?
-[A-ri] I've been great.
What?
-Since when are they so close?
-[Yu-rang gasps]
[Du-seong] So awesome!
My sister's like a rock star here!
God, she's really famous, huh?
She is.
A-ri looks really cool right now.
[camera shutter clicking]
[sighs] Shit.
[sighs]
Stop drinking. You're already drunk.
They just shoved me in some corner
while Seo A-ri's
living it up with the VIPs.
Maybe you should say something
to Chae-hee.
I think maybe she's right
about needing a drink.
Since we have to stare
at that bitch Seo A-ri from back here.
Excuse me for a minute.
[upbeat music continues]
I didn't expect to see you all here.
I thought I should at least say hello.
Fuck off, you crazy bitch, okay?
We're not exactly
on speaking terms, are we?
No, of course we aren't.
We live in different worlds.
And the tables in my world
-sit at a different level than yours.
-What?
[Min-hye] Seo A-ri,
don't let this get to your head.
Because you used to be a bottom-feeder.
You think getting that M
makes you any better than us?
Doesn't it?
According to your system, it does.
An M is pretty powerful compared
to basic K's. Don't you agree?
-[scoffs]
-What?
You're the ones obsessing
about where people sit
in this arbitrary ranking system.
[scoffs]
The tables have turned,
and now you can't take it?
Are you really surprised?
Hey! Watch yourself, A-ri.
You've forgotten your place, haven't--
There it is. "Your place,
how dare you, you're a loser."
You're still spewing
the same old bullshit.
But take a look around.
Open your eyes, Min-hye.
This is the world we live in.
And according
to your little immature ranking system,
I'm on a whole nother level than you now.
-[Min-hye] That fucking bitch.
-[Yu-rang] Wait, don't.
Hey, Seo A-ri.
Hey!
[screams]
[all gasp]
[crowd gasps]
[music halts abruptly]
[indistinct chatter]
-[pensive music playing]
-[Chae-hee exhales]
[gasps]
[Chae-hee breathing heavily]
[screams]
Chae-hee!
-Just calm down.
-[Chae-hee breathing heavily]
[Ji-na] Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Here, this way.
[Chae-hee continues breathing heavily]
[Ji-na] Let's go.
Come on.
Uh, I think we should go too.
[Min-hye sighs]
Whoa. A-ri, are you all right?
Do you know those people?
[gasps] Oh my God, your dress.
I'll be right back.
God, A-ri what do we do?
This dress… [sighs]
It's a sponsored item.
[A-ri] It's fine. I can just buy it.
[music halts]
[pensive music playing]
Did I really say I can just buy it?
[Tae-jeon] Miss Seo A-ri?
[chuckles] Funny running into you.
This charity event, my wife's hosting it.
[woman] Sir, no, please!
-Someone please help me! I won't go!
-[Yong-tae] I told you get out of here!
No, stop!
[Yong-tae] Stop. Calm down.
[woman] You have to help me.
Please, sir! Please! [sobbing]
Please listen to me.
My brother just isn't the kind of person
who would die that way.
He wouldn't die like that
leaving me and my mom--
[Yong-tae] Shut up, you bitch!
What in the world are you doing?
Oh God, Miss! [breathing heavily]
-[woman sobbing]
-Are you okay? Miss, are you all right?
[woman] It's not true.
My brother didn't kill himself.
[whimpering]
He wouldn't do that.
He wouldn't do that to me and my mom.
[Si-hyeon] I'm sorry, Miss.
What do you mean by that?
There was a suicide? Who's your brother?
[Tae-jeon] Honey!
[woman] I need my brother.
Please help me. [whimpering]
[Yong-tae] The thing is, that girl…
[woman continues sobbing]
[woman] It's not true!
Help me! I need someone to help me!
Aren't you going
to take care of this mess?
-[woman] Please help me!
-Oh, of course!
Come on, get up. Time to get up.
Let's just talk outside, okay?
-[woman screams]
-Outside, right now.
-[woman grunts] No! Get off me!
-[Yong-tae] We'll talk outside.
Outside! Let's go!
[sighs]
[Jun-kyoung] Come with me.
Let's go now.
Could it be…
[exhales shakily]
It was that man!
The man was
that poor woman's brother, right?
Wasn't he?
[scoffs]
[Tae-jeon sighs]
[Si-hyeon breathing shakily]
[engine roaring]
Don't hold back, and just ask me.
I saw that woman earlier.
We almost hit her outside the club.
Why…
You know what?
Seeing that look on your face
makes me not want to know the answer.
Pull over at the corner up there.
I think I need some fresh air.
I'll get some too.
I've been feeling that way as well.
[pensive music playing]
I know you haven't asked me yet,
but I think I need to let you know.
I…
I need you, Seo A-ri.
I know that's not the case for you yet…
but I hope that one day you'll
feel the same way about me.
[pensive music continues]
[A-ri] I remember
feeling the breeze on my skin
like it was yesterday.
It was so warm.
And so gentle.
[Si-hyeon breathing shakily]
[exhales]
[A-ri] Isn't it strange?
I still remember
everything about that moment so clearly.
Back then, I had no idea.
About what was to come,
or that my heart was opening up.
I didn't know that night was…
the last…
moment of peace I would ever get again.
[music fades]
[sighs]
Oh, Yu-rang.
Hey, uh,
you said that you saw something strange
in your husband's briefcase, right?
Some paper that was
an agreement with Taegang.
Uh-huh.
[heart beating]
[whooshing]
[keyboard clicking]
[whooshes]
[keypad clicking]
[phone buzzes]
[chimes]
-[whooshes]
-[chimes]
[A-ri] Bbb, it's nice to see you.
It's been a while.
[whooshes]
[keypad clicking]
[chimes]
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
Forget you? I would never do that.
I kept sending you DMs,
but you were the one
who wasn't responding.
-[chimes]
-[whooshes]
[keypad clicking]
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!!
YOU IGNORED ME
EVEN AT THE BRAND LAUNCH EVENT!!
YOU IGNORED ME AND ALL MY DMS!!
[chimes]
I had no way to respond to you
because I shut down all my social media.
I sent you numerous DMs
once I was back online,
but you never messaged me back.
_BBBFAMOUS
TYPING…
[pensive music playing]
[chimes]
YOU BETTER NOT TREAT ME LIKE THIS,
IF YOU HAVE COMMON SENSE.
[keyboard clicking]
[whooshes]
UNDERSTAND?!
RESPOND RIGHT AWAY WHEN I'M TALKING!!
[chimes]
No, I'm afraid I can't comply
with such a ridiculous request.
More importantly,
I need you to answer
some questions for me.
Who are you, bbb?
Why are you doing this to me?
I think it's time for me to find out
what kind of person you are.
ACTIVE NOW
OFFLINE
Is it confirmed?
He died not too long after the incident.
His body was cremated.
[sighs]
Once the man's family
started looking for him,
they were told he killed himself.
[Si-hyeon exhales shakily]
That lady we saw at your event
was his younger sister.
[inhales shakily]
[breathes deeply]
Stay out of it. I'll take care of this.
How could I stay out
when my husband used Taegang to do this?
You can stay out, and you should.
Why do you always try
to handle things all by yourself?
You're allowed to pass the torch
to other people.
You can say you're exhausted
and can't handle it alone.
You've always been like this.
[gentle music playing]
Hmm.
-You're here early.
-Mm-hmm.
Is that…
It is.
Didn't you say it was a little big?
That I bought the wrong size?
You did. That's Han Jun-kyoung for you.
Did you get a different size?
Oh no, I'll just wear it.
My ever aloof boyfriend
probably picked it out
without much thought.
But it's still a first.
I didn't want to exchange it.
I didn't just pick out whatever.
"Will it make her happy?
Will it look good on her?"
I wanted you to love it.
[chuckles]
-That's a very sweet thing to say.
-Well, it's true.
I ordered us wine. It's our usual.
[chuckles softly]
[Si-hyeon] I still remember so much
about the time we spent together that day.
Even the air that surrounded us
inside that restaurant.
I could still describe it
to you perfectly.
[sighs] I know, Mom.
I know Dad needs this,
and our family needs this.
But come on, Mom.
Do I even get a say
in the kind of life I want?
Please, you have to stop.
I don't want to hear this.
Bye.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[Si-hyeon gasps]
When'd you get here?
Just right now.
Sorry, I didn't mean to listen in on that.
[phone buzzing]
MOM
-I--
-Taegang.
And Tae-jeon.
I understand.
You marrying into
a rich corporate family like mine
won't help your dad become prime minister.
But Taegang's a law firm
that could prove useful.
[inhales deeply]
Doesn't it… [sighs]
…bother you
when my family calls me
about these things?
[chuckles]
Well, why should it?
These things happen sometimes.
And really, the choice is up to you.
[phone buzzing]
MOM
She'll worry if you don't pick that up.
[phone continues buzzing]
I'll get us coffee.
Latte, right?
[Si-hyeon] It hurt that I could never tell
what you were thinking
or how deeply you really cared about me.
And that was why I went back to Seoul.
I thought,
"When it comes to Han Jun-kyoung,
I guess I didn't mean
all that much to him."
That's what I realized.
Do you know what's funny?
I couldn't help but hold on to that dress,
even though I couldn't bear to wear it
or throw it away.
It felt like the sad remains
of the time we had spent together.
I want you to understand
that you meant so much more than that.
And those weren't sad memories.
However, I realize now
I should've answered you before you asked.
That back then,
I needed you.
That's no longer the case for us,
and it can't be.
But, Si-hyeon,
stop holding it all in
and shouldering the burden alone.
I'll do it.
-[Mrs. A-ri] It's so pretty, isn't it?
-[woman 1] It is.
-Ji-min, would you help her out over here?
-Of course.
-Oh, look, you're here!
-[woman 2] Hey.
Yes, just go right upstairs. [chuckles]
A social marketing collab
with a Chinese influencer?
[Gyeong-bae] Exactly.
Yes, an e-celeb contacted us directly.
Her name is Zhang Wei,
and she has a whopping
38 million followers on Weibo.
Oh, I've heard about Zhang Wei.
I know she has incredible pull
in the Chinese market.
Wait till you hear this.
She likes Ari.& so much
that she wants to collaborate
on a live commerce project.
Using our products!
Wait, are you serious?
Uh, hold on. Do you think our production
can handle this kind of scale?
Our current factory is already struggling
to keep up with the sales as is.
A-ri, this is something
worth investing in.
This is the opportunity of a lifetime!
Uh, still, we just shouldn't rush
into things like this--
A-ri.
Business is all about opportunities,
and this is the time for us to strike.
You should get prepared.
And I'll try to pull some funds together.
You understand how big
the Chinese market is, right?
If we take off there,
we're talking 10, 20 billion.
No, no, this company
could be worth ten times that.
The sky's the limit!
[chuckles]
[inhales]
How can this goddamn fucking bitch
have more followers than I do?
Shit! [inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[phone buzzes]
[phone continues buzzing]
What the fuck? Who's texting?
[sighs]
MISS JIN CHAE-HEE, AREN'T YOU CURIOUS
ABOUT HOW SEO A-RI REACHED HER FAME?
I COULD TELL YOU.
What the fuck is this about?
[chimes]
IF YOU REVEAL THIS,
YOU CAN GET RID OF HER RIGHT AWAY
[thunder rumbles]
God, my account isn't what it used to be.
[sighs] What am I even doing
looking at this stuff?
[crunches]
Hmm?
"Blowing the lid off"?
[gasps]
Oh my God.
Honey!
Honey, have you seen this yet?
They're talking about your clinic in this.
Where are they talking about it?
What are they saying?
Come on!
Someone wrote this crazy post online.
About your clinic!
And they're saying somebody died there!
[dramatic music playing]
-What?
-Look at this.
Apparently, Chae-hee and her girls
were doing drugs at Aragon
and someone ended up dead.
-They're saying your clinic is involved.
-Shut up.
You shut the fuck up!
[Min-chan breathing shakily]
JUNKIES WITH POWER
BEHIND AN UNDESERVING DEATH!
MOVED TO KMC PLASTIC SURGERY
TO HIDE THE DRUG PARTY
TG IS COVERING IT UP
DESPITE QUESTIONS FROM VICTIM'S FAMILY
-Sir, there's a post--
-Yes, I know.
That post,
do we know how far it's spread yet?
[tires screech]
How'd it go?
We reached out to the website
and got them to take down all the posts.
That's not enough.
By now, I'm sure it's been screen-capped
and spread like wildfire.
Scour every corner.
Find it all, and make them
take down every single thing!
The loan and investment commitments
are finalized.
They must've seen the potential
because they were approved right away.
Right. Okay, I'll see you
at the meeting tomorrow.
[line ends]
[gentle music playing]
I'm sorry, but the store's
already closed for the day.
You're Seo A-ri, aren't you?
The CEO of Ari.&.
[phone buzzing]
[dramatic music playing]
[line ringing]
Come on. Just pick up the phone, A-ri.
Yes, I am the CEO, Seo A-ri.
And… who are you?
We finally get to meet
after all this time.
Seo A-ri,
good to see you.
[phone continues buzzing]
CEO HAN JUN-KYOUNG
[closing theme music playing]
[music halts]