[English subtitles are available]
Where's the place in the photo?
Doi Mae Pliang, in Chiang Mai.
Is it the mountain that rains all year round?
I would love for you to go to Doi Mae Pliang.
The VVC camp.
The camp got vets.
And the villagers.
My name is Kung.
That lady is something.
I got the key. Shall we go to our room?
Tai, why are you here?
I want to ask you first.
I come with Lomfon for a school project.
So what about you?
Bow and I are doing a research for an article.
In the VVC?
Yes.
The pet hospital of my soul mate
arranges this camp.
Didn't you say you didn't know anyone?
Lomfon, his soul mate is here!
So, your soul mate is here?
Yes. You'll see him later.
Soul mate...
Can I do something for you?
Tai, that's him, right?
Yes. He is my soul mate.
His name is Patts.
Patts.
This is my brother, Saengtien.
And, that's my brother's friend, Lomfon.
Patts.
Yes.
Could you allow me to confirm something?
You are really Tai's soul mate, right?
Yeah.
You know what? I really want to see you!
Hey! Where are you going?
You and I need to check in. Don't waste the time.
Excuse me.
Why is he in such a hurry?
I'll catch you later. See you.
See you.
Lomfon!
Let's go to our room.
OK.
Let me hold that for you.
Thank you.
Which side would you like?
This side, thanks.
Umm...
What's up?
We haven't been together for a month.
The last time we were together,
we were…
I'll go to check the kitchen.
I heard they are short of hands.
See you.
This side's mine!
Okay.
Tien, give me the camera.
Hang on.
Be careful.
Where did you get this keychain?
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
This chain is important to me.
You're so heavy-handed.
It looks familiar to me.
It hangs the key to my dorm.
How could you haven't seen it?
Not like that.
I think I've seen someone else used this kind of keychain.
So who's that?
Like I said,
we are reciprocal to each other here.
We help each other out.
So how about we go to work now.
Let's go.
So, did you get your roommate?
Yes, but I got the bad ass of this camp.
The bad ass?
Hello, Bow!
Okay, guys. Let’s get started on our favorite kitchen work.
Bow, and...
Saengtai.
Saengtai? What a great name?
It's unique.
I want to have the same name with you. So I'd go with Saengkung.
Alright, Saengkung!
Yes, Bow!
If you get some problems, please let me know.
Bow, Saengtai, I'm looking forward to tasting your cooking.
So, who's your roommate?
Don't you know yet?
Saengkung!
Look at her.
Are you okay, Kung?
I'm going to faint.
She is definitely a bad ass.
But you two might hit it off.
Why do you still look unhappy?
Stop that, Saengtai!
Listen! At first, I also thought it would be OK.
But, when I got into the room and spotted a hot guy,
a very hot guy,
I thought I'd take the chance and talk to him.
And then the Saengkung...
got in front of me and pounced to him a female tiger!
I was the one who supposed to talk to that guy!
But she always get in my way.
I swear to God
that I must win this time.
Yeah, you guys are a perfect match.
Let's change the topic before I mess up this dish.
Okay.
Oh god, my head.
I really have a headache.
Ugh!
Let's continue our cooking.
Why are these beans broken?
Oh, now you are asking.
-What?
-Look.
Come on!
I think I've seen someone else used this kind of keychain.
So who's that?
I can't remember.
Why are you so curious about this?
That's none of your business.
The owner of this keychain saved my life.
I didn't see his face clearly.
But I treated him as my first love.
First love?
You're weird person. You even don't know whom you fall in love with.
It's important to see the person's face, you know?
But what about the people who have hearing loss?
The camera's set. Let's go!
Talking to you is such a waste of time.
Talking to you is such a waste of good mood.
Kung! You bitch!
Here, put it right here.
You shoot from this angle.
Try to shoot the details of their actions.
I will edit the video footage into the part where they are cooking.
Make me look good in the photo, okay?
Okay.
I'll give you the first taste.
(Singing) ♫The flowers are on the hill.♫
Hey you, look.
Zoom it.
That's adorable, right?
Leave me alone.
Oh.
Let's go. We'll be late.
Go. Push it.
You're helping me, right?
I am helping you.
Food is here!
Thanks for your hard work.
Here's some fruit.
Hey, Patts.
I just realize your boyfriend has a brother.
He's not his boyfriend yet.
You should get it right.
They are soul mates in a romantic relationship.
You are Lomfon, right?
Yes.
If you want some further information,
interview villagers,
or take photos of somewhere,
please tell me. I'll help you out.
Thank you.
Patts, eat your food.
Stop staring at your boy.
I'm waiting for him.
You're working here, not taking care of your boyfriend.
(Singing)♫ He is not his boyfriend yet.♫
Here we go again...
Patts, you should eat now.
We'll have a meeting with volunteers, and then with villagers at nine.
It's almost time.
Huh? From 9 am to 6 pm?
Yes. We also need to be there earlier.
I feel that Fluke and Ruj make jokes on us.
Will this be our daily routine?
This is even not a big deal.
Tomorrow, we will go to the village on the hill tomorrow.
What?
On the hill? That's so hard.
I'm starving.
Can I join you?
Sure!
Are you done with all?
Yes.
They all look delicious.
This one looks good.
My brother!
Your little brother is right here. Don't you want to say hi?
Are you even close to them now?
Don't you dare speak that loud.
They are like my brother-in-law's friends.
Anyway, you will take care of me, right?
He's not your brother-in-law. You are not making any sense.
Please excuse me. I'm full.
Lomfon!
Alright. We need to hurry up too.
The meeting, remember?
Seriously? I didn't eat my fruit yet.
Shut up. We are the seniors in the camp.
It looks juicy!
Why don't you eat, Patts?
I was waiting for you.
But you'll have a meeting.
I told him. He doesn't listen to me.
Never mind. I want to have my meal with you.
I just want you to be here with me.
Eat! Now!
Okay.
Quickly.
Lomfon!
What do you want?
You said something bad and walked away just like that?
It was you talking nonsense about your brother and Patts.
Have you ever asked them how they feel?
Though they are seeing each other, they might not like somebody to mention it.
That's not what you are thinking about.
I warn you now.
Think twice before you do something.
My brother and Patts are soul mates.
I won't let you get into their relationship.
You got me wrong.
Hey, you, aren't you feeling well?
-Where did you not feel well?
-Right here.
Please take notes and follow me.
Its name is Plaboo?
Yes.
It got a wound on the leg, right?
Did it get bandaged it well?
Okay.
Gently, gently, please.
Please cherish this plate.
-Be gentle to it.
-Exactly.
Please let me help you.
Like this way.
Gently wash it.
I took its temperature.
It got a fever. Look. It's shivering.
But, this one is healthy. I'll give it another check.
Good cat.
We're done. Good kitty.
Okay.
I treated its wound. There are some medicine in the bag.
-Please remember to get it the medicine.
-OK.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Let me get you a check-up.
This one is strong.
Patts.
Yes?
Can I interview you?
Sure.
Do we have to prepare that much?
The medical supplies?
Yes.
Of course.
When we arrange an activity, we can't really assume the concrete number of animals.
Let alone the quantity of the sick pets.
We do have to prepare this much.
At least, it's better to...
Better to have more than less.
Patts, please continue writing.
Oh.
You look sharp this way.
OK. OK.
Please cherish these plates. They're expensive.
Wash it gently, please.
Step back! It's better to wash them like this way.
Bow.
I think...
Bow, you must wash it gently.
You get to wash it slightly.
I think...
You can't wash them clean that way.
Please wash them like this, Bow.
We're running out of time!
I think you cannot, please! Bow!
No! Saengkung!
-We should washing them fast!
-Bow!
No, please.
It's just dish-washing!
Bow!
Everywhere is wet, Bow.
You got that!
Ugh!
(Together) Thank you.
-Safe back home.
-Bye bye.
See you.
-See you.
-Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Please put it here.
Thank you.
Wow.
Bow.
Saengtai.
Can't I have that one?
Just drink yours.
Okay. Thank you.
This work is quite tiring. Don't you think?
But, I think it's fun.
Yeah.
After I graduated, I have never experienced something fun like this.
You know that I hate crowds.
But I see you smiling all the time.
-(Laughing) La la la
-Stop that!
Alright.
Tai.
Let me ask you something.
When will you set your relationship with Dr. Patts?
I have no idea about that.
It's not entirely up to me.
Why do you ask that?
Well, I got something in my mind.
How should I put this?
I feel like you guys are a perfect match.
I want you to be happy with him.
I know that the current status doesn't matter.
But what makes it different is that, it makes clear
that you guys are a couple
to others.
To others?
Yeah.
Seriously.
I can see from his gaze and words.
Lomfon likes you!
Bow, don't you say that again.
I can feel that Dr. Patts has the same idea.
I'm a 100% sure.
Because I am an observant person.
Uh?
Tai, I know I should not say this.
But you are my close friend.
I don't want someone else interfere with you two.
I really support you guys, you know.
Really.
I'm rooting for you. OK?
How long do you want to shoot?
Half an hour. I set the timer to shoot.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're acting weird.
Why do you have to be so possessive of your brother?
I'm not.
If not, why are you mad at me?
If you don't think the way exactly as what you said,
then we'll be cool.
So, you are really mad at me?
Yes.
OK. I'm sorry.
Listen. I just don't believe in soul mates.
Don't you think it's strange that the universe could control our destiny since we were born?
It's hard to say.
The one who has hearing loss can hear only one voice when it rains.
If that's not a destiny, then what is?
Coincidence?
Huh?
A situation that just randomly happens.
That's not destiny.
No one can ever get your love life fixed into a certain way, right?
Only you can control it..
You can't compare them in that way.
If someone can hear your voice when it rains,
and you get exactly that one's voice,
and if the hearing loss guy lacks a soul mate,
his world will be filled with emptiness.
You are thinking with your emotions.
There are things that don't have to make so much sense.
We're talking about love.
You're talking like you've ever been in love.
Stop laughing.
Sorry.
What are you doing?
You look so cool just now.
Why didn't you ask first?
I got my own handsome angle, you know?
The pose was the best.
You'll act weird if you know that I'm shooting you.
OK. Then you are the only not-weird-guy.
Mocking me now, huh?
How long has it shot?
Not ten minutes yet.
I'll take a nap then.
Go ahead. I'll wake you up when time's up.
Lomfon.
Lomfon!
What's wrong?
Look.
So beautiful.
It is beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Did I wake you?
No.
I couldn't sleep.
My muscles are sore.
Too much work, I guess.
How about I give you a massage?
You can do that?
Yeah. I used to do it for my father.
Then, please be my masseur.
OK.
May I?
Here we go.
Okay.
That's so good.
Why are you staring at me?
I don't know if you know this.
Now, you're so cute.
You teased me first.
I'm not ready.
Give me more time, OK?
Can I help you, then?
Tai.
Are you sure about doing this?
[I go to work.]
[I see you sleep tight so I don't want to wake you up.]
[P.S. I don't have to work at the last day in the camp.]
[Let's go up on Doi Mae Pliang together that day.]
Saengtai.
What are you looking at?
Who's that girl?
She's very cute.
I didn't see her yesterday.
Her name is Nara, I think.
She just arrived here this morning.
Bow. Saengtai.
Come here and give me a hand.
I get some work for you.
Nara. I get this guy to help you.
I told that to him.
OK. Go ahead.
We are so busy today.
-Bow.
-Yes.
Yes?
Could you help me pick the vegetables?
No problem.
Here you go.
OK.
I am Nara.
What's your name?
Saengtai.
Saengtai!
What a nice name.
It reminds me of aurora.
Yours are cute, too.
Me?
I mean your name.
Oh.
I prepared all of these but I'm not sure whether that's enough.
Can you help me check it out?
I think these are enough.
Well, shall we start then?
Alright.
They're cute, aren't they, Bow?
They're getting along so quickly.
Bangkok people are so cute, right?
That's weird. Tai usually get along with others very slowly.
Bow, I'll  get the car. I'll leave you to this, OK?
Of course.
Take care of Bow, you all.
Yes.
What's that?
An umbrella.
Why you do this?
To make sure you look great.
The bento looks cute.
Really? I made it for my ex boyfriend.
Your ex boyfriend?
Yeah. He's also a vet and he's in this camp.
Once I heard that, I came here to make up with him.
But, I've been breaking up with him for a long time.
It's weird I can still remember every detail about him,
about what he likes and dislikes.
The omelette must not be cooked with so much oil.
He also likes flower-shaped carrots like this.
I'm sure you'll make up with him.
I'm relieved as you say so.
Thank you.
Not at all.
Nara.
What's the name of your ex?
Maybe I know him.
Everybody!
The car is here!
Let's go!
OK.
Let's go. Help each other with the stuff.
We need to go now.
All good?
All good.
Food is here.
Food is here. Come and eat, everyone!
Please come here.
Bow.
Yes.
Food is here.
Please come and eat.
Take your food.
It's so hot today,
right?
Wow. Is this the bento with fried eggs?
Yes.
Wow.
Tien!
Hey, my brother.
Stop! It's not yours.
I'm your little brother!
I already knew that.
Have you seen Patts?
He's not done yet, I guess.
I heard he went to the village for some cases.
OK.
OK. OK. OK.
Your food is there.
The brown box.
It's not a special one.
Because I don't care.
Just leave them alone.
Yeah.
Saengtai.
Hey, did you have your meal?
Not yet.
Let's go eat with us.
Yeah? Let's go.
Let's go and eat.
Yeah.
Patts is still working.
It'll take for a while.
I'm not hungry.
Alright.
Let's go.
Just eat a bit first. Then you can get to Patts later.
Go, go.
I'm starving. Let's have some food.
Saengtai, Patts is...
Over there?
Thank you.
(Singing) I'm starving.
Anyway, they will find it out.
Tai's gone.
What?
Let's go and check the back of the camp.
I'll check the room.
Tai went to Doi Mae Pliang.
Why didn't I think of that!
Oh no.
It's going to rain.
No one is allowed to get into the mountain.