[English subtitles are available]
Yesterday, I just responded to the soul mate.
What??
Friends like you. No thanks.
What’d you say? Do you want a fight? Huh?
Maybe, the name’s Duer.
Oh wait. Don’t take it home, please.
Why do I want to talk to him now though I haven’t answered him for 2 years?
[Phat Wetchutianan]
Hey, you!
What’s your name?
What?
Phat. My name is Phat.
Um. Just a moment.
Phat...
Are you still there?
Yes.
Last night, the rain stopped before I finished?
Well, I think I'll defy my destiny.
Come again?
I think I might have found "the one".
I know it's none of your business.
Having been talking with you for 2 years might have annoyed you enough.
But... thanks a lot for listening.
OK.
Hungry now, Duer?
Hey, I got you some snacks.
Want some?
I think I might have found "the one".
So, this is what it's called heart-broken.
Dad.
Dad! Dad!
Can you not go?
How are we going to live without you?
No. Please don't go.
When you miss me, you just come visit me.
Then, we can go out together.
But I want to stay with you every day.
Chan.
Chan, Chan.
No! Don't go.
Don't do that.
You're making it hard for Dad.
Now that it comes down to this, you're really not going to say a thing?
Say something now? You won't even understand.
As if not saying something now's going to help?
Good!
It's best... that you know nothing.
Dad! Dad!!
Chan, Chan. Don't.
Dad!
-Dad!
-Tai!
You called me. What's up?
I'm worried about you.
I found my soul mate!
He said he'd defy his destiny.
He said he found "the one".
I saw him right here. I remembered his voice.
And, I took a peek at his name.
Then, it rained. So, I talked to him.
I asked him, then that's when I knew he's my soul mate.
I don't think he knows I'm his soul mate.
It's the one and only time we met.
He's super adorable!
Hey!!!
You... dragged me out in the middle of the night.
On the rainy day.
You know, before I arrived here...
I took a bus, I took a train.
I took a motorbike, in the rain.
I am wet and exhausted.
In order to learn that you found your soul mate.
And, he's got "the one". Am I right?
Now, you say he's cute.
Right?
Just like that?
What have you been doing in the last 2 years? Tai!
Hey, dude, calm down.
When he said he's got the one of his own...
I was like...
I'm like...
Saengtai!!!
What are you looking at? I'm freaking tired, man!
Listen to me.
You already fucked with love, un-! fuck! it!
[Unfuck it]
Don't you forget.
Hey!
Tien! Hey! I didn't finish!
Are you okay?
Can I help you?
"Unfuck it"?
Tien, you little...
Um. It is um... the new topic that...
I'm about to write.
That sounds weird.
Got to go to work very early tomorrow. Please excuse me.
Achoo!!
That little prick!
Yes, Pingpong?
Heyyy, my little bro!
Where are you?
In the university. What's up?
Look, I really need your help.
I'm sending you the location. Come, please.
-What's this about?
-Just come!
Don't ask. I'm in trouble. Just come here.
My life needs sighing this much!?
You've got to be joking?
I'm serious.
This look suits you.
So cool.
This look?
Yes!
Seriously, what is this about?
Here, read this.
A short film?
Yeah.
Listen to me carefully.
The actor that I assigned arrived the set this morning.
And, he got a COVID test. He found the 2 lines...
Meaning he got COVID?
Meaning, he's pregnant.
Just kidding. He got COVID, yeah.
Now, when he got COVID, I was like, hey, I already paid for this set!
I paid for the lights, the cameras.
Do you think I would waste all of it?
Do you think I would not give my bro a call?
There's always "my bro" with you.
Just help me out, my bro.
Listen, the role you got here is named "Tongfah" (Sky).
Tongfah is 17. He quit studying.
He started to sing for a living, in various events.
In various places.
-He helped his family.
-Uh-huh?
He's quite poor though.
And, one day, all these elite kids...
threw a party.
They were looking for a dorky country-music singer.
"Feels-like-a-bullying" thing, you know?
Like, they hired the singer just to bully him.
OK...
But when Tongfah went there, he saw his friend.
A childhood friend named "Gonmek" (Cloud).
So, they like each other?
Finally, you met him when you're surrounded by the bullying elite kids. Something like that.
Got it?
Damn... deep script.
Yeah, you can do it.
And, who plays Gonmek?
Gonmek...
Hey!
I think you know him very well.
So, this is Gonmek?
"Gone-with-acting", maybe?
See? This is just the beginning.
I knew it. You guys' chemistry is lit.
I love it.
I just fought with him, you know.
That's the thing. That's why I called you.
Pingpong, I have friends who are very good at acting.
Maybe we should replace this guy?
Replace you, indeed?
Guys, don't. You two are actors.
And, "I" am the director.
Where's "the-show-must-go-on" spirit?
Trust me, guys.
Just listen closely when I explain the blocking. I've already wated so much time.
Job!
What's wrong?
Um... I don't think I sang that well.
A lot of people laughed at me.
Just ignore them.
I don't really care about them that much.
Cut!!!
What do you think you are doing??
Shit... I've had more than 10 takes with you guys.
Difficult dialogue? No! You studied acting.
What the hell is wrong with you guys?
-Pingpong, maybe we just change this..
-No! Zip it! I don't want to listen to any excuses.
Just go! Go take a rest. Go!
You come here.
Job, come here.
How late are we?
-We're 2 hours late.
-2 hours?
You had to know that I wasn't going to make it?
Come here, you. Come. Come here.
Why didn't you tell me we're behind!?
Huh!?
-Come here. You come here.
-Calm down, Pingpong.
You and I need to make a deal.
Let's do a cease-fire for now. Finish the job and talk.
A cease-fire? I don't see you as an enemy.
What are you saying?
I mean, you and I get the job done and just escape each other.
Yes. But, it's not like we can do it in one take?
You rehearse with me.
How?
The workshop.
That the professor taught.
Remember?
Yes. I remember. But which one?
Close your eyes.
Scene 3, cut 10, take 45. Action!
What's wrong, Tongfah?
I think I didn't do it well.
They all laughed.
Just ignore them.
Yeah, I don't really care about them.
Why do they turn so good now?
May it pay off for the shit I've had all day.
What happened Tongfah?
We haven't seen each other for a big while.
Ever since you left the school.
I had my own reasons.
Family issues?
Family issues.
What? The script doesn't have holding hands?
Shush! Let them be!
You know "magic moment"?
Do you want to talk to me about it?
Perhaps later.
I'm worried about you.
If you ever want to talk, I'm here.
Thanks.
Um, isn't it too romantic?
It's good the way it is.
Love does bloom anytime.
Tai, what are you thinking?
The food isn't good?
Are you in love? Have you fallen in love with someone?
What!! I took the right guess?
Woah! Easy, easy.
Answer me.
I met my soul mate.
What!! Are you for real?
Sorry.
When? How?
How did you know he was your soul mate?
Is he handsome? Hmm?
I found him at a coffee shop.
I remembered his voice.
When it rained, I asked his name.
So, I knew he's the same person.
So, you did answer to him.
How did you know his name?
I saw it on his gown.
He's a veterinarian at Sirivech Hospital.
Woahhh!
You haven't talked to him for 2 years, but he's been this close to you.
Does he know you're his soul mate?
I don't think so.
Because I haven't answered him.
He couldn't have remembered my voice.
Let me guess...
You met him for the first time and already started to like him?
Hmm?
Whattt! So cute!
Then what? How far are you two now? Hmm?
That's when it gets complicated.
I don't have the guts to talk to him.
What...
I just didn't know how to start, which topic to start, or what am I supposed to...
Saengtai, Saengtai.
If you like him, you talk to him first.
He is your soul mate.
When it rains, you talk to him.
I think he must be glad because he's been trying to reach you in these 2 years.
It's just... It's just that...
You like it so much?
To complicate things?
You like him, you make a move.
How?
Begin with things he likes or you like.
He's a vet?
Yes.
Duer.
Huh?
Duer?
Meow!
We're here.
Are you afraid?
Sorry, bud.
Let's follow Bow's advice.
Hello! Is this the first time here?
Yes.
How can we be of the cat's service today?
It wants vaccines.
OK. Please fill in the profile form at the counter.
OK.
Just a moment please. The vet will come in.
Yes.
Hello! First time here?
Cat!
What an adorable cat!
The name's Duer.
Alright. Duer.
Mr. Saengtai...
Can I call you Saengtai, so we can be close?
I don't mind.
Let's bring the cat on here.
Come here.
First time?
On the back first.
It never got vaccines, right?
No, nothing.
I found Duer on the street.
Ah...
Is there something wrong?
Heart and lung seems normal.
Okay.
Let me see your front, buddy.
But we need to clean the ears, okay?
What about your teeth here?
Also normal, overall.
Today, I'll get the first vaccine for it.
-Please help hold it.
-Yes.
Hang on. Just a little jab.
-A little jab.
-Just a little of this.
Good job.
And, we're done.
You may take it home now.
Good job, good job.
Normally, how many vets do we have here?
Normally, we have six veterinarians.
Four general vets, two specialist vets.
OK.
Is there something wrong?
No, nothing. It's just that...
I see this place is huge, so I just want to know how many.
Normally, if the attending is unavailable,
there will be a substituting attending.
Yeah?
Yes.
OK.
We're good for today.
Please bring it here again for the second vaccine in the next two weeks.
Don't forget.
I won't.
In the next 7 days, don't get it bathed.
And, please observe any irregular conditions.
If those conditions occur, you can always bring it here.
Sounds good.
And, the second vaccine, a kind reminder once again.
OK.
What happened?
No, I'm fine.
I meant...
Oh! I just got it a vaccine.
First vaccine?
First vaccine.
Duer, is it?
Got a jab, right?
Yes. It stayed the whole way through.
Good job.
How are you doing on "Unfuck It"?
Um, I wanted to revise it, so I wanted to see you.
Right.
Yeah?
Please excuse me. I have to go.
Who's in love around here?
Is the singing necessary?
It's just the right vibe.
Right?
What?
Pass it to Wit, pass it.
Who?
Let me do a roll call.
Here.
Wittaya?
Jessada?
Here.
Ratchanon?
Lomfon?
Here.
Saengtien?
If not here, then I may mark "absent".
-Here!
-Hoorayyy!
Just in time.
First class and you impress the professor just like that?
The prof will target you.
Everyone's targeting me. Yet, here I stand.
The new prof looks sloppy. Right?
Sloppy? This is an assistant professor.
Oh, okay.
Hello, all students.
Hello.
Before we get started,
I'm assigning you some mid-term work.
So, you guys got the objectives to study.
I'd like pairs of students to make a documentary.
Telling a story with visuals and silence.
Professor, but we haven't studied anything yet.
But you study film, am I right?
If you don't make films, how do you know you can make films?
Yes.
In terms of pairing, I'll randomize the names.
You are Saengtien?
Yes.
Please pair with Lomfon.
What!?
What?
Are you not close?
When you are on set, you work with only close friends?
Being on a set is being with humans.
If you can't collaborate with others,
I may have to consider hard about letting you pass this class.
Duer.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Are you mad at me?
What have I done today?
How are you doing on "Unfuck It"?
Um, I wanted to revise it, so I wanted to see you.
In the next two weeks until seeing you, right?
You're hiding from me now?
Look, you needed to get the vaccine.
You can't blame me.
What now?
Mom asked,
Got any food request?
She'll prepare it.
No.
Sure?
Yeah.
Duer.
Hey!
I'll leave you alone.
Forty baht, please.
OK.
-Just enough. Here.
-OK.
Thank you.
Tien?
Just arrived?
A while ago.
Why not go in?
Should I though? I go in alone, I got complained alone.
You didn't do anything wrong. Why are you talking about complaints?
Oh my, I exist therefore I got complaints.
You don't know or just pretend to be dumb?
Just get inside. I want out already.
Did you really want to come?
Really wanted to come.
Reeeaaally!
Okay. I'll be in a hurry to check the timeline of the UAT and check with the developer again.
You think it’s too slow, right?
And, our database is ready.
I'll update the post-launch strategy asap.
Okay.
Mom.
To the table please. I'll catch you.
Hey, isn't it Sunday?
Have you ever seen her free from work?
Already managed. No worries.
What's with the fancy dress?
Ah. I'm meeting with a foreign client about a contract.
They happen to be available today.
I prepared all the food you like.
If want something more, tell me.
I wouldn't finish all this.
Alright. Eat then.
Tien.
The grades are not so good, you know?
Yes.
Skipped a lot of classes?
Why would I do that?
Why would I know that?
It's been a force of habit since your high school.
Maybe, things have changed?
If you don't want me to think like that, make good grades then.
You got to study what you like, didn't you?
Yes.
And you, Tai? How's your work going?
So so, I guess?
"So so" doesn't really mean "good". Am I right?
I just talked to my friend in the UK.
If you want to go for a master's there, they will take care of you.
All the costs, I'll manage.
I don't remember telling you I want a master's?
I'm not forcing you.
It's not a crime just looking into it.
If you want to go study somewhere, we can always talk, right?
-I just don't want to see you waste your time with...
-Mom...
Why did you call Tien and me here? Is there anything important?
Remember Uncle Nu?
Uncle Nu, your boyfriend?
Uncle Nu and I may have decided that...
we're getting married.
Saengnuea and Saengchan already know this.
That's the reason I summoned you two here today.
Does Dad know?
-Yes, he does. And, he doesn't seem to...
-Mom!
Isn't it too fast?
How about Dad? How can he live?
I didn't expect this much of your selfishness.
Hey.
Tai.
I'll go talk to him.
Tai!
Tai. Can you just calm down?
You can't do this.
Let me ask you this.
What is it that's "can" or "can't" for you, huh?
"Can" she remarry just like that?
You got me wrong.
You can't just walk away like this.
You didn't even try to talk to her.
Talking to her now won't make me understand.
You know...
Every time I see Dad, I can always feel it.
I feel that Dad still loves her.
To tell you the truth, I'm confident...
that I shouldn't talk to my soul mate.
Rain.
Sorry. Let's chat later.
You heard that, didn't you?
I'm sorry. That won't happen again.
Saengtai
Isn't it Lomfon?
Wasn't sure you'd remember.
Wasn't sure about your name. But, I remember you.
Are you working?
Yes.
I always come here to work when I'm free.
Don't you have to go to class?
It's canceled today.
Tien didn't tell you?
We don't live together.
We'd fight to death, otherwise.
Agreed.
You and that brat are very different.
Oh!
I like that book so much!
Me too. It's my second time reading it.
Really?
I've read 2 times too.
Did you read the other books by this author?
No. Will you suggest some?
Yes. Here. All good stuff. Hang on.
Seriously?
I love that too!
The first-published version was so rare!
You know what, I got that version.
Really?
No way! How!
This one is so hard to find.
I really want it.
Can I get your address?
Huh?
I'll ship it to you.
It's OK, Lomfon. I know it's hard to find and it's expensive.
You keep it.
I just see your wish.
And, I think these books belong to the one who really loves them.
Better that way.
Also, you are the bigger fan of this author than I am. So...
Um...
Alright. I'll pay you.
Just give me your bank account.
No need.
Buy me a coffee. That should do.
Really?
One more Americano, please.
Okay.
Do you want anything?
Never mind.
Okay.
Thank you.
Frankly, you're the first one I feel fun to talk to about books.
Right.
I think, it feels nice when two people talk about their mutual interests.
It's fascinating to discover someone who shares my passions - just like you, don't you think?
Um, nice convo always carries away, right? Maybe I should continue working.
I may work now.
OK.
Same vet, please. Same vet, please.
The owner of Duer may come in now.
Yes.
Hello, there.
Here we go again.
The second jab now, right Duer?
Be good.
Hurt a bit, okay?
Stay still. Stay.
Not gonna hurt, okay Duer?
-Woah, woah!
Duer!
Duer! Duer!
Guys, it's running away!
What happened?
Cat's running away. I was giving it a vaccine.
-Where?
-You move first!
Stop! Naughty cat!
Oh!!
Duer!
Here you are, you naughty cat!
-Wait!
-Woah!
-Duer!
Duer!
Your name is Saengtai, right?
I'm Phat.
See? We know each other now.
Didn't you hear what the professor said?
Why didn't you say something?
How about you? Why didn't you say you didn't want to pair up with me?
That's my glass!!
You got someone else. You shouldn't talk to me!