[English subtitles are available]
[Watch on kisskh.co]
Tai, as your father, I didn't think that I'd get to meet your soul mate.
Father!?
Yeah.
Let's hide from the rain.
Maybe my place? It's not far from here.
So I can get into your home?
Tai, do you have a bath towel...
Tai, I'm out of the shower.
You can go now.
What's wrong? Are you shy?
No. I'm not.
Then, go and take a bath or you'll feel uncomfortable.
Patts...
I didn't see anything.
You liar!
Okay. I only saw a little.
Then, I went to take the shower.
Not buying it!
Did you see my scar?
Do you have a scar?
I didn't see it.
See? Liar. That was a test for you.
How can you be so sure I don't have a scar?
You said you didn't see.
Liar.
Alright. What can I do now,
to make you happy, not embarrassed, and...
take a bath?
How about this?
I'll just take this bath towel off.
You'll see me naked.
Then we'll call it even. Alright?
I'm taking it off now.
Patts! Stop!
If you were someone else, I would not think too much and just stop here.
But now, I want to wait for you to be ready.
I hope this is not a momentary impulse.
I want you to know
that you're important to me.
Go to take your shower.
The woman in the picture is your mother, right?
Yes.
What's the place in this picture?
It's Doi Mae Pliang, in Chiangmai.
Oh. Is the mountain raining all year long?
Yes.
It is said that if someone can climb to the top of the mountain
when it rains,
any wish he makes can come true.
My parents reached the top on a rainy day.
And then, my father proposed.
That's romantic.
But, they are divorced.
When we reach some point,
the point where we've grown,
you'll realize that only love is not enough to stay together with your loved-ones.
But, I trust in the bond between you two.
You guys will make it.
OK.
In fact, I think you should go there.
I don't know if you can understand what I'm going to say.
But I think this wish thing
is like our thoughts.
Our thoughts?
What do you mean?
If you go there, you might get to know something,
and you can understand your parents better.
Let's go there when we have time.
It's up to you. When will you be available?
We'll see.
As for our hospital's corporate social responsibility,
in the past two years, we helped the society by funding financial support to various charity projects.
We are pretty busy in hospital everyday.
Now, Fluke and Ruj, our respected seniors,
also the founders of this hospital,
think we need to carry on what they did,
which is exactly the two projects I have mentioned.
But, our respected seniors are unwilling to do by themselves.
And, they might have expected that we can take this.
Am I correct?
Patts, you can't say that.
It's our second time to do this project.
And, I don't see any other project is the better
for us to help out the society.
See? Did I make myself clear?
OK. Actually, I did some research.
And, I have an idea.
Doi Mae Pliang village?
We didn't do our project there.
Pang Pliang village, Doi Mae Pliang.
In Chiangmai?
Yes.
Why do you choose this village, Patts?
The previous one you got wasn't bad.
And, it's much more closer to here.
That's the point.
Pang Pliang village is quite far from the city.
From the map, we can get to know that
villagers need to walk one to two hours to get to the hospital in the city.
With that distance,
villagers find it inconvenient to get animals being treated.
I have already called the relevant organization for consultation.
And I learned that the village is divided into five sub-villages
with a total of 158 households.
Many families have pet cats and dogs,
which takes account of 70%.
So does that mean that it's inconvenient for villagers to get their pets being treated in hospitals.
and there is no organization has reached out to them?
Because the village is relatively poor and remote.
So the problem is that the number of animals has increased a lot.
as they are not properly sterilized.
Besides, most of the animals do not get the vaccines that they need.
So I think that compared to the previous choice,
this choice is better.
I agree.
Hey! Way to go! Patts!
But going to Chiangmai is a huge deal.
If you choose this one, you need to get more people.
Only a few of us are too busy to handle it.
Don't you worry about that.
Fluke, Ruj, our university will arrange a volunteering camp.
We can get in contact with faculty of Veterinary Science,
to see who would like to volunteer with us as a vet.
They will definitely approve a good project like this.
Good job!
Let's do this!
I'll do the paperwork and talk to the university.
I'll keep you informed of something new.
OK. Let's call it a day.
Patts!
Yes.
Great job.
-Very good!
-Thank you.
-I think so, too.
-Really?
What are you standing there for?
Saengtien!
Yes?
Lomfon!
What a coincidence, my dear friend!
Come here.
How can I help you, Pingpong?
Today...
Please don't tell us your reshooting stuff.
I'm going to hit your mouth!
Hit it hard! You'll see!
That work is done and I got four credits.
However, today...
I'll invite you to my wrap party!
Woohoo!
Can I not go, Pingpong?
I really don't want to go.
Hey!
What did you just say?
-Okay, I'll go.
-He's missing a big one.
Awesome!
Look at Saengtien. He never rejects me.
Of course not!
So, let's go now.
Hey, Pingpong.
Can we come with you?
Did you play a role in the video?
No.
Are you in this project?
Did you do something?
Not really.
Then, you can't come.
I'll be waiting at home. See you!
Okay.
Pingpong.
Yeah?
We go with this outfit?
Hey. It's a party in my house.
Chill. You can dress anything you want.
Got it?
Okay. Got it.
Besides, most of my friends are going to graduate.
You will definitely be able to expand your network this time.
See you then.
I'll wait for you!
Okay!
Let's get some drinks, then.
Thank you.
What's up, Patts?
Do you remember what we talked about last night?
Where is the place in the picture?
Doi Mae Pliang, in Chiangmai.
Oh. Is the mountain raining all year long?
My parents reached the top on a rainy day.
And then, my father proposed.
Yeah.
I want you to go there.
Today, we talked about CSR in hospital.
We finally decided to go there for a project.
And, we collaborate with a university.
Those who are interested can also go together.
Would you like to come with me?
But what can I do there?
I'd feel useless, if I went.
There are actually many things to do.
Maybe you choose something that you can do.
I'm afraid I don't want to go.
Because of the camp or Doi Mae Pliang the place?
Okay.
I understand.
But may I speak from my perspective?
Nothing is more important than you.
And I do think that
we might find more about our state of being soul mates,
if we go there together.
Okay. Let's have our meal.
Okay.
Cheers!
Woohoo!
To tell you the truth, I want to thank all of you.
You have worked so hard until the last minute.
I scolded all of you, but you weren't angry with me.
Cheers!
Yay!
Woah.
Saengtien is the real deal!
Wow.
Woohoo!
That's how we do it!
Everyone, this is Saengtien.
I'm thirsty all of the sudden.
Let your Pingpong man fill your cup.
-Hey!
-Nice!
Awesome sauce.
Awesome sauce!
Cheers!
Aren't you really good at this?
Trying to play the cool?
Mr. Lomfon, please drink it.
Bottoms up. Bottoms up. Bottoms up.
More. More. More and more.
A round of applause!!
Attaboy!
Where's Job?
Job!
Maybe he is drunk and went back?
I saw he puked at the front gate.
Really?
Yes!
What!
-Job!
-Hold on.
You come here.
You are my assistant here, not a dog.
Who's get to buy some ice for me?
We are running out of it.
-Job! We need you to go buy it!
-I can!
I can go to buy the ice.
Oh, please behave yourself.
You're too dumb for this!
I let you buy ice, but you get me coke.
I tell coke, and you buy Sprite.
I'll just buy it in person.
You guys come with me. Help me out there
I'll pay.
Okay?
(Together) Yay!
-Let's go!
-I pay it all for you all!
It's just for you all.
I'll pay for it.
Buy as much as you want. Can you grab…
Where are you going?
To buy the ice?
Um, sir, please shut up and have a seat.
Just stay in the house.
I'll go and buy it.
My house is in your hands.
I got it, bro!
See you, bro.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I don't think so.
You're now as soft as water.
Oh, your shoulder is soft.
Can I stay here for a minute?
Why are you staring at me?
Nothing.
Can I sleep here?
Okay.
Good.
Cheers!
You're not that bad when you are drunk.
Shit.
What the hell is the water?
Come here.
Brother. My brother!
Get in!
Watch your head. Your head!
Oh, oh!
Move! Move!
He's quite heavy.
Luckily, he can call you to pick him up.
Here.
Thank you.
He always doing this.
When he's do drunk, he always makes some trouble for me.
How do you go home?
Or you'll stay?
I told them I wanted to call it a night.
If I stay, it'll be called morning.
And, I got a cab, too.
It'll be here soon.
Okay. I should go then,
before he pukes in there.
Okay.
Hey, thank you for taking care of him.
If there's anything I can help you, please let me know.
Just be my guest.
Well, can I have a dinner with you?
OK.
I got to go.
Saengtai. Can I get your number?
I wonder if you can tell me when Saengtien arrives his place.
Sure.
-Thank you.
-See you.
Tien. Move!
You're such a big baby.
(Singing) I'm a big baby.
Let's go.
(Singing) Who's the big baby?
Ugh! I hate headache!
Well...
Well, what?
Don't you throw up here.
Drink that much and wake up this early? I'm kind of respect you.
Woah!
Saengtien is the real deal!
I have to take the class.
How was last night?
They might stay to the morning.
I went home after sending you off.
Did you do anything weird to me?
What are you saying?
Only you got drunk and threw a drunken fit last night.
Really?
I'm normally cute when I'm drunk.
But my ribs hurt when I'm awake.
And also my back.
Did you kick me?
Or the taxi driver kicked me.
Why didn't you look after me?
You were just drunk and being a big burden. That was all.
Especially troubled your brother.
Tai, you mean?
Bro, my bro!
Get in!
Watch your head. Your head!
Oh, oh!
Move! Move!
He's quite heavy.
Jesus. Are you for real?
He'll definitely tell my parents.
I'm dead.
What should I do?
Holy shit!
-You...
-Excuse me.
Veterinary Volunteering Camp...
by the Faculty of Veterinary Science,
collaborating with a vet hospital in Mae Pliang District,
Chiang Mai province.
Hey..
You know what I'm thinking, right?
I'm thinking what you're thinking.
Listen to me.
The camp's got vets,
animals, and villagers.
And villages on the mountain.
We just roll the camera from the start,
until the moment they treat the animals.
I figured the concept out!
We figured the concept out.
We figure the concept out!
You do the PPT work. We must hurry to hand it to our professor.
Good job, Lomfon.
What will you do then?
Presenting.
Do you not help me with the PPT?
I present. You do the PPT.
We do our own job. Yeah!
We both need to present.
I can present by myself.
OK. Double check the stuff.
Do you know what's wrong with him?
He looks so gloomy.
Are you OK with this?
I'm here!
Hurry up, will you?
You are so slow.
What's wrong with Patts?
The one he invited doesn't come.
I heard he has been pursuing that person for a long time.
Yeah.
Until now, they are not officially dating yet.
Just in the stage of learning each other.
But you guys are wrong.
Ahem.
Saengtai.
What's up?
What are you doing here?
Because you wanted me to come.
Yes, but I'm not expecting that.
I said I don't want to come, didn't mean that wouldn't.
Do you feel being enforced?
No.
I gave it a thought about what you said.
Going to Doi Mae Pliang might get me something.
Did you ask for a leave from work?
Well, about that.
Here's how it went.
I made a proposal to the company that I could write a column about the vets taking care of the animals in the community.
Bow supports this idea.
They liked the proposal. So we're here.
That's nice.
Ahem. Ahem.
You guys are so cute. I want to barf.
How long are you two going to talk?
Yeah?
OK. Why not both of you join my team now?
You team?
I'll introduce Bow to everyone.
I'd love to! I love to meet new people!
Hello!
Especially meeting a hot, kind, sporty, and pet-loving guy!
Great! Can you help carry these?
Here.
All of these?
Yes.
And this one?
All of these.
Thank you very much.
Let me help you.
Thanks for the help.
You can put it in my car.
Not too heavy, right?
No, not at all.
-Please hurry.
-You guys have to carry all of these?
I'll be back for that bag.
Okay.
Pull over!
What?
Do you want me to drive?
No need. You actually slept all the way through.
Dude. We're here.
So beautiful.
Tien, we have to go.
Or we'll be late.
Okay.
Don't be so slow.
You peed so frequent.
It's normal, right?
We'll be here for several days.
Wow! Saengtai!
Here is beautiful.
Come here, Saengtai!
Chiangmai's so beautiful!
Come on. Come here!
Look at the umbrellas. So cute!
Wow.
They really prepared something.
That gal is quite over the top.
Hello.
Hello, everyone.
You all are looking good.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Kung.
I'll be taking care of you guys in this camp.
Who's got some concerns or doubts, please text me.
I have my social media. You can add me as a friend.
That woman is definitely something.
Now, let me start with the first thing.
Firstly, I'd like you to pair up as roommates.
Who's got their roommate, please take your keys and refreshing water right here.
You look sharp.
Bow.
Stop. I know what you're about to say.
This is exactly why you two don't get any closer.
Come on.
I'm really worried about you.
You're not going to be my roommate?
No.
Who's going to be your roommate then, if it's not me?
I'll just find someone.
So, I get to make new friends.
Tai.
I got the key. Shall we go to our room?
What are you doing?
Dr Patts is waiting.
Everything OK?
Yes.
Everything is OK.
Everything.
Let's go then.
I get to go, Bow.
Yeah, you go.
See you, Bow.
Bye bye. Take good care of him!
Sure.
Oh. I think I left something in the car.
Please wait here.
I'll be right back.
OK.
It's definitely OK.
You are so beautiful.
You, too.
Yeah.
Are those flowers for me?
Who's my roommate?
It's me, Kung, yeah.
Yeah, take your flowers.
What's the drink?
Cantella asiatica juice, yeah.
It's fresh, I prepared it just for you.
To clear inner hear, huh?
Yeah.
OK.
We're finally here.
Where should we go first?
How would I know? I came with you.
Tai!
Why are you here?
I want to ask you that.
Lomfon and I are on a school project.
So why are you here?
I'm doing a research for my column here.
In this VVC?
Yeah. The vet hospital of my soul mate organizes this camp.
Soul mate!
This is going to be the first time I meet your soul mate, bro!
Yeah.
What?
Lomfon. My brother's soul mate!
So your soul mate is here?
You'll see him soon.
Ouch.
Soul mate?
What can I do for you?
Where did you get this key chain?
Hey.
You guys are my brother-in-law's friends.
So you will take good care of me, right?
He's not your brother-in-law.
I warn you.
My brother and Patts are soul mates.
I will never let you interfere in their relationship.