I won't do it, I'm going home.
Wait!
Your brother took the money already.
Go, Take off your clothes.
You can stay here for now
until we figure something out.
Tian
is my new employee.
But las sure you
that this young girl
can be trustworthy
bailed on Mr Ba and hit his head!
He put it out on me!
He even took back the 40 thousand baht he gave me.
I'm your sister
but you dare sold me!
Give me back the ring necklace.
Then we don't have to see each other anymore.
Give me back my necklace!
It's my necklace!
-Mom gave it to me! Give it back!
- Damn Tian!
or do you want Mr. Ba to come pick you up?
Chan.
Tian!
Are you okay?
Who are you?!
Chan!
Don't, Boss!
Don't hurt my brother.
I'm begging you.
Your brother
is more humane than you.
Let's go Tian.
Stop!
Where are you guys going?
You came in here and assaulted me
I will file a report-for trespassing
I guarantee you will ibe nationally famous
I will also tell the police
you took your brother to do porn
Let's see who will be in jail longer
If you want to take Tian,go ahead
But the two of us raised Tian for a long time
You should have some kind of compensation for us
Don't Boss.
Don't pay them.
I'll give you guys 50,000
But from now on,
don't mess with Tia n everagain.
If it's a deal,
then give me'your account number.
Boss
I'm sorry I got you in trouble
I promise you when I have money.
I will pay you back
Please'don't be mad at me.
I'm mad
that you came here
and didn't tell me.
It's just..
the ring necklace that my mom gave me
is missing.
But I probably won't get it back anymore
Here.
It fell in the room you were staying in.
Thank you Boss!
I will forever be grateful.
I feel
very familiar with the initial on the ring.
How did your mom get this ring?
I don't know.
But Mom told me to keep it on me at all times.
WU 9969
What's up Pao?
You and him seem very close.
So,
why...
did he willingly pay50 K?
That's a lot of money.
Thon is acting up again
You need to go back with me right now.
Thank you so much Jane
for bringing me to save Tian in time.
This is.
a small token from me.
Let's go Tian.
Tian!
Boss!
Ms. Thip.
Dr.Pao and Mr s. Pajust left a minute ago
There was an urgent case at the clinic
How is Thon doing?
He was trying to get off the bed.
He kept calling for Pit p lern
Dr.Pao sedated him
to get him to calm down
So,
how did you find her?
Tian went to get something back home.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you first.
So lwasn't here to help you look after Mr, Kama it hon.
I wasn't depending on you anyway.
-Let me help you.
-No need.
Did you wash your hands?
It's dirty.
Let Ms, Thip handle it.
Who is Pit p lern?
It doesn't concern you.
I'm sorry
I made you upset.
It's fine.
It's not your fault.
If it's not my fault,
then why are you mad at me?
If you punch me
and it makes you feel better,
you can go right ahead
If I have permission
then why are you scared?
I don't like
people who talk nonsense.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
If you want to be a man,
don't be a wuss.
I don't want to be a man
but...
There's been enough problems for today.
Go get some rest.
What made you call for Pit pler n, Thon?
She probably forgot about you
Pit p lern.
I miss you.
Thon.
Thon! Don't go!
Don't go!
Thon!
Hey
Dreaming about Thon again?
By now his spirit
is probably in some hell hole
Thon probably didn't go to hell
By now,
he's peacefully in heaven.
Heaven?
I llmake you go to heaven
I'm going to go pray.
Mr, Thon.
You want to go outside?
I'll help you.
Come.
Pit p lern.
You came to see me.
You really came.
No.
My name is Tian.
Wait here while I go get Ms. Thip.
Wait one moment.
Slowly.
Ring.
Mr, Thon.
Where did you get this ring?
This is my ring.
Give it to me.
Mr, Thon!
Taks as ut.
It's Dad's ring
Dok tian!
Where did you get that ring?
It's my ring.
If you don't believe me,
ask Boss,
He's the one that gave it back to me.
Don't lie.
You were going through Mr.. Thon's things'we ren't you?
Thief!
I didn't.
My mom gave me this ring.
I swear to you.
What's your parents names?
My dad's name was Chai.
My mom's name was Thom ya.
Mr, Thon!
Thon.
Thon wake up.
You can't die right now.
Take it easy.
Please don't move right now
Rome
You'll be okay.
You have thick skin. You won't die
It's exactly what I thought.
Stay calm.
Don't say anything.
Wait until you feel better first.
Rome.
Taks as ut's heir
isn't Kula chart.
But it's that kid
What the hell are you talking about?
You're deranged right now.
Do you
remember Chai and Thom ya?
Welcome,
If you want to change your-mind and not marry Thon,
it's not too late. You can tell me
Rome!
With a shitty mouth like that,
I hope you stay single forever
You're not cute.
Let's go.
Mr. Tat! Don't hurt Chai!
Don't me dale Thom ya!
Your husband is a troublemaker!
He accused me of gambling and snitch ed on me to my father!
Calm down!
What the hell?!
Why are you meddling?!
-Huh?!
-Tat!
Tat!
That's enough!
Thon let me go!
-- Don't meddle!
- Stop it right there!
The person that needs to leave this house is you,
ungrateful son!
Go!
Dad,
How can you believe Chai?
He's just the driver.
But I'm your son.
I told him to follow you around.
To see what you've been up to!
You're a scumbag!
How can you miss an important meeting with a client?!
From here on out, do not step foot in my company again!
You're fired!
Wait Dad.
I'm sorry Dad.
Those bad friends
Those bad friends of mine invited me to go with them.
Dad,
Please forgive me
Please Dad!
Dad!
Please forgive Tat.
Give him a chance
Don't meddle!
Your job is to prepare for the wedding with Pit p lern!
Alright.
For your brother's sake,
I will transfer you to a different department temporarily
Okay?!
Go!
Who is that young fellow?
Hi, sir.
I'm Rome.
Thon's friend!
He's the one that got first class honors that l told you about
From here on out,
he will be helping out at the company
You have a good aura
Alright.
Keep an eye on Thon for me
Help each other out.
Hey Thon
The bride and groom aren't supposed to see each other before the wedding.
Don't you know?
Hey...
Tat.
You won't invite your brother in law?
Pit p lern.
It's me Thon.
I want to see your face, Can you open the door?
P lern!
Let go!
-P lern!
-Let me go!
P lern!
-Pit!
I want to die!
Calm down.
Tat raped me!
He raped me!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry l couldn't protect you. I'm sorry on Tat's behalf.
He was probably drunk.
He was n't in his right mind.
How can I move on?
How can I?
How can I keep on living?!
There has to be a solution.
There has to.
Don't worry Mom and Dad!
I will take good care of Pit p lern.
If not for my family's name
I would never step foot at this wedding
Why won't you pick up Thon?
Thon!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
Why don't you go inside?
Why are you avoiding everyone?
I have to Rome
Everything is all ruined.
Tat promised me he would take good care of Pit p lern
Pit pler n is hisnow.
This is the last time l forgive you.
What are you saying?
What happened?
Tell me right now.
Help!
Dad!
I promise
I will change myself-for the better.
I will be a good father
I will be a good husband!
I will work with Thon
to manage our family's business
I won't disappoint you ever again.
Trust me Dad.
You.
Get out.
Dad b
Yes Dad?
Go get Lawyer Dam rong for me.
Tell him
I want to write up a will
Sure Dad!
It has n't been that long since you got your position back.
You swindled over a million already, Mr Ka molt at.
What's your problem huh?!
These are fake documents!
You're trying to discredit me?
Don't listen to him Thon!
I've known about this for a while now Tat.
Rome.
Thank you so much
but don't tell anyone about this.
Let me clear this with my brother.
Are you j insane?!
You're still going to protect him?!
Are you slandering me?!
You bastard!
Hey Rome!
Rome! Tat!
Calm down.
Rome :
I'm begging you
don't tell anyone about this
For my father's sake.
Enough of this shit!
I won't get involved with your family again!
I quit!
Enough Thon.
Don't say anything
Let'stalk about it when you feel better.
There's not much time.
Rome.
You need to know about that ring necklace.
The ring necklace
is very important
I want to leave the family's ring to you
and give it to him on the day he is born
I'm leaving it with you.
You
must be strong.
lim entrusting you to look after everything in my place
have planned the future for you already
Dad!
What's wrong?!
Doctor!
Doctor come here!
All of the Taks as ut's inheritance
will solely go to one person.
There is no allocation whatsoever.
It will go to...
the first grandson of the family
when he reaches the age of 20
Mr Kama it hon will be in charge of the assets.
Liar!
This is a fake will!
Thon.
You and him worked together to write this fake will up, didn't you?!
Tat.
Why would l do that?
I'm sterile and l can't have children.
As for your position and shares you have in the company,
it will remain the same and nothing will change
But if you bear a son
the inheritance will go to your son.
Which is equally yours
What happens if I don't have a son?
You will receive dividends from the company every year
until the company shuts down
As for Mr. Koson's personal assets
it will be used to build the Taks as ut Foundation.
Mr, Kama it hon will manage it.
I don't believe you!
My dad would never write this crazy will!
Show me.
Let me see it!
Calm down Mr K a molt at!
I said let go!
Calm down!
Let go!
Tat!
That's enough!
Don't meddle Thon!
Bro.
Let go!
That's enough
Mr s. P itplern!
Pit p lern.
Are you okay?
Thon move!
Pit.
Why did you come down?
The doctor.said you're not healthy.enough
If you have a'miscarriage, we'll all be screwed!
My stomach hurts.
Tat.
Take her to the hospital
Hello.
I came to visit my nephew.
Mr Kamoltat Taksasut'sson
How is he doing?
One moment please
The patient was very weak so she had to have a cesarean section.
But the baby is healthy now.
Yes Mr, Wit.
I'lgoin and clear it for you tomorrow.
Chai
Why are you here?
Mr, Thon.
Don't tell me that Tho my a's baby?
It's unbelievable.
Your wife gave birth at the same hospital like my brother
Actually,
Mr K a molt at
had Thom ya come look after Mr s Pit p lern.
Leading her to give birth here
Please excuse me.
Wait.
Can I take a look?
You're really lucky.
You have another son.
Yes.
How about this?
To welcome the baby.
That's okay.
Just take it.
Mom always taught me
no matter how poor we are,
I must not go steal or rob from other people
We might be poor but we have dignity
Mom would never steal this ring necklace
Rome
Right now
Thon is with the doctors now
He will be fine.
If Cha i'schild is a boy
then why is Tian a girl?
Hold on.
You're taking this quite serious
May be Thon
was just talking nonsense
What about that ring necklace?
You already know
Ka molt at would never let that necklace be in someone else's hands.
Unless...
he didn't know that that day
Thon gave his niece the necklace
So?
So T at switched his child with Chai's child
Are you crazy?
That's his child we're talking about.
He wouldn't just give his child up to'someone else!
He's done worse.
Don't you remember?
What he did to me,
what he did to Thon.
Aha.
I knew it.
Your brother would never turn a new leaf.
How much this time?
I won't tolerate this
I'm bringing this into the meeting
You still have the evidence from last time, right?
Yeah.
I saved it on a hard disk.
It's good that you came around
So,
does Ka molt at know about this?
He does.
He threatened i me but lim not scared
Im on my way to get the evidence from you
Hm, okay.
Hey!
My car can't brake.
Hello?
Thon?
Hello Thon?!
Rome.
I contacted my supervisor.
Right now,
we need to move Thon for his surgery over there becau so it'll be safer
Not enough equipment here.
Earlier,
the police called and said the brakes were cut.
It must have been Ka mol tat's doing.
Cold-bloodedmurderer.
He probably got scared that Thon was gonna expose him.
So he tried to kill his own brother
Sonofabitch!
Hey wait!
Where are you going?
Calm down!
We don't have evidence that he actually did it!
Over there!
Thon!
He's what's important right now.
But Pao,
we can't let Ka molt at know
that Thon is alive still!
Doctor
There was an immigrant who died in a fire accident.
No documents, no family.
What do we do?
Gosh Thon.
You shouldn't have.
You were still young.
May you rest in peace.
I will continue the work you were doing
My condolences :
will you be taking him with you today?
Sure,
U was thinking of-finding a temple nearby to cremate him.
So he will be able to reach a good place sooner
Okay.
Excuse me.
brought you your food, Boss
You have to eat.
Just put it down. I'm not hungry yet.
Fire!
Help! There's a fire!
Go put out the fire first!
Boss!
You have to leave!
Let me go!
This is the factory my dad left for me before he died!
Help put out the fire!
Don't Boss!
You will die!
You have to get out of here!
Let me go!
Don't!
I said let me go!
Boss!
Mai!
They destroyed the CCTVs
I didn't have evidence that it was arson and l was left broke
If your relative didn't help me
I wouldn't be able to reestablish myself.
Hey!
You still remember?!
I thought you forgot about it
Confused?
It's because of you
that l broke my doctor'soath
I had to wander around and open a clinic herein Ranong
It's good that you ire here.
I wanted to ask for my money back
Confused?
Well,
the fee to look after Thon
and loss of opportunity fee.
Hold on.
I think l will charge you
three million!
That will make me rich!
Greedy!
You're worse than those unofficial loan sharks
You're just realizing that?
Asking money from your brother in law?
I'm giving you a chance to take that back
My mother is here
I'm not.
I was just kidding
wanted
my brother in law to be in a good mood!
Good mood!
See? He's smiling. He's in a good mood.
So, how's Thon doing?
Doctor!
Mr. Kama it hon has passed away!
What?!
It's not true is it?
I took care of him for years.
Mr Thon's condition was never that bad.
It's all Tian's fault.
He made Mr. Thon...
T hip.
Be reasonable.
It had nothing to do with Tian.
It does.
Tian went and stole something from Mr Thon's room
Mr, Thon woke up to see it.
Tian didn't steal that ring necklace.
I assure you.
Even if he didn't steal the necklace,
he might have stole something else
You can't trust
a kid on the streets like that.
By the way,
who is this Tian person?
What necklace?
I'll tell you later.
Pao is at the hospital right now.
He's taking care of the body.
I came here to change
and will go contact the temple.
The funeral will be a private one
One day vigil then cremation.
Okay.
Then,
I will go get ready
Wait.
Where's Tian?
Since the incident.
I haven't seen him.
Where did she go?
Did she run away again?
Where are you going?
Boss.
I'm...
I'm heading to the bus station.
Running away?
Thief.
I didn't steal.
My mom gave it to me when I was little.
Prove it.
I don't have proof to prove anything.
But if you don't believe me,
you can send me to the police.
You're bold.
I will believe you this time.
Thon is already dead anyway
Mr. Kama it hon!
I'm the jinx.
I've only been there for a few days.
I caused him to die!
My parents died because of me too.
Just let me go.
If l stay,
you might get unlucky
Did you forget
you still owe me?
Hi Boss.
N hong!
Boss is here!
Okay!
Hi Boss.
Hi Nhong.
You're here late
What did you get today?
A lot of squids.
They're huge and all grade A
New worker?
He looks like a puppy.
Will he be able to work?
Not here.
N hong.
You can get back to work
Sure. Good evening
Bye!
I brought you here
in case you can see
that it wasn't easy for me
to get to this point.
Good evening Boss
Hi.
This is a frozen seafood factory
I built it with my own brain and two hands
It's a big factory
You're very skilled.
I didn't have a choice.
Before,l took over the furniture factory from my father
But it went bankrupt and I went broke
So I had to reestablish myself here
If l had given up that day
I wouldn't have today
Oh!
I know.
You want me to work here to pay off your debt?
Don't worry, I can do anything you want me to do.
To...
make up for Mr. Kama it hon'sdeath
Before Thon
had the condition that you saw,
he was a handsome,kind man
Everyone loved him.
I'm sorry.
Thon's death
was not your fault
But there is an evil person
who's done me and Thon wrong
He made Thon disabled
He burned down my factory.
Someone like that exist?
Why didn't you tell the police?
The police can't do anything to him
He's rich
and has power
We have to go off the books with him
to satisfy what he did to us
If he's your enemy,
then he's my enemy too
Nice words
If I want to get revenge for Thon
will you help me?
Bad people must get punished
I am indebted to you.
Whatever you tell me to do
I will do it.
Then let's begin.
At this factory?
No.
Il tell you later.