I won't go!
I'm telling Mom
that you're D ad'smistress.
I think we should stop being enemies.
With the person trying to be my new mom?!
Are you insane?!
If we agree to be allies,
I will tell you how to live in this house comfortably.
From now on,
you j must always wear this pearl necklace.
I'll keep that necklace
safe for you.
Be careful.
Who is Tian?
beautiful girl like Tian into his care?
I just know that
Tian is an orphan.
Also, she has done Rome a favor.
That's why Rome wants the best life for Tian
Quunsni auuuunu naiannn
au a u naunn
au au
My name is Laksa mon.
What is your name?
My
name is Dok tian.
Your English is not bad
" Ma muang "
Mango.
" See lue ang "
Yellow.
" Kwai "
Buffalo
" Meed "
Eto!
You're a quick thinker
Welcome to Laksa mon Classroom
Rome asked me to teach you English.
Thank you,
Professor,
That sounds old
You can just call me Lak.
Lak.
I'll call you Mr, Lak then.
Okay.
Are you sure
the doctor hung himself?
I'm sure.
He's been dead for years
So you called me here
having to drive from Ranong to Hua Hin
just to look at this?
So you can see with your own eyes
that we've come to a dead end
Why is Heaven siding with an evil person like Ka molt at?
He blocked all of our roads
This world isn't fair so why even believe in good or bad karma?
Can you just calm down?
Rome.
Maybe it's not time for Kamol tat to get his karma yet.
Then when?
In a few months,
he's going to get everything of Taks as ut.
You know that.
May be
I'll be the judge of everything
Wait!
Where are you going and what crazy shit are you gonna do now?!
Don't meddle.
I'll be the one to drag him to confess his sins right in front of Thon's ashes!
I can't suffer anymore.
Please come get me
Let me go be with you.
Hey!
Miss!
What are you doing?!
Why did you stop me?!
I want to go be with my husband!
Stay calm.
Okay?
Don't commit suicide, I'm begging you.
You guys will never understand
Don't bother me!
I think
we should talk it out first
So we can help you fix the problem
I'm Pao.
Dr.Wor a wong's junior.
Dr.Wor a wong died
because of me
He shouldn't have to sacrifice that much for me.
In that case.
can you please tell us the truth?
Perhaps
we might be involved in his death
20 years ago,
I was sick.
I had leukemia
I needed treatment
by bone marrow transplant
The cost was so expensive
But he managed to get the money for the treatment.
He said
the hospital
was giving out loan opportunities.
But til today.
I found out the truth
where that money came from
It's because of this journal.
Hey.
Ka mol tat's name is on there.
Come on Doctor.
It's no big deal.
Just write down
my wife is having a boy?
I just want to surprise my wife.
How about this?
Hl give you two million.
Well discuss the details later.
I'm sorry.
I took a long time in the restroom.
How's the baby? Is it healthy?
Hey
Our son
is very healthy.
But...
you might have to doc-section.
Doctor
I want to have a natural birth
I want to see my son's face
when he opens his eyes for the first time
In my embrace.
It's just...
the baby is in a breech position
For you and your baby's safety,
you would need ac-section.
Ever since that day,
King and I rented a house in Hua Hin.
My life hasn't been happy since.
I'm so shameful of myself.
I had to take antidepressants
and sleeping pills every night
Until now,
I've made my decision
that I can no longer wear the honorable white coat
Hello.
You moved to Hua Hin.
You broke the promise
You told the truth about the baby
to Pitp lern, didn't you?
I never told anyone about this
I swear.
It's not true!
This journal
was left unfinished
the night before he killed himself.
I don't believe
that he would kill himself
I think it was murder.
If that's the case,
why didn't you go file a report
and use this journal
as evidence?
I don't want Doctor
to ruin his reputation.
I think
Ka molt at is behind this.
He wanted to silent Dr.Wor about swapping the babies.
Ms. King.
I want you
to be a witness in charging Ka molt at
to seek justice for Dr.Wor.
We'll go right now.
No.
I won't go.
If l go,
that means
I've ruined Doctor's reputation that he's upheld all his life
A dead person
only has his reputation ruined
But the one who is still alive is deceived into being someone else's child is suffering.
We're doing this
to expose Ka mol tat's evil deeds.
Okay?
No!
I won't go.
You guys should leave my house now!
Ms, King.
Ms. King!
las sure you
Ii never told Mr s. P itplern about it
I swear.
Why did Pit p lern know
that the babies got switched?
Only you know about this
Hmm?
Doctor.
If you're struggling and have no money to spend
you can tell me.
Enough.
Let me do evi I just once in this life.
I will resign and live here and won't go back to Bangkok.
I want everything to end.
I won't ask anything else from you.
Please just let me go
I never trust anyone
Except myself.
Hey!
Hey! Ka molt at!
What's wrong?
You're sweating.
I'm fine.
J just had a bad dream.
It's morning already?
Barely 5:00am.
I set the alarm.
I want to go prepare offerings for the monk
I saw you twisting and turning.
You must want me dead?
The donation envelope the monk gave you
did you put the money in yet?
I can give it to him later.
Why?
You think I'm that sinful?
Whatever you did,
You know it.
Are you mad at me
that you had to become my wife instead of Thon?
Whatever you wanted, I would give it to you.
Except for the moon and star
Can you give me my child's life back?
I told you our daughter died after birth.
How many times have l told you?
Wher e's her body?
If our daughter really died,
can you show me her body?
I didn't want you to be sad sol adopted Chart.
Like how you burned Thon's body,
made him an unidentified corpse.
You see?
In the end, we go back to this.
The reason you'remaking merit everyday
is because you're scared he won't go up to heaven right?
I just want you to know the word "give ".
Give with a pure heart.
Not expect anything in return
So Kula chart
won't have to receive the karma
that the adults have committed.
That is all l hope for.
Damn it!
I'm the one
that controls karma
I will show you
I'm done.
Let's take a look
20 questions
and you got 16 correct.
Not bad Tian
When Kr u Pon was teaching me
I liked English the most.
Kr u Pon?
Kr u Pon was my English teacher from Grade 1to Grade6
Then I took the exam and got my NFE non-formal education )
Okay Tian.
Let's try conversation now.
Try speaking English. Say...
one sentence.
Would you like some candle therapy?
Candle many many smell
Lavender, lemon grass, mint.
This one for 30baht but
four for one hundred. Please?
What's so funny Mr Lak?
That's what I say when I sell the candles.
The foreigners understand i me.
It's not wrong.
But grammar isn't actually correct
I have an idea.
Studying here doesn't give you the vibe
Let's go outside.
Can you
drive?
Dr...
Can you drive?
Motorbike is broken
Broken bike.
You understand how to create a learning situation.
No Mr, Lak.
It really is broken.
I can't start it.
What do we do?
We drove so far?
Did you bring your phone?
don't have a phone.
But let me try fixing it.
Are you joking?
I'm serious.
I used to help Dad a lot.
Let'stry.
Excellent job Tian!
I did it!
e
Tian be careful!
Hey!
Tian! Are you okay?
Pao.
Come inside and have coffee or food then go home.
No.
I have to go back and open my clinic.
Because I was so busy with your business,
my patients probably went to another clinic by now.
Okay.
Can you tell Pa about what happened then?
We need to be ready.
I'm gonna start attacking Ka molt at.
Catch him off guard.
Hey.
Rome.
I'll be honest with you.
I fee I just as bad as Dr W or
who have to cooperate with you to do the same old things.
Then you have to do it even more.
Once Ka mol tat'sevil deeds get exposed
Dr, Wor's spirit will get to rest in peace.
And you won't have to feel any shame
Don't look at me like that.
Fine.
We've come this far already.
What can I do?
I'll take off now.
Yeah.
Are you tired from traveling?
Je ab
Go bring a cold glass of water.
Sure
Are you hungry?
I can go prepare your food
It's okay, I'm not hungry.
How's Tian?
Was she mischievous?
Did she focus on learning etiquette with you?
I rather not tell you
You might think I'm a snitch.
What did Tian do?
Ever since Mr, Lak came here,
they ve been hanging out alone together.
When l want to teach her or train her,
she always avoid me
Those two actually left somewhere together since morning
Oh, there they are
Speaking of the devil.
What happened?
What happened to you guys?
Motorcycle crashed.
It's my fault.
I had Tian drive me around
My goodness Mr Lak.
Your leg hasn't healed yet.
I was driving.
Mr. Lak did nothing wrong
It's my fault.
It's both your faults!
Lak.
I brought you here to recover.
I had Ms. Thip look after you
But instead you go outside to play.
You too.
I had Ms, Thip teach you manners and etiquette
on how to be a lady
But you went out to ride a motorbike until it crashed.
Good thing it's just this injury.
What happens if you hit your head and become handicapped or even die?
It's a small injury Boss.
I used to ride a motorbike down a hill and it hurt a lot more than this.
Don't argue!
I'm sorry.
I'll go clean my wound now.
Don't help her Ms. Thip
Let her walk on her own so she learns
Why are you so upset Rome?!
Why are you scolding Tian so much?
It was just a small accident
You don't know
how important Tian's life is.
I don't understand when you said
that Tian's life is important.
What do you mean?
Someday you'll know.
You speak in secrecy.
I want to know even more now
Unless...
you have some kind of feelings for her?
What the hell?!
When it comes to women, it never crossed my mind.
If you speak of this again,
I will kick your other leg.
You want that?
No!
I give up!
I won't say anything.
Some an.
Lak and Tian won't join me?
I brought Mr Lak his food already
As for Tian,
I knocked many times but she won't answer
I guess she's going on a strike because you scold her.
This kind of personality is
quite difficult to train.
But I think Miss Tian
is unable to come down
She was limping earlier.
Going on a hunger strike?
No.
Did you know
besides not liking stubborn kids,
lying,
I also hate people who are sarcastic,without reason,
and goes on protest.
I'm not protesting you.
But...
I just want to punish myself for getting you upset.
What if you get gastritis?
Will that not cause me trouble?
I'll be fine.
I've faced worse hardships before.
I've starved for days and I was fine.
You struggled that much?
Yes.
Mom and Dad would move around often.
Sometimes we had to live on a farm
When there's a lot of flood,
we couldn't go out to buy food.
If you live with me,
you will never struggle like that again.
I promise.
Boss.
But you have to listen to me
You won't do anything risky again
Okay?
Sure.
will not do that again.
Boss.
You're no longer mad at me?
What's it gonna be?
Feed yourself or l feed you?
I'll feed myself.
Thank you Boss.
Thank you all for honoring TS Group.
Our company now is moving forward
Commercial building and housing development business
with a focus on the northern region
like Chiang Rai
Nan,
and Mae Sot.
Everything is done according to policy
and state special!
Also,
our second goal
will focus on five star luxury hotel
focusing on coastal areas in the southern region
Whether it will be on the Andaman side or the Gulf of Thailand, we will inform you later.
The company is at the top of the stock market.
What inspired your success, Mr Ka molt at?
Gratitude
I did everything to continue my father's dream
He wanted his grandson to be the successor to his business.
That he iris
Kula chart Taks as ut
Will Mr, Kula chart be the youngest executive?
Well, maybe.
But now Kula chart has to fly to England to study business administration.
When he returns, I hope he will come back to develop the company and not disappoint everyone.
Can l please interview Mr. Kula chart...
He was just here.
Hurry.
Did anyone follow you?
My boss is still shook from the last raid
Why are you so scared?
Trade. Quickly!
Kula chart.
Gosh!
It's my dad's side chick.
I thought it was someone else.
Hold on.
Hey.
Are you crazy?!
Why are you getting high right now?
Everyone is looking for you out there.
Get going.
-Go!
-What the hell?
I will make the karma you created
come to fruition faster, Ka molt at
Your people did a good job.
Keep following the target.
That bastard son screwed me!
I managed to make him look good in public
and look what he did!
It's probably all over the internet.
People must be having fun gossiping
I really don't understand
who would do this?
Must be people with bad intentions
to the point of hurting Kula chart to this extent.
Yeah!
People with good intentions wouldn't do this.
You too.
I trusted you to take care of him!
So careless!
I'm really sorry.
J assure you this won't happen again.
Go make this news go away as quietly as possible
Leak some other celebrity news
You know how to do it.
Sure.
Are you meeting the chairman?
Pat is my people.
You can leave now
I'm dealing with the villagers who are refusing to sell their lands
Only a few plots of land left
If subtle doesn't work, strong measures will have to be used!
I didn't call you here for that.
I have a bad feeling about something.
Are you sure you cleaned up all the evidence from that rental house?
Rental house?
When we took care of Dr.Wor.
Gosh, Boss.
That was years ago
It's probably nothing left
But the statute of limitations has not expired
If his family gets crazy
and reopens the case, then what?
Then...
you can rest assure.
Dr.Wor left behind a wife and has no other extended family
His wife just had a heart attack and died
Someone informed me yesterday
Oh really?
That's a relief.
There are only a few months left
before the will is due.
I think
you should prepare to celebrate.
Let'sstart with the towel
Spread it.
Hold here.
Yeah.
Then place it here.
Nicely.
Good.
Let's find animals now. There's eight.
They're...
vertical and horizontal
Okay?
Eight?
It's easy, You're smart.
I'll help you.
There!
I got the first word
Rab...bit.
Wow!
Faster than me.
You were too slow.
There.
H-O-R-S-E
Ho...
Horse!
Yeah, you're right.
Horse.
Rome.
Huh?
No.
Teacher
Let'shave them partner up.
Sure.
Let me change to you holding his shoulder
Stay calm.
Don't be nervous. Stay calm.
You'll attend more of these functions.
Get used to it.
This is your first test.
If anyone asks about you
tell them what l told you
Sure.
Hello Mr, Rome
Hello.
Your table is over here
Okay
Thank you.
Make yourselves comfortable
Excuse me
Come.
This is another lesson that I haven't taught you yet.
You have to slowly sip the wine,
tenderly.
Savor the flavor.
Yes.
Be careful not to get drunk too
because it is a type of alcohol
What is it?!
I'm going to use the restroom.
Not enjoying it?
Why are you alone out here?
Oh.
No.
I wanted to get some air.
Well then.
I'll go get you a drink.
What would you like?
That's okay.
I'll be right in shortly.
Let me serve you.
Who are you?!
This is my wife!
Don't mess with her!
Understood?
Go!
I'm sorry.
Sam,you're misunderstanding
Misunderstand what? Come here.
Come here.
Sam!
You're hurting me!
You have a high tolerance.
I won't get drunk
Not a big deal.
Cheers.
Can you come with me?
I'll be back
What is it?
Earlier I saw..
Mont ira and.
her boyfriend sitting right here.
Mont ira?!
Yes!
Maybe you saw wrong.
Mr. Rome
You're here as well?
Hello Mr. Seu a.
Mr. Wit is also'here
Why don't you go say hi to him?
Sure.
Tian,'ll be back.
Okay.
Let's go
This way.
Which way to the restroom?
By the swimming pool.
Come here!
You're misunderstanding me!
Misunderstand what?!
Stop!
You want to get hit like this?!
You'll be punished like this!
Do you like it?!
Hey! Stop right there!
Don't meddle!
Stop!
Subtitles by oh sweet haven.com Timing by Angel Lakorns
Ka molt at
upgraded his son, Kula chart,
to study abroad,hoping to get a degree soon.
We can't delay any longer.
We need to change our plan or we'll be late.
What's your name?
My name is...
Tian.
Mr Ka molt at.
MASTER KOOL P No matter how hard i try to resist it, Ican't stop it
SUN GRACE
PIt'snot like howl used to be
PIc an't stop loving you
POr should I give up
P No matter how much I forbid it,
in the end my heart can't do it