P You're the only one who gives me concern
P and love that seems sincere
Pl trust you with everything
P But today your embrace feels empty
P The word love that doesn't seem sincere
P The closer you get, the further you are away
P What made you like this?pn n uas na
Us-annu
tan unawu
us-onauwus
PThe love given
n no u
Pis worthless
ny wa saunis up Can you come back to being naw us
aucinsni auuuunu nadannn
P Can you do that for me?
P Love me like you did yesterday
au a u nauann
I love Kula chart.
The two of us
are in love.
It sounded like someone came in so he hung up.
It's just strange.
Or...
Tian is being imprisoned by that boss guy.
I must get revenge on her no matter what.
Just name the price.
and l don't know anyone.
Sure.
I'll find one for you.
Can I catch a ride with you?
You can drop me off anywhere.
There.
Mr. Lak.
" If you don't want him to die,
then come alone and don't call the cops.
If you don't know the house number,
you can't go inside.
Do you not understand?
You're the one that doesn't understand!
This is an emergency.
My boyfriend got kidnapped by some pervert and is being imprisoned!
Can we go in?!
You can't!
Gosh!
Don't pull!
Jane!
It's me Tian.
Tian!
How did you get here?
Boss's address?
I don't know.
Go ask someone else.
Dong.
You're Boss's close subordinate
If you don't know then no one knows.
I'm not telling you.
You guys are going to bother him.
We're not going to bother him
We just want to deliver anchovy sauce to have him taste
Am I right Jane?
That's right.
My family's special recipe.
Delicious like no other
Please Dong
I just want to deliver something to Boss. I won't bother him
-Please Dong-Fine.
But under one condition
You
have to let me
taste tone too.
You got it.
Just forget about that.
Why are you dressed like this?
Were you forced to do it?
Did he force you to wear this?!
I'll tell you later.
There's an emergency right now
It's me M r, Kiat.
It have a friend who wants to discuss divorcing her foreign husband
Can l have her go see you at your office?
Oh.
Im about to drive pass that.
Thank you so much
The lawyer actually
is talking to a client in a cafe up ahead
I'll drop you off.
Thank you Rome
You're always sweet
It's fine.
We're friends
...
want to go back in time.
I think
it's impossible.
You should move on.
Hello Ms. Thip
Tian left the house?
Since when?
Just now.
She probably got mad I told her to practice cooking.
So she took the opportunity to leave while l turned my back on her.
I think this kid
is a lost cause.
Tian.
You devil!
Where's Mr, Lak?
Gosh, Can.
You're not going to say hi to me?
You're some an.
Last time,
you played rough that I was on everyone's feed on Facebook.
apologize for that.
Let Mr, Lak go.
He looked in really bad shape.
I'm taking him to a doctor.
Sure.
But you have to become my girlfriend first.
las sure you
I will take good care of you
My family's rich.
Whatever you want,
I will give it to you.
Okay.
Deal.
We're a couple
Now can you tell me where Mr, Lak is at?
The room next door.
What are you doing?
Well,
we're a couple
We're in a motel room
What do you think?
Chart!
Stop!
Don't!
Chart!
Stop!
Should we barge in there?
They went quiet
Tian said to wait ten minutes.
If he doesn't come out,
then we barge in there.
Do you think any police will come?
Of course the police will come
Hey.
Can you be quiet?!
Pay attention to Tian.
That woman is holding a knife to go into Tian's room!
Shit.
What do we do?
Stop Chart!
Get away from me!
Get away!
Don't go!
Please stay
Let go!
You're trying to steal my man?
Die!
e Chart!
-Be mine!
Let me go!
-Stay with me.
-Let go!
Tian run!
The police are on their way!
You can't escape now!
Oh.
You're done?
Where's Chart?
He fell asleep.
Mr. Lak.
Come on.
Thanks Tian.
Don't let them go!
Catch them!
Damn!
Hurry!
You betrayed me?!
You cheated on me?!
Damn!
You're so annoying!
Can we argue later?
Did you not hear them?
The police are on their way here!
It won't open in time!
Let's go!
Hurry!
-Hey!
-Get them!
Go!
You can't escape.
Jane!
You wanna be tough?!
Go!
How did you get here?
I followed the GPS on Tian's phone
Fuck!
The plan is all ruined!
I was so close to making candle my wife.
Wife?
I'm your wife
bastard!
I'm giving Candle that wife title.
She...
is the angel of my dream.
We're the same age
We are compatible in every way.
Not wrinkly and old like you.
You're going to leave me?
Do you know how tired I am with you?
Don't be pretentious.
You got involved with me
because you were bored with my dad
Young like me,
did you really think
I want an old hag like you as my wife?
Huh?
Kula chart!
You want to die?
Die then!
What the hell man?!
Hey!
Napa!
It's all my fault.
It's...
Kula chart wanted to get revenge on me.
So he lashed out on you.
Why did you decided to go solo?
How many times have I told you?
Do you not listen?
I thought you promised
that you would listen?
Shepherd's boy.
Hey!
Why are you badmouthing Tian?
Tian just risked his life back there.
He almost died.
Instead of comforting him, you criticize him?!
This is between me and Tian.
You're not involved.
Tian and l are a couple!
I'm taking him back to Ranong
Couple?
You two are a couple?
You're crazy.
You suddenly dressed Tian up as a girl.
Tian is much more of a man than you two!
The best on the beach.
Right Tian?
Tell them
what we are.
Jane.
I'm sorry l made you misunderstand that I like girls
I did it because Mom asked me to
But the truth is
I'magir I just like you
What?
I don't believe you!
You're being deceived by these two men right?
You were forced to do it right?
No.
Jane.
I'm sorry.
Take this money
Go home.
I'm not a charity case!
Remember this Tian.
Jane.
Jane, I'm sorry!
Where are you rushing off to?
To the hospital.
Why? Are you sick? Have the driver take you.
It's okay.
Your secretary Napa is in bad shape.
Kula chart is looking after her at the hospital.
What?
Doctor.
How's the patient doing?
Congratulations.
The baby is safe.
Excuse me now.
Baby?
What baby?!
Didn't I tell you to use protection?!
Are you trying to destroy me,
destroy my family?!
I'm sorry sir.
I didn't mean to.
It was Kula chart.
Kula chart raped me!
Hey!
You raped me!
You forced me to do things!
You threatened me that if I don't do it,
you will tell Dad about school
Dad!
I was the victim.
I was hurt
and embarrassed.
You were hurt
and embarrassed?!
You bastard!
Where did you get this habit from?!
Bastard!
Dad!
Ka molt at!
Stop!
You hitting your son,
what do you get from it?
It happened already
You can't fix it.
Just accept the truth
Okay.
Fine.
You'can go home now
I'll handle the rest
Get rid of Napa
Don't make it obvious :
The quicker, the better.
Take him.
That's enough!
Why are you arresting me?!
Hey!
-Take him.
-Wait!
Let go!
Why are you arresting my son?
What did he do wrong?
We have a warrant
The victim filed a report
that your son Mr, Kula chart,
assaulted
and imprisoned them.
Deprived them of freedom.
That's not true.
Where's the evidence?
Let's go talk at the police station.
We have a witness
evidence,
and CCTV footage
capturing Mr, Kula chart very clearly
Take him Sergeant
Let's go.
Dad!
Help me Dad!
What about Mr, Kula chart studying in England?
What are you doing?!
Hey!
Dad!
Dad! Help me!
Who?
Who filed a report to slander my son?!
Huh?!
The person who got assaulted
was my brother Laksa mon
This time, your evil blood
won't survive Ka molt at.
You again?
You slandered him?!
Bastard!
Sir!
Calm down.
Calm down Mr. Ka molt at
Want another assault charge on you Mr Ka molt at?
It's a direct offense.
I'think it's best that you two don't confront each other.
Regarding Mr. Laksa mon's case,
I will work on it.
Mr. Ka molt at.
Please have a seat.
Whatever you stole,
keep it safe.
Beware of those who have the rights
coming to claim it back.
Why you...
Rome
Ground Tian.
Don't let her leave her room.
But Rome --
No but s!
Do as I say.
Ms. Thip.
Keep an eye on Tian.
If she goes missing again,
I will condemn everyone for it.
Yes Mr, Rome.
Hello?
Out on bail?
How so Inspector?
Where were you all night to come home in the morning like this?
It's nothing Mom.
Just a small problem
But I won't accept Nap a's baby as mine
She probably got pregnant with someone else and is claiming it to be mine.
Did you get involved with her though?
Yes.
But it's different.
Kula chart.
How can you say it's different?
You getting involved with your father's woman is bad enough
I never thought you would do something like this.
I didn't mean to do it.
That old hag tricked me!
She seduced me
You want that kind of person as a daughter in law?
Whether it's this woman or any other woman, she's still a woman
I won't let another woman get harassed again
Especially
if you harassed her
You have to take responsibility.
I'm the one that has to take responsibility
Chart.
Go pack up your things and be ready to fly.
Where are you taking him?
Put him in a safe place.
Do you know
what crime this bastard committed?
Tell me what you did.
Kidnapped and imprisoned Rome's brother.
Lured the girl Tian to come out to see him
so he can rape her!
Kula chart!
How can you do something like this?
Good thing he's smart
and said Napa was the mastermind
So the police let him out on bail
You see?
Your son isn't stupid.
You wanna be smart with me?
Will you go or not?!
What are we going to do?
Pray.
You're good at it, no?
Subtitles by oh sweet haven.com Timing by Angel Lakorns
Hello.
Please sit and wait while l bring you some water
Continue playing, It was getting good.
Hello.
Who are you here to see?
Have we met before?
Thank you so much 139 SAVE
139.
Without your help,
I would be in so much trouble
I have my cards and cash in here 139.
AVE
It's you.
You helped me.
What a small world.
Last time,
I didn't get to ask for your name.
What's your name?
Tian.
My name is Dok tian.
And...
what are you to Rome?
I'm a child under his care
I'm an orphan so Boss took me under his care.
I'm...
used to be a close friend of Rome's.
Right.
You look..
very familiar.
I must know your parents.
My dad's name...
Rome.
Pit p lern.
I'm happy
to see you
happily living well
As appropriate.
I'm not struggling.
You must be doing well.
You already know
I had no choice.
Thon asked me to stay alive......
and I'm trying my best.
Tian.
Sit here.
This is Mr s, P itplern,
the person l told you
that she used to date Kama it hon,
my best friend.
I told Tian about some of the old stories.
Tian is my friend'sdaughter.
We're pretty close
Alright.
Let's talk about the present.
Why did you come see me, Pit p lern?
About my child.
About Kula chart.
So it's about that...
brat of a kid
I'm begging you Rome.
Think of him
as a son or nephew
and not press charges against him.
He's still a kid.
He did it without thinking it through.
You know something?
That brat kicked my brother and almost killed him!
Plus he tried to sexually assault Tian.
I can't let it slide.
I'll leave it to the police
to let them handle it
Rome!
I'm begging you.
It's my fault
and Ka molt at.
We didn't raise him good enough.
That's why
Kula chart is like this.
Kids
are like a white fabric.
They sometimes can get dirty
That's because the parents labeled them that way.
I'm begging you Rome.
I never asked anything from you.
Can you please forgive Kula chart?
Can you?
Don't do this.
No!
I'm begging you.
I will be g you
until you forgive Kula chart.
Tian.
I promise you
I won't let Kula chart bother you again.
Can you forgive Kula chart?
I'm begging you.
For Thon's sake,
for our friendship,
I will forgive him.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you Rome!
Thank you so much Tian
for-forgiving Kula chart.
My mother taught me that vengeance must be stopped by not holding vengeance
You're a good kid.
Your mother
must have taught you well.
Why didn't you press charges?
Do you think I did the right thing?
More than right.
I figured.
Figured what?
I figured you would do it for Mrs. Pitplern's sake.
Forgive and not press charges
Why do you think that way?
Because my boss is a kindhearted and the best person in this world.
For this case,
Kula chart confessed to all charges.
He told us who the mastermind was
and is being held as a witness.
Who was the mastermind?
The name is Napa.
We're questioning her right now.
But she won't be able to escape.
She's being treated at the hospital right now.
The patient is in Room A616
But I'm not sure if you can visit her or not.
The police are outside the room
Thank you.
Taks as ut Group?
I'd like to have the number for Mr, Kamol tat's secretary, Napa.
She called me for a meeting
but I can't get ahold of her right now.
Kula chart.
Hello?
Im Rome,
the relative of the person you and Kula chart imprisoned
What do you want?
I have two options for you.
Take 500 thousand and golive a happy life
Or receive a court warrant and go to prison.
You choose.
500 thousand for?
I have a job for you.
Job?
What job?
I know you're Kamol tat'ssecretary.
You must know all of Taks as ut Group'stransactions.
You want me to betray my boss?
I'm giving you the chance
to get revenge on your boss
He has cut ties with you
Kula chart told the authorities that you were the mastermind behind everything.
There's no way.
Kula chart would never betray me.
Because...
Because what?
You won't get anything from me.
Think about it.
I'll be waiting for your answer
It's me.
Boss told me to help you escape.
Escape?
Escape to where?
To a safe place.
He doesn't want you to give birth in prison.
The court has issued an arrest warrant for you.
I won't go.
I'll wait for him or Kula chart to pick me up.
Stop!
Okay.
Hey!
Stop!
I'm begging you, please don't hurt me!
I'm begging you!
Once I marry Kula chart,
however much you want
I will give it to you!
Just please don't hurt me!
were asking for death
You were too ambitious!
Get up!
Please don't hurt me. I'm begging you!
Miss.
Why did you bring me here?!
I didn't even tell Pal had an urgent meeting.
What's wrong?
Stop talking.
Let's go.
Help her.
She's critically injured
How is she?
The mother isn't so worrisome.
But the baby...
didn't survive.
How pitiful.
Not even two months yet.
If I were to guess,
the baby
was Ka mol tat's baby.
So he sent his men
to silence her.
Rome,
You're guessing again?
How many guesses have you made?
Each one of them isn't a trivial matter either.
Look at her condition.
I think you should file a police report.
He's going to make an excuse
and save himself again.
This woman
is an important piece of evidence I will keep to get back at Kamolt at.
Enough Rome
I have to get back to Ranong
Yeah.
Ill handle this.
I have news for'you.
But I don't know if it's good news or bad news
Open it.
You have strong hands
Do you have a boyfriend yet?
What are you asking sir?
I'm still single.
In that case, I will transfer you from PR
to my secretary.
Any objections?
I would very much appreciate that.
I won't disappoint you.
So...
what about Napa?
Oh.
Another company will pay her more
so she left me.
I will never do that to you.
Really?
Leave first.
All done?
Yes.
Staged as a robbery.
She turned in her resignation letter in advance
according to labor law.
Good.
She asked for her own death.
And..
what about Kula chart?
What do you want me to do?
Have him stay at the safe house for now.
Wait until this dies down.
But I have an important job for you right now.
What is it?
Get rid of my number one enemy
Rome.
You're back?
Where have you been since morning
The temple
You think I'm stupid?
l know
you went to ask for Rome'saddress from Pat.
Pat told me.
You knew already.
So why ask?
Why did you go see him?
I went to ask for his mercy
not to press charges against Kula chart.
You shamelessly went to beg him?
Both mother and son are so stupid!
Loss of my dignity.
Look.
I went to do my duty as a mother
and l succeeded.
Rome for gave Kula chart.
You're the one that has to thank him.
You're really stubborn.
We will win the case regardless.
Chart met with Napa at the motel!
As for Lak,
he got jumped by who knows who
Tian went to save him because Lak sent her those photos of him getting beat up.
Everything was a coincidence
No evidence that connects us to it.
Most importantly,
I used money to shut down every pathway.
You troubled yourself for nothing.
Does your money
teach Kula chart to know right from wrong?
Once this is over
he will cause another problem
Right now,
he got a woman pregnant.
That woman
probably won't take your money either
Don't meddle
I will handle this matter.
I can't not meddle.
That baby is my grandchild.
Ae.
Bring me a basket.
Ae!
Hey!
I told you not to meddle!
I sent someone to take care of her.
If you show up there, the reporters will know!
Just stay put.
Boss.
That's blood.
Red juice.
A kid spill ed it on me.
You're not lying to me are you?
Gosh you!
Who do you think you are to question me?
Are you my guardian?
No!
It's just...
I don't want to see you injured.
I don't want to see anything happen to you.
If that happens
I would rather die in your place
Is that'so?
It's true.
I can die for you
Thanks Tian.
But nothing will happen to me.
I gotten through my lowest point in life already.
From now on,
only good things will happen.
And you...
are the best thing that has happened to me.
Ive been ready to go for a long time!
Yo!
Let's go Dad.
The condo launch event
where Mon is the broker,
it's just a bridge
for me to introduce Tian to society,that's all
I had to quickly buy this place
because l want it to be an engagement gift
for my son and Tian.
Will you marry me, Candle?
P No matter how hard I try to resist it Ican't stop it
PBecause my heart keeps thinking about you 300 Metro mobile
NE
PIt'snot like how I used to be COVER MARK
. K MA
PI can't stop loving you
POr should I give up
Wang ree
PNo matter how much I forbid it,
in the end my heart can't do it House