=Drunk to Love You=
=Episode 10=
So the thing you've always
said you needed to do
was for your mom.
Qing.
I have a proposal.
Why not stay home
and take care of the kids?
Leave the company matters to me.
Our son is at an age
when he needs companionship.
But...
Trust me.
Give me the recipe
for Flower Moon Night,
and I will surely
make a good life for us.
Trust me, will you?
You registered the patent
in your own name.
Why are you so agitated?
You're scaring our son.
Don't cry.
I need this investment
from Ada's family.
So I had to do it, honey.
Jiang Qifan.
You lied to me.
(I thought I made my family unhappy.)
(But then I found out)
that my dad stole my mom's recipe.
I didn't expect that to happen to you.
But if it were me,
I probably wouldn't know how to face it.
Regardless of what adversity we're in,
every day, we wake up to a new day.
So we should treat each day
as if it were our last
and live it vigorously.
Where did you learn all this crap?
From you.
Regardless of what adversity we're in,
every day, we wake up to a new day.
So we should treat each day...
I forgot you saw that.
How embarrassing.
So you saw my talent
from the very beginning.
That's why you chose me for R&D.
Otherwise, why do you think I chose you,
moved into your house,
and live with you?
(So that's why.)
Okay.
Then, I'll go through
fire and water for my boss.
(Your boss.)
Once the R&D is successful,
we'll be even.
By then,
I'll be free again.
Perhaps by that time,
I might even realize my dream
of opening my own little tavern.
And it would be called
Drunk Pub.
You're so eager to be free again.
I have a life.
Right now, every single moment,
I'm working for you.
Only when the debt is paid off,
will I not need to fake a marriage
or a relationship.
And I can pursue a real romance.
Sounds like we have the same goal.
Liu Yali.
Let's work hard together
for Flower Moon Night
and your freedom.
Legend has it that Flower Moon Night
has a magical effect.
When people truly in love
drink Flower Moon Night,
they will eventually
live happily ever after.
This barrel has aged a bit long,
and the taste is wrong.
But how?
My dad stole my mom's recipe,
but he didn't master all of it.
However, in that less competitive era,
it was enough for him to make a fortune.
I see.
(We can definitely do it.)
Spill the beans.
What's going on?
Nothing's going on.
Liu Yali.
Haven't you realized it yourself?
Ever since you met Jiang Lu,
you blush when you drink.
How could that be?
I can hold my liquor very well, okay?
Unless you've fallen for some guy again.
Impossible.
Have you ever considered
why you care so much
about Jiang Lu's affairs?
After all, he's just your creditor
and your boss, that's all.
Yeah.
And now I finally understand
why he approached me.
And he also agreed
that once this matter is over,
my debts will be canceled
and I'll be free.
Shouldn't that make you happy?
I am happy.
You'd better be.
He sees you as an employee.
Don't see him as your boyfriend.
After opening hours,
the equipment is at your disposal.
Are you sure, Shuang?
I love you.
I'm helping you,
not him.
You have to find the answers yourself.
I will.
Alright.
Stop making faces there.
I agree.
But, Shuang,
there's a small issue.
We both work at the company
during the day,
and we need someone
to run errands for us.
Buy some materials and such.
Running errands?
Shuang.
Look what I brought for you.
What are you doing now?
You said before that you liked fishing.
I'll take you to Jiuyan Bridge to fish.
Chen Xiaofa.
I'm begging you.
I like fishing.
I like fishing?
Why are you mad?
Shuang.
Do you not like Jiuyan Bridge?
Then next time I can take you
to the Tonghui River, okay?
Chen Xiaofa.
You seem intelligent
with extraordinary talent.
Now, I'm offering you a part-time job.
Will you take it?
It won't pay much.
So, no.
Let's take a look.
"Baby, slay me."
What?
D-Don't get me wrong.
I only like Shuang.
In that case,
take our part-time job,
and we'll go fishing.
Deal?
Deal.
I'll take it.
Come on.
Starting today,
our team of Flower Moon Night
- is officially established.
- Established.
Look.
This is the bait
that needs to be cast.
You've become more tolerant of alcohol.
I really have.
Thanks to your lessons.
(He sees you as an employee.)
(Don't see him as your boyfriend.)
(You have to find the answers yourself.)
Jiang Lu,
So, you came to me
because of my skills.
So, maybe
you don't have
any affection
toward me.
Of course, I do.
(Okay.)
Then, I'll go through
fire and water for my boss.
In a way as a boss to an employee.
(I've actually learned to lie.)
So,
have you fallen for me?
Of course not.
(Liu Yali.)
Let's work hard together
for Flower Moon Night
and your freedom.
(Liu Yali.)
You lied.
Liu Yali.
Actually,
I like you.
=Drunk to Love You=
♪A momentary gaze between us♪
♪Like a fleeting streak of fireworks♪
♪The silence after confession♪
♪On the beach, in warm breeze♪
♪The orange sunset♪
♪In each other's arms♪
♪A wondrous whirlpool♪
♪Lying in the turbulence of night♪
♪In a way♪
♪I record your silhouette♪
♪Too many ifs between us♪
♪All twinkling in the eyes♪
♪If the world is slightly drunk♪
♪Only you and I are left alone♪
♪Let's dance together♪
♪Say goodbye to what's slipping away♪
♪Baby, can you hear me♪
♪Radio waves from the fridge
behind my ears♪
♪Midnight hours
under splendid ceiling lights♪
♪Only you and me are here♪
♪You and me♪