I believe the general managers...
are the symbol of the hotels.
So general managers
must have good leadership skills...
to represent the hotel.
He has to be warmhearted.
He has to be able to work long hours.
He has to be able to give and serve.
It is the general manager's job
to welcome the guests of the state...
and famous individuals
from all over the world.
So through this industry,
general managers can contribute...
to a national business.
As I mentioned, they have to have love...
for taking care of people.
That's what we do.
That's our business simply stated.
Trying to make people feel good.
We must create an environment...
that feels like their home...
and give them the amenities
they can enjoy at home.
We also had to import
special pasta for him...
and special water to boil his pasta in,
so it was a unique experience
with Pavarotti.
I received the former President
of the United States, Bush,
and the Queen of England.
If you're told to smile automatically,
people can see through that.
If you genuinely smile
and show genuine care and sincerity...
through your service,
I think that's a valuable gift to have.
And I think those are the kind of people
that we're looking for.
- Right here?
- Yes. That's a good spot, right?
That's good.
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
- Should I start?
- Yes. Go ahead.
Okay.
Seoul Hotel...
So to say a bit about Seoul Hotel...
Be quiet.
Hey, where's Manager Seo?
She went to the National Assembly
to invite VIP guests to today's event.
She must be here by now.
No need to feel nervous here.
I can't do this.
Hey, call her now.
Call Seo Jin Young to get here now!
(Episode 1, People Behind the Curtain)
- Oh, my. I'm sorry about that.
- It's all right.
Are you all right?
Okay. Bye.
Good work. Bye.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Goodness, Eun Jin. Be careful.
- Gosh.
- Thank you, Manager Seo.
- Okay.
- You pulled an all-nighter, right?
- Yes.
Right. Today's event is very important.
- Think of it as an emergency.
- Okay.
- Good work.
Hello.
- The lipstick color looks great on you.
- Really?
- That's a great color on you.
- Thanks.
It's so hot.
Manager Seo.
You're wanted at the event site.
Okay. Give me five minutes.
You must be here in a minute.
Manager Oh is throwing a fit.
Tell him I'm dead.
Hello.
Are you late again, Mi Ae?
The Japanese clients finished at 4 a.m.
- So you overslept?
- They wanted something for the hangover.
So I even joined them.
Brush your teeth.
I can smell sundae from you.
Manager Oh is going to kill me.
- Make sure to brush your teeth!
- Okay.
Manager Seo.
Tell him I'm dead.
Mr. Yoo said he would love to see you
one more time before you died.
Okay. I'll be upstairs soon.
Tell him his speech moved me,
so I came back to life.
Hello.
- Hello. How's your child?
- Good.
Hello.
- Hello.
I'm sorry.
We don't have that at our hotel.
Okay. Please give us 15 minutes.
- Yes. Young Chul.
- Yes.
Go buy a burger.
A burger?
Gosh. The five-year-old kid
is only asking for the burger.
Go buy the burger. You have ten minutes.
Yes, sir.
Room service.
Hey, what happened to the fried egg
for the Japanese guest in Room 1612?
- The gas valve is broken.
- What?
Hey, then run to the kitchen! Hurry up!
Which room was it?
- Room 1612!
- Okay.
Oh, dear.
- Have a good day.
I'm sorry.
My hands slipped.
You just ruined the appetizers
for the event.
Ask the inventory to see
how much caviar we have left.
We brought everything up earlier.
How much time do we have until the event?
Less than an hour and a half.
Check how much mushrooms
and asparagus we have in the fridge.
Yes, chef!
And make the shrimp marinade again.
Make the assorted vegetables again.
And...
Okay.
We'll use the live salmon
for our appetizers.
Call and order two boxes
of live salmon now.
Yes, chef!
The salmon must be freshly caught
from the South Pacific Ocean.
And we need them here in 30 minutes.
- Yes, chef.
- Tell the inventory that...
this is an emergency
and ask them to help us.
Yes, chef.
- And Manager Lee.
- Yes.
Get the girl out of the kitchen now.
Hello. Is this the inventory?
- This is the main kitchen.
- Hey. Wait.
- We have an emergency.
- Hey.
Yes.
- What are you doing here?
- What?
- I need fried eggs.
- We need fresh salmon.
The gas stove in the room service kitchen
isn't working.
- So...
- Gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- Okay.
Wait!
This is driving me crazy!
Hello, sir.
Why are you so late?
The color of your outfit
looks great on you, madam.
I'm not married yet.
Do you want to die?
Do you know what time it is?
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry. I was stuck in traffic.
What's wrong with your lipstick color?
Is this a bar?
I'm sorry. I'll fix that.
You're late and unpresentable.
I'll deduct ten points.
This will be taken into consideration
for your performance assessment.
Get to work.
Hey.
This costs 3,000 dollars.
I'll deduct 30 points
for your carelessness.
How long has she been doing that in there?
At least for over 20 minutes.
She must be fighting with the mirror.
Right.
She must be going through a breakup.
Goodness. She needs a man first
to go through a breakup.
Don't forget to add four pillows.
This particular guest today
likes to be surrounded by pillows.
Okay. We've already put more pillows here.
If you're done making the bed,
clean the floor of the living room again.
Make sure to open all the windows.
- Okay.
I'm telling you.
She's going through a breakup.
She doesn't have a boyfriend.
Are you there,
Manager Lee of Housekeeping?
Yes, this is Lee Soon Jung
from Housekeeping.
This is Seo Jin Young.
Yes. What is it?
(No Entrance)
This is the sixth complaint so far.
Six in an hour.
- When will you be done?
- I'm almost done.
Please hurry,
so the guests can use this path.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
Didn't I give you the notice yesterday?
I told you to pay more attention
to Room 206 on the 6th floor...
because the guest
was infamous for being picky.
- Hello.
The guest is allergic to blankets.
So change them to cotton blankets.
Or at least get thin wool comforters.
Are you there? Manager Lee?
- This is odd.
- Are you there?
- I can't hear you at all.
- Manager Lee?
I can't hear you.
- Can you hear me? I can't hear you.
- You can't hear me?
- I can't hear you. Can you hear me?
- Hello? Manager Lee?
- I can't hear you.
- Answer me, Manager Lee.
If it's that urgent,
you can do it yourself.
Manager Lee.
Lee Soon Jung!
Sir, I can take it from here.
No. It's okay. Get back to work.
This is the restroom.
I'll wait here...
and walk you to the coffee shop.
I'll meet you out here.
Okay. Thanks.
You're very kind.
Do you work in this hotel?
Yes. I do. Please go ahead.
I see. Then you're the hotel boy.
People don't use that term anymore.
You can say I'm a hotel employee.
Right. I'll do my business and come out.
Sure.
A hotel boy.
Hello, sir.
Who said it was allowed to smoke indoors?
You entered through the main lobby
like guests.
On top of that,
you didn't know when the shift ended...
and just strolled around the hotel.
As if it wasn't enough,
you smoked in a non-smoking area.
When will you grow up?
I'm sorry, Dad.
"Sir!"
Sir.
If I find you slacking off again,
I'll cut you off. Forget about
getting a salary or allowance from me.
It's crooked!
No, the other side.
Raise it higher. Yes.
Stop. You got it. Perfect.
Turn on the lights.
Mr. Yoo,
please start setting up the tables.
I got it. Okay.
Set up the tables.
Bring them closer.
You'll go home
after you fold 200 napkins today.
Yes, sir.
Are you all right?
It's time.
You still haven't changed.
What have you been doing?
This is the tie, right?
What is it? Did something happen?
It's about Young Jae.
I thought he would grow up
once I gave him a job.
But he has a long way to go.
It's been only three months.
You should try to baby him a bit.
He's our only son.
Don't be so strict with him.
Managing a hotel is tough...
even when you start your career
from the bottom.
You're kind to the employees
as if they're your own children.
Why are you so tough on your own son?
I don't know where his head is at.
That's enough, CEO Choi.
It's a good day. Try to smile.
Come on. Smile.
You told me that anyone working
at a hotel had no choice but to smile.
Go to your positions
to receive the guests.
(Announcement of Vision 21 to Celebrate
the 30th Anniversary of Seoul Hotel)
Pay special attention in escorting
the guests to their assigned seats.
And if you can, keep Assemblyman Park...
and Chairman Choi of Hando Products
away from each other. Okay?
- I got it.
- Okay.
And we should serve the water
once all the guests are seated.
We poured the water too soon last time.
So the water got lukewarm.
I got it.
Is everything ready?
Should we open the doors now?
The food has to come up first.
What?
Hurry! Hey, get out of the way!
- Move!
- Out of the way!
- Move away!
- Hurry.
- Get out of the way!
- Move!
- Hey.
Hurry up!
We'll be late.
Oh, no. The event is about to start.
How come nothing is set up?
It's the salmon.
- Assistant Lee.
- Yes.
- Shrimps.
- They're ready.
- Vegetables.
- Refill the sauce.
- It's done.
We only have 25 minutes until the event.
The guests will walk in at any minute!
Prepare the lettuce
and get the garnishes ready.
Yes, chef. Let's go.
You're not going to put out any food?
We're about to start!
Will you keep nagging
when I have food out here?
You're spitting on my food!
We must receive the guests
after 15 minutes, at the latest.
You must finish everything before then.
Okay?
You now have 14 minutes, not 15 minutes.
You all heard her.
We only have 14 minutes left.
Excluding the time we need to transport
the food, we have ten minutes.
Hurry up.
This is Manager-in-Charge Seo Jin Young.
- The guests are arriving.
- Okay. I'm going up now.
Hello.
What's going on, Manager Seo?
We must open the doors now.
The kitchen wants us to wait ten minutes.
The CEO will be here soon.
Where have you been, sir?
- I was dealing with a guest.
- Gosh.
CEO Choi is coming in.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Jin Young.
Why are you making the guests wait here?
They usually wait inside.
The live salmon arrived late.
How long is the delay?
Only ten minutes. I'm sure everything
will be ready by then.
What's going on with the kitchen?
What is this?
How come the food isn't ready?
Come on. It's time to open the doors now.
Wait.
No, it's past the opening time.
What on earth is going on?
Ask the salmon.
Hey, who's Salmon?
Get two people on each cart.
We don't have time. Hurry and go upstairs.
Be careful when you get in the elevator.
Keep it close, so it doesn't get stuck.
What's he doing?
Hey!
Hey! Move!
Chef!
Hey, get the elevator!
Get the elevator!
Are you all right, chef?
I'm all right.
Get him to the infirmary now.
- The rest of you, get the food out.
- Are you okay?
Are you all right?
I'm okay. Transport the food first.
Congratulations.
It's already been 30 years.
Thank you for coming.
So tell me. How does it feel
to have run an inn for 30 years?
Sorry. It was a joke.
Thank you for coming, Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee got the scholarship
this semester.
She has a long way to go
before she graduates.
But we've been getting
a lot of suitors for Yoon Hee.
Should I put your son on the list too?
Have a good time.
Mr. Yoo!
Open the doors.
- Welcome.
All right.
This is a celebratory party
for Seoul Hotel's 30th anniversary.
I sincerely thank all of you...
for attending this meaningful occasion.
As you know,
Seoul Hotel...
boasts...
a picturesque natural environment...
where four seasons are pronounced
throughout the year.
Thirty years ago,
this place was nothing but a humble hill.
But as for now,
our hotel was able to grow...
into a luxury hotel that
represents Korea...
thanks to the hard work...
our hotel staff has put in over the years.
I can sum up our past 30 years in 3 words.
Ambition.
We were passionate about our future.
Devotion.
We were committed to helping our guests.
Creativity.
We were creative in serving our guests.
With these three goals,
our hotel staff...
worked hard behind the curtain...
where people couldn't see them.
Among them,
my wife, Yoon Dong Sook,
is included as well.
However,
there are people
whom I'm more grateful to.
I would like to express my gratitude
toward them.
Countless guests...
have visited our hotel...
for the past 30 years.
I believe they are
the true owners of our hotel.
Don't smile, buddy.
Because you bounced,
I ended up working here like a dog.
Chef!
What happened?
Is the injury serious?
I'm fine.
- Are you sure? Let me see.
- Gosh.
I'm all right. I put some doenjang on it.
I'll be fine.
Gosh. Facility Maintenance Department
told me that they fixed the steam valves.
They didn't do anything wrong.
My guys messed it up.
Why today, of all days?
It made the day even more hectic.
That's life.
On hectic days, it gets crazier.
On slow days, nothing happens.
This is a battlefield, to begin with.
How's the event going?
It's going very well.
Do you still keep in touch with him?
Does he call you?
Did you hear any news?
Seo Jin Young.
What?
I'm talking about Han Tae Jun.
I should go upstairs.
I'll check on you later.
How much do you want?
How much will you sell this hotel for?
I didn't know that you were interested
in the hotel business.
I'm willing to offer...
a five-percent premium
on top of the market price for the hotel.
And...
if you want to keep working at the hotel,
I can make you an advisor
for the time being.
This is a happy occasion,
so I'll let that slide as an awful joke.
Ms. Kim, where are you going?
Who are you?
I'm lost. Can you tell me
how I can get out of here?
This is the path to the downtown area.
Where are you going?
Why do you ask?
So you can hail a cab for me?
What?
Hello.
Where are you?
How dare you leave without telling me?
What? The school library?
Then you should have told me
that you were leaving.
Okay. Finish up quickly and go home early.
The only thing she's interested in
is studying.
I'm glad
she doesn't take after her mother.
Do your job right.
Play some music.
What?
Is this the library?
Hey. Wait.
Do you want me to pay you for the ride?
No. It's not that.
Then go back to the hotel
and guard the door.
Hey.
People rarely meet like this by chance.
It'd be a shame if we parted like this.
My name is Choi Young Jae.
What's your name?
I'm nobody.
So he followed you here?
He didn't follow me. He gave me a ride.
Interesting.
Wouldn't a bellboy get fired for this?
Quit looking at him.
He's not leaving.
He must totally be into you.
Guys like him are so predictable.
Stop looking at him.
Deduct a point.
Goodness. Why can't they be cleaner?
- Manager Oh.
- Gosh.
What's going on?
- I needed to talk to you.
- About what?
I'll never be late from now on.
Can you not deduct any points
from my tardiness today?
There's a promotion test coming up
for the captain position in two months.
So what?
Having a lot of penalty points
won't be favorable for my promotion.
- I'm sure you know that.
- So what?
I really need to get promoted
this time around.
You want to get promoted...
to captain over hard-working employees
when you're always late?
Please, Manager Oh.
Can you please let it slide this once?
What was that?
Hey.
A hundred eighty-eight.
A hundred eighty-nine.
A hundred eighty...
A hundred ninety.
Who's there?
Are you done with your library visit?
The library visit?
Can you give me one more ride?
Sure. Of course.
- Get in, Eun Joo.
- Okay. Thanks. Bye.
Bye.
She's not getting in?
Her family will send her a car. Drive.
Let's go.
Hello?
It's me, Seo Jin Young.
Answer your phone.
Hey, Manager Han. You should call me.
Gosh. You're unbelievable.
Are you having a blast
after leaving me here all alone?
Do you like Las Vegas that much?
Answer the phone.
Darn it.
(Hotelier)
Yes, of course.
One blue margarita
and one screaming orgasm.
- Hi, O'neal. Sorry for being late.
- Yes, we can.
That will be about ten minutes. Okay?
Thank you, sir.
Let's go, Jun. You have a new order.
- Outside?
- Yes.
Where am I supposed to take it?
The poolside. There's a gentleman
out there who'd like a screaming orgasm.
- Orgasm?
- Yes.
- Maybe, he's Japanese.
- Exactly.
- Hi, Lola.
- Hi.
Jenny?
Jenny. Did you leave the door open...
Three messages. Message One.
It's me, Seo Jin Young.
Answer your phone.
Hey, Manager Han. You should call me.
Gosh. You're unbelievable.
Are you having a blast
after leaving me here all alone?
Do you like Las Vegas that much?
Seo Jin Young.
Now they cut my landline also.
Yes, this is the General Manager.
What? He's here?
Where?
At the site?
You can see this location...
when you go under the basement.
Sir, you're early.
What happened
to the additional loan we applied for?
I applied for a loan at a few banks.
But they must have heard
that we were tight on cash.
They're being quite thorough.
- And...
- What else?
I'm not sure if we can pay off
the promissory notes next month.
Go on.
Sir, I believe...
we might have bitten off more than
we could chew with this construction.
The construction is already ongoing.
Are you telling me to abort this project?
And the construction will be finished
in a couple of days.
What are you getting at?
We're struggling financially.
The value of my company alone...
goes over 300 million dollars.
Square your shoulders.
And have pride in your job!
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
It's okay. Sit down.
All right. I should take a break too.
Manager Seo, do you still
keep in touch with Han Tae Jun?
No. It's been a while since we lost touch.
I shouldn't have let him leave like that.
I bet he must be very disappointed in me.
I'm sure Tae Jun understands.
That was no one's fault.
Tae Jun had no choice but to leave.
And you weren't in any position
to stop him from leaving.
I should have...
pushed forward with Vision 21
just like he planned.
But it's going well now.
I need Han Tae Jun.
I need him here
to make things go smoothly.
Will you keep playing hooky here?
What?
I'll get back to work.
Chairman Kim Bok Man of Hangang Logistics
is waiting for you in the office.
Have you given my offer...
some thought?
The offer about buying your hotel.
I told you I took it as a joke.
I don't joke about business.
Then let me make myself very clear.
I will never sell this hotel to anyone.
You took out an additional loan
of 2.5 million dollars...
for the construction.
I'm sorry to say this,
but no banks...
will lend Seoul Hotel any money now.
- What?
- And...
if I wanted to,
I could easily demand my money back.
Do you think you can take over my hotel...
with those mere promissory notes?
I will have to put in a bit more work
to get your hotel.
What is this? Are you blackmailing me?
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you yell at me?
I'm telling you
to give up on your stupid hope...
and stay at home
after you retire from the hotel.
You jerk!
You should have braced yourself for this
when you decided to challenge me.
Don't you agree?
You scumbag.
Call me when you change your mind.
But if you take too much time,
it won't be good for you.
The clock is ticking.
A multi-resort village...
with a wide variety of entertainment
will be built.
This is the 1st stage of completion
in 2003.
Reach 300 million dollars in sales.
Reach the ordinary income
of 50 million dollars.
It will transform into a resort
in the heart of a city.
We can use the environmental change
as an opportunity to grow...
and reacquire the reputation
of a prestigious hotel from the past.
I plan to create a framework that
can exist and improve in the long run.
We must come together
to find the right direction...
for our future generation,
how to achieve that,
and design the future.
I summarized my plan
as the vision of Seoul Hotel.
That's why I'm giving you
this presentation today.
(Letter of Resignation)
A new business will be launched...
based on our know-how.
Launching a franchise
for hotels, restaurants,
and resorts.
Through e-commerce, you can launch
food distribution businesses...
and e-businesses through operating
the total website for food and beverages.
There you are.
I brought pine nut porridge today.
You've lost your appetite lately.
Is pine nut porridge okay for you?
When will we get to have
a family meal together?
Come here, honey.
Come on.
Are you sleeping?
Should I get her for you?
This game is over anyway.
Yes, sir. It all worked out rather easily.
Perhaps, the universe was on your side.
To run a successful business,
you need both skills and luck.
Are you ready?
Of course, sir.
I will make my move as soon as
you give me your word.
Do it after three days.
As soon as their mourning period is over.
Yes, sir.
Chef No, shouldn't we
at least wear black ribbons?
Right. Yes.
I know this is a hotel,
but he was like a father and a big brother
to us. And he's gone.
We must show our respect.
Who was that?
Who told the staff to wear black ribbons
on their uniform?
Lee Gab Soo, have you gone mad?
Who gave you permission to do so?
Wait. Manager Oh.
We're all mourning for his death.
We were like children to him.
So he was like a father to you.
But was he an enemy to me?
This is a hotel!
Go to the front.
All the bellmen are wearing black ribbons.
The guests are checking in, but they're
seeing mourning ribbons at the hotel.
Who would like to stay
at a hotel like this?
No, it depends on what you make of it.
The guests can also...
How does that depend on
what you make of it?
Hey.
He was our leader. Why can't we show
that we're mourning for our leader?
Don't wear it if you don't want to.
What did you say, you jerk?
Don't call me that.
- Why are you hitting me?
- Hey.
- Come on. Stop it.
- That's enough. Stop it!
- Why did you hit me? Darn it.
- Mr. Oh Hyung Man! Stop it!
- You jerk.
Stop it!
I understand where you're coming from,
Manager Oh.
But you didn't have to make
a violent scene.
We're all heartbroken that he's gone.
We can't start picking fights
against each other.
What are you doing?
Lee Gab Soo, you'd better be careful.
Suit yourself. Do whatever you want.
Assistant Lee.
Manager Oh.
Assistant Lee has a point, though.
Listen to me. This is my call to make!
I'm the Deputy General Manager.
Whatever I say goes!
Don't you look down on me.
We have a VIP guest from Japan.
The guest is only asking for you.
Okay.
I got it. You should go down
to the second floor.
- Okay.
Hello, Mr. Yamamoto.
I'll take it from here.
- This way?
- Yes.
(Letter of Resignation)
I'm sorry...
to resign so soon
after the death of Mr. Choi.
If you're sorry, take it back.
Ma'am.
You can't do this to us.
It hasn't even been a few days
since his funeral.
I know that
you're an employee of the hotel.
But it's unethical of you to resign now.
It's torturing me too, ma'am.
I'm truly sorry.
- All right.
- Please come back another time.
This isn't a good time to meet her.
No, listen.
This is an urgent matter for us.
- Get out of the way.
- Wait.
Let me schedule an appointment.
You can come then.
Sir, please do something.
They are here on behalf of the creditors.
I told them to come back another time,
but they are being unreasonable.
Don't stall time.
Tell Ms. Yoon to come out.
Sir!
I know nothing about managing a company...
or a hotel, for that matter.
But there is one thing I do know.
It's...
that...
my late husband loved this hotel
more than anyone.
This hotel...
was his life.
Of course.
I understand how upset you must be.
But you can't run a business
with just sentiments.
First of all, I plan to bring in an expert
who specializes in managing hotels.
Who on earth would work here
as a general manager...
when the hotel is going down?
Did you even think this through?
Who said our hotel was going down?
Our hotel is doing well.
For the time being,
I will take the CEO position...
and honor his aspiration.
You've never seen me smoke, right?
I tried to quit multiple times.
But I just couldn't.
I even promised my husband that
I would quit smoking.
But I always smoked in hiding.
Now, there's no need to hide to smoke.
Open it.
(Employee Personal Card)
This was on his desk
right before he passed away.
My husband must have remembered him
in his last moment.
That's understandable. They got along well
as if they were a father and a son.
It's not easy to find employees
as distinguished and diligent as him.
Which brings me to my question.
Can you go and look for him?
The banks and creditors...
can't wait to tear this place apart.
The shareholders are on my back
to sell off the hotel.
I can't hold out for long by myself.
But...
I know that it's awkward between you two.
Think of it as the late CEO's last wish.
Can you go and bring Han Tae Jun back?
Where did it go? Is it out?
Yes. It's out of bounds, sir.
One more.
I'm sorry, sir.
So she didn't listen to your threats?
She knows nothing about the industry
or how business works.
But what?
That's why our threats
aren't working on her at all.
We were happy that Mr. Choi was gone.
But we may have
a bigger problem on our hands.
The general manager even quit.
What does she think she can do?
This is the sixth time.
One more mulligan.
Do you know anything about that,
General Manager?
Well, I heard she was planning
to hire someone.
What?
- Good shot.
Hey, go find the balls.
All seven of them.
What?
It's not easy
because of the foreign capital.
Gosh, this is going to give us a headache.
So what's our plan?
We need an expert from abroad
who has experience in M&A.
Great. Get an expert then.
I don't mind how much it costs me.
Here. I put together a file.
He successfully led nine M&A cases...
in the last three years.
And half of the cases
went over millions of dollars.
He specializes in mergers and acquisitions
in the hotel industry.
He's a Harvard Law graduate
and worked at a law firm on Wall Street.
He has connections
and is good at what he does.
On top of that, he's Korean.
Where is he right now?
He's working on an M&A case
of a hotel in Las Vegas.
Las Vegas?
Are you still hung up
on what happened three years ago?
- That was an accident!
- Yes, it was!
Goodness.
Jenny, get in!
There's only so much I can put up with.
How can you put this on the table?
It's dangerous.
Here's your coffee now.
I'm fine.
Gosh. What is he doing?
What's wrong with you guys?
Sir.
Don't touch her!
Mister!
Mister! Help!
- Stop the car.
- What are you going to do...
in the middle of a desert?
Stop the car right now, you stupid coward!
Fine. Suit yourself!
Hey, give me my bag!