♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you
is written all over the binary♪
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
♪Every tap, every key♪
♪The codes are saying I like you♪
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪For us, I'll work hard
to defeat the BUG♪
♪Always on standby,
never lag, never hang♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪Want to be together
♪And live in your arms♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪I'll key in you and I♪
♪In every special and sweet program♪
=Cute Programmer=
=Episode 22=
So, you've finally returned...
Yicheng.
Is it you?
Why are you here at this late hour?
Aren't you going to let me in?
Actually, I heard
that you and Lu Li had a divorce.
Where did you hear that?
Zitong told me by accident.
Everyone in the company
knows about it now.
They said it's because of me.
This has nothing to do with you.
That's a relief.
If Lu Li has any misunderstandings
about our relationship,
I can explain it to her personally.
You have nothing to explain to her.
I don't even know why
she filed for a divorce.
I told you already.
A young girl like her
is unpredictable.
I guess she must be tired
of the relationship.
Tired of it?
Yeah.
Actually, I knew
you were forced to marry her.
Actually, having a divorce
can at least cover your losses.
Who told you I was forced to marry her?
That's not the point.
The point is you're free now.
Lu Li is still young.
She's reckless.
She never thinks
from your perspective.
After my observation,
I think she doesn't suit you at all.
It's a good thing for you two
to be separated.
I know the best
whether she suits me or not.
I don't need you
to remind me about that.
Your wound hasn't fully recovered yet.
You should return and rest.
Sorry.
If my words made you uncomfortable,
I'll apologize for it.
I'm just worried about you.
I just feel troubled as there are
too many things to do lately.
You should return.
All right.
Rest well, all right?
I'll return first.
(It's fine.)
(We still have a long way to go.)
(Yicheng,)
(you'll definitely
return to my side one day.)
(Lu Li,)
(why are you still fantasising about him?)
What are you doing?
I was watching my drama, you know?
The news will begin soon.
I know you love drama,
but we need to be concerned with
national affairs as well,
am I right?
National affairs?
You're not even concerned with
your family affairs.
Did you buy the free-range chicken
for our daughter?
This...
I didn't manage to buy it.
It was sold out when I went there.
Who's that?
At this late hour?
Coming.
Li, why are you back at this late hour?
Where's Jiang?
Didn't he send you back?
I came back alone.
Li, come in.
Come.
Come in.
Are you going on a business trip?
Dad, Mum,
I resigned from my job.
Dad,
do we still have any
Instant Cardio-Reliever Pill?
I think so.
Please get it for me.
You guys can take it
if you experience any chest pain later.
Wait.
I think our hearts are pretty healthy.
Tell us.
What happened between
you and Jiang Yicheng?
The person he truly fancies has returned.
So,
I choose to back out
of the relationship.
Back out?
What do you mean?
You guys are married, you know?
Dad,
Mum,
I'm sorry.
I failed.
What do you mean by saying you failed?
When did it happen?
Today.
Have you completed the procedures?
Not yet.
I've signed the divorce settlement.
Divorce?
Wait.
Are you guys having a divorce?
Li,
be honest with me, okay?
Did Jiang Yicheng force you
to go for a divorce?
I'll look for him.
Dad,
I made the decision myself.
But why?
When you got married, you told me
that you were more afraid of
having regrets than of failing.
Do you regret your decision now?
I don't.
Without this period,
I can never understand how it feels like
to contribute to one's relationship
in a unilateral way.
You'll never win a person's heart
by giving in all the time
while disregarding your principles.
Mum,
I was the one
who forced the marriage to happen.
Now, everything is back
to its original place.
Good.
Where are you going?
I'm going to sleep.
Wait.
You...
How could you sleep at a time like this?
What about our daughter?
Your daughter can make her own decision.
She didn't even discuss
her marriage and divorce with us.
Now that the dice is cast,
what else do you expect me to do?
Marriage isn't child's play.
She can't just get married
and have a divorce
whenever she feels like it.
Li,
how about this?
I'll bring you to
the Jiang Family right now,
all right?
Let's have a chat with Yicheng.
Come.
Let's go.
Dad,
I already had a chat with him.
Next,
I plan to live in a new environment.
Where are you going?
Chongqing.
Chongqing?
That's too far.
How about this?
I'll register a tour for you,
all right?
Let's go on a relaxing trip.
Listen to me, okay?
Lu,
you saw it yourself.
Your daughter has
made arrangements for everything.
She's just here to notify us.
Fine.
You can do whatever you like.
I'm too tired to care.
Dad,
I've sent my resume to them.
The company in Chongqing told me
to go for an interview two days later.
You're something else.
Where's Lu Li?
I wanted to ask you the same question.
You didn't answer my call
the entire night.
What happened between you and Lu Li?
Did you divorce her?
Don't you know where she is?
That's a strange question.
How would I know where she is?
If so, what did she tell you
two days ago?
That day, she gave me a coffee cup.
She said she wanted to thank me
for taking care of her.
I didn't expect it
to be a farewell gift.
Why are you staring at me?
Don't tell me you think that
she and I...
She got in your car
after she mentioned to me
that she wanted a divorce.
I do admit that I was frustrated
at that moment.
But after I cool down,
I realised that it was
a misunderstanding.
We've been brothers for many years.
I'm sure you won't do that
behind my back.
It seems like you retained your clarity.
But you always had
a great relationship with Lu Li.
Do you know why
she wanted to divorce me?
Didn't I remind you long ago?
If you don't communicate with her,
you'll regret it.
I did ask her what happened.
She wasn't willing to tell me.
Men and women are different.
Sometimes, you need more than
just your ears to listen.
What do I need then?
You need to use your heart.
You two have been married
for quite some time.
Let me ask you this.
Do you know what's
Lu Li's favourite food?
Besides programming,
what else does Lu Li like to do?
What's her favourite movie?
What's her favourite colour or book?
And,
do you know where her home is?
Have you been there before?
You see.
These might be the reasons
why she left you.
That's impossible.
We got married to each other on terms.
She won't file for a divorce
because of petty things like these.
Didn't I tell you already?
How are you this slow?
Forget it.
Actually, I promised
Lu Li not to tell anyone about this.
But it seems like you will never
find your answer
if I don't tell you about it.
What is it?
Do you still remember
the first game you created?
Dream Maker?
Log into the game.
You may find the answer you seek.
(ID: ZERO, Password)
Koala.
(Sofun Game)
Take a break.
You won't get any inspiration
from staring at the screen.
You'll get conjunctivitis instead.
I didn't expect a genius like me
to be stuck here.
Since you don't have any inspiration,
you should change your mindset
and relax for a while.
How do I relax?
The game you sold to Chendong,
Dream Maker,
it's very popular now.
Why don't you log into your account?
The games I sold
are just like spilled milk.
Besides, I don't know
what changes they've made to the game.
What if they did a bad job?
I'll be infuriated by then.
You should take a nap then.
I don't wish
to see you becoming
the first wealthy kid
to die because of his own business.
The interface sucks.
The animation is rubbish.
They did make great changes to the game.
(Koala)
(If you're free,)
(why don't we team up
and kill some monsters?)
(I can test the attack animation as well.)
(Okay.)
(Battle Angel, Level 30)
(Congratulations)
(Game guru, you're awesome.)
(Please lead me to victory.)
This must be a brat.
(What grade are you in?
Don't you need to study?)
(I'm in 12th Grade.)
(You should study
instead of playing games.)
(Aren't you playing it as well?)
(I'm a postgraduate, you know?)
(Little brat.)
(What's your major then?)
(I don't even know
which major to choose.)
(I feel lost.)
(You're playing video games every day
even though you're a little brat.)
(Of course you'll feel lost.)
(I don't play video games every day.)
(I just love to play Dream Maker.)
(I think the game developer)
(is amazing.)
I guess you have great taste.
(Why is Dream Maker
your favourite game?)
(Because it can help me
get rid of the real world's trouble)
(temporarily when I play it.)
(I can head to another world.)
(It's just like parallel spacetimes.)
(I can never feel this immersion)
(when I play other games.)
Immersion?
(Game guru,
you haven't answered me yet.)
(What's your major?)
(Computer Science.)
(Not bad at all.)
(You achieved a breakthrough point
in such a short time.)
I met a 12th Grade kid
when I was playing Dream Maker.
She's pretty interesting.
I played many matches with her.
In the end, I received
plenty of inspiration.
So, is she your goddess of inspiration?
I think her name is Koala.
(Game guru, it's been one week
since you last logged in.)
(Have you been busy lately?)
♪Will no longer see my waste♪
(It's been 16 days
since you were online.)
(If you see this message,)
(please)
(add my QQ account.)
♪The more you yearn for me,
the more it hurts♪
(Game guru, I decided
to follow your suggestion.)
(I will take Computer Science
as my major.)
(So, I can't play video games)
(before NCEE.)
(I will get into the University of Xinhai.)
(Wait for me, all right?)
(By the way,)
(I kept forgetting to tell you my name.)
(I'm Lu Li.)
♪You said we're meant to be together♪
(By the way, I forgot to tell you
that I'm Lu Li)
♪I try to hold back my tears
and face the lies with a smile♪
(By the way, I forgot to tell you
that I'm Lu Li)
♪But the sky pours down the rain
and drenches my face♪
♪You said we'd meet again
that very spring♪
♪And you showed up on time♪
(Goodbye, Jiang Yicheng.)
(Jiang Yicheng,)
(goodbye.)
♪To those good old days♪
(Uninstall Dream Maker)
♪Thank you for finally
saying goodbye to me♪
♪All night I kept thinking and thinking♪
♪About that one summer in my memories♪
(Uninstalling Dream Maker.
Please wait...)
♪A record of our past♪
♪You said we're meant to be together♪
♪But that will never happen♪
♪I try to hold back my tears
and face the lies with a smile♪
Li,
these are dried fishes
and some cold dishes made by
me and your mother.
Open your luggage.
Let me put them in.
Dad, there's no need for that.
My luggage is too heavy.
If you put it in, it'll be difficult
for me to carry the luggage.
What should I do then?
How about this? Let me send you there.
You don't need to carry me, all right?
Dad,
I'm a big girl now.
And, when the child of our neighbour,
Aunt Wang, went abroad,
no one saw her off.
I'll be fine.
All right then.
When you reach there,
you should send me your address
once you find a house.
I'll mail them to you.
I made an appointment with an agent.
We'll visit some houses once I'm there.
Look at you.
You insist on going somewhere far.
Listen,
when you're outside by yourself,
as a girl,
you must take note of your own safety.
Your purse, mobile phone,
identification card, you need
to keep everything safe.
Don't go out at night
unless it's an emergency.
You need to give us
a video call every day, all right?
Don't forget about it.
Okay.
Dad, I got it.
It's almost time.
Caixia,
Li will head to the airport soon.
Caixia?
Mum,
I'm sorry.
I know I'm being willful.
I know I didn't consider your feelings.
But with my current life experience,
I think this is the only way for me.
Mum,
Dad,
thank you for tolerating my willfulness.
You two must take
good care of yourselves.
I will visit you two often.
I must've owed you a huge debt
in my past life.
Move aside.
I'll ask you one last time.
Will you regret your decision?
That's good to see.
This is your life.
We only have the right
to give you suggestions.
You're the one
who'll make the decisions.
If you truly don't regret your decision,
I'll respect your choice.
Your mother's right.
It's fine as long as you're happy.
Dad, Mum,
being your daughter
is the happiest thing in my life.
Licking my boots
won't solve everything, you know?
Listen up.
Next time, if you're in trouble
and you keep everything to yourself
without discussing them with us,
you can forget about coming back.
Hurry and see our daughter off.
We don't have much time.
Let's go.
Mum,
actually, I...
Hurry, the lift is here.
Coming.
Hurry.
You won't make it in time. Go now.
She's coming.
(Game guru,)
(I got into the University of Xinhai.
I'm majoring in Computer Science.)
(In the future,
I'll be your direct junior.)
♪Maybe you only want to break out♪
(I finally found out
about your name today.)
(So, your name is Jiang Yicheng.)
(I didn't expect you
to be this famous in school.)
(If I go to find you,)
(will you remember who I am?)
♪So here you are, caught in a struggle♪
(I met you today.)
(Actually, I wanted to
introduce myself to you.)
Hello, senior.
My name is...
I don't care who you are.
Stop following me.
(But you said you were
uninterested in me.)
(I feel a bit upset now.)
(In addition, you have
a non-mainstream hairstyle.)
(Today, when I was at the library,)
(I sent you a painting in secret.)
♪Want to break out♪
(You didn't take it,)
(Senior, good luck with your viva voce)
(but you replied with a smiley face.)
(I was elated.)
♪And turn back on the whole world♪
♪Only to worry about your troubles♪
(Today, you presented me with an award.)
Congratulations.
(You were the third person to my left.)
(This was our first photo together.)
(I will cherish it.)
(After I graduate from university,)
(I will surely join your company.)
(Wait for me.)
♪The world is back♪
(A lot of things happened today.)
(I joined your company.)
(And I knew that
you like to eat prawns.)
(Marriage certificate)
(Today, I'm going to be married to you.)
(Lu Li)
(Will you fall for me?)
(She's back.)
(So, it's not that
you won't fall for anyone else.)
(It's just that you won't fall for me.)
♪And you want to go home♪
♪I'm all alone on a deserted street♪
(Jiang Yicheng,)
♪As the sky laughs down at me♪
(goodbye.)
♪Washing down my face with rain♪
♪The world is back♪
♪But I'm not going back♪
Dad, Mum,
where's Lu Li?
Who are you calling Dad and Mum?
You're something else, huh?
You turned up in front of us
before we went looking for you.
Great.
Let me teach you a lesson today.
What are you doing?
Don't do this!
Who told him to bully Li?
You mustn't do this.
Why are you stopping me?
You want all of our neighbours
to know about Li's divorce?
Fine.
I'll let you off today.
Dad, Mum...
I dare you to say that again!
I'm sorry.
I really wish to have a chat with her.
Jiang,
this marriage
was proposed by my daughter
in the first place.
But
you guys can't live together anymore.
I think you two should
just lead separate lives.
There's a misunderstanding between us.
What misunderstanding?
Listen,
from today onwards,
you will never get to see Li again.
Scram!
If she doesn't want to see me,
I'll wait here until she sees me.
That's useless.
She's not here.
Where did she go?
What has that got to do with you?
And,
you're not welcomed here.
In the future, I'll beat you up
whenever you show your face!
She went to the airport.
Wait!
Thanks, Mum.
You!
Wait.
Don't go.
Just let him go.
What if your heart can't take it?
What should I do then?
I can't take that, you know?
Even so, you shouldn't tell him.
You!
Don't worry. He won't make it in time.
The plane has departed.
Youngsters nowadays
are glib talkers, you know?
I'm just worried that
your heart can't take it.
(Security Check)
Morning, Mum.
Are you arranging flowers?
Morning.
Tong,
are you heading to the company?
Yeah.
Wait a moment.
I need to send something to your father.
I can visit Li as well.
Let's go.
I suddenly remembered that there was
nothing for me to do in the office.
I think I can skip work today.
You've skipped the morning shift,
you know?
What would other employees
think about you if you skipped
the afternoon shift as well?
By the way, Mum,
my car broke down.
I can't drive there.
We can call a cab then.
I think I'm having a stomachache.
Is this appendicitis?
Your appendix is over here.
It's not acute gastroenteritis, right?
Mum,
bring me to the hospital.
My tummy hurts so much.
It hurts.
Did your father cheat on me?
Did Dad cheat on you?
With who?
If that wasn't the case,
why did you stop me
from going to the company?
What exactly happened?
Mum,
I...
Did something happen
between your brother and Li?
They're fine.
It's just that they're busy lately.
(Hello.)
(The number you have dialled
is unavailable.)
Tell me honestly.
What happened between
Li and your brother?
This is the first time
she has not answered my call.
Why did she turn off her phone?
This...
I...
Don't you want to tell me?
Fine.
I'll head to the company myself.
Wait, Mum.
It's not that I don't want to tell you.
Just let me go.
What are you doing?
Let me go!
I'm sure you're hiding something from me.
I need to ask them what happened.
Brother!
Mum wants to head to the company.
Yicheng,
tell me.
What happened between you and Li?
What's going on?
She wants a divorce.
Mum.
Calm down.
Come.
Have a seat.
Was it because of Li Man?
I told you before.
I told you not to be in touch with her.
Even if Li has the nicest temper
in the world,
she can't stand it
when you're having your way
with both women at the same time.
My son,
I know you like Li.
How about...
How about this?
Let me bring you to her.
Maybe, Li will forgive you
on account of me.
Let's go.
Mum,
she left.
Where did she go?
She left Xinhai.
I don't know where she went.
Mister,
please drive slower.
Safety is our priority.
Miss, don't worry.
I'm the best driver
in Chongqing.
Okay.
(Chaotianmen Square;
Liberation Monument)
Hello.
I've reached the location you mentioned.
Where should I go after that?
Continue along the path.
You'll see a building in front of you.
There's a flight of steps
beside the building.
Go down the stairs.
I'll be waiting for you
in front of the house.
All right.
Thank you.
Excuse me, is this the right path?
Yes.
This path is nearer to the house.
Chongqing is a mountain city.
You need to climb hills quite often
when you're here.
It'll be fine when you get used to it.
Chongqing is a 5D city indeed.
Of course.
We have plenty of delicacies here.
- Yet you won't see many fatties around.
- Let me help you.
It's because we need to
exercise every day.
Thanks.
Miss, you can do it.
Why don't we carry it together?
It's fine. It's not that heavy.
Wouldn't it be great
if I got to know Lu Li
when I was in university?
Calm down.
Take your time.
You'll find her eventually.
Why didn't she tell me?
What to tell?
Do you want her to confess to you?
Brother,
you don't understand women at all.
Do you know why people
have a crush on someone else?
It's because they're afraid that
they will no longer be friends
with their crushes once
their confession fails.
But if she doesn't confess to me,
how would she know
what the result will be?
When you like someone,
you'll feel inferior subconsciously.
Moreover,
you haven't given her
enough sense of security.
You weren't there by her side
when she was caught in an accident.
I've already explained it to her.
Rome wasn't built in a day.
That incident might just be the fuse.
Moreover, it wasn't
just a normal accident.
I'm sure she was terrified back then.
It's normal for her to hate you.
What do you mean by
it wasn't a normal accident?
She was tailed by someone.
She was caught in an accident
because someone tailed her.
Didn't she tell you about it?
Where's the assailant?
Did they manage to catch him?
Not yet.
That person wore a face mask.
Lu Li couldn't identity his features.
She just saw a scar on his hand.
Besides, it happened
at the CCTV's blind spot.
So...
Wait.
You said there's a scar on his hand.
Was it the left or the right hand?
The right hand.
Do you know that person?
I need to verify something.
Pay the booking fee for me.
Yicheng,
I didn't expect you
to ask me out for a meal.
I was in a bad mood last time.
Sorry.
I understand.
So, is this meal my compensation?
Can I choose the venue then?
Go ahead.
Seat belt.
Thanks.
No thanks.
Thank you.
I'll foot the bill.
Amy,
I'm not in the office.
We can talk after I return.
So, are you seeing somebody?
Why are you here?
Don't worry.
Even if the cops find me,
you won't be implicated.
Because Lu Li collided with
the car herself.
I didn't push her.
She can only blame herself
for her bad luck.
What kind of nonsense are you spouting?
Didn't you call me here
because of Lu Li's accident?
What accident?
When did I call you here?
You sent me a message.
You told me to rush here.
Look.
(Man: The cops are here.)
Stop pretending.
(Come immediately)
Only the two of us are here.
Are you addicted to acting?
Get up!
What?
Just leave!
Hurry!
Since you're here,
we should have a chat.
Were you the one who sent the message?
It's all thanks to you for
using the same password
even after so many years.
Come.
Your lipstick is smearing.
Let me head to the washroom.
Wait for me, okay?
What's going on?
Why did you do this?
Because Lu Li saw someone
chasing her with a knife.
And, there's a scar on his right hand.
Listen,
I just wanted to scare her off
so that she could leave you.
Actually, I can swear to God.
Lu Li's accident
has nothing to do with me.
She collided with the car herself.
I also found out about it just now.
I didn't order him to do this.
Speak!
It's all me.
It has nothing to do with Man.
It's my fault.
I took it upon myself to act.
Stop pretending.
Are you addicted to acting?
He said that just now, right?
I wasn't pretending.
He was spouting nonsense.
I was truly in the dark.
How could he know who Lu Li was
if you didn't order him to do so?
It's because Man
couldn't let you go.
And you have another girlfriend.
That's why I followed you guys.
So, did you do it because of her?
Of course.
Last time, you were still
abusing your daughter.
But now,
you're saying that you did everything
because of her.
How do you guys still dare to say
that you are not pretending?
Yicheng,
it isn't what you think.
Give me some time.
I'll explain everything to you,
okay?
You didn't tell me the truth before this
because you guys wanted to put on an act
so that I can discover
what happened three years ago myself
and feel guilty about it, am I right?
You did change.
I don't even know who you are anymore.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted
to make you fall for me again.
I told you long ago.
It's all in the past.
It will never be the same
as the present.
Our relationship
ended three years ago.
But my love for you hasn't ended yet.
You said I changed.
Yes,
I did change.
But if I didn't change,
I would never be able to get
to where I am right now.
And I'll never be able
to meet your mother's requirements.
I have no way
to stay beside you officially
if I didn't change.
Why do you think I'm doing this?
I did everything because of you.
So, do you think I should
accept you and what you've done for me?
Stop deceiving yourself.
You're just unwilling
to accept the truth.
Am I unwilling to accept the truth?
Isn't it because
you already fell for Lu Li?
My relationship with her
has nothing to do with you.
We should never meet in private again.
By the way,
I plan to report this to the cops.
You!
Who does he think he is?
Are you happy now?
Man,
I tried to teach Lu Li a lesson
because of you.
Now, are you pretending
to be my kind father?
Where were you when I needed you?
I know my mistake now.
I want to make it up to you.
How do you plan to do that?
What else can you do
besides dragging me down?
Would you do these things for me
if I weren't as wealthy?
I didn't do it for money.
Fine then.
Return me the money I gave to you.
I...
It's been so many years.
I really had enough of you!
You should ponder over what you'd done!
Miss Lu,
it must've been tough on you.
You're here to check out the houses
right after you arrive here.
This house
satisfies your every need.
And,
there are several
huge industrial parks nearby.
Most people who work here
will rent a house in this area.
And, the quality of the tenants
is pretty high.
This house looks new.
Yes.
Initially, the owner
wanted to stay here.
But he changed his job after that.
That's why he's renting it out.
Miss Lu,
if you do wish to stay here,
I can give you another 200 yuan offer.
All right. I'll move in immediately.
Immediately?
This is my first time
seeing a tenant like you.
Is there a problem?
No problem at all.
No problem.
(From today onwards,)
(I, Jiang Yicheng,
will pursue you again.)
(I will surely find you.)
(Lu Li,)
(wait for me.)
(There's a popular Chinese proverb.)
(The best time)
(to plant a tree was ten years ago.)
(The second best time is now.)
(Maybe, it's the same
for relationships.)
(As long as you wish to start anew,)
(it will never be too late.)
♪Tall and big,
you have a childish voice♪
♪Naive♪
♪Petty♪
♪Small and little,
I feel a little stressed around you♪
♪Afraid to go near♪
♪I hope to see you every morning♪
♪So that my day can be meaningful♪
♪Waiting to hear your voice every night♪
♪To break the silence of the night♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Sometimes you're a little stubborn♪
♪A bad temper♪
♪With a touch of jealousy♪
♪So I'll just have to coax you
and let you have your way♪
♪Hurry, hurry, go away rain♪
♪This song is for you,
the one I love the most♪
♪We'll walk down
the path of the future together♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Never mind♪
♪I love you♪