♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you
is written all over the binary♪
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
♪Every tap, every key♪
♪The codes are saying I like you♪
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪For us, I'll work hard
to defeat the BUG♪
♪Always on standby,
never lag, never hang♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪Want to be together
♪And live in your arms♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪I'll key in you and I♪
♪In every special and sweet program♪
=Cute Programmer=
=Episode 28=
Are you okay?
I lost.
When you were young,
you couldn't win against me.
Now that I'm old, I can't defeat you.
In the past, I didn't know
how to analyse strategies.
I didn't know how to
defend and retaliate.
Now, I know how to do it.
I just need to be patient
and wait for your mistakes.
That's right.
So, if you wish to win,
you need to understand
your opponent first.
Do you think you
understand that Lu fellow?
What do you think about his personality?
What about his work status,
friend status, and family background?
Do you know all of them?
Why should I know about them?
You don't even know
the basic conditions of your love rival.
How could you hand over
your wife to him just like this?
Why do I have a son like you?
Lu Li fell for him.
Back then, your mother
fell for that Zhao fellow as well.
Listen,
if I didn't strike first
and show your mother
the true nature of that playboy, Zhao,
you and Tong wouldn't
have been born in the first place.
Listen,
back then, I've spent a lot of effort
to court your mother.
That's how she fell for me in the end.
But look at you.
The divorce isn't even over.
Yet you're already retreating.
Listen,
you're being an embarrassment.
It's no wonder Lu Li doesn't wish
to return with you.
Oh yeah,
we haven't gone through our divorce yet.
Listen,
you always had the right to act.
If you're my son,
you should never cower.
Stop retreating and hesitating.
Get Lu Li back,
all right?
But what if this Lu Jingwen
is someone worth handing her over to?
You don't need to figure that out.
At least, you should do it first.
Am I right?
Even if you lose, at least
you gave it a try before.
Let's go.
Let's go for another round.
I don't believe that I can't win you
in the next round.
Brat.
(Listen,)
(you're being an embarrassment.)
(It's no wonder Lu Li doesn't wish
to return with you.)
(At least, you should do it first,)
(am I right?)
(Even if you lose, at least
you gave it a try before.)
(I know what I want.)
(I know who I like.)
I wish my life would be
just like programming.
I wish it can proceed smoothly.
Forget it. You don't need to jump.
Just go.
(Our relationship wasn't harmonious
when we first got married.)
(I thought I could
shorten the distance between us)
(by making your favourite dishes.)
(Dumb koala,)
(this time, I won't back down again.)
(I'm willing to do anything as long as
it's for your happiness.)
(Because,)
(I love you.)
It's me.
Investigate someone for me.
This is all the intel I have
regarding Lu Jingwen.
Is he engaged?
Are you sure?
Yes.
There's a picture down below.
His fiancee posted it online
after their engagement banquet.
Understood.
Are you leaving again?
I'm done with the documents. We can
talk about other things when I return.
Where are you going?
I'm going to Chongqing.
Brother,
I wish you success.
Jiang Yicheng,
you did come back.
Let's talk this over.
You're already engaged.
How did you know?
Don't!
My parents arranged that engagement
for me. I didn't even agree to it.
Does Lu Li know about that?
I think I forgot to tell her.
But
I...
Why do both your sister and you
love to hit people in the face?
Can't you let me finish my words?
I thought you left.
I did.
But I couldn't let go of you.
But why?
You know why.
You can't entrust your future
to Lu Jingwen.
Why are you saying that?
Although this may make me
a despicable person,
I still need to tell you.
He has a fiancee.
What?
Calm down for now.
If you still wish
to be together with him,
I know how to make him
cancel his engagement.
Why are you doing this?
My father told me that
if I love someone,
I need to do everything I can
to steal her back.
That's what I thought at first.
But you made me understand something.
If you love someone, it doesn't mean
you have to possess that person.
You should give that person your love
without expecting anything in return.
If your happiness
can only be supplied by Lu Jingwen,
I'm willing to let go of you
and help you fulfil your wish.
This is between me and Lu Jingwen.
There's no need to trouble yourself.
I will resolve this issue myself.
What do you plan to do?
I will break up with him.
If you already have an answer to that,
that means I'll never let go of you.
Lu Li,
give me another chance.
Let us start anew, all right?
Are you sure?
But I...
If you're talking about the child,
you can rest at ease.
I will treat him as my own child.
I will raise him together with you.
Are you sure you aren't
doing it out of impulse?
I know what I'm doing.
Rest early.
Good night.
I'll take a closer look when I return.
You guys should do the same.
We'll discuss it next time.
All right?
Mr. Lu, we've gone through everything.
Why don't we hear about
Lu Li's thoughts first?
She understands the game the best.
All right.
Tell us your thoughts.
I'm not really familiar with
how film adaptation works.
But Boss is relatable as
it is built upon
the conflicting relationship
between bosses and employees.
That's why gamers get a kick out of it
when they find interesting ways
to beat the bosses.
If the film adaptation doesn't follow
the core concept,
it'll be meaningless to develop this IP.
Great words.
Mr. Lu,
I beg to differ.
Let's not talk about
the fact that there aren't any
relationships or plots within the game.
There's no way for us
to create something like
100 ways to die in films.
If we don't alter the concept greatly,
I'm afraid it won't even
pass the first evaluation.
I think you have a point as well.
So, everyone should consider
what they've said
and think about what to do.
Let's discuss this next time, all right?
Meeting dismissed.
Lu Li, stay here.
Mr. Lu,
what happened to your nose?
I went for a Guasha treatment
as I felt heaty.
You guys can resume your work.
Close the door as well.
What's with you acting mysteriously?
How dare you still laugh?
I was hurt because I wanted
to test Jiang Yicheng for you.
Did Jiang Yicheng beat you up?
We fought each other.
But I don't think he was injured
when I saw him last night.
It's because I let him win on purpose.
Did he tell you about my fiancee?
Look at how despicable he is.
He couldn't deal with you.
That's why he investigated me
and reported me to you.
So,
for your safety,
you should abandon me
and choose your fiancee.
Did you two reconcile with each other?
Does he know about the child?
I haven't thought of a way
to break it to him yet.
You see, if a man still doesn't give up
even if you had a child
with someone else,
it's either he's silly or
he's truly in love with you.
Anyway, to me, he's a pass.
I think you shouldn't
be too hard on yourself.
Actually, I'm afraid.
In the past, he was something
unobtainable to me.
But now, he's right in front of me.
I feel surreal.
If so, you should take the chance
and enjoy his courting.
Men might deceive people
with their mouths,
but they won't deceive people
with their actions.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
The best way to treat a man is to
be gentle with a hint of deviousness.
Senior,
thank you for teaching me so much.
Are you just thanking me with your words?
I didn't betray you
even when I was hurt.
Don't you think you should
do something in exchange?
You can continue to sponge off me.
Great.
But you need to make something
that can improve blood circulation.
No problem.
Hello,
are you Lu Li?
Hello.
I am Lu Li.
These are your parcels.
I didn't buy all these things.
Did you send them to the wrong person?
No.
Please sign here if there's no problem.
But these aren't mine.
They're mine.
All right.
Please sign here.
Over here.
Thanks.
No problem.
I'll leave first.
Wait,
I remembered I brought that as well.
Why did you send all these things to me?
From today onwards,
I'll stay together with you.
Why didn't you discuss it with me first?
We're still legally married.
So, what's mine is yours
and what's yours is mine.
You're not allowed to say no.
Can you be reasonable for once?
We're living separately.
Right now, I don't want to be reasonable.
Are you opening the door or not?
My house is too small for you.
I can sleep on the sofa.
(Where is he?)
(Wasn't he cooking?)
(I thought he was cooking.)
(Why is he taking a bath?)
Lu Li,
bring my stuff for me.
What stuff?
Bring me my pyjamas from the luggage.
Take it yourself.
I'll take it myself then.
I'll bring it over here for you.
And bring my underpants as well.
You better don't be too much.
I mean, I can choose not to wear it.
I'm just afraid you might not
get used to it.
Thanks.
By the way,
do you have any clean towels?
There's a new towel under the sink.
I need two of them. One for my face.
Another for my feet.
Both of them are parts of your body.
Why are you being picky about them?
I'll use yours then.
Jiang Yicheng!
You're not allowed to use mine!
I!
I use that to wipe my feet!
It's fine.
I don't mind.
Jiang Yicheng!
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Are you here to create a mess?
I...
I just wanted to learn how to make soup.
It's hot!
Did you go through the same thing
when you learned how to cook?
I'm way better. You can't
do two things at once.
I'm just inexperienced.
I won't repeat the same mistake next time.
I was not referring to it.
I was referring to you.
Actually, you don't need to
force yourself to do this.
I'm not forcing myself. I'm doing it
of my own accord.
I'll order some deliveries.
You haven't turned off the tap yet.
(Today, I've finally gotten
one step closer to you.)
♪The love is sprouting♪
♪Leaving a doodle on the cake♪
♪All the lover's prattle I want to say
to you under the stars♪
♪I want to watch the cherry blossom♪
♪Set off fireworks with you♪
(Today, I've finally gotten
one step closer to you too.)
♪Yes. You'll be my baby♪
♪Yes. I'll be your guardian♪
♪I'll give you happiness♪
♪Not allowing you to shed a tear♪
♪Yes. You'll be my baby♪
♪Yes. I'll be your guardian♪
♪I'll give you happiness♪
♪You perfect my life♪
(In your fourth month's pregnancy)
♪The words I speak in the cable car♪
♪A kiss on the cheek under the sunset♪
♪I want to watch the cherry blossom♪
♪Set off fireworks with you♪
♪I'll turn my love to you
into a fairy tale♪
♪Yes. You'll be my baby♪
♪Yes. I'll be your guardian♪
♪I'll give you happiness♪
♪You perfect my life♪
♪Yes. You'll be my baby♪
♪Yes. I'll be your guardian♪
♪I'll give you happiness♪
♪Not allowing you to shed a tear♪
♪Yes. You'll be my baby♪
♪Yes. I'll be your guardian♪
♪I'll give you happiness♪
♪You perfect my life♪
Why are you here?
Lu Li is still asleep.
This house belongs to my wife.
Why can't I be here?
You sneaky thug.
Go away.
I'm looking for my junior.
I warn you.
You better stay away from Lu Li.
I will take care of her and her child.
So, are you biting the hand
that feeds you?
Jiang Yicheng,
you'll regret it.
Who was that just now?
Someone from the
property management team.
By the way,
today's your rest day, right?
What do you plan to do?
I plan to go out.
Let's have a meal before we go out then.
You brought so many things here.
Are you not planning to return home?
My home
is the place with you around.
Did I say something wrong?
Why did you take so many of them?
You have such long hair.
I'm sure you'll finish it
in a blink of an eye.
I'm buying more just in case.
You can buy one for testing purpose.
And I plan to cut my hair short.
That way, it'll be easier for me
to manage my hair.
I think you'll look great
in short hair as well.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
Of course I was afraid that
you might laugh at me.
Now that I think about it,
I guess I fell for you
before we got married.
Let's go.
It's fine even if
you don't want to cut your hair short.
I'll wash your hair for you
in the future.
Let's go.
Lu Li,
why haven't I seen you wear any of these
radiation-proof pregnancy suits before?
It's inconvenient for me
to wear them at work.
I'll just be more careful.
Your work is to interact with computers.
Of course you must be cautious.
Senior has found someone else
to share my burden with me.
Now, I deal with projects. I don't need
to deal with computers for a long time.
If he really cared about you,
he wouldn't have let you
continue your work.
If I'm not mistaken,
I think you assigned me to the project.
I...
Are you two looking for
radiation-proof pregnancy suits?
Do you need any recommendations?
- Yes.
- No.
You see,
it's common for people to use
electronic devices nowadays.
So, experts have suggested
that pregnant mothers should wear
radiation-proof pregnancy suits
when they're zero
to four months pregnant.
I think you're less than
four months pregnant, right?
So, do you have any recommendations?
What about this?
For this type, the lower skirt is longer.
It's better when it can
cover a larger area.
So, is there anything
we should take note of?
I don't suggest wearing it outdoors.
If you wear it outdoors,
it'll affect her from
absorbing sunlight.
Mister,
I'm sure you're a new father, right?
Father?
Lu Li.
Darling!
I like you.
I know that.
Can you stop shouting?
What did you know?
I know you like...
What I meant was,
the counter is over there.
It's a misunderstanding.
It's over there.
Where?
Jiang Yicheng.
What's the matter?
Are you sure that you don't mind
about my pregnancy?
I would be lying
if I said I didn't mind it at all.
But you're the one I care about.
The child is a part of you as well.
That's why I can accept it.
What about the company?
What will you do with your company?
I don't need to be
in my company every day.
But it's different for you.
I wish to stay by your side
during such a special period.
Let's go home.
We still have time.
Let's go to the market.
I'll cook dinner for you tonight.
Are you sure you're not trying
to burn down my house?
Last night, I was just testing
a new program.
Today, I'll use the updated version.
Let's go.
Come.
I can't believe that
you made all of these.
In the past, I thought
cooking was troublesome.
That's why I didn't
give it everything I got.
Excluding last night's experiment,
I guess you can say that
this is my first time cooking.
You're the first person
to try my cooking.
What about the time
you cooked for my parents?
That doesn't count.
Congratulations on unlocking
a new skill then.
Here you go.
How's the taste?
It tastes bland.
Did you forget to put salt?
You're pregnant.
You can't eat anything too salty.
If you consume too much salt,
you'll experience high blood pressure
during your gestation period.
Freckles will grow on your face.
And
it'll affect the baby's
hair growth as well.
So,
the salty food you used to love,
you need to consume
less of them in the future.
How did you know that much?
I told you before.
I will take good care of
you and the baby.
By the way,
you're allergic to seafood.
So, when you consume other food,
you need to consume something
that's high in protein
and calcium.
Seafood allergy isn't hereditary, right?
You can eat first.
I'll check.
Is seafood allergy hereditary?
Since you made the dishes today,
let me wash them.
There's no need for us
to assign the chores equally.
I'll do all of these in the future.
Will you be okay with them?
Do you not believe me?
I just felt that your change
was too sudden for me.
I haven't got used to it yet.
You need to get used to it eventually,
since we're still in the first flush
of our marriage.
Let's wash them together.
It'll be faster that way.
Reverse.
Sit down.
Staying by my side
is the greatest help you can offer.
This unit
is through from North to South,
and it has especially great lighting.
The subway station is just downstairs.
Its price and location are great.
Please.
Is this a work building?
I think you should
take a look at residential units
instead of this.
Who said I'm going to stay here myself?
What do you plan to use it for?
I'm planning to open a training course.
Are you renting it for me?
This unit is near to your house.
You can reach here
in ten minutes by walking.
It'll only take one stop
for you to reach your company
using public transport.
And there are plenty of
tables and chairs here.
The space is just enough.
Because I don't want you
to overexert yourself.
If there are too many students,
your body won't be able to take it.
What do you think?
Are you upset?
I just wanted to give you a surprise.
We can take a look at other units
if you don't like it here.
Thank you,
Jiang Yicheng.
There are many ways for you
to express your gratitude.
Which one will you choose?
I won't choose any of them,
because I'm rejecting your kindness.
But why?
If I open a training course right now,
I won't be able
to teach my students
after a few months.
Actually, I don't want you
to tire yourself out either.
But I'll support you as long as
you want to do it.
Actually, I did it because Zhong Yao
was interested in programming.
I just wanted to help her out.
But after that, I realised that
many people,
including their parents, think
that it isn't suitable for a woman
to be a programmer.
And many people don't know
what they truly like
when they're selecting their majors
before entering university.
Not everyone is as lucky as me.
I had someone to guide me
to my true answer
when I was making my life decisions.
Now,
do you still think
that it's fortunate for you to meet me?
That's right.
Back then, you were the one
who opened the door to programming for me.
Now, I wish to become
the person who can guide
all those girls out there.
So, you wish
to promote a programming course
that targets women?
That's right.
Not only do I hope that this course
can help them to understand programming,
but I also hope that people
in the society
may eliminate their prejudices
against female programmers.
Programming isn't only meant for men.
Women have the right
to learn it as well.
And female programmers are just
as good as their male counterparts.
But this is much harder than
opening a training course.
It'll be a long journey,
and it'll take a long time.
Maybe, you won't achieve anything
noteworthy during this time.
Yeah.
I've thought about that as well.
Although I may be an ant
trying to shake a huge tree,
I still wish to do something about it.
One day, I hope I can break through
the gender barrier embedded within
the computer science industry.
You're not an ant.
You're a tree-climbing koala.
Remember to bring me with you
when you climb the tree.
At first, I thought you would
analyse the pros and cons
and reject my idea.
That was the past me.
Now, I plan to go with the flow
and support my dear wife.
Come.
Have some fruits.
It's getting late. I need to rest.
Let's talk a little longer.
There's nothing to talk about.
Tell me about your work.
I can give you some suggestions.
Actually, I haven't come up
with a complete concept yet.
But I hope more people
can understand what
I'm trying to do here.
I hope those people who are interested
can contact me themselves.
First, I think I need
to promote the idea.
That's a great idea.
But how do you plan to achieve that?
It isn't realistic for me to buy my spot
into Weibo's hot search.
And it doesn't last long.
What do you think about posting
programming videos
on short video platforms?
If I do so,
maybe I need to wait for a longer time.
But once I have enough people
following my account,
it'll be useful for future promotions.
What you need now
is a way for you to use the least amount
of time, money, and human labour
to achieve the best promotional effect.
Does such a way exist?
I do.
But tell me
how you plan to thank me first.
Tell me about the idea first.
As for time, I only need three days.
As for money, I only need printing fee.
As for human labour,
I only need you and me.
Are you telling me that we're going to
give out pamphlets?
Giving out pamphlets is only
the first step in my promotion strategy.
The second step is
the most important step.
We can contact free venues
and hold a salon event that revolves
around the theme of programming.
People who will participate in the event
are the target audience that
we give our pamphlets to.
That way,
we can promote programming itself
while interacting with people
who are interested in it face to face.
What do you think about my plan?
I think it's pretty good.
Why haven't I thought about that before?
The plans I had were too complicated.
I think a simple
and direct plan like this
is the most realistic plan for us.
So, how do you plan to thank me?
Do you think I'm going to kiss you?
I didn't say yes.
When do you plan to say yes then?
Why didn't I realise that you were this
thick-skinned in the past?
My father told me before.
If I'm a man, I should never cower.
I should stop retreating and hesitating.
Don't you want to talk about work?
I won't talk to you.
You're only good at being a thug.
That's right. I'm a thug.
Boss?
Why haven't you completed
the new function
that the Planning Department asked for?
I'll add it in once I finish
the anti-plugin.
Why is it so noisy over there?
Boss,
I'm playing video games in a cybercafe.
Do you still have time
to play video games?
You have two days to complete your task.
Brother,
I have to go.
you want to leave right after winning?
Don't you think it's unsuitable?
Let's play a few rounds.
It's meaningless when you're this bad.
You should brush up on your skills.
What do you mean by that?
Are you trying to disrespect me?
Let go of me.
You have a short temper, huh?
Do you dare to
play another round with me?
If I lose,
I'll agree to your every condition.
I have no interest in that.
Someone fainted!
Call the ambulance!
Hurry!
Yeah!
Are you okay?
Don't leave.
Don't let him leave.
Call the cops!
- Why?
- Calm down.
Why did he beat him up?
I'm going to sue him!
What gives him the right to do so?
What kind of person is he?
Lin Shutian?
Do you know me?
The person inside is my employee.
This is my name card.
(Xu Yuanzhi, Chairman)
I may be able to help you.
Basically,
people with great business ideas
love to gather at our place.
So, I will provide a place
for them to gather around,
interact with each other,
and find capital to do their business.
So, you plan to transform this cafe
into an incubator meant for attracting
potential investors and entrepreneurs?
That's right.
But we're still in the early stage.
- This way.
- So, most of the time,
we need people to organise home parties
and salon events
to cover our daily expenses.
So, do you have any requests for us
if we are to hold a salon event here?
You can hold it here.
What kind of content
do you plan to make?
I plan to introduce
and promote female programmers.
Many people came here
to promote online businesses and so on.
But you're the first person to talk
about things like female programmers.
Don't you think
your theme is a bit niche?
That's precisely
why we need to promote it.
We've viewed a lot of venues.
We think your venue
is the most suitable for our event.
You have great taste.
First, let me thank you two
for your support.
Let me ask this first.
When do you plan to hold your event?
And how many participants
will be coming?
I plan to hold it during the afternoon
the day after tomorrow.
As for the number of participants...
We can't confirm that for now.
Is that so? You see,
our venue is free.
We can only cover our daily expenses
by selling coffee,
snacks, and Western food
to the participants.
So, we do have certain demands
over the number of participants.
So, how many participants do we need?
At least two hundred participants.
According to the past salon events
that had been held,
less than one-third of the expected
participants will turn up for the event.
Moreover, your theme is quite niche.
I'm afraid the number of
participants will be fewer.
You guys can take your time.
All right then. Two hundred participants it is.
All right.
It's decided then.
This is great!
There are so many gifts!
I'm so envious of her!
She's so blissful!
She even has fresh flowers!
♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
How many flowers are there?
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you
is written all over the binary♪
(Twelve-year-old Lu Li, happy New Year)
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
(Six-year-old Lu Li, happy Children's day)
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
(Eighteen-year-old Lu Li, Happy Birthday.)
♪The codes are saying I like you♪
(I hope you can hold on to your dreams.)
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪For us, I'll work hard
to defeat the BUG♪
♪Always on standby,
never lag, never hang♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪Want to be together
and live in your arms♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪I'll key in you and I♪
♪In every special and sweet program♪
(A great love)
(isn't giving the other party
a bigger world to explore.)
(A great love)
(is to hold the other party's hand
and explore the world together.)
(A great love is to have the courage)
(to say)
(Hello World)
(even after experiencing love and hate.)
♪Tall and big,
you have a childish voice♪
♪Naive♪
♪Petty♪
♪Small and little,
I feel a little stressed around you♪
♪Afraid to go near♪
♪I hope to see you every morning♪
♪So that my day can be meaningful♪
♪Waiting to hear your voice every night♪
♪To break the silence of the night♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Sometimes you're a little stubborn♪
♪A bad temper♪
♪With a touch of jealousy♪
♪So I'll just have to coax you
and let you have your way♪
♪Hurry, hurry, go away rain♪
♪This song is for you,
the one I love the most♪
♪We'll walk down
the path of the future together♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Never mind♪
♪I love you♪