♪Secretly keying love into the program♪
♪Ctrl＋Love♪
♪Thinking of you
is written all over the binary♪
♪Save and back up every word of concern♪
♪Two hearts growing closer♪
♪Every tap, every key♪
♪The codes are saying I like you♪
♪I'll brave through the night♪
♪For us, I'll work hard
to defeat the BUG♪
♪Always on standby,
never lag, never hang♪
♪Just to meet you♪
♪Want to be together
♪And live in your arms♪
♪Spend the four seasons together♪
♪I'll key in you and I♪
♪In every special and sweet program♪
=Cute Programmer=
=Episode 24=
Lu Li.
Apologise to her.
So, in your eyes,
is she the only person worth your trust?
I'm the person who was together
with you morning until night.
But you think I'm someone
who only knows how to mess around.
Did you ask me out
because you plan to forgive me?
I'll leave after finishing my words.
I hope you can pull out
from the Xuan Zhong Ji project.
Why?
Because I don't want to
be involved with you any longer.
But I've explained everything
to you on that day.
I was really in the dark
when my father went to see Lu Li.
And now, he has received
his just desserts.
Do you know something?
He's actually in bad health right now.
I'm uninterested
in your father's matter.
Your relationship with him
has nothing to do with me.
You have three days
to do your work handover.
This is a requirement, not a suggestion.
I disagree.
Even if we have personal grudges
against each other,
we shouldn't bring them to work.
You were the one who deleted
Boss's demo, right?
I've explained everything to you.
I went to the office
to turn off the lights.
The CCTVs were fixed.
It proved that the lights in the office
have been left off.
So, have you been
investigating me in secret?
You have never trusted me.
If you insist on staying here,
I will present this evidence to EG.
They will pursue your responsibility.
Do you really need to resort to this
because of a person like Lu Li?
I owe her a clear name.
I need to return it to her.
But she doesn't care about it anymore.
She has left.
She will never come back.
I will find her.
It's a pity that it's too late.
Lu Li was at the hotel as well
when we went to the hotel
to meet Andrew that day.
The receptionist told me about it.
A girl in a white t-shirt came
to search for our names.
I forgot to tell you something.
That day, I left my lipstick mark
on your t-shirt.
She thought we got back together again.
That's why she gave up entirely on you.
Do you think she'll still forgive you?
Do you even know who you are right now?
Lu Li,
come here.
Director Gao,
can I help you?
I have a file that I was supposed to
show to Mr. Lu.
I think I deleted it by accident.
Can you restore the file for me?
I can.
When did you delete it?
A few days ago.
All right.
Let me take a look.
(Data Recovery)
Is this the file?
What I want is last year's
wage summary sheet.
But I've restored everything
you deleted for the past week.
This is the only file I got.
I'm sure I've deleted it.
All right.
I'll give it another try.
Please take a look
and see if your file is in these.
It isn't there.
Do you even know how to do your job?
She joined the company
through backdoor means.
What can you expect from her?
Lu Li,
you can tell me directly
if you're not good at your work.
Since Mr. Lu was the one
who recommended you,
I won't make things difficult for you.
But there's no need for you
to make all these trash
to waste my time.
Where's last year's payroll record?
Why do you need that?
Don't tell me you want to
redo it right now?
I need to remind you.
Two people from our department
spent half a month completing that.
Where's the file?
I got it.
Lu Li,
what exactly are you doing?
Do you know we can start a new project
with the time you're wasting right now?
Done.
(Payroll of December 2020)
That's impossible.
That's right.
This is the one.
She used barely five minutes
to complete it.
How did you do it?
When you use Microsoft Excel
to deal with data,
you need to key in the data
multiple times.
But it is embedded with VBA Programming.
It can store high numbers
of repetitive functions
as a VBA code.
Director Gao,
I think you should be more careful
with the files our colleagues
have worked so hard on.
If you wish to learn about
report automation,
you can come to me at any time.
I don't mind wasting my time
to teach you.
Lu Li!
You were so cool just now.
That was satisfying.
I don't think I'm that cool.
Before I became a network manager,
I was a programmer.
She'll only embarrass herself
when she challenges me.
Actually, Director Gao
didn't delete the file.
She just wanted to
make things difficult for you.
I know.
The computers will never deceive us.
Lu Li,
you are so cool.
I will surely court you
if you were a man.
If you want a programmer as a boyfriend,
I can introduce some to you.
Sure!
It's best if they're as capable as you.
I want a man who can make
my report automation come true.
Actually,
you can use your time
in filling out the datasheet
to learn VBA Programming.
If you do so, you won't need to
worry about it in the future.
You're right.
I always heard people
talking about programming.
So, what exactly is programming?
Actually, programming
is the process where
humans interact with computers.
You mean humans can give orders
to other humans,
and even computers
by using different languages?
Is that what you mean?
That's right.
By using certain words,
sentences and formats
that computers can comprehend,
you can form a source code
when you place them together.
The process where we write source codes
is called programming.
Thank you for leading me
into a new world.
Master, please accept my bow.
You may drop the formality.
In the future,
if you wish to learn programming,
you can come to me at any time.
That's great.
From now on, I will unshackle myself
and proceed to become
a master of administration.
My dear Li!
You are having your meal.
Let me show you my fruits of labour.
Are you only having vegetables?
You should have some meat.
You shouldn't be this stingy on yourself.
I can pay them for you.
I just don't feel like eating meat.
I feel like puking
when I smell meat lately.
Why do women have to suffer so much?
Not only do we have
to bleed every month,
but we also need to bear the pain
of giving birth.
Tell me, why do men
have the privilege to be carefree then?
This is so unfair.
Wait, why did I mention that scum?
I saw him last night.
What?
Did he go to find you?
I think he's here on a business trip.
But he didn't see me.
He must be a toxic person.
He's still haunting you
even though you went somewhere far away.
Forget it.
Let's forget about him.
How's the progress with your neighbour?
Don't spout nonsense. He's my boss.
Will your boss send you to work
and pick you up every day?
We're staying in the same building.
I guess only a person like you
won't notice it.
Look at how he's treating you.
It's obvious that
he's interested in you.
Look at the condition I'm in right now.
How could I ruin his future?
How is this ruining his future?
Don't tell me you wish to stay single
for the rest of your life?
But it's better for you to be cautious.
What if he's a playboy
and he flirts with
every girl beside him?
Did you receive the local speciality
that I had sent to you?
I think they've arrived.
I haven't opened the parcel
I received just now.
Give me a second.
Lu Li,
look.
I didn't buy that for you.
Tianqi's dad made it for me.
I'm sure that he's flirting with me.
But it's unfortunate that
I've fallen for him.
Don't tell me you're dating him online?
What if he's a sleazy middle-aged man?
What should you do by then?
I don't think that will happen.
He's a great artist.
He even knows
how to make clay sculptures.
He's gentle, kind, and humorous.
Even if he's not Prince Charming,
I guess he's an artistic youth.
I think it's best for you
to meet him in person.
If he doesn't live up
to your expectations,
you can give up on him sooner.
You're right.
I should meet him in person.
If he's a great guy,
I can be his girlfriend officially
so that no one can steal him from me.
All right.
I'll stop disturbing you.
Remember
to eat more meat, all right?
Goodbye.
The hotpot seasoning is great.
So delicious.
The hotpot seasoning is tasty indeed.
Are you a deliveryman?
Who are you looking for?
Why aren't you knocking?
Don't tell me he's still here?
I'll call the cops
if you continue knocking.
Caixia, it's me.
It's Sister Wang.
Coming!
I'll get the door.
Coming.
Sister Wang.
Caixia.
Mum.
Mum?
Is this your son-in-law?
He's handsome indeed.
This...
Look at the number of things
he brought with him.
My child, hurry and enter.
Thank you, aunt.
Caixia,
your son-in-law is top-notch indeed.
You did a great job at hiding him away.
The people in our dance group
kept gossiping about your daughter.
They said Li had a bad husband.
Some people even say that
she got a remarried husband.
You have great tolerance indeed.
Are these dumplings for us?
Thank you.
See you next time.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Dad,
Mum.
This...
These are the local specialities
I brought back from Chongqing.
Please try them.
- Why did you go to Chongqing?
My company is working together
with a company in Chongqing.
We don't lack food here.
I think you can keep them for yourself.
But I'm already here.
Just try them.
(Chongqing's local delicacies)
Did you guys go to Chongqing as well?
I have friends all over the world.
Yeah.
My friend in Chongqing sent them to me.
He's right.
It's none of your business.
Hurry and leave.
Just leave.
I won't interrupt your meal then.
(From Chongqing to Xinhai, Lu)
Look.
Why did you leave the boxes here?
Did Lu Li send them here?
- No!
Is Lu Li in Chongqing?
- No.
Thank you, Dad, Mum.
Chongqing's hotpot is pretty good.
Why did he thank us?
He didn't realise it, did he?
It's because of your stupid boxes!
I already told you to throw them away!
But you couldn't bear
to throw them away.
Wait.
It's because I was busy preparing
the ingredients just now.
You could've thrown it away
if you watched less drama.
I do every other chore in the house.
Tell me, what have you done
for the family?
Fine.
You're always right.
Enough.
We should stop arguing.
We must do something
about this situation.
It would be good
if they could reconcile with each other.
Reconcile with each other?
Do you want him to bully Li again?
No way in hell!
Let's finish our meal.
Yiming,
I need to head to Chongqing.
This might be a long trip.
I'll leave the company to you.
Didn't you just return?
Is something wrong with the contract?
It's more important than that.
Call me if anything happens.
I'll hang up now.
I guess I must've owed
you and your brother
a huge debt in my past life.
I feel like puking.
Now, you feel like puking.
What were you thinking
when you were drinking?
I didn't drink for fun.
I drank to get rid of my troubles.
Drank to get rid of your troubles? Sure?
Of course.
My sister's boyfriend cheated on her.
My brother had a divorce.
The person I like doesn't like me.
It's too hard for me!
Your makeup will be smeared
if you continue to cry.
Yiming,
tell me. Why isn't our relationship
proceeding smoothly?
When you like someone,
it doesn't necessarily mean
that they'll like you back.
I need to donate my money.
But why?
I'm sure it's because I'm too rich.
That's why God is taking away
my love from me.
When will you reach home in this state?
Let me carry you on my back.
Can you carry me on your back
for the rest of your life?
Only until I send you home.
Yiming, thank you
for picking me up.
Thank you for picking me up.
I can't return home.
My parents will give me a beating.
I told you I couldn't return home.
Did you hear me?
What? Don't tell me you want
to stay in a hotel?
I don't want to stay in a hotel.
I don't want to stay in a hotel!
Fine. What about my house?
All right.
Go!
I need water.
I finally managed to sleep on his bed!
That fool!
Why are you wearing my shirt?
I smell like alcohol.
But you didn't even
change my clothes for me.
You're annoying.
Go and wash up.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Don't move.
Zitong, stop messing around.
I dreamt about this scene before.
Let me enjoy this moment once again.
I should've sent you home last night.
Go and wash up.
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Yiming,
why don't you dare to look at me?
Is it because
I look attractive right now?
I think you should
look at yourself in the mirror.
Why did I use toothpaste?
Zitong, are you done?
Breakfast is ready.
Zitong,
come and have your breakfast.
Just ignore me.
I'm too embarrassed to face you.
(Hangout)
Hello.
Did your company
hire an employee called Lu Li lately?
This is her picture.
I'm sorry.
We didn't hire her.
Thank you.
(Namelist of tech companies)
(Lu Li, tracing family member)
Hello, mister.
(The 47th Floor)
Hello,
I wish to pass a message to my wife
(The 47th Floor Food Stall)
using this platform.
All right.
So, what do you wish
to say to your wife?
Lu Li, I'm sorry.
I'm at Chongqing.
Can we meet up?
I'm still using the same phone number.
I heard that you came to Chongqing.
I'm here for my private matter.
What private matter?
Do you need help?
I'm here to find my wife.
You don't even have a girlfriend.
Since when did you get yourself a wife?
Are you helping me or not?
Of course.
I want to see
what kind of woman she is.
She has great taste for dumping you.
I'll hang up for now.
Wait.
Come and sign the contract.
After that, I'll treat you to a meal.
We'll celebrate our cooperation.
Mainly, I want to
understand your situation
so that I can help you find your wife,
am I right?
Sure.
Mr. Lu, looks like
you're in a good mood today.
The guy I hated the most
was dumped by his wife.
He reaped what he sowed.
All of the ladies I fancied
went to court him.
I'm curious about the lady
who had avenged me.
Sign here.
I heard that you were accepting
students in the company.
I'm doing it to increase
the company's work efficiency.
Boss, will you add my salary?
Only my girlfriend can spend my money.
Why don't you
give it a try?
Do you want me to quit?
You're no fun.
Don't you know that it's a joke?
I won't increase your salary.
But I can treat you to a meal.
Let me bring you out
for a feast today.
You can forget about it.
I'm used to sleeping early
and waking up early.
You're wasting your beautiful youth.
Honestly speaking,
I don't know what happened
to you in the past.
But since you came to a new city,
if you wish to start anew,
you shouldn't isolate yourself.
You need to interact with others
more often.
At least, you should
make yourself happier.
Mr. Lu, since you wish
to treat me to a meal,
I won't stand on ceremony then.
Mr. Lu,
have you ever heard of the saying
"Heaven spares nobody"?
Maybe, you'll experience the same fate
as your friend in the future.
Bye.
Thanks.
I think the people we referred to
have the same name,
but their age doesn't match.
Lu Li?
Sorry about that.
You're here.
Have a seat.
Mr. Lu, was this what you meant
by treating me to a meal?
Yeah.
It just so happens that
I need to welcome my guest as well.
That's why I called everyone here.
Don't tell me you don't wish to see us?
I would've stayed home
if I knew this would happen.
My guest will arrive soon.
Come.
Sit beside me.
All right.
By the way, Gao Xi,
later,
Mr. Jiang will sit here.
You must attend to his needs.
No problem.
Mr. Jiang?
That's right.
Mr. Lu prepared this feast
to welcome Mr. Jiang
from Enchant Technology.
Don't tell me you don't know?
Sorry for being late.
Mr. Jiang.
You're finally here.
I guess the VIP is always
the last person to arrive, huh?
Did you go to find your wife?
Let me introduce them to you.
This is Lu Li, our company's
network manager.
She's our junior as well.
Hello, Mr. Jiang.
What?
Do you two know each other?
No, we don't.
We...
All right.
Come.
Let's welcome Mr. Jiang with a toast.
Welcome.
Mr. Jiang is not a stranger.
You don't need to be shy.
Dig in.
Put on some weight.
Miss Lu, since you graduated from
the University of Xinhai,
why did you come to work in Chongqing?
I like Chongqing.
I heard that you majored in
Computer Science.
Isn't it a waste for you to
be a network manager at a film company?
Why didn't you become a programmer?
That concerns my privacy.
I do not wish to answer that.
Mr. Jiang, I haven't
offered you a toast.
Since we know each other,
let's drop the formality.
If so, Mr. Jiang, let me offer you
a personal toast
as my acknowledgement
of your talent and good looking.
Can I do so?
A beauty is offering you a toast.
If you don't drink it,
you're not a gentleman.
Cheers.
You may do as you please.
Thanks.
It's rare for the three of us
to gather at the same place
after graduation.
Junior,
don't you think you need to
offer your senior a toast?
Mr. Lu, I can't drink.
Are you sure you can't drink?
Or, are you refusing to drink
because Mr. Jiang is around?
I don't think it's good for you
to act so arrogantly.
It's inconvenient for me to drink today.
Mr. Jiang, if you don't mind,
I would like to
replace my wine with juice.
Lu Li, you don't know your place at all.
I don't mind.
Our junior isn't drinking with you
because you aren't
as important as I am to her.
Come, Junior. We should drink
when we're this close to each other.
Jingwen,
I'll drink on her behalf.
Bottoms up.
I finally understand
why you're not drinking.
It's because you become a hoodlum
after you drink.
Darling,
I've finally found you.
Give me a hug.
Can you see closely before you hug me?
I'm not your wife.
It's you.
I was wrong.
Will you please forgive me?
Jiang Yicheng,
get your dirty hands off me.
No!
You're disgusting.
Get away from me.
You're not allowed to push me away!
I was wrong.
Forgive me.
Lu Li,
please drive faster.
I can't take it anymore.
All right.
Darling, give me a hug.
(He drank so much just now. Will he...)
(I'll drink on her behalf.)
(Darling, I finally found you.)
(I was wrong.
Will you please forgive me?)
Why are you here?
Do you think I wish to sleep with you?
You were the one
who wanted to sleep with me.
You've tainted my reputation.
Where's Lu Li?
Of course she's at her own house.
What?
Don't tell me you want her to serve you?
It's your honour
to be served by a person like me.
Last night, you called me your darling
and you kept hugging me.
I was drunk.
One's true nature will be revealed
when they get drunk.
Speaking of which,
when did you get married?
Why didn't I hear about it at all?
Why did she dump you in the first place?
Did you cheat on her?
Or did she cheat on you?
Don't use your standard
to measure our relationship.
You should at least
reveal something to me.
You're making me very curious.
So, what kind of girl
can torture you in this way?
Do you have any pictures of her?
Let me have a look.
Are you kidding me?
Is this your wife?
Later, I'll follow you
to your company for an inspection.
Inspection?
Aren't you leaving?
I'm not leaving.
Is this the car you rented?
What? Do you have something to say?
I thought
you would rent an expensive car
which feeds on petrol.
I didn't expect you
to rent an electric car.
It's better for the environment.
Pardon me for my rudeness.
She's here.
Junior.
Mr. Jiang will fetch us today.
No thanks.
I'll take public transport.
I need to go to your company anyway.
And last night, you drove us back.
Precisely.
You don't need to stand on ceremony.
Get in the car.
Your seat belt.
What? Did the music offend you?
It's too noisy.
You have such a lousy personality.
It's no wonder your wife left you.
Fine.
I'll stop adding salt to your wound.
What's with the silver strip?
It looks so shabby.
I'll give you
a better accessory next time.
No need for that.
This is the only one of its kind.
Is this some kind of top-quality
product that I have never heard of?
My wife made this herself.
Why are you hanging all these
accessories on a car you rented?
I remember that you hate
these kinds of accessories in the past.
My wife loved them.
What's with you referring to her
in every sentence you speak?
So, what made her leave you
in the first place?
It's fine.
Junior, you'll keep this a secret, right?
She's asleep. You can tell me.
Lower your volume.
By the way,
I need to attend a meeting later.
I'll ask Gao Xi to bring you around.
I wish to know more about
your company's network management.
Why did you come to a film company
to know more about network management?
Maybe it's because I'm a programmer.
I think you two have
a common interest then.
Junior,
I'll leave him to you then.
Show him how amazing
our Network Department is.
All right.
See you.
Mr. Jiang,
is there anything
you would like to know?
I wish to know
how you're doing lately.
If there's nothing else,
I'll ask Director Gao
to take over from here.
Lu Li,
there's no need for you
to be this formal with me.
Mr. Jiang,
I'm afraid you found the wrong person.
I'm not responsible for
any of the company's projects.
Naturally, I have nothing to say to you.
You knew that I was not here
because of those projects.
If that's the case, there's no reason
for us to speak at all.
We need to have a chat.
When will you stop ignoring me?
Are you here to sign
the divorce agreement?
No.
If that's the case,
I have nothing to say to you.
Is our divorce the only thing
between us right now?
Aren't you curious
as to why I chose to stay here?
I don't care.
Mr. Jiang,
please excuse me.
I still have work to do.
You're different now.
Gao Xi,
did you see Lu Li?
No.
I'm looking for her as well.
Strange. Where did she go?
If you see her, tell her
to come to my office.
My computer broke down.
All right.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid that they'll
know about our relationship?
We're...
You better shut up
if you don't want me to quit.
Are you a dog?
Lu Li, did you see Mr. Jiang?
He's at the depository.
All right.
Mr. Lu was looking for you.
Got it.
Mr. Jiang,
Mr. Lu told me to attend to your needs.
Please tell me if you need anything.
I'm quite curious about something.
Last night, when we were having dinner,
I saw that Lu Li and Mr. Lu
were quite close to each other.
What kind of relationship do they have?
Mr. Jiang,
I'm just an employee.
I don't think it's suitable for me
to gossip about my boss.
Are you implying
that they have another relationship
with each other
besides being a boss and an employee?
I don't know the exact details.
I just know
that Mr. Lu brought her
into our company.
Many colleagues
saw them coming to work
and returning from work together.
And Lu Li
frequents Mr. Lu's office.
Lu Li may seem innocent,
but she's pretty devious.
I wonder what she did
to make Mr. Lu care so much about her.
Mr. Jiang,
Mr. Lu is your friend.
I think you should advise him
to be wary of her if possible.
Director Gao,
I heard that you're from Chongqing.
That's right.
Mr. Jiang, if you're interested in
exploring Chongqing,
I'm happy to be your tour guide.
I heard that there are ten must-eat
snacks when people visit Chongqing.
Please buy all of them for me
before lunch break.
Before lunch break?
I'm afraid I can't make it in time.
And some of them are hot dishes.
I'm afraid they'll be cold
when I bring them back.
I heard from Jingwen
that you're the most capable person
in his company.
Don't tell me you can't even
complete an easy task like this?
Mr. Jiang, if this is your wish,
I'll do my best to achieve it.
I'll go and buy them right now.
What kind of lousy computer is this?
It logged out instantly
when I just logged in.
My friends are waiting for me
to join their game.
Your computer wasn't designed
for gaming in the first place.
I'm done.
Miss Lu, you're amazing.
Why don't you take me in
as your disciple?
I only accept female students.
I decline.
Say, regarding the drivers...
What are you guys doing?
(Correcting the wrong codes
is much harder than writing new codes.)
(Just like a relationship,)
(it's tough to resolve
the misunderstandings between couples.)
(Instead of wasting our time on it,)
(it's better for us
to put down the past temporarily)
(and follow our heart.)
♪Tall and big,
you have a childish voice♪
♪Naive♪
♪Petty♪
♪Small and little,
I feel a little stressed around you♪
♪Afraid to go near♪
♪I hope to see you every morning♪
♪So that my day can be meaningful♪
♪Waiting to hear your voice every night♪
♪To break the silence of the night♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Sometimes you're a little stubborn♪
♪A bad temper♪
♪With a touch of jealousy♪
♪So I'll just have to coax you
and let you have your way♪
♪Hurry, hurry, go away rain♪
♪This song is for you,
the one I love the most♪
♪We'll walk down
the path of the future together♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Every time the phone rings,
I wish it were you♪
♪When I hear your voice♪
♪A smile grows on my face♪
♪Your words
are always a little childish♪
♪It makes me want to tease you♪
♪Sorry♪
♪Never mind♪
♪I love you♪