Arghhhhh !!
Hey !
Mintra.
Mintra !!
Korn ...
Uh ...
Acting like a heroine?
Hmm?
Arghhhh !
Win !!
Enough ..
But she started first, Korn.
Why you have to do like this?
Com'on, get up.
Double-faced.
Korn ...
Oh, it hurts!
Fibber !
What happened here?
Tell me, what happened?
Pawin ...
Pawin ?
What Pawin ?
She did it herself.
Don't you guys see?
Host too.
You don't have to look at me like that.
Win.
You have to see Miss Suzie.
Host.
Ehh.
Follow me!
Looks delicious right?
I made it for Korn.
What are you doing?
I'm asking what are you doing?
Well, I'm doing like what you did.
Ill mannered.
Tut!
Just like you bitch!
I'm asking what the hell are you doing?
What the heck is wrong?
Are you crazy? Huh?
I am a bullshit.
Oh ...
Looks so beautiful.
What the hell are you doing?
You wanna try me?
Hmm ..
Slap me ..
Com'on slap me !!
Go ahead.
Don't you want to slap me?
Why not ??
Are you insane?
Stop!
You out of your freaking mind?
Arghhhhhh !!
Are you hurt?
No, it's not.
Something else ...
Hurts me more.
Ouch!
You okay?
Bear it a little more.
It will get better soon.
What happened?
What have you done?
Done?
What have I done?
Win has done nothing yet.
Why would Win do that?
But if Win really did it.
Huh ..
She could be ended up worst than this.
You may haven't done this,
but something else,
don't you think that I wouldn't know.
You want something that is already occupied.
Once you get it ...
It will be a success on other people's sufferings.
And it was just a momentary happiness.
Don't make it any worse.
You may leave.
Get out !!
You've already known who he is.
But you chose to hide from me.
How can you do this?
I did what I should.
You did what you should?
I thought he's dead,
He's dead by me.
Do you know ?
I went to see him today.
How bad he is?
Worse than anything I've experienced in the past 7 years.
I ruined one's life.
Destroyed his future.
But you still do nothing ...
You are no different from those who seeks only benefits from me.
Do you still have a humanity?
A kid that act so dissolute like you.
How could you do anything?
If I didn't lend you a hand.
Will you still have your face to stand and complain me right now?
Oh!
Stop!
Stop all the fuss!
If you drink then you became a jerk like this.
No matter how much your value is.
I can cut you off instantly.
Go back to the House now.
No!
I'm an actor.
Not a slave.
What the hell are all these rules?
This is not a house.
This is a prison!
Whoever wants to stay, just stay.
But fucking not for me.
Heyyyy!
Report an emergency.
The car just crashed in front of the mall.
Please come quickly
Please go to the police station.
Please ...
At least ...
If I knew that he is still alive.
I can help him something ..
What will you do?
Look after him ?
Bow down?
Begging?
Apologize?
Say "I was wrong."... like that?
You still didn't know how to deal with your own life.
Do not show off with me.
Just do as I've managed.
Alas!
Get out now!
Why the heck you still here?
Or did you eavesdrop me?
Well ...
You just asked me to leave.
Didn't ask me to not listen.
Or ...
You got secret?
Gun
Are you okay?
You can talk to me if there's anything.
Bro !
Are you hurt?
It's okay.
Just leave.
But ..
But you ..
Stay out of my face ... Go !
I want to be alone.
I .. got it.
This house ... is
damn fucking fun.
How did you get into this room?
I just walked in.
Or I cannot enter this room?
Only me who can get into this room.
Miss Suzie
Hello ... sis'.
Never mind.
You are all here.
I've prepared some wine.
Shell we drink together?
You want some?
Don't you drink?
What exactly do you want?
I want to ruin everything.
Ruin people's lives?
You knew it all the time.
Why you keep hiding it to me all the time?
But this is one's life.
I destroyed his life.
Destroyed his family.
Why the heck you still here?
Or did you eavesdrop me?
You just asked me to leave.
Didn't ask me to not listen.
Or ...
You got secret?
Ruin people's lives.
I know your relation doesn't go well.
Would you make it better?
or make it worst?
Then you guys pack your things and get out from this house.
Good ...
Does it heal?
Umm.
Barely leave a mark.
I think ...
I got a very good care.
Now, our relation between 2 of us ...
is still the same?
What's done is done.
Don't you get it?
Then what you are doing right now? What is it supposed to mean.
I think I spoke clearly.
You're an idiot.
You see me as a sure thing.
When you eager to have me .. just come to have me.
Then throw away when you don't need me.
What kind of creature you see me as?
You thought that when you're not having me.
You could make it through?
Korn!
Is there anything wrong?
Yes, there is.
There is one thing I need you to correct.
The last one,
which is telling that ...
Me and Korn cannot be broke up.
I don't want to work with him anymore.
Am I look like playing like a child?
Rules are always the rules.
Start seeing each other, never breaking up.
They hired you.
Because of the imagined couple between you and Korn.
You think you could've came this far?
Being on your own.
If you don't want to renew, you don't have to ...
I do.
Glad that you renew the contract.
Oh!
Totally forgot.
There is a new job coming,
just for you alone.
Interested?
Contact me just a minute ago.
Yes, I do.
Arghhhhh!
Korn.
Should we go out for a walk?
There's a newly open Japanese restaurant.
No.
What's the matter with you?
Not in a good mood?
I think ...
We shoull ... stop our relation here.
Actually, I'm just a coward.
Without Mintra,
I'm just finding a new toy.
What I'm doing right now.
It's no difference from riding Mintra's wave to become popular.
But ...
I never think you're riding my wave at all.
Korn, bro.
You listen to me.
Well ...
I've liked you.
I know ...
You may not like me now.
But ...
We can be brothers, what do you think?
We ...
can go out, watch movies, do anything we could.
Right?
Don't you think so~ ... Pleaseee.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to think about this anymore.
Wait, Korn.
Korn, bro'.
Ohhh~
Eventually, you are leftover.
At least,
I have more dignity than a falling star like you.
Away from luring those mens.
Seeing the news recently would be great.
You will know who is
the falling star.
Hey.
Huh? .. What it is?
I've heard that Pawin,
turn himself in exchange with a leading actor.
What ?! Really?
About to fall.
What?
A falling star~.
What are you talking about?!
Pawin, are you a feminine actor P.?
who is a sugar baby who turns yourself for the investor.
In exchange for a leading role?
Turned myself in exchange?
Sugar baby?
What are you talking about?
Pawin!
Stop!
I told you to stop !
Why you have to stop me?
I need to beat this bitch once!
Sighhh.
I know that you are mad.
But hold your temper for now.
Miss Suzie wants to see you.
Sighhh.
Don't you care about your life anymore?
You think that the issue you're facing is a big deal?
It's your choice.
If you want to stay here.
You must manage yourself.
Hey ...
Did you forget something?
What is it?
Cuttt ..
Wayha.
I think you would be nervous.
Can we do it again?
Yes.
Sorry.
Okay .. slate, com'on, come.
F-Speed.
10/5 Cut 5 Take 2.
Marked.
Ready?
3 .. 2 .. and .. action.
Poy.
Did you forget something?
What is it?
Cuttt ..
Wayha!
I think it wasn't good at all.
It was not natural.
Can you do it more natural?
Yes.
Sighhh ..
I'm so sorry, director.
I think ..
Wayha could be anxious.
Because it is his first time in the shooting set.
Ummm ..
Give him a little break should be better.
May I speak to him?
Yeah?
Yes.
Okay, go ahead.
Thank you.
Wayha.
May I speak to you?
Okay .. touch up our cast .. com'on .. let's go.
Wayu.
Yes.
I didn't do well right?
Wasted everybody's time.
Wayu also wasted your time being friend with me.
Sighhh ..
Not at all.
I was also like this for my first time too.
But ..
I've tried so hard to study it from the computer.
Including watching series you gave me to watch.
At that moment,
I didn't feel that it is too difficult.
Hmm ..
As I act it myself ..
I don't know how to feel like.
When I do, it's not natural.
When kissing,
you have to feel it like this.
Well ..
Are you good now?
Umm ..
Let's break a leg.
Let's go!
Cut.
Bravo.
Well done Wayha.
It looked so real.
I was worried about you.
Thought you can't make it.
I'm relieved now.
Well done, well done.
Our House of Stars has yet founded for 9 years.
I sincerely thank you everyone,
for putting so much effort,
and keep following the rules.
Even if there's someone,
who broke the rules,
until he almost get kicked out ...
from the house.
Oww! .. Miss Suzie.
I knew that you've been through a lot of tough time.
I hope you guys enjoy yourself to the fullest.
Then .. let's continue our job tomorrow.
Cheers.
Take care these boys.
“ Every single tear that dropped, every pain I've beared ”
“ No one stands right here with me now. ”
“ Even if I have to betray, I'm willing to do. If it leads me to the goal. ”
“ Exchange with anything, I would give everything. If I could accomplish. ”
“ A realm that everybody's searching for, a radiant lights with a frosty look. ”
“ Millions of stars painted in the sky, I will go grab it. ”
“ Fall down and scramble up half my life, found everything I could've asked for. ”
“ The realm that build from tears. I will not let it slip away. ”
Pitch, are you drunk?
No.
Cheers~ / Not yet ..
Com'on !
It's all out.
I will go get one.
What took you so long?
Here Pitch ... you are such a bawler.
Let me.
Com'on ...
Hey!
Gun, why you have to snatch my glass?
Stop drinking.
No, I'm not, bro.
Don't you see?
Zo has passed out.
Ohh!
Such a wuss.
Let's go.
Get back to your room.
I'll take you there. / No, to where? I'm not going, Gun.
Miss Suzie told us to enjoy to the fullest.
So tonight, if I'm not finished, I'm not quit.
Korn, bro. Help me.
Korn.
Gun he will ..
Hey .. Wayu, which one you like?
Whatever.
Thank you.
Can I sit with you?
Com'on.
Cheers.
Well ..
Well?
I want to feel that way again.
That way?
Wanted to feel that way once again.
Wanted to memorize ... the memory.
I'm not sure that .. Wayha would feel the same?
But I wanted to kiss.
Well ..
We must have felt the same way then.
[INSANELY SCREAMING !]
What the heck is happening? Miss Suzie?!
Due to the crime scene,
has a high possibility that it was an accident.
Then we have to invite all of you guys,
to the police station for the interrogation.
The reason why your brother became like this, it's because of me.
I drove the car and hit your brother,
then Miss Suzie keep it in the dark.
About Miss Suzie .. you are suspecting too right?
that is was not an accident.