nice
But the foothills,
not only a few,
it's fulsome and
I want to report
and why are you there again
It's me again
And today I reported you
What do you want to report
You tell me
I also wanna try
You say it
Nanxing, you are busy with your business
I'll talk to her about this
Let's go out and talk
What?
Are you afraid that I report you for hiding your unethical behavior?
I hide my unethical behavior?
Okay, the director is here
You say it
How can I hide my unethical behavior?
She is a little third, shameless behavior
I hide the little third
Who is the little third?
Hua Xiaorong
You two divorced
You can't pour the dirty water on her head
Look
This is not a cover
You are Hua Xiaorong's
I am her ex-husband
You can find a normal man
She is looking for a rich husband
How do you know?
If you don't know, you can't do anything
Do you have evidence?
Of course I have evidence
Her mask is so ugly
I don't know
You can ask about her mask
Who gave her?
But I have to say it again
If you can talk to her
Let her share half of her income every month
I don't see her little third shameless behavior
We don't know about Hua Xiaorong
But the economic problem between you and Hua Xiaorong
Is to use the judgment of the court
Or the divorce agreement
Related to the relevant regulations of the property division
In addition
We have no reason to persuade her
Let her give you half of the income of the hair salon
But you can't use any reason to threaten her
Let her share half of her income, right?
How do you talk?
What is threat?
I see it
You are all in the same group
Ok
Wait for my ugly thing
I will let everyone know
I advise you
You should find a job seriously
Be independent
You are better than anything
Better
You can persuade yourself
What's the situation with Hua Xiaorong?
Yesterday, Du
Hid in the hair salon of Hua Xiaorong
I have no idea
I went to the salon in the middle of the night
To ask for money
What's wrong with the salon?
I really don't know about the salon
I sometimes go to the hair salon
But I can't go to a hair salon
And ask how the salon came
Yes
Or you can know it
Director
I am worried about you
According to what Hua Xiaorong said
Du, her ex-husband
Divorced because he liked gambling
I guess
He has no money these two days
So he went to the salon to make trouble
Ok
He Beibi
Come here
Hello
He Beibi is not here
Ok, call her when she comes back
Ok, bye
How great
levels sister
This is S GM
I am looking for you
What's wrong?
It's too troublesome
Take a look
Chen Qingqi
Box musketeer
Alma zmu
Yes, that's his house
The balcony on the second floor
was extended out
and installed on the door of the first floor.
How could it work?
How did it work?
That area
is the old residential area.
It's complicated.
When it was installed,
they didn't do any procedures.
They installed it secretly.
It's hard to let them demolish it now.
Right.
I think there's a son
in the Luo Man Man's family.
Right.
Well,
arrange it as soon as possible.
Have a meeting
at your judicial office.
When the legal review is over,
talk to the judicial office.
When you finally go to the judicial office,
you should do your job well.
Okay.
I got it.
I'm leaving.
Take care.
Sister Lan Xin.
You're back.
Did you find Zhou Hang?
We found the place where he lives.
It's the small house
that we rented with Mr. Liang.
Did Zhou Hang figure it out?
Sister Lan Xin,
you overestimate him.
What are you going to do?
I have a trick.
Look.
This is Zhu Li An.
It's possible that he's Zhou Hang's son-in-law.
The photos are so close.
It must be a different relationship.
This Zhu Li An
posted on Weibo
his intimate photos with Zhou Hang.
And he's still in the state of
not having a divorce with Zhou Hang.
Isn't he afraid that others will know
their relationship?
Is it possible that
he doesn't know
Zhou Hang's whereabouts?
It's possible.
But we can see it.
Liang Yin can't see it.
Doesn't he know Zhu Li An's existence?
You don't know
Liang Yin's obsession with Zhou Hang.
With his obsession,
even if he saw the photos on the train,
he might have another interpretation.
He won't think Zhou Hang is a ghost.
Sister Lan Xin.
Do we want to
tell this Zhu Li An
the real situation of Zhou Hang?
Of course.
Quiet.
At this time,
the British side
should be sleeping.
There's a time difference.
I think
he'll come back when he wakes up.
Hello, Li Kang.
What's up?
The doctor urged
Liang Yin to do the surgery as soon as possible.
Otherwise, it'll be troublesome.
But Zhou Hang doesn't answer the phone.
What should we do?
Don't worry.
We'll do our best
to find a way.
Liang Yin has been asking me
whether I should do the surgery.
I think
I should do it.
He's been asking me
when Zhou Hang will come to see him.
I don't know
how to answer him.
Don't worry.
If we can't
change Zhou Hang,
we can still rely on the law.
Okay.
I'll wait for your news.
Bei Bei.
Let's go to the hospital
to see Liang Yin.
If he's in the legal aid area,
we can also
ask him to apply for legal aid.
Dating has to be scripted.
Dubbing她
is dangerous for the Devil's
Did you record it?
the
All right.
Mr. Lin is so nice to us.
Is he still mad at me?
He's really mad at me.
He wants to divorce me.
Help me persuade him.
Don't worry.
We'll do our homework.
Then, have a good rest.
We'll come to see you in two days.
Okay.
I'll see him off.
He still has a little fantasy about Zhou Han.
He always thinks Zhou Han is angry.
Were they in a good relationship before?
Yan ma aircraft,
we're also afraid you'll become too kind.
They love each other in college.
They share a similar background in the original family.
That's why they can talk well with each other.
and sympathize with each other.
Understand and sympathize
are not equal to love.
Why don't you tell us
what they were like at the time?
Right.
It will also help us
convince Zhou Hang.
Okay.
From the third grade,
Zhou Hang often came to the dormitory
to find Liang Yin.
Other people's love
is always a surprise.
You are good at this.
You are always surprised.
Go away.
Shut your disgusting mouth.
I don't have anything
to say to you.
You don't know how to play the guitar.
You can learn to play the violin.
How can you be so stubborn?
Okay.
I want to see
when you find a boyfriend
and sing a love song for you downstairs.
At this age,
you are not as crazy as him.
Stop looking. Let's go eat.
Let's go.
Later,
they almost never part.
They did everything together.
At that time,
he was planning
his future with Zhou Hang.
Li Ke.
Wait for me.
What's wrong?
Take me back to the dormitory.
I'm running late.
You...
He used the time to work outside.
He went to work after class every day.
He will come back very late.
Liang Yin.
Li Ke.
You just came back.
You have an exam tomorrow.
Don't forget it.
I know.
I will definitely forget it.
I have to study.
Liang Yin used the money he earned from working as a junior worker
to rent a small house
with Zhou Hang.
At that time,
we were all very jealous
of the love and affection between them.
Zhou Hang was
banned from studying
because of his excellent grades.
Liang Yin also passed the test
with his own efforts.
When we
wanted to celebrate for him,
he suddenly told me
that he would give up studying.
You really decided that?
I can't do anything about it.
It's just that we are in a situation
where we can only
allow others to continue to do things.
Didn't his family
sponsor him when he went to school?
Why did he have to give up?
His family
is not equal to him.
He has long ignored his mother.
From the fourth grade,
his family completely broke his economic background.
So,
he earned money with you
just to earn his tuition.
Why didn't he go to work by himself?
He is a lazy person.
He also wanted to work.
I didn't give him a chance.
He is over you.
He can work
without his wife.
No.
Think about it.
As long as he can complete his studies,
study salt,
and then study
you don't have to worry.
We have made a deal.
As long as he can go to study,
we will get married first
and then he will go to study.
Before Zhou Hang went abroad,
they held a wedding.
First of all,
thank you for coming.
You are very kind.
You can come to my wedding
with Liang Yin.
I didn't know
if I was a sun-dressed man in my previous life.
I can hold hands with Liang Yin in this life.
I also know
I can't give you
a very rich life now.
But today,
I invite you all to come
to witness for us.
I promise
I will use my remaining life
to protect you,
make up for you,
and treat you well.
Good.
Cheers.
Come on.
Thank you all.
Liang Yin.
I know
marriage is a hard thing
for a girl.
You gave me everything you had.
But now,
I can only give you
such an unparalleled wedding.
Please believe me.
I will spend my life
with you.
This is my promise.
Your hands are stupid.
I
took off such a ring.
But I made it with my heart.
Liang Yin.
I forgot to put it on for you.
I'm willing to.
Oh my god.
This is so romantic.
What should I do?
Liang Yin.
This ring
is a promise
and a career.
I believe that
in the future,
I will buy you
a big ring just like this.
Again, I swear
that
I will be loyal to you.
For some girls
I think men are more happy when they are in a relationship
Sometimes when a girl comes out
I think you are not as good as a boy
But I think we are in this aspect
Although it's a big pressure
But I think girls have their own characteristics
We can be more patient
And we can be more passionate
The teaching is in front
But we also talk about friendship
So from the perspective of friendship
We say that friendship is limited
And we use the opposite to the base
The bottom is not dry and the bottom is not too thick
It's me again
I'm the one who took it off
Yes
It's good to have a hand to hold it
Then you can talk to him
Just like this
Ready to stand up
Look at him
He is so calm
You have to read it
Then he said OK
You can't just put it on your head because you are married
See, there is no violence