The first person to get a job
is Zhang Yubing
I'm really in no mood now
I must pay you back
I...
I can't let you
put the interviewer in the interview
I can't run either
Do you think so?
Sang Yu
He met
I'm a POA
POA?
We must find a way
to get them here in time
The first person to get a job
is Zhang Yubing
Morning, boss
Morning
You're in a good mood today
Okay
Morning, everyone
Morning
Beibei
How's your conversation with Shen Hao?
It's a bit long
Let's talk about it in the meeting room
I'll talk to you later
Okay
Let's go
So he officially
went to the People's Conduct Committee
to ask for a solution
for the problem of Shen Hao's mom
and her health
Shen Hao is really good
He will be staying there for a while
He also gave us a time
to find a way to get a job
That's right
Shen Hao's economic conditions
are indeed better than his brother and sister's
They just think
he's doing better
and want to give him to his mom
How can that be?
Is his brother and sister's economic situation
very bad?
I don't think so
People with bad luck
are all good
Even if you are your own new parents
you can't do anything for your daughter
and just throw away the package
We have to insist on
the behavior of bad luck
to happen in our eyes
We have to insist on
the behavior of bad luck
We have to say no
But
his brothers and sisters
are not good at making trouble
I guess our conditions
will be very difficult
What's so terrible about that?
We can't be sure
Shen Hao's family relationship
is more complicated
He said
his brothers and sisters
are all very difficult to deal with
So I think
we have to be very careful
about the conditions of these people
Otherwise
it will be very difficult
The parents of Shangyang
are the legal reasons for their children
If they don't travel
and are evil
they may be punished
But
they have to take the responsibility
If they pursue their behavior that day
they will be punished
There is a saying in China
called
if you don't tell the truth
if the old lady doesn't tell the truth
we still can't solve it
Shen Hao said the same thing
He said that
his parents will never
be able to solve their own children
I will talk to the director of the street
about this matter
If necessary
we can make a big team
with the street and the police
We must have the old people
to do as we please
Okay
I am the director of the police
Mr. Wang
Sister
Are you off work?
Why are you here?
We have dinner together
What's wrong?
Sister, go
We are in the police
Go, go, go
Let's have a chat
Boss
Chat
Did you find the street loan company?
Yes
Can you help the local flow?
Did you go with them?
I dare to
They will deduct it after I say it
I think so
I will go to see what's going on
and find their place after I spend a lot of money
The cousin is here
The cousin is here to pay the money
Go in and talk
Just talk here
Yes
The body is here to pay the money
How much do you owe them?
I don't know
Did you bring the money?
I want to
But you have to tell me
how much he owes you
I will go back to pay the money
You are always the cousin
How can you prove that you are his cousin?
Do I have to prove it?
I am here to pay the money
not to pay the debt
Do people from the same company
come here to pay the money for him?
We still have to verify your identity
You have to work in the bank
to earn money first
You agree, right?
Yes
Then you go find him
Don't do that
Do you want money?
Of course I do
Then tell me
how much he owes you
400,000
Do you have a balance?
Yes
The balance of the past
and the balance of the future
The money and the income of the country
are all together
400,000
They also said
they estimated the price of the fish-fish-fish-fish-fish
at the bottom of the oil
is about 500,000
If the fish-fish-fish-fish-fish-fish
can't pay the money in the deadline
they will be angry with him
But the fish-fish-fish-fish-fish-fish-fish-fish
said he only borrowed 200,000
Even if the interest rate is over 300,000
he will become 400,000 in no time
I am also a nambu
I went out to find him
What did he say?
He said he only borrowed 200,000
but later he couldn't pay the money
Those people forced him to write a new loan
Later he wrote it twice
and he took away Yuan Xian
It became 200,000
400,000
They are not putting the loan on the high-end loan
They are putting the loan on the law
Put the loan on the law
But from the first round
they are doing it without a doubt
You can't find the evidence
of them putting the loan on the high-end loan
Yuan Xian's loan has been destroyed
The current loan
is clearly black and white
400,000
They are the rulers of the legal system
The ruler of this thing
is still his girlfriend
If he didn't say he wanted to buy a house
and paid such a big loan to the nambu
how could he borrow the loan?
You have found this person
What kind of woman?
There are a few colors
I can't even see it
It's so dirty
I have to be very self-conscious
Are you crazy?
What do you think?
This woman
is not a part of the loan
for the nambu
This is hard to say
This is a legal control
It's impossible to do
Tian Yi Niu Feng in the procedure
We will take the opportunity
to find a way
to catch them and punish them
Eat two bowls
I don't want to eat
I have something else to eat
You eat
Eat two bowls
I don't want to eat
Qing Jia
That's all for today
Don't worry
Our daughter is here
We will treat her like a biological daughter
Don't worry
I don't worry
Let's go
Go back
May I ask Mr. Shen?
Yes
We are from Chengxin
I am Han Chou
This is He Bei
Hello
What do you want to see me for?
We can go in and talk
Okay, okay
Please
Li Li
Here
You are also very hard
It's really not easy to get a hot meal
It's not easy
Mr. Shen
I told you to buy tea
You always forget
Look
Don't worry
I am sorry
I will drink some white water
Thank you
Mr. Shen
Mrs. Shen
We are here
to ask for your opinion
about Mrs. Shen's mother
We are here today to ask
how you arrange
Mrs. Shen's life
Do you understand?
Yes, of course
Is there any discussion
between your children and women?
What kind of discussion?
To be precise
Mrs. Shen's nursing plan
It's like this
There is a plan
and discussed it
But
she has sent her mother to the old house
The old house
is now single
and the family conditions are good
It's not suitable
to take care of the old mother
The old house is young now
and has the ability
We are relieved
to have her nursing
Yes
You two said the old house is Shen Hao, right?
As far as I know
he has been abandoned since he was young
So he has nothing to do
with your mother now
You know it very well
Shen Hao
has been abandoned
But
my mother
is also his biological mother
She should be in the hospital
for nursing
After all
my mother
has given her life, right?
Have you discussed
the matter
that Shen Hao gave to her mother?
What's there to discuss?
Her life is given to her by her biological mother
Is it also the right thing
for her to take care of the old woman?
What else do you want to discuss?
So you
just send her to the door of the house
and leave
It's none of your business
Have you ever thought
if Shen Hao doesn't go home that day
then
shouldn't she
move in the cold
environment?
This is a big threat
to her mother
Have you ever thought about it?
No wonder
she and her sister did this
I went to see her
to see if she was okay
Yes
That day
Yu Li and other things
left first
I didn't expect
my two sisters
to be so rude
How could they leave first?
Okay
Let's talk about the political issue
Who's the mother
who lives in Shen Hao's house now?
But it's temporary
The obligation of raising her mother
is to be with you
and Shen Lan
This is a legal responsibility
You are the main reason
for raising her mother
Can you understand that?
Of course I understand
We are not fools
These years
we have always been
to bear the obligation
of raising her mother
We have never been to
find any trouble in Shen Hao
The current situation
is that
our situation
has changed
Just now
the wife you met
at the door
is our relative
The wife
is about to enter the house
You know
the conditions in our house
There are so many people
So
we thought of Shen Hao
Shen Hao
is my mother's
biological son
Now
he is the one who comes to raise her
It's not too much
Right?
To be honest
I can understand
what you mean
From now on
you don't care about
the mother
You only care about
Shen Hao, right?
We have already done it before
It's like a manager's gang
Now this gang
is in Shen Hao's hands
Exactly
Look
We ran 100 meters before
Now it's only 50 meters
No
Now it's probably
less than 50 meters
Why can't Shen Hao
keep running?
Shen Hao
takes care of her mother
She has to
do what she has to do
She has the moral and conscience
If you and your two sisters
don't do this
you have to bear the legal responsibility
What are you talking about?
Who told you to come?
At least my family
can use you
to say goodbye
Go, go, go
You are not welcome here
Li Li
Su Ke
You are not well
and you are so angry
Look at you
You have to bear the legal responsibility
to take care of her
Let's go
We are
getting angry
to fix the divorce
It's not a waste of money
Now
you know it
Let's go
She doesn't want to talk
So we
will provide some
legal services and legal materials
to the other party
What should we do next?
The public legal service
will give her
a way to
take care of her next step
and solve the problem
In the process
there are some legal problems
The Ministry of Justice
has also
called the Ministry of Justice
to call
to ask
If you don't feel comfortable
to call
you can go to
Siva County
The authorities
take extreme care of her
And she has
Got back at the estuary
I always checked a cart
I always got渗