[English subtitles are available.]
And The Winner Is Love
Episode 31
But sorry, grandpa.
I’m afraid I’ve disappointed you.
I’m not good enough
to live up to your expectations
But, grandpa,
I really couldn’t do that.
Sorry.
Every time I saw disappointment in your eyes,
I felt like dying inside.
Sorry, grandpa.
The Hall of Flames is now closed
and I’m the one to blame.
I’ve failed to keep our ancestors’ achievements.
Now
I can only bury you
in a hurry
at this remote place on mountain.
But I promise
I’ll coffin you father
properly one day.
Your Highness.
You’ve done all the talking?
Everything’s ready.
Only one last step to go.
This is important.
Please, Your Highness,
make your decision soon.
One step forward
and we’ll have no way back.
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
This trap
is too complex for them
to solve.
And Your Highness
will be the only key to the puzzle.
Let’s see if they
want this key.
Good.
Ask the Imperial Guards
to stand by
and get ready.
Yes.
[Sword Manor]
Master,
Master.
The Hall of Flames has been closed.
What happened?
I heard that
Chong Xuezhi and Muyuan
had failed to deliver the weapons in time.
Now they’ll be disposed by the military
and the Hall of Flames
is thus closed.
Where are they now?
The last time people saw them
was when they were taken to the execution ground.
Other disciples have been dismissed.
Now
no one knows where they are.
Master,
how can
the Hall of Flames end up like this?
They have been targeted by all sects for years,
yet managed to survive.
But now they are closed overnight.
There must be something behind this.
Is it because Chong Xuezhi
mastered the Nine Moves
and the government started to fear her?
We don’t know the reason yet.
For years, we’ve been the only ally
of the Hall of Flames.
Though we kept a low profile for some time
to avoid suspicion,
it’ll be improper for a respectable sect like us
to be an onlooker
when the Hall is facing such a fatal challenge.
Qingmei,
tell people
that the Sword Manor
is open to homeless disciples of the Hall.
If the Hall is closed for good,
other sects
will lose an equal match as a target.
Then we
will be in trouble too.
Yes.
Also,
there must be something behind
the shutdown of the Hall.
Go and
gather information around
to see if we can get something.
Remember,
keep a low profile.
Don’t let anyone notice you.
Yes, Master.
Please come in.
This is the place.
Look.
There are little trees around the yard.
It’ll be cool here in summer.
And this
is the kitchen.
Spacious enough.
This house
used to belong to my younger brother.
It’s been out of use for some time,
so it’s a bit messy here.
Small as the place is,
I think it’s perfect
for the two of you
to stay temporarily.
What do you think?
Much better than I expected.
Good.
If you like it,
then I’ll buy
this house.
This…is too much.
No.
Please use
the excess
to buy us some daily supplies
from the fairs around.
Ok.
I’m going now.
Xuezhi,
sorry for
letting you stay at a place like this.
Have a rest.
I’ll go check the yard.
Mister.
Chief Guardian,
how can I help you?
You know me?
The Hall of Flames is famous around here.
How can I not know you?
Who are you exactly?
Easy, Chief Guardian.
Don’t worry.
I’m just a local farmer.
I worked part-time in Peace County
during the slack seasons of farming.
I once
delivered weapons to the Hall.
That was
when I met you and Leader.
And that’s how I know you.
Is this really
your brother’s house?
It was my brother’s house indeed.
But his family
died of the flu years ago
when it went rampant.
I almost died too
when
the Hall of Flames
came to rescue.
Now you’re in trouble
and I’m paying you back.
I don’t really feel right
to take your money for this.
It’s really kind of you to say so.
The Hall could never sit by
when the flu was killing so many people.
We’ve done nothing serious.
Nothing serious?
Without
the Hall
and Master Shangguan,
I should be a ghost now.
You said you often
go to Peace County?
Did you hear anything
about the Hall of Flames
in the past few days?
After the Hall was closed,
the heroes from the Hall
were all dismissed.
I’ve heard nothing since then.
But I’ve been
keeping my eyes on this.
I’ll tell you
when I get something.
Thank you.
Lord Lu,
Master Shangguan is here.
Bring him in.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Tou,
Have you made progress
in go game lately?
Your Highness,
why don’t you just get to the point?
Shangguan Tou,
you should go with the flow,
not against it.
I’ve told you before.
You don’t want your pawns
to be cleared out completely
from the chess board, do you?
If Your Highness can let your obsession go,
I’ll quit the game at once.
That’s impossible.
I’ll get to
my destination.
Aren’t you worried that
I may reveal your agenda
to the whole world?
I would have been
if the Hall of Flames still existed
But now that
the Hall is gone,
there’s nothing I should fear.
I’ll make it clear.
Getting rid of the Hall of Flames
was one step to remove the obstacles.
Look at the world now.
We don’t need the world of martial arts.
Your Highness have spent much more than needed.
You could have sent your army
to kill all martial people.
That would be much simpler, right?
You’re right.
Just now I reported to His Majesty
that the Hall of Flames
had hidden imperial weapons
and worked with other sects for rebellion.
I’d help His Majesty
to repress the rebel forces.
You’re making up stories out of thin air.
The Imperial Advisor should know
more about making up stories
and covering things up.
Your Highness,
what has the Hall of Flames done wrong?
There are all trades of life in the world,
and they choose to practice martial arts.
That’s what they’ve done wrong.
People practice martial arts
only to help the government
to bring the evil to justice.
Why do you hate them so much?
That’s not their business to care about.
That’s
the government’s responsibility.
Let’s go back to Xiangzhou.
I, Shangguan Tou,
swear to the clear sky
that I will protect Xuezhi,
no matter how many difficulties
are lying ahead.
Whether she’s a leader or a fugitive.
Whether she’s with a righteous or an evil sect.
Whether
I can spend the rest of my life with her.
I’ll keep her safe anyway.
Please,
let me protect her.
Muyuan,
why are you staring at me?
Do I look
weird?
Of course not.
This is the first time
you’ve cooked for me.
I just feel happy.
Muyuan,
we’re living
a normal life as the ordinary people.
Look at you.
Chopping the firewood and boiling the water.
But that’s different.
Back at the Hall,
we didn’t lead an extravagant life,
but we had good food, nice clothes,
and basically everything we needed.
But now
you are reduced to staying here
in a desolate mountainous place with me,
having the simplest food.
I feel sorry.
Don’t be.
I like where I am now.
At least it’s much quieter here
than before.
Now
I don’t need to handle affairs of the Hall.
I won’t be annoyed
by the noises from weapon forging.
It’s a care-free life.
See?
It’s just been several days
and I’ve almost forgotten
the past.
But thinking about past,
I used to be
pathetically naïve.
How grandiloquent I was
to say things like
“I’m gonna see what the world has got.”
But now
the bygones have been bygone.
Muyuan,
do you remember
what I said?
I said,
if I was not the Leader of the Hall,
I would rather
be an ordinary girl.
Look at me.
I’ve
become an ordinary girl now,
saying ordinary stuff,
doing ordinary things,
and having an ordinary dream.
I remember how you always
complained about having no freedom
to do whatever you want
back at the Hall.
And now,
we are both free.
Let’s go hunting
after the lunch.
Good idea.
Are you saying
Lord Lu has started
to suppress all sects now?
That’s right.
If His Majesty approves his request,
the martial world will have a catastrophe.
What a tough move
Lord Lu has made!
Isn’t he afraid the sects may rise against them?
Father,
do we need to
tell all sects to get ready?
Tell them?
Tell what?
Tell them to run away or rebel?
That
would not help
Tou,
I need to write to His Majesty.
There you go.
Smells good.
Today
is the Dragon Boat Festival.
Let’s
celebrate this.
Well,
in the simplest way.
All we’ve got are wild vegetables and cheap wine.
You deserve better though.
I like wild vegetables.
Wild food with fragrant wine,
going well with the beautiful night.
That’s true.
I’ve been pondering
in the past few days.
I want to try my best
to gather our disciples
and rebuild the Hall of Flames
in the near future
when things get better.
I need to give you back
what your father has left to you.
Muyuan,
what my father has left to me
is not confined in the buildings at the Hall.
It is
in my heart,
in your heart,
and in the hearts of Chequ
and Zhusha.
It is in the hearts
of all the disciples of the Hall.
We will never be defeated.
What I want now
is that
no one will get hurt because of me.
And I have
nothing further to ask for.
Seriously
you want nothing more?
I know you.
You are saying this
to comfort me.
In fact,
you’re still very much haunted by the past,
and everything about the Hall.
Am I right?
I even promised to rebuild
the Hall of Flames for you
within 3 years.
Now that promise
sounds ridiculously impossible.
Muyuan,
you have done
enough for me.
Let’s just
enjoy the hermit life here
and forget about the past.
OK.
Then,
let the bygones be bygone.
Happy Dragon Boat Festival.
What’s this flower?
It’s hollyhock.
They bloom around the Dragon Boat Festival.
Legend has it that there was a man
who was obsessed with all kinds of flowers.
Once,
when he was sleeping at the garden,
in a trance,
a lady in black
led him to the fairyland,
where all gods were singing and dancing.
But then a wind came
and woke him up.
He realized
there was nothing around him
but a hollyhock
swaying in the wind.
He then stumbled onto the fact that
all those beautiful scenes
were nothing but an illusion.
This is an ominous flower.
Throw it away.
Why should I?
That’s just a legend.
Besides,
maybe when the man woke up
he’d be reminded of the beautiful things
whenever
he saw the hollyhock.
But illusions
is bubbles to be broken.
The more you enjoy the illusion,
the more disappointed you’ll be
when you wake up, right?
Muyuan,
what’s wrong with you today?
You’re being sentimental.
Let’s have dinner.
Eat.
Here.
Xuezhi,
just like the man
led to the fairyland,
every second here with you
is too beautiful to be true.
I don’t want the wind to come
and blow everything away.
Even if this is an illusion,
I want it
to last forever.
Time brings enormous changes to the world.
All I ask for
is but an ordinary moment
and you.
If you like it,
I’ll give you
a flower every day.
Tou,
if you still feel the same way,
then don’t let the hollyhock wither.
But if you don’t,
then just let the wind
blow it away.
Xuezhi.
Muyuan, I’m here.
What are you doing
at this time in the morning?
I’m looking for the hollyhock
I brought back yesterday.
But I just
can’t find it anyway.
Even if you find it,
it won’t be as it was
after a whole night of wind and rain.
We just can’t keep beautiful things,
can we?
It’s not like that.
It’s just…
we tend to miss them.
Everything will be gone, right?
I won’t.
Bracelet!
Did you make it?
Of course.
I asked the land lady
for some cords last night.
But I was not a dab hand at this.
It took me the whole night to finish it.
Let me put it on you.
I’ve never got a bracelet like this
ever since I grew up.
You know what?
From now on, I’ll give you a bracelet
every Dragon Boat Festival
and make you moon cakes
every Mid-Autumn Festival.
Long story short,
I’ll be with you
for every festival.
Thank you, Muyuan.
Don't thank me,
You’ve said this phrase enough
that I won’t forget it ever.
I don’t want your gratitude.
I just want you
to see me.
I’m going hunting.
Don’t
go with me today.
You won’t be able to kill any animals.
We’ll be eating wild vegetables tonight
if you come.
Then you go hunting,
and I’ll cook some nice dishes for you.
OK.
good
The Nine Moves deserves its reputation!
You just mastered the sixth move
and you can defeat enemies way outnumbering you.
How invincible you’ll be
when you reach the ninth!
So the legend is true
that a master of Nine Moves can rule the world.
Qingmei,
come here.
From tomorrow on,
I’ll be teaching you the seventh move.
But
you must know
that the seventh, eighth,
and ninth moves
are the toughest ones
among the Nine Moves.
Mr. Hong,
why is that?
The three moves
are basically the same.
If so, does that mean
I can master the three moves in one shot?
That’s not the case.
This is where the complexity lies.
One same move,
three different states.
If you don’t perceive them,
you won’t be able to master them.
That means
if I want to master the three moves,
I have to improve my comprehension.
Exactly.
Maybe
the tricks are written in the Lotus Sutra.
But don’t worry.
If you work hard,
with my guidance,
you’ll learn the last three moves anyway.
But
if I master the Nine Moves,
I will inevitably try to use them in fight.
That will cause me
a lot of troubles.
Nine Moves is the most powerful in the world.
Who will dare to rise against you then?
The Hall of Flames was shut down,
and Chong Xuezhi almost lost her life.
These terrible things happened
all because people feared the Nine Moves.
I’m worried that
if I keep practicing the Nine Moves, I will…
What’s that supposed to mean?
You’re afraid now?
You were the one who begged me
to teach you the Nine Moves.
Don’t you want to learn
the best martial art in the world?
Chong Xuezhi is no less competent than me.
But the Hall of Flames
was closed overnight.
You’re wrong.
The shutdown of the Hall of Flames
has nothing to do with the powerful art.
It’s all because the Nine Moves
was not under the government’s control.
Looking back
into the history,
most martial experts
worked for the powerful and wealthy.
But think about it,
if not so,
how many chances do they stand
to establish their reputation?
Chong Xuezhi
will be a perfect warning to you.
warning?
What do you mean?
You know the answer.
You mean,
I should work for the government?
Impossible.
This will be
betrayal to my sect.
Betrayal?
Xia Qingmei,
I’ve long seen you through.
You are a man
coming from a poor family.
You don’t want others to look down on you,
so you pushed yourself hard
and finally won the Hero Assembly.
What you want
is the approval by Lin Zongxing.
But
you are not satisfied by
by the Seven Techniques of Universe.
You want more powerful art
because you want to rule the martial world.
What do you mean?
It is good
to have aspirations.
With your ability,
you’ll start as a general at least
if you join the government’s army.
But if you stay here at the Sword Manor,
you’ll be a humble disciple your whole life,
treated casually
by Miss Lin.
That’s the life you want to live?
Xia Qingmei,
a wise man
needs to seize the opportunity
in adversity.
Please come here tomorrow.
I’ll find some work for you to do.
Let’s call it
a day now.
Please go home.
Go home.
See you tomorrow.
Mr. Manager.
Mr. Manager, please wait.
You must be
Guardian Chequ and Guardian Zhusha.
How are you doing?
We’ve come to see
if there’s any work we can do here.
Well…that won’t be an easy job for me.
Even if
we have vacancies,
I’m afraid we can’t turn to you.
What?
What do you mean?
The Hall of Flames has been closed.
No one
dares to hire you anymore.
Sir, Ma’am,
I have a family to support.
So please
don’t give me a hard time.
Did you see that?
We’ve done
so much for them in the past.
Now we are in trouble
and nobody comes to help?
People!
Zhusha.
Complaint is of no use.
We should find a solution.
Solution?
Where can I find a solution?
Dummy.
Hey,
if we had worked harder
for the Hall,
maybe the Hall
would not have been closed, right?
Sorry.
I should have worked harder.
That’s not what I mean.
Chequ?
Zhusha?
Mr. Xia?
Guardians.
Why are you here, Mr. Xia?
I heard that
the disciples of the Hall
have been dismissed.
So my master asked me
to inquire about the reason.
The reason is…
Why does Mr. Lin
want to know about this?
He thought there must be a reason behind.
He sent me here to figure it out
so that we can help the Hall out of this.
I see.
There is a reason behind
the shutdown of the Hall.
But we haven’t
found it out yet.
What’s your plan
for future then?
We don’t know.
We want to try our best
to do more things for the Leader.
What about this?
You two can
come and live in the Sword Manor.
What do you think?
Mr. Xia,
why…
We have been allies with the Hall
for years.
We should
lend a helping hand
when the Hall is in trouble.
This is a message from my master.
He asked me to gather
the dismissed disciples of the Hall
to the Manor.
Zhusha,
that might be a good way
to gather our disciples.
And this will help
when Leader wants to rebuild the Hall.
Indeed.
Mr. Xia,
we’re grateful for the generous help.
We’ll be responsible
for gathering the disciples.
OK.
Come to the Manor for me
if you need anything in the future.
Goodbye.
[BaicaoHerbs Pharmacy]
Master, please wait here.
Doctor,
what’s wrong with her?
She’s suffering from
depression.
Depression?
Something’s on her mind
that keeps upsetting her.
Will she recover?
She won’t
be able to recover completely.
But
some spleen and heart tonifying medicine
will keep her calm down.
And keep her from irritation.
Her illness will be alleviated then.
But tell her
not to be too emotional.
Otherwise
she’ll relapse.
Doctor,
is there any way
to help her recover completely?
That’s the furthest I can do for now.
I’m going to prescribe some medicine for her.
Thank you, doctor.
It’s been a long time since the last time
I saw such a tranquil night.
I can smell the fragrance of the soil in the air.
Is this
the idyllic life everyone’s craving for?
Exactly.
No worries.
Care-free.
Getting up for work at sunrise,
and going to bed at sunset.
Look, Xuezhi.
Fireflies!
Miss Chong,
you are as clear
as crystal.
I want you to keep it this way.
Don’t ever become worldly.
However dark the night is,
there will be light like the fireflies.
They are like the hope in the darkness.
Miss,
don’t ever lose hope.
Xuezhi.
This is for you.
What’s this?
Open it.
It’s beautiful.
Must be expensive.
Muyuan,
I don’t need such valuable jewelry
when we are in
a remote place like this.
I know you want to cheer me up.
You want me to be happy.
But
I don’t really need them.
Let’s exchange them for some food.
No.
When we were in the Hall,
I did buy you
some jewelry.
Those were but small gifts
that made your already good life even better.
But these eardrops are different.
They are
my betrothal gift to you.
Muyuan,
stop it.
Xuezhi,
listen to me.
The happiest time
in my life
was when we were kids.
All I thought about at that time
was exercise,
and exercise more.
After that,
all I wanted was to spend time with you.
Then one day,
I swore to the ancestors of the Hall of Flames
at the clan hall
that whatever it took,
I would keep you safe
for the rest of my life.
But then
I failed to keep this promise.
Do you want to be there with me
to fight for the revival
and the rise
of the Hall?
Muyuan…
Don’t rush.
Again,
take your time to think about this.
I won’t push you.
Tell me
when you have made your decision,
whatever it is.
Your Highness.
Yes.
These are blades forged by the Hall of Flames.
They do have
excellent techniques.
Pity
that they no longer exist.
Yes.
Send the box
to the Imperial Advisor’s Mansion
as a gift.
[Imperial Advisor’s Mansion]
His Majesty
rejected Lord Lu’s request.
His Majesty knows
that an arbitrary decision
will inevitably harm the innocent.
If the martial world
is ruled by one person,
the world will be in chaos.
The priority of the benevolent
is to do good things for the people
and eradicate the evil.
We can’t afford another case
like that of the Hall of Flames.
Lord Lu
is prudent enough.
He will make another plan
even if
he fails this time.
Father,
what do you think his plan will be?
Mr. Advisor,
several martial men are waiting outside
to see you.
What for?
They want to thank you for
upholding justice for the martial world.
They have got some gifts for you.
What?
Mr. Advisor,
I am with the Sword Manor.
I’ve come with the disciples of other sects
to express our gratitude.
It’s kind of you.
May I ask
how Mr. Lin’s wound on the shoulder is?
Mr. Lin’s wound on the shoulder is  much better.
Mr. Advisor, you came to rescue
when the government was about
to find fault with all sects.
You are our savior.
Our leaders sent us here
to present you with some gifts.
Hope you will like them.
Thank you for your kindness.
But I can’t
accept the gifts.
These are just some herbs
that carry our gratitude.
Nothing valuable.
Please keep them, Mr. Advisor.
Sir,
we’ve still got work to do.
Will you excuse us?
Stop.
My father has never spoken to anyone
about his words to His Majesty.
How did you know about that?
[Ganoderma]
What’s this?
Tell me.
Who sent you here?
Did you bring
the Imperial Guards here?
Sir!
Sir! Bad news.
Imperial Guards came with an imperial warrant.
Imperial Guards?
Father,
we’ve been set up.
Lord Lu didn’t just make a report.
What he really wanted is to set us up.
These are martyrs working for Lord Lu.
Now they’re dead,
but the blades are still here.
We won’t be able to escape from
the trap Lord Lu has set.
He’s really made up his mind
to kill me.
You can’t stay here.
Tou,
you must leave at once.
But, father…
Go hold the Imperial Guards back!
Yes.
Father,
I can’t leave.
The Imperial Guards will break in soon.
I need to stay to prove your innocence.
Lord Lu has set us up.
If you stay,
then
he’ll get what he wants.
Father,
let’s go together.
No way.
I am the Imperial Advisor.
If I leave at a time like this,
I’ll become a traitor.
And the Shangguan family will never
be able to undo the injustice.
Tou,
you have to leave
and stop Lord Lu.
But, father.
-I…
-Wuming.
Take him out of here right now!
Father.
Master.
I don’t want to leave you alone…
Leave.
Father.
Just leave.
Take care.