[English subtitles are available.]
And The Winner Is Love
Episode 1
Father.
[Leader of Hall of Flames Chong Ye]
Father. Why did you refuse to see me?
Were you avoiding me?
Did I do anything wrong?
I promise I won't do it again.
No.
I’d never avoid you.
Never.
You’re the best.
I hope I can always be with you
and watch you grow up.
Then you can spend more time with me.
Xuezhi,
remember what I told you in the Hall of Flames.
Take good care of yourself.
I’m afraid I can’t...
[Years Later]
[Hall of Flames]
Inside a cup,
there’s a whole world.
A tea leaf can decide its fate.
The sword shapes the world
while the tea nourishes it.
No sword, no achievement.
No tea, no wisdom.
Young Master,
once you're outside this gate,
you’ll be facing the unknown.
Young Mistress
are you ready?
[Young Master of Hall of Flames Chong Xuezhi]
I’m eager to challenge it.
Today is Young Master’s comeback day
and the time to leave for Dongdu
for the Hero Assembly as agreed in the pact.
Then
the Lotus Sutra and Nine Moves will reunite.
We’ll prove to the world
that Hall of Flames is not a cult.
[Elder in Chief of Hall of Flames Yuwen Zhongsong]
I, Chong Xuezhi, promise
[Chief Guardian of Hall of Flames Yuwen Muyuan]
that I’ll prove to all sects
at the Assembly
that Hall of Flames is legit
[Guardian of Hall of Flames Yuchi Huaheng]
and nonviolent.
[Guardian of Hall of Flames Liuli]
I’ll clear our name,
get father’s Nine Moves back
to complete the Lotus Wing
and restore our former glory.
[Guardian of Hall of Flames Haitang]
Hall of Flames has been quiet for five years.
[Guardian of Hall of Flames Zhusha]
All sects are eager to size us up.
[Guardian of Hall of Flames Chequ]
Young Master’s trip this time
won’t be safe.
When in danger,
you must make sure of Young Master’s safety.
No mistake are allowed.
We’ll do our utmost
to protect Young Master.
The owner of Lotus Wing will rule the world.
You’re going to the Assembly
with the Lotus Sutra.
Many will try to steal it.
You must keep it well.
Be very careful.
If it’s lost,
we’ll be...
I won't disappoint you.
Silver Whip School?
How dare you sneakily attack us!
That scum Chong Ye killed the innocent.
I, Chief Disciple of Silver Whip School,
Guan Peng, is here to eliminate the evil.
Hall of Flames has made a pact with all sects.
We’re only out to attend the Hero Assembly
with no ill intentions.
Feud in the past has already been resolved.
Resolved?
It’s only natural
for you to pay for your father’s debts.
Bah!
You’re here for the Lotus Sutra, aren’t you?
If you want it,
you can win it fair and square
at the Assembly.
You call yourself a decent sect
by ambushing us?
Go back and tell Wang Yinya
that Hall of Flames won’t offend others
but if someone dares to
harm our Young Master or steal the manual,
we will fight back.
Get lost!
Let’s go.
Is anybody hurt?
More dangers are awaiting us ahead.
Be extremely cautious.
Yes.
Stop.
Who are you?
Why are you in my way?
Whoever offends Hall of Flames
must die!
Hall of Flames! Kill him.
If…if you kill me…
[Leader of Moon Valley Shangguan Tou]
What happened?
Chief,
that man said
he was taking revenge for Hall of Flames.
[Chief of Silver Whip School Wang Yinya]
Hall of Flames?
Peng,
Don't worry.
I’ll avenge your death.
All disciples!
Pass my order!
Kill that witch Chong Xuezhi of Hall of Flames
at all costs!
Yes!
[Huashan Sect]
Are you ready?
Yes!
Mo,
how long has our Huashan Sect been in mourning?
[Feng Cheng's Son Feng Mo]
Father,
it's been five years.
Back then, that monster Chong Ye
killed your grandfather
and countless members of our sect,
including
your brothers,
and fathers.
That was a disgrace to our sect.
So
Hall of Flames must be destroyed
for the greater good!
Young Master,
this is the real world.
All sects have evil intentions
underneath their seemingly upright cover.
Wang Yinya used to be a bandit,
so
Silver Whip School doesn’t have a decent root.
Their members are mediocre in martial arts
but are skilled in ambush in the woods.
Let’s get out of here quickly
and take the main road.
Sure.
Young Master, Chief Guardian,
have some water.
Chequ,
Young Master must be tired, traveling on foot.
Hire a carriage.
We can
meet at Yunxi Inn ahead.
Yes.
[Yunxi Inn]
Excuse me.
Zhusha, time to eat.
Why are you standing here?
Zhusha said things she shouldn’t,
so Chief Guardian numbed her
and asked her to stand here
to teach her a lesson.
But she was speaking for me.
Good.
Food here is as good as ours at home.
Brother Muyuan,
eat up.
Liuli,
tell Zhusha to come in and eat with us.
Young Master,
rules can’t be broken.
Dig in.
Divine Spirit Temple.
Flag of Heaven.
Sedan carried by eight people.
Show off!
Divine Spirit Temple is strange.
That sedan is huge!
They have men carry it instead of horses.
Look at their disciples.
They're short and skinny
unlike other martial artists.
Divine Spirit Temple
is a notorious cult.
They're known for making poison
and killing others with it.
They're viperous.
Their leader Man Feiyue
is a woman whose disciples are all men.
She even tests poisons on them,
so she’s condemned by others.
They compare us
to that cult?
How ridiculous!
Carriage!
Chequ is back.
Stop the carriage.
Make a way.
Are you deaf?
Roads are built to park carriages.
Why should I make a way for you?
Cut the crap!
Didn’t you see the flag of our temple?
-Your temple
-Let’s go.
is an infamous cult.
Don’t you know that?
Nonsense!
Why am I told
ours is decent
while yours is a cult?
What are you doing?
How dare you hurt our people!
I’ll make you pay.
Young Master,
these lackeys aren’t worth your strength.
[Chief Disciple of Divine Spirit Temple Feng She]
Who’d know Young Master of Hall of Flames
turned out to be a pretty chick?
Why don't we
[Chief of Divine Spirit Temple Man Feiyue]
make friends?
I won’t be friends with cult members.
Young Master,
watch out. They may be after the manual.
Let's go back inside.
Don't move.
You want to steal the manual?
What a joke!
Give me the antidote
if you want to live.
Hurry.
Or it’ll be too late
to regret.
Fine.
I’ll give it to you.
Stop!
Young Master!
You guys stay to treat Zhusha.
Zhusha!
Paper!
Paper.
You’re awake, Miss.
Who is it?
Don't move.
The lime got into your eyes just now.
I applied ointment on you.
You’d better stay still.
Are you looking for this?
Who are you?
your savior.
Do you mean to harm me
or help me?
Do you think
I mean to help you
or harm you?
I don’t know.
Hey,
where’s Paper?
How is he?
If by Paper
you mean that white horse,
I’m afraid he's already dead.
Dead?
Sir,
can you please take me to him?
He grew up with me.
It was a gift from my father.
Too bad,
I’ve buried him.
buried
You care so much about him.
I don’t think you want him to be left there
and devoured by coyotes and crows.
Thank you, Sir.
Can you do me a favor?
What is it?
This is a whistling arrow.
Can you please fire it?
Once my family sees it, they’ll find me.
I’m willing to help
but you probably don’t know
we’re in a cave.
It's raining outside.
Even if the rain
didn’t damp your arrow,
the woods would block it.
Why don’t you wait till the rain stops?
What do you think?
Young Master and Chief Guardian
have left for so long.
Why aren’t they back yet?
Did something happen to them?
Let’s go find them.
No.
No one is allowed to leave.
Chief Guardian asked us to wait at the inn.
If we leave but don’t find them
and we get separated,
it’ll be more troublesome.
But it's already late.
Just stay and wait.
Sir,
what time is it?
About 9 pm.
Already?
Here. Have some water.
May I ask
where you're going next
so that I can repay you for your kindness later?
Repay me?
That’s unnecessary.
As for where I’m going,
I’m going to protect someone.
Protect someone?
That person
must mean a lot to you.
I’m not sure
what I should say to that.
By the way, Miss,
when speaking of Paper,
you were so concerned.
I assume there must be a special bond
between you two.
I've been into horses since I was little.
My father gave Paper to me as a gift.
My elder brother also has one.
Mine is called Paper.
His is called Ink.
We grew up
with them.
So our bond is tighter
than that of others.
You love your horse so much.
I’m sure you love your brother
even deeper.
Since I started to remember things,
we practiced martial arts and swords
and got yelled at together.
But after I grew up
and became...
Young Master,
don’t expose your identity to strangers easily.
We barely know each other.
You don’t need to tell me everything.
You should learn to
hide your identity in front of others.
Sir.
Sir?
Miss,
once the rain stops,
I'll fire the signal for you
Eat up.
Sir.
Sir?
Sir,
the rain is about to stop.
We should head back to Dongdu.
Young Master!
Brother Muyuan
Young Master,
I've been looking for you all night.
Are you alright?
Where’s your horse?
I’m glad you're fine. Let’s talk on the way.
Let’s go.
[Chief Disciple of Sword Manor Xia Qingmei]
Peach blossoms are so beautiful.
If Fengzi sees it, she will definitely be happy
Master.
[Leader of Sword Manor Lin Zongxing]
We're leaving for the Hero Assembly today.
I’m confident to win.
Master.
Your swordsmanship has improved significantly.
I couldn’t have come this far
without your teaching.
Rise.
This time, you’ll represent Sword Manor.
Remember to always speak and act cautiously.
I’ll engrave that in my mind
and stay away from all disputes.
You’ll be traveling
with Nine Moves of Lotus God.
Other sects are eager to get their hands on it.
You must stay alert.
Yes, Master.
I promise
it’ll arrive at the Assembly safely.
Good.
Nine Moves are Hall of Flames’ secret skills.
Whoever practices them will become invincible.
That set of skills used to
cause a bloodbath.
Hadn’t we guarded it,
the chaos wouldn't have stopped.
This Hero Assembly
will decide on the ownership of the manual.
Now that
the five-year pact has ended,
it should be returned to Hall of Flames.
But once they get it back,
panic will rise.
Master, you’re highly respected by all.
Our sect is known to be fair and just.
Qingmei, remember,
the upcoming competition is only a cover.
Pay attention to what’s going on behind it.
I understand.
[Dongdu]
Young Master,
I’ve asked Haitang and others
to wait for us at Tianbao Inn.
They should've been there by now.
Hadn’t I acted rashly and fallen into the trap,
Paper wouldn't have died,
you wouldn't have had to walk for so long
and our trip wouldn’t have been delayed.
Don’t beat yourself up.
Walking a few miles is nothing.
Let’s have something to eat.
Please enjoy.
Young Master,
you haven’t eaten anything for a night. Dig in.
Muyuan,
Dongdu is surprisingly bustling.
Indeed.
The outside world
isn’t as safe
as it seems.
You're new to it, Young Master.
Be extremely careful.
Don’t run away alone
like yesterday.
I won’t, Muyuan.
Hey,
stop calling me Young Master.
We aren’t in Hall of Flames anymore.
We're out now.
You can call me Xuezhi.
I’ll still call you Muyuan.
I can’t.
Why?
We used to call each other like that.
That was in the past.
Now it’s different.
I serve under you
as Chief Guardian.
How could I call you by your name?
It’s an order.
Young Master…
Muyuan, have a bun.
Thank you, Young Master.
Thank you, Xuezhi.
Good. That's right.
Sugar-coated haws!
Miss, buy a painting, please.
No.
I haven’t sold one all day.
I need money to buy medicine for my mother.
She is sick.
Please just buy one.
Please. I’m begging you.
Fine. I’ll buy it.
This is Abbess Ciren.
This is Feng Cheng of Huashan Sect.
Who’s this monk?
Leader of Moon Valley, Shangguan Tou,
Imperial Advisor’s son.
It’s also
the best-selling painting.
If he isn’t a monk,
why is he bald?
Rumor has it that he was a womanizer
and fell in love with her schoolmate,
so he shaved his head to prove himself.
Surprisingly,
many followed suit.
They all copied his style?
Were they insane?
It was true.
It's said that Mr. Shangguan
is more charming in person.
I doubt it.
I bet
the painter
made him look handsome deliberately.
Don’t you agree, Muyuan?
This gentleman is good-looking
and charismatic.
You two are a perfect match
and are meant to be.
Aren't you sweet?
Who’s this ugly shrew?
Leader of Hall of Flames, Chong Xuezhi.
She’s in charge of a cult
and is intimidating.
Did you ever see her?
How did you know her look?
I...I dare not see her in person.
They say she’s heartless.
Whoever saw her all died horribly.
I...
Xuezhi,
don’t take those rumors seriously.
I...
Excuse me,
how much is this painting?
Twenty coppers.
We’ll buy this one of Chong Xuezhi
as a souvenir.
Sure. Thanks. Thank you so much.
Well,
I don’t think it's that bad.
You aren’t the one in it.
It’s easy for you to say.
Paintings! Paintings!
How much is it?
Five coppers. Buy one get one free.
Five coppers?
Stop there!
-Xuezhi.
-Stop.
Xuezhi?
Fengzi.
It's me.
[Lin Zongxing’s Daughter Lin Fengzi]
Although we haven’t met for years,
I recognized you instantly.
You’re even prettier than before.
Fengzi.
How could you be friends with a witch?
[Leader of Swallow Sect Yuan Shuangshuang]
If others see this,
they’ll think we side with
Hall of Flames.
Who are you calling a witch?
Xuezhi, don't be mad.
My master means no harm.
Let me introduce her to you.
Leader of Swallow Sect, Yuan Shuangshuang.
Fengzi, just ignore her.
She sounds insolent.
How ungrateful!
Hadn’t it been for Sword Manor’s protection
five years ago,
Hall of Flames would’ve been long gone.
Master.
Does Leader of Swallow Sect
always talk to others like this?
Muyuan, let’s go.
Xuezhi…
What’s going on?
-Don’t know.
-Not sure.
Take care.
What happened?
Young Master, Chief Guardian,
you’re back.
I’m worried sick.
Who are they?
Shark Sect, Young Master.
Shark Sect?
Young Master,
those nobodies clearly underestimate us
by coming here to pick a fight.
[Owner of Tianbao Inn Mr. Qi]
Greetings, Chief Guardian Muyuan.
Mr. Qi,
I’m sorry
that we’ve caused you so much trouble.
Please forgive us.
That’s too kind of you.
[Tianbao Inn]
Tianbao Inn values money
as well as rules.
I've taken your deposit,
so I’ll guarantee you a comfortable stay.
I’ve long heard that Mr. Qi
although nonaligned,
is a man of his word.
Your reputation is indeed well-deserved.
I’m flattered.
Listen,
lead our guests to their rooms.
Prepare a banquet.
I’ll treat them later.
-Please.
-This way, please.
Xuezhi,
you didn’t sleep well last night.
You should go to bed early.
What?
What’s wrong?
Young Master, Young Master,
Chief Guardian just called you Xuezhi!
Was it true?
You heard it.
I told him to call me that.
Really?
That’s unfair.
We grew up with you.
Why can’t we?
Unfair?
Answer me,
who went after Man Feiyue for you?
You did, Young Master.
May I call you Xuezhi, too?
Fine. Then I’ll call you Sha.