[English subtitles are available.]
And The Winner Is Love
Episode 38
Since he won first prize in the Hero Assembly,
I appreciate him very much.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Welcome to our manor.
Fengzi and I will call on you to express gratitude.
Alright. Alright.
I've admired you.
In the future,
I have many things
to count on you.
Okay.
Your Highness.
I’m already a commoner.
He’s just an ordinary kungfu practitioner.
How can we afford Your Highness's favor?
Uncle.
Don't misunderstand me.
I came here this time
just to be close to you.
Since childhood,
I’ve thought kungfu practitioners are awesome,
let alone talented people
like Young Hero Xia.
I have yearned for kungfu since my childhood,
but because of my poor health,
I can’t practice it.
So even if I want to do something,
I have no strength.
Uncle, Sword Manor
enjoys high prestige in Wulin.
And all sects in Wulin follow your lead.
If you help me get what I want,
it will
get twice the result with half the effort.
All of you may leave.
Yes.
You mean that
you want me to help you
control Wulin.
You should say it like this.
You
and I
can make Wulin better.
Lord Lu is very modest
and cherishes talents.
He takes good care of people on the same side.
But he isn’t soft on
those disloyal to him.
Now Hall of Flames has been sealed up.
Mr. Lin.
You should
make arrangements for yourself.
Was Hall of Flames sealed up
because of you?
I just wanted to have a chat.
Why did you mention
these unrelated matters?
Yes.
Young Hero Xia.
I heard that in the Hero Assembly,
you were excellent and unrivaled.
But I didn't have a chance to see it.
If you don't mind,
can you
have a competition with my warrior
to feast my eyes?
Qingmei.
Since Lord Lu said so,
you can have a try.
Remember.
Stop at where it should.
You may leave.
Your Highness, please forgive him.
There is a winner or loser
in the competition.
But I hope
you
can fight with all your strength next time.
Well,
so,
I’m leaving.
Please think about
what I said just now.
If we are united,
we will
be ever successful.
Your Highness.
You just fought with Xia Qingyang.
What do you think of his kungfu?
Your Highness.
Although he uses ordinary moves,
he has strong inner strength,
far better than me.
Your Highness.
What do you want to do next?
Since he doesn't want to fight with my people,
I'll find another one to fight with him.
If a man who has a grudge against him
is in front of him,
he must
be able to fight with him.
Qingmei.
Just now,
Lord Lu obviously wanted to test your kungfu.
I don’t know his intention,
but you must remember
not to show your real strength.
Okay.
But
I think Lord Lu
might test me again.
We don’t need to worry about the competition.
In my opinion,
he came here this time
to send wedding gifts on the surface,
but in fact, he is forcing us with authority.
You heard what the adviser said just now.
I'm afraid he wanted to
warn us with Hall of Flames
and draw Sword Manor to serve him.
Serve him?
He is a prince.
Why is he suddenly so interested in Wulin?
Last time when we had a family dinner,
I found that he was quite interested in Wulin.
According to what he did today,
he has coveted Wulin for a long time.
Hall of Flames
has been removed by him.
Next one
will be Sword Manor, I’m afraid.
How do we deal with it?
I must stop him.
I will warn the whole Wulin
of his plot.
The Jianghu has been broken up for many years.
It's time to unite all sects.
But Qingmei,
I have to invite some unrelated persons
to attend your wedding.
Master, it doesn’t matter.
I’ll follow your arrangement.
[Sword Manor]
Take invitations and send them to all the sects.
Brother Xia. Brother Xia.
Be careful.
You must send invitations
to the chiefs of all the sects.
-Yes.
Let’s go.
Your Highness, as you expected,
Lin Zongxing
sent his disciples out
at midnight.
According to the spy,
they went to
Emei Sect,
Shangqing Sect and Luduan Temple respectively.
He intended to keep everything simple,
but now he wants to entertain guests.
So he has to send invitations in secret.
Lin Zongxing is careful.
He deliberately avoided Huashan Sect.
Since Uncle Lin didn't invite Chief Feng,
let's have him come here on his own.
I have to get them together.
Feng Mo
is indispensable.
Yes.
Your Highness.
What should we do next?
Lin Zongxing considers carefully.
The pressure I put on him in the daytime
has bothered him.
But he doesn't know
what my real intention is.
So he's just trying to woo people
to protect himself
He
helps me gather people from the Wulin,
I feel relieved.
The day when Sword Manor holds the wedding
is the day when Sects Alliance is established.
Has Chief Guardian come back?
Not yet.
Do you think
Chong Xuezhi
will die this time?
Yuwen Muyuan was eager for an antidote.
As the old saying goes,
care brings confusion.
Perhaps the fake antidote
has been taken by Chong Xuezhi.
It depends on her luck.
I hope Chief Guardian will come back soon.
I need him when I take actions
Have you met the commander of imperial guards?
I just visited him.
For the search of Imperial Advisor’s Mansion,
he handled it impartially and was rewarded.
He is very grateful to Your Highness.
He got a report
and enjoyed the fruits of others' work.
How could he not like it?
So when he heard that
he could return the favor,
he agreed.
Okay.
Let his people wait.
If the people I'm waiting for don't come,
his men
are just on standby.
You may leave.
Yes.
How can a common fellow
read the mind of a great man?
I put it here.
Here.
Wait.
I…
I put it here.
Are you sure?
Wait.
Take it back.
I’ll make a change.
Make a change.
A gentleman should not retract in a chess game.
Do you understand that?
But I am a girl.
I just got the news.
Lin Zongxing sent invitations
to chiefs of all sects
to gather at Sword Manor
on the fourth day of the next month.
It’s strange.
Uncle Lin never gets involved in affairs of Wulin.
He even sent Chief Disciple to participate in
the biennial Hero Assembly.
This time,
how could he
invite all sects in Wulin
to Sword Manor?
Xuezhi.
Do you remember
when Mr. Lin stood out last time?
Do you mean that the five-year agreement
Uncle Lin made
with all sects in Wulin
to protect Hall of Flames?
Right.
Sword Manor
is the largest sect in Wulin at present.
But Mr. Lin
keeps a low profile.
In Wulin,
he always remains neutral.
That's why all sects in Wulin trust him
and respect Sword Manor.
Except for
the five-year agreement he made for Hall of Flames,
Mr. Lin
has hardly interfered in affairs of Wulin.
This time,
in the name of Sword Manor,
he gathers all sects.
It must be a great event vital to Wulin.
I'm not as thorough as you think,
but I also think
Lin Zongxing's is very strange this time.
Tou.
Do you have any plans?
Xuezhi and I have a special identity.
Let's wait and see.
Tou.
It's vital to Wulin.
Do we really not participate?
Mr. Lin took great pains.
It must be Xue Lie who is forcing him.
You and I are Xue Lie's eyesore.
If we act rashly,
we may provoke him.
I'm afraid that Mr.Lin’s plan
will be in vain.
Let’s
just wait and see
and take no action.
When we have the exact information,
we will make a plan.
Okay.
But no matter what happens,
you can't hide it from me.
Let's face it together, okay?
I promise you.
Sister Hongxiu.
Xuezhi.
You don't taken medicine today, right?
[To Shangguan Tou]
They prepared it just now.
I'll ask her to take you to drink it, okay?
Tou.
You have to stay.
I have to calculate
your food, drink and accommodation fees
in Winehouse of Fairyland during this period.
I’ll follow your arrangement.
Xuezhi.
You go first. I'll be there later
Hongxiu.
What’s up?
[To Shangguan Tou]
This is a letter from Crown Prince of Dongdu.
Crown prince?
Chief Guardian.
I've been
concerned about you.
I, Yuwen Muyuan,
will pledge to follow Your highness.
Chief Guardian.
What’s the matter?
Please stand up.
Has
Master Chong been cured?
Chong Xuezhi doesn't need me anymore.
Or rather,
She never needed me.
Shangguan Tou is with her.
How could she see me?
Is
the antidote not working?
Shangguan Tou is with her all the time.
How could she take the antidote I gave her?
The antidote Your Highness gave me
was thrown away by me in a rage.
Please forgive me, Your Highness.
It doesn’t matter.
I gave it to you.
You can dispose of it at will.
I just feel sorry for you.
In the end,
you still failed.
Since she trampled on my love
again and again,
why should I care about her?
Just think about what I’ve done for her so many years,
I feel unworthy.
What’s your
next plan?
From now on,
in my mind,
there will be no more personal affection,
but
only Hall of Flames
and Your Highness’ Sects Alliance.
Guards.
Yuwen Muyuan,
in front of His Highness,
no weapons are allowed.
Your Highness, thank you.
I, Yuwen Muyuan,
will pledge to follow Your highness,
so will
Hall of Flames.
Step back.
Great Guardian, please stand up.
That's what a real man should do.
Instead of being trapped in love,
you should try your best
to achieve a great cause.
I
will do my best
to help Hall of Flames.
Thank you, Your Highness.
The Crown Prince said in the letter that
Imperial Advisor’s Mansion had been checked.
There is something
he wants to hand over to me personally.
So he invites me to go.
Do you trust him?
What's your plan?
At that time,
when my father was put in jail unjustly,
it was Crown Prince
who explained the situation to His Majesty.
So my sister and I were not involved in the case,
and survived.
I know very well that
His Highness's
invitation
is just a pretext.
He can't tell
the truth.
The thing that he can’t tell me
must be a tough one.
Tou.
You just rescued Xuezhi.
Lord Lu's business
has nothing to do with you.
Why do you get involved in it?
On my father's fiftieth birthday,
he taught me that
no matter whether I’d engage in politics or not,
we are subjects of His Majesty.
Loyalty, filial piety and righteousness
must be put first.
Now that you’ve made up your mind,
you have to think it carefully.
Don't act impulsively.
You can rest assured.
First,
Crown Prince is benevolent and virtuous.
He won't frame me.
Second,
in the Jianghu,
a storm is brewing.
If I keep avoiding,
I'm afraid that when Lord Lu is in power,
It’s impossible for me to acquire a peaceful end.
If I want to stay with Xuezhi forever,
I won’t allow him to do so.
I know
you've made up your mind.
It's no use persuading you.
I just want to tell you
to be careful.
Hongxiu.
After I leave,
I have to count on you
to take care of Xuezhi.
She has not yet fully recovered
and needs careful care.
You write down
all the fees.
When I come back,
I'll pay them in full.
Who asks you to pay?
Winehouse of Fairyland is huge.
Do I really mind if you
eat and live here?
You.
You promised Xuezhi
that you would never hide anything from her.
Did you forget that?
Even for selfish reasons,
I have to keep it
from her.
Alright, alright.
If you
love her less,
you won't be so selfish.
Sir.
For Yuwen Muyuan’s defection,
what do you think?
In my opinion,
we can trust him.
But after all, he is from the Jianghu.
We should be careful.
Chong Xuezhi is really lucky.
We failed to kill her this time.
Chong Xuezhi
will die sooner or later.
Your Highness, take your time.
We have got something this time.
Yuwen Muyuan
thinks no more of Chong Xuezhi.
It's not a waste
of my best poison.
Fortunately, the poison
wasn't found.
Otherwise,
it’s difficult for us to succeed.
I have passed Yuwen Muyuan’s test.
But he
hasn't passed my test yet.
I need to further test
his loyalty.
Xuezhi.
When I got back downtown
I realized how happy I was in the mountain.
The sun is covered pine trees.
Wine is made from plum blossoms.
But now…
From now on,
I can't be with you anymore.
What are you looking at me for?
You are quite pretty today.
So you mean
I was not pretty before?
Of course not.
You are pretty all the time.
In fact,
I seem to have yearned for
the days like this for a long time.
Now I finally have them.
I feel very happy.
We’ll have
a lot of them in the future.
Tou.
Now,
when I think back to
our first meeting,
I feel like…
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Xuezhi.
It’s not a dream.
It’s true.
We've gone through
so many twists and turns,
and finally stayed together.
In the future,
nothing
can separate us.
Well,
when I recover,
we'll go back to Moon Valley
to stay with Uncle,
brew tea, grow flowers,
and pay no attention to other affairs, okay?
Pay no attention to other affairs?
Okay.
I listen to you.
Xuezhi.
Forgive me for leaving without saying goodbye.
I'm going to Dongdu.
I'll be back in three days.
With this red line,
I am anxious to return.
Wait for me.
[Lord Xin’s Mansion]
Don’t worry about me.
I wonder
why Your Highness
wants to see me.
Mr. Shangguan.
I do have a request.
Because of Lord Lu?
Now I
really can't see through
him.
He came to Dongdu this time,
in the name of
sending wedding gifts
to Uncle Lin’s daughter.
As far as I know,
Uncle Lin never invited
any officials.
He came uninvited this time.
I really feel uneasy.
But
you know,
not long
after he came to Dongdu last time,
Imperial Advisor…
Your Highness, I know what you mean.
I feel the same as Your Highness.
This time Lord Lu
came here
not just for sending gifts.
I heard that
Mr. Lin
sent out invitations
to all sects to attend the wedding banquet.
If I guess correctly,
Lord Lu
will certainly attend.
This time,
I can go and find out something
for Your Highness,
so that Your Highness can rest assured.
Well,
thank you.
I can't attend in person.
In Wulin,
I don't have anyone to trust.
So I have to trouble you.
For my father's injustice,
Your Highness helped the Shangguan family a lot.
Now,
since Your Highness has entrusted me,
I
will never refuse.
I know
Lord Lu
wanted to kill you.
But you can rest assured.
Although I can’t attend in person,
I will protect you
in secret.
Your Highness
is also suspicious of Lord Lu.
In the past,
I would never believe that Lord Lu
would do a rebellious thing.
But
since your father…
I know
Imperial Advisor died unjustly,
but I can't find any evidence.
If this matter
is really related to him,
such cruel and meticulous scheming
makes me
shudder.
You have long been estranged from Lord Lu.
What Lord Lu thinks,
of course you don’t know.
I've been fond of him.
He is my brother.
I know that he is not in good health,
so I always hope that
he can read more historical books,
and may be put in an important position.
If Lord Lu
could understand Your Highness,
now
he would not go astray.
Seriously,
I still don't believe he did those wrong things.
In fact, Lord Lu
is already mature.
But Your Highness doesn't want to believe that.
In that case,
I'd like to
go to find out the truth for Your Highness.
On the wedding day at Sword Manor,
I will send someone to protect you secretly.
But my men won't show up
until they have to.
Otherwise,
I’m afraid someone will make an issue of it.
So
we’ll
take the cuckoo's call as a signal.
In case of any accident,
you can follow the call
to a safe place.
Your Highness, thanks for your protection.
Your Highness.
Lord Lu came to Dongdu this time.
Do you have any news about my sister?
I don’t know the details.
I only know that
Princess Lu
didn't come with him this time
That’s good.
She is safer
in Xiangzhou.
I'm really envious of
the relationship
between you and your sister.
My sister
is my only relative now.
As long as she is safe,
I am willing to bear everything for her.
Mr. Shangguan.
I'm counting on you.
Xuezhi.
What are you thinking?
Don't worry about him.
Hongxiu.
Tou said
he will come back in three days.
Tomorrow is the last day.
I'm really worried.
Silly girl.
Don't worry about him anymore.
Be at ease.
Perhaps,
he is on his way back now.
Xuezhi.
Hongxiu.
Today is the third day.
I'll meet Tou in person.
[Sword Manor]
Here comes the bride.
They looks good.
Perfect match.
The first bow is for the heaven and earth.
Make a bow.
The second for the parents.
The third for each other.
Make a bow.
Done.
Good, good.
Here comes Huashan Sect.
Is it him?
Congratulations, Mr. Lin.
Congratulations, Mr. Xia.
Is he here to make a mess?
Yes.
Sword Manor has a wedding.
Mr. Lin.
Why didn’t you invite Huashan Sect
to celebrate together?
Miss.
Don't take it off.
It's unlucky.
Qingmei.
Take Fengzi away.
Alright.
What’s happening?
They’re leaving?
Such a big day.
Mr. Lin.
Why do you have such a simple wedding?
I didn’t invite you to congratulate me today.
Chief Feng came here without invitation.
Good.
Both of us are in the Jianghu.
Since we can't avoid each other,
we'd better make it clear.
Mr. Lin, if you have anything,
just say it.
To be honest,
what I am talking about today
is related to Lord Lu.
Everybody,
Hall of Flames was destroyed suddenly.
Don't you think it's strange?
You mean
the event of Hall of Flames
has something to do with Lord Lu?
Priest Xingyi
You're slinging mud.
Lord Lu
is lenient.
He is not from the Jianghu.
How could he do such a thing?
Yes or no,
just have a test.
I guess Lord Lu will take actions soon.
His goal
is probably to
control the Wulin.
Mr. Lin, how do you want to test?
You have to state your stand before test.
If Lord Lu
does fight against the Wulin in the future,
whether against Sword Manor
or other sects,
will you
follow him?
Everybody.
Are you all confused?
Hall of Flames is a living example.
Now the Jianghu is in a state of flurry.
Without the care of Lord Lu,
I'm afraid it would have fallen apart.
It seems that Chief Feng
is determined to follow him.
If following Lord Lu
can benefit Wulin,
Huashan Sect
is willing to follow him.
Good.
Since Chief Feng has already made a statement,
I will…
Lord Lu is here.
Why is he here?
Yes.
-Your Highness.
Pay respects to Your Highness.
Chief Feng, don’t to be polite.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Here comes Hall of Flames.
Hall of Flames is also here?
What's going on here?
Yeah.
Why Hall of Flames is here?
Chief Guardian, please.
Mr. Lin.
Long time no see.
It’s you.
You rat.
Why are you here?
Chief Feng.
Now he is my respected guest.
In such an occasion,
how can he not come?
Am I right?
Your Highness has already sent gifts, right?
Why are you
here again today?
I’ve sent gifts,
but
I should also congratulate them in person.
It's a pity the ceremony has finished.
Your Highness made the trip in vain.
Never mind.
Now that the ceremony has finished,
I'll discuss another event
in your place.
But as a host,
I really don't deserve this.
I think
the wedding
is cold and cheerless.
A wedding
needs a lot of people to be lively.
Right?
Master.
There are many officers and men outside.
What should we do?
Uncle, what’s up?
Your Highness.
Let’s have a chat in the side hall.
What do you mean?
Uncle.
If you still don't understand me now,
we
may not be able to have a chat.
Your Highness.
Hall of Flames has been sealed up.
I just provide a shelter
for its disciples.
They are innocent.
Why do you press hard on them?
You know Hall of Flames is sealed up?
But by whom?
Me?
No.
It’s sealed up by His Majesty.
It’s sealed up according to laws.
I'm not disrespectful to His Majesty.
I just helped them
out of Jianghu morality.
What is Jianghu morality?
It's
a clear excuse for their lawlessness
Your Highness.
You did this
just to get
the support of Sword Manor?
Uncle.
You are a wise man.
You know best
why Imperial Advisor was convicted that day.
You can’t get involved
in the event of Hall of Flames.
It’s okay that you saved
the disciples of Hall of Flames.
But you leaked out information.
And the imperial guards got the information.
If in your manor,
you have a conflict with the imperial guards
and make a big trouble,
even if I want to help you,
I am powerless.
I’m not afraid of death.
I just want a clear conscience.
I know
you
have integrity
and are not afraid of death.
But you have to know
why you die.
If the disciples of Hall of Flames you saved know
someone in Sword Manor practices Nine Moves secretly,
got a lot of lawsuits,
and made Hall of Flames a scapegoat,
I wonder if they will still
appreciate your kindness.
Then Sword Manor
will lose its reputation.
Impossible.
My disciples are always strict with themselves.
They will never steal kungfu from other sects,
let alone the Nine Moves.
It seems you still don't know.
As far as I know,
The one who practices the Nine Moves
is your own Chief Disciple,
Xia Qingmei.
No.
He is now your son-in-law.
Nonsense.
If I'm talking nonsense, you can test him.
Now Chief Guardian is outside.
He can compete with Mr. Xia.
Then you’ll know the truth.
I'm here today
to congratulate you sincerely.
How could I hope my cousin
and her husband don't get along
as soon as she gets married?
What do you want?
Just say it.
It’s easy.
Today,
I brought Yuwen Muyuan here
to help you
deal with Hall of Flames.
As soon as you speak,
the imperial guards will retreat.
And I will not spread
the information about Mr. Xia.
Hall of Flames
will be taken over by Yuwen Muyuan.
Sword Manor
can escape unscathed
from the chaotic situation.
Why don't you do it?
Your Highness.
It seems that
I underestimated you.
You're not the only one
who underestimated me.
Mr. Lin, you stopped midway in your explanation.
I don't know what you are going to discuss
with your guests you invited to the Sword Manor.