[English subtitles are available.]
And The Winner Is Love
Episode 44
You’re right.
Did the killer
take these chiefs?
If that's the case,
Xue Lie
isn't just making an example of others.
There's something bigger going on
behind his moves.
Xia Qingmei!
Free me!
You!
Release me!
You rooted out my Sand Sect.
I won’t let you get away!
Isn’t that Leader Chong?
Shangguan Tou.
Lower your bows.
Leader!
It’s us.
Zhusha, Chequ?
Master Shangguan,
you…
you’re not…
It’s a long story.
What are you doing here?
We’re not alone.
They are all here.
We’re all here.
Leader Chong!
I never thought
I would meet you at here.
Haven’t I dismissed the disciples
after Hall of Flames were closed down?
What brings you here?
We know
that you did it for our sake.
You wanted us to stay away from the trouble
and live a peaceful life.
But Chequ and I
couldn’t just leave Hall of Flames.
So we planned
to settle down in Peace County
and then figure out a way.
Later, Xia Qingmei came to us,
saying that Sword Manor
would like to take us from Hall of Flames in.
So we gathered every one
we could find.
At present, some are hiding in Sword Manor,
the rest
come with us to find the missing disciples.
I don’t know
so many things have happened since then.
Leader Chong,
why are you
and Master Shangguan here?
And,
there are rumors
that Chief Guardian
has turned to Lord Lu?
Is it true?
Yuwen Muyuan
did turn to Xue Lie.
But,
last time when he came to Chequ and me,
-he…
-Wait.
You
met him?
When did you meet him?
It was
two days before Lin Fengzi’s wedding.
According to the date,
he has
turned to Lord Lu at that time.
But,
he told Chequ and me
that he would revive Hall of Flames.
He told you that?
Yes.
He
sent me away
and told Chequ in private.
Didn’t he?
He did say he’ll revive Hall of Flames.
Did he tell you anything else?
Did he tell you
how to revive Hall of Flames
or did he have a plan?
He never mentioned of a plan.
Nothing in particular?
Nothing.
I can’t believe
even the Chief Guardian betrayed Hall of Flames.
And he wounded Master Shangguan…
Gladly, you’re still alive.
I can’t expose my identity.
So please
keep it a secret for me.
Trust us.
By the way,
didn’t you settle down in Peace County?
What brings you to Mount Tianmushan?
Actually,
before Chief Guardian came to us,
we had planned to go back to Sword Manor.
He said he would revive Hall of Flames.
So we thought
we should gather all the disciples
and try
to find Nine Moves.
Have you found it?
Not yet.
We’ve been to so many places,
but found nothing.
Until recently,
several sects
were slaughtered by Nine Moves,
we predicted
that the murderer
must be the man who stole Nine Moves.
How did you find out
his next target
is the Purple Hawk Sect?
There’s a letter.
Do you know who sent it?
We don’t know if he’s a friend or a foe.
At least we know he and we
both want to stop the slaughter.
When we arrived at
Purple Hawk Sect headquarters,
they were all killed.
And then,
we met you.
Did you see the murderer’s face?
I saw that man’s back.
His back?
I didn’t see his face,
but he boasts his lightness of foot.
He jumped so swiftly
across the wall seizing Liang Henshui.
He must be much better than I am
in martial arts.
Of course he is.
You don’t say.
He’s grasped the ninth move of Nine Moves.
He’s not just better than you.
You’re a world of difference from him.
You misunderstand.
Nine Moves belongs to Hall of Flames.
But judging from his deft foot,
he isn’t one of us.
Instead, he’s like…
Like what?
Someone from Sword Manor.
Sword Manor?
How could anyone from Sword Manor
practice Nine Moves?
Has Uncle Lin turned to Xue Lie?
If Lin Zongxing has turned to Xue Lie,
that explains
why he picked Xue Lie’s side
on the wedding day
when Xue Lie announced the Sects Alliance.
But I don’t think it’s him.
When Xue Lie sent Imperial Guards to kill me,
Lin Zongxing tipped me to hold him hostage
so that I could get away.
If he turned to Xue Lie,
why would he help me?
I don’t believe it’s Uncle Lin, either.
As my uncle said,
Uncle Lin is a decent man.
Chequ,
I know you didn’t see his face.
What about his figure?
Do you think it’s Uncle Lin?
No, no, no.
He’s strong.
And he’s probably about my age.
He’s at your age
and boasts lightness of foot.
Only one meets the criteria
in Sword Manor.
Xia Qingmei.
Your Highness,
Liang Henshui has been locked in the dungeon.
Good job, Master Xia.
You’re my right-hand man.
In two days,
take him and He Qiliang
to the hunting field in the mountain.
The two of them
will complete the mission for me.
Yes.
Sugar-coated haws!
Tou, are you alright?
I’m fine.
After so many things happened lately,
there’s no time to grieve.
Take a look.
What is Fengzi doing here?
Sugar-coated haws!
Tou,
I’ll go meet her.
Go ahead.
She wouldn’t want to see me.
The jade is plain.
And there’s a crack on it.
I’ll give you two taels for it.
Sir,
would you please check it again?
My father gave it to me.
It’s made of prime jade.
How could you
give me only two taels?
Miss,
if you don’t like my offer,
please
inquire elsewhere.
All right.
Two taels it is.
We don’t want to pawn it anymore.
Xuezhi?
Fengzi,
I’ve learned
about the Tianling Stone from Tou.
Thank you for saving me.
The Tianling Stone
is of no use to me.
On the contrary,
it means responsibility.
It’s well applied
to save your life.
I’m so glad
to see you’re fine.
By the way, Xuezhi,
I’ve heard about
Master Shangguan’s death.
Don’t worry about me.
I’ve come through.
I should do something
to avenge Tou
other than
drown myself in pain.
Don’t do anything stupid.
The deceased can’t come back to life.
But you’ve got a life to live.
I’ll be fine.
I hope you will, too.
Fengzi,
are you married
to Xia Qingmei?
Great.
You’ve
always been the person he likes.
By the way,
why are you alone here?
Where is Xia Qingmei?
And
why did you go to the pawnshop?
Is everything alright in Sword Manor?
In fact,
Qingmei and I
have left Sword Manor.
Where do you live now?
In the suburb along the road
not far from here.
I see.
I have nothing to do now.
Why don’t I walk you back?
Fengzi,
you and Xia Qingmei
are living here?
Yes.
It’s not as comfortable as Sword Manor,
but I’m satisfied.
Have some tea.
Thanks.
Hey, Fengzi,
where is Xia Qingmei?
I don’t see him anywhere.
He hasn’t come back for weeks.
Well,
do you know where he is?
I don’t.
Maybe
he’s no command over himself.
What do you mean?
Did anything wrong
happen to Xia Qingmei?
Xuezhi,
actually,
I want to tell you something.
Hello, brother,
an uncle asks me to give it to you.
An uncle?
[Shangqing Sect is in danger]
Fengzi,
I know
Xia Qingmei is practicing
Nine Moves.
You know?
Is that why
you and Xia Qingmei
left Sword Manor?
My father was furious about it.
They had a terrible argument
Qingmei swore he’d never go back to Sword Manor.
I had no choice but to move out with him.
Do you know whom he learned
the Nine Moves from?
I don’t know
the details.
But I overheard them mention it.
I think Qingmei
saved
the monk who stole Nine Moves.
He learned it from the monk.
So it’s true Hong Sheng didn’t die that year.
Where is he now?
He was killed by Qingmei.
Xuezhi,
this is also why I told you about it.
Qingmei is behaving
more and more erratically
I’m worried about him.
I didn’t think much at the beginning.
I thought he was unhappy
and grumpy
because he felt unfulfilled
and made no progress in practice
after we moved out.
But in recent days,
his temper has been getting worse and worse.
He often smashes things
and complains about headaches.
One day,
I was so worried
so I followed him
and I saw…
Xia Qingmei
practicing Nine Moves
without the help of the Lotus Sutra.
I’m afraid
he’s fallen in deviation.
Xuezhi,
before he does anything unforgivable,
Would you please teach him Lotus Sutra?
Fengzi,
I would like to teach him,
but I’m afraid he has
Made a huge mistake.
What do you mean?
In the last month,
four sects
in the martial arts world
have been slaughtered.
And they all died of the ninth move
of Nine Moves.
I’m afraid
Xia Qingmei killed them all.
how can it be
Qingmei would never do that.
Qingmei is…
Xuezhi,
did you
come to Xiangzhou
to look for him?
Did you come to kill him?
Xuezhi,
I beg you.
Please don’t kill Qingmei.
-Fengzi.
-I beg you. Don’t kill Qingmei!
Get up. I won’t kill him.
I beg you.
Promise me, or I won’t get up.
I promise you. I won’t kill him.
Come on.
Get up. Come on.
I promise. Get up.
I promise.
But Fengzi,
do you know
why Xia Qingmei killed those men?
I don’t.
All I know is Qingmei
is working for Lord Lu.
As for what he’s done for him,
I have no idea.
So it is Xue Lie.
Xue Lie,
what do you want?
Rude man!
How dare
you common men address Lord Lu by his name?
They’re my guests.
Xue Lie,
I know you slaughtered the small sects
because we opposed to the Sects Alliance
you proposed in Sword Manor.
Now
you drag us here.
What do you want?
Either
you let us go,
or
you kill us.
Make a choice!
It’s possible for me
to set you free.
I doubt it.
Tell me.
What is the price?
I admire martial artists
and would like to take any chances
to behold all kinds of martial arts.
As you can see,
this is my private hunting field.
There is a way out at the bottom of the hill.
We’ll remove
your shackles.
If you can defeat my Warriors in Black
and make it to the exit
before the incense burns out,
I’ll let you go.
It’s quite a surprise
that the martial arts of the two sects
are so incredible.
I thought less of them before.
Your Highness,
I think it’s enough.
You can stop.
Yes.
Do you know when a man is desperate?
It’s when they believe…
Come on.
…there’s hope.
Go.
Fire.
Your Highness, they’re now in pieces.
What?
They’re now in pieces.
Say it again.
Did you hear it?
In pieces.
No matter how good you are,
even if you’re made of iron,
I can blow you into pieces.
Hey,
is Fengzi
alright?
I don’t know.
What did you talk about?
The man we’re looking for
is Xia Qingmei.
I was right.
He killed the leader of Shark Sect, Tie Xiao,
turned to Lord Lu
and silenced different voices for him.
So many lives
taken by him.
Many martial artists
are scared of Nine Moves
because of him.
He practiced Nine Moves
and killed innocent people
under cover.
While the world thinks you killed them.
You bear too much for him.
There’s no need to be tolerant.
It’s easier said than done.
He’s under Lord Lu’s protection
and he’s achieved the ninth move of the Nine Moves.
Though I’ve practiced Lotus Sutra,
he’s still more powerful than me.
Besides,
we don’t even know where he is
or where he’ll go.
Shangqing Sect is in danger?
I don’t know who sent it,
or if it’s a trap.
But,
maybe we can find some clues
from this note.
What if it’s true?
Look,
let’s go back and meet with Zhusha and Chequ.
Then we’ll head to Shangqing Sect.
Sure.
Your Highness,
the Warriors in Black spying on Chong Xuezhi
are back.
Any news?
Chong Xuezhi has been missing
since Lin Changran took her away.
But two days ago,
she was spotted
in Xia Qingmei’s home.
And
according to the scouts,
there was a young man with her
who looks a lot like
Shangguan Tou.
What?
Calm down, Your Highness.
They said like,
it may not be
Shangguan Tou.
Are you comforting me?
How many men
in this world do you think look like him?
It’s my fault.
I ask for your punishment.
Have they met Xia Qingmei?
Chong Xuezhi met
Lin Fengzi.
Women are all loose-tongued.
Chong Xuezhi must have learned from Lin Fengzi
that Xia Qingmei loses his mind
from time to time
because he’s practicing Nine Moves.
Xia Qingmei went to Yunlai Mountain.
Any news from him?
There will be soon.
Send Warriors in Black to Yunlai Mountain.
If they run into Chong Xuezhi and that man,
kill both of them.
Your Highness,
Xia Qingmei’s trip to Yunlai Mountain
is top secret.
Even Lin Fengzi doesn’t know.
How could
Chong Xuezhi know?
Sir,
just do as you’re told.
Yes.
Wait.
It’s about time
to honor my promise to Yuwen Muyuan
to let him take over Hall of Flames.
I want to see
if sects in the martial arts world
have learned the lesson or not
after the cleansing.
Send out invitations.
Tell them I require their presence
at Yuwen Muyuan’s induction.
Yes.
To what honor do I owe
the guardians’ visit?
Leader Lin, do you know about
the massacres in the martial arts world?
The Sand Sect and the Purple Hawk Sect
are both brutally slaughtered.
I heard rumors about it.
I guess it’s just the conflict
between minor sects.
You might have a point.
But it’s quite strange
that these sects
were all killed with Nine Moves.
Are you sure?
The Hall of Flames has nothing to do with it.
It originates from the Hall of Flames,
but even our leader cannot
reach the top level in such a short time.
However, the murderer has mastered
the ninth level of the Nine Moves.
Leader Lin,
this man not only mastered the supreme martial art,
but he uses it to scourge
the martial arts world.
The Hall of Flames
is his scapegoat.
I know what you’re trying to say.
This will come to light sooner or later.
The man you’re talking about
is likely Xia Qingmei.
Leader Lin, are you admitting
that Xia Qingmei practiced Nine Moves?
He was my disciple for ten years.
Yet I failed to see him through.
However, Lord Lu
sensed his ambition so clearly
and recruited him.
I failed in instructing him.
I was a poor master
and a sinner to the martial arts world.
Leader Lin,
This is not the time for remorse.
Xia Qingmei has achieved
the ninth level of the Nine Moves
and has become Xue Lie’s puppet.
Xue Lie has ordered him to kill
any disobedient minor sects.
Once he does that,
he slaughters the entire sect.
Leaving him unrestrained,
the decent and loyal men of martial arts world
will be all killed by him one day.
Though the fact that he has Lord Lu’s shelter,
Xia Qingmei
has been extremely cruel.
We think because he’s been using Nine Moves,
he is now at the stage of obsessive insanity.
Insanity?
I’m afraid that
even as we speak, he’s killing people.
Leader Lin, are you going to do nothing?
I give you my word.
Xia Qingmei was my disciple.
I’m responsible.
I’ll do everything in my power
to stop him.
Chief Guardian,
how much can the Black Fire
empower a man like me
who doesn’t
know any martial arts?
If I’m right,
the supreme martial arts in the world
is Nine Moves.
Do you think
it can defeat the Black Fire?
No.
If it cannot,
why do the martial artists
practice painstakingly each day?
We don’t practice
to pursue perfection in martial arts,
but to guide our will.
You think too highly
of those ruffians.
They’re nothing
but dumb animals.
They know nothing about will.
Chief Guardian,
don’t mind it.
I’m not referring to you.
I guess you know
how much I admire you.
Yes, I do.
You’ve been working for me for some time.
It’s time for me to honor
my promise to you.
You will assume the leadership of the Hall of Flames.
I have decided
to hold an induction ceremony for you
and invite guests from all sects
to be your witnesses.
From now on,
whether Chong Xuezhi is alive or dead,
the leader of Hall of Flames
can only be you, Yuwen Muyuan.
From now on,
the Hall of Flames is no longer
an evil sect shut down by the government,
but a decent sect with loyalty.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I’m thinking
to hold the induction ceremony
here at my mansion
to show you my sincerity.
What do you say?
It’s not simply
for my takeover
that you want it to be held here, right?
Uncle Lin.
Xuezhi.
Leader Lin.
Shangguan Tou?
As you can see, Leader Lin,
I’m safe and sound.
When I heard of your death,
I felt extremely guilty
Leader Lin,
you need not to worry.
In fact,
I appreciate your help that day.
It was my plan
to feign my death.
I fly low
to let Xue Lie’s guard down
and escape from his hunt.
By doing this, I can stop his next move.
Today,
we invite you here
to discuss one thing.
I’ve learned about what Qingmei has done.
Whatever he’s going to do next,
I’ll do my best to stop him.
I won’t draw back even if it means
the loss of my life.
We’re so grateful to you, Uncle Lin.
I heard news
that Xia Qingmei is likely
to go to Shangqing Sect.
It’s said
that Priest Xingyi and his disciples
are in secluded training at Yunlai Mountain.
Xia Qingmei is likely
to attack Yunlai Mountain.
If he succeeds,
Shangqing Sect
will probably be slaughtered, too.
What are we waiting for?
Let’s head out now.
Right.
It’s a great joy to talk to a smart man
like you.
It’s been days since my proposal
of Sects Alliance.
The rogues
have been eliminated one by one.
I think
it’s time to set the alliance up.
So Your Highness intends to take this chance
to announce its establishment
during my induction
when sects leaders will all be present.
Right.
Your Highness,
well,
I hate to steal your show.
Since Your Highness wants to announce it,
I’d like to assume the leader of Hall of Flames
in another day.
Otherwise,
I’m afraid I’d overshadow you.
Chief Guardian,
I just complimented you on your loyalty.
What?
Have you lost your wits?
Your Highness,
do you want me
to follow Lin Zongxing’s example
and be a puppet?
How dare you?
I’m an imperial lord.
It’s not proper for me
to summon martial artists.
When you came to me,
you shared my vision
to bring benefits to the martial arts world.
Now you’re going against your words.
Is that how you repay
my appreciation?
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I
will follow your order.
Chief Guardian,
I don’t want to hide behind you.
But in the martial arts world,
few men share the vision
we have.
If I come forward,
given my status,
there’ll be rumblings.
I just want to take
your induction as a chance
to do some pragmatic things.
I see.
Good.
If so,
I’d like you to run an errand to Huashan Sect.
Huashan Sect?
First, Feng Mo is dead.
Huashan Sect lost their leader.
I need an august man to discipline them.
Second,
Xiangzhou is small,
but it’s home to numerous talents.
Hall of Flames’ disciples
detained at Sword Manor
are waiting for you to take them home.
Yes, Your Highness.
Master Xia.
I knew Lord Lu would send men here,
but I never thought it’d be you.
Now that you do,
let’s cut the nonsense.
Answer me.
Are you in the Sects Alliance or not?
Supreme Lord, bless him.
Old Taoist!
You are
digging your own grave.
It seems you’re determined.
All right.
I’m in a mood to fight.
Let me send you to your maker!
Qingmei!
Master.
What are you doing here?
I know what you did.
I order you
to go back with me immediately.
Master.
It’s out of your hands.
Do you have any idea of what you’ve done?
When you left Sword Manor,
I thought it was just temper tantrum.
I never imagined you would do things so wrong!
Qingmei,
you’re still young.
Don’t make more mistakes.
Master.
Don’t come over!
If you still regard me as your master,
go back with me.
Don’t help the devil.
Have you forgotten the sect rules you learned
in the last decade?
I don’t understand
what’s so wrong about working for Lord Lu?
Isn’t it good to have a united world
with all sects in perfect order
and no more conflicts?
Master,
isn’t that your dream for decades?
No!
The martial arts world needs diversity,
not tyranny!
Not to mention unrestrained killing
in the name of Sects Alliance!
Qingmei,
have some sense.
Think about Fengzi.
Let’s go home.
No.
I’m not going back.
I have work to do.
When it’s done,
I can build my own sect.
By then,
you all will have to bow to me!
You have no sense of righteousness.
Even if you become a sect leader,
what would you do to win their trust?
Lin Zongxing,
you have no right to judge me.
I’ve learned all Nine Moves.
I’m the best in the world.
No one is strong enough to control me.
Even though you’ve learned Nine Moves,
you have no right to kill at will!
What you did
is against the rules of the martial arts world!
If you don’t stop now,
the whole world will jump at you!
In this world, the strongest is the king.
And the king
makes the rules.
I’m the best in the world.
Anyone who dares to get in my way
will have to die!
You’re not the best yet.
Chong Xuezhi?
You’re not
until you defeat me.
You’re not dead?
You lost to me years ago
in the Hero Assembly.
What gives you the courage
to challenge me?
I did lose to you
in the Hero Assembly.
But I’m no longer that person.
You stole my manual
and practiced it against all rules
You killed innocent men and framed it on us.
Today,
I’ll bring justice to you.
I’ll clear the false charges on Hall of Flames.
Lotus Wing is never an evil practice.
What’s evil is men’s heart, is you.
All right.
Then try your luck with me.
I don’t want to kill
in such a tranquil place.
Why don’t we
fight it out at the peak
of Yunlai Mountain?
Defeat me,
and you’ll have no rivals.
Then you’ll be the best in the world.
All right.
I’ll wait for you.
Xia Qingmei!
Thank you for taking a stand.
Your help is needed
and will be remembered by Shangqing Sect.
I’d like to give you a hand in the fight.
Thank you, Priest.
But it’s a fight
between him and me.
If you step in
and I win,
I’m afraid it couldn’t be called a fair fight.
Xuezhi,
you haven’t fully grasped Lotus Wing.
But Xia Qingmei has reached the ninth move.
I’m afraid
he’s too strong for you in fight.
You could lose your life.
Though Xia Qingmei has mastered
the ninth move of Nine Moves,
my Lotus Wing
joins Nine Moves and Lotus Sutra.
It’s the supreme martial arts of Hall of Flames.
I think
I’ll figure out a way to defeat him.
All right.
Xuezhi,
if the imbecile
refuses to give in,
kill him for me.
My uncle told me once
that vengeance has a way of rebounding back.
If I killed Xia Qingmei today,
I would
incur more hate in the future.
I hope
he can get it straight himself
and stop.
Xuezhi,
how sure are you?
You push your luck
each time when you know
your chances are slim.
I’m afraid
this is the only way
to stop him from massacring others.
Don’t worry.
I’m here by your side.
Tou, I know your concerns.
But this time, I need to face this on my own.
I used to escape and hesitate.
I used to make wrong decisions.
But it’s different this time.
As long as I try my best,
I won’t have regrets in the future
regardless of the result.
Lotus Wing is Hall of Flames’ secret manual.
It’s my father’s life work.
He even paid his life
for this manual.
And I carelessly lost it
to others who did harm to the world.
It all started with my carelessness.
I should end what I started.
So
only if I settle this chaos by myself
can I bring peace to my father’s soul.
Xuezhi!
Chong Xuezhi,
you lost.
It’s not the end.
Why do you think I should yield?
Do I have to kill you
to make you yield?
You can try kill me,
but I won’t yield.
If you don’t stop now,
everyone will leave you.
The strongest man
will have people’s support.
You’ve reached the ninth move of Nine Moves.
I bet you think you’re the strongest.
But ask yourself this.
Except Fengzi,
who else gives you their support?
I don’t need them!
I’m satisfied to be with Fengzi.
Compared with Fengzi,
I’m afraid your fragile ego and lust for power
are more important.