[English subtitles are available]
[Mr. Bad]
[Episode 22]
Are you still bothered
by what Ms. An said?
Times are different now.
She didn't really mean it.
She won't stop you from seeing me.
It is not about that.
So what's bothering you?
I am just wondering
how much you like Mao Xiaojun.
So many years have passed.
Why are you still
not moving on?
Are you jealous?
A little.
Anyway,
I didn't like him as much as I like you.
It is true.
Do you remember I told you
that he and I were close
because we grew up together?
Actually, we were
only close
when we were kids.
As we grew older,
he suddenly stopped
telling me what's on his mind.
Besides, he didn't seem to notice me.
I knocked.
I knocked again.
I knocked. But you didn't hear me.
Go out.
What are you doing?
Writing diary?
Go out.
I am just curious
what you are doing in the room all day.
Okay. I got it. I am leaving.
Mao Xiaojun.
Wait up.
[He was also like that]
[when we were in school.]
[He didn't let me talk to him.]
What a coincidence.
Why are you here?
I will say this one more time.
Next time when we are in school,
don't pretend that you know me.
And don't talk to me too.
I don't have to pretend that I know you.
I have known you for a long time.
After that,
he triggered my desire to win.
I thought
[maybe if I confessed my feelings,]
[he would start talking to me again.]
Mao Xiaojun.
What do you want?
I like...
Didn't I tell you to
go home by yourself?
Stop following me
or looking for me.
[Mao Xiao Jun]
I didn't say anything in the end.
Ms. An knows
how I feel.
She knows I am a bit slow
which is why she's always
purposely
creating opportunities for me.
Nan Xing, hurry up.
I am running late.
Don't forget your homework.
You are going out?
Nan Xing.
Aunt An.
You need to work overtime?
I am on night shift.
Then why don't you
let Nan Xing stay with us?
She won't get a good sleep
in the laboratory.
I can't trouble you like that
all the time.
It is no trouble at all.
I was actually thinking of
cooking more dishes tonight
and would like to ask you
to join us for dinner.
Thanks.
But we have eaten.
Then after making dinner,
I will ask Xiaojun to send you
some food for late-night supper.
Okay.
I still can eat.
Xiaojun needs to study.
You'd better not disturb him.
Don't say that.
You might not feel like eating
but Nan Xing does.
Right?
That was the day
the fire broke out at the laboratory.
My dad is still in there.
Nan Xing.
Are you okay?
My dad is still in there.
I'll go save your dad.
Mao Xiaojun.
Don't worry.
Wait here.
Uncle Nan.
Let's get out.
Dad. Dad!
Mao Xiaojun.
Mao Xiaojun!
He was so nice,
so smart
and so outstanding.
He could achieve
whatever he wanted to achieve.
Sometimes I even think that.
Except sports,
I am not good at anything.
Sometimes I think
he should be the one
to survive.
He might even be more outstanding
than my boss.
Besides, Ms. An
wouldn't be so sad.
It is just that he was
such a good person...
He was a good person.
But he died because of me.
He died in vain for someone
he hated so much.
He didn't hate you.
Actually, he had always liked you.
How is that possible?
If he was alive,
he would have woken up
out of anger at me.
He hated stupid people.
It is true.
Since returning from Hehuan Palace,
I had a dream about him.
Actually, those times
you thought he hated you
were just his way
of liking you.
How is that possible?
You don't even know him.
How could you dream of him?
Stop worrying about me.
After my work in the company
is all done,
I will ask my boss
for a two-day leave.
I will take a two-day break
to spend with you. How about that?
Alright. Let's go home.
Come on.
He was such a good person.
But he died because of me.
He died in vain for someone
he hated so much.
Sometimes I think
he should be the one
to survive.
The doctor said
this can only be solved
by the one who caused it.
But the people who can
untie the knot in my heart
are dead.
In exchange for your return
to save Nan Xing,
you have to complete a mission.
So this is the mission.
Can I ask you something?
What?
If the male lead in the novel
found that his beloved woman
is suffering
and he could help her
to untie the knot in her heart,
but the result of this
would be his disappearance
from this world.
If it were you, what would you do?
Heal her, of course.
But you would die.
I would do that too.
[The Falling of Gold Fish 2]
[Su Yu.]
[You are passionate about the world.]
[Chapter 1, The Smile of the Revenant]
[You should really embrace it,]
[travel every corner of it.]
[This is our last project.]
[You have sacrificed so much for me.]
[It is time to take a break.]
[I like you.]
[But I want to give you]
[real freedom.]
[Moreover, you should be]
[spending time on yourself.]
[Do something]
[that you really like.]
That sounds good.
If you have time,
you can
do something that you like.
You don't have to worry
about the company.
[Just go.]
[Do something you really like.]
How long are you planning to be here?
Boss,
are you trying to chase me away
with that tone of voice?
I am talking about your career.
Are you getting into making wonton?
Are you planning to take over my shop?
I...
I really don't understand
what the point of you
being highly educated is.
[Comments]
[One is not afraid of danger]
[while the other is worried
she will be in danger.]
[My heart melted.]
[It is so torturing.]
[Why did two people]
[who obviously love each other]
[push each other away?]
[Ma Leng is so inconsiderate]
[of Su Yu.]
[If it were me,]
[I might hesitate too.]
[Stop commenting
if you don't know the story.]
[Do you know how much]
[they have gone through?]
[They are already
the most important one]
[in each other's life.]
[Besides,]
[Ma Leng has matured because of Su Yu.]
[If two independent and different souls]
[want to be together,]
[they must sacrifice something.]
[As long as they love each other,]
[what can a little danger
change anything?]
[Xiao Wudi]
[Good morning. Did you sleep well?]
[Wait for me when you finish work today.]
[I will pick you up.]
[Good morning.]
[I just got up.]
[Did you sleep well?]
Come in.
Mr. Lu,
this is the contract
you wanted me to go through.
I have labelled all problems
on the licensing
of Gold Fish.
You seem to have
mastered this faster than me.
I picked up a good book.
By the way, Mr. Lu,
can I apply for leave
for the next two days?
I've checked our schedule
for this week.
We don't have
anything important going on.
I have arranged
to follow up on
the sales of Murdered
and have fixed your schedule.
I think you should just resign.
Mr. Lu,
I just want to
apply for leave.
I...
The company has a provision
for that.
You are a good assistant.
These two days,
I have been reading your pieces
and the readers' feedback.
I think you can't waste
your writing talent
on this position.
Hence, I got them
to prepare this yesterday.
After you sign it,
you will become
our full-time author.
This also means that
you must resign from your current post.
Can I really do this?
This is your personal matter.
You have to think it through yourself.
Take as much time as you want.
Mr. Lu, I have thought it through.
I will sign this.
So soon?
I believe that there are some things
that don't need too much thought.
I should trust my instinct.
I think you need to think it through.
I have thought it through.
Go out and think it through.
Calm yourself first.
I am very calm.
Go out.
I am not calm?
Why did he say I am not calm?
Am I not calm?
No.
You are so calm.
I knew it, right?
[Resignation Letter]
Right sleeve
goes on top of the left sleeve.
Good.
Lower the waist.
Xiong?
Give me a minute.
Continue practising on your own.
I will be right back.
Xiong, why are you here?
Aunt An,
I need to talk to you.
Just put them over there.
Here, give it to me.
Take a seat.
Aunt An, why don't we
go somewhere else?
Just talk here.
I need to practise later.
Well...
Xiong,
actually I know
why you are here.
I am not against
you and Nan Xing being together.
You don't see me asking
about your family, right?
When I asked you
the other day
about your future plan,
you said
you haven't thought about it.
That's why I am very worried.
What's going on with you two?
Is there something
you can't solve?
Aunt An,
actually, I am not
from this world.
I am a fictional character
of Nan Xing's novel,
Xiao Wudi.
Hence,
I can't stay in this world.
He is so cool.
Mum, when did you come home?
Right after I finished working.
This Xiao Wudi
is more charming than
your male lead, Lu Zichen.
I got it now.
You two must be
treating me like a three year old kid.
Right?
How can you expect me
to believe a story like this
that you have made up?
Aunt An.
So
how did you
come to this world?
I only realised yesterday
my mission
in this world.
Mission?
Actually,
I am here to heal Nan Xing.
This is my mission.
You mean her panic disorder?
Yes.
The doctor said her treatment back then
wasn't very successful.
But
this can only be solved
by the one who caused it.
Both her father
and my son
are dead.
Regarding that,
you must have got it wrong.
Actually, the one who caused it
has always been Nan Xing.
She is the one
who created the knot in her heart.
If she doesn't let something out,
she will never be able to untie the knot.
What do you want to do then?
I need your help.
Yes. Come in.
Other than
these few terms and conditions,
the rest are fine.
Thank you.
Feel free to contact me
if you have a problem.
Mr. Lu, are you looking for me?
I have approved your resignation.
You can focus on writing from now on.
Okay. Thank you, Mr. Lu.
Becoming an author
won't be as easy as being an assistant.
I have high expectations of the pieces.
Got it.
But...
I know.
I will leave
when the new assistant takes up her post.
You can deal with
the Human Resource Department then.
When you are on it, help me to find
if there is any suitable candidate.
Why don't you sit in
during the interview?
That's not necessary. I trust you.
I will send you
the remaining information
after I organise them
tomorrow.
Okay. We'll get going now.
-Alright.
-Bye.
Bye.
Why are you here?
I am here to celebrate Nan Xiaoxing
officially becoming a full-time author.
Didn't I tell you
I would be having dinner
with Miss Ye today?
I told you not to come over.
I know.
That's why I came to cut in.
I want to be the first person
to share your happiness.
I thought you would think
I am too impulsive.
How would I?
You have a talent.
Of course you have to use it.
Besides, when I think of
the fact that you don't need
to be Lu Zichen's
assistant,
I am all for it.
But with this change,
I will have a lot of work to do.
There will be a lot of stuff to hand over.
I won't have time to accompany you.
Don't worry.
I will find every opportunity
to accompany you.
Since you're going to
have dinner with Miss Ye,
I'll send you there.
After your dinner,
I'll go and pick you up.
Why are you so nice?
Of course. You just noticed it now?
Let's go.
Since I can't have dinner
with you tonight,
I'll treat you to a big meal
tomorrow night.
How about that?
Great.
Let me think
what Xiao Wudi likes to eat.
He told me
he must have at least 10 dishes
for breakfast.
Then, let's have dim sum for breakfast.
We can order egg tarts.
-[My time here]
-Shrimp dumpling.
[is running out.]
Stir-fried rice noodles with beef.
-[Whatever you do, I'll accompany you.]
-And chicken feet.
Here comes the food.
It is still piping hot.
This is a lot.
Nan Xing,
we don't have customers now.
Qing will eat with you.
Okay.
Here, mum.
We serve these here.
Try them out and give me some feedback.
Sure. Thanks, Mrs. Ye.
One more dish is on the way.
You may start eating first.
Okay.
Don't trouble yourself, Mrs. Ye.
Quick, eat while they are still hot.
Try these.
These are all from my mum.
Congratulations
on becoming an author,
Miss Nan Xing.
Don't tease me.
Actually, when I first
went for the job interview,
I only thought of
getting the job
so that I can
work with my idol.
I never thought
you would give me that opportunity.
It never even crossed my mind
that you would encourage me to write
and make me believe
that I can become an author.
This is all thanks to you.
Other than thanking me,
you should also thank yourself.
I was someone
who didn't have a dream.
But now I've found one.
My dream
is to become a good author.
It is a great blessing
to have a dream to work towards.
You must cherish this.
Keep it up.
How about you then?
What is your dream?
Set up a company,
get it listed,
earn a lot of money
or what?
Your dream must be great.
My dream
is to realise a dream
with a guy.
In that case,
do you no longer want to
realise that dream with him?
Actually, I was someone
who was very afraid of loss.
But now I think that
as long as two people are happy together,
face challenges together
and look forward to the future together,
even if it may not
be a happy ending,
at least
we won't regret it so much.
I think I am
less afraid of loss now.
Here comes the food.
You've prepared so much food for us.
Here.
What else do you want to eat?
Tell me.
I am good, Mrs. Ye.
This is a lot already.
Thanks, mum.
You two shall go ahead.
I will let you enjoy your food.
Okay. Thanks, Mrs. Ye.
You should try it.
Which one should I start with?
Fried tiny fish.
I've been eating this since I was little.
Have a try.
Does it taste good?
Now try this one.
Mr. Lu,
this Thursday, representatives
from the platform will be coming
to discuss about copyright.
I will need to check with you
about the content.
Remind me again.
Why do you need to be
reminded of such a thing?
Xiao Wudi, we are talking about work.
Your relationship looks stable.
What's wrong with you, Mr. Lu?
Falling in love
seems like a far-fetched thing for me.
But at least I am still rich.
Not so much these days,
it seems.
But I still have my talents.
You've improved so much.
You can crack a joke now.
Crack a joke?
You think I am cracking a joke?
You think I am not talented?
The last one is a joke.
That is quite funny.
Good.
I am looking for a place to stay.
When I find a suitable one,
I will move out.
Don't worry, Mr. Lu.
You don't need to rush it.
Really?
When are you moving out?
Xiao Wudi.
I am just showing my concern.
I don't want to be in the way
of your creative process.
Don't ever think that
becoming our author
is easy.
Alright, Mr. Lu. I got it.
I will go to bed now.
Okay.
Mr. Lu.
I had dinner
with Miss Ye just now.
I think she is
very concerned about you.
Do you want to find a time
to chat with her?
This is not the time yet.
I can only go near her
when I am no longer so childish.
But
what if she doesn't wait for you anymore?
If that's what she really wants,
she can make another choice.
But you can't.
Your only choice is me.
Got it.
I want to brush my teeth.
Carry on.
You seemed to have
a good chat with Nan Xing.
Yes.
She is now
officially an author.
I am happy for her.
True.
It's a pleasure indeed
when one is able
to do what one enjoys.
You should be doing so too.
[What about you then?]
[What is your dream?]
[My dream]
[is to realise a dream]
[with a guy.]
[Actually, I was someone]
[who was very afraid of loss.]
[But now I think that]
as long as two people are happy together,
face challenges together
and look forward to the future together,
even if it may not
be a happy ending,
at least
[we won't regret it so much.]
Mr. Lu,
are you ready?
The car is here.
Mr. Lu...
Are you so eager to go to work?
Of course.
Your breakfast.
It is only for you.
Don't share it with anyone.
Got it.
Before you go to work,
do you forget to do
something?
What?
Your lips look dry.
Why are you so clingy lately?
Am I?
Well,
perhaps I'm worried that
if I don't be clingy now,
I will lose my chance.
Don't talk nonsense.
The car is here.
Yes.
I'll get going now.
Okay.
Come home early.
Xiao Wudi.
Why didn't you catch
the love I gave you?
I dropped it.
I'm keeping it now.
♫ Slowly breaking down ♫
I will give you one too.
♫ Our process of knowing each other ♫
♫ Each sentence is carefully carved ♫
♫ How Encounter Chapter describes me? ♫
♫ When did you adore me? ♫
♫ Such an ordinary me ♫
♫ Walking between the lines ♫
♫ Aftertasting sweet clues ♫
I am leaving now. Bye.
♫ Guess who likes each other more ♫
Bye.
♫ If it wasn't for writing a novel ♫
♫ In case of memory errors ♫
♫ How should the lost be found? ♫
♫ Only love can be summarized in a word ♫
♫ Maybe a little insubstantial ♫
♫ Just entrust it with time ♫
♫ Word-by-word consideration ♫
Why aren't you letting her in yet?
Do you think she is
fit for the job?
Yes.
I think she is a very good fit.
When I look at her resume,
I just don't know what to ask.
Since she
sent in her resume,
let's just meet her first.
Can we
start the interview now?
Miss Ye,
why don't we just
get over with it now?
Miss Jiao.
Let me do this.
Miss Ye.
Miss Ye Qing.
The position you applied for
is the President's assistant.
May I know why you applied
for this position?
In our company, this is a position
with the highest turnover rate.
In our company,
the president's assistant
is a position
with the highest turnover rate.
Even if you fail,
it is no big deal.
It is because
I want to do
something I really like.
What do you
really like to do?
I treasure every book
that Mr. Lu has written.
Working with him
and growing with him
were once my biggest dream.
It has never changed.
This faith will support me
as I take on the job
and face bigger challenges.
Never abandon, never give up.
I have been taught as an athlete
to never give up until
I have achieved success.
Never abandon, never give up.
Good.
Welcome to X-Culture.
Thank you, interviewers.
I'll work hard.
Miss Ye,
it is so great to have you back.
Miss Ye.
Miss Nan Xing,
you've become so daring.
I have already resigned.
I can do what I want.
About Mr. Lu...
Don't tell him.
I will take her to his office.
Let's go.
Come in.
Mr. Lu,
I'll bring the newly recruited assistant
here to see you.
So soon?