I’m
back?
He’s back.
Beidao.
Hey, Miss.
Yes. You.
Come and do me a favor.
Coming.
You’re He Buzui, aren’t you?
I hear your family had a winery before
but it went out of business later.
I even hear that someone died
and trouble was stirred up at their house.
Nonsense.
Nobody died because of us.
My dad closed the winery
because I was ill and needed to be cured.
You’re ill?
Beat it. Stay away from me.
You carry germs.
Yes,
I’m ill.
I’m even infectious.
Don’t bully her again.
You can turn to me if you’re bullied again.
Class Eight, Senior Two.
Yi Beidao.
You’re back?
When did you get back?
Where are you now?
Boss,
if there is anything,
I’ll get back to sleep.
I had a sleepless last night
and now I’m too sleepy.
Get up.
Get up!
Make it clear.
What’s going on downstairs?
What?
The flavorings, snacks,
pots and pans, my fish
and that cat.
I couldn’t sleep last night.
Originally I wanted to chat with you
but you had been asleep
so I didn’t disturb you.
I bought those snacks.
You always have to work so hard
and stay up late. Surely you’ll be hungry.
We can eat them together.
It’s my treat.
But if you insist on reimbursing me,
I’ll not reject it
I’m still keeping the invoice.
I never eat junk food
and I don’t allow you to eat them.
Throw them all away.
Fine.
You know what?
I’m a good cook.
I was hungry last night
and made myself noodles.
If you’re worrying,
I can prepare a meal for you.
I’ve bought the flavorings, anyway.
You just need to
pay me for cooking.
I’m afraid I’ll be poisoned by you.
Sure,
it’s not weird for hateful people
like you to be poisoned.
What about the cat?
The cat?
Last night it kept pushing the door and meowing.
It was cold and hungry
so I took it home.
You pitied a stray cat.
What about the fish in my aquarium?
Why should they be eaten by a wild cat?
The cat ate your fish?
Do you have any evidence?
It’s a cat.
Do you have any common sense?
It’s the cat’s fault.
You can educate it.
I order you to get rid of it
within twenty-four hours.
Besides,
clean up
this mess
in your room.
Turn off the lights before you sleep.
I can do anything except that.
I can’t fall asleep without the lights on.
I’m afraid of darkness.
You’ll be afraid, too?
I thought you were the reincarnation of a superwoman.
It doesn’t matter if I can’t have a good rest.
If your sense of taste is affected,
that’s really bad.
The electricity bill will be deducted from your salaries.
The richer, the meaner.
You got a pimple.
I got lots of problems after I met you.
If you weren’t a fool,
I would think that you were sent by my dad.
How come I’m a fool?
You didn’t know you’re a fool.
That’s really confusing.
Such a bad temper.
If you don’t have pimples, no one should.
Clean these up and go downstairs.
Quickly.
Okay,
Pimple.
Clean up my house right now.
Finally there was a big move among sommeliers
who haven’t made the headlines for a long time.
The learned and famous sommelier,
Mu Chunfeng,
threw down the gauntlet to
the sommelier of genius, Lu Weixun, without any warning.
Lu Weixun hasn’t responded to it yet.
We’ll follow up this matter
and continuously report on it.
Now let’s ask for the fans’ opinion.
It doesn’t deserve to be talked about.
Mu Chunfeng just wants to be popular.
He’s stealing the spotlight
and we hate this behavior the most.
Do you think Lu Weixun will pick up the gauntlet?
You can never tell.
He’s an eccentric man.
Lu Weixun only signed contract
with our magazine.
If he wins,
that’s naturally favorable to us.
What if he loses?
Lu Weixun has absolute sense of taste.
Why should he be afraid?
He should confront directly
if he’s a man.
Lu Weixun won’t lose
but he doesn’t need to pick up the gauntlet either.
What does she mean, Zhuzhu?
What’s this?
-It looks...  -Put it down.
You’re not allowed to eat spicy food now.
But I like it.
Quit it.
Why?
Tyrant.
Miss He,
did I employ you to enjoy yourself?
We only have three chances to exchange our senses of taste
and I have plenty of work to do.
I need you to do all you can to cooperate with me.
You want me to be a plug-in of your sense of taste.
A plug-in?
You’re at best a container.
I think this matter...
I’ll make arrangements as quickly as possible.
You want to talk about Lu Weixun with me?
Yes.
I want your opinion.
My opinion?
I’m responsible for his drafts
but not for him.
I won’t know if he’ll accept
Mu Chunfeng’s challenge.
Lu Weixun has been in this profession for years
but he only writes a column for our magazine.
Currently,
you may be the only person who can talk him round
or handle him in the circles.
He has kicked out
five veteran editors before you.
In other words,
he always keeps a low profile.
This column
is his only contact with the circles
and probably
you’re his only friend.
I’m not too wrong by saying so, am I?
Friend?
Lu Weixun doesn’t have friends.
He can’t be friends with me either.
If you want me to persuade him into accepting the challenge,
that’s out of my reach.
Now taste them.
So many delicious things.
Which one should I eat first?
It’s good.
How does it taste?
Sweet.
Sweet?
What kind of sugar is it?
According to the degree of sweetness,
sugars alone
are divided into fructose,
glucose,
maltose
and sucrose.
Sucrose
is divided into light brown sugar,
dark brown sugar,
white sugar,
rock candy
and sugar lump.
Through a variety of processing, different materials
are made into different foods.
For example,
Swiss sugar,
fruit candy,
caramel,
peanut brittle,
sesame seed candy,
peppermint,
lollipop,
marshmallow, crisp candy and toffee.
There are so many kinds of candies already,
not to mention other complicated food.
There are no
absolute short cuts to master them.
You can only work hard and memorize them.
Today you’ll memorize the tastes of these candies.
Mr. Lu,
can we take a progressive approach?
If you want me to memorize all these tastes,
roughly I’ll need
one week.
That only shows that you’re stupid.
You must memorize them today.
But I need to do something tonight.
If I memorize all of them,
can I go out?
There’s no absolute freedom.
Freedom is bound up with restriction.
What do you mean?
Stay here until you memorize them.
Doctor Wine is ranked number one
in its industry
while Lu Weixun is a sommelier of genius
who has absolute sense of taste.
It’s collaboration between the strong.
Our status is indestructible.
If he takes up this challenge and wins,
that will be the icing on the cake.
But if he loses, that will be irremediable.
You always play it safe.
I really can’t figure out
why you want him to gamble with his reputation.
Will Lu Weixun lose?
I don’t dare to guarantee that he’ll win
but I’ll try not to let our magazine lose.
Mia
even if we won’t lose our status in the industry,
our magazine still needs the icing on the cake.
I’ll be careful.
Oh, my throat.
It’s not easy to be a container, isn’t it?
Are you going out?
Have you memorized them?
I’m starving.
I’ve been tasting them all day.
My brain, my throat and my stomach
are stuffed with sugar.
Your stomach works better than your brain.
Hunger will affect my judgement of taste.
I’m considering
for your sense of taste.
Don’t take in salt or wine
after ten at night.
Take a photo of yourself
and the food before you have dinner.
Mr. Lu, don’t worry.
Mr. Lu, see you around.
Mr. Lu, take care.
Kiku-Masamune sake
is made by putting brewed sake into barrels again
and taking it out when its texture is the best.
Therefore,
it combines the intrinsic flavor of Japanese sake
and the light scent peculiar to Yoshino firs.
Mr. Lu.
How careless I was.
I didn’t expect her to drink here.
I mustn’t let her detect anything.
It’s good.
Your comments
are especially concise this time.
Its taste is strong.
It deserves to be called Men’s booze.
Let me be straight with you.
I didn’t just come to give you booze.
Mu Chunfeng’s challenge...
If you came to persuade me
into accepting the challenge,
your treat will be in vain.
I’m not here to persuade you
but to tell you some information.
It’s up to you to decide whether you accept it or not.
I didn’t know except working,
my editor is also keen on gossiping.
Mr. Lu,
I don’t wish to be your friend.
But after so many years of cooperation,
I can’t show no emotion at this matter.
I hope you can patiently hear me out.
I won’t accept this challenge
whether you say it or not.
You must accept it.
These two
and a sashimi.
Okay.
-Thanks. -Wait a few minutes, please.
Thanks.
How are you doing?
Fairly well.
How about you, senior ?
Quite badly.
You’re still keeping that bottle?
Yes,
I’ve been keeping it.
I cherish
old times.
It’s been so many years.
Actually over the years,
I’ve always wanted to ask you a question.
Why didn’t you show up that day?
You disappeared
from then on.
Where have you been
in the past seven years?
On your birthday,
I had a car accident.
How about now?
Have you recovered?
I’m all right now.
I stayed at the hospital too long
and my mom fell ill when I left it.
In order to look after her,
I had no choice but drop out.
You should have at least told me.
I may be of help.
I've been looking for you.
I thought that...
You thought I was dead?
Afterwards,
I couldn’t tell you.
Why?
After I left the hospital,
I found that everything
had changed around me.
I was too young
to cope with those changes.
Instead, I was exhausted by them.
You must have had a hard time.
Yes, very hard.
Alright,
it’s all over now, anyway.
I’m back again.
I’m really glad to
see you again.
First,
from where the magazine stands,
I prefer that you accept the challenge.
If you don’t,
it’ll be a disadvantage to our work.
Second,
public opinion is turning against you.
Someone saw the odd thing about you in the magic show.
Plus lately you’ve been rarely on the screen.
Suspicion is spreading among the public.
If you don’t accept the challenge,
I’m afraid it’ll go rampant.
Third,
Mu Chunfeng is a newcomer
and his career is in ascent.
You’ve dominated the profession for years.
The others have wanted to replace you for long.
What do you think, Mr. Lu?
You said someone looked like me. Who’s he?
He?
He’s my boss.
Your boss.
When you’re complaining about him,
I feel like
you’re complaining about your boyfriend.
Who?
Lu Weixun?
How’s that possible?
You misunderstood.
Lu Weixun
is just a jinx.
Since I met him,
my life has become hard.
You simply can’t imagine it.
Although his IQ is like those of ordinary people,
his EQ is so low that it’ll make you furious.
He has eccentricities all over him
and he’s extremely irascible.
I bet his hairline will recede sooner or later.
Why are you here?
I’m wondering about that, too.
He Buzui.
Lamb Kidney.
What a coincidence.
They’re both your friends?
Who’s he?
What’s your relationship with him?
He’s my senior.
Please, don’t embarrass me.
He’s my boss,
Lu Weixun.
I don’t think anyone as my enemy
and I don’t wanna accept the challenge.
I hope you can reconsider it.
He Buzui.
This is my senior,
Yi Beidao.
This is my boss,
Lu Weixun.
Hello.
You look nothing like me.
What?
senior,
I’ll treat you again another day.
Let’s go back quickly.
I need to study.
What’s the rush?
We’ll sign a supplementary agreement at home.
What is it now?
Don’t date anyone before the contract expires.
I don’t allow you to
kiss.
Why?
We’re just working together.
I didn’t sell myself to you.
You don’t let me date anyone.
What if I’m left on the shelf?
I’ll take the responsibility.
Don’t think too much.
I’m not gonna marry you
but I can compensate you with money.
All you can see is money, isn’t it?
Can you buy love and youth with money?
There are so many things I want to do.
Why should I date someone?
You’ve never fallen for a girl, have you?
I’ll only fall for a bottle of nice wine.
Sure.
People like you
don’t deserve love at all.
Only blind and crazy girls
will be attracted by you.
Excuse me,
there are too many people who like me.
It’s easy for me
to be in a relationship
and it just depends on my wish.
Unlike you
you’re always thinking about
but you’re neither gentle nor caring.
Considering you face
and figure,
not a man will marry you.
You...
Excuse me,
you are harassing me
by following me.
Miss,
aren’t you flattering yourself?
This is the way to my home, too.
Okay,
go in front of me.
So now are you harassing me?
Taxi.
I’ll add another one.
Don’t walk alone without waiting for your boss.
You ought to work out.
You’re too weak.
The wind will blow you over.
I can beat ten people like you.
Does it work to run so fast?
Do you know the password?
Paper tiger.
Your sound control lamp is broken.
Fix it quickly
or your villa will lose face.
How come nothing has gone wrong
before you live here?
[Zhuzhu]
Hello, Zhuzhu.
Mi Ya,
let me tell you some gossip.
What time is it now?
You’re still in the mood for that?
Hear me out.
Today
I met a female fan
of Mu Chunfeng on Weibo.
She told me
actually Mu Chunfeng...
Really?
Okay, I’ve got it.
Thank you, Zhuzhu.
Sorry that I kept you waiting.
That’s alright.
Have a seat.
I just arrived here, too.
This place is close to my work.
But I asked to meet you
and gentlemen shouldn’t keep ladies waiting.
Have a try.
Thank you.
Verbena,
rosemary,
and chamomile.
They all have a sedative effect.
Miss Mi Ya,
have you suffered from stress recently?
Yes.
Facing a capable player
who told almost all of the ingredients
of a tea before he drank it,
I feel stressed.
You flatter me, Miss Mi Ya.
Unlike some people,
stumping others is not my style.
Is the tea not to your taste, Mr. Mu?
I hear you once studied in France
so I specially ordered its herb tea.
That’s kind of you, Miss Mi Ya.
Actually,
the quality of herb tea is much the same.
But if people
make it in different ways,
its texture will vary slightly.
I don’t get it.
What’s wrong with the tea I made?
It’s too rush.
Why?
High temperature
will destroy tannin and caffeine in tea leaves.
The texture will be much worse.
A box of fine tea leaves
and a pot of boiling water are there.
Could you really hang on, Mr. Mu?
Sure.
I don’t think so.
Last night...
You don’t need to thank me.
The pimple on your forehead is gonna burst.
I had experiences with pimples.
If you don’t deal with it,
there will be more soon.
There’s a convenient store there. Pull over.
I’m in a hurry.
I didn’t expect the perfectionist, Lu Weixun,
would allow pimples on his face.
Anyway, it’s not on my face.
Never mind.
Alright,
let’s change the subject for an easy one.
I hear you studied in France for a long time.
It provided you with
the first taste of red wine, didn’t it?
When I was a student,
I wanted to study to make wine, too.
According to your tone,
you didn’t realize your dream, did you?
That’s why
I particularly wanted to see you, Mr. Mu.
Why did you
give up studying in France, Miss Mi Ya?
You’re so outstanding.
No school would reject you.
It’s because of my family.
What a pity.
So I envy you
having that kind of chance.
Your family must have been very supportive.
Not really.
Then you must have
seized a special opportunity.
Your tea is cool.
Let me change it for another one.
Here you go.
Take it.
How should I use it?
Stick it on your pimple.
Left.
Right.
Higher.
Squat down.
That’s too low.
You asked me to squat down.
Okay.
Why are you laughing?
I still can’t believe that you got a pimple.
Did you secretly eat pig’s feet at night?
He Buzui,
you are courting death.
Hello, Mr. Lu.
What do you
think of Lu Weixun’s refusal to accept
Mu Chunfeng’s challenge?
To be honest,
Mu Chunfeng is a good lad.
If he wins this game,
I’ll consider letting him
manage Rose Winery.
I have faith in him.
-What’s your relation... -I don’t know him.
Are there holes in
the heads of those rich men?
Otherwise, why do they always
have those dumb ideas?
What holes?
It may be a pimple.
Let’s go.
That’s it for today.
The interview is over now.
-Go.  -We’ll talk again in the future,
okay?
Thank you.
Hello, Mr. Lu.
Hello.
What can I do for you?
Do you know the dope on Mu Chunfeng?
With my strength,
I don’t need to know that.
Take care of everything here.
The president wants to talk about the competition with me.
Okay, Chief Editor.
The actor hasn’t agreed to perform yet
but you’re putting up the stage already, aren’t you?
Do you know Mu Chunfeng’s
relationship with your father?
Their relationship is just about a winery.
Do you know
who’s the investor behind Mu Chunfeng?
There’s someone behind Mu Chunfeng?
Of course.
I just learned that today.
Tell us.
Don’t keep us in confuse.
Yes, tell us now.
The president of the Lu Group,
the boss of Rose Winery
and the dad of the wine expert, Lu Weixun.
You mean Lu Linong?
He’s challenging his own son.
Tell me about it.
Isn’t that exciting?
Lu Weixun is doomed to failure.
Mu Chunfeng and your dad...