Thank you for a nice stay.
You are welcome!
Thanks, Mr. Wan.
It’s my pleasure.
Hope you’ll come again.
Sure, we will.
Bye!
You are so early.
Mr. Wan, shall we go now?
We are so behind our schedule.
We have to go to the winery today.
The car is not big enough
to hold all of you.
Bai Jing, you stay here.
Why me?
If I get lost,
how are you gonna explain to my parents?
You stay here!
I can be your assistant!
She must go.
You…
You stay here.
You are the most useless one.
We don’t need you.
I’m useless?
I’m the assistant and bodyguard of Lu Weixun’s assistant!
I say, you are the most useless one!
Weixun, look!
How dare he talk to me like that?
Alright, stop.
Hao Yong, you stay.
Then let’s go.
Please watch the suitcases for us.
Don’t lose them!
You are really leaving me here alone?
Welcome! Welcome!
Welcome!
Mr. Yang!
Zeze!
They are
the people I mentioned to you.
This is Lu Weixun,
a well-known sommelier.
I’ve heard so much about you!
Zeze talks about you a lot.
I was.
This is his girlfriend.
Assistant.
He Buzui.
Good name!
He Buzui!
How catchy!
This is Yi Nanke,
owner of a popular bar.
Nice to meet you.
This is Bai Jing. She’s from France.
Miss Bai.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Welcome!
You are
all Zeze’s friends.
So you are my friends too.
Zeze already told me
why you are here.
But unfortunately,
we don’t produce Pear Blossom anymore.
What?
It’s been over a month.
How interesting!
Mr. Yang,
I remember last month you still asked me
to take some for my dad.
That was the last batch.
I know your dad likes to drink.
So I saved some for him.
Now I don’t have any.
It’s alright.
Since we are here already,
we’ll just take some other wine back.
Make the trip worth, right?
Right!
It’s the first time
they come visit this winery,
let’s show them around a little.
Sure!
Please come in!
Let’s go!
Come on.
This way.
This way! Over here!
Please follow me.
Our winery has many turns.
You’ll get lost easy.
Here, follow me.
Let me introduce.
Our winery
adopts ancestral brewing methods.
It’s
pure grain brewing,
no blending.
As the saying goes, “Good wine needs no bush,”
our winery never advertises
as people know how good our wine is
and always order
by a large number of bottles.
They usually save the wine for special occasions.
Although our winery is small
and has no advanced equipment,
our wine
has already been sold
on overseas market.
Come here.
These types of wine
are specially made by our winery.
This is bayberry wine.
This is plum wine.
This is yam wine.
And this is highland barley wine.
Please have a taste.
The flavor of the wine here is very rich.
The older the wine is, the better it tastes.
These types of wine are all about 10-20 years old.
Please try some.
The spirit tastes sharp
and strong.
I don’t know what’s good about it.
Mr. Yang.
The passage we just passed by,
what’s that for?
It’s a storage house,
for storing old equipment.
You can’t smoke here! Please don’t!
Beware of fire!
It’s a non-smoking area!
I’ll go somewhere else.
Let me
show you our workshop.
This way.
Mr. Yang.
I have to visit the girl’s room.
Just proceed without me.
I’ll be back soon!
Now, let’s go first.
This way.
Yi Nanke.
You think there’s something wrong too?
I think I smelled something familiar.
Let’s go.
This is the smell of Pear Blossom!
How is it?
Not bad huh?
Miss Bai.
You work for WSA,
which enjoys high international reputation.
Would you like to
introduce Chinese spirit culture
to the world?
We don’t know much about spirit.
We only focus on wine and Whiskey.
As long as you’d like to try.
I’m actually going to
start red wine business.
Of course,
not at here.
I need to go to the restroom.
You guys keep talking.
Try to hurry.
Zeze,
I’ve asked them to prepare lunch.
Let’s eat here today.
Okay.
We have enough wine here.
Drink as much as you want!
The smell comes out from inside.
But the door is locked.
There’s not even a window.
How are we supposed to get in?
Are you sure this is the place?
You are quite good at this!
Even have a tool.
All skills have pros and cons.
Bad people use them to do bad things.
Yet good people
use them to punish bad people.
That makes sense!
Don’t you have any safety awareness?
It’s dangerous
going in like this.
This room is locked up.
They must try to hide something.
I’ll go first, you stay behind.
That’s it!
It is Pear Blossom!
Judging from the wet ground,
the wine shouldn’t have been destroyed for long.
This Mr. Yang
must have something to do with the incident.
And he must be related to my father’s death!
I’ll go confront him!
Wait!
It might alert them.
If they really have something to do with Pear Blossom,
they must have already prepared for this.
Plus, these broken wine bottles
won’t prove Mr. Yang is guilty.
Without evidence,
even if we call the police,
they can’t arrest them.
So we’ll just wait?
He is obviously involved!
Yi Nanke,
take some pictures
as proof.
I’ll collect some wine
as samples.
Who is it?
Somebody locked the door!
Now,
step back.
It must be Mr. Yang!
He is definitely related to the whole thing!
Mr. Yang is
such a decent man.
Especially to his wife,
he’s very caring
and sweet!
About that,
people might think I’m henpecked,
but I think
it should be called compromise!
Love
- is compromise!  - Boss.
Zeze.
Please accompany Miss Bai to take a walk.
Excuse me for a while.
Okay.
I’ll see you later.
I don’t want to eat here.
Let’s go back.
It’ll be fine. Try it.
It’s not bad.
He Buzui!
- He Buzui!  - Lu Weixun!
It’s Lu wiexun!
Lu Weixun!
He Buzui!
We are in here!
Lu Weixun!
Is it you, Lu Weixun?
We are in here!
We found Pear Blossom!
The door is locked!
So Mr. Yang is really hiding something!
Stay calm!
I’ll try to break the lock and get you out!
Hold on!
Stop! It won’t work!
If only you were the one outside.
At least you know how to pick a lock!
If I were outside,
I might not be willing to help you!
It’s not the time!
Could you let it go?
Stop it!
Go hide yourself!
Mr. Yang must have known that we are here.
If you get caught too,
we’ll all be dead.
Okay!
Then I’ll go get Mr. Yang.
Hold on!
Wait for me!
He Buzui!
Be brave!
Why isn’t he back yet?
Weixun, I’ve been waiting.
what took you so long?
Where’s Mr. Yang?
He asked us to
have lunch here.
Crap!
What’s wrong?
Mr. Yang is up to no good!
What?
Why?
He might be involved in a murder!
Are you serious?
How come?
Mr. Yang wouldn’t do that!
They’ve collected evidence
about Pear Blossom.
I’ll call the police and let them
investigate Mr. Yang.
You guys leave first.
I’ll go find Mr. Yang.
No.
I won’t leave without you!
Bai Jing!
What? Let’s go together!
You go first!
Take her to go! Hurry!
- Why?  - Hurry!
Hurry up!
Weixun!
Right!
They are here for Pear Blossom.
Mr. Wan,
they were brought by your son Zeze.
And Zeze is with them too.
He must have no idea what’s going on.
He’s being used.
Don’t worry.
I’ll make sure he’s safe.
I’ve locked up those
who are looking for Pear Blossom.
Don’t worry.
That’s right.
Get rid of them?
Well…
Mr. Wan, is it necessary?
Mr. Wan,
they are all kids.
Can’t we just scare them off?
It’s not necessary.
You know
that I only want to make money.
We don’t have to do this.
Hello?
Some people got kidnapped in Joy Winery.
Who are you?
Move!
What?
What are you doing?
Move!
How are you related to Pear Blossom?
Who asked you to do this?
Pear Blossom?
What are you talking about?
I’m not sure I follow you!
Don’t play dumb!
I know
that you locked up my friends!
You’d better set them free now!
Otherwise you’ll face serious penalty!
Why are you accusing me of?
You don’t have any evidence! It’s a slander!
I should sue you!
Sue me?
You are the one wants to kill us!
Don’t you have family?
How could you do
a ruthless thing like this?
You want to sue me
because of
a few empty wine bottles?
Hello, Mr. Wan.
Listen,
if you don’t get rid of them now,
don’t blame me I didn’t warn you.
Well, Mr. Wan…
Yang!
What’s going on?
Honey?
How did you…
Mr. Wan! Mr. Wan!
Please don’t do this!
You can’t do this to me!
I haven’t seen your wife for a long time.
We’ll have a nice talk
and catch up.
Just finish your work
at hand,
then come to my house for a drink!
Mr. Wan! Mr. Wan!
I feel dizzy!
The air here is filled
with alcohol.
And there’s no window.
We’ll be suffocated if we stay here for too long.
And the floor is covered by alcohol,
we’ll be dead
if Yang throws in a lit match!
I don’t want to die!
I haven’t lived long enough!
I can’t die either!
I still have a lot to do.
Lu Weixun!
Where are you?
Are you okay?
- Come here and sit down…  - I’m fine!
Hypocrite!
Hypocrite?
Can’t you see
that I want to help?
He Buzui.
I can forget the grudge held against our parents.
But you are still accountable for
my brother’s death!
I wouldn’t forgive myself either
if it were really because of me.
Right,
you should feel guilty!
Because of your family,
I’m the only one left in mine.
When I was little,
my parents had me
Eat more.
And my brother.
Everybody was happy
even just having a simple dinner together.
I wish I could stay in that happy moment forever.
Until one day, my dad was gone.
And my mom was in deep sorrow.
To get justice for my dad,
my mom took us to He Wine Distillery.
But your dad, He Wangyou,
was intended to shut our mouth by money!
My mom told me
that my dad was gone because of your father!
Then my mom tried to find my dad all over the place.
But she fell ill not long after.
Ironically, it was such a small world,
I met you in high school.
I wanted you to suffer.
But when I watched you being bullied,
my brother saved you.
You know what,
He’s changed
ever since I met you!
Why did you do that?
You promised you won’t touch her again!
You promised you won’t help her again, but you did anyway!
What?
You are going to hit me for that girl?
You like her?
I don’t!
Do you swear?
I swear!
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
And then, in order to buy you a birthday gift,
my brother worked too hard
and died from overfatigue.
The misfortune
of my whole family
was brought by your father and you!
When I went to my brother’s place
with his things,
I found his diary.
September 1, 2012.
School starts today.
I just arrived city B,
still haven’t got used to it.
Nanke is left to check-in by himself.
Will he do well?
Hope everything’s fine.
December 24, 2012.
Today is Christmas Eve.
Mom is sick again.
The medicine cost a lot.
I need to find a job.
It’s the first snow in City B.
Nanke feels quite happy.
I think I’ll tell him about mom later.
Hi!
Hi! Please take a look!
January 1, 2013.
I found a job!
I’ll take Nanke out for dinner tonight!
Hurry up! Customers will be here soon!
Okay!
February 10, 2013.
It’s the first time I didn’t go home for New Year.
But Nanke is there,
hope mom won’t feel lonely.
Buzui.
Happy New Year!
March 11, 2013.
My job is getting busier,
and I can’t see Nanke quite often now.
He seems to be angry with me.
Hope he can find a girlfriend this year.
How about you?
Have you been doing well?
April 1, 2013.
Beginning of spring.
The weather is getting warm.
The doctor said mom is getting better.
Nanke is very happy about that.
It’ll be your track and field contest next week.
Good luck!
April 30, 2013.
I haven’t heard from you for a long time.
It makes me feel uneasy.
Where will you go to university?
Will we be able to see each other again?
July 8, 2013.
I’ve been feeling so tired.
But the thought of seeing you soon
cheers me up greatly!
I still remember the pale look of my brother.
That was the last time I saw him.
Brother.
Mail this to mom.
Brother!
How hard do you want to push yourself?
You’ve become like this.
Why do you still work so hard to buy birthday gift for He Buzui?
She is your enemy!
I like her.
I want to do something for her.
You don’t understand.
My brother thought that he forgot
his password for his QQ account.
Actually I changed it
without telling him.
After I got out of the jail,
I logged on his QQ account,
and I saw that you kept sending him messages.
Do you know how happy I was?
Could you not think of others
from your point of view?
Do you know
that your brother
didn’t want you to waste your time
on taking revenge.
He only wanted you to be happy and safe!
Yi Nanke.
You are his twin brother!
But you don’t understand him at all!
His heart was filled with love.
He never hated anybody.
All he wanted was you to be happy!
But you…
Look what you’ve become!
You disappointed him!
The one who should feel sorry
is you,
not me.
You had a chance to stay alive,
but you stuck to look for death!
Just a few kids! You think you can screw me?
You overestimated yourselves!
What are you hiding?
Tell us!
Let me tell you,
you can’t afford to play this game!
You’ll lose your lives!
Listen!
If I let you go,
and you swear you’ll never
mention anything about Pear Blossom,
I’ll spare your lives.
Otherwise,
none of you can leave here!
Where’s Yi Jianguo?
Did you also
kidnap him like this?
Yi Jianguo?
Why do you ask about him?
How do you know him?
Where’s my dad?
You guys know too much!
It’s either you die or I die!
You can all disappear together with Pear Blossom!
What are you gonna do?
You shall be responsible for your act!
Let us out!
Open the door!
Wan Zeze.
Will Weixun be in danger?
He was so furious just now!
It was an emergency.
You need to understand him.
Wan Zeze.
You and your father can’t even tell
who’s good and who’s bad!
Mr. Yang is my father’s friend.
He’s been very nice to me.
I don’t think he would do something like that!
No.
I have to go back!
It’s too complicated.
And I brought you guys over there.
How could I leave?
I need to go back too!
I can’t leave Weixun alone
in a dangerous place like that!
Let’s go!
Have you gotten rid of them?
I have.
Don’t worry!
If you don’t get rid of them
and the evidence,
you will be dead.
Luckily, you are quite smart.
I got it! Got it!
Mr. Wan.
Hello?
Honey!
Okay! Okay!
I’ll go to pick you up now!
Be patient!
Yi Nanke!
Hold on!
How come we are off today?
Don’t know!
- Why are we off?  - Who cares!
Have you seen Mr. Yang?
- No!  - No! No!
He’s injured!
Look at his hand!
Badly injured.
He Buzui!
Lu Weixun!
I’m here!
Hold on!
Mr. Yang said
that he’ll let us disappear together with Pear Blossom.
He Buzui!
I’ve called the police!
They’ll be here soon!
Hold on!
Please go!
If he sets here on fire,
it’ll explode.
Then, we’ll…
we’ll all…
No!
I won’t go!
I’m right here!
Stop trying!
Just go!
You can’t open the door!
I’ll be here with you!
I haven’t found your sense of taste back!
Lu Weixun.
If
I’m gone,
will your sense of taste be gone too?
I don’t want my sense of taste!
I only want you!
He Buzui! Hold on!
Do you hear me?
Hold on!
Hello?
I want to book two tickets to America.
As soon as possible!
The Mr. Yang you talked about
didn’t set the winery on fire.
We found a burnt-out match in the storage house.
But we can’t find him.
I’ll continue to investigate.
Don’t worry.
Thanks!
Turns out Mr. Yang still has some conscience.
Because I’m blessed!
See,
shouldn’t you be nice
to a lucky penny like me?
So you mean
I can’t leave you anymore?
You injured badly!
Does it hurt?
I’m fine.
Let me see that hand.
It’s not hurt. I’m fine.
Let me see!
We’d better get out of here.
Come on.
Let’s go see a doctor.