You’re up.
You know who is the richest person is in the world?
Bill Gates.
Buffett.
Jack Ma.
Who is it?
Ant-Man.
Ant-Man?
All cash machines
are printed with his name
ATM.
Lu Weixun,
was that supposed to be a joke?
Not funny?
You should smile more.
Your look is average.
A long face is even less attractive.
You...
Am I worried about myself?
About me, I know.
Then why did you...
Trust me.
We’ll win.
I promise.
Let’s eat.
Is it good?
There are 3 rounds in total.
For the first round,
one from each team
will select three wines for the other
to taste
and write down the names and the wineries.
You will have 15 minutes.
Ready?
Yes.
You may begin.
After you.
Blackberry, cherry, raspberry,
liquorice, coffee, and dirt.
Child’s play.
The first glass.
Blueberry, blackcurrant, blackberry.
Strong fruity aroma,
together with rose, anise,
and baked spices.
Creamy texture, layered flavor,
soft tannins
mixed with black fruit
refreshing taste.
Well-balanced acidity,
persistent aftertaste,
plus a hint of
dark chocolate.
The second glass.
Blackberry, liquorice.
Strong flavor,
layered, and rich.
And plum, mulberry, Shiraz,
but not the usual kind.
It’s more condensed
with balanced and complicated texture.
It’s...
The third glass.
Stop.
Time is up.
The first round ends.
Let’s see
the first bottle.
No.1,
Napa Valley from the U.S.
This is the first bottle.
The second one,
d'Arenberg The Dead Arm Shiraz,
from the McLaren Vale region of Australia.
And the last bottle,
it’s
Chateau Pavie, Saint-Emilion Grand Cru Classe, France.
Miss He’s answers are all correct.
Now,
let’s see Mr. Lu’s wines.
The first one,
Chateau Angelus, Saint-Emilion Grand Cru Classe, France.
This is the first bottle.
The second one,
Chateau de Beaucastel, Chateauneuf-du-Pape
Hommage A Jacques Perrin, France.
And the last one,
Penfolds Koonunga Hill Shiraz
Cabernet, Australia.
Mr. Lu’s third answer is wrong.
So,
winners of the first round are
Lu Weixun and He Buzui.
Congratulations!
An entry-level Shiraz
from Australia,
sold at a little over 100 Yuan
with no specialty.
Lu Weixun,
well played.
Fine.
You found my weak spot.
You've been away from this industry for too long
to know the consumers’ tastes.
You got lucky.
Mr. Wan.
Buzui,
how have you been?
We’re good, thank you.
Sure.
Mr. Lu, nice to see you.
Have a seat.
Thank you.
How is your son Zeze doing?
Thank you for your concern.
He’s strong as an ox.
Good.
Mr. Lu,
thank you for giving me that chance
so that I could pay for Zeze's surgery
and we could come this far.
Don’t mention it.
Mr. Wan and your dad seem close.
Is that a coincidence?
You know that girl?
She’s one of the He Wine Distillery.
Who?
He Wangyou’s daughter.
I remember it.
Enjoy your meal, sir.
Let’s go.
Mr. Wan,
please excuse us.
Have a good night.
You too.
See you.
See you. Bye.
Zeze,
the doctor recommends hospitalization
to improve your health.
I’m not sick.
Zeze,
Mr. Wan is doing this for your own good
For the second round,
there are 101 glasses of wine.
You will taste them simultaneously.
The one who first
writes down the names of 51 glasses correctly
will be the winner.
Are you ready?
Yes.
You may begin.
Come.
You can do it.
Yes.
Let’s continue.
Master.
No need.
Let me save you some time.
We've already won.
Don’t be so confident.
Besides, they can’t get it all right.
Focus. Let’s continue.
Cabernet Franc.
Go ahead.
Winners of the second round are
Lu Linong and Mu Chunfeng.
Congratulations!
I’m sorry.
I should've done it faster.
It’s OK.
You did well enough.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I’m not used to
this gentle side of yours.
If it were before,
you’d be all sulky and depressed.
Shut up.
See you tomorrow.
We’ll win the third round.
Good night.
We can discuss
the acquisition on Wednesday.
Move the meeting after 2 pm.
Wait.
Don’t waste your time.
The third round is similar to the second.
No matter how close you and that Miss He are,
she’s not you.
You don’t stand a chance.
I shall remind you that
I couldn’t have an excellent palate
without your training.
Denying me
is denying yourself.
I believe in myself.
Weixun,
each glass
had a
piece of fruit in it.
Taste the water
and tell me what kind of fruit it is.
Watermelon.
Correct.
Next one.
There was no fruit in it.
It was mint.
Mint isn’t fruit.
Brilliant!
Good job!
If it were for mom,
I wish we could wind back the clock.
Do you really know your mom?
This isn’t a dream
but my lost memory?
Hello?
Yi Nanke,
I want to tell you something
but I’m not sure if it's real.
Then I don’t need to know.
Wait.
There might be a body
under the old winery.
What did you say?
Ever since my palate started to recover
after I had Pear Blossom,
I’ve been having
weird dreams.
I dreamed about
the night I fell into the wine jar.
The same night my dad went missing.
Yes.
In my dream, I saw
a person in black.
Who was it?
I don’t know.
I couldn’t see his face.
You mean it was him
who buried a body?
Yes.
If that’s the case,
we need to call the police.
But
I don’t know
whether it’s a dream
or my lost memory.
Perhaps I was being paranoid.
Without proof,
the police won’t file the case.
Let's go there
and check it ourselves.
We can go there later.
I mean now.
Now?
But how?
Your gangster friends
might be able to help.
What?
Yi Nanke...
My...
gangster friends?
De?
Buzui.
Mr. Wan.
It’s late. Where are you going?
I’m going out to meet a friend.
At this time?
Oh, I mean,
it’s too late and dark outside.
It's not safe to go out alone.
I can give you a ride.
I’m fine.
I’ll call a cab.
It’s convenient.
What’s your friend's name?
Yi Nanke.
We need to run an errand.
I’ll be back after it’s done.
Don’t worry about me.
Good night.
You’re here, too.
What are you doing?
To help him, of course.
Let’s go, guys.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
Money talks.
Are we leaving or not?
Yi Nanke,
isn’t this too rash?
Did you forget what happened to Yang?
Let’s go play mahjong.
I lost a ton last time.
My hands are itchy.
I haven’t played for long.
Oh, come on.
Play with me, please.
Come back.
Are you blind?
Didn’t you see the guards?
Guards are there.
What should we do?
I can get us in.
I used to be a guard.
I know a thing or two.
Getting in is easy,
but after all these years,
this place has changed dramatically.
It may take a while
to find that old spot.
Let them come to us.
What do you mean?
Distraction.
Beibei!
Where are you, Beibei?
Beibei, come back to papa!
What’s going on?
How could you leave me, Beibei?
Who are you? What’s with the screaming?
My Beibei ran inside.
Who’s your Beibei?
It’s my dog.
He got in.
Open it.
- I need to find...  - What dog?
I didn’t see it.
This is a warehouse
of Lu Group.
Don't you know Lu Group?
Go find your dog elsewhere.
There’s none. Leave.
What’s that attitude?
It’s a warehouse, so what?
I’m not afraid of Lu Group.
Nobody can steal my dog!
Go away, you hear?
Are you deaf?
Open it.
No.
Let me in.
You can’t.
- Beibei!  - Get down.
- Beibei!  - Get down.  - Beibei!
What are you doing? Stop it!
- Get off it.  - Beibei!
- Beibei!  - Get down now! Are you nuts?
Guys, come here!
Get down!
What’s wrong?
Stop it. Get down.
Down.
- You hit me!  - What’s going on here?
What’s wrong?
Yi Nanke.
Be careful.
Gather round. There’s a fight. Go help.
Coming.
Is that it?
This place has changed completely.
Give me a minute.
I think it’s that warehouse.
Let’s go.
This is probably it.
You're ganging up against me?
So what?
What are you doing?
Who is it at this godly hour?
Get out of here now!
You hit me!
We did, so what?
- How dare you!  - What can you do?  - Fine.
Problem?
Fine.
You deserve it!
Briar, Bramble!
Charge!
Block them!
What are you doing?
Get down!
Get off it!
Charge!
Quickly. Go straight in.
Stop them!
Go away.
Let’s go.
- Catch them!  - Run!  - Hurry!
Stop!
Go to hell!
Catch them!
Stop!
Hello?
Mr. Wan,
the warehouse called.
What happened?
Some people barged in and were digging around.
They caught them?
Not yet.
Also, Mr. Wan,
we lost track of Yi Nanke and He Buzui.
So useless!
Should we call the police?
We can’t.
No police.
I’m on my way.
Yes.
I need to go out.
Take care of Zeze.
Yes, Mr. Zhong.
Here, here.
Catch them. Hurry.
Stop. Don't move.
Here.
Beidao.
Gear up.
Don’t move.
Drop it. Don’t move.
Put it down.
Beidao,
hurry up.
I got your back.
Beat them!
What is it?
My parents’ wedding ring.
It’s true.
It’s not a dream.
Stop.
Call the police.
Yes, call the cops.
No, no, no.
Beidao,
let's think about it.
Hey, this...
Mr. Wan.
You’re finally here.
Who called the police?
Not our men.
When did the police come?
A while ago.
They beat us for no reason.
I don't know why.
What happened?
They just hit us.
They barged in
on purpose.
Monsters!
The call said it was a murder case.
It is.
Stop your nonsense.
Be quiet.
Tell us,
what do you know?
My father, who’s been
missing for 20 years, might be buried here.
Officer,
that’s impossible!
Utterly impossible!
Good lord!
This is huge!
Boss,
a murder case.
I’m scared.
What are you afraid of?
We're now part of
something huge.
- Mr. Wan.  - Mr. Wan.  - Mr. Wan.
- Mr. Wan.  - Mr. Wan.
- Good evening, officer.  - Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
Officer,
sorry for troubling you.
Mr. Wan.
I apologize.
You know him?
You can talk to me.
He used to work in my dad’s winery.
We received a call about a murder case.
I thought you knew him, too.
Buzui,
what are you doing here?
You know them?
Yes, I know that girl.
Buzui,
is he that friend you talked about?
Naughty girl.
Go back now.
Mr. Wan,
are you aware
there might be a body buried here?
Young man,
be careful about what you say.
This is proof.
Bag it.
We’ll conduct an investigation
to verify it.
In the meantime, you can’t leave
before it’s over.
We’ll take you to the station for statements.
All of you!
We’re doomed!