=The Queen System=
=Episode 5=
Who's there?
Do you think you can hide here
and meddle along like this?
You watched costumed dramas.
You know how the concubines
end up, don't you?
I don't think I can live
to the last episode.
By the way,
I died once, didn't I?
Let me die again, then.
Stop finding excuses.
I'm warning you.
If you die again,
we'll never return to the modern world.
Then could you
give me
some pure missions?
(Kiss Emperor Jingxuan.
Get the new mission.)
(Kiss Emperor Jingxuan.)
How about
(Get the new mission.)
kissing Emperor Jingxuan?
(Kiss Emperor Jingxuan.
Get the new mission.)
As the daughter of the Prime Minister,
why do you do the embroidery so poorly?
(So,)
(I'm the daughter
of the Prime Minister.)
(Daughter of the Prime Minister)
(I'm really from a great family.)
How careless you are!
Why do you still do the embroidery
when your wrist is wounded?
I don't have a choice.
I'm doing this for you.
Before I got married,
I was taken good care of
and I didn't do any housework.
If I weren't
Lady Wu,
I wouldn't do the embroidery.
Feeling aggrieved?
I don't think you're that kind of girl.
In the Palace, as far as I see,
no one but you
dares to be against Noble Consort Li.
You're the emperor,
but you're afraid of your noble consort.
Aren't you too weak...?
Your Majesty,
it's been cold lately.
Put more clothes on,
in case
you catch a cold.
I know.
See?
I came to your palace
to get warm.
But I'm still practicing embroidery.
(Is she playing hard to get?)
Come.
Come with me.
(I'll see)
(what other tricks you can play.)
I'm a principled girl.
Before we're in a relationship,
don't dream to sleep with me.
Don't you get funny with me!
No concubine dares
to talk to me like this.
Looks like you've never experienced
the cruelties of life.
Let me teach you
what a good husband should do.
Fine, fine.
I won't sleep with you today.
I will
just sleep here.
May I?
Womanizer, get off my bed!
Mu Wu,
what did you just call me?
♪I miss you a lot♪
♪But I pretend I don't♪
♪We met hurriedly
and you stole my heart♪
♪The pledges we've made♪
♪Shall I believe them♪
(Emperor Jingxuan, Mu Wu)
♪In your heart I want to be♪
♪The one and only♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)