=The Queen System=
=Episode 3=
(One thousand. Three thousand.
Four thousand.)
(Three thousand. Four thousand.)
Good taste.
But you don't have enough points.
Come on, just some dresses.
Wow, a cellphone?
(Get Emperor Jingxuan's favor +10.
Get the new mission.)
As long as you get
Emperor Jingxuan's favor,
you'll have points.
Then you can do clothes shopping.
I just need to play with him, huh?
It won't get me baffled.
Noble Consort Li has arrived.
Wicked girl,
since you came to the Palace,
you haven't saluted me yet.
What an impolite girl!
Theoretically, I should salute you.
I heard
that you didn't marry His Majesty
until you were 28.
In terms of age and seniority,
I'm far inferior to you.
I married His Majesty when I was 16,
not 28.
How dare you slander me!
Bai Qingqing,
come and slap her.
(Bai Qingqing)
Your Grace,
Lady Mu is the host
of the Palace of Tranquility.
I'm a mere concubine in the side hall.
If you want to slap someone,
slap me, please.
Get up.
My Lady,
nice to meet you for the first time.
You're Lady Mu
while I'm a mere concubine.
I don't deserve to stay by your side.
What an unruly place!
I'll slap you myself.
Ridiculous!
Who dares to stop me?
Stop it!
How dare you
slap my girl!
Your Majesty,
don't forget.
The war against the Luo State
is ongoing.
If you still defend this wicked girl,
I'm afraid
it's detrimental to our state.
You carry tales
and distort facts.
You're the wicked girl, actually.
Shut up!
Don't be ridiculous.
Nonsense!
She isn't a wicked girl.
However,
Wu Mu dares
to talk frankly.
I...
I haven't seen such a girl before.
Wu Mu, I want to make you Consort Wu.
What do you think?
Master.
I...
What a great chance!
Don't forget your mission.
The earlier you become the empress,
the earlier you can leave.
He looked handsome when defending me.
But I don't want a hopeless romance.
Who knows if he's a womanizer?
(She doesn't want it?)
I...
(Get Emperor Jingxuan's favor +10.
Get the new mission.)
(Mission completed.)
Your Majesty,
the job of managing the imperial harem
gets less and less attractive.
I...
I would rather join my brother's army.
(Noble Consort Li)
♪I miss you a lot♪
♪But I pretend I don't♪
♪We met hurriedly
and you stole my heart♪
♪The pledges we've made♪
♪Shall I believe them♪
♪In your heart I want to be♪
♪The one and only♪
(All rights of network communication
reserved by Tencent)