Seems like just yesterday
you were in diapers.
How is Joon-pil? How's your dad?
I haven't seen him in ages.
When are you going to start work?
We'll have to clear the spider webs,
and catch some mice.
Do you want to start today?
Gross.
Are you leaving?
Yes.
They say every family has a delinquent.
You should at least give a proper goodbye.
You're such a prick.
-Hello?
-The place needs to be renovated, right?
Grandma, are you kidding me?
This is a bit much for a joke, though.
This isn't a café, it's a pigsty!
So? You won't do it?
Then don't,
but I'll confiscate
your apartment and car.
My car!
I didn't even get to say goodbye
to the kids.
He must have had his reasons.
That's your problem.
Even if he had his reasons,
he can't do this to you.
Didn't you like your boss
even better than me?
What did I tell you?
I told you not to trust anyone but me,
including Mr. Hong.
But you didn't listen. What did you do?
You gave your heart to Mr. Hong
and to your boss.
But you were distant from me,
who likes your mom.
Mr. Gu!
Ji-hyang.
-Mom.
-What are you doing?
Do you have any idea
how upset Eun-chan is?
But rather than comfort her...
-What? Who likes whom?
-So...
I'm saying it's a nice day
and the wind is blowing,
but even if a typhoon comes,
the sun will rise again.
Even if this jerk mistreated Eun-chan...
Good arises out of bad.
Life is full of surprises.
Justice will prevail in the end.
Shut up!
I will shut my mouth.
I'll do whatever you ask me to do.
You must feel terrible.
I'm upset too.
He wasn't a bad person from the start.
He must have been desperate to do that.
I should be understanding, right?
What other choice do you have?
It will just kill you inside.
My mom is really kind.
I'll go get the dolls.
Okay.
Who is it?
I'm from the real estate agency.
Please come in.
How may I help you?
You put this place up for sale.
We're here to have a look.
What do you mean?
Isn't this Bang Nam-jeong's property?
We just received the call.
She said she wanted to dump it
right away for cheap.
Bang Nam-jeong?
Han-gyeol isn't only the one who's upset,
I'm more agitated at you.
What? "Mom, I think
this is too much as well"?
How is this too much?
Your son is the one who's too much.
He's almost 30,
but he never once had a decent job.
He's half-hearted with his studies
and life.
How did you raise your child?
Come on, Grandma.
If you're upset about something, tell me.
Don't take it out on Mom.
Is this about the blind dates?
So that is it.
You're right. I acted in bad faith.
I'll do it for real this time, okay?
That boat has already sailed.
If you won't run the café,
just live as you wish.
Fine. Then...
give me a job at the company.
If you make me a general manager--
Do you think our company is a playground?
We don't hire slackers like you!
You're being harsh today, Grandma.
You have three months
to triple the investment.
If you succeed, I'll give you
your inheritance early.
Mom, how could you say--
That will support you for life
as long as you don't blow it big.
Grandma! Why would you die?
You're stronger than young people.
-You punk!
-See?
See? Look how strong you are.
So what will you do?
I don't know.
I don't want to run a business.
I'm suited to bum around without working.
Whatever. I won't do it.
I refuse.
Really? Then start with the renovations.
Your starting salary
is 800,000 won per month.
Please leave me be.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you bother?
He doesn't try hard with anything.
Just keep living like that.
You'll get sick
of not doing anything eventually.
If you don't even realize that,
you're a hopeless cause.
Aren't you late?
You should hurry,
if you're going all the way to Namwon.
I'll see you later, Mom.
You need respect yourself first.
Why would anyone do it if you won't?
You're making me work way too much today.
The dishes, cleaning the storage room...
Am I your housekeeper?
Do you have that little to say to me?
You're making me work
because you feel awkward.
It's because I need help.
You're sweating. Should I turn
the air conditioning on?
No, it's fine.
Oh, right.
You don't like air conditioning.
All done.
Good work.
Come over here.
Why?
Just come.
What now? What will you make me do now?
These new shoes are killing me.
What is this hole?
Nice. It is soft.
Jump!
It's gone.
I should keep going.
Where is this?
What a strange smell.
Gross! Help!
I need to run away!
I've escaped. What is this place?
I'll have to leave the shoe.
This is so soft. What is this?
Monster!
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Where are you?
At home.
May I come over?
I won't, if you're working.
It's okay.
I'm not working today, come over.
Oh, okay.
Hey.
Hey. Where's Yoo-joo?
She's washing the dishes. Come in.
You don't even drink. How did you know
that I was craving wine?
You two always got each other
better than I did.
Anyway, how long has it been
since the three of us hung out like this?
Three years,
since Yoo-joo left you three years ago.
You're such a punk.
Drink up.
You guys look good.
Did you have a dramatic reconciliation?
Was it dramatic?
A bit.
I should get going.
I can tell that I'm intruding.
I'm sorry for interrupting
your romantic time.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Don't leave.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you ask me over?
I wouldn't have come if I had known.
But that doesn't matter to you, does it?
It only matters to me.
Where have you been?
Home.
Did you see your dad?
Yes.
Was it bad?
Can't you free yourself
from your issues with your dad now?
It's dragging on for too long.
Too long?
I didn't tell you about my issues
with my dad...
so you could attack me.
-Han-gyeol.
-A 17-year-old kid's hatred of his dad...
Forget it.
Yoo-joo. When a problem stays
with someone for a long time,
it's because there's a reason for it.
It's not for nothing.
Han-gyeol.
You're really leaving?
Hey, Han-gyeol!
Mister, I'll take two bags this time.
Don't be greedy, just do one.
You can't finish it by Thursday.
I can do it.
Give me one more bag.
I have a lot of free time now. Okay?
Babe, your shoelace is untied.
-What the hell?
-I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Watch where you're going!
-Are you okay?
-I'm okay.
Look at this!
Why you little! What should we do?
-I'm sorry!
-What the hell?
How dare you touch my woman's breast?
This can't get wet. Hang on.
This little punk. Hey. Are you kidding me?
Where do you think you're going?
Get over here!
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
-Babe, it's not a big deal.
-You punk.
Why are you starting a fight?
-What? It's not a big deal?
-Let's just go.
Is it him this time?
You were flirting with that other punk
last time. Is it him this time?
You're making me lose my temper.
-Screw you.
-Hey.
-Where are you going?
-Let go!
-What's the hell? Let go!
-Enough.
-Mister.
-Hey! Stop right there!
You're dead if you don't stop!
Let go! Shit!
Hey, you.
-Hey, you. You just won't stop.
-What?
You let go, and you're dead.
-Wait, what I--
-Hey.
Why would I let you kill me? Tell me!
-What? Let us both die.
-What the hell? Why are you hitting me?
Where are you going? When will you change
that temper of yours?
Hey! Stop right there!
Get back here. Say that again.
-Say that again!
-Sorry. Don't be mad.
This day sucks.
Why?
-Whatever.
-Why?
-Just run.
-Okay.
This is nice.
Hey, Mom.
Me? I'm at a friend's house.
It suddenly started to rain.
I'll go back once the rain stops.
I don't think the rain will stop today.
Don't get the dolls wet,
and just sleep over.
What? Don't come home?
You tell your daughter not to come home?
Aren't you even worried?
Your face itself is a weapon.
Okay, I'll take care of it.
One, two, three. Attack!
What are you doing?
Don't touch them with your wet hands.
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Are you crying?
No.
Collecting records is my hobby,
and your wet hands were touching them.
Are you angry?
My dad liked to collect these too.
He had this too.
Is something wrong?
No.
Hey. Water...
I'm sorry.
The taekwondo gym is closed.
The master packed up and fled.
I didn't get paid,
and I didn't get to say goodbye
to the kids.
Just find another gym.
A guy shouldn't cry
over something like that.
Shake it off.
It's easier said than done.
Go change.
You look like a wet mouse.
Oh, you're making kimchi fried rice?
You know how to cook?
You don't look like you would.
Get the rice.
It's hot. Hurry!
You must have a high tolerance for heat.
Did your dad pass away?
So, you're the head of the family?
Aren't you going to eat?
It's done.
Hurry.
-Hot. It's hot.
-It's hot.
It's really good.
Do you have some more rice and kimchi?
You're good at sewing.
That's unexpected.
You can do anything in order to survive.
How much do you get for each of those?
Do you get 500 won?
No, 50 won.
Who would pay 500 won
for simple labor like this?
That's ridiculous.
That looks fun. I want to try.
You can't do it.
Why not? I'll show you.
Watch carefully.
If you miss the center,
it will be cross-eyed, so do it right.
It's harder to take it apart.
Hey.
Why don't you have facial hair?
You're 24... 25?
You're old enough. Why are you so behind?
It's because I don't eat much.
You don't eat much?
Enough. You need to focus.
Hurry up! You should better do it right.
Okay.
How does a guy have such pretty hands?
Look who's talking?
Are you feeling down today?
You said before while we were running
that this day sucked.
Why?
Girl problems?
Tell me. I'm good at
giving relationship advice.
My grandma can't stand to watch me
laze around and not work,
so she wants me to run a ridiculous café.
That's why.
It really isn't girl problems?
The other time...
"You got hurt!"
Are you seeing her?
I am.
So you are.
Are you very close?
She's a habit.
Like drinking water in the morning.
I just can't bear not seeing her.
I try, but I keep going to see her.
It's a bad habit.
Sounds like you really like her.
I guess you'll marry her, right?
That's enough.
Okay.
It's a coffee shop nearby, right?
What is it called?
It's not a coffee shop, it's a pigsty.
It's no prince. It's a pauper's cave.
Prince Coffee?
-You live nearby, so you must know.
-Is it really Prince Coffee?
Mr. Hong sold it?
That's weird.
Run that coffee shop. Please?
It's in a great location. Do it.
Why are you so excited?
Do it. And let me work there.
I can clean well and I'm strong.
I'll do whatever you ask me to.
I still owe you money.
I can't pay you back without a job.
Come on. Let me work there too. Do it.
It's a bother.
And it's not a bother to breathe?
You laze around instead of working.
That's why the girl's family disapproves.
You're not desperate enough,
so everything is a bother.
I would do it just to show them.
I would show the girl I like
how successful I could be.
Enough.
Enough what?
If it fails,
then, so be it.
You have nothing to lose anyway.
If it goes under,
you can just bum around again.
Am I wrong?
Well, that does make sense.
If it succeeds, you can impress
your grandma,
and your girl.
If it fails, you can go back
to your current life.
Run the coffee shop. Okay?
-Come on, do it.
-Hold on.
Go brush your teeth first.
You smell like kimchi. It's gross.
Go!
Run the coffee shop.
Shut up. Don't say anything.
Habit.
Bad habit.
Like drinking water in the morning?
What does that mean?
I don't drink water in the morning.
What are you doing? I'm brushing my teeth!
You grumble even when
you're brushing your teeth?
Wipe your mouth.
You have no manners.
Why do I need manners with another dude?
You can sleep on the sofa.
I'm not sleeping over.
I'll leave once the rain stops.
It splattered on my pants.
Hey, why is your butt so small?
Why did you slap my butt?
Your butt won't wear out
just because I slapped it.
It's just funny how small it is,
that's all.
Here.
Are you going to sleep?
Let's hang out some more.
I'm tired.
I have some good stuff.
Do you want to see?
Are you a teen, watching stuff like that?
Just don't take it with you.
-Are you sleeping?
-Yeah.
Good night.
Okay.
He acts like he's so clean.
The eyes are crooked
and the stain won't come out.
What can I do with this? You keep it.
Also, you should run the café.
And hire me too.
Think it over. Promise!
He's so cute.
Grandma, give me my car.
What do you mean, "Why?"
You said to run the café.
I'm not doing this as a joke.
When I do something, I do it right.
Hey, Hungry. Are you busy?
Hey. You lied to me, didn't you?
How is this a good location?
If you clean up a bit and advertise...
Shut up and get in.
We need to do a market research.
You know the area, right?
Of course, I know it inside-out--
Are you hiring me?
We'll see.
Are you really the boss?
What?
Regardless, you need to pay me well
for today.
I blew off an important job.
It will be 100,000 won, okay?
You see me as money, right?
Yes.
But it won't be easy in that car.
Get off of me!
But we're going downhill!
I can't push my butt back.
Do it. Stop overreacting.
There's Star Café. Bean Café's over there.
Two big cafés within 500 meters.
This sucks.
Stop.
Why is there such a big crowd there?
It's the most famous waffle place
in the area.
Why are they all girls?
That's a women's college.
-Really?
-Yes.
One waffle, please.
That looks good!
-It's so good.
-One for me, too.
I want the freshest one.
Seon-gi, the cops are coming.
Okay. Thank you.
Hey, follow him.
-What?
-Hurry.
Excuse me!
I would like us to work together.
Are you interested?
Don't you want to work
in a proper setting?
What's with that guy?
I can't work under someone else.
Think about it.
Please come to Prince Coffee!
Go.
What? Pretend you're a guy?
That's nonsense.
A girl is a girl. A girl isn't a guy.
Please.
Even if you do fool him right now,
what about later on?
I'll tell him later on.
Let me get the job first.
I lied to him that I was a guy
and I made a lot on a part-time gig.
So why did you take his money?
I know.
I hate myself too.
But if I tell him now,
he'll get really mad.
Please, just this once.
I'll tell him later. I promise.
Let's get some decent baristas.
Mr. Hong is the barista.
It's my kitchen. No one else can run it.
Do you know why your shop is such a mess?
Because your coffee sucks.
It doesn't suck.
Yes, it's dirty, but...
The coffee tastes incredible.
Try some.
-Put that away.
-Try it.
I don't want it.
Forget it. He doesn't know anything
about coffee.
He probably only drinks alcohol.
He can't drink.
He passes out after one shot.
Where are the bean samples?
What?
We'll target women in their 20s,
since there's a women's college nearby.
Just stick to the 70's and 80's concept.
We'll go for variety in the side menu.
Waffles.
A side menu? Give me a break.
You're so superficial.
Those waffles.
There's that famous waffle guy
by the women's college you like.
You're kind of smart.
Let's change the name first.
-We'll go with "Coffee Prince."
-That's the same thing.
There will be three to four workers,
all princes, just like the café name.
Prince? Guys?
What about me?
Not you. What if...
Why not?
He's my first recruit.
He's trustworthy and responsible.
Start working from tomorrow.
Be right back.
Hi.
How have you been, DK?
Who was that?
DK.
This song is really nice.
Why did you hang up so quickly?
He just called to ask how I'm doing.
Do you not like my talking to DK--
It's fine.
You don't look like it's fine.
Give me some time.
I'm hungry.
-Something spicy?
-The spiciest.
Okay, in ten minutes.
Five.
-Seven.
-One minute.
What are you doing over there?
What are you hiding?
I saw everything.
A present?
It's a free gift.
I took a bigger one. It should be useful.
Thank you.
It's a ladle.
I brought it especially for you.
We usually only give out the gloves.
You won't get in trouble?
It's fine.
I'll get going.
Take care.
How are things going
with Guy A and Girl B?
Oh, that...
I heard they eat together,
take walks and have tea together,
things like that.
So it worked out, then.
That's great. Congratulations.
I guess you won't need
my counseling anymore.
I heard something else, though.
Girl B has a Guy C.
-An old flame.
-Come here.
Then...
Did Guy A not know about Guy C?
He did.
He knew,
but he wasn't so pleased
when Girl B talked to Guy C
on the phone.
-Isn't he pathetic?
-No.
I can totally understand Guy A.
They broke up. Why is she talking
to her ex-boyfriend?
Girl B is kind of... You know.
Paw.
But...
Is Guy A that insecure about himself
regarding Girl B?
Tell him I think he's pretty cool,
and to have confidence.
I will.
May I ask you a question?
What?
There's this guy who thinks this girl...
is a guy.
What do you mean?
My deliveries are backed up.
I'll tell you next time.
-Okay.
-Bye, Sweeper. Bye!
Thank you.
-Hey!
-Yeah?
Sorry for bugging you.
I don't know whether or not
we'll run into each other, but...
So, in case we don't, will you give me
your number so I can call...
Never mind if you don't want to.
I don't mind...
What's your number?
It's 010-2917-1215.
What's your name?
-Han...
-Sweeper's dad.
Sweeper.
See you.
Take care.
010-2917-1215
I got it finally. Choi Han-sung.
We'll redo the interior,
replace the equipment, kitchen tools,
furniture, sign, and hire new workers.
That will be 100 to 150 million won.
And work on Mr. Hong.
I won't work with him
if he shoots down all my ideas.
How did you meet someone like that?
-Mr. Hong is equal in rank with you.
-Equal?
In other words, you're both CEOs.
Neither of you can fire the other.
You can do the interior yourself
for 700,000 to 800,000 won.
Use the equipment you already have.
You can pay the workers
with what you make.
I'll give you 50 million won.
And you must submit receipts
for everything.
Grandma, how can you go
from 150 million to 50 million?
I'm going to a meeting.
She's impossible.
-Did you look around?
-Of course.
Dong-su's factory will provide the paint.
Min-cheol will provide the furniture.
I'm leaving the interior to you.
I may be unable to pay you properly.
I owe you so much.
We're built on trust, okay?
Thanks.
Move. You're blocking me.
Do it anyway.
Work hard if you want a nice figure.
She can't have a nice figure.
She's a guy starting tomorrow.
Right.
Then...
I should build up muscles.
Are you really going to act like a guy?
What if you get caught?
Don't worry.
They won't know
as long as we don't bathe together.
I totally agree with her.
Her front is as flat as her back.
Anyway, I know I can do it,
so don't worry.
Once I get paid, I'll pay off the debt
and buy you shoes.
I don't need...
I'll just bring you
some snacks then, okay?
Don't come. What if I get caught?
Don't worry.
I'll say you're my son.
I'll say you're definitely my son.
Down your drink
Cool. The shop
is the definition of "amazing."
This is incredible.
I'm burning with desire
to tear everything down.
Does he even know what he's doing?
We'll open up the kitchen.
You're not opening up my kitchen.
Opening your kitchen means
showing everyone your know-how.
True know-how can't be copied,
even if seen.
Let's just open half of it.
Half will be open,
and the other half closed.
We'll kill two birds with one stone, okay?
Good morning.
A sharp nose.
Slim jawline.
Full lips.
Are you a guy or a girl?
-Who is this?
-My lover.
That lover.
No wonder rumors were flying.
That must have been nice.
He's totally my type.
Hi, I'm Jin Ha-rim.
How old are you?
Twenty-two?
Twenty-three?
Twenty-four, Koh Eun-chan.
Okay. Eun-chan.
You look cuter the more I look at you.
Let's get started now.
What time are they coming?
They'll be here soon.
Let's dump the trash first.
When will we finish cleaning this?
It's so filthy.
-What? What is that?
-Hey.
Hey, what's wrong?
Mouse.
Is that all it was?
Did you catch it?
It got away.
The mouse was as big as a cat.
I nearly peed my pants.
I got it!
-I caught a full bottle. I'll light it up!
-Seriously!
That kid has got guts.
Get the ceiling here, please.
Okay.
Who's that?
What are you doing here? Move.
Eun-sae refuses to see me because of you!
You took away my only angel.
I saved you from going to prison.
Leave quietly. I'm busy right now.
There cannot be two suns in the same sky.
Let's finish this!
Fine. We can do it
after I finish moving this stuff.
Help out.
Are you crazy? Why should I do that?
Move quickly, so we can fight quickly.
You're so dumb.
Okay, fine. Then I'll finish this quickly.
What is he doing?
Is this Hercules' home?
Do they eat ginseng every day?
Hey, it would be nice
to have someone like that around.
Hey, you. Who are you?
And who are you?
Do you want to work here?
No.
I'm the boss here.
If you need a job, work here.
Don't you dare. You do, and you're dead.
Okay, let's battle now.
Here. Use this.
Look at your skin.
What was that for?
Apologize.
Apologize. Now!
There he goes again with the "apologize."
I'm so sick of that.
-He's so obsessive.
-Apologize. Now.
-Mr. Hong, order the coffee beans.
-Apologize.
Eun-chan!
Order the beans
I told you about yesterday.
Okay!
Apologize right now.
I'm sorry.
Look at my eyes and apologize sincerely.
Aren't you going to order them?
I'll do it!
That's enough.
Min-yeop!
What is it?
Order the coffee beans.
The number is
010-6980-4213. Twenty, two-kilo bags.
-Apologize.
-What is the number again?
010-6980-4213. Twenty, two-kilo bags!
Make me repeat it again, and you're dead!
010-6980-4213.
-Twenty, two-kilo bags...
-I'm scared.
-Apologize.
-Wait.
-How many bags?
-Apologize!
Enough, okay?
How long will you do this?
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth.
Let's get to work.
He's just a jerk with a pretty face.
Serves you right.
What is it, Han Yoo-joo?
Were you sleeping?
No.
I'm sorry.
For what?
That day...
I didn't consider your feelings.
I shouldn't have said that
about your dad.
I won't make excuses. I'm sorry.
Are you really sorry?
Yeah.
Then do me a favor.
I need a mural in my shop.
So you agreed to do it.
Yeah.
Did we overcome an obstacle
in our relationship now?
I was so scared before.
Do you actually get scared, too?
Of course.
I'm scared of you and your cousin.
Han-sung is always between us.
Friend.
Don't be like that.
Fine, I won't.
You sound very tired.
I want to sleep,
but I can't.
Maybe I'm overly tired.
You know I have insomnia.
What now? Do something.
Then, do you want to paint the mural now?
Now?
No?
Okay.
Let's meet there in an hour.
Han-gyeol.
You're here.
I was worried we wouldn't have wine.
I'm impressed.
How can Yoo-joo work without wine?
There's music too.
I'll be able to draw well now.
Pour me a glass.
There.
My flat chest will get even flatter.
Hey, boobs. This is like...
guys choking their necks with neckties.
I'm definitely not torturing you.
Done.
Eun-chan.
Now that you've got a job,
it will be smooth sailing ahead.
I can do this!
COFFEE PRINCE SHOP NO.1
He's early.
Who are you?
I think we've met before.
Scooter?
Right? Don't you remember me?
How can he not remember?
He's the guy who snatched your purse.
I feel like I've been beaten all over.
That's nice.
I thought it went well
with the color of the cement.
Looks good.
How are you two...
It's a long story. Right?
My head isn't your armrest.
Stop resting your hand and arm on it.
Did you on a painkiller patch?
You plastered your body with them
after doing that little work?
Yes, I know you're a bloodhound.
My name is Han Yoo-joo.
Let's go eat.
You must be hungry from working all night.
Let me greet him properly first...
You can greet him later.
Clean the wine glasses
and that stuff over there.
What should we eat? Tofu soup?
My stomach isn't so great.
Let's get something light.
Something light?
The coffee beans are here.
What do you mean,
20 pieces of 20-kilo bags?
We ordered for 2-kilo bags.
Mr. Hong, what's going on?
What happened?
-You placed the order...
-Quiet.
I'm sorry.
I must have mistakenly ordered
20-kilo bags.
Can we have a refund?
-Are you kidding me?
-Who would kid in this situation?
And even if we did order that,
why would a new café
order 20-kilo bags of beans
that cost hundreds of thousands
of won each?
You knew it was a mistake,
but you sent them anyway!
I thought it was strange too,
so I confirmed over and over again.
"Are you sure you want
the 20-kilo bags, not 2-kilo bags?"
Didn't I ask you that?
We will not take them back.
Sir!
I'm sorry, but is there any way?
Send the 14 million won
by the end of the day.
Wait! You can't just leave like this!
Eun-chan.
Come with me.
Didn't you go to grade school?
Can't you even differentiate 20 and 2?
I'm sorry.
I'll go and try to talk to them--
Business is built on trust.
Do you realize that?
If we return beans from the beginning,
who will trust us later?
Who would want to do business with us?
Stop yelling at the kid.
I'll call your grandma and...
Is this how you've been doing business?
All you do is depend on others.
You insist on your way, and if you fail,
you put it on others.
What was that?
-You punk.
-Mr. Hong, calm down.
You really are a prick.
People make mistakes.
Why must you berate him like that?
Stop it.
Getting angry won't fix it--
Why do you think I'm angry?
Do you think this is a joke?
Your mistake may kill the shop.
Don't you feel guilty at all?
I'm just getting angry?
You disrespectful brat!
Are you crying? Hey.
Does crying solve anything?
You cry at the drop of a hat. Stop crying!
Let's get some fresh air. Come out.
I'm fine.
I apparently misjudged you.
If you're going to keep fooling around,
just quit right now!
Would you please excuse us?
Okay.
Eun-chan, if you don't mind,
how about we get some coffee?
I'm fine.
You should go to him.
I heard you bought 20 bags of beans.
Eun-chan. Let's roast the beans.
What are you doing?
I said to taste it.
If you're going to keep this up, get out.
I don't need you.
You're curious about him?
This is what he's like.
Let's change the name first.
We'll go with "Coffee Prince."
-Coffee...
-Prince!
Prince!
My son, Mom's here!
Hey, Ji-hyang.
I think we should get going.
Did you say anything about me?
Do you know our boss?
Why can't I get used to her?
What if I suddenly grab your hand?
-Eun-chan?
-Can you pretend you don't know me?
Subtitle translation by Jeong Lee