We brought you here
to ask some questions.
You must answer truthfully.
Something happened to Lu Yang.
He...
What happened to him?
Lu Yang is dead.
He...
He's dead.
How could he die?
Come back to our hometown with me.
Sure. What do you want to do back home?
I can work
in an engineering team,
and I
might become a teacher.
Who did you offend?
How could you die?
The portrait we got from Old Deng,
after image comparison,
has a very high overlap rate
with the surveillance video at the scene.
The on-site trace inspection
did not find any
DNA residue.
The more I hear this, the more it sounds like a hired killing.
Combining the two cases,
Lu Yang knew Tian Liang and Xia Lin
had an improper relationship.
So Lu Yang used this to threaten Xia Lin.
Coincidentally,
right after we questioned Xia Lin and Huang Xiaoyun,
Lu Yang had an accident.
We must investigate if this is a coincidence.
We can't find the person,
and the license plate is blocked.
Then look for the tire tracks.
Are you blind?
What are you doing? Right?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
I saw everything, you hit him.
Did you do it on purpose?
What are you talking about?
Sorry,
brother.
Tell me what you want.
I'm in a good mood today.
Take your car and get lost.
Okay, sorry.
What's wrong with this person?
Alright, stop talking.
Let's go.
Ms. Xia,
sorry to bother you.
Sorry to bother you.
Why are you here?
Well,
we have a few questions to verify with you.
Haven't you already asked?
They are a few new questions.
Don't worry.
Is it convenient to tell us
what you were doing last night?
I went home after work last night.
I didn't go anywhere.
Do you have witnesses?
What do you mean?
Nothing else,
just a normal inquiry for related persons.
The surveillance camera recorded me going home.
And at night, Xiaoyun, Qiming, and I
all ate at home.
Did Ye Qiming go out again?
No.
We went to sleep after dinner,
quite early.
Then we won't bother you anymore today,
Ms. Xia.
Thank you.
Okay.
Mr. Ye.
What a coincidence.
We just came from your house
Yes.
to ask you a few questions,
and we ran into Ms. Xia.
She said
you were at home all night yesterday.
I was at home.
It's nothing serious.
Just some routine questions.
You've had a long day.
You can go back and rest now.
Okay.
Thanks for your hard work.
Contact me if you need anything.
Any thoughts?
Not really.
I just feel that,
after all, it's a matter of life and death.
Not nervous, nor excited.
He is a bit too calm.
Indeed.
Looking at it this way,
Xia Lin's reaction is the normal one.
Not many people know Lu Yang.
He is one of them.
Alright.
Let's go.
Yuna, Yuna.
What's wrong?
The project funds are gone.
Qiming.
Here,
try the apples I bought today and see if they're sweet.
What's wrong?
You don't look so good.
Did something happen?
The over one million in relocation funds for the farmers,
I lost it.
What?
The relocation funds are gone?
How could this happen?
Did you call the police?
I already did.
But when we'll get the money back
is hard to say.
That's so much money.
If it can't be given to the farmers in time,
what will they do?
The money owed to the farmers
can't be returned to them in time.
Well,
don't worry.
I'll cover the money first.
You'll cover it?
That's over a million.
I... I...
No wonder my right eyelid has been twitching lately.
Did you offend someone?
Someone might be trying to set you up.
It's really hard to say.
But,
I'll figure it out.
It wasn't money in the bag.
What?
It was swapped.
What do we do now?
Let's leave it at that for now.
Did Ye Qiming plan this,
or is he in the dark too?
Xiaoyun.
Look, I bought winter melon and ribs.
We'll have winter melon and rib soup tonight.
Wash the vegetables.
Okay.
Xiaoyun.
Where are you going?
Wash them here.
What's wrong?
What's wrong with you?
Lu Yang
is dead.
What did you say?
Lu Yang is dead.
How did he die?
The police told me
he died in a homestay apartment
from gas poisoning.
How could this happen?
Was it an accident, or did someone murder him?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Don't worry.
The police are on it.
They will find out the truth.
Auntie,
I want to go back to my room and rest for a while.
Go ahead.
Lu Yang is dead. Did you know?
What did you say? Lu Yang is dead?
When?
How did he die?
Xiaoyun said
it was carbon monoxide poisoning.
This kid,
how could he be so careless?
That's why I say girls looking for a partner
must be careful.
Actually, I think Lu Yang's case,
whether it's suicide or murder,
must be related to
his usual bad deeds
and misbehavior.
How do you know he did bad things?
I...
I was just guessing.
Xiaoyun is in a very bad mood lately.
I already tried to comfort her,
but she wouldn't listen.
Why don't you try talking to her?
Okay.
About Lu Yang...
He didn't study hard
and often went to bars and nightclubs,
messing around.
The point is, he made enemies.
What happened to him today
is his own fault.
There's no need for you
to be too sad for him,
okay?
But where did he get all this money?
People change.
His usual consumption records
can be easily checked.
You are just too innocent,
and he kept you in the dark all along.
But even if he did those things,
he didn't have to die.
Xiaoyun, don't be sad.
I promise you,
I'll look into this matter for you,
alright?
Thank you, Uncle.
Don't be sad. I'll get going now.
Come here.
You just said you'd help Xiaoyun figure this out.
How are you going to do that?
Does Lu Yang's death have anything to do with you?
Don't talk nonsense.
You need evidence to back up your words.
Ye Qiming.
I know you too well.
If I didn't have proof,
I wouldn't say such things.
Are you saying I'm a murderer?
A highly educated intellectual
marrying a murderer.
Don't you think that's ridiculous?
Then why did you marry me in the first place?
I married you back then
because I was blind and misjudged you.
It's not just your family who looks down on me.
Actually, deep down,
you've always looked down on me all these years.
If I looked down on you,
I wouldn't have gone against everyone's objections
to marry you back then.
Now I even suspect
that the thugs I encountered while sketching
were arranged by you.
A city lady
is nothing more than this.
You are simply hopeless.
I'm hopeless?
Is it my problem?
It's clearly your problem.
Ye Qiming.
I think you just got rich
and want to dump me, right?
Don't worry.
I could never dump
the arrogant Miss Xia Lin.
I'm just giving someone a taste
of their own medicine.
Ye Qiming.
You disappoint me so much.
Despicable.
Xiao Li kept telling me when he got off work just now
that he didn't want to get off work.
His mentor just pushed him out directly.
He had to go home.
His dark circles were almost down to his feet.
How could I not let him go home?
Xiao Li has made progress recently.
You should praise him.
Don't always scold him with a long face. He's young.
All right. What did I say to him?
Shen Feng.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm a little scared.
Scared of what?
When the case is closed,
it'll be time to go back to the office.
Then there will be plenty of people staying up late with you.
Xiao Li should be well-trained by now.
He didn't help much when he came.
Still causing trouble.
Captain Jiang.
Look what this is.
The final payment.
Today, at Lu Yang's door,
I saw Ye Qiming.
Two buns, please.
Meat or vegetable?
One of each.
Okay.
Two more fried dough sticks, boss.
Okay, wait a moment. Coming right up.
Sister Wang, did you hear?
Around here recently,
a college student died.
I wonder when the police will solve the case.
I hope it doesn't affect our business.
The rice tofu is spicy.
Numbing.