I didn't kill him.
When I got there,
he was already dead.
What did you say?
On the night of the 25th,
he was already dead.
Clean it up. Don't let the police get involved.
Okay.
So you dismembered the body in the bathroom?
Why did you dismember the body?
I really didn't want to deal with you people.
He was already dead.
I was afraid you would suspect me,
so I disposed of the body.
Who is it? What are you doing there?
Me.
Manager Chen.
What are you doing there?
Moving some dirt
to weigh down the rebar.
There's a big pit ahead.
I'm filling it with dirt.
Let me help you.
No need.
Go do your work.
Okay, we'll wait for you in the car.
Go.
How can you prove you didn't kill him?
You've already been to my place, right?
There's a solid black lighter.
You must have brought it back already.
Whose is this?
It was left by the killer.
At the time,
it was right by Tian Liang's feet.
Does this count as redeeming myself?
Mr. Jin.
Um...
Can't you two sit down and rest a bit?
What's the use of calling me all the time?
We finally got this clue.
This DNA result
is very important to us.
All right, I know.
No, when will the results be out?
Mr. Jin.
Answer me.
Wait a minute.
The results are out.
It's confirmed
that the bloodstain is Tian Liang's.
Great.
We can finally confirm that place
is the primary crime scene.
The lighter has been handed over to forensics
to see if there are any useful clues.
That house is under Xia Lin's name.
We can interrogate those three now.
Thanks, Lao Jin.
You did a great job, Lao Jin.
Thank you.
Hurry, hurry.
On the night of July 25th,
what were you doing?
July 25th
was Xiaoyun's birthday.
We were at home celebrating her birthday.
Until 11 o'clock,
neither of us left.
With Ye Qiming?
Yes.
Huang Xiaoyun,
what were you doing on the night of July 25th?
At home.
Uncle Ye and Aunt Xia were celebrating my birthday.
Do you have any proof?
Yes.
I took photos and videos at the time.
I'll bring them to you later.
Okay.
Make sure to give us the videos and photos.
Why didn't Lu Yang go to your birthday?
He took me out for lunch.
He doesn't really like Uncle Ye,
so he wasn't invited.
Was Lu Yang at school in the afternoon?
Yes.
We left school together in the evening.
Do you recognize this house?
No, I don't.
This is not my house.
Tian Liang died in this house.
I didn't know.
This house is under Xia Lin's name.
We suspect Xia Lin is connected to Tian Liang's death.
That's impossible.
Xia Lin is so weak.
And that day,
we were together the whole time.
These statements
are flawless.
None of the three had time to commit the crime.
Ye Qiming even firmly insists
that he doesn't even know about that house.
Why do I feel like something isn't right?
Isn't Ye Qiming keeping himself a bit too clean?
Fortunately,
we've found the dismemberment scene and the culprit.
We are getting closer to the truth.
Hello.
Who is this?
It's me.
Mr. Ye.
What?
You want to cooperate?
Let's talk.
It seems you don't have any leverage right now
to negotiate with me.
I can't believe you're in this situation
and still so greedy.
You know,
those who go against me never end well.
Total disregard for human life.
I've seen it.
Like that female reporter.
You had a hand in that too.
Once you're in the game,
I'm afraid you can't walk away clean.
Maybe I don't want to walk away.
After all, you gave me no way out
and dragged my son into this.
Are you threatening me?
You threatened me first.
Do you believe
I can have you killed?
I have nothing to lose in a fight to the death.
You...
I will use those documents.
In exchange for my son's freedom,
is this deal worth it?
You decide.
The project in the eastern suburbs,
I'll help you secure it.
Your Tongda Group
will definitely be jumping over the dragon gate.
Who let you in?
Didn't you order the wine?
Let me check the order.
This waiter
looks very unfamiliar.
Let me.
We didn't order wine. You made a mistake.
Please leave quickly.
I'm sorry.
The waiter brought the wrong wine.
Let's continue.
Our group can't afford any mistakes right now.
Mr. Ye.
Illegally transferring ten million yuan
will get you in jail, son.
Yu Na won't lie to me.
Son,
listen to Dad.
Yu Na is definitely not the kind of person you think she is.
You guys stay out of it.
I know what I'm doing.
Son, listen to me.
He is very confused right now.
He won't listen to anything you say.
I'm here.
I'll figure something out with you.
I just feel that for so many years,
I've really let you down.
Why are you saying this?
We still have a long life ahead.
Take good care of yourself.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you here?
Didn't you promise to take care of me?
How about this?
Tonight,
I want to invite Yu Na to dinner.
Ye Yuan's matter can't be delayed any longer.
Then let's have her over.
I'll go get ready.
All the evidence points to this Chen Hao.
But he keeps saying he didn't kill anyone.
He said when he got there,
Tian Liang was already dead.
Right now, we can't find
a third person's DNA at the scene.
The only evidence we have
is that lighter.
We must find everyone related to the lighter
so we can figure out
whether Chen Hao is just stalling
or he really didn't kill him.
The fingerprint match for the lighter is out.
Kuai.
Previously,
he committed intentional injury at Jiangbei Club.
He was sentenced to seven years and just released three months ago.
His fingerprints are in the database.
Captain Jiang.
I handled this case.
I know where he is.
You just got out and want to go back in again?
Do you have anything else to explain?
What is there for me to explain?
I got caught by you,
so that's it.
What deep hatred do you have against Tian Liang?
To be specific,
there's no deep hatred.
But I just knew he wasn't a good guy.
I mainly took money to do things for people.
Who gave you the money?
The boss of Tongda Company,
Ye Qiming.
Tell me the details.
Not bad.
For you.
I quit smoking anyway.
Get the job done,
and you'll get your money.
Use Tian Liang's phone
to send that message to this person.
Don't worry.
Your business
is all in my head.
Leave it to me.
Did you bring the stuff?
Where are the goods?
Welcome to our home, Yuna.
What? Afraid to drink?
Afraid it's poisoned?
Come on, wife.
Let's have a toast.
Let's eat.
Okay.
I never thought
we could still eat at the same table.
Maybe I'll even have to call you mother-in-law in the future.
Let's have a toast as a family.
Come, Xiaoyun.
Come, dear.
Let's drink together as a family of three.
Yu Na,
I asked you to come here today
to talk about Ye Yuan.
You know,
my target
was never Ye Yuan.
I don't care about anything else.
As long as you leave Ye Yuan out of this
and let my friend pick him up,
the controlling stake of my company
will be yours.
We wouldn't be here if you said so earlier.
Let them take Ye Yuan away.
I'm not the one pestering him.
Don't worry.
I'm not interested
in a kid.
Shameless.
Yu Na.
You can still stop
before it's too late.
All I want
is you.
Yu Na.