The deputy mayor of the city is retiring these days.
The competition for
this position is fierce.
With your abilities and level,
the new deputy mayor
has to be you.
Abilities?
We have a female division head
who hasn't been working long.
She has strong connections.
The former division head was just 50
and got pushed out.
Do you need my help?
You know,
I hate collusion between officials and businessmen the most.
Old classmate,
I'm helping you
and I don't need anything in return.
This isn't about getting anything in return.
It's unfair to others.
We've all experienced too much unfairness.
I hope the unfairness in this society
can be reduced as much as possible.
It's exactly for fairness
that we need
leading cadres like you to step up.
Seize this opportunity,
okay?
Qiming.
Are you...
Hello.
The bank loan needs your signature.
Come over quickly.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Go ahead if you're busy.
Old classmate.
Trust me.
I do.
It's time.
Look at these photos.
Not bad.
I'll give you another 50,000 yuan.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Do you understand?
Understood.
Go.
This bidding proposal is fake.
You've been set up.
I really underestimated him.
It's a pity about the project.
He's already suspicious of you.
I guess you won't be staying long.
He won't be able to kick me out.
After all, we are in the same boat.
Unless he wants mutual destruction.
Doesn't he still have that precious son?
Qiming is here.
Your calligraphy is getting better and better, sir.
Qiming.
I heard from Jiang Tao
that your company is doing a project in the western suburbs.
Yes.
We encountered some difficulties.
It's not about the project.
It's about fair competition.
So what do you think?
I want to change all of this.
I'm ready.
Inappropriate.
Your idea is very dangerous.
I'm not doing it for myself.
I won't regret it.
Qiming.
Don't be too stubborn.
Listen to me.
Qiming,
I will give you a piece of calligraphy.
Thank you, sir.
Great virtue carries all things.
Thank you so much, sir.
I won't bother you anymore.
Thank you, sir.
Qiming, wait for me.
Slow down.
This is the company. What are you doing?
Ye Qiming, I don't care if it's the company!
Ye Qiming!
Yu Na.
What did you call me?
Suspend all your current projects.
Take paid leave.
I was the one following up on the projects.
Why stop them just because you say so?
Calm down.
If you keep acting like this,
just go home now.
I have sacrificed so much.
I must get everything.
Rest assured.
Ye Yuan will definitely become
the most powerful tool against Ye Qiming.
Little guy.
How have you been lately?
I'm doing okay.
Let's go.
Okay.
Let me carry it for you.
Hello, sir.
Please show your ID.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Open the trunk, please.
You are the fresh blood of our bureau,
and you are very capable.
But
Tian Liang's case
and Lu Yang's case
have made no progress,
causing an uproar in the city.
Now the higher authorities
are very dissatisfied
with our work.
Chief Wu.
Shen Feng and I have been investigating.
I...
I don't care about the process.
If it's murder,
there must be a killer.
If it's suicide,
there must be a reason.
Yes.
Having pressure
isn't a bad thing.
Treat it as an experience.
Turn the pressure
into motivation.
I understand.
But we won't shirk our responsibilities.
There is indeed a problem on our end.
This case
has dragged on for too long.
Use your initiative.
Don't doubt your abilities.
I believe in you.
You can do it.
We will definitely do our best
and strive
to solve the case soon.
What a coincidence.
What's wrong? You look down.
You must be getting pressure from above.
The chief and the others are probably anxious too.
Aren't you anxious?
The longer it drags on, the worse it is for the case.
Don't you know that?
Open a new line of inquiry
and investigate Ye Qiming.
How do you open this candy?
How could there be a traffic accident?
Look into it.
Find out what exactly happened.
Just invite him to the police station
under the pretext of the migrant worker accident.
Okay.
We can use this chance to warn him.
Mr. Ye.
We asked you to come here today
to find out a few things.
Some time ago,
I heard you owed the village demolition compensation,
and the villagers got into a car accident on their way to collect the debt.
To show your apology,
you delivered the money to them in person.
Is that right?
Yes.
Our company let the villagers down.
We shouldn't have owed them money.
The responsibility is mine.
It's good that you realize that.
Regarding the demolition,
did you go to the village often?
Yes.
For work,
I went there frequently.
By the way,
regarding this traffic accident,
please rest assured,
and tell the villagers to rest assured too.
We will investigate it jointly with the traffic police brigade
and definitely find the vehicle responsible.
I thank you both on behalf of the villagers.
Thank you for your cooperation too, Mr. Ye.
Cooperating with the investigation is our responsibility and duty.
Yes.
Then there's another matter
we need your cooperation on.
Go ahead.
Regarding Lu Yang,
we are also very sorry.
Yes.
I sponsored Lu Yang's education.
I didn't expect such an accident to happen.
Besides your annual sponsorship,
did any other organization or individual sponsor him?
I don't know about that.
But there's one thing I find puzzling.
I heard from Huang Xiaoyun
that he often went to places like bars,
drinking and stuff,
and spent money lavishly.
I think
he shouldn't have been like that.
Could you tell us your impression
of Lu Yang?
I had very little contact with him,
so I don't know him well.
Then why did you sponsor him?
Mainly because we are from the same hometown.
We are from the same village.
It's not easy for someone from our place to get into college.
I didn't want him to go through the hardships
that I experienced back then.
So I sponsored him,
so he could focus on school,
and contribute to society in the future.
Given your relationship with Huang Xiaoyun,
we'd like to ask,
about their relationship.
What do you think of it?
That's their own business.
I don't care.
Didn't Huang Xiaoyun ask for your opinion?
I'm busy from morning till night every day.
I basically have no personal communication with her.
None.
So did you know or not?
I guess I knew a little.
How did you know?
Does this have anything to do with the case?
No.
I just want to understand
Xiaoyun and Lu Yang's relationship.
Then I'm sorry.
If you want to know,
you can ask my wife Xia Lin.
She knows much more than I do.
I see.
Did you go near Lu Yang's house the day he had the accident?
Yes.
I went to talk to the villagers about development.
Did you see Lu Yang then?
No, I didn't.
So you went straight home after work that day?
That night,
I got home around 10:20.
What's the matter?
You truly are a businessman, Mr. Ye.
Yes,
remembering the time so clearly.
After 9:00 that night,
I also called Lu Yang.
I told him to study hard.
I didn't expect
it to be our last phone call.
You've done all you could.
My condolences.
Thank you. Thank you.
Officers,
is there anything else?
If not, I'll take my leave.
Of course.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Do you need us to see you out?
No need, please stay.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Watertight.
He's been in business for a long time,
so he won't tell you anything easily
unless you have leverage over him.
But judging from the shoe prints and tire tracks,
he did go to Lu Yang's house
and observed him.
He admitted going near Lu Yang's house,
but there are no footprints of his inside,
nor are there any fingerprints on the stove.
Did Lu Yang turn on the gas himself?
Theoretically, yes.
But he came all this way just to take a look at Lu Yang?
Lu Yang's death.
No clues for homicide.
No motive for suicide.
It's too strange.
Isn't this Mr. Shen?
Are your old arms and legs still doing okay?
So-so.
No way.
Let me ask you something.
Why did you retire from the frontline back then?
If you hadn't retired,
I'd have to call you Captain now.
Please don't.
You leaders love to joke around.
Forget it if you won't say.
Come here.
Tell me.
There are many colleagues around. Don't make me look like I'm flaunting my seniority.
You are still
young now.
When you reach 30, you'll feel
a 9-to-5 job is okay.
I don't feel that way.
You can't feel it.
You'll hope you never do.
As for you.
Want some coffee?
I'll make you a cup.
Captain Shen.
Want some coffee?
Sure.
Two cups.
What is it?
Your letter.
My letter?
Don't let your mentor make coffee.
I'll make it.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Captain Shen.