NETFLIX SERIES
When bullets hit the brain, the heart
or major organs such as large blood vessels
Almost no
We can take emergency measures
Other soft tissue damage
It is best to learn some emergency measures in advance
Just in case
Nairobi
If this place in Denver gets shot
You need to first understand what organs are in this area.
Only then can we judge the injury, right?
liver
It's not the liver, right?
Can you draw it?
I have pretended to be a nurse several times when I committed crimes.
It doesn't bother me
Pull it down again.
Hey, let me see, that's either the appendix or the small intestine.
This guy is really loyal.
GAN
liver
Why don't you try Rio?
The doctor has the scalpel ready for you.
I don't understand why this kind of thing is happening?
Because this mission is life-threatening.
Life-threatening? I think it's child's play
Your attitude
Even if you get shot, I won't pull the bullet out for you
Rather than letting a rookie like you pull the bullet out of my hand
Fiddle with it
It's better to leave it alone.
There's someone here who's not a rookie.
Wow, are you really a doctor?
What kind of doctor is this? I've dropped out of school for a while.
Anyway
I only do what is within my responsibility.
Play the hospital game by yourselves
The brat deserves a beating
No matter if he died from being shot or from having the bullet pulled out
It's up to you.
Looks really delicious
Have you eaten?
Please give me a bowl
What have you been busy with recently?
You're asking me now?
I thought I was invisible.
I am with a bunch of bad friends
Taking drugs and messing around
I came back with no money.
I will talk to the school
Just apply to resume your studies.
Shall I prepare some bath water for you?
So impressive!
How much would this kind of house cost?
About 400 to 500 million won
How can I earn enough to buy a house like this?
Could it be a robbery?
If North Korea's hereditary class
South Korea is hereditary wealth
Aren't you curious?
An ignorant young son of a rich family
How to join our action?
This
Everyone probably has their own reasons.
Hey mom, let's have a drink together
No hope
So
Oh, I'm so hopeless.
Why did you come to pick me up?
Do you think this is coming to pick you up?
Would you mind our plan?
Have you complained to your family members?
If this happens, your family will be in danger.
Oh, what are you saying?
If you know this is the case
I told them a long time ago
Oh, what a fucking shame.
What a pity
Did I say that at the beginning?
What we are going to do
It's not a joke, nor is it a meaningless rebellion.
This is once you join
Something that I can't get away from in my life
Oh, you're so nagging.
Rio
Although it may sound like a rehash of the past
But I still want to say one thing
Always avoiding will eventually become a habit
One day you have to face reality
-Comrade Captain, something big has happened
-Hello, confirm.
identity!
- Was he shot?
-He is the Director of the Banknote Printing Bureau.
Authentication
- They said those people were not robbers
- No filming for a moment.
-etc
-We need to know the truth!
Is it confirmed that someone was shot? Who was that person?
The hostage is Zhao Yingmin, director of the Banknote Printing Bureau
- A hostage.
-Can't!
I repeat, the person who was shot was a hostage.
Who told you to mess around?
- Hello, how are you? Get up.
- Hey, open your eyes.
Rio, come help!
Cheer up, Rio!
Judging from the location of the gunshot
There shouldn't be any danger to life.
Of course, it would be terrible if that person died!
Now we are all done!
(Director Zhao Yingmin)
-Hey over here!
-Drag it here!
-Hey, be careful.
-Let him lie here!
Hey, bring the first aid kit over here!
-First aid kit
-Here it comes!
What should I do?
It seems like the bullet went in very deep.
If emergency measures can't save him, should he undergo surgery?
Wake up, bastard!
- You can't fucking die here
- Cheer up!
-What?
-Telephone
I want to call
My wife
Hey, shut up! Opening your mouth makes the bleeding worse
Wait, Rio, you have to think of something.
- Hey wait
- Too much bleeding
-Rio!
-What should I do if so much blood is coming out?
Hey Rio, why don't you come and take a look!
Rio!
Think of a way.
result
You guys still took action
How is the Director's status?
He is not dead yet
Just like we agreed to negotiate, is this how it's going to be?
It was you who created the emergency first.
Was there an internal conflict among the robbers?
We still tried our best to maintain a safe state
To the hostages
You're the ones who fired the shot.
There's no time to argue about who's right and who's wrong.
Don't you also hope that there will be no casualties?
How about being honest?
Police shoot hostage
Who will get in trouble for this?
Both sides will do
I mean, if the media keeps pursuing this,
So how do you plan to solve it?
Better get to the hospital as soon as possible.
You should know this is impossible.
Then…
Let the medical team in.
Saving lives is important
I'll call you back in ten minutes.
- No entry here
- Just take a picture, please.
Wait a moment
etc.
Please wait a moment
-etc
-Wait a moment
Huh? What did you say?
So how do we determine whether someone is dead or alive?
You should give me some information.
- You can't come in.
- Wait, I can't see
Sorry, it was my error in judgement.
It's my decision.
They're not stupid either.
They should agree to let the medical team in.
I hope so
Now is not the time to blame yourself
maybe
This would be a great opportunity
I'll go in with the medical team.
Can't fall for their tricks
In this situation, let outsiders come in
Who knows what tricks they'll play?
Can't let the hostages die
If I could die from such a small injury, I would have died long ago.
That bastard is now clamoring to talk to his wife.
I think he's quite spirited.
Besides, he was killed by the police.
We have nothing to lose.
Anyway, it's like this
Let him die comfortably.
How about doing some articles for the media?
“Police create excuses for coercive repression
Deliberately shooting a hostage
Don't think too much about Berlin
We haven't settled your account yet. We will settle it later.
Now this mess
Isn't it because you executed a hostage?
There can't be any more victims
I decided that I couldn't tolerate this.
Professor, no matter what
I clearly warned you
The chief wants to speak to his wife before surgery.
She should get a call.
Do you agree?
After one hour, only
Minimal medical teams and equipment
knew
Is it really possible?
So far the robbers have been one step ahead of us
It seems like everything was planned
Except for the director of the Banknote Printing Bureau who was shot
Make sure to let this
Become a factor in our favor
Even if I hide in the medical team and get in successfully
The robbers stared with wide eyes.
Captain Che, what can you do if you go in alone?
Weapons at the ready
When were these prepared?
Our army needs to prepare for any situation during the battle
Always Be Prepared
So I asked what to do with this...
As you said, Chief.
The robbers' attention
It will definitely be placed on the medical team.
We will take this opportunity to counterattack
Let the special forces sneak in.
in short
It's a feint strategy.
Comrade Director is very lucky.
A medical team will come.
Move this guy to the exhibition hall.
Come on, act fast!
Come back to the team!
hurry up!
Is that person going to die?
He tried to escape on his own and was shot.
Did the robber open fire?
Actually, the police opened...
Quick return
She's in this state.
What's the point of putting her here?
There is no other way
The professor doesn't know she's still alive, right?
Because of that bastard in Berlin
Anyway, that guy is the leader here.
So I think no matter what the professor says
It won't have any effect at all
Ouch, what should I do?
I said you still...
-What's going on?
-Oh shit
What? She's really still alive?
Ouch
-What's wrong?
- So serious?
If you don't have surgery right away
Her legs might be broken.
-What?
- Then you do it.
That's right
A doctor will come over.
I'll try to steal some surgical tools.
-that's all
- Please
Not that
Who will be responsible if Berlin finds out?
I can't do it even if you ask me
Rio
At least I'll keep it a secret
I don't want to cause trouble.
-Rio!
-Hello
Let this damn bastard go!
Let me take the place of that coward.
What can you do?
Didn't you hear him?
If I'm not careful, my leg will be broken.
Are you kidding me about the surgery?
Anyway, I'm going to try it
I fired the gun.
I should also be responsible.
oops
-But…
-Um?
You said the doctor was coming.
What does it mean?
That
Police accidentally shot a hostage
who?
No
Yingmin, huh?
He is in a much better situation than you. You don't need to worry about him.
The medical team will be here soon.
Dad, please take good care of her.
We'll be back in a bit, okay?
knew
Go ahead
What's wrong? Where do you feel uncomfortable?
You put this
Pass it to Yingmin
What's this?
He and I...
maybe
I'm leaving like this.
There is an underground vent
Kitchen leading to the staff restaurant
It will take some time to dive into this structure.
But this is the only way to avoid the surveillance cameras
Dangerous but feasible
Once inside, just mingle with the hostages...
The medical team is here
You should already know
Captain Che Wuhe
They will go in disguised as a medical team
yes
I understand the basic terminology and knowledge
Just treat me like an assistant.
How long does the surgery take?
If the injury lasts at least 30 minutes...
Please do not delay the surgery.
Try to delay the time
Where is Director Zhao Yingmin’s wife?
She's waiting outside.
What is this?
-What do you mean?
- That woman
I almost died.
Isn't it the director's fault?
But look at this
Look at what she said sorry
Are you interested in her?
ah?
Are you crazy?
I mean my brain
I can't understand her thoughts.
Is it necessary to understand?
Yeah
I apologize for my previous behavior.
each other
It doesn't matter
Stay away from me you murderer
What the hell are you talking about?
Hero of the Banknote Bureau
That is, Director Zhao Yingmin's wife has a connection
Is that your cell phone?
I'm about to see the King of Hell
You just remembered your wife, right?
What is the password?
One Two Three Four
Hey, it's rare that you didn't get caught for having an affair
Isn’t it?
Well, that's what I mean.
Come one two three four
Okay, what name did you save the number under?
My Favorites
"My Favorites"
- I'm talking about romantic comrades
-yes
If you take such a risk again
Be careful, you may die before the operation.
Hello?
(My favorite)
Wife
It's me
husband
The police said you were injured.
How are you feeling?
Hear your voice
I really feel alive.
Are the kids around?
If I Die
Tell them dad loves them very much
And your wife
I love you
Captain Che went in with the medical team.
Then convey the internal situation to us
While the robbers were paying attention to the operation
Some of our elite troops will infiltrate
After the important personnel sneaked in
Quickly defeat the robber leader
Ensuring the safety of hostages
At the same time, a comprehensive sweep inside and outside was launched
It sounds good, but
How do you plan to convey internal information?
The body search must be very rigorous
This is a wireless transmission function
Glasses camera
Don't let me drop the chain
I don't want to see anyone get shot again.
What are you looking at?
Wear masks now
Even though it's a fake gun, just give it to me.
You won't be angry with me, will you?
You know it was forced by the situation.
fine
I blame myself for believing the liar
Are you worried about something?
The monitor is out.
How do you feel about going there?
Nothing, just thinking
Will the police play some shady tricks again?
We kept you here just to prevent this kind of situation.
So look carefully.
Yeah, it should be
That's right
Put your stuff on the security check table
Open your arms and take three steps forward
(Occupy the Banknote Printing Bureau for 53 hours)
There are reports that gunshots were heard at the Banknote Printing Bureau
Just before this, the photography team used a telephoto camera
Capture the scene of the medical team entering the Banknote Printing Bureau
The police only repeated that the situation was "urgent".
No position has been expressed on this
Is the injured person a hostage?
Was it the robbers?
The situation is worrying
Just a moment!
Among them are police officers
See what I said? Which guy?
Tall man with glasses
I'm sure I've seen him in the opposition group.
Damn bastards
I shot the hostage by mistake.
Kindly ask them to come for treatment
The result was a stab in the back?
Is it too late to regret now?
Why regret?
This is a good opportunity to catch the police together.
Listen, they won't just
Take the risk with the inside scoop
To find out what they are planning
Please store your personal belongings here before leaving.
No objection?
Stop for a moment
Since the inspection must be done seriously
All back to original position
Raise your hands and turn back
Go inside
Entrance passed
A long queue of people wearing masks in the hall
Judging from the number of people, there should be a lot of hostages among them.
We dive in now
Is it okay to just let the police in like this?
What does the professor say?
- Ask us to sweep them into a hornet's nest
-ah?
Aren't jokes funny?
Are you kidding?
Want to change your career?
Even if they are all special forces
There won't be a head-on confrontation.
So I'm going to try it out.
See what they're up to.
I can do it with medical forceps in one go
Medical…
Oh, I mean pass the pliers.
how's it going?
Is there any hope for our comrade director?
Although the bullet is stuck in the pectoralis major
Fortunately, there is no danger to life
How long will it take?
-About two hours...
-It'll be done within an hour
Could that guy be the professor?
No, he has a Pyeongan accent.
The tone is obviously different
The real professor should be watching this somewhere.
scalpel
Give me any one
Wait a minute
Can you perform the surgery if you're shaking like this?
You get out of the way
Come on, I see you're the only one who's not shaking.
You seem to be quite courageous. Aren't you afraid?
Most people would tremble if a gun was pointed at them like this.
My reaction is slow
Do you have a cultural accent?
I have never heard of Ping An revealing the male nurse
Who are you?
- I think I was discovered.
-What?
What should I do?
actually…
- I'm a police officer
-What?
I just want to make sure
The medical team came in for their personal safety.
No other intention
I'm sorry for hiding my identity.
But from the perspective of the authorities
If you are not sure, just send the civilians in.
Is the plan scrapped now that it's like this?
I think it was Captain Che Wuhe who used his ultimate move.
The role played by Captain Che
It's a feint strategy to prevent the robbers from noticing our attack.
That guy finally told the truth.
Berlin is pretty scary, isn't it?
It's too early to let your guard down
Based on what I observed from the opposing team
He is clearly not an ordinary police officer.
This will attract the attention of the robbers.
All will be focused on him alone
Can you guys, the undercover team, arrive at the cafeteria as expected?
Protecting civilians? You want me to believe that?
If only a medical team is sent in
They were also held hostage.
How embarrassing would that be for the authorities?
so what?
What can you do if you come in here alone and unarmed?
If a medical team becomes hostage
The higher-ups told me to blend in with the hostages.
It's quite like that.
OK
It is important to save our director first.
Denver, you're in charge of keeping an eye on this guy.
Yeah, got it.
Hey police, back off!
Arriving at the destination
keep going
What takes so long?
The man named Denver
Is that your son?
That kid is actually not a bad person.
He just met a useless father.
So
If you want to blame someone
Just blame me
It doesn't matter
I told him to shoot.
I looked around and didn't find anything wrong?
Could it be that the guy was telling the truth?
I feel like something is fishy but I can't tell what it is
I said professor
if
Berlin did not execute hostages.
No
If the hostage is still alive
Things won't develop to this point, right?
It should be
Why do you ask?
nothing
Arrived at the target location and wait for attack
Then sew it up and it's over.
Is that so?
As for you, comrades, you can stay if you want.
I'll leave when the surgery is over.
So that’s all done, right?
I'll help sort it out.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Oh, really
- There are changes
-What?
In those glasses
Is it possible that there is something hidden?
There may be eavesdropping devices or even cameras.
If they want to pass on the inside information
There is only one reason
Feint Strategy
I'm sorry just now
One of the robbers left the room first.
Could it be that he discovered it?
Even if you find out something, it's too late
It’s time
We're going to attack
While that policeman is distracting us
There must be enemies sneaking in from other places.
How is that possible?
Didn’t see anything in the surveillance?
Maybe there is a path we don't know about.
What should I do then?
Keep calm and listen
come out
Follow me
What's all the fuss about?
Oh this one?
We changed our mood
What do you think?
Thank you to the hard-working medical team.
Everyone applaud!
Oops
Can't attack and retreat
Huh? We've already infiltrated.
They changed their masks and you will be exposed if you go in.
Stop planning!
Withdraw quickly!
knew
The feint strategy was exposed
They will find you even if they turn the house upside down.
Hurry up and seize the time!
how's it going?
All possible infiltration routes have been checked.
No problem
here you go
What about the Trojan horse?
It's packed and sent back.
pretty
After the professor saw through the feint strategy
Immediately counterattacked
When the situation is at a stalemate
The enemy will find a chance to sneak in.
Like a Trojan horse, it sneaked into the Bureau of Printing
Oh, that one?
I know
- Brad Pitt
- I've seen it too.
Uneducated guys
-What?
-What's wrong?
All we need to do is to find them and deport them?
That's right
But it doesn’t stop there
What else?
We arrested all those policemen.
How about being a hostage?
No
We have to take advantage of the situation
Start from this link
The success or failure of our plan depends on you, Rio.
(Finish)
The professor not only drove away the enemy
How to stab the enemy in the back?
When was our plan discovered?
Is it when I reveal my identity as a police officer?
Or before that?
No matter how smart the professor is,
How could he be so powerful?
I don't have an answer either.
All I know is…
The professor was standing over us and teasing us.
But when Officer Xuan realized this
The professor has taken control
Come on in!
Go Faster
Go quickly
Go fast
We still have time
There is a more important thing to solve
But will it be useless if I turn off my phone?
Oh, that phone can't be turned off.
Um?
I mean even if I turn off the power
It just looks like it's turned off.
In an undead zombie state
What the policeman said about his phone call
You can get the picture that the camera is facing
Oh, it's amazing.
What's that expression?
Did you run away without doing your homework?
It seems the anesthesia is taking effect.
Damn, why are my hands shaking so much?
Dad is bleeding
Please wipe it carefully!
I'm wiping it.
But what should I do if the bleeding can’t be stopped?
You should do it carefully!
Stop rushing me!
- This won't work.
-Um?
- I'll go get Rio.
-Rio?
Will the boy in Rio be obedient?
Drag him over here.
You try to stop the bleeding first.
Okay, I'll think of a way.
Oh, this blood
-Why won't the bleeding stop?
-Can be stopped
Hey, be careful.
Yingmin's surgery
how's it going?
Have you recovered?
What about Yingmin?
The operation went well
The doctor said he would recover soon.
You don't have to worry about him
So lucky
And I…
Am I going to die?
What are you talking about?
Tokyo just went to call someone who can perform surgery
Please bear with it
Good job
Hello, what are you doing?
Let go! What are you doing?
I'm having a serious conversation with Rio.
You're here, things are easier.
What did you say?
What else could it be?
You two know it but I don't.
What are we going to do in Tokyo?
Don't be unreasonable
Threatening hostages alone
That's not enough for you, is it?
I didn't expect you to confess.
But Rio will tell me, right?
If I threaten you and hand you over to the police
Dangerous person who always causes trouble
I can't just leave it alone, right?
Tie them up and throw them directly to the door of the Banknote Printing Bureau
The police will come and handle it.
This is going to be a good show
Can you do it?
What if I tell the police everything?
Can you? You won't.
You didn't come here for the money.
Anyway you hope
The professor's plan can be successful
Even if you get caught
What does that mean?
Well, let her tell you in person later.
Now that's not the point
I just said
Handing Tokyo over to the police is no joke
Did you pass the note to him?
yes
It was given
What did Yingmin say?
He...
She cried so hard and said she was very lucky
And said he loves you
What else did you say?
He said, "Once you get out of here
I will treat you well forever" and so on.
-It seems it's finally here
-Oh, Tokyo is here?
Hey, hurry up.
Fuck it
I thought we had a good understanding.
I am so disappointed.
In the end, I still have to do it myself?
Is what Berlin said true?
You don't join for the money.
I am more worried about whether the plan will succeed than whether I will be caught.
What is going on?
Do you really
In love with the professor?
What time is it?
What do you know, little brat?
Hello
You've had enough of this.
If this woman were alive
Killing a chicken to scare the monkeys won't work.
Scare everyone by saying he killed someone
It turned out not to be true
What will the hostages take our words for granted?
-Berlin!
-Fuck you.
You shoot me and you think you can get away with it?
I have to shoot her.
Just need you to get out of the way
What?
I didn't hear clearly, huh?
I count to three
one
If the professor knew about this, he would definitely not let you go.
I really can't figure it out
What is your reason for doing this?
What unusual sparks have been created in the past two days?
Because I feel guilty towards her.
-two
- Feed us...
-three
- Not in Berlin!
That's it.
Put down your guns Oslo you too
You are all so mean!
That is…
etc.
I have sharp eyes.
I remember you were on my side.
You're too much.
You have to kill a living person.
How can I join you?
She seems to be almost finished without my help.
-What's wrong?
-Why is this happening?
- Do something?
- You calm down.
What's wrong with her?
Rio
If you don't help she's going to die.
It can't be me...
I'll do the surgery.
Dad, please do something, don't faint.
Don't treat me like a kid.
You might as well just run away.
Wasn't it you who caught me?
Everyone including that bastard in Berlin
They're risking their lives here.
Whether it's for money or something else
Everyone has a good reason
But you said you were stuck here because you couldn't escape?
Those who say this are brats.
I'll come
Are you afraid of blood?
I have been vomiting and fainting when I see blood since I was a child.
Then why go to medical school?
It was planned from the moment I was born.
Our family has been doctors for generations.
You have this problem
Doesn’t your dad know?
Are you talking about my antiques?
He knew that and still sent me to medical school
He said I was weak-willed.
Not working hard enough
I really tried my best to disappoint him.
He just won't let go of his obsession
He's going to be extremely disappointed now.
That's what I mean
My identity has been exposed.
My antique saw...
But I...
Now I don't want to mess around anymore.
I thought about it
so far
I've been thinking about how to embarrass my dad.
There's nothing I really want to do.
So you have it now?
If this plan succeeds
I want to buy a very beautiful island
Sounds good
Right?
I plan to live there
With you
I passed by
Hello
I mean it.
I want to be on that island
Living a secluded life with your loved ones
Is there anything wrong with this?
It's just a dream, it doesn't matter what you think
Are you awake?
Even if it's not the same blood type, as long as it's O type...
Because I'm type O, they said they can give me a blood transfusion.
Medicine is very advanced, right?
What you said before
They are all fake, right?
Which sentence?
No
That person
He never used that word when dating me.
Which one?
"Love"?
Oh shit
sorry
I was going to give him the note.
But everything went haywire halfway through
It doesn't matter. I've always come this way.
That bastard was just before the surgery.
He yelled that he wanted to see his wife and children.
Honestly, I can't stand it.
But on the other hand, I can understand
Before a person dies
I suddenly miss some people like this.
But
I suddenly thought
If it's my turn to face this situation
Who will I miss then?
If you want to talk, it's my dad?
If I go ahead of him
But I'm afraid he'll kill me.
So I can't see him
Just go quietly by yourself.
Our old man is so strong.
Thank you
Saved my life
Oh, really
OK
You said Yoon Mi-sun is still alive?
Look at the lounge.
Well done indeed.
From now on, you will be in charge of the on-site command in Tokyo
What should be done with Berlin?
Let him answer the phone
You should understand why I do this.
I understand it, but it doesn't mean I agree with it.
You should know
Breaking the rules has a price
Want to control
Severe punishment is essential
I hope you understand
So what is the punishment?
Your gun will be confiscated.
and detained until I deem fit
I'm sorry for calling you a liar.
What? I'm a liar.
Enjoy yourself while you still have time.
Banknote Printing Bureau Hostage Incident
It started to turn into an extreme bloody incident
According to our reporter's on-site investigation
The person shot and wounded by the police this afternoon
Not a robber
Mr. Zhao Yingmin, Director of the Banknote Printing Bureau
This ridiculous incident
Because the police failed to distinguish between robbers and ordinary people
Foreign media also reported this extensively
This case has become an international joke.
The actual leader of the confrontation team
South Korea's negotiator
Officer Xuan Yuzhen seems to be responsible for this
Some people said that Officer Xuan was not
The best person to handle this case effectively
(Netizens demanded that the negotiation expert be replaced)
The key is the time when the robbers occupied the printing office.
Far exceeded expectations
The public attributed this to Officer Xuan's incompetent command.
This view is becoming the mainstream voice.
And there are claims
It is necessary to comprehensively rectify the North-South joint confrontation team
Even within the police
It is also necessary to significantly reduce the negotiating authority of Officer Xuan
- and changed to a hard line
-mom
-I'm back
-Oh, Xuan Yuzhen is back?
I'm hungry, is there any food?
Okay, I'll prepare it for you.
You obviously want to save people.
Those people are eager to kill people.
Don't mind these things.
-Where's Min-ah?
- Just fell asleep
Hey, look at my memory.
To put these in
What happened to you? Are you okay?
Wait, sorry, I have an important call.
Hello?
Stop the reporter! How can such news be broadcast?
There is also overseas media that are holding on to it and cannot be stopped
I'm worried about Officer Xuan Yuzhen. I haven't seen her for a long time.
Even if she stayed here, she would still be in a mess.
I told her to go home and rest for a while
She can't fall down after stirring up such a hornet's nest
Really
(Congress is concerned that the Bank of Printing incident will affect the summit)
Yuzhen
sorry
I…
I think I should apologize to you.
Today's Events
I saw it on the news.
without…
No big deal
There are always times when work doesn't go well
Then I'm leaving
Aren't you tired?
Live like this?
No matter what the rough police are facing
Or facing your family who can only rely on you
You can't appear tired.
Don't show weakness in front of them.
You have been holding on
That's why I can get to where I am today
No matter what someone says behind your back
Or her ex-husband, who has terrible character, gets elected president or something.
To protect my family
I can only be smarter than anyone else
Stronger than anyone
So on days like today
You have no place to complain, right?
-Sun Ho
- I see you are too tired
And I need someone to talk to
You can lend me your shoulder
Want to go in and have a cup of coffee?
Is there any wine?
Everything is as the professor expected
The State of the Banknote Printing Bureau Inside and Out
And Officer Xuan will come back to look for him
But there's one thing the professor hasn't expected.
Something that is about to happen that is beyond his expectations
Don't be lazy, come out quickly
He didn't expect his inner feelings.
Subtitles: Rita Huang