MISS NIGHT AND DAY
You.
You…
You're Sun, right?
Are you Sun?
Honey.
Wait a second, honey.
You're Sun, aren't you?
Right?
Sun.
You're her, aren't you?
Right, Sun?
See, honey! I told you Sun was alive.
She's standing right here alive.
She's not dead!
Sun.
Where have you been all this time?
Where were you?
You've been doing okay, right?
You came because you missed me,
but I didn't recognize you.
I kept kicking you out
and chasing you away.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
I'm not Aunt Sun.
I'm Mi-jin.
What are you talking about?
What is it?
Are you mad I didn't recognize you?
I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
I'm sorry, Sun.
My goodness.
Sun.
I'm so sorry.
Dad.
Mi-jin?
What?
You…
Where did Sun go? What?
Where did Sun go?
Mi-jin? Where's your aunt?
Your aunt.
Where?
Mom.
She can't come back anymore.
You saw it too.
Aunt Sun…
Let's put her to rest.
It's the only way
she'll be able to find peace.
Okay?
But Mi-jin…
Why are you…
Why?
Honey?
Mi-jin, why?
Why?
Why is my girl like this?
Wait, what is this?
What happened to my daughter?
My goodness!
Heavenly Father!
SEOHAN DISTRICT COURT
The defendant has admitted guilt
and shown remorse.
He has cooperated with investigations,
served the community for years,
and is currently in poor health.
Taking the kidnapping victim's
request for leniency
and other factors into account,
we hereby sentence the defendant
to three years in prison.
I was wondering if she would,
but I guess Ms. Lee isn't coming.
She won't be able to.
But she'll be at Gong Gi-cheol's trial.
What?
You didn't know?
Ms. Tak summoned her as a witness.
She'll have to submit
a witness absence statement.
Why? I guess it would be hard
for her to attend?
She has a reason
why she can't come during the day.
Did you hear?
Lee Mi-jin's attending
Gong Gi-cheol's trial.
I was curious.
What's so special about her?
Why would the great Gye Ji-ung
go to such lengths to protect her?
Wait, what's going on?
I have to do whatever I can
to return to my original state.
For me
and for my mom and dad.
Still, just in case,
I have to prepare.
MY BUCKET LIST
Number one.
-Mom, get up.
-Okay.
Take Mom and Dad to the hospital.
-Have them get medical check-ups.
-Me?
-We'll go if you're ready.
-Okay.
Number two.
Abstain from drinking.
Allow for drinking only once a week.
Or twice a week?
Yeah, twice a week!
Okay, ladies. Have fun with it!
-Left, right!
-Number three. Join a gym.
-It's to prevent rapid aging.
-Left!
-Just a little.
-Okay, all the way. Let's go!
One, two, three, four!
All right!
-See you next time!
-Great job!
Great work.
But what if I suddenly
get really old or sick?
What about my mom and dad?
Number four.
Take out an insurance policy.
Number five.
Just in case,
look into nursing homes.
Number six.
Do good deeds.
-There you go.
-Maybe volunteer to help abandoned cats?
I know it's a hassle,
but we have to clean our face.
Good kitty.
Look at your tail standing up!
Here's your food.
This cat looks just like me.
Look at its face.
It's you.
-Number seven.
-Careful, it'll burn!
Go on trips with my parents
while they're still healthy.
-That's hot!
-It's good!
Have some meat now.
-Sweet and salty!
-You'll rot your teeth!
-It's okay.
-Meat needs garlic.
It's so good.
One, two, three!
-Cheers!
-Number eight.
-Okay.
-Take lots of pictures.
-One, two, three.
Kisses! One, two, three.
Do it to Mom! Okay. One, two, three.
Wow!
I'll deliver this.
-Number nine.
-Okay!
Bye, Dad.
-Find something I can do.
-I need meat for stew.
-For a stew?
-Yes.
Business? Cleaning?
Thank you.
Or take mom's job?
Yeah, I did it.
And run her butcher's shop?
Do two of these make 600 grams?
It's a bit more.
-Okay, I'll take these two.
-These two?
Do you know what's scarier
than studying again?
It's having to face another situation
where I have to give up.
That's why I want you to do
something you like.
Whatever that may be,
even if it's not studying,
I want you to do what you love
and feel excited instead of being scared.
Yeah, I should do
what I really want to do.
Number ten.
Do what I really want to do.
Mi-jin, come and eat…
MY BUCKET LIST
Goodness.
Mi-jin!
Get up.
What are you doing?
-Get up.
-But why?
We have somewhere to go.
-Go where?
-Come on!
Mom, what's wrong with you?
-Where are we going?
-I said come on!
Tell me first!
There's a skilled shaman
at the foot of Obongsan. Let's go.
Jeez, I've already tried it!
I tried everything!
Jeez! No matter what I do,
it doesn't work!
That shaman said,
"Show me, show me, show me."
But he didn't see anything
and couldn't fix me!
Skilled, my foot! I won't go.
So you're going to keep living like this?
You said you're getting older!
What if you become older than me?
How are you going to live then? How?
What do you think?
I'll just live with you two until I die.
Why would you die, you brat?
Is that why you wrote all that
in your notebook?
The things to do before you die.
What was it? A bucket list?
That's just…
I could just end up
continuing to live like this.
I just wanted to prepare.
Why on earth would you live like that?
I mean, what do you want me to do?
Goodness.
This is driving me crazy.
-Seriously.
-My goodness!
This is ridiculous.
I'll get wrinkles if I cry.
What?
Goodness, I can't believe this.
Put some on.
But this is Mom's.
It's okay. I bought it.
-Here too.
-Okay.
That is a bit better.
You're slowly getting
more premature gray hairs.
They're not premature. They are grey.
-They are?
-I should dye my hair, right?
I have some!
-It needs to help prevent hair loss too.
-What?
Is this all-natural?
Probably.
-Jeez, you need to get reading glasses.
-What?
Can I borrow these, Mom?
These are comfortable
once you get used to them.
It is all-natural.
Good grief.
It would've been nice if it was brighter.
I think it's just black.
Whatever.
Can you do this for me?
Okay.
-I'm good at it.
-Here.
-Ga-yeong.
-I have so many grays now.
Sun…
I've been through so much.
Mi-jin is driving me crazy.
-If you'd told me…
-Can you take her away?
-Come on!
-Just come with me!
-For crying out loud!
-Come on!
Why are we here?
The culprit has been caught,
but you didn't change back.
You could be old like this forever.
You need to take care of yourself.
I can't afford it. I'm leaving.
-Come on!
-What's with you?
It was a two-for-one deal.
I already had mine done.
How's my radiant and dewy skin?
Want to try? Just once?
Two-for-one? Let's go!
This is to make up
for the scar under your chin.
That machine can really get rid of it?
Jeez, just trust me.
-Hello!
-Hello.
Goodness, your daughter
must care about you so much.
She made the reservation
and brought you here herself.
I'm leaving.
My goodness.
Please do it fast.
Okay. Ma'am!
This doesn't hurt at all. Calm down.
So…
-Goodness!
-Mom.
I'll do what I can
to drag Mi-jin around all day,
so no need to worry.
-Wow!
-It's so bright!
You look ten years younger!
-Really?
-Yeah, it's so cool!
What do you think?
But I'm already 29.
What's great
about looking ten years younger?
Come on.
Everything's on me today.
Okay? Just leave it to me.
Come with me. Let's go.
Let's go! It's all on me!
-Which one? This?
-The first one.
Okay, it's ready.
-Look here.
-Okay.
One, two, three.
-What's that?
-Smile. One, two, three.
Hey, you wanted to do it!
Wait!
TAKE PHOTOS HERE
Lady.
I'm not a lady!
Are you kidding me, lady?
I was born in 1996!
More like 1969!
Why did you push me?
You want me to call the cops?
Should we go?
-Okay.
-What do you want to eat?
I know a great place.
I'm hungry now after all that fun.
I recently found an amazing restaurant.
What is it?
What?
You want pig's trotters?
Let's not go here.
No, let's get chicken instead.
Mr. Chu
On my lips, chu
Sweetly, chu
I lose all strength in my body
You shake up my heart
You shake me up
I'm falling, falling for your love
Hey, you
On my lips, chu
What is it? What are you doing? Let's go.
I found a great chicken place recently.
They don't use sugar,
so their food's not sweet.
I told you everything was on me today.
This is the best part.
Can we not go in here?
Why not? This place is good!
You don't want to go?
Come on, let's go.
Damn.
You can have both drumsticks.
-Enjoy.
-It looks so good!
Eat up.
It looks so good.
No!
Babe!
Right.
What? I gave you both drumsticks.
Why are you so depressed?
To be honest,
I once came here when I was working.
I see. Damn it.
I picked the wrong place.
I didn't really know it back then.
Know what?
I didn't know
just how much
I liked that job.
But you know what?
I only realized after it was gone.
It's just like my youth.
What on earth?
Since when did you become an old soul?
Did you age emotionally too?
Thanks to you,
I know what I want to do now.
What is it?
It's good.
You're not going to tell me?
Then, give this back. Okay.
Goodness, he's back again.
Why does he look so thin?
That handsome face is wasting away.
-Stay here.
-What?
Go give this to him.
Tell him not to skip his meals.
-All right.
-Okay.
You don't have to visit.
I couldn't even if I wanted to.
I've been called up to Seoul.
Really? That's great.
Yes.
-Thank you for everything.
-Gosh, I didn't do anything.
-Take this.
-No.
-You don't have to.
-Stop.
You'll upset her. Just take it.
Please thank her for me.
Okay.
I'm almost home now.
I'll get going now.
-Mr. Gye!
-Yes?
Gosh, there are so many stars out tonight.
What's he looking at?
You know, the plum wine we made
fermented really well.
How about a glass?
I drove here.
-I'll go now--
-Wait!
There was something I wanted to tell you
one last time. Will you hear me out?
-Sure.
-The thing is you're always so busy.
I bet you can't work out much.
I want to teach you some stretches.
Try this. Follow me.
Put that down and try.
-Follow me.
-Okay.
To the left too.
Goodness, you're so stiff.
Grab my shoulders and press down.
Press harder!
Are you okay?
You're good. Should we try this too?
Now, stretch.
You have to pull too.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What are they doing?
Why are they exercising at night?
I don't believe this.
You must work out.
Yes, in my spare time.
Okay, then.
Right.
I'll be on my way now.
Wait… Well…
-Take care of yourself.
-I will, sir.
Goodbye.
Hey, drive safely.
-Okay.
-Yeah.
Is Mr. Gye leaving?
Damn it!
Goodness.
Dad, Mom!
What took you so long?
You said you'd come ages ago!
Stop it.
Jeez.
What's with him?
You should've come earlier, you brat.
But is it something
to get that angry about?
I don't know!
Jeez.
I'll be on my way now.
Hey, drive safely.
Hey…
Don't forget about me.
-Okay.
-All right.
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's do what needs to be done.
Do what needs to be done. I'll do that.
ADMINISTRATIVE LAW
CONSTITUTIONAL LAW
SEOHAN DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
It's so…
expensive.
LOCAL DEALS
SECONDHAND
You're not buying
secondhand couple rings, are you?
Rings from couples who break up
before three months are practically new.
But still, how could you buy
secondhand rings?
You know my current financial situation.
Then, get ones within your budget.
Why go overboard and get scammed again?
Then, to make up for that,
you'll be scammed again.
What's wrong with secondhand rings?
If you look carefully,
new and unopened ones suddenly…
Holy cow!
WEDDING RINGS IMPORTED FROM US
800,000 WON
If you buy this,
you're hitting the jackpot.
A Cartier at this price
is pretty much a steal.
They're practically new.
They're not "practically new."
They are new.
How long were they worn for?
Honestly, they were never worn.
We broke up on the first day.
-I might jinx it.
-But we got back together.
You should wear them then.
My business became really successful
after we got back together.
So I got
four-carat diamond rings instead.
Really sparkly, right?
Wow.
That's absolutely incredible.
I see.
But if you look at them closely,
I see some fine scratches.
Where? I can't see them.
No, right there.
It's about 0.2 millimeters long.
-I'll give you a discount then.
-Yes, of course.
-How much?
-Okay, I'll take 5,000 won off.
That's all?
Plus another 5,000 won,
so a 10,000-won discount.
Thank you. I'll transfer the money now.
-Quickly.
-Okay.
I knew this would happen.
Mr. Gye.
Long time no see.
What are you doing here, sir?
I should ask the same for you.
Where do you think you're going?
My hair. Wait.
-You'll pull it out.
-Come peacefully.
Last time was our first meeting,
so it took ten minutes.
Since we're already familiar,
let's make it quick. Get up.
I can't believe this!
Was this an undercover operation?
What's going on? Do you know him?
He has seven prior fraud convictions…
Wait, is it eight now?
Gosh, I'm dying.
How could someone like him
get out so fast?
Fraud?
Fraud? You punk!
-Fraud?
-Jeez, come on.
-Goodness.
-You punk!
Hey, you punk!
I could sue for assault, you know.
How dare you scam me?
Hello, Detective Kwon.
I caught a perp on scene.
Can you pick him up?
Come here!
Get over here!
Hey! Come here!
I got you! Come here!
Just don't do anything from now on.
How do you get scammed so often?
I'm not bad for being scammed.
It's the fraud who's bad.
If you were scammed once,
you should be more careful.
Why would you dive
straight into a mess like that?
It was clearly a scam.
How do you fall for that?
For goodness' sake.
Pull over by the station over there.
Why? Are you going to stay
at a bathhouse again?
Why would you care?
Here.
What's this?
I mean, it's not much.
GIFT CERTIFICATE
HANDONG
Mr. Gye!
Mr. Gye, I love you!
-I love you!
-Get off!
I said I love you!
Go away! It's too hot for this.
Wow.
It's a farewell gift.
What do you mean "farewell"?
Farewell? What are you talking about?
Did you think if you gave me this,
I'd happily say goodbye? Did you?
Where are you going without me? Where?
How was it?
This is great.
-So pretty. Okay.
-Take it like this.
You didn't discuss it with me at all,
so tell me now.
Where are you going? You can tell me!
Tell me! This is so frustrating!
Where are you going without me?
Why? Why are you leaving?
Don't go! Please, don't go!
I'm right here!
Seriously.
What do you think?
Hey!
I hated being young.
People think you can
do anything if you're young,
but there are so many things you can't do.
I would've rather given up my youth.
But it wasn't until after I'd lost it
that I realized.
My youth was a gift.
The time we take for granted
never lasts forever.
This came out well too.
Look at this.
How's this?
-This is good.
-It's great.
Right?
What?
I'm leaving.
You're leaving now?
Yeah.
I feel so strange.
I thought I'd be happy.
Didn't you want me gone?
I did, but…
I'm kind of at a loss
of what to do without you now.
Just do what you've been doing.
You made everything I did happen.
I was able to do it because of you.
I could've never done it on my own.
You know,
I understand how you feel.
But you're wrong.
You were able to do it because it was you.
Only you could've done it.
You're me.
You were a gift to me.
But the thing is…
you always had that gift.
You just realized it a little late.
You know, being old…
was really sad.
Work as much as you can.
Have fun and meet lots of people.
You can fall in love too.
But it'd be so nice to do it
when you're younger.
That's what I think.
You're young.
You should do
everything you want to do in life, right?
Do you think
I can be brave again
without you?
You already are.
I'll go now.
Goodbye.
Your move isn't for a while.
But you're packing already?
It seems like you wish I'd leave sooner.
Of course not.
Your eyes look sad, but you're smiling.
That's a misunderstanding.
Yeah, right.
I'll be living here
until the end of your contract,
so I'm very grateful,
and I feel at ease moving in.
But you're really just going to leave?
It was a sudden transfer.
I had no choice. The case is over too.
No, not that.
Just let me know how she's doing.
Ask Ga-yeong about her.
You took good care of it.
We will begin witness examinations.
Witness, please step forward.
SEOHAN CITY SERIAL MURDER CASE
DEFENDANT
Is the witness not here yet?
The witness will be here.
Please give her a bit more time.
If the witness cannot attend…
At the abandoned house where the defendant
imprisoned Lee Mi-jin, we found…
drugs made from poppy extract,
the weapon used to commit the crimes,
and…
the victims' remains.
The prosecution rests.
WITNESS STAND
Does the defense have
any additional questions for the witness?
I didn't intend to kill them.
They brought about their own deaths.
I said I just happened to kill them.
The statute of limitations
for the murder of my aunt…
and the other victims have expired.
But the pain
that families have felt for years,
not knowing the fate of their loved ones
who suddenly disappeared, still remains.
Your Honor,
as a relative of the victim
and as a victim
who was almost killed by the defendant,
I hope the defendant
will be severely punished.
-Stop looking for him.
-What?
You keep looking around
for Mr. Gye in case he shows up.
I guess Mr. Ju isn't here yet.
Yeah, because it's not his case.
Right.
He's very busy too.
It's about Mr. Gye.
He's going back to Seoul.
Hey, they're starting.
All rise.
Verdict for criminal case number 2024-317.
On October 15, 2024,
the defendant brutally killed
the victim Na Ok-hui
by striking her several times with an axe.
In addition, the defendant
murdered a witness to this crime,
the victim Ko Na-heun
by severing his ankle
and throwing him into a reservoir.
Past crimes cannot be punished
due to expired statute of limitations.
But the murders of Na Ok-hui
and Ko Na-heun,
the kidnapping
and imprisonment of Lee Hak-chan,
and the kidnapping, imprisonment,
and attempted murder of Lee Mi-jin
are inhumane crimes
that cannot be tolerated.
Despite this, the defendant shows
no remorse for her crimes
and was deemed to be
a high risk of reoffending.
Above all, the victims and their families
have requested severe punishment.
Therefore, the defendant
must be permanently removed from society.
The court sentences
the defendant to death.
All rise.
Death?
I'm going to appeal!
You bastards!
I'll sue you all!
Let go! Let go of me.
You damn beast!
You call yourself a human being?
You killed my sister
and tried to kill my daughter too?
Death is too good for you
and Hell wouldn't be enough.
You damn devil.
You better wait in Hell for me.
I'm going to chase you down,
and I'll tear you to pieces!
See you in Hell.
You'll never be forgiven even in death!
Sun!
My poor sister!
Mom.
Ms. Lim left, and you're leaving too.
I'll be all alone here.
I'll make a recommendation
for you when I get there.
Why would you do that?
Mr. Gye.
You did a great job.
Thank you, sir.
Hearing that you're leaving
is so refreshing. I mean…
It's sad.
For a talented prosecutor like Gye Ji-ung,
he belongs in the big leagues, not here.
For sure.
I'll get going.
All right.
Good work.
No need to see me out.
PROSECUTOR GYE JI-UNG
Gosh, that's good!
Here.
-It tastes so good.
-Nice!
-I brought more. Eat up.
-Wow!
Thank you for the food.
It's good.
-By the way, Mi-jin.
-Yes?
I hear you're quitting
your environmental public service job.
What are you going to do now?
Dad, do you want to be dragged out again?
-Eat up.
-I mean…
What if she tries to prepare
for the civil service exam again?
I just said it since I was worried.
I am going to start again.
Start what?
Studying for exams.
So you've been going out every night
to study for the civil service exams?
I was going to tell you after I'd passed.
But I don't know when that'll be.
Are you crazy?
I'm sick of hearing about civil servants.
-Don't even dream of it.
-You wanted me to be a civil servant.
But what I'm studying for
is what I really want to be.
There's something I really want to do.
That's why I want to start again
and do it properly.
Even if I fail, I won't regret it.
Okay?
Goodness.
Cheers!
Okay!
Yeah, cheers!
What's with you all?
Come on, Mom!
Don't be like that.
We're missing someone's glass.
Jeez. Whatever. I don't care anymore.
Jeez!
-Good luck!
-Good luck, Mi-jin!
-How refreshing!
-It's so good!
-I'll do my best.
-You better, you brat.
Don't worry, okay?
-Take some meat when you go.
-Mom, wrap this for me.
Don't be ridiculous!
But your shop gave away pork shoulder!
-Jeez! You're drunk!
-Gosh, be quiet!
-I think your dad needs to go home.
-Dad.
Come on, Dad.
I've already had three shots.
SEOHAN DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
Okay, you may now begin your work.
If you have questions, ask your superiors.
Good luck.
-Have a nice day, ma'am.
-Have a good day.
Let's see here.
It looks like everyone's in uniform.
-So follow me.
-Okay.
I heard a legendary intern
used to be here.
Yes, there was!
The legendary intern!
-Her name was Lim Sun.
-That's right.
-Really?
-She was amazing.
She threw herself into harm's way!
She stopped a terrorist attack!
-A terrorist attack?
-She helped catch a serial killer too.
-The rumors were true.
-Stop exaggerating.
What?
Are you writing a biography?
I'm saying there's a reason why
the term "Senior Avengers" exists.
Where is she now though?
I don't know.
I want to know too.
I wonder where she is
and what she's doing.
Before resuming activities
after your military service,
we wanted to know why
you're releasing a single album first.
I wanted to communicate through my music
rather than show my appearance.
I took such a long break,
so I was itching to work again.
Your fans are especially interested
in the first track.
They want to know if it's based
on a real romantic experience?
The lyrics are so poignant.
Ko Won,
having someone as remarkable as you
be my friend and supporter
reassured me so much.
But things aren't over between him and me.
I'm trying really hard
to be close to him again.
Well…
I have no comment on that.
I'll keep your secret.
Ma'am…
You kept my secret too.
You know too many vitamins
can make you sick too, right?
I'll get you an iced coffee
every morning. Deal?
That's cold!
Everything you say is so typical…
but it's nice.
Thanks for being Ko Won's fan.
And I hope you continue to support him.
It's a precious memory
I want to keep to myself.
Wow!
It looks so good.
If it's for you, I can do anything.
But is today a special day?
I tried so hard to think,
but I have no idea what this day is.
To be honest, today…
I'm celebrating
the early repayment of my loan.
So you… paid off all of your debts?
Yes, finally.
You've worked so hard for that.
Congratulations!
So to celebrate the early repayment,
I've prepared something.
-What is it?
-Wait just a moment.
Let's see.
Where was it again?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Where is it?
What?
What's this?
What? What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Ga-yeong, please accept this.
I can't take it.
I see…
-It's okay.
-So help me put it on.
Do it for me.
Wow.
It's so pretty.
You're even prettier.
-Can I take a picture?
-Yes.
How's Mi-jin? Is she doing well?
Yes.
She's preparing
for the third round of exams.
Already?
Wow, that's incredible.
She passed the first two rounds in one go.
But I'm a little worried.
She always does well and then slips.
How?
On the day before her Grade 7
civil service exam, her appendix burst.
She had a car accident the next year,
so she couldn't make it.
Everything,
from shingles to kidney stones.
They're all actually stress-related.
It's the pressure of having to pass
and a type of mental anxiety.
But who knows this time?
She has a clear goal now.
A goal?
Well…
How's Mr. Gye doing?
I see.
Yes, he's the same as always.
They looked so good together.
Just like us.
Gosh.
Stop it.
SIX MONTHS LATER
You don't feel it?
-Feel what?
-Where was it?
Seohan? Seohyang?
-Seohan District?
-Yeah, that's it.
Since returning, you've been persistently
poking your nose in everything.
Working hard at my job is a problem?
No, doing it needlessly well is a problem.
Don't overdo it.
If it's not for personal gain,
you'll be called a sociopath.
Hey, they're here.
This year's top investigator hire.
A new Grade 7 recruit
was assigned to my office.
She's totally my type.
A woman with a sexy mind.
She wrote a statement in five minutes
and organized supplies and receipts
in Excel sheets as soon as she came in.
It's like she's done it before.
It's all done.
I'll make a formula that will manage
the supplies efficiently.
There's someone else who's that good?
Yeah.
Are there seats?
It's the prosecutor I called dibs on.
Incredible, right?
Ms. Lee, over here.
Okay.
Hello.
Take a seat.
Okay.
She's incredible.
We studied together before,
and she was hired as a recruit.
She bombed the Grade 9 exam back then.
What are you talking about?
But I'd say that created an opportunity.
Yeah, it did.
What are you doing this weekend?
I have tickets to the Coolplay concert.
How did you get those?
I really wanted to go.
Can you sell them to me?
Want to go with me?
No, I have plans.
What plans?
I'm seeing someone I like.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Do you have a boyfriend?
Me?
PROSECUTOR YOON BAK
By any chance, do you like pasta?
Let's end work early today
and go to the new pasta place nearby.
I usually try to avoid working late.
How is eating dinner
the same as working late?
That hurts my feelings.
I bought the concert tickets.
Want to go with me?
I usually try to avoid
working on weekends.
You're so funny.
Working on weekends?
I'm asking you out on a date.
I usually try to avoid dating coworkers.
Then, what am I supposed to do?
I usually don't pay premiums
on concert tickets,
but I made an exception--
You didn't really pay a premium, did you?
Is one of our nation's prosecutors
violating the Minor Offenses Act?
And did I just witness that?
I can't report a colleague though.
-What should I do?
-Stop it.
You should be leading by example,
not scalping tickets.
Our department head will…
Wait, was that the reason?
He asked for you.
-You should go.
-Hey!
Why are you telling me this now? Jeez!
Because I just got here.
What's Coolplay anyway?
Did you need something?
No, not really.
I was curious about something.
Why do you hate dating coworkers?
I never said I hated it.
You just said you hated dating coworkers.
Yes, because he asked me,
but it depends on who is asking.
Right?
So you were just turning him down, right?
I mean…
To be honest,
it's been so long…
-My gosh!
-My hand!
Why would you touch that?
-Does it really hurt?
-Yes.
-Should I stop?
-No, it's fine.
Gosh, what if this leaves a scar?
Why did you pretend
to not know me back there?
Because you did it first.
It's not because you have a boyfriend
and felt uncomfortable, is it?
I said I had a boyfriend?
You didn't say you didn't.
But you said there's someone you like.
I do.
She's right in front of me.
-I don't have one.
-What?
I don't have a boyfriend.
People will look!
What if someone sees us?
Who cares? No one's around.
Do you know how hard it's been for me?
Do you know how long I waited?
I missed you so much.
I really did.
Tomorrow's Saturday.
Should we go on a date at night?
Why at night?
We can't meet during the day.
It's daytime right now.
-You're right!
-What's with you?
What happened?
We can see each other during the day now?
It just happened.
But how? All of a sudden?
I know. It was sudden.
For no reason at all?
Mr. Gye!
What was that?
Did you hear that?
No, I didn't hear anything.
What did you hear?
It looks like you heard something too.
I didn't hear anything.
-Are you okay? Are you hearing things?
-How strange.
Gosh, the weather's so nice.
It really is nice.
What's nice?
MISS NIGHT AND DAY
SPECIAL THANKS TO YOON BAK
Subtitle translation by: Sue Mounce