[HEART BEATING]
[JARED] Coach,
Uno shouldn't be in this team.
- [LARRY] Okay, why?
- [JARED] ‘Cause he has a
temper.
[PARKER] Barbie! I knew it!
What a wimp. Noob!
[JARED] As a senior member
of this team,
I think I know
what's best for us.
[LARRY] You never win...
because you lack discipline,
focus, and frankly, skills.
Because you're too caught up
in the flair.
You prioritize your arrogance
and create drama
just to mask your weaknesses.
Being an athlete
doesn't stop when practice ends.
It's your first day,
and you're already late.
You have to serve a punishment.
[PARKER] Mr. Volleyball!
You're finally
where you truly belong!
With the effeminate gays!
[LARRY] You still have something
to say to me, Jared?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I quit!
- [DIAMOND] Wait, what?
- [KIDLAT] Girl, calm down.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BELL DINGS]
- [CARMEN] That's it!
Ciao!
I'll see you next time!
[BELL DINGS]
[CARMEN HUFFS, SIGHS LOUDLY]
Ma, let's eat.
Give me five minutes.
It takes a lot of energy
to keep talking.
- [CARMEN HUFFS]
- I've told you lots of times.
You don't have
to keep live selling.
Son,
I just want to save up.
Ma.
I'm not going
to quit volleyball,
if that's what you're
worried about.
I'm not worried.
It's just that.
I know your true passion
is basketball.
How's it going with volleyball?
I'm struggling with training.
I'm finding it hard to adjust.
My teammates don't like me.
Really? Why?
I don't...
I don't really
get along with them.
Wait, I don't understand.
You get along with everybody.
You're very friendly.
Sure, you have a temper,
but you've never had
trouble making friends.
You even made friends
with those bums outside.
Ma, it's just that.
my teammates are all... gay.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
So?
Uh--
They think differently.
They talk differently.
I don't get their humor.
And they're mean to me.
They're irritable towards me.
It's like I can't do anything
right with them.
And since I joined
the volleyball team,
people have been teasing me
that I'm gay.
- Are you gay?
- Of course not.
Why are you defensive?
Would it make
you less of a person
if people thought you were gay?
And if you're not gay,
why would you be offended?
It doesn't matter
if people think you're gay.
All that matters is
you know yourself
and you're not hurting anyone.
Remember that.
I don't know, Ma.
I don't know how
to handle their teasing.
Uno,
if you won't take
volleyball seriously
just because you're worried
about your reputation
and masculinity,
then you should just quit.
Stop going to trainings.
I can now pay for your tuition.
My live selling is taking off.
I have so many followers.
And I'll be promoted to
team leader at the call center.
Anyway, you should
be ashamed for
feeling that way
about your teammates.
If I were your teammate,
I'd be pissed at you too.
I would be annoyed
by your presence as well.
Let me remind you.
When you were the captain ball
of the basketball team,
you found it irritating
whenever people joined the team
just to be cool.
Imagine how your
teammates,
who are so passionate
about volleyball, feel.
If you want to continue
playing varsity volleyball,
Uno,
I suggest you commit to
and embrace it.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Let's just eat, Ma.
[SIGHS LOUDLY]
Live selling is exhausting.
But I have so many followers.
[CHUCKLES] I'll be famous.
["BUGHAW" BY MAKING PLAYING]
[KNOCKING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[FARRAH] Cuz?
I cooked some pork stew for you.
I know you can't resist it.
Come on. Have some.
I'll get in trouble with
your mom if you don't eat.
You told her?
Of course not.
But you have to eat
so she won't suspect
that you quit volleyball.
Tsk.
[UTENSIL CLINKS]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- Cuz.
- Yes?
Do you also think I'm not
good enough to play volleyball?
No!
You're good.
But not as good as you?
Jared, we're different.
I know.
But...
When it comes to technique,
skill, speed, and strategy,
you're on another level.
You're my idol.
Can I be honest?
Yes, you lack discipline,
but you don't lack talent
and passion for the sport.
You're an amazing
volleyball player.
But Coach Larry also made some
good points that might help you.
You're taking
Coach Larry's side again.
No. There you go again.
I'm just saying...
Coach Larry has some good points
that would help you
and the team.
This pork stew is too salty.
Cuz, come on.
You're quitting just because
you were criticized?
That's petty.
- Want me to shave your head?
- Go!
By all means, shave my head.
But my cousin is not a quitter.
And I know
that you and Uno have history.
And what he did was...
disappointing.
But are you going
to give up something
that is so important to you
for someone
who doesn't matter to you?
Cuz, we have goals, right?
To be the next Alyssa Valdez.
Mm.
Hmm?
To be the next Olympians.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Your pork stew
doesn't taste good.
It's gotten bitter.
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know why?
Your face is bitter.
Wait 'til I shave your head.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Whatever, you're just hungry.
I'll leave so you can
finish your pork stew.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[BALL SMACKS]
Why can't you dig the ball?
One more time.
[SMACKS BALL]
That was a hard hit, Coach.
It wasn't hard enough.
Hey! Farrah!
Wait!
Fars,
are you mad at me?
Our training ends here.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Now I know why you
wanted to train with me.
You didn't want to be associated
with your teammates.
You think I don't notice?
Fars.
That's not true.
[FARRAH] Uno,
the queers that you shun
act like real men
more than you'll ever be.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Whatever being a man
truly means to you.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CLASS BELL RINGS]
[LARRY] Players,
I need your parents
to sign these.
Okay, please distribute.
Take one and pass.
Thank you.
Team building, Coach?
Yes, team building.
Before you become
great volleyball players,
you need to learn
how to be a team first.
So we'll know who among you
is good enough to join
the Juniors' V-League.
Coach, Jared didn't
come to school today.
He hasn't replied to any of
Ethan's messages as well.
[SIGHS]
Um...
Um, okay.
Sorry, guys.
Training is cancelled
for tonight.
You may go home.
Sorry. And thank you.
[GRUNTS]
Lucien, Diamond...
Kidlat, Ethan,
please stay.
We're going somewhere.
Uno!
You're coming with us.
Okay?
Where are we going?
Uh...
[CLEARS THROAT]
We're going to Jared's.
Coach?
Why do I have to go with you?
Yeah, Coach, why does
he have to go?
Well, we all know...
Jared has a problem
with you, right?
Coach,
with all due respect,
you're the one he's mad at.
He's angry after everything
you said last time.
Exactly!
But... you're not
that innocent, Uno.
I mean,
come to think of it,
you're the root of all--
Evil. I finished it for you.
Well, I was going
for conflicts, issues,
troubles, problems
conundrums, predicaments,
difficulty of situation.
- That's enough, Lucien.
- It's the same thing.
Santillan, you're coming
with us.
Coach, Jared and Farrah
live in the same house, right?
Why are you concerned
about that?
Yeah, what's the problem?
Nothing.
I just don't think
I should go with you.
You're going to talk
with Jared anyway.
As our Coach,
you are our representative.
You know what?
TBA... to be...
honest,
Uno has a point.
That's what I think.
You're overcomplicating things.
What do you want?
Do you want Jared to
come back to the team or not?
Of course we do, Coach.
That's a given.
Why, of course!
Yeah!
There is no team without Jared,
and we all know that.
There you go.
So, as one team,
we will convince him
to come back to the team.
Okay?
- Let's go!
- Okay.
Let's go, sisters!
- Let's win him back.
- Come on!
Alright, let's go!
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Coach?
- Oh!
- Shall we?
- Okay.
- Come on!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello.
Good evening.
- Good evening.
- Please come in.
You may wait for them inside.
This house is huge.
- What's Uno doing?
- They're rich.
[JARED] Promise me...
that nothing will change, okay?
I think I might be...
gay?
You like boys?
[JARED] I think?
Okay.
Okay?
Okay!
Come on!
Of course, it's okay!
- Really?
- Of course, it's okay!
[SCOFFS] No worries.
Wait, I just need to
go to the bathroom.
I really need to pee.
Don't cheat! Cheaters are
uncircumcised losers!
That's you!
Just wait there.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNO] Uh... Jared,
I have to go home.
Sorry.
Uh... my mom might
be looking for me.
I thought we were
going to keep playing?
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Yeah, but it's getting late.
My mom might be looking for me.
I should get going. Bye.
[JARED] Uh--
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[LARRY] Farrah.
Farrah, is Jared home?
I've sent for him, Coach.
How is he right now?
Well, he's been staying
in his room all day.
He's like that
when he's avoiding people.
Coach, are you okay?
Huh?
Me? Yes, I'm fine. Why?
Well, you look pale
and a bit sweaty.
[LARRY CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
No.
It's probably my jacket.
It makes me feel hot.
You're hot, Coach?
- But the AC is sterilized.
- You mean centralized.
Centralized?
- Centralized.
- Sorry.
It's fine.
Coach, just admit it.
You're nervous.
You're afraid of Jared,
aren't you?
[LARRY] I'm not afraid
of anyone, Ethan.
[ELLEN] Oh! [CHUCKLES]
- Ethan!
- [ETHAN] Hi, auntie!
- [ELLEN] Diamond!
- [DIAMOND] Hello!
Storm.
[KIDLAT] Hi, auntie!
[ELLEN] I'm so glad
you came to visit.
Lucien?!
You're back!
I am! Hi, auntie!
I'm so happy
you're back on the team.
I'm so happy, too.
I missed you, Auntie!
[GIGGLES]
Um... Auntie, this is
Coach Larry.
He's our new coach for the
boys' division volleyball team.
Hello. Good evening, ma'am.
Good evening, Coach.
Welcome to our home.
Jared didn't mention
that you're all coming here.
Are you the reason why my son
has been hiding in his room?
[CLEARS THROAT]
Uno!
Juan Paolo Santillan,
is that you?
[ELLEN CHUCKLES]
Auntie.
Oh my god!
You've gotten so tall!
And handsome, too!
[ELLEN CHUCKLES]
Wait, why are you with
the volleyball team?
I'm confused.
Auntie, I'm now part of
the volleyball team.
Aren't you part
of the basketball team?
Uh, not anymore.
Auntie...
You know Uno?
Of course!
He was Jared's
childhood best friend.
I wonder what happened
between you guys.
Wait,
didn't Jared tell you?
[JARED] No, Mom.
I didn't think it was
important to tell them.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
And the plot thickens.
Mom, please excuse us.
Stay for dinner.
I'll just have it prepared.
Mom, that won't be necessary.
They won't stay long.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Why are you all here?
Uh...
Jared, I have a consent form
for you.
This is for our team building.
Your parents
need to sign the form.
Team building?
Team building.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What part of "I quit"
don't you understand?
You quit volleyball, dear?
Mom. Please stop listening.
Please go back to the kitchen.
Jared, can we please
stop this madness?
Please?
I know we've had
our differences,
but that has never
been grounds for quitting.
I know I'm irritated
with you right now.
But I can set my feelings aside
because you're my captain.
You are my friend.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
And if I may add,
you talked to me.
You convinced me
to join again.
Jared,
I sacrificed a lot to be here.
To be back
in the volleyball team.
For what?
For you to leave me behind?
Oh please, Jared. For real.
Stop this tantrum.
So what now?
Come back...
Come back to the young
and beautiful you!
[LAUGHS]
You're so annoying.
Stop making us chase after you.
Are you a beauty queen?
[CLEARS THROAT] Coach.
It's your time to shine.
You first.
Coach, I have nothing
to do with this.
I've always been
on Jared's side.
Right?
Come on, Coach.
Um...
Jared.
If you really want to quit,
then it's fine.
But before you go,
give it a shot first.
Join us.
After that, if you really
don't want to stay,
if you really don't like me...
then it's okay for you to leave.
He'll join the
team building, Coach.
Dad!
Sorry. I overheard.
Your voices are echoing
inside the house.
And yes, he's coming.
And Farrah as well.
Farrah, you'll go with Jared.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Uncle...
I think the team building
is exclusive
to the boys' volleyball team
and Diamond.
Shouldn't the invitation extend
to the whole volleyball team,
Coach?
Farrah and her team
should join as well.
Right, Farrah?
It would be a shame
if the girls' team
missed out on the team building
and the training.
Farrah,
if you want,
I could ask Coach Conrad for you
and the girls' volleyball team.
How about it?
[PENSIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's okay, Coach.
Just give me the consent forms.
I'll take care of it.
I still haven't said yes.
And you haven't said no either.
My god, Dad!
Stop!
Jared!
You should come.
The team needs you.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Please.
I'll think about it.
Jared, let's have dinner!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, Uno!
Hey. What's up?
You packed a lot for one night.
I know!
I had to leave
my other luggage behind.
Our nanny couldn't go
with us after all.
You were going to bring
a nanny?
Yeah!
And it's better to be AP.
What's AP?
AP. Always prepared.
Seriously.
Can you help me
put these inside?
Thank you!
[LARRY] What is that?
[KIDLAT] Wait!
Coach, give me a minute.
Can you hold this?
Why did you bring a clock?
Because time is always
on my side, Coach.
I even brought
a bubble blower
to show my bubbly personality,
or something like that.
Coach, isn't my face card
enough?
No.
Our driver won't let you in.
Aah!
See? I told you it's there.
Thank you
for this kind of consent!
Is it signed?
It's signed by my parents.
- Okay, very good.
- Yes! Perfect!
Thank you.
- Okay, your stuff please.
- I'll get these, Coach.
Thank you so much!
[CHUCKLES]
I'll leave this one with you.
- Bye! Thank you.
- Thank you.
Consent form please.
Thank you.
Good. It's signed.
Good morning.
- Here you go, Coach.
- Hi, good morning.
Consent form signed, okay.
Very good.
Hi, thank you. Thank you.
Signed. Very good.
Signed? Yes, very good.
Signed by your parents?
Thank you.
Coach,
I need to use the restroom.
Okay. Be quick.
And here's mine, Coach.
- Wow, thank you.
- Signed by my mom, Lucy.
- Wow, very nice! Fur!
- You like it, huh?
- Yes! Thank you, Coach.
- It's my new look.
- I like it!
- Okay, thank you.
- [LUCIEN] Hi!
- [DIAMOND] Hi! Surprise!
[LAUGHTER]
- [LUCIEN] I know!
- [DIAMOND] Just a sec.
Coach, he's not here yet?
No.
I don't think he's coming.
I guess we have to go.
We might get stuck in traffic.
- I'll go inside.
- Okay.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Good morning.
Good morning!
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
Consent form. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Coach.
Thank you.
Uh... Coach, can I talk
to you?
Sure.
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
Me being here
doesn't mean I'm all in, Coach.
I know.
That's the deal, right?
You're going to give it a try.
You know what, Jared?
I'm not going anywhere.
I know that you
don't know me,
but I want to make
this work.
I know, Coach.
We've had a few coaches
in the past,
but none of them went to my
house to try and win me back.
You showed us how each one
of us is important to the team.
I respect that.
And that's the goal, isn't it?
To be different.
- So, are you good?
- You're a fast learner, Coach.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Yes, I'm good.
Also, I'm sorry
for being late.
And I'm sorry
for being harsh.
It's fine.
Come on.
Thank you, Coach.
- [BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
- [APPLAUSE, CHEERING]
I can feel that you're
genuinely happy.
Guess who's back.
Wait!
Let's make it
a group hug.
Welcome back!
- Are we okay?
- Yeah.
Alright.
Oops.
My god! You're still fighting?
Hmph. Switzerland.
Why do you keep
saying "Switzerland?"
Are you going on a world tour?
You are such drama queens.
Maybe I should knock some sense
into you.
I don't mean you, of course.
Come here.
Sit beside me.
I know it's my snacks
that you missed.
Of course! What do you have?
Clingy much?
[LARRY] Okay.
Good morning, everyone!
Team captains, are your
teams complete?
All accounted for?
Yes, Coach. We're complete.
Coach Conrad knows
that you're joining us, right?
Yes, Coach. He's just busy.
That's all.
- Jared, your team?
- Oh.
Coach, we're complete.
I think we should go so we
can avoid the traffic rush.
[LARRY] Okay, mister.
Let's go.
[UNO] Wait! Coach!
I'm here.
You almost got left behind.
Take your seat.
[LARRY] Okay. We're complete.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
I smell a new love tandem.
I think it's #FarNo.
Farrah and Uno!
Or maybe #UnAh?
Or #FarUn!
[BOTH LAUGH]
- No, URah!
- URah.
- URah!
- Rawr!
Shh. Sit down.
Quiet please.
[GROANS] This is going to be
an exasperating ride.
Exasperating?
[KIDLAT] Okay, guys.
Are you ready to go?
[CHEERING]
[KIDLAT] So, let's start
the car!
This is fun!
You know what
I'm talking about?
- Yay! Whoo!
- [CHEERING]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
Right this way.
- Tweet, tweet, tweet.
- [LAUGHTER]
Come on in! Come on in!
- [BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Let's go!
- Alright.
Okay. Welcome, Brixton
High School Volleyball Team!
Just a few reminders
while we're staying here.
The girls' dorm is up those
stairs on the right side.
It's up there.
The boys' room is
on the left side, okay?
Uh, Diamond, where do you want
to stay?
With the girls?
Or with your team?
With the boys.
It's okay if she stays
with us.
Stay with us, Diamond.
Yeah! You can stay with us!
And we can paint our nails pink
or whatever color you like.
Thanks, but I want to be
with my teammates.
But I'll drop by
so we can do our nails together.
- Okay! Promise?
- Mm-hmm.
Alright. Cool.
Once you've settled in,
we will have our lunch,
and then we'll
start our activities.
But we have some house rules.
Rule number one.
No cellphones.
Coach, no!
What?!
No cellphones, please.
- [QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[LARRY] Thank you. Thank you.
[SOFTLY] Please take care of it.
I have my crush's photos there.
Okay, I will get you
an extra pillow.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cellphones, please.
Coach? Can I not?
Sorry.
But...
Sorry, but you can't keep it.
Okay, fine.
Your other phone, please.
- Fine.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Coach! Why are you doing...
Why are you doing this to us?
How can I do my fierce reels?
No cellphones. Do you know
why we're doing this?
It's because we are here
to disconnect from the world
and connect with each other.
Well, Coach. I'm
connecting with someone.
He hasn't replied yet.
- Come on.
- Give it up.
- Rules are rules.
- There.
- Girls, your cellphones.
- Girls, please. Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Once you guys have settled in,
we will eat.
And then we will start
with our activities.
- Okay? Okay.
- Okay.
- Go!
- Go.
Okay. Go.
Get settled in.
Oh my god! I want the lower bed!
I want the top bed!
I want the one closest
to the outlet.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Our goal for this
team building is simple.
We want to build chemistry
and camaraderie
among each other
to be a team.
Chemistry, huh?
We know teamwork is
important to volleyball, right?
- Right, Coach!
- Yes.
For the first game,
the girls team
will be up against the
boys and Diamond.
The winner will get a prize.
- How much, Coach? Oh.
- Secret!
The losers will wash the dishes
for our entire stay.
- Um, no.
- We're not doing that.
- Rookies, you know what to do.
- We got this, guys.
Gentlemen first!
Let's go!
Ready!
Get set!
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
Go!
- Go, go, go!
- Stay calm.
- Hurry, hurry, hurry!
- I can do it.
Come on! Come on!
Silence please!
Oh my god, hurry up! Hurry up!
- I'm on it, sir!
- My goodness! Hurry up!
- Just wait, okay?
- You're overreacting.
- Okay. Calm down, everyone.
- Hurry up!
Don't yell at me!
I'm warning you.
Your head's too big
for the hoop.
Hey! That's a personal attack!
I'll make it personal
if you don't pass me the hoop.
- Hurry!
- Oh my god--
- There!
- He's shouting.
Hurry up! Use your voice!
Hurry up!
It's not that difficult!
Lucien, go!
Girl, bend your knees!
Hey! Hurry up!
Stop pressuring me!
It's not that hard, Lucien!
I don't want to ruin my hair!
- Go home, then!
- Go!
Macky, go! Focus!
- Go, go, go, Macky!
- Yes!
- Go, go!
- Yes! Yes!
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- Yay!
- Oh my god!
- [CHEERING]
- That was so easy!
- One minute!
Okay, it's the girls' turn.
Ready!
Go, girls!
- Get set!
- Go, Farsies!
- Just follow me.
- Go!
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Go!
- Go, go, go!
- Go, girls!
- Nice one!
Coach--
Faster.
- Yes!
- Last one! Last one!
Yay! [CHEERING]
- Three, two, one...
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
Brixton...
- Hawks!
12 seconds!
Oh my god!
Okay. Take it slow.
- Careful now.
- Ah!
I'll do it.
- What a diva. [LAUGHS]
- What?
Nothing.
Take it easy.
This is just a game, gays!
This is not just a game.
We have to beat
the girls' volleyball team.
Ready! On three.
One! I said on three!
- You pulled too hard.
- Hey, just relax.
[SNICKERS]
That's rich coming from you.
- I'm making an effort.
- Oh, wow.
Good job for trying.
Such an honor.
Hey, gays!
And Uno...
I don't want to lose, okay?
Let's do this.
Ready! Focus, please.
On three. One, two...
There... Easy does it.
- Careful now.
- Okay, okay, okay.
- There.
- Pull. Pull.
Ready!
- Get set!
- Move backwards.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
- Walk.
- Focus.
- Hurry.
- Okay, okay.
- Wait, wait.
Let's set aside
our issues for now.
Set aside your issues. Hurry up.
Stop making insinuations.
- Stop fighting!
- Got it? Can we do it?
Steph, Liv, Sinag,
take the lead.
- Steady, steady, steady.
- Wait.
Faster! The girls
are taking the lead.
Pull, pull.
- Yes, pull.
- Calm down.
Tighten your pull.
- Steady.
- Focus.
- Ah!
- Oh my!
- Whose fault is it anyway?
- Who else but the rookies?
- Wow!
- It's Jared!
Okay. Okay.
Go, go, go.
Hurry!
The girls are taking the lead!
Calm down!
- Go!
- Slowly.
- Wait, wait.
- To the left.
Move, move, move.
Be careful.
Go, go, go!
- Walk.
- Quickly now.
- Okay, okay.
- Slowly now.
There, there.
- Ah!
- Argh!
- Who was it?
- Let's not fight! Quickly!
- Look at the girls.
- Lucien!
Pull, pull, pull.
Almost there.
Okay, we got this. We got this.
Walk faster!
They're getting ahead.
My gosh! I'm sweating!
- Go, go! Two more steps.
- Two more!
Okay, okay, okay.
- Be careful.
- Faster. They're almost done.
Down, down, down.
- We can beat them!
- We can!
Slowly.
- Down!
- Okay.
- Yay!
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
Brixton...
- Hawks!
- Congratulations, girls!
- [APPLAUDING]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING]
[KIDLAT] It's over.
[LUCIEN] So, we lost again.
Jeez.
That was embarrassing.
[SIGHS]
We didn't win anything.
Not even one.
We always lose
volleyball games.
And we can't even win
team-building activities?
Don't get me wrong. I am not
disappointed that you guys lost.
I'm disappointed by how you
chose to solve your problems.
Coach, we get it.
But why are we the only ones
who are being punished?
[KIDLAT] Yeah, Coach. Why?
(In gay lingo) Agree-ana Grande.
This is so unfair, like...
I do not disturb this.
Let's be real.
You have issues to settle.
Finally!
Thank you for saying that
out loud, Coach.
And thanks for excluding us.
But...
don't you think you're also
part of the problem?
Me? [SNICKERS]
You want to join them, Lucien?
Ah-- Okay. I'll shut up.
Hmm. Yeah.
[SIGHS]
In volleyball,
you are always confronted
by this ball.
Coming from a serve
or a spike
that has to be confronted
by a receiver.
You have to set it
so the spiker can
confront the ball head-on.
And no matter how powerful
that spike is,
it can always be confronted
with a block.
Volleyball is very direct.
It thrives on communication.
If you hear someone
call out "Mine,"
you have to trust that
your teammate will receive it.
This isn't like basketball,
where you can pass the ball
to Kobe Bryant,
and he'd do it all himself.
He'd do a layup,
shoot it, miss,
rebound again,
layup one more time, miss,
and do it all
without anyone's help.
- Huh?
- I don't get it.
- What?
- In volleyball,
that will never work.
Let me remind you.
Confrontations don't have
to be aggressive all the time.
You have to talk it through.
You have to listen.
You have to trust.
Always remember.
Famous volleyball players
are not famous
because of their skills alone.
They are famous
because they are team players.
That is how you become
great volleyball players.
So...
talk about it.
Press the ball tightly
against your chest.
If the ball drops...
We get an additional hour.
Correct. Thank you.
Okay. Let's go.
Sorry, guys.
This is fun.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
What did we get ourselves into?
Is it alright for us to leave?
The mosquitoes are killing me.
What do you expect?
We're here for a retreat, but
you're dressed for a mall show.
[RAIN PATTERING]
[CLEARS THROAT]
So...
don't you have something
to say to me?
To you?
[KIDLAT] Shouldn't we be
the ones asking you that?
I have something to say.
Can you sort it out already?
I'm hungry.
We've been here for hours.
Fine.
I'm sorry.
There.
That sounded forced.
No.
I mean it.
I'm sorry.
- Because...
- [SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I let my pride and emotions
get the best of me.
You trusted me
to be your captain, but...
I let you down.
I'm sorry, too.
I didn't know...
that you and Uno
were best friends
and you had
unfinished business--
Ah... No.
That's done.
I was just being practical,
Jared.
- I know Uno can be a jerk--
- That's harsh.
No, no, no, no.
You can be a jerk.
You were a jerk to me.
- To us.
- [CLEARS THROAT]
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
When I first saw Uno spike,
I thought to myself,
"He can be a great asset
to the team."
I sensed that
he was just using us
to save his scholarship,
but maybe we can show him
what it means to be a team.
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
You made this team safe
for everyone, Jared.
Remember when I almost
got kicked out
for wearing the girls' uniform?
You said, "Hey, it's okay."
Then you invited me
to join the team.
You said, "Come train
with the volleyball team."
You said that the sport itself
and the players
are not going to judge me.
You promised me that even though
I still couldn't express myself,
you would call me by my name
and by my preferred pronouns.
Thank you for that.
I felt seen, heard,
and understood
as myself.
As Diamond.
But Jared,
people will never understand us
unless we let them in.
We have to invite them in. Okay?
[JARED] I'm scared.
If I let people in,
they might hurt us.
[DIAMOND] I know.
Oh, come on.
What are you afraid of?
You have us.
Silly.
I always have your back.
I'm sorry, sis.
But you slapped me so hard
I wanted to pull your hair out.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, fine.
(In gay lingo)
Let's stop fighting.
I admit it's my fault.
You're so fake!
Why don't you cry-ola some more?
Do I have to cry-ola
so we can be friends again?
- Through the rain.
- Through the fire?
- Through the end?
- [LAUGHTER]
Guys, I'm sorry, but...
what are you talking about?
- [THUNDER RUMBLING]
- [LAUGHTER]
- Sorry, my saliva--
- It's okay!
I'm being serious.
I don't get it.
- (In gay lingo) Huh-tdog.
- [LAUGHTER]
Wait, why don't you
cry-ola instead?
- True.
- Huh? Why would I do coloring?
He thinks we're talking
about crayons.
[LAUGHTER]
So, are we done confronting
each other?
Maybe you and Uno want
to confront each other?
- J...
- No--
No confrontation needed.
My god!
What is happening here?
Is this some sort of gathering
or prayer meeting?
Some sort of gathering?
Anyway,
drop whatever you're doing.
Let's go! Come on!
- What's up?
- Huh?
Just do it. Come on! Let's go!
- Come on.
- Follow my lead.
- Let's go!
- Whatever it is, we're in.
Come on, guys!
["KUHA MO NA"
BY NAMELESS KIDS PLAYING]
[UNO] Is this allowed?
[KIDLAT] Of course not.
But it's fun to break the rules.
[CHUCKLES]
Just kidding!
[UNO] What if we get caught?
[LUCIEN] We're only going
to get caught if you tell.
Plus, I already saw Coach
took a ton of melatonin.
So, for sure,
he's already asleep now.
[DIAMOND]
You need to relax, Uno.
We're teenagers,
and we're allowed to be one.
Now, drink up!
["KUHA MO NA" CONTINUES]
[SWEET MUSIC PLAYING]
[UNO] Farrah! Farrah!
Why are you following me?
- Where are you going?
- I really need to pee,
- so I'm going to the restroom.
- Farrah.
Talk to me, please.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You slept on me on the bus.
You didn't speak to me
the whole time.
Jared is back on the team.
And he said the dean
has approved of it.
We're okay.
So, stop being mad at me.
Please.
First of all, Uno,
stop talking about
how I slept on the bus, okay?
And second,
we both know that you and
Jared didn't only grow apart.
And what irks me off is that
Jared is even protecting you.
Do you even know
why he's mad at you?
- You haven't even apologized!
- I know!
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you sure?
I bet you don't know
what you did to me.
To you?
- Isn't this about Jared?
- It is.
And if I were you,
I'd do something about it.
Can you stop staring
at me like that?
Like what?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Your eyes are beautiful.
Huh?
[COUGHS]
This is so annoying!
- I really need to pee!
- Farrah, wait!
["KUHA MO NA"
BY NAMELESS KIDS PLAYING]
["BUGHAW" BY MAKI PLAYING]