Let's go.
Show me how to run.
No.
What?
What are you doing?
I'll do an interval training from today.
What's that?
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute?
What?
It's very effective.
This is an interval training.
You have to do 60 seconds of running and 60 seconds of rest.
I'll make a mistake that your body is doing a high-intensity exercise.
Now, I have an important appointment.
Please listen.
Yes.
Didn't you say you had an important appointment?
The most important appointment is my heart and promise.
Oh, good.
It's so delicious.
It's a good idea, right?
Yes.
Oh, my nose is coming out.
It's a good idea.
Oh, my.
How did you overcome the pregnancy?
Oh, yes.
Oh, good job.
Mr. Do was very relieved because Miran wasn't coming out.
I think it's a breakup with a lover.
Aren't you two a couple?
No, that's not it.
Mom, are you forgetting our past memories?
I thought you were a drama man.
No, I'm not.
You don't like someone else other than your mom.
I love my sister.
That's right.
I was going to tell my heart in the mirror earlier.
What?
You're the best of mine.
Oh, my.
It's a good idea to have a baby.
No, it's not.
Oh, my.
Who is it?
I think it's the first time I've seen it.
Oh, my.
I think I'm going to get a facial mask.
No, your waist is this big.
I think it's less inside.
Oh, my.
I don't think I've seen it anywhere.
I saw it on TV.
I see.
I think I've seen that person somewhere.
What is it?
It's a lecture meeting.
Why did the influencer with over 1 million followers come all the way here?
Aren't you curious?
Yes, I'm not curious.
Why?
I sent you a DM.
You did well, right?
That's amazing.
Can you tell me that Alex sent you a DM and Kang Seol-hyeon came here?
What does our health center not make sense?
Director, I don't know who Kang Seol-hyeon is.
Kang Seol-hyeon is a mega influencer with over 1 million followers.
1 million!
Where Kang Seol-hyeon is wearing?
This is the entrance ticket.
Everyone sold out.
Where Kang Seol is going?
It's a hot place.
When Kang Seol eats it, it becomes a secret restaurant.
Oh, my God.
What are you doing there?
Hey, come here.
What are you doing in the English language?
Get out of here.
What?
Oh, my God.
It's paparazzi.
If you use that much influence, you can be sponsored by a very good hotel center.
But why are we in the health center?
Director, how can I come out?
I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
I'm so tired.
I don't know why I came here or how I came here, but we have to catch that sash.
This is a huge opportunity that the sky gave me.
I can't catch it.
Why?
I'm going to give it to you.
What do you mean?
Everyone can't focus on exercise because they're looking at me.
The person who interferes with exercise can't be left in the health center.
Then, please go out.
The director is the most disturbed.
Chairman.
Is there a lot of music here?
Kang Su-ae.
I don't know what you're thinking about, but this is not where you are.
Attention!
Everyone pays attention.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm going to pay attention.
Why, why, why?
From now on, I will tell you about the new rules that you have to follow in the health club at 24.
Rules?
Aren't you saying not to eat?
First of all, everyone is forbidden to interfere with other people's exercise.
The distance between a fancy top, a fancy high, and a fancy makeup is very far.
This new health center is a sports center.
It's not a fashion store.
If you don't want to, go out right now.
No, this is not a high school in the 70s.
There's a complex.
I like the bright color.
It's a cool summer.
I heard that the director only looks at the body and muscles.
I guess you're more concerned about something else.
People here don't seem to be interested in other people's fashion.
That's right.
What does it matter if you wear this or that when you exercise?
You could be a little more interested in fashion.
You're making a fuss.
Next!
In the health club, it is forbidden to interfere with other people's exercise.
Is there anyone like that?
I'm not.
I'm not either.
Then...
Then who are you talking about?
I...
Me?
Hey, you're the director.
Is there anyone with a personal feelings?
No, I'm not.
Stop it.
What kind of a person is that?
What's wrong with you?
Let's go inside.
It's okay.
What are you doing?
I'm really...
I know what you want to say.
I'm Anna's brother.
It's PT time.
Shall we go to exercise?
Director Do Hyun-joon?
First, we'll do a deadlift.
Deadlift...
It means you're pulling something.
It's romantic.
The deadlift I'm doing is not romantic.
Let's start.
One!
Two!
Three!
Yes!
Make the posture accurate! One more time!
Kang Sol.
I don't know why you're here, but I can't come out of my gym again.
I'm going to make you hurt.
The hurtful thing you gave me.
Let's break up.
One more time!
Live your life alone with a heart that's not useless.
Two!
One, two, three!
Three!
Four!
Director Do Hyun-joon!
You can't do a deadlift because of her.
Five!
If it's hard to follow, it's better to give up here.
This is the beginning.
No, it's too good.
It's more than expected.
I think you did a good job.
What are you thinking about?
I'm so happy to see you have a granddaughter.
You look good together.
You're so bad at it.
What's wrong?
It's not good to have a recommendation.
I'm screwed.
I want to eat tteokbokki.
Suddenly?
Always always always always always.
Hello.
This is your house.
I'm just going to go in.
Hello, I'm here at the convenience store.
Welcome to my house.
Hello, Cha-young.
Thanks to you, I'm safe.
That's a relief.
What are you doing?
Interval.
What is that?
It makes my body mistaken.
I'm eating tteokbokki right now, but I'm eating salad.
Your body is making you mistaken.
What are you talking about?
I was in the rolling machine for an interview today.
Even though I didn't pull the rolling machine, my heart rate is so high.
It was quite effective.
So I'm going to apply it to the restaurant.
Honey.
Yes?
Are you stupid?
I think I'm just a pig.
Hey, you little bastard.
Do you want to see a pig?
Thank you.
It's really swollen.
I guess the restaurant doesn't have an interview.
What's that from the morning?
Director Kwon?
No.
I know.
Who likes to go to the dentist?
You look good.
What is it?
Wait.
Hold on.
It's okay.
You're a fan of dust, so you keep getting dust in your eyes.
You're not in yet.
Don't overdo it.
Why are you so mean?
I know you don't look good with 24 hours.
Listen to me, please.
Mungwon.
Roy.
My name is Roy.
Mungwon.
The one who doesn't look good is you and Roy.
Okay?
I'm going to work out.
Bye.
What do you think you're doing?
You're going to be so angry.
Director, good morning.
Yes.
Start working out with a squat 50.
What do you mean by working out with a squat 50?
Then what is tteokbokki you eat before you eat salad?
What?
How can I...
Hold on.
The right side is the chair and the left side is the shit.
Didn't you say you only ate salad for me?
Are you crazy?
I did a test.
I'm not sure if you can get used to the interview.
I'm serious.
Squat 70.
70.
50.
Don't think about losing weight.
You're a fool.
I'm going to work out.
I can see everything from here.
I like your eyes.
It's 2.0.
2.0.
Sit deeper.
What?
I'm sorry.
Please.
I saw it.
Did you see it?
Was that picture accurate?
Stop.
It burst my ranking.
Gosh.
I should probably go to the other room.
Kang So-hyun, what are you doing?
You're going to make all my members on your side?
How can you be so hard on me?
It's okay. I didn't see anything. Really.
Really?
Of course.
Oh, thank god.
But I guess you like the cat character, right?
Oh, you're good.
Don't worry. I'm the only one who saw it. Really.
But that's a relief.
I bought a cute panty today.
I really like a love panty.
I forgot about the love panty that I heard in the hole on this day.
Really?
I'm so glad you didn't.
Oh, is it too much?
No.
It's so cool.
Why are you so good at that?
You can't do anything.
What do you do if you're already ruined?
I can't turn back time.
I'll give you this leggings even if I don't have time.
I'm so grateful.
It's okay.
I'm giving it as a gift.
No, leggings look expensive.
I have to give it back.
Well, if it's a little too much to just buy it, you can just be friends.
Friends?
Yes, we're friends from today.
Do you do anything?
What do you do?
About eye-tickling?
What is it? Why are there so many followers?
You were a very famous person.
Oh, I saw it somewhere.
I saw it here.
Oh, do you like Kang Seol, too?
No, he's very famous.
Of course. He's the most famous person these days.
Kang Seol's clothes and food are all my wannabe.
I want to see him in person.
What?
Did Kang Seol follow you first?
Yes, she already did.
No, why?
Why are you following me, Kang Seol, the human Kang Seol?
Go to the gym.
No matter what.
Mi-ran, come here a little bit.
Don't be late and come here.
Oh, my.
What?
Why is this person in our gym?
Oh, my.
Oh, my friend.
Wait a minute.
I'll open it for you.
Oh, my.
You were there last time, right?
Wait, wait, wait.
It's a special force if you have a weapon. I know it.
You know it?
Get off.
Get off the dangerous thing.
Oh, my.
What's wrong?
Raise your hand.
I know it.
Move.
Smile.
I'm sorry.
I was going to the police station because of me.
No, I didn't pay the price today. It's okay.
What?
And the one who saved me was Sol.
You're really good at fighting. What's this?
I've done a lot of fighting.
Oh, my.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Yes.
Enjoy your meal.
But is this okay?
I wanted to buy you something delicious.
Don't say that.
There's nothing more delicious than this in the world.
It's delicious.
But don't you think it's a little boring to eat this?
One drink.
Cheers.
But it's really amazing.
What?
I'm eating with Sol.
I was sent to the health club at 24 o'clock.
Me?
On the day I was bullied and bullied by my boyfriend on the street, it was my worst day in my life.
But Sol sent me to the health center.
Your ending is not here.
You can change your life, too.
Of course, I saw you drunk and drunk.
Thank you.
I guess it was fate.
What?
I'm a friend like this.
It's salty.
Why is it so sweet today?
But I think I'm the only one who's drunk.
It's okay.
Milan is cute, too.
Thank you.
I'm not really hoping for a big thing.
I'm not as much as I love you.
I'm just asking if you can like me as much as you like.
I know you well.
Sol?
I don't think Sol had anything like that.
Who?
Who can be like Kang Sol?
I have.
You're crazy, Il Chi-kwang.
Hurry up and try it.
I'm sorry, but I'll just take it.
Why?
I had something to fight.
Who?
It was someone who didn't even care about me for a single time.
I'm embarrassed.
I'll be right out.
Where are you going?
Oppa.
What's more important than me is your body.
Oppa, what should we do after the competition?
Do you have anything you want to eat?
Well, now I have to.
Do you know it's my birthday today?
Let's go eat seasoned ribs today.
Huh?
I'm going to eat seasoned ribs with you today.
Okay.
You eat seasoned ribs.
I'll eat it with the pork chop.
I knew it then.
I can't be the first place for him forever.
Live your life alone with a wide heart without a use.
That's why you hurt him on purpose.
With the word that hurts him the most.
So that the heart of that man hurts.
Well, I don't know if it hurt, but...
Anyway, don't ever meet a guy who works out.
You know how your heart is stimulated.
People who don't know about women's heart pain.
You bad guy.
Break your heart.
Like this.
No, like this.
What's wrong, director?
I love the heart.
What?
Oh, what's wrong with you?
Why?
Did you drink and get into an accident again?
Did you hurt your tongue?
I'm full before I drank.
Then what's wrong?
What did you do after drinking?
It's delicious.
Excuse me.
Do you want to go on a blind date tomorrow?
I just remembered someone who posted it on Miran.
Don't lie.
You really don't?
Really?
You haven't called yet?
What?
I'll call you right away.
I'm full!
I'm going on a blind date.
What?
A blind date?
I was going to see you today.
I really don't want to go.
I can't drink. I have to clean up.
What is it?
I smell alcohol.
Oh, it's me.
I smell...
It's the best to have a small heart.
Oh, until the 27th?
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
I think my heart is beating a bit these days.
I'm massaging.
Where are you coming in?
Why can't you go in?
It's a place for our gym and our members to use.
Get out of here.
Really?
Then I'll just be here to see you.
I'll do it.
Here's the membership.
I think Hyo-ri will come here often, too.
What are you doing?
I don't have a card.
We only register monthly.
One month?
200,000 won.
It's 30,000 won.
To be properly registered, one year is...
I should register.
One year?
Why not?
How long should I let you go?
Wait a minute.
That's...
Okay, please do it.
What?
One ten.
Okay?
Thank you.
But the card name is Lee Bong-won.
Who is Lee Bong-won?
Stop.
Yes.
Thank you.
Now that I'm here, did I have the right to talk to you?
I don't know what you're thinking about, but stop right now.
I don't think you're going to worry about that.
Are you embarrassed?
I couldn't even pose because of the woman on an important day.
Please sign here.
I've cut it off with 200,000 won.
240,000 won.
It's 242,000 won in December.
Sorry.
I gave you a service for the towel and sports uniform.
Yes.
Welcome, madam.
Have a good time.
Okay.
Don't hurt me anymore.
If you don't want to be a mousse again.
See you later.
Yes.
Goodbye.
What's wrong?
Are you going to the blind date?
Like someone who's going to the library?
I really don't want to go.
What do you hate so much?
Look.
I'll make you pretty.
I hate your makeup.
I'm going to blind date you.
It's okay.
I can't take a break.
If I take a break, I'll die of love.
You were alive?
Do you know?
You're so handsome, you're nice, and you have a good personality.
Why does that person come out of my blind date?
Don't come out of the blind date.
Stay still.
It's all done.
Just do it.
How is it?
Isn't it so pretty?
What is this?
It's a cute cat.
It's not a tiger to live.
You have to go like this.
I'm so scared.
I'm sorry.
No, you have to do this.
I think I'm going to catch a person.
It was almost late because of this.
I think you're going to look good with me.
Oh, oh, let's go.
Hello.
Are you in the right place today?
Oh, yes.
Oh, yes?
You came early.
Did I come a little late?
It's not late, but I didn't come in a second.
What?
Usually, you come 10 minutes first in this seat.
Oh, yes.
I'm sorry.
The car is a little blocked when I'm coming.
It's not time to go outside.
It's not time to go to work, it's not time to go home, it's not time to have lunch.
4 o'clock.
Yes, yes.
It's not blocking.
I guess you really like coffee.
He's my band.
Yes.
So I think I prefer 4 o'clock after Saturday for the time of the blind date.
Why?
I can't even close the car and drink coffee like this and judge.
I'll have dinner and find out more about the other person.
Or drink coffee and break up neatly.
Oh, oh.
You're so...
You're a manager.
What's the manager?
Oh, I guess you were a British scholar.
I'm a major.
Oh, you're a major.
Do you order a drink?
What?
It says 1 and 1 and 1.
1 and 1 and 1.
I already ordered a manor.
Oh, a manor?
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes.
Hello.
I'm Park Jung-han, a friend of Sol.
I'm here to see you today.
What?
You're here to see me today?
Awesome.
I'm a little late, right?
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
I think I had a plan today.
Oh, thank God.
I haven't ordered a drink yet.
It says 1 and 1 and 1 here.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I'll buy it for you.
No, no.
Yes, over there.
Bye.
Fighting.
I'm sorry I'm late today.
It's my first time here, so I'm not on the right track.
No, you might be. It's okay.
What is it?
Why is a fine guy coming out of the blind date?
It says this place is famous for cakes.
Try it.
Oh, yes.
I thought you were ordering a chocolate cake.
It's not latte, it's just for eating.
Chocolate cake goes well with Americano.
What?
Would you like to change mine?
No, no, no, no, no.
I like latte.
It's going to be more delicious.
Yes.
What?
Why are you so sensitive?
Let's go.
Are you uncomfortable?
Well...
I guess my body has been weak these days.
When I eat sweets, I get a little stiff.
I guess you should go to the dentist.
Do you have a dentist's insurance?
Yes, that's right.
This time, it's a dental insurance.
I'm getting older, so the dentist is not afraid of treatment.
It's afraid of treatment.
So I...
Jeonghan, I have a dental insurance.
What?
There are all kinds of dental insurance, dental insurance, and dental insurance.
You've already heard all the insurance and you're diligent.
If you have a good product, please introduce me to one.
I was looking into it.
I really wanted to get a recommendation, but it worked out well.
What?
Shall we get up now?
I made a reservation near the restaurant.
Restaurant?
We have to eat something delicious together to open our hearts.
Let's go.
I'll take care of it.
What time is it?
Why are you taking it out?
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Don't be too focused on your self-care.
I'm so nervous.
Oh, my God.
Hey, look at the camera.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Where are you?
Hurry up and tell me.
Thank you.
Hey, where did you come from?
I'm worried about you.
So did you eat something delicious?
What did you eat?
Did you have a lucky day from today?
I'm also a brother now.
What brother?
I ate a lot.
Then you can choose.
So I said, let's meet again next time.
I don't know.
It's a little weird.
Why?
I'm going to eat dinner with you.
It's all cooked.
Enjoy your meal.
It looks really good.
Eat it.
I can't eat it today.
I'll get it.
But I dropped the spoon after eating and went to the table.
That's like a nail on your ankle.
It looked like a crime scene.
Were you a criminal?
Are you okay?
What's that on your ankle?
What's that?
Wait a minute.
This is a swimming pool locker.
What kind of swimming pool locker does it look like?
I was nervous about the blind date today, so I forgot to wear a sportswear.
If I hadn't told you, I would have been in the car.
You really solved it.
I heard you were learning swimming.
I even saw your hair.
It's weird.
It's a little weird, right?
You brought ten of the locker.
You were a criminal.
I'm not sure.
You can't swim.
I can tell you how to swim.
Then it'll work.
But the weird thing is that something urgent happened.
I'm going to go to my studio for a while.
What? You're going to the studio from the first meeting?
This is totally a player.
So? Did you follow me?
Yes, I did.
It was a little scary.
It was dark.
What's that?
I didn't even hear a big sound.
I couldn't hear it outside.
Oh, my gosh.
Were you surprised?
No.
Mi-ran.
Why are you...
I have something prepared for you.
But you don't have a pen.
It's a strange thing.
Wait a minute. What's that in your hand?
A little long and shiny?
Knife! Knife!
It doesn't hurt. What is it?
It's all flowers.
The only one who doesn't come on Saturday.
I just bought it.
It's warm.
I just bought soy sauce.
I like gochujang.
The food I like the most is...
Bingo!
It's weird.
I think he's a good guy.
It doesn't feel right with me.
I don't have anything to pull.
I'm not good at pulling or pulling.
I can't listen to you anymore.
What?
Are you still Jun-seok?
Are you crazy?
Then?
Are you a guy who likes someone else?
Then why are you doing this?
Unnie, don't catch a useless guy.
Don't take care of him.
Okay. Let's find out.
Miran, how was the blind date today?
Jeong-an said she really liked you.
I think we've met a few times.
Jeong-an is a really good person.
Yes. Thank you, Sol.
Don't hurt me anymore. Let's do it right away.
If you don't want to be a heart that can't be used again...
What is this?
I'll guess it right.
This is the sound of your muscles.
No, this is the sound of your cold water.
What is this?
Oh, this is the sound of your muscles.
No, this is the sound of your cold water.
Have this. It's water.
I don't need it.
Are you cold?
No.
Oh, my. The boiler is too old. It's completely broken.
It's old, so there's no part. You just have to replace it.
Oh, I mean...
I'll just put the boiler on.
Yes, I think that's what I should do.
The cold water is the help of the construction site.
Please replace it. You can change it right away, right?
Then I'll start the construction today.
Yes, thank you.
Thank you.
No, sir. If you start the construction like this...
It's okay, sir.
This time, thanks to the director of the construction site,
there are a lot of new features.
Thanks to the director of the construction site?
Yes.
The director of the construction site put our health department on the feed.
Not the story, but the feed.
I thought the interior of our health department was a concept because the director of the construction site was there.
I really knew it.
The director of the construction site is really like a person of luck.
Please give me a thank you greeting during the class next time.
Thank you greeting.
Our health department is on the feed.
Okay, I'll be sure to do it.
Yes.
Alex, let's go and see.
I have something to say. Let's see outside for a while.
What do you think?
Did you ask me to learn this?
Eat it.
I chose it as my favorite high-end white rice cake.
The eel tail.
The eel tail is very good for stamina.
You have to eat well because your body is a property.
I'll take care of stamina well.
Tell me what to say.
Why did you come back to me?
Let's eat first.
You have to consume protein in two hours after exercising.
There are 100g of eel and 179g of protein.
Are you not going to eat it?
Eat this all.
Let's go somewhere.
Hello.
What is this place?
How big is it?
Is it about 2X?
It's 3X.
It's a lot bigger.
Red, blue.
Red.
Blue is so cute.
Next, you have to have a basic one.
Try this on.
Why should I try this on?
I'll explain it to you when you try this on.
Okay.
You look good in blue.
You're cute.
No, no.
Next.
You have to cut it.
What's wrong with your face?
Smile.
Next.
Yes, simple is the best.
The most confident pose.
I'm good.
This is it.
Give me everything you've worn today.
Okay.
Am I a liar?
You're a liar.
No?
No.
Tell me now.
What's the reason you're doing this?
It's going to be a fly.
Take it.
You have to get off or I'll have to go.
I thought about why you came here.
I didn't come here because I didn't have anything to do with exercise.
I'm sorry.
I can't accept your heart.
Who wants to be my wife?
Then why did you come?
Not your wife.
Did you get anything else?
What?
Among the things you have,
the best one.
The best one among the things I have?
I'll call you tomorrow. Take it.
Get off.
Among the things you have,
the best one.
Is it possible that you want to...
Seorak.
Why did you get so lonely?
How about tomorrow evening?
I have a restaurant I want to go with you.
I didn't think you'd want to see me.
No.
I'm just a few years older than you.
I'm expecting someone who's older than me.
You like meeting people, right?
If I see you...
Why is that...
Isn't that still on the stage?
Who is it?
Who keeps putting in tissue in the toilet?
How many times have I told you not to put tissue in the toilet because the math is weak?
It's not me.
It's not me either.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure either.
What is this?
I didn't do an interview.
Why is my heart beating?
What is this?
It's a failure.
What's going on?
I can't even breathe.
Let's go.
Yes.
Who is it this time?
It's a failure.
I'm sorry for the sudden change.
I think it's important to fix it.
Eun-ah, start!
Yes!
I'm annoyed.
I haven't turned it off yet.
I must be crazy.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure either.
Ms. Lee!
What is this?
You must be careful with your tissue.
I'll be careful with my tissue.
It's a failure.
I'm so mad.
What are you doing here?
I was left out.
Didn't I have a lot of bruises?
When I was thrown away in a house like that,
I was thrown to the water and got hit by a bush.
Why did you do that to a man who had bruises?
Why did you do that?
I'm so sad.
Sad?
Even if you forget your feelings soon,
you can't forget your body.
You can't forget your body.
Why are you so mean?
The medicine is the scariest thing about your body.
What?
I'm so sad.
See you at the new hotel at 7 tomorrow.
I'll tell you the reason tomorrow.
Do you really have feelings for me?
When did I ask you to meet me?
Ask me the best thing about you.
Let's be in the eyes.
I'll do it.
I was in the car.
Stop it.
Stop watching TV shows at the beach.
beach
Do you meet me at 7 at the new hotel?
The best thing about you is that you came to see me.
What are you thinking about?
Do Hyunjoo is not going.
No.
I'm not going.
I have something to tell you.
Kang Sol.
There are two new members at the new hotel.
Kang Sol is coming to see you.
Is that so?
You have to pay for the change.
Pay?
It's okay to be here.
The building owner was making a fuss about the beach every time we meet.
He changed his face because he was famous.
Shouldn't we give him a present?
A present?
Ask him if he wants anything.
He has to pay for it.
If you want something, you can't give it to him.
What's there to give to Eunin?
You have to pay for everything.
Give it to him.
Give it to him?
You have to give it to him.
Two new members came today.
Two?
The manager has to do everything for the head.
The manager is responsible for everything to protect the head.
Thank you.
Okay.
I know everything about the health center.
I'm sorry.
Sol?
Come in.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I can't miss the best opportunity in my life because of that.
Okay. I'll go crazy.
Our manager...
You look desperate.
Thank you for your help, Mr. Sol.
What?
I'm so tired.
I saw too many things.
No, no, no.
Get your hands off me.
Good luck, Miran.
Hello.
Look at this.
You're so sweet.
You even take out the chair.
What are you doing?
Run.
Are you okay?
The steak here is good.
And the fish is good.
Okay.
Hey, Miran.
Why do you always say that to a guy who buys you something delicious?
Why are you still?
Are you out of your mind?
Have some of this, too.
Thank you.
What the...
I'm here for the steak!
I told you several times to eat with confidence when I'm eating beef.
I'm here!
If you don't have enough oil, you'll have the most protein on your conscience.
Just dip the sauce a little bit.
A little bit?
What the...
What are you doing?
I'm here for the steak.
What the...
What?
I'm sorry, Jeonghan.
I was really...
I was crazy.
I'll pay for it.
I'm really sorry.
What's wrong with me?
Miran.
Miran is crazy.
She's the perfect man.
She's the best.
Did you miss her?
She's crazy.
Are you done?
My mom.
What?
Let's go.
I was tired.
I should go to the hospital to get the protein.
What's that?
Even if Seol-yi likes it,
it won't do anything.
Was it the director?
I wanted to believe that it was an interview.
I wanted to believe that my heart was in the wrong.
But I ended up falling in love again.
Are you here, oppa?
Come in.
What did you do to the two of you?
I just wanted to show you the room.
When will you do this next time?
Next week?
How can I wait for you next time?
I'm so curious.
You're crazy.
I know.
I'm a thinker.
It's good to see someone you want to see
when you like a trainer.
But...
You two are definitely different.
I've never seen you look like that.
Do you know how different I am?
I didn't want to be a part of Choa's side.
Do you have someone you like?
Director, what's your relationship with Sol?