[Xiumin]
[Side dish refills are self-serve!]
[Chu So Jung]
[Lee Sae On]
[Lee Soo Min]
[Kim Hee Jung] [Woo Hyun] [Oh Ji Ho]
[Heo's Diner]
[The characters, organizations,
and events in this drama]
[are purely fictional
and unrelated to historical facts]
[Animals were filmed under expert supervision
in accordance with welfare guidelines]
Are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
What about you?
I'm fine.
What a relief. That was close.
Bungeoppang... What a waste.
If you have the energy to worry about that,
I guess you're all right.
I will buy you more next time.
Who the hell drives like that?!
You almost hit someone!
Get out of the car now!
I said, get out!
Wait...
You're...
- Thank you-
- Mae Chang!
Oh, Mae Chang!
Mae Chang! Wake up.
Jung Mi Sol, I know you're awake.
That's it, I'm calling the police.
Oh, don't!
Mae Chang, you're awake.
Thank goodness you regained consciousness.
Didn't I hit you with my car earlier?
As you can see, I'm perfectly fine.
No one got hurt.
Still, why would you do
something like that?
That was way too dangerous.
I have to ask, did you drink?
You're already caught up in enough scandals.
Are you really adding drunk driving to the list?
What?
I didn't drink a single drop!
Lee Hyuk was my target.
You two just got in the way.
No way.
Then, you tried to hit Chef Lee on purpose?
He ruined my life, so I better give him
a taste of his own medicine.
Ah, I wanted revenge on Lee Hyuk...
But you two ruined my plan!
Don't slander him.
He's a good person.
Huh?
That's true.
He's not a bad person.
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
Do you have any idea
what he put me through?
I thought you were my fan, mister.
If you're my fan, you should take my side.
You keep calling me a "fan".
What does that mean?
Oh, wow.
Did you already leave my fandom
now that my career is over?
What is leaving a fandom?
Okay, that's enough.
Jung Mi Sol, this guy stopped me
from calling the cops.
So just drop the revenge act
and live your life properly
I've had a rough day too.
But I wouldn't act as recklessly as you.
She's right.
One moment of anger
can bring a hundred days of regret.
Hurting him won't fix anything.
What a joke.
Neither of you even know
what he's really like.
Oh, Mae Chang!
You're still weak.
Lie down a little longer.
Here?
This is my room!
Where am I supposed to sleep, then?
My, my!
Do you have no compassion, young lady?
Are you going to kick Mae Chang out
into the freezing cold when she looks this pale?
That's heartless.
You can't be serious.
Who's been feeding you
and giving you shelter this whole time?
Now I see why they say
never to take in a black-haired beast.
Forget it, I don't want to rest
in this shabby room any longer.
Did you say, "shabby?"
I can't get myself behind the wheel today
so can you take me home in my car, mister?
Let's go.
Hang on!
Why are you taking Mr. Homeless?
Call your manager.
I don't have a manager.
I fired him.
I couldn't stand seeing him cry
because of me anymore.
So, take me home.
All right.
I will take her home.
What do you mean, "All right?"
You don't even have a driver's license!
What? He doesn't have a license?
There's only so much he can do.
I guess I need something called
a driver's license.
Don't... I'm Jung Mi Sol.
Look at her, sleeping soundly
in this shabby room.
How is she so carefree
after causing so much trouble?
And yet, I can't sleep just thinking about
reopening the diner tomorrow.
Wait!
There's a cockroach in my soup
and that's your reaction?!
Oh, my head hurts.
Why is it so cold?
I better repair this soon.
Ugh, it's freezing.
Aren't you cold, Mr. Homeless?
- Thank you-
- Mae Chang!
Don't you even have compassion, young lady?
Are you going to kick Mae Chang out
into the freezing cold
when she looks this pale?
Who cares if he's cold?
Mister, Mr. Homeless!
Mister!
He's freezing.
Mister, wake up.
You'll freeze to death if you sleep here!
Mister!
What is the matter?
A young lady grabbing a man like that.
Are you in heat or something?
I should've just let you freeze.
But why is it so cold here?
Until I get that window fixed,
you should sleep upstairs.
Come on, just go up.
I'm not ready for this.
Fine, then stay here and freeze.
On second thought, I'm ready.
What's that sound?
Is it Mae Chang?
Yes.
So much for getting any sleep tonight.
At least she seems to be sleeping well.
Even her snoring makes you happy, huh?
Wow, your dedication as a fan is next-level.
Again, with that "fan" thing!
What does that even mean?
It just means liking and supporting someone.
So that's why Mae Chang keeps calling me a fan.
Among them, lunatic fans like you,
who chase after celebrities
as if their life depended on it,
are called stalkers.
My mind is perfectly sound!
Of course, I cherish Mae Chang as an artist.
But that's purely...
Okay, stop right there.
I don't need to hear the details.
I left a blanket here,
so lay it down and sleep.
Wait, this is...
You washed my robe.
It's spotless, perfectly cleaned.
Of course.
I almost dislocated my shoulder
trying to hand-wash that thing.
Huh?
What's this?
It was ripped, so I stitched it up.
And no, I wasn't the one who tore it.
I know.
But this...
I was just bored.
Is this... bungeoppang?
Wait, why is this one only half a fish?
I ran out of thread.
If you don't like it, I can take it out.
Who said I didn't like it?
I was just making an observation.
Then go to sleep.
Thank you.
The more I see you, the more I realize...
you're truly a warm-hearted person.
I can't tell you how relieved I am that I met you
instead of someone else in this unfamiliar world.
Didn't you call me heartless earlier?
You even stormed out, saying
you didn't want to be used for money.
And yet, here you are again.
Come to think of it,
you're surprisingly spineless.
How did you know?
If there's one thing this Transcendent Genius lacks
it's exactly that.
And I'm the fool for taking you seriously.
I came back because
I realized you were right.
After hearing what you said, I looked again.
And this place isn't the Yuldoguk I dreamed of.
Now, I think I understand
why you're so desperate for money.
I'm sorry for pushing you earlier.
I was just anxious about not being able
to pay my mom's hospital bills
if the diner failed.
However, money can be earned.
If it helps you make money,
I'll gladly lend a hand.
Because I never want to see you cry
over money again.
You don't want to see me cry?
Why?
Why, you ask?
Because...
Excuse me.
About the car parked out front,
have you seen Jung Mi Sol by any chance?
Oh, she's upstairs...
Hey, aren't you Mi Sol's stalker?
Where's Mi Sol?
Watch your mouth!
I'm not some lunatic!
You're here for Jung Mi Sol, right?
Yes, I'm her manager.
I've been looking everywhere for her.
So that's what happened.
She was acting strangely during our last call
so I was worried sick.
Thank goodness nothing happened.
This guy deserves a lot of credit for that.
Thank you.
I am not a stalker, just a regular fan!
Mae Chang is sleeping soundly.
So don't wake her.
Come back in the morning.
Still, I can't just impose like this.
She's been through a lot lately.
At least let her get some proper rest.
Then...
Please contact me when she wakes up.
Got it.
Let's go upstairs and get some rest.
It's late.
Wait.
We need to finish our conversation first.
What conversation...?
That thing you were about to say earlier.
What exactly did you mean...
when you said you don't want to see me cry?
Well...
When you cry...
I'll just go first.
Mr. Homeless, I think I...
Because it's ugly!
What?
Your crying face is so ugly,
that I couldn't possibly
bear to see it twice!
Excuse me?
I've seen a lot of ugly faces
back in Joseon...
But compared to your crying face,
they were practically noble...
I'm someone who has to return.
I can't afford to let myself
have useless emotions.
What's with the vibe here?
Mae Chang, did you sleep well?
I couldn't sleep a wink
because it was uncomfortable.
But this feels even more awkward.
Says the person waking up at noon.
It's already that late?
But why isn't there a single customer?
Is it closed today?
No.
We're open, but we're having a slow day.
You'll go out of business soon.
Thanks for the vote of confidence.
I'm just saying, it's a shame.
If this were back when I was still popular,
I could've promoted the place.
But now, that's not even an option.
All right!
Instead of waiting around
for customers who may never come,
we should eat.
I'll prepare something special.
No thanks. I'll just throw it up anyway.
You two enjoy your meal.
I'll get going now.
That won't do!
This is a diner, after all,
so I can't let you leave on an empty stomach.
I saw in a video that you have nausea issues.
Even if you throw up,
you need to eat something to keep going.
Not sure I want to eat food
from this kind of place...
And what exactly do you mean by
this kind of place?
It's lunchtime, and the place is empty.
Isn't that a sign the food's bad.
For crying out loud...
Our food tastes amazing.
Mr. Homeless, show her.
I will.
Please give me a moment.
Wait.
Your "special dish" is just porridge?
I don't even like porridge.
Did you say, "just porridge?"
This is no ordinary porridge!
It's Bangpungjuk, made from wild parsnip sprouts
that survive harsh winters before sprouting.
Not only is it known to prevent strokes
but it also improves circulation
and relieves pain.
And the flavor!
The rich aroma fills your mouth
and lingers for days
leaving you in a good mood
long after you've eaten it.
That's why, despite having tasted
all of Joseon's finest dishes
this remains one of my personal favorites.
Fine, I'll try it.
This guy must've sold
a lot of snake oil in his time.
Oh?
This is delicious.
See? I told you so.
Mr. Homeless is an amazing chef.
Eat as much as you like.
If the food is this good,
then why aren't there any customers?
There was a cockroach incident yesterday.
That is absolutely false!
From the ingredients to the cooking tools,
every part of my dish is meticulously controlled.
Nothing enters my kitchen unless I allow it.
I swear on my honor.
No, my very life that this is the truth!
It's really strange, isn't it?
I've lived here since I was a kid
and I've never once seen a cockroach.
My mom was really sensitive about it.
And yet somehow,
one magically appears in our soup?
A paparazzi must've scammed you.
- Paparazzi?
You know, those people who stalk celebrities,
waiting for dirt to use against them?
They snap a bad photo,
then demand hush money.
Didn't they ask for money?
Detective Kang.
You guys go on ahead.
Let's go.
You punk...
How dare you come here! Huh?
Come on, a job well done
deserves fair pay, doesn't it?
You're just gonna ghost me like this?
Look at this punk.
Are you crazy?
Have you lost your mind?
Why? Should we go inside together?
What, missed the taste
of prison food after a few years?
If people find out what you had me do...
I doubt it'd be good for you either.
And you think anyone would believe you?
A punk like you who has been swindling
and threatening people for a lifetime.
Beat it, you punk.
And don't even think about showing
your face around here again.
And especially that alley,
stay the hell away.
You heard me.
I said, do you hear me?
He didn't ask for money.
Well. Some reporters publish
articles without demanding money.
All done.
You finished the whole bowl.
Strangely enough, this porridge is amazing.
I told you.
Bangpungjuk is a true delicacy.
Mi Sol!
Hey...
How did you even find this place?
He was here last night, too.
While you were sleeping.
I told you to find other ways
to make a living.
Why won't you ever listen?
We're on the same boat.
I practically raised you on my back.
Look at your face, all worn out.
You haven't been eating well, have you?
Sorry.
She slept well and had a good meal,
so don't worry.
Is that so?
Thanks anyway.
Mi Sol, let's go.
Sit and wait a little.
As you can see, I just ate.
If I leave now and throw up,
that'd be a waste.
You know how expensive
my car's Italian leather seats are.
If you've been dealing with this,
you should have told me.
Why hide it from me as well?
It's nothing I'm proud of.
Mi Sol, can't you stop
making yourself throw up?
It's ruining your body.
You're not even working right now.
Why not take a break from dieting?
It's not because I'm on a diet!
No?
I wish that were true.
Don't tell me Lee Hyuk fooled you too.
Then why do you throw up everything you eat?
Back when...
I was doing a lot of commercials as a kid.
Everyone wanted me to stop growing.
Directors, advertisers...
and even fans.
But especially my mom.
Jung Mi Sol!
Mi Sol, are you out of your mind?
Did you hear what the director said?
Everyone here is relying on you
and you can't even stop eating?
Open your mouth.
Open up and spit it out!
Mom...
If you keep growing
your career is over.
No one will even look at you.
Is that what you want?
As your mom...
I believe in you.
The pressure not to eat kept getting worse.
Eventually, my body started rejecting food.
Yes, mom.
She's gotten way too big.
She was so cute as a kid, but now...
A child model's career ends
the moment they grow taller.
Why put so much pressure on a kid?
As your mom.
I believe in you.
At first, it only happened sometimes
but then it became constant.
Now, no matter what I eat,
I throw it back up
I've been to so many doctors
but nothing helps.
I had no idea...
I'm sorry, Mi Sol.
So, it comes from deep pain.
It must have been hard for you.
Oh?
Wait… It's been a while since you ate.
Shouldn't you have thrown up by now?
You're right.
It's weird.
Are you okay? Do you feel sick?
No.
This has never happened before...
I made plenty, so take some home with you.
Here you go.
Come by anytime you're hungry.
There will always be a meal
waiting for you here.
I really wasn't planning on
taking in a stalker.
But you keep impressing me.
I'm not a stalker.
I'm just a fan.
Take care of yourself, Mi Sol.
Both your body and your heart.
Can I call you Eun Sil?
Thank you, Eun Sil.
So, how long have you two
been living together?
Huh?
Live together? It's nothing like that!
Mister, why are you just standing there?
Say something.
We are, uh...
We are strictly… business partners.
I see.
That's perfect.
Thank you.
Take care.
"That's perfect?"
What's perfect?
What's wrong?
Did my ugly face startle you
after looking at pretty Mi Sol for too long?
There you go again!
You're not ugly.
Just your crying face is.
Why, you!
Never mind.
There's something more important right now.
More important?
Like what?
What are you doing?
Are you picking fights
with those haters again?
No.
Like Mi Sol said.
If the guy who claimed to find a cockroach
in our food was after money…
Then he's probably pulled this scam before.
[Some shady guy's been lurking around]
If I dig through similar cases
I might find a lead.
So you can pick fights
and track down criminals
all on that tiny plank?
What an enchanting object.
Mister, can you untie this for me?
You should keep it on a bit longer.
This is life or death for our diner.
Hurry.
All right.
Let's see...
Luckily, it looks like it's healing well.
You should be fine.
I better go buy ingredients for tomorrow.
Did you enjoy the meal?
I enjoyed it very much.
But then...
How should I put it?
The dishes feel a bit modern.
The dignitary wishes to showcase
authentic Korean flavors to the state guests.
Yes, I understand.
I'll revise the course menu
to focus on traditional elements.
I know you're deeply invested in
globalizing Korean cuisine, Chef Lee.
Taking charge of this state dinner
will be a great opportunity for you as well.
It would be a tremendous honor.
I'll do my best to craft a menu
that meets your expectations.
I heard you're working on
a Korean cuisine-themed project.
Is everything going well?
Yes, it's in the final stages.
I'm looking forward to it.
No need to see me out.
Sir.
There's a call for you.
Who is it?
Well...
He didn't give a name
but said he works with Detective Kang.
Hang up.
From now on
handle these calls without informing me.
[I think I got scammed by a shady customer]
Found him.
[If you've had a similar experience
with this man, please get in touch]
[Your post has been uploaded]
Chef Lee!
No customers...
Again.
We only had one table earlier,
and that was it.
Keeping the place open
with no customers every day...
The losses must be piling up.
At this rate, we really might go under.
Would you like some coffee?
No.
But thank you.
Please have a seat.
Once a bad rumor spreads,
it's hard to recover.
I've experienced it firsthand,
so I know how it feels.
You mean Jung Mi Sol's case?
Eun Sil, even with things like this...
Do you still want to keep running this place?
I can cover all your losses.
With that money,
you wouldn't have to struggle.
You could focus entirely on
caring for your mother.
It's a generous offer
but I can't just walk away.
This is the place my mom
built from the ground up.
Even if I have to close,
I need to restore its reputation first.
But your losses will only keep growing
and restoring a reputation
is easier said than done.
That's why I started looking into that guy.
Turns out, he's a repeat offender.
I posted his photo
in restaurant owner communities.
Want to see?
No, that's okay.
Uh...
But... will catching him really change anything?
At the very least, it'll stop him
from targeting other restaurants.
That's reason enough for me.
I'll make sure he gets caught.
And once we clear our name...
Even then...
If things still don't improve...
then you have to buy this place
at a good price.
I will.
But if it ever gets too hard, don't hesitate.
Come straight to me.
My man!
You seem to be in a good mood.
Not really.
If it's something good, you should share it.
Just like bungeoppang.
I'm fine, really.
It's still warm.
I'm not feeling too well.
Oh, that is concerning.
Could it be from the accident?
Oh, right!
Thank you for letting it slide back then.
It's nothing, I didn't want things
to go out of hand, either.
As expected, you're a man of great generosity!
I made sure Mae Chang understands
not to pull anything like that again
so you don't have to worry.
Yes, then...
I hope he stays healthy.
Traditional flavors...
Mister.
If the diner really goes under,
what will you do?
Watch your words!
Don't say such things!
They say words have power.
The truth will come out eventually
and customers will return.
Easy for you to say.
Why are you cooking so hard
when we barely have any customers?
My man said he wasn't feeling well,
so I'm making Bangpungjuk for him.
Chef Lee said he's unwell?
He seemed to be in a good mood,
but he did say so.
He seemed fine earlier.
All right, then...
How should I pack this for him?
This looks perfect!
Oh, not that!
This is my mom's prized jar.
It's been passed down
to the daughters in our family.
Oh?
I just thought it'd be perfect
since it has a lid.
Close it, now.
If you open it, my mom will flip out.
There's something inside...
She said it's an heirloom
from our ancestors.
If it's been passed down that long,
it must be worth a fortune, right?
Should I take it
to a TV show for appraisal?
It doesn't seem all that valuable...
Excuse me?!
Anyway, what should I use
to pack the porridge?
Sir.
You have a visitor.
Who are you?
Oh, Chef Lee Hyuk!
I've tried calling you several times,
but you're not easy to reach.
I asked who you are.
Come on, you don't recognize me?
You must've seen the video
I sent Detective Kang.
I have no idea what you're talking about
I knew something was up
the moment Kang started snooping around
this fancy restaurant of yours.
The guy seriously underestimates me.
By the way, this place is impressive.
You must be making good money.
Please stop blathering and leave.
Before I report you for business interference.
It was you.
The one who ordered to shut down that diner.
Look, I didn't want to come here
and cause a scene.
But now, the entire nation knows my face
thanks to someone.
So now I can't even make a living.
Let's cut to the chase.
Just pay me what I'm owed,
and I'll walk away quietly.
Whatever you've done has nothing to do with me.
Take your complaints elsewhere.
Over here!
Send this man out right now.
- Please leave.
- Please leave, sir.
- Come on out!
- Thank you.
- Coming through.
- Let go of me!
Detective Kang, how the hell...
are you planning to handle this?!
- Get out!
- Why are you doing this to me?
Careful!
Watch yourself,
you nearly spilled the porridge!
Wait, you're...
You're that pyeonsa who falsely
claimed there was filth in my food!
[Pyeonsa: A swindler in the Joseon era]
Hold this for me.
I've been waiting for this moment!
What do you mean, false claim?
I just said what I saw!
Then why did you run away back then?
Let's settle this once and for all.
A fraud like you deserves
to be paraded around Gwanghwamun!
You got proof, huh?
Where's your proof I was lying?
- You have none, do you? Now let go!
- You're still spouting lies!
- Let go of me!
- How long do you plan on lying?
Why are you like this?! Let's talk it out!
Oh, let go...
You!
What are you doing here?!
Chef Lee, what should I do?
Should I spill the beans or not?
Go inside. Okay.
Chef, do you know this man?
This is the bastard who lied about
finding a cockroach in our food!
I mean... This is the guy.
Who said I was lying?
Where's your proof, huh?
All you do is serve dirty food.
How dare you!
How dare you spew more lies?!
You want proof?
Take a good look.
It's the cries of the restaurant owners you've scammed!
Darn it.
So, you're the one who put my face
all over the internet!
Chef, how do you know him?
I don't know him.
Of course.
My man wouldn't be
involved with trash like him!
Oh, really?
Then why was he coming out of Dorae?
That's because...
You, punk...
Didn't I tell you not to set foot
in this neighborhood again?
You are...
that officer!
What brings you here, Detective Kang?
He tried the same stunt at our restaurant.
I just finished calling the police on him.
- What the hell are you talking about?!
- You, punk.
I didn't know he was the man
you were looking for, Eun Sil.
This is great.
So, after messing with our place,
you went after my man too?
What a scoundrel!
Oh, you want me to talk?
Should I start spilling
who the real scumbag is here?!
You, punk...
Save it and just come with me.
Chef Lee.
You just saved our diner.
Did I... Save your diner?
Once the police confirm his crimes
our diner will finally clear its name.
You've saved us!
You could say that
from a little further away.
I'm glad I could help.
Now I feel like I can keep going.
It's all thanks to you.
Oh, wow!
I don't even know
how to express my gratitude!
I get it, enough of that.
I won't give up and do my best.
Thinking of you, Chef Lee.
I can do this!
Someone in hanbok dropped this off earlier…
Come to think of it…
I can still get rid of him
to bring down that diner.
What's all that?
We can't just sit around
waiting for customers.
What's the point of saying that we're clean?
We have to show it.
That makes sense.
Seeing is believing, after all.
You said words have power, right?
One step back for two steps forward!
Let's turn crisis into opportunity!
Let's do this!
That's quite a bit of enthusiasm.
Down, like this.
Okay?
Going up!
No, not up! Go down.
Great! Isn't this fun?
You need to match the line.
My goodness, look at me
I almost missed my mom's visiting hours
I'll be back soon,
so make sure to finish painting all of this.
All of it?
- All of it.
- Alone?
I'm off!
Finish everything!
Have a safe trip.
Was it like this?
My man!
I was wondering if you had a moment.
The young lady went to the hospital.
But I'm not here to see her.
I'm here for you.
Me?
Never thought I'd see the day
you'd seek me out first.
I am all yours.
This isn't the best place to talk.
Shall we head to my restaurant?
What is this about?
Mom, I spread that guy's photo all over the place
so he can never pull that trick again.
But can you believe it?
He tried it again at Chef Lee's
restaurant and got caught.
Guess the saying is true,
"Bad guys always get what they deserve".
Maybe there is some truth to that.
Well...
This time, it wasn't heaven that punished him.
It was Chef Lee.
He's such a generous person.
Mom, we're remodeling the diner right now.
You'll be surprised when you see it.
If you're curious, wake up soon.
I'll get going now.
Where did Mr. Homeless go?
Where's this chill coming from…
I don't think we ever had a chance
to sit down and talk.
I thought it'd be good to talk openly at least once.
I've been wanting that for a while, my man.
A proper talk needs a drink between men.
Here, have some.
I should be finishing the paint job...
But I suppose one glass wouldn't hurt.
Wait...
Did you...
Yes?
Does something seem off?
Did you add honey to the liquor?
There's no way I can stop at one.
Drink as much as you like.
We have plenty of liquor.
Where did he and why isn't he back yet?
Did he run away just because
I made him paint?
[Heo's Diner]
[Serving meals with sincerity]
Your cooking skills are exquisite.
The porridge was truly delicious.
Really?
Hearing that from you,
I feel like I'm soaring.
If you don't mind me asking
what's your secret?
There are no secrets.
If there is anything, it must be the palate,
memory and touch of this Transcendent Genius.
With such talent
why waste it in a rundown diner
with no customers?
Just look at yourself.
A man as full of life as you,
wasting away for the rest of his days
locked in a house
without even a single window?
What's the matter?
Nothing.
After a few drinks,
you seem to resemble my friend even more.
Is that so?
I...
don't look that old, do I?
It's strange, isn't it?
You are not my man
but you are just like him.
The dignitary wishes to showcase
authentic Korean flavors to the state guests.
Leave that diner
and join me.
I'll turn you into the finest Korean chef.
Pardon?
You have quite the sense of humor
when you're drunk.
I have always been anything but humorous.
Have I ever been anything but serious?
It's been a while since I drank
and it's really getting to me.
I should call it a day.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Are you content to stay
in that shabby diner
for the rest of your days?
Then,
are you content to live like this
for the rest of your days?
Gwansong.
I missed you.
This will guide Mr. Homeless
even on the darkest nights.
Let's work together.
I'll give you the best possible offer.