No more nonsense, Mr. Fei
I promise to marry you
Miss Fang suddenly wants to marry me again
You really like me
Still acting?
Of course I don’t really like it
The pros of marrying you outweigh the cons
Between people
The longest relationship is the relationship of interest
So before I marry you
Definitely still needed
Get to know you better
Before Mr. Fei got engaged to me,
Just send someone to inquire about me.
Did you have a martial arts stand-in before?
My name is Su Xiaoxiao
She is my martial arts stand-in
We haven’t contacted each other since we left the country.
They all say that the actor and the stuntman look alike
Do you think it looks like it?
I'm just me
If the fee is better than mine
If you are more interested in a substitute
Then there's no need for us to talk any more.
don't worry
Of course I am more interested in Miss Fang
Won't you invite me in and sit down?
My house is a bit messy, maybe next time
Now that we're both engaged
I still need to know you better
All right
Fortunately, I was prepared
I'll get some fruit
Mr. Fei, do you want to eat fruit?
you don't go home
Experience life here
Of course not
Because I don’t want to get engaged to you
So I was kicked out by my dad.
You're pretty good at finding reasons
Right
Weren't you injured before filming?
Mr. Fei, you are very suspicious.
It is recommended that you seek medical treatment as soon as possible
I think we need
Learn more about
Mr. Fei
If you want to eat cherries, just say so
what do you want to do
Don't be in a hurry, right?
You still don't admit it
You are not Fang Min
I'm not Fang Min
who am i
You have a really good attitude
So good that I feel
You are really Fang Min
Su Xiaoxiao twenty-five years old
Learned martial arts and practiced Sanda
Also studied special effects makeup
All-around talent
Playing Fang Min is just to reject me
In the end, it was a mistake.
It seems that my professionalism is not enough
I would like to ask you where is my flaw?
After wearing the mask for a long time, it really becomes your face.
So
You announced your engagement in public
It was to force Fang Min to come out
Be polite first and then fight with soldiers
As long as I'm in the media tomorrow
Play a sad drama
The whole world will search for Fang Min with me
And what about your substitute?
You can take a break
You
It's just one
Hypocrite pretending to be affectionate
what do you know
Ridiculous
no
The game is not over yet
Take a look
What will happen if this video is broadcast?
The media won’t help you find Fang Min
I will only report you extensively
Cheating
support
Violence
What happened to your voice?
The voice also changed when I took off the mask.
Doesn’t Mr. Fei know?
In movies and TV dramas
Is there a thing called a voice changer?
I don't like your voice
You can use my own voice if you like it.
And in this video
It seems that you are more proactive than me
Once this video is released
You can't explain it better than me
What if you were smart?
Just tell me where Fang Min is
I can still let you go
Mr. Fei, she’s coming after her.
parking
I can tell you where she is
But you need to give me time to confirm
I like doing deals with smart people
See you at my house tomorrow night at six o'clock
What will happen if this video is broadcast?
The media won't help you find Fang Min
This sound is so similar
The weather is very good today
There is sunshine and wind
Check Su Xiaoxiao again
Check everything in detail
Okay, Mr. Fei