Xiaoxiao
Your temper hasn't changed at all.
Your kung fu has improved a lot.
You are quite smart
Know that I will return to the company
so
Stay here and wait for me
with your IQ
It's just these tricks, right?
I figured it out when I got back
all this
It's all designed by you
It was you who made the plans
Let Fang Min beg me to play her
and then misled me further
Go to Fei Mingxuan and steal the contract evidence
Why didn't you find out before?
You look like a bed bug in the gutter
Good calculation
Good guess
But everything seems irreversible
Evidence of signed contract
It's in my hands now
Have you ever heard the saying
A woman who doesn’t fall in love
IQ will rise several levels
Do you think I will let you go so smoothly?
Then we'll see
Right
A friendly reminder to my good classmate
you are there for him
It's just one
Just Fang Min's stand-in
It's me Fang Min
Xiaoxiao
I regard you as a good friend
But the Tang and Song Dynasties
He is a social scum
Are you sure you want to stick with him?
Xiaoxiao, don’t worry
Just because he hurt you
I won't forgive him
He now has evidence of the Tang and Song dynasties
He will definitely hurt Fei Mingxuan
this time
I want to protect him
No matter what identity you use
Xiaoxiao
Just do whatever you want
I figured it out
Things like identity and skin
It's all external
the most important is
who am I
Everyone
we got a piece of information
It’s about the last contract for formaldehyde-containing materials.
And on this contract
The person who finally signed the approval
That's Mr. Fei
Mr. Fei’s signature
Can he sign this?
he won't do this
It’s really Mr. Fei
everybody knows
Our Minghao Group has regulations
If a manager makes a major mistake
causing stock prices to fall
Then we have the right to vote veto
to decide
Should he hand over management rights?
agree
Anyway, Mr. Fei gave it to an actor
Nineteen percent of the shares
How childish is the decision-making from now on?
You can imagine it
Stop grinding
If you don't want me to be eliminated, please raise your hands.
Xiaomin you
Actors also have the right to vote
It's like some irrelevant people
Shamelessly stay here to force yourself
Wait a moment
Here is another piece of information
Mr. Fei and I are over there at Fengsheng.
Retrieved the decoration materials shipment list
Found someone doing something inside
The contract clearly states that environmentally friendly materials are used
The shipping bill contains formaldehyde-containing products.
You can carefully compare the contracts
Just know
This contract is indeed different
Really
That's it
So that’s what happened
Since there is garbage mixed in,
Then I'll make it clearer
It is precisely because of this
The yin and yang contract where middlemen earn the price difference
That leads to shoddy products
Formaldehyde material appears
Cause damage to the company's reputation
I'm doing my best to make up for it
As for those who want to be in the middle
People who fish for oil and water
Wait until I find proof that you actually collected money.
This is economic crime
As for the consequences?
I think you should understand very well
By the way, Mr. Fang
I hope you won't listen to those rumors again
I'm too anxious
But it’s true that he failed to supervise
Now he's in front of half of the shareholders
lost credibility
I made the account of 300 million very detailed
Just find an accountant to support you then.
waste
Three percent of the shares are given to you for free.
Cerebral thrombosis will make you angry
A waste like you
How could Xiao Min marry you?
Mr. Fang
I have another way
What can you do
You are a waste
I tell you
Xiao Min is much better than you
That Fei Mingxuan
I also gave her 19% of the shares.
No
Mr. Fang
The real Xiao Min will help me
boy
don't let me down again
Do you understand?
Get out of the way
Busy
Come here and help me
what are you doing
What do you think looks good?
That's good
Xiaoxiao
actually
You don’t have to act as Fang Min today
Arrived at the scene
you are you
Although I turned into Fang Min today
But I won't do it again just because I'm a substitute
And feel humbled
I may still be because
I really want to deal with Tang and Song Dynasties, right?
I said you don't need to show off in front of me
knew
Xiaoxiao
Come
Will you trust me again
Then turn around
Su Xiaoxiao
It's snowing
Beautiful?
nice
sorry
I couldn't help it
Xiaoxiao
It can snow in the subtropics
Iron trees will also bloom
your wish
Realized
How about I teach you how to see snow?
What do you think?
Are you optimistic?
Crazy
Try lying down