[Choi Soo Young]
[Gong Myung]
[Kim Sung Ryung]
[Kim Sang Ho]
[Jo Yoon Hee]
[Second Shot at Love]
When I drank,
I was able to laugh.
I was able to cry my heart out
and I was able to become
someone else other than me.
And I became even more miserable.
I want to quit drinking and...
I want to live right again.
Please help me...
Ui Jun.
[Episode 5: The Reason I Cut You Off]
[Bochun Clinic]
[Skeletal Muscle and Fat Analysis /
Obesity Analysis]
I-Is it broken?
[Audit-K Examination: Han Jeong Su]
[Audit-K Examination: Han Hyeon Ju]
[Audit-K Examination: Han Geum Ju]
How does it look?
Does it look really bad?
All three of them have an alcohol dependency,
and their livers don't look good.
Especially for Geum Ju,
these numbers are...
Why? How bad is it?
If you try a little harder,
the government will say, "You're a patient,"
and they'll treat you for free.
Yeong Rong, aren't you busy? You can go now.
Sure, Unni.
You can stop drinking now and start managing.
Same with you, Mr. Han and Noonim.
But I'm surprised. I didn't know
you two would join Geum Ju.
I couldn't just ignore it as her father.
I couldn't just ignore her as her sister.
Yes, I'm glad you did.
It's a good decision for both of you as well.
Yes, she's right.
If you continue to drink habitually like this,
it could progress to
hepatic cirrhosis or liver cancer.
What?
Oh, my goodness!
I can't believe you drank until your body
deteriorated like this!
Please don't worry. Once they quit drinking,
they'll improve very quickly.
Where should we begin?
First, let's get rid of all the alcohol in the house.
The best way to avoid temptation is to avoid it.
Goodness. Don't worry. We don't have alcohol in the house.
I threw all away when I told them not to drink.
Do you really think so?
[Dae Geun's House]
Dae Geun, here's your snack!
Come, come. Good. Have your snack.
So, you've been drinking
behind my back all this time?
What's this?
Why a toner?
It's soju.
Wh-
What?
Daebak!
What a fresh new way!
Whoa! It's really soju!
Dad!
No.
Don't worry about me.
As Ui Jun said, just do the right thing from now on.
You won't drink going forward. Right?
You quit drinking now.
Of course!
I guess this is what happiness means.
Are you that happy?
Of course! I'm so happy!
Wondering if you'd come home injured somewhere
or what if you hurt someone else?
Thinking you're ruining your health
while vomiting, holding the toilet.
I can totally stop worrying about that stuff now.
Gosh, I'm so looking forward to it.
Forward to what?
Seeing how the three of you will change.
That's what Ui Jun said.
Only after a few days of sobriety,
you'll notice many things that have improved.
That's right.
We improved in many ways.
[Daily Schedule: Beer, Soju, Beer+Soju]
The time and money we used to spend on drinking
[Daily Schedule: Personal Growth]
was spent more productively.
Once we eliminated booze and drinking food,
we lost our gut as well.
[Body Fat Ratio: 20%]
Geum Ju, you're absolutely glowing!
We achieved the goal of making dull skin glow.
Our lives drastically changed.
Hooray!
That's what we thought we'd say.
Now that we quit drinking,
don't you think about it even more?
That's what I'm saying.
It'll look great on her.
It will be a nice gift.
Yes.
He's just a friend.
I have no intention of dating him.
Why did you call me out this late?
It's booze hour.
Booze hour?
It's about time you crave booze.
It's about time you think
you could decompress and
fall asleep easily with a drink.
That's right. You're not wrong.
With that logic, it's booze hour
for me 24/7 these days.
What?
Just think about it.
Look over there. Over there!
Cheers! Cheers!
Everywhere I look, people are drinking.
[Beyond exhilarating]
[The climax of beer, Ceulnatda]
Booze everywhere when I turn on the TV.
Booze everywhere on social media.
Our country is heaven when you're drinking.
But it's hell when you're trying to quit.
Let's run.
All of a sudden?
I told you.
The best way to avoid temptation is to avoid it.
I called you out to run,
so you don't think about booze.
All right...
The loser buys the winner at a convenience store.
That guy, seriously?
Wait...
Hey. Wait, wait, wait...
I can't run anymore...
Hey, what are you doing?
I really can't run anymore.
My stomach is about to rip.
Stop whining. A human stomach
doesn't rip with this.
Let's go.
Wait, I'm not whining.
I really can't go. Hey, I have a cramp.
What, where? Let me look.
Here, here, here.
Here?
Hey!
You said so yourself.
The loser buys the winner!
Here.
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Are you sure you're fine with just water?
Yeah.
I really wanted to drink refreshing water.
Wow, quitting drinking is really hard.
Did you have a tough time quitting, too?
No. I couldn't quit.
What?
It's one thing if you didn't know
the taste. How can I quit?
You don't quit drinking. You just hold out.
Daebak!
Unless you don't know the taste at all,
how can you hold out?
You tell yourself, "Just 10 minutes."
"Just for one hour. Just one day."
"Just one more day."
I just did it like that.
Wow!
Hey, you're impressive!
You can do it, too.
It's been a few days already that you're sober.
Just hold out for a week.
As a reward, I'll grant you anything you want.
Anything I want?
Yeah. Anything you want.
You go this far only
to win the convenience store bet.
Don't you need that much to withstand one week?
Listen to this guy.
You have no idea what I'd ask for.
What if...
I asked you for all of your assets?
I'll give it to you.
Hey, you think I can't?
Sorry, but I'll do it if I-
may not be able to...
Why?
Tomorrow's the weekend.
There will be tons of guests at the pension.
They'll go all out drinking.
The hell will unfold...
What are you doing tomorrow?
It's the weekend. To encourage Geum Ju,
how about we all go and get fresh air?
What's with this guy?
Where are we going?
Somewhere there's no booze.
What's he saying?
Where in this country could we not find booze?
There is. A place we're not allowed to drink.
[Drinking Prohibited]
[Wild Flower Habitat: Drinking Prohibited]
There is a place you're not supposed to drink.
What do you think?
It's a perfect place for Geum Ju,
who decided to be sober, right?
Not sure...
she even drank at a sobriety camp.
Hey, you really can't drink here.
If you do, you'll be arrested immediately.
That'll never happen.
I'll hold out for a week, no matter what.
A week?
Yeah. If I stay sober for a week,
he said he'd grant me anything I wanted.
A week? Anything you want?
Yup.
Sure, what the heck?
I have money, and I'm competent.
Daebak.
What do you mean?
Hey! Why do you think he's making
such an empty promise?
There's no way he'd keep his word.
I'm sure she's determined now.
But how long could our drunkard Han Geum Ju last?
Hey! Come on! Just wait and see.
I'll really show you.
And you! You can't take it back.
You'd better not say, "No, no, I'm not doing it."
"No, no." I'm not doing that.
What should I ask for?
To find a place in Seoul, I need money.
Borrow money without interest? No.
Should I ask for your car?
To make it my second car?
She's so excited. So excited.
♪ Now, we're falling in love ♪
♪ You and I in love ♪
♪ Like large snowflakes, like ocean waves ♪
♪ Embracing us cozily ♪
♪ Now, we're falling again ♪
♪ Happiness that's about to explode ♪
♪ I hope we can stay together forever ♪
♪ We're falling in love ♪
Gosh, I'm out of water.
Hey, I'll go get some water
from the mineral spring.
You want some, too?
Huh? Yeah.
Thank you.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Hey, so...
he's totally fine with you now?
What?
Think about it.
He says he'd grant you anything
if you hold out for a week.
He initiated us to all come out here.
I can see he's taking care of you.
It must be his sense of duty as a doctor.
Trying to succeed in my sobriety or something.
If it were that, how about Hyeon Ju and your dad?
He would've brought all of his patients.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just curious.
If it was that easy, why did he
ghost you all this time?
Why did you guys cut ties, anyway?
I never cut ties with him. He cut me off.
What?
If you're curious, you ask Ui Jun yourself.
Why he did that back then.
How about you?
Don't you want to know?
Gosh, so unnecessary. It's all in the past.
I'll just let it stay in the past.
I'm going to the restroom.
Excuse me.
Yes. Welcome!
We want to check-in.
By chance, are you Shin Jeong Yeon?
You're Jeong Yeon, aren't you?
It's me. Han Hyeon Ju
from Joongdo Group Secretary's Office.
What?
Hyeon Ju... Oh, my gosh!
My gosh! What in the world!
Hey! You haven't changed at all!
My parents run this pension.
Really? Daebak.
It's so good to see you! How long has it been?
I know.
So, who's this?
Come.
My husband. Say hello.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Yes. Hello.
Gosh, what am I doing?
I shouldn't let you stand here.
Wait a moment over there.
Please wait just a moment.
Okay.
It's so good to see you.
Hey, you look prettier.
Take a break for a bit.
Your friend?
Yeah.
How neat.
I thought she was a helper.
I almost didn't recognize her.
She used to be drop-dead gorgeous.
[Year 2018]
Hello!
She was an ace of all aces
at the Secretary's Office.
She was super successful.
After the meeting...
She got promoted first out of our colleagues.
CEO.
And she got married first, too.
Although she divorced first, too.
Divorced?
Yeah.
I guess it was a total scam.
Her husband made tons of money in stocks
and got arrested for corporate crime.
I heard he took out tons of loans
under Hyeon Ju's name, too.
Gosh, he got her real good.
On top of that, she's a divorcee with two kids.
Noona, you must be having a hard time.
It must be tough to stay sober.
Look at these pretty flowers and get healed.
Next time, let's come together, Noona.
Bye!
What the heck?
What do you mean?
"Next time, let's come together, Noona. Bye!"
You're so happy. So happy, huh?
You want to die?
I told you to play ignorant.
How can I?
When you're making it so obvious?
What are you going to do?
She's my sister's friend.
Your wife is your friend's sister.
That's not the same.
If your sister finds out, you're dead!
I almost killed you, too,
but you're still alive like this.
Here we go again! Why do you try to one-up me?
Are you preparing for "Show Me the Money"
or something?
Hey, hey. Shut up.
Don't mind me. Mind your own problem.
Prepare for your anniversary, coming up in two days.
Hey, that's truly none of your business.
That's an issue between my wife and me.
It's also about my sister.
You punk, seriously...
What are you going to do about it?
Look at this guy. Aigoo. This guy...
I should just do a turn kick on you.
Geez!
Hey!
They're here.
You got all cocky and passed us. You only got this far?
Wow.
How can we pass this beautiful view?
Hey, come, come here.
Come here.
One, two, three.
Hooray!
Wow, this is amazing!
I know. Daebak!
Seon Hwa!
Wait.
Yeah. I'm at the peak...
You can't hear me?
See? Aren't you glad we came?
Excuse me.
Aigoo.
Thanks to me, you got to come here.
Aren't you grateful?
Yes. I'm so grateful.
So, Geum Ju, let's stay sober.*
(Geumju means "no drinking" in Korean)
You can do it. Fighting!
Fighting! You can do it.
So, cheer up.
It's too bad you didn't win twice in a row.
But you can win again next year.
I got it.
Hey, the DIY car competition
doesn't end this year. Right?
Did you come all the way here to say that?
No.
Look.
♪ You said it'll all be okay now ♪
♪ You smile silently ♪
Isn't this amazing here?
It is. It's amazing.
As good as your healing spot, Lake Bochun,
you go to when you're upset, right?
It is.
It's totally amazing.
Let's cheer up here while we're in Seoul.
Sure. Let's do that.
Thanks.
Okay...
Let's do this! Fighting!
Fighting!
What are you thinking about?
Huh?
The day I was upset about not winning
the DIY car competition.
I just thought of that day.
Yeah. I remember that.
It was so amazing there, too.
Did you go there again?
Since that time while you were in Seoul?
Yeah.
Well, at times?
Hey, you'll catch a cold as you cool down.
I have many patients at the clinic besides you.
So, hurry up and zip up.
What are you doing? Here. I'll do it for you.
Actually, I didn't go.
No, I couldn't go.
Here.
I'm okay, though...
♪ The way I looked at you ♪
♪ I didn't know it was love ♪
♪ My clumsy feelings ♪
♪ It just felt awkward ♪
♪ I tried to forget ♪
♪ I thought I had forgotten ♪
♪ At the end of the time
we spent thoughtlessly ♪
I realized it after you left.
The reason I felt comforted there
wasn't because of the night view.
It was because I was with you.
♪ I am running to you ♪
♪ I call your name, missing you ♪
♪ The days I couldn't let go ♪
♪ I can't go back ♪
Let's go down. We should head home.
♪ 'Cause I still love you ♪
Ta-da! What do you think?
Give me your feedback
since you have an exceptional taste.
This is why you called me out.
But what's up? Can't believe you're shopping.
It's our wedding anniversary in two days.
We're going to a concert,
but I have nothing to wear.
I see...
Hey, how about this one?
Wow!
It totally brightens your face.
Your husband will fall for you again.
What?
Gosh, that can't happen.
He'll go all night.
What the heck?
What? Say that I'm pretty.
He'll say he loves me all night.
What did you imagine?
Aigoo, aigoo, hey.
How can you say that to a divorcee?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I'm so jealous, girl.
You have it so good, girl.
Go and try it on.
Okay.
You should test your liver like me.
I bet your liver numbers are no joke.
Try some.
An uncle in Byeongcheon
made it himself and sent it to us.
Wow!
Wow! The liver is melting in my mouth!
Not this liver. Worry about your liver.
You'll be in big trouble. You'll regret it.
Gosh, come on!
Hyungnim, I don't want to live long.
I'll just eat and drink like this and die.
How much longer would I live anyway?
Hyungnim, I think you're the one regretting.
You look like you're regretting
more than when you lost
your junkyard and the restaurant.
I bet one million won that
Hyungnim will start drinking in a month.
Hi, it's me, Gi Beom's mom.
Be sure to pay me back in full right away.
Gwang Ok, what's that about?
What else?
Looks like you have a lot of money.
Why do you waste your money on daily interest?
What do you mean it's nonsense?
He must be rolling in dough to sit around at a store,
drinking beer and making a bet.
G-Gwang Ok, why are you doing this?
Why?
Don't you have money to throw away?
Instead of helping someone trying to quit,
you encourage him to drink?
A-A-Aigoo... that wasn't it...
Hey, there's a good eel place nearby.
That's great. Let's get some. It's my treat.
Why would you buy?
What do you mean why?
You all made time today for me.
I should repay.
This is how great a person I am.
Put that great person away for now.
Gosh, I'm tired. I just want to go home and rest.
Why? Let's eat and go.
Wow, this place has awesome eel.
We're about to die from exhaustion.
This guy. The driver, Ui Jun, must be exhausted.
Let's go get some eel.
What? "No, no, I don't want to."
You would've said that repeatedly.
What do you mean? She wants
to eat because we're tired.
The chondroitin sulfate found
in eel is good for joints.
And carnosine is excellent
for reducing muscle fatigue.
It's good to eat on days like today
when we walked a lot.
It's my assessment as a doctor.
I-Is that right?
It must be. He's Dr. Seo.
Yeah!
Hey, wake Young Woong up.
He'd wake up right away
when he hears we're eating eel.
Geez, seriously.
Hey, Young Woong, wake up now.
Hey, wake up already!
Hey, hey! Where did he go?
Huh? What are you saying?
What?
Young Woong isn't here!
Call him. Call.
The phone is turned off. After the beep...
His phone is off. The battery must be dead.
Hey, turn the car around!
Geez, how far did these guys go?
Hey, idiot! Get in already!
What are you doing? Get in!
These morons...
Hey!
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, hey, hey! Young Woong!
[Healthy Life, Happy Future, Bochun Medical Center]
Hey,
you should've checked your passengers
before you drove off.
Am I an express bus driver?
To check the number of passengers?
You said you'd be resting in the car first.
What did you do?
What's this?
C-Chestnuts? What are these?
There was a chestnut picking
event, so I did. So what?
You know how much Hwa Yeong likes chestnuts.
My goodness.
If it weren't for those chestnuts,
you would've eaten eel and had a passionate night
with Seon Hwa.
Hey! Come on, seriously! Stop it, already.
What's she talking about?
I mean when you're married...
Don't say stuff like that...
Young Woong...
Young Woong! Young Woong, Young Woong!
Gosh, what exactly happened here, huh?
Don't worry. He'll be fine once he rests for a few days.
Seon Hwa, I'm sorry to make you worry.
No, no. Don't say that.
Gosh, I'm so relieved it's not worse, Young Woong.
Your face is half the size!
Oh, no. I think you lost weight, babe.
You have no idea how scared I was.
Gosh, my heart hurts...
[Dae Geun's House]
In any case, I held out another day.
Great! Let's just keep going like this.
What? Staff dinner?
Hey, what staff dinner while you're on leave?
There's this Mr. Kim...
who says, "Staff dinner is a continuation of work."
He's a typical geezer.
Mr. Kim got promoted.
He joined our team as the chief engineer.
He wants you to come to the welcoming dinner, too.
You know he holds a grudge, right?
If you don't want to suffer when you
get back, you'd better come.
How can I not go?
Working life is not so easy.
Thank you!
In the world full of men,
I worked tenaciously to survive.
Cheers!
I drank tenaciously, too.
As a result, no one could catch up
to me in work and drinking.
Even so, you can't always
control your professional life.
I was able to endure because
of the booze. If I didn't-
How would you know the life
of someone always striving?
Forget striving. You should rehabilitate now.
You can't drink anymore.
I know.
Not to waste the time I spent sober,
I really don't want to drink.
I thought I just had to survive the weekend.
I can't believe I have an even bigger crisis.
It's so hard to quit drinking.
Hey.
Seon Hwa.
Yeah?
The doctor just came by, and he said I can go home now.
What are you talking about?
You insisted on going home.
The doctor said to stay a few more days.
What?
But it's our wedding anniversary.
I really wanted to go to the concert.
You were looking forward to it.
That's not important right now.
Gosh, no, no. Stop rambling.
Do as the doctor says.
Here.
Hey, you go to the concert with Hyeon Ju.
What?
I talked to a divorcee about
my wedding anniversary and all.
I acted without thinking.
That bothered me, so it worked out.
You take her and cheer her up.
Okay!
Nope!
What do you mean nope, you punk?
Hey, you bastard! He's your brother-in-law.
I know. He's so rude, that punk.
What do you mean "That punk," Young Woong?
He's your brother-in-law.
I'm just saying, why are you
sending him with Hyeon Ju?
What do you mean?
Hey, that's right.
Buy Hyeon Ju dinner at a nice place with this.
Be sure to cheer up, okay?
Think of her as your own sister.
No, it's okay, Noona. I'll buy her dinner.
What if he doesn't think of her as his sister?
What if he doesn't think of her as his own sister?
What are you talking about?
It's Hwa Yeong's teacher.
Yes, teacher. Hello. Yes.
What exactly do you want to say,
you brother-in-law punk?
I can expose everything,
you brother-in-law bastard.
Hey.
I will-
I'm sorry. I said I'd take care of it.
You moron brother-in-law!
So, sort out your feelings, you crazy brother-in-law!
I should just...
I'll take care of it, so...
Does it hurt? Does it?
I should just- Hey.
Here.
You came.
Five servings of galbi to go, right?
Gosh, thank you.
Why are you taking so much?
I thought he was going home
in two days. Why not feed him at home?
You know.
Young Woong has a bigger appetite when he's sick.
Aigoo, I'm sure Seon Hwa is feeding him well already.
Feeding him well already?
She makes the food so bland,
saying Young Woong is getting fat.
He has no appetite now.
After he started living with her,
Young Woong looks so haggard.
He's just no good.
Haggard? Who? Young Woong?
Are your eyes bad?
His face is glowing and dripping with oil.
Just stop it, already.
How long will you grumble, wanting
to tear into your daughter-in-law?
Other people would think
this is true. What did I do?
There's no daughter-in-law like her nowadays.
To put it bluntly, does she cause
trouble drunk like you-know-who
or does she ignore her man, being into booze?
Who's that "You-know-who"?
Clamp down on your inappropriate husband.
Don't badmouth my Geum Ju,
who's doing well staying sober.
I didn't badmouth her.
You just never know what will happen.
There will be many occasions
to drink once she's back at work.
Why don't you just pray for her ruin? Huh?
I'm just worried about her.
Don't worry about my daughter.
Ui Jun is taking care of her in so many ways.
Ui Jun?
[Health Examination Result: Han Geum Ju]
I thought I just had to survive the weekend.
I can't believe I have an even bigger crisis.
It's so hard to quit drinking.
[Pneumococcus Vaccination for 65 and Older]
Yes?
Doctor, since we finished early today,
can you make some time for me?
Sure.
Is it important?
Of course. Your life depends on it.
Pardon?
[Her fate is the best fate]
[Fortune Telling Club, Class 3]
To see this day,
I must've joined this club.
You joined a fortune-telling club, too?
What is it you want to tell me?
Oh, my gosh!
You know, the clinic director
wants to set you up with his daughter.
Just in case, I looked up
your compatibility with her.
My goodness! Unbelievable!
It's a match made in heaven!
There's no match made in heaven like this one!
Come on. Why are you doing this?
Why not? You can't miss the match
the heaven has bestowed on you.
He said she's ready to meet you
anytime you give her a call.
Even today.
No. I won't.
Why not?
Why don't you just meet her once?
Will once do?
Once she sees my face, twice, three, four, ten times.
She'd want to keep seeing me.
Gosh, I won't. I don't want to be bothered.
What?
I'll get going first. I have plans.
What plans? Who are you meeting?
Not Han Geum Ju, right?
Gosh, I don't even need to read
her compatibility with you.
It's a fail, starting with her face!
So, did you prepare for the staff dinner?
Yes. Don't worry.
I won't waste the effort I put in thus far.
I have a trick.
A trick?
If they say, "Let's have a drink," I'll say this.
"Gosh, that's too bad.
I brought my car today."
Aigoo, I'll call a driver for you.
Just drink up.
Aigoo, how unfortunate.
I'm taking herbal medicine.
Aigoo, the drink will go down smoother
since you're taking medicine.
Drink up. Cheers!
I have a physical tomorrow.
Oh, that? You just can't drink after 8 p.m.
So drink.
What do you want me to do? Seriously.
Just be honest. Say you quit drinking.
Tell them off and say, "Will you
be responsible if I die like this?"
Hey. Who's going to die, anyway?
Did you forget about your liver?
If it gets worse, it's really dangerous.
You should take this situation seriously.
Gosh! I got it, I got it.
I'll take this seriously. Aigoo...
You wanted to meet,
so you can nag, huh? Aigoo...
I have to go now.
Hey, let's go together. I'll drive you.
I have to go to Seoul, too.
You go to Seoul often.
Like when I bumped into you at Han River.
Right. So, let's not go separately like last time
and waste gasoline. Let's go together.
[Jang Beom June Concert]
Seon Uk!
Hey!
What are you thinking?
Pardon?
Just...
You're so pretty, Noona.
Really?
It was worth getting dolled up, then.
But what do I do? I feel bad for Seon Hwa.
Why should you? She gave them up voluntarily.
Just enjoy it.
Okay.
Noona, give me a moment.
Hey, Hyeon Ju!
Hello.
You're here for the concert, too.
Yeah.
We came to Bochun for this concert.
Since we missed his Seoul concert.
I see.
Noona, here.
Who?
Huh?
My boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
He just said, "Noona"...
Oh, he's younger by five years.
Say hi, babe.
My colleague from my old job
at the Secretary's Office.
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Hi.
So, he's a divorcee, too?
No way.
Never been married.
The concert will begin in a moment.
Please head to your seats...
We'll go ahead.
Enjoy the concert.
Bye now.
Shall we go in, too?
Sorry for lying.
Don't be sorry. Noona, it's okay.
You go in first. Let me...
go to the restroom.
Noona.
[Small Theater]
The customer is not answering the phone.
After the beep...
I thought she was a helper.
I almost didn't recognize her.
What can you do?
She ruined her own life.
My boyfriend.
Noona.
Why did you come here?
How about the concert?
That's no big deal.
I couldn't stand it without drinking.
I was so embarrassed.
About what?
You saw, too.
I guess I wanted to be
pretentious even to that extent.
Because I'm so shabby.
What do you mean shabby?
You're not shabby, Noona.
You were the prettiest out
of all the people at the concert.
Wow! As expected of Bochun's looker!
Bochun's goddess!
I'm not trying to comfort you. You're so...
pretty and elegant, Noona.
And you have such a great personality.
Bold and exciting!
I must be crazy...
Noona.
I'm crazy.
Just die. Die...
Call me when it's over. I'll wait after I'm done.
You don't know when I'll finish, though.
You'll be done early if you don't drink.
All right.
Geum Ju.
Do you know the most difficult thing
while seeing my alcoholic patients?
What?
For them to decide on their own
about wanting to quit.
But you did that.
I hope...
you don't go back on that decision.
Don't worry.
I'll succeed somehow and get what I want from you.
Please do.
Don't regret it.
Thanks for the ride. I'll go.
Okay.
Cheers!
Long time no see!
Just hold out for a week.
As a reward, I'll grant you anything you want.
Yes.
Let's hold out.
Hold out.
Yes, hold out.
What can you do? Mr. Kim-
Oh, he's the chief now.
Anyway, that nuisance...
He insisted that I call you to come
since you're on his side now.
Is he trolling you when you took leave
for not getting the promotion?
Honestly, I was so nervous that you'd quit your job.
No way. I'd never make them happy by quitting.
Wait until I get reinstated.
I'll get my position back.
As expected of Han Geum Ju.
Why aren't you drinking?
Huh?
Well...
Actually...
Chief is here.
Thanks.
Gosh, I'm sorry I'm late.
Ms. Han, you made it.
Congratulations on your promotion, Chief Kim.
Thanks.
Are you enjoying your time off?
Yes. Well, you know.
We're on the same team when you come back.
Let's do a good job.
Yes, sir.
Have a seat. Let's sit down.
Okay.
I came late, but I just caught up with you with this.
As for the wave... give me a bottle.
Let's start with Ms. Han since it's been a while.
No, Chief. I...
I quit drinking.
What?
This is the funniest thing I've heard all year.
You quit drinking, Ms. Han?
Your joke is going too far.
I'm not joking. I really quit.
Hey, why? You even called off
your wedding over alcohol.
To live a healthy life.
What?
This is the second funniest thing I heard this year.
Okay! I got it.
Just drink until tonight
and quit tomorrow and live a healthy life.
If-
I keep drinking, they said I might die.
What?
I don't want to die.
Really? Is that true?
Yes.
Sure, sure.
You shouldn't die.
Then, you won't be drinking, Ms. Han.
Here.
Thank you, Chief Kim.
Now, now, now. Let us drink.
Fill it up.
What?
Who doesn't have any alcohol? Here, here.
Hey, are you really sick? Is that why?
It's not serious. But I might as well.
That's good, then.
But wow, what's up with that moron?
I know.
Congratulations.
This really worked?
Okay, endure!
One shot! One shot!
How do I endure this?
[Seoyeon University Hospital]
Hey, Sunbae.
Can you come out for a second if you're free?
I'm in front of the hospital.
What?
What brings you to Seoul?
I came to see you, Sunbae.
Huh? You came to see me?
That makes no sense.
You came for something else
and are trying to kill time.
Gosh, how can you say that...
so exactly correctly?
Are you a doctor or a shaman?
How are you doing these days?
You're doing well, right?
Let's meet and talk.
Yeah.
Hurry up. I'll be waiting.
I saw Dr. Seo Ui Jun.
What? Dr. Seo Ui Jun?
Didn't you say he works outside of Seoul?
Yeah. I thought he'd be stuck in the countryside.
I wonder what he's doing in Seoul.
He's not trying to come back here, is he?
Gosh, no way. After what he did?
He's afraid of that, and that's why he's in hiding.
Okay, take this starting with this side this time.
Pardon?
Again?
Why? You don't want to?
All right, let's call it a night.
I think you're drunk. I'll call a driver.
No, no... I'm still perfectly fine.
Well...
But...
Ms. Han.
You really won't drink at all?
You can't even drink a glass, huh?
Yes.
Okay...
Fine.
I got it.
Why did he smirk? So offensive.
Sitting sober at a drinking party is such torture.
Oh, here you are.
Oh, be careful, Chief Kim.
Thanks.
But who is it?
What do you mean?
The baby's dad.
Pardon?
You can come clean with me.
You're pregnant, aren't you?
Excuse me?
Why else would you quit drinking, Ms. Han?
Because you couldn't get the promotion,
I thought you left out of anger.
I guess that wasn't it. Why?
Did the hospital tell you to take it easy?
No-
You can fool a ghost, but not me.
You didn't call off your wedding over alcohol.
You had another man, right?
I didn't think so, but you're quite skilled, Ms. Han.
What the heck are you talking about?
It's not like that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't get angry.
Your baby will get scared.
Your stomach just moved, right?
The fetal movement, right?
What are you doing?
Seriously.
If you want to drink, drink nicely.
He's such an SOB now that I see him sober.
What? SOB?
Is she crazy? Hey, you...
Damn it. Hey, you!
Seriously.
You!
Ui Jun.
Who the hell are you, asshole?
Let go of me. Come on.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Stop drinking now.
You were never this bad before
when you were drunk.
You weren't this trashy.
What?
Let's go.
Hey...
Are you okay?
Should you just let this slide?
He had it coming. If he's human, he'd pull it together.
♪ When the life becomes weary ♪
♪ When I feel like going somewhere ♪
♪ Think of me in those moments ♪
♪ I'll be by your side, no questions asked♪
Why are we here?
We were going to cheer up here in Seoul.
I want you to release your anger here.
♪ When you enter your world ♪
How is it?
Are you feeling better now?
What?
Yeah.
Right.
I think so.
♪ I'm within your reach ♪
♪ I'm still behind your shadow ♪
What?
Nothing.
I feel much better.
Yeah.
I feel better, too.
What's going on with you?
Did something happen to you, too?
No. Nothing.
Why?
I think something did happen.
This is no good.
Do you want me to cheer you up for real?
How?
Come here.
Oh, hey!
Hey, look over there. What's that?
Where?
Hey, try to smile.
Okay... hey.
Hey, what is it? Tell me. Hurry. You'd better.
Okay, okay.
Come on.
All right.
Hey, hey, hey! Wait!
Hey, wait! No!
Hey, I'm really scared!
It's so pretty.
Hey, look at this!
[Successfully sober for one week!]
I did it! I succeeded!
Aigoo! I'm so proud of you!
Aigoo, good job, good job. So proud of you.
Congrats.
I was able to withstand critical moments, thanks to you.
Thanks.
What did I do?
Well, that's that.
You'll keep your promise, right?
You'll grant one thing I want, right?
All right. I got it.
Say it.
What do you want?
Answer my question honestly.
What?
That's it?
It's not a small thing.
I've been wanting to hear it for so long.
I tenaciously kept my promise
so I can hear this from you.
Why did you cut me off?
I was going to let it stay in the past
but when else would I hear the reason if not for this?
I still don't understand...
why we had to drift apart back then.
Because I liked you too much.
♪ The love began again
when you called my name ♪
Because I liked you so much.
♪ Can't stop now ♪
♪ I am running to you ♪
♪ I call you name, missing you ♪
♪ The days I couldn't let go ♪
♪ I can't go back ♪
♪ 'Cause I still love you ♪
[Epilogue]
Han Geum Ju...
[I love you, Han Geum Ju]
♪ I don't know, it's because of you ♪
♪ I can't stop smiling ♪
♪ I didn't know this would happen ♪
[Second Shot at Love]
Because I liked you so much.
Sorry. I had no idea.
Because I like fish. I like...
Because I like big cars.
I think you're feverish, too.
No, I'm fine.
You should've confessed your love 10 years ago!
Were you the only one young and naive?
I liked you back then, too.
I'll try harder.
Until you open up to me.
I'll take care of you from now on, Geum Ju.
♪ No matter how brightly the world shines ♪
♪ I only see you ♪