(Kim Byung Chul)
(Yoon Se Ah)
(Park Ju Hyun)
(Kim Young Dae)
(Yoon Sang Hyun)
(Choi Ye Bin, Lee Si Woo)
(Kim Do Hyun, Special Starring: Kim Myung Soo)
(Perfect Family)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Staff ensured child actors' safety in the filming of this drama.)
(Episode 3)
Who is it?
It's Sun Hui's friend, Su Yeon.
Su Yeon, it's you.
Is Sun Hui home?
I'm afraid she isn't feeling well today,
and we have a visitor.
- Maybe some other time... - I must see her.
It won't take long. Can you let me in?
Please.
Get up.
Get up, darn it!
What are you playing at?
You set the fire, didn't you?
Why did you do it?
Why?
Why on earth did you set the house on fire?
Whatever you do...
won't change the fact that you killed Gyeong Ho.
Right?
You killed him.
That's what we agreed on.
Right, Sun Hui?
Right?
Say something!
How did the situation escalate like this?
Some more people have died.
It doesn't matter, though.
Turn yourself in.
Are you once again...
going to pin the fire on me?
Like you did back in the day?
No.
No, Su Yeon.
You were adopted by this family...
and have been living the dream.
But because of you,
my life was flushed down the drain.
This is the very moment to pay back the debt.
Sun Hui.
Your dad's a hotshot lawyer.
Wouldn't he get you out of this mess somehow?
I'm sure he'll handle the matter...
as long as you turn yourself in.
I can't.
What?
I...
I can't turn myself in, Su Yeon.
If...
If I do,
my mom...
Your mom?
Are you worried you'll disappoint her?
You think you'll be abandoned?
I almost had a mom of my own!
If only you hadn't ruined my chances.
You took everything from me,
but you still won't help me?
Su Yeon, it's not what you think.
Shut it, you obnoxious cow!
I'm reporting you.
I'm reporting you to the police.
I won't be lying since you started the fire.
You did this.
You killed them. Not just Gyeong Ho,
but also his parents!
We're off to the police station, so get ready.
Mr. Choi.
Are you done talking already?
Sorry?
Are you leaving?
Sun Hui and I have somewhere to go.
Why would she leave when she's sick?
Where to?
Do you want me to drive you?
No, that's all right.
Take care.
Oh, no.
(Perfect Family)
(Self-Directed Learning Room 3)
(Did you watch the news? It's Gyeong Ho's place, right?)
(It's his house. I've been there before.)
(No way!)
(That's insane.)
(It's terrifying.)
(Paint thinner was found at his house.)
(Has he been inhaling that?)
(Could he have set the house on fire while inhaling it?)
(He set the house on fire while intoxicated on paint thinner?)
(It wasn't paint thinner, but drugs.)
Drugs?
Well,
you saw Gyeong Ho's house burn down.
What about it?
Rumour has it that he set the house on fire...
while intoxicated on paint thinner or drugs.
(Police)
Hey, what brings you here?
Hey, I have something to tell you.
You came at the right time. Come in.
Come in.
Ta-da!
What is all this?
It's a surprise for Sun Hui.
What do you think? Does it look okay?
My goodness, this one is...
It's horrible.
What?
Gosh.
What a nice thing to say.
Don't do stuff like this.
- Why not? - You will fail.
You...
Do you...
Do you also...
like Sun Hui?
What?
I was only joking.
Can you text her...
to drop by my place after her classes end?
It'll be more of a surprise if it comes from you.
You can do that for a friend, right?
Check this out. Once she enters the house,
she'll be led this way...
Darn, that's out of place again.
Gyeong Ho.
Yes?
You gave this to Sun Hui, didn't you?
Why do you have it?
She gave it to me,
saying she wasn't interested in you.
Sun Hui couldn't care less about your feelings.
Will you still tell her how you feel, though?
Sun Hui...
isn't like that.
What?
She isn't like that.
Whether you found it or stole it, give it back to her.
I don't want to.
- Then give it to me. - I don't want to.
It's mine now.
Gosh, why are you doing this?
Why are you giving Sun Hui a hard time?
Give it to me.
Why...
can't I have anything?
Hand it over.
What are you doing? Are you out of your mind?
Yes, I'm out of my mind.
- Let go. - Stop it.
Let go of me!
What's wrong with you?
I'm out of my mind. Let me go.
Let me go!
- Come back to your senses. - Hey!
Gosh.
- Su Yeon. - Stay away from me!
Why did...
the hope that I barely found...
disappear so fast?
Please don't look.
Don't look.
Goodbye.
- Su Yeon. - Now...
Put that down.
Put it down, Su Yeon.
People like me...
might as well die.
Su Yeon, what's wrong with you?
- What are you doing? - Let me go.
Don't apologize!
- Let me go! - Hey!
This is none of your business!
Su Yeon.
Sun Hui.
Why are you here?
Su Yeon...
You promised me that you wouldn't come.
Why don't you keep your promise?
You are making me miserable!
My life is ruined...
all because of you.
It's all because of you!
Sun Hui.
Sun Hui, you should eat.
Dad stepped out for a moment,
so let's eat first.
Mom.
Yes?
If...
the police come...
Why would the police come here?
Let's eat.
Mom.
Are you really not going to tell me?
Why my cell phone and workbook are...
back in my room?
What happened...
at Gyeong Ho's house last night?
How would I know what happened at Gyeong Ho's place?
My daughter,
you still seem unwell.
Let's eat when your dad returns home.
(We're Happy to Serve Our Citizens.)
Now that I've gotten old,
every joint in my body hurts.
(Rejuvenate Your Joints)
I'm all good. I feel much better now.
I'm good. Nothing hurts at all.
Detective Lee.
Did you find anything in Park Gyeong Ho's cell phone and computer?
Hey, what are you doing? Did you fall asleep?
No.
I tested if I could sleep with one eye open.
That's ridiculous.
Haven't you seen "Leon: The Professional?"
What about "Leon: The Professional?" Are you bringing up movies again?
This is what Mathilda says to Leon who is a killer.
"I've never seen anyone snore with one eye open."
That's exactly what I'm saying.
Did you find anything in his computer?
Nothing interesting.
I found nothing in particular in his recent history.
He was in Australia until a year ago.
Like a troublemaker, he smoked and inhaled paint thinner there too.
It's not so surprising.
Girls acquainted with him were absent.
And his guy friend went home early, so I couldn't meet any of them.
Wasn't she at the scene of the accident?
Gosh. Yes, that's her.
She's one of the students who were absent.
Her name is Lee Su Yeon.
I need to meet her.
Lee Su Yeon.
At which speed do you want me to push you?
Speed level four.
Okay.
Faster. This is fun.
- Is it fun? - Su Yeon.
Come in.
Come in, Su Yeon.
Su Yeon, say hello.
Hello.
Is your name Su Yeon?
Would you let me see your face?
What's wrong? Do you find me scary?
My goodness.
It's okay.
We'll get going.
Please get back safely.
What a fool.
I'm so stupid.
(Lee Su Yeon)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the beep...
(Lee Su Yeon)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the beep.
There will be charges...
It's for you.
I got it customized. That's why it took so long.
Gosh.
That's hilarious.
It's fascinating.
I know.
(Fire in Ihyeon-dong)
("A House Catches Fire and Kills the Entire Family")
(Father of the family was a painter.)
(He possessed paint thinners.)
Gyeong Ho.
Yes?
Oh, hello.
Hello.
Hyeon U.
I wanted to go to Gyeong Ho's funeral with Sun Hui.
Oh, I see.
Hyeon U, you're here.
Hey.
Are you feeling okay, Sun Hui?
Yes.
Are you okay, Sun Hui?
Sun Hui.
Sun Hui?
Are you okay?
Have some water.
Dad.
Sun Hui, are you okay?
She seems to be in a big shock.
Let's go.
Get home safely.
Thanks, Hyeon U.
Sure.
See you.
Are you sure you don't have to see a doctor?
I just want to go home.
Since you were close to Gyeong Ho,
you won't feel better anytime soon.
Losing a close friend...
could fade over time.
But you'll have to live with that scar...
in your heart for the rest of your life.
Dad.
Have you also parted with a friend before?
A friend?
Sure, I could call it that.
Anyway, what matters...
is the family that is living with us.
I have...
you and your mom.
And you have Mom and Dad.
Not everything will go back to its place right now.
But as time goes by,
it will all go back to when it was perfect.
Your mom and I will help,
so will you follow us?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's go home.
It's here.
Gosh, it's incredible.
It is a huge mansion.
I should've become a lawyer too.
You couldn't have with that brain of yours.
I could have! And...
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Wait in the car. - Okay.
What's going on?
We're the police.
Regarding the fire at Gyeong Ho's house,
we have a few questions to ask his friend.
Please cooperate.
A fire?
Yes, we have a few questions we'd like to ask your daughter...
regarding the fire.
Give me this as a present.
What do you think? Isn't it a good idea?
I can't have it?
Why is this...
in this car?
Thank you.
We're the detectives in charge of the recent fire case.
There are some things we need to check.
Sun Hui, we heard you were close to Gyeong Ho,
one of the victims in the house that burned down.
Is that right?
Yes.
Did you hear anything from Gyeong Ho recently?
Like his concerns and stuff.
Not much.
Not much?
Then do you know a girl called Lee Su Yeon?
Yes.
Was she Gyeong Ho's girlfriend?
No, she wasn't.
I see.
We can't reach her.
Can you reach her?
Sun Hui, you're in the same class as Su Yeon, right?
Yes.
And you two were close?
Yes, we were,
- but... - But?
I also...
didn't see her.
- Let's go. - Sorry?
Please excuse us.
- Thank you for your time. - Wait, Dong Ho.
Oh, gosh. Goodness.
Oh, right.
Sun Hui, if Su Yeon calls you,
please call us at this number.
Sure.
Okay. Goodbye, then.
Goodness.
Sun Hui.
Why didn't you tell them that Su Yeon was here?
Well, I...
Sun Hui, you sure take after me.
It's good that you didn't tell them that Su Yeon was here yesterday.
It's true that you didn't see her today,
so you weren't lying about that.
And the detectives didn't ask if you saw her yesterday,
so there was nothing wrong with your answer.
She's indeed the daughter of a lawyer.
- Are you happy? - Of course.
Choi Sun Hui.
Don't be scared.
I got you.
No matter what happens,
I'm on your side.
I...
will go back to my room and rest. I'm tired.
Dong Ho, I had more questions to ask. Why did you leave?
What more was there ask?
She's obviously hiding something.
Asking any further questions would've been a waste of time.
Dong Ho! Wait for me!
(Lee Su Yeon)
(Su Yeon, where are you?)
(Did something happen? Su Yeon, are you okay?)
The phone is turned off.
You will be redirected after the tone.
There will be charges...
Hey, Hyeon U.
Hey, Sun Hui. What's up?
Did you happen to get any text from Su Yeon?
No, not yet.
The police just came by our place.
The police went to your place?
Why?
They asked about Su Yeon and Gyeong Ho.
I see.
Do the police think the fire...
at Gyeong Ho's place is related to Su Yeon?
Last time,
you walked Gyeong Ho and Su Yeon to their houses, right?
Can you tell me where Su Yeon lives?
Sure. Should I tag along with you?
No, it's okay. I'll go alone.
Oh, gosh.
Who are you?
I'm Su Yeon's friend.
Okay. What about her?
You see, I can't get in touch with her.
Did she cause another problem at school?
Sorry?
She hasn't come home in days.
Even the police came by this morning.
She promised to attend school diligently.
If she contacts you,
tell her that her sister is worried...
and to call me first.
Oh, okay.
You punk!
What on earth is the problem?
It simply doesn't feel right.
Feel right, my foot. Stop spouting nonsense.
Are you implying this case is connected to teenagers?
Then, quit being a detective...
and guide teenagers to the right path!
And...
think like a modern detective.
Stop investigating with your gut!
Why don't you resign...
and become a fortune teller, you hayseed?
Good grief. What an eyesore.
Get lost.
Why don't you get lost?
You little...
You pretended to cough to badmouth me, right?
No. I'm coming down with a cold.
Stop causing trouble.
Only do what you're told. Got it?
Gosh. What's the use of not investigating deeper?
(The Nation's Police, Righteous Korea)
If you're that unhappy with the orders, quit your job!
Quit your job as a detective and establish your own police station.
Seriously. And how am I supposed to do that?
Look at you. How dare you talk back at me?
What a cheap and nasty guy. I should get promoted.
What was that?
I can hear you, you know?
I'll become the Commissioner General.
You jerk. Do you have a death wish?
Enough.
- Chief. - What is it?
- What? - We have the autopsy results.
It's unlikely to be asphyxia.
Look at the stab wounds.
- What is it? - You punk!
Aren't these Park Gyeong Ho's autopsy results?
Give it back!
- Come on! - Give me a minute.
Let me take a look, all right?
"Results show the cause of death was not carbon monoxide poisoning."
"There is a possibility that it was caused by a stab wound."
"The possibility!"
Are you still going to tell us to close the case?
Are you?
- Are you? - Are you?
That day, after leaving my house,
she cut off all contact and disappeared?
And...
Su Yeon's belonging was found in Dad's car.
But why?
Sun Hui.
You're so big now.
Do you remember me?
Who are you?
Did I scare you?
I'm a relative of your dad's.
I came by last time, but only got to see you today.
Oh, I see. Hi.
I don't blame you.
We met when you were little.
It's natural not to remember me.
Why are you looking at me like that?
What?
It's nothing.
Is that the window to your room?
No.
Then whose room is it?
Don't you know?
I'm sorry for asking something weird.
Anyway, I'll see you around.
I'll come by often.
Sure.
Sun Hui.
Be careful...
of your dad and mom.
(Epilogue)
It's boring.
I hate myself for not living up to the expectations.
My father won't acknowledge my paintings.
It apparently has no personal appeal.
I don't agree with him.
I believe...
you should paint as you wish.
Why don't we draw each other's faces?
- Sun Hui. - Yes?
Face the front.
- The front? - Yes.
Yes, just like that.
Perfect.
How am I supposed to draw like this?
Don't expect too much.
But I like it.
I'm almost done.
All it needs are some final touches.
I'm done.
What?
It's amazing.
Hey, stop it. It's embarrassing.
No, I'm serious.
Here. Let me take a look.
I see.
Let me have this.
Okay.
I may be an ugly duckling right now.
But I should live as I am.
I'll give it to her tomorrow.
(Perfect Family)
How much more must we hide it?
I'm home, Sun Hui.
What is it? Where are you going?
Please wait here.
She seems to know something.
Why do you have that?
What now?
We better move our plan forward.
Why are my parents trying to keep this boy a secret?
Shut it!