(Kim Byung Chul)
(Yoon Se Ah)
(Park Ju Hyun)
(Kim Young Dae)
(Yoon Sang Hyun)
(Choi Ye Bin, Lee Si Woo)
(Kim Do Hyun, Special Starring: Kim Myung Soo)
(Perfect Family)
(All people, locations, organizations,)
(incidents, and backstories in this drama are fictitious.)
(Happy Birthday, Sang Ho.)
(Final episode)
Let's eat.
Sure.
How was...
the seaweed soup?
My daughter.
Sun Hui.
You're alive.
- Where are you? - I've been...
watching you.
What do you say to a new life together?
A man and his biological daughter. Just the two of us.
You can no longer...
live with those people anyway.
That being said,
can you do me a favor?
What...
can I do?
The pills I gave you were strong, weren't they?
That's...
my girl.
Keep your promise.
You don't have to remind me.
I have no more business with these two.
I'll never...
bother them again.
Would you like...
to taste what I cooked, Dad?
I'm good.
I'll have this.
Wait.
Is it too soon to have a drink...
before the deed is over?
For us to start a new life,
we'll need money.
There's a safe in his study.
It has money.
The lock combination...
is my birthday.
Your birthday?
Was it...
June 29?
That's 0629.
(Perfect Family)
- Enter passcode. - It's 0629.
Invalid passcode.
Sun Hui.
It's not opening.
Whose birthday...
is June 29?
Oh, right.
I got it wrong.
Your date of birth is... Let's see.
I'm certain.
Can't you remember?
It came to me.
Enter passcode.
- Invalid passcode. - Darn.
- Enter... - My birthday.
The date...
I was born.
Invalid passcode.
Enter passcode.
- Invalid passcode. - You!
Dad.
Don't you remember my birthday?
Of course I remember!
Your birthday is...
Enter...
Invalid passcode.
When is it?
- When was it again? - Invalid passcode.
- Invalid passcode. - Darn!
Your birthday...
Your birthday.
That day,
the sun was blinding.
And it was scorching.
(Mirae Maternity Hospital)
(Choi Sun Hui)
Sun Hui.
You were born...
Enter passcode.
(Choi Sun Hui, Date of Birth: August 27, 2007)
Got it.
With money,
I can be...
a good dad too.
This was...
the only way.
I'm sorry.
Mom?
You can't.
You're my precious daughter.
I told you...
I would protect you.
We...
are family.
What happened here?
(3 years later)
Have you been well?
As always, I'm doing well.
It's already been three years since you went to Canada.
Everyone is worried because we can't get a hold of you.
It's been the same for me.
Recently, I had a school assignment of making a house blueprint.
My professor told me that...
my floor plan was unrealistic.
I wanted to create a space where everyone living inside...
could have a good time.
A place that no one has seen before.
I guess my intention didn't seem clear.
It's difficult.
A place where...
someone is waiting for you.
A place where someone returns.
I want to build a house...
that makes the family life richer.
That's my goal now.
My dream that I told you about...
became clearer.
Speaking of houses,
I visited your house a few days ago.
After remodeling, the house became cleaner.
Thank you for letting me see the house.
I'll get going now.
Stay for dinner.
- But I... - You should if you have time.
Then, shall I?
Thank you.
Your parents are doing well,
but they can't hide how empty they feel.
Su Yeon is expected to be released from prison next month.
Sun Hui.
What are you thinking now?
I don't know if you'll read this email,
but I hope that you're staying healthy.
(I miss you.)
I miss you.
(Send)
(Sent)
(Choi Jin Hyuk, Ha Eun Ju, Choi Sun Hui)
(Sergeant Lee Seong Woo's Tomb)
Is it snowing over there too?
Things have been the same here.
I'm still using the lighter that you gave me.
It looks like a famous scene from a movie.
Which movie was it?
You would have told me which movie it was...
right away.
A Japanese horror movie?
A family breaks down?
That sounds fun.
A girl named Mathilda says this to Leon who's a killer.
"I've never seen anyone snore with one eye open."
Oh, right.
You don't smoke.
We bought a lot again when there are only two of us.
You're right.
What's the matter?
I feel like...
someone is watching us.
I must be wrong.
Hyeon U.
I'm really sorry.
I don't even prick my finger even when I have an upset stomach.
I'm fine now, so I forgive you.
Thank you so much.
Sis.
You've been through a lot.
Thank you.
I should get going. Take your time. I'm going to work.
Okay.
What do you want for dinner?
I want sujebi made by you.
Gosh, okay.
See you.
I miss Sun Hui.
Although I have no right.
Sun Hui?
I can't get a hold of her anymore.
She moved to Canada,
but no one can get a hold of her now.
Everyone is worried.
I heard that she hasn't been to school for two months.
I see.
What is it?
At the orphanage,
Sun Hui said that she wanted to be a mom all of a sudden.
You mean, your mom?
Yes. Isn't that funny?
She was a child, but she wanted to be a mom.
I didn't know Sun Hui said something like that.
She probably said that...
because I have never seen my mom.
Sun Hui said, "I'll be your mom..."
"and protect you so that no one can hurt you."
That's what she said.
It made me so happy to hear that.
To me,
it was such a great hope.
No, that's not the way. Scratch it faster and harder.
No. You can't do it slowly.
Faster and harder.
I'm scared.
You shouldn't be.
I'm not scared at all.
You say that because you're brave.
You said you would become my mom.
A mom should be brave to protect her child.
You're right.
I'm your mom. You're my mom.
Moms should be brave.
Here. Eat this, Su Yeon.
Oh, my.
I could never imagine...
how the love and warmth of a family feels.
I thought she was the definition of a family.
When Sun Hui and I drifted apart,
I couldn't even sleep well because I was so lonely.
But since that day,
I was so lost...
to the point...
where I couldn't see my future.
Then I thought of Sun Hui.
I wished she could be there to help me.
That's why I went to her school...
to look for her.
I see.
It would have been better...
if I were honest with her from the start.
I was bad at expressing my feelings...
that I cornered her even when I liked her.
I made her suffer so much.
When Sun Hui comes back,
you can just tell her that.
Right.
I wish I could do that.
It's quiet.
Right.
Do you...
remember?
What?
When we first brought Sun Hui to our place...
after adopting her from the orphanage,
Sun Hui seemed nervous as she entered the house.
She couldn't move from the front door.
Right, she couldn't.
That's when her stomach growled.
It was really loud.
I thought she was hungry.
So I wanted to feed her.
I asked her, "What do you want to eat?"
Right, what did she say?
She said she wanted to eat fish cake.
So I quickly made a dish...
with all the ingredients in the fridge.
Right.
She said it was the best fish cake she'd ever had.
She ate a lot of it.
Then I told myself...
that I would make delicious food...
just for this little girl...
for the rest of my life.
I think...
I just saw Sun Hui.
Sun Hui?
Sun Hui!
Welcome home.
You must be hungry. Let's eat.
I'm sorry I made you worry.
I thought I should be gone...
so that both of you...
could be happy.
I should have...
disappeared then.
But I was too scared.
After that day,
no matter how far I went,
I missed you both...
very much.
So for the last time...
For the last time...
I wanted to leave...
after seeing all of you one last time.
That's what I told myself before coming here.
We were waiting for you.
Leave? What do you mean by that?
Do I deserve...
to live with you?
Of course.
You are my daughter.
You are my everything.
I don't know what to do.
I don't deserve...
to hear those things from you.
All I did was try to cover everything up...
when you said you stabbed Gyeong Ho.
I thought it was the right thing to do for you.
But actually, I did that for myself.
I couldn't let my family...
break down again without doing nothing like a fool.
I could not...
lose you no matter what.
Seized by those thoughts,
I failed to see you...
as you were despite being before me.
Even though you must've been watching me,
it never...
crossed my mind to watch you.
Because of me, you took on everything...
and ended up suffering.
Sun Hui.
I'm sorry.
Your dad,
you, and me.
None of us are perfect.
Even so,
if one cries, we'll give them a hug.
If one smiles, we'll hold their hands.
Can't we live like that?
We need you in our lives, Sun Hui.
As a family.
Your mom and I aren't perfect.
But can we still be your parents?
May I...
live...
as your daughter?
Of course, Sun Hui.
Mom.
Dad.
Thank you.
Dear Grandmother.
I hope you're doing well.
Please forgive me for sending you this letter...
out of the blue.
Dad once told me...
to write a letter...
if I wanted to convey my sincerity.
He said...
Mom was the one who suggested it first.
I want to take a family photo.
It would be nice if you could join us.
Hoping you would come,
I will be waiting.
From your granddaughter who believes you,
Sun Hui.
I abandoned my family.
I couldn't keep the family together.
It's my fault.
I was desperately trying to survive alone.
Little did I know my youngest was getting bullied.
I left him to die.
My eldest...
blamed himself for it and was in pain.
And yet, I didn't take good care of my eldest.
That was the sort of mother I was.
I was...
also quite hard...
on Sun Hui.
But to ask me to come.
Will you really not regret joining them?
What would I do if I go there?
I'm not sure.
But you have...
always made...
a decision...
without consulting me until now.
If, by any chance,
you're debating whether to go or not,
doesn't it mean...
you haven't given up yet unconsciously?
My apologies for crossing the line.
Where's Sun Hui?
She asked us to wait a little.
Your necktie.
Thank you for coming.
I'll walk from here.
I'll wait here.
What do you think?
Will it look empty without it?
Let's see.
Dad.
Yes, Sun Hui?
- Mother. - Your daughter told me to come.
Let me apologize to you.
I put you in agony, didn't I?
I'm sorry for everything.
I...
didn't try to understand your feelings.
I'm sorry for everything.
Eun Ju.
You must've suffered the most.
I'm sorry for everything.
Mother.
I'll take the photo.
A big smile, everyone.
One, two, three.
Goodness, the color looks very appetizing.
- Honey. Take this, please. - Sure.
Thank you.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(Thank you for watching Perfect Family.)
(Perfect Family)