Hongyo and Akari-san,
did something happen on their date?
I'm curious...
But not really!
Well,
by doing it just once or twice with Hongyo,
I felt like I had more advantage than Akari-san,
but, in reality,
that thing has no meaning at all.
What are you doing Terada-san?
Cleaning up the sink...
You're working hard...
No...
I'm free anyway...
I...
...have always waited.
I've never done anything.
I never did something myself.
Hongyo!
What?
Well...
I mean...
Think of something! Think of something!
Just say anything that I can do right now.
Terada-san?
Sleeping together,
do you want to do it?
Well, I mean, only if you really need it...
Really?
When?
Tonight?
Tonight is a bit...
Then, how about tomorrow?
All right.
Thank you, Terada-san.
You just saved me.
Good night, then.
Good night.
I saved him, huh?
Huh?
Is this okay, though?
I like it like that babe, give me last first kiss ♫
English subtitle by eveychooey
I'm getting sucked into it ♫
Our eyes meet, Our hands touch ♫
Afterwards, la la love motion ♫
I like it like that babe, give me last first kiss ♫
I'm being drawn into it ♫
I can't stop it, I don't want to stop it ♫
Just the two of us, la la LOVE-cation ♫
It's a secret ♫
KAKAFUKAKA
Screw-Up Adults'
Sharehouse
It's not okay after all...
I've thought about it all night long,
and I felt that this isn't right after all.
Let's cancel it...
He's not there?
Ah? Terada-san?
- Good work today.
- You too.
Would you like a cup of coffee?
Yes, thank you.
Those kind of feelings...
...are what I have for Tomoya.
- Here.
- Thank you.
By the way,
um...
Did something happen?
I wonder how you felt after going on a date with Hongyo...
I'm a bit curious...
Ah, right...
I've tried asking him a favor, though.
A favor?
There's still one more proposal.
I have a favor to ask you...
I-I-I want you to give me a hug and a kiss...
If we're going to marry,
I think those things are important.
I don't think that's possible.
WHY?!
Doing those kind of things with you,
I think,
it would feel like I'm peeing on a stone statue of Jizo (guardian deity of children). Or something like that.
- Peeing...?
- Well, to be honest, I felt a bit glad.
That means, Tomoya thinks of me as a sacred thing that shouldn't be stained,
or, a holy ground that he shouldn't invade, right?
Why? Is there any problem?
Our feelings are mutual, in a way.
But, still...
I feel like it made me want to try all those things with him even more.
Is that so...
I see.
Akari-san feels those were some nice words.
That means...
Nothing happened on that date, huh?
I feel relieved.
Huh? Terada-san?
You're heading home?
Yes.
- Good evening.
What are you gonna cook today?
No. Akari-san won't be home tonight, so, I think I'll eat at a convenience store.
Then. How about eating out somewhere?
- But...
- Why?
Are you nervous after I seriously proposed to you?
Well....
You really are.
I feel glad that you're aware of my feelings.
I really want to eat yakiniku right now.
Please come with me.
Yakiniku...
This is...
...different from the yakiniku I know!!
Really? This is the kind of yakiniku I always eat.
I'll go for the tongue! Tongue!
But, before eating the meat,
you want some salad first?
No, I'm fine. I'll scoop it myself.
Then. I'll dig in first.
That's the way it is, huh?
"Adequate for my needs."
Never mind.
Let's grill the tongue.
So good!
Today was truly a feast.
Thank you so much!
Don't mention it.
It was really good!
It was my first time eating that kind of meat.
Glad to hear that.
What should we do next? Go for a second round?
Ah, no...
I already have plans for today...
Plans? After this?
Yes.
What is it? Sleep with Tomo again?
How do you know?
So, that's true...
You're still gonna do that for real?
You were so worried about being pregnant that you couldn't tell Tomo anything.
Now that you're not pregnant, you decided to do it again so easily?
I mean, Tomo also already thought about doing that again, huh?
Are you a fool, Terada-san?
Yes.
I'm a fool.
You know,
I'm already so full right now.
So, good night.
Hase-san's heartbeat,
I could feel it clearly.
Come to think of it,
being hugged normally like this,
this is the first time after a long time.
What should I do?
I might enjoy this...
The relationships I've had so far were,
when I was in junior high, with this carefree little ordinary boy,
Hongyo Tomoya.
Our relationship didn't last long.
The second guy was when I was in high school.
Let's just break up.
I didn't even know why I dated him.
We broke up so easily.
Then...
The 3rd boyfriend that I had dated since we were university students,
he cheated on me,
or had a change of heart.
In other words,
In my whole life,
I've never had any memories of being passionately needed by someone.
This isn't right.
This isn't right!
I feel like,
I am, indeed,
enjoying this.
Ah, sorry!
I have to go back to the office.
Can you go home by yourself?
Yes.
I'm sorry. You can use this for the taxi fare...
No need to! I'm fine. Really.
Is that so?
Then, take care.
Thank you for today.
I'm the one who is thankful. Thank you for the meal.
Darn it!
I wanted to slowly close the gap between us, but why was I impulsively doing that?
But...
Tomo also already thought about doing that again, huh?
Are you a fool, Terada-san?
Yes.
I'm a fool.
I think you should stop sleeping together with him.
I'm afraid that you may experience something bad later.
Welcome home.
I'm home!
You went out?
Yes. To have dinner.
By the way...
Hongyo.
It's about our sleeping-together plan.
Sorry!
Is it okay if we don't do it tonight?
Forgive me for saying such a selfish thing!
But, you know, after I thought about it once more,
I felt this isn't quite right...
But you were the one who suggested it.
Why cancel it now?
I was trying to tell you this morning, but, you weren't home.
I really...
...feel guilty towards you,
but, today...
Well...
But...
Hongyo?
I get it. Let's not do it today.
I'm really sorry! Hongyo...
He looked a bit scary...
Hongyo...
Was he mad?
It's nice to know that someone needs me.
While thinking about Hase-san's heartbeat,
I can't help but imagining the warmth of Hongyo's body on my back right now.
Somehow...
I feel suffocated.
It's killing me.
Is this because I feel guilty towards Hongyo?
Or...
Basically, Terada-san has no confidence in herself.
That's why, she tends to get influenced easily.
I impulsively hugged her last night and she hugged me back because she couldn't help it.
If that's the case,
then, I should make a good use of it.
Hase-san...
Good morning!
You got up early even though it's your day off.
I'm thinking of finishing my work at home today.
Is that so?
Request : Mapo Tofu - Sichuan-Style.
"Sichuan-style..."
Can I make it?
Terada-san, can you help me for a moment?
Of course I will pay you.
I want to stick some materials into a scrapbook.
- Yes. I can help you with that.
- Really?
Then, let's do it.
I'll be in my room, okay?
Okay.
He's great as usual...
By the way,
you didn't sleep together last night, did you?
No...
Glad to hear that.
Also, I'm sorry for doing such a weird thing yesterday.
No.
Don't worry about that.
I also sent you that message in the end.
You know, it was also my first time doing something impulsive like that.
I don't know why I did that.
Terada-san gets influenced easily,
so, she just needs something to trigger her.
Hase-san?
Ah, but, this kind of excuse might sound too far-fetched.
Wait...
Hase-san?
What?
I'm so tired!
Let's take a break.
Sorry, we've got a lot of materials here.
Well...
You know, um, I just...
...remembered...
I got some work to do...
Is that so?
Then, that's it...
...for today.
Goodbye...
What was that?
It was only for a brief moment, but he kissed me?
But...
maybe,
I was...
...slightly aware of that.
I knew Hase-san is serious about me.
It would be embarrassing if I misunderstood him, so I denied it desperately, to cover it up.
I stepped into that room without having any expectations.
I got carried away...
...for a while.
I think...
...I must have turned her off, right?
Yes. I'm sure of it.
I mean,
I'm so incompetent!
I was too hasty, no matter how I look at it...
By using such a lame excuse,
I invited her to my room.
What was I doing, really?
I think I got carried away somehow...
But...
I didn't feel anything at all.
It was just...
...a simple kiss.
If it was Hongyo,
I would have exploded!
Somehow...
Being touched by him already made me happy,
embarrassed...
and feel weird...
From the back side of my stomach,
I'd have felt the explosion.
I see...
So, that's how it is...
I realized it once again...
Hase, you were home?
Yes. I'm working at home today.
- You're making coffee?
- Yes.
You want some too?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Are you waiting for Terada-san?
No.
I see.
Come to think of it, Tomo...
...did it with Terada-san, right?
I wonder...
...how he feels about her.
Such a good smell.
You startled me!
It's because I just bought it.
What are you doing, Tomo?
It's indeed this smell.
Your perfume.
What about that?
When Terada-san came home last night,
I smelled this perfume.
That smell wouldn't have lingered on her if you just went out together, right?
I was marking my scent on her.
I'm going back to my room.
The coffee will be ready in a minute. Please enjoy it!
After that kiss with Hase-san,
I'm even more convinced about my feelings for Hongyo.
What should I do?