=Dream in the Mirror=
=Episode 14=
So you're actually that amazing.
But why you...
I've heard that hostages
practicing martial arts
is a capital offense.
From now on,
you must listen to me.
Don't you remember me?
I've traveled all over the place
and met too many people.
Memory lapses happen.
Does the Floating Sea Market
really exist?
How do you know about it?
I told you?
Of course.
Double Blossom Mirror came from
the Floating Sea Market.
You saw it yourself.
It worked, didn't it?
The stuff I sell works
just like the store owners tell me.
I spent a lot on them.
But every time I sell something,
they called me a swindler.
You're injured?
What?
By day, it's Zhao Qingqing,
at night, it's Nanyan?
Why would I lie?
But let me tell you,
you mustn't tell anyone.
Forgot the water.
Mr. Baili, you're injured?
It's nothing.
Let me apply medicine for you.
No need, you may go.
I'm idle anyway.
I also feel reassured
watching you here.
Idle, seriously?
Have you chopped the wood?
Fed the fish?
Swept floor? Cleaned windows?
So many things to do,
yet you see no work.
Mr. Baili,
if I did all these chores,
what would servants do?
Just do it.
Apply the medicine.
What are you looking at?
Take off your clothes.
If you don't undress,
how should I apply it?
Sweep the floor?
I'm doing all the chores.
Sweep the floor,
mop the floor...
General,
Baili's attacked again?
Are the injuries severe?
Some minor injuries.
Where're they?
They are in the room.
Is it Jingxing's Room?
General, wait.
Why do you like
to blindfold people so much?
How can I apply medicine if I can't see?
Your skin is so delicate and tender.
Mr. Baili!
General.
Yan?
How were you injured?
I'm not injured.
It's him who got injured.
The person behind Jiang Beimo
turns out to be Chancellor.
Last night, Nanyan tested it.
The black-clad guy at Chancellor's place
has the same moves
as that of the assassin
who tried to kill me.
Didn't expect they would do this
in broad daylight.
Luckily, my daughter is highly skilled.
Yes.
Thanks to her,
I survived.
Right.
I use the Green Dragon, White Tiger
and many other moves,
and killed them all.
These days,
I will send additional manpower
to strengthen the guard.
You better not go out
if it's not necessary.
Thank you, General.
If you died,
wouldn't Nanyuan be in great turmoil?
Why would Chancellor do this?
Chancellor Li and General Su
are King's right and left arms.
They're well balanced in skills.
But now,
The King of Nanyuan
betrothed Su Nanyan to me.
Once I return to Dongque,
the General's power will surge.
But if I were to die,
Chancellor Li could then
accuse the General
of failing to protect the hostage.
When my father seeks accountability,
the Su family may become
the scapegoat for Nanyuan.
This is too much.
This is getting more complicated.
It's not just my issue alone.
You, and the Su family,
we must work together to stop them.
Rest assured.
I will take you away from here.
(Nanyuan)
Mr. Baili,
if one day you can return to Dongque and
ascend the throne,
you'll surely be great.
Governing a country needs intelligence,
not violence.
And,
stop mentioning Dongque's throne.
Now that Qingqing was found,
once I leave here,
I am determined to take her
to live a carefree life.
A woman
has made you give up the throne?
Endure a bit more.
Soon, you'll be free.
Endure?
I've endured 15 years.
Can I not endure?
I just hope
that your patience
can make them spare you.
Mr. Baili.
Where is he?
I just wonder
how is my family doing.
From youth,
you came to this foreign land with me.
I've seen you as my brother.
When we leave here,
I'll accompany you to your home first.
Okay.
One more round.
Mr. Baili,
this time I will try my best.
Can't do it.
I can't move even a bit.
And you still want to protect me?
Mr. Baili,
I've been holding this in for long.
I'm not sure
if it's appropriate to say it.
Say it.
You really can't
reveal your martial arts in public.
If you get caught,
you'll die here.
You're aware of that day.
How could I just stand by?
The general will send extra guards
to protect us.
Besides,
in broad daylight,
they wouldn't dare to storm in.
We should be safe staying here
during the daytime.
The Flower Festival in ten days
is when Dongque and Nanyuan
are due to conclude a peace treaty.
As a hostage of Dongque,
I must attend it.
I fear that will be a challenge.
Who's it?
How did you get in?
I...
What did you hear?
I... I heard
you say I'm not versed in martial arts.
So I...
I...
I have an idea.
Let's hear it.
Since Su Nanyan is
Top Martial Arts Master in Nanyuan,
that means
this body
is very talented in martial arts.
You just mentioned
that festival or something,
isn't it ten days later?
How about you teach me martial arts?
These days,
I dreamt of gliding across rooftops
and exerting fatal moves with ease.
Perhaps,
with this body,
I could truly become Nanyuan's top...
No, the 108th top masters.
Chancellor,
a spy reports
the General arranged men
patrolling near Baili's Mansion.
Our people can't get close.
Have them all pull back.
Do not alert them.
The Flower Festival in ten days,
Dongque's hostage will surely attend it.
At that time, let Mozhu
join forces with the masters here
to strike together.
With so many people present,
the Dongque hostage
can't show his martial skills.
This time,
I will make sure
they cannot escape their fate.
♪Drunk with fine wine
under the red candles♪
♪Curtains fill with the aura of spring♪
♪Old acquaintances meet again♪
♪A smile blooms like pear blossoms♪
♪Among the people in the world♪
♪I love you only♪
♪Bird in the cage♪
♪Flower in the mirror♪
♪The one in my heart♪
♪The parting one doesn't return♪
♪Do not drink alone beneath the flowers♪
♪Dreams linger long♪
♪The silhouette is somber
under the moon♪
♪A melody yet to finish♪
♪Do not let the lingering notes
trouble others♪
♪A dream in the mirror♪
♪I'll search for you all my life♪