=Dream in the Mirror=
=Episode 17=
You're truly brilliant.
This is a win-win,
not only protect Mr. Baili,
but also took down Jiang Beimo
and Chancellor.
Both dealt with.
Truly satisfying.
Do you think
they can't turn the tables now.
Before returning to Dongque,
he should not make any more moves.
Yes indeed.
They have made a fool of themselves
at the festival.
Everyone saw that.
And I think
this time nobody
can save them.
If it were not for this move,
the situation now
would be hard to say.
I've saved you again.
How will you thank me?
You've reminded me.
I've put Jiang Beimo
into the dead cell.
You should thank me properly.
How is it that I owe you a favor now?
Mr. Baili,
if you truly
have affection for Zhao Qingqing,
I won't interfere.
It's just that
now I share a body with her,
many things are inconvenient.
You need to give me some time
to adjust.
Si?
Si!
What's wrong?
The assassin's sword was poisoned.
Call doctor.
I'll call.
Mr. Baili,
my condition,
I'm very aware of it.
Si?
Si.
Si...
I
won't be able
to accompany you back to Dongque.
Someone, call the doctor!
Si!
Si.
You must beware of everyone around you.
Although Jiang Beimo and Chancellor
have been imprisoned,
the general has not returned yet.
And the reason is unknown.
Mr. Baili,
I know you dislike court affairs.
But some people,
you cannot protect them
with your strength alone.
Only by caring for the world
can you protect the important ones.
Si!
Miss Su,
protect him.
Si?
Si...
Si!
Father,
where did you go today?
Why weren't you protecting the hostage?
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Save me!
How dare you, at the Flower Festival,
try to hurt the hostage?
Who can save you now?
It's Jiang Beimo.
It's all Jiang Beimo.
He told me to do so, Your Majesty
Your Majesty!
Greetings to Your Majesty.
When I was asking questions,
I learned of your abilities.
I awarded you with Dianmo Studio
to enlighten you, Jiang Beimo.
You shall serve the country.
But I did not expect
that you would collude with scoundrels,
carelessly
plotting to harm the hostage.
You have disappointed me.
Your Majesty,
these accusations are unfounded.
I schemed against the hostage,
but all of this
was for you, Your Majesty.
Surmising my will?
Do you know your crime?
I heard General Su
guarded the empty city gates
all day long.
Do you know
if not for today's close call,
the Su family would fall into the trap.
At the least, imprisoned,
at worst,
the execution of the whole clan!
Not to mention if the hostage died,
Dongque might seek revenge from Nanyuan.
Two countries in a war,
will the common people
have good days ahead?
Yan,
all this,
how could your father not understand?
But as a general,
I have my duties.
The sovereign's order
must not be disobeyed.
Baili Jingxing
frequently encounters assassinations.
How could you be unaware?
During the Flower Festival,
the general's troops
are so crucial
for protecting the hostage.
You must be well aware too.
Yet you insisted
to have the general guard
the empty city gates.
Your Majesty,
forgive my bold speculation,
you did this
because you want Baili Jingxing to die.
How audacious!
If the hostage died,
we will start a war.
How could I want the hostage dead?
The founding General,
commanding significant forces,
deeply cherished by the people.
This is your concern.
You cannot directly strip him
of his military command.
Thus, for so many years,
it's always been the Chancellor
maintaining a balance with him.
If his son-in-law, Baili Jingxing dies,
the Chancellor
would surely make a big fuss out of it.
Then you may take the opportunity
to seize his military power
and remove this concern.
This is one thing.
The heirs of the King of Dongque died
one after another.
He, Baili Jingxing,
is the future king of Dongque.
If this sole heir dies,
Dongque will surely fall into chaos.
Your Majesty, you would certainly
not miss such a great opportunity.
At that time, we can take down Dongque
and reap the benefits.
What makes you think so?
Your Majesty, as the ruler of a nation,
deigned to visit this death cell
to see me, a disabled man.
You must have something to say to me.
You are quite clever.
It's a pity that Chancellor
has such a narrow perspective.
It was a waste of talent.
So all of this
was the King of Nanyuan's idea.
When the sovereign orders death,
the subject must die.
This battle,
we cannot win.
Your Majesty,
thank you for the great grace!
I will certainly serve you
with diligence.
♪Drunk with fine wine
under the red candles♪
♪Curtains fill with the aura of spring♪
♪Old acquaintances meet again♪
♪A smile blooms like pear blossoms♪
♪Among the people in the world♪
♪I love you only♪
♪Bird in the cage♪
♪Flower in the mirror♪
♪The one in my heart♪
♪The parting one doesn't return♪
♪Do not drink alone beneath the flowers♪
♪Dreams linger long♪
♪The silhouette is somber
under the moon♪
♪A melody yet to finish♪
♪Do not let the lingering notes
trouble others♪
♪A dream in the mirror♪
♪I'll search for you all my life♪