(This story is purely fictional)
(Filming of child actors and animals
All follow safety regulations)
Where am I?
Oh my god, you're awake.
Where? This is the palace.
In the palace?
How did I get here?
What about him?
What happened to the man I was with before?
He is receiving medical treatment but has not yet regained consciousness.
Don't move yet.
I'll get you some porridge.
grown ups?
No
Lying there is the river tide attached to the adult's body
This is my fault again.
I know Jiang Chaoli will not remain indifferent
But because of the desire to be with adults
Foolishly believed the omen
I just fooled myself into thinking everything was going to be alright
It's all my fault
My Lord, you are in this situation now because of me...
His Majesty has arrived!
What happened to Prosecutor Yin?
Didn't I tell you to keep a close eye on him?
Your Majesty, please forgive me.
He begged me to let him go somewhere
But he didn't show up at the agreed place.
I searched around and found him at the bottom of the cliff
Unconscious
Can he survive?
His life is safe for now, but his sword wound is very serious
Sword Wound
The sword pierced deeply
It's not easy to wake him up.
Could it be the work of bandits?
The sword wound was caused by a master swordsman.
We also found a few nearby
Man's footprints covered up in a hurry
Was he wounded by the sword?
No, it's not like that.
I didn't kill that guy.
Was he telling the truth?
Is it true that all this wasn't caused by Jiang Chao?
This person
This happened because you were doing something for me.
Heal at all costs
Yes, Your Majesty
He must survive
We will
Find the real culprit
Who is that woman?
We found this woman passed out beside him.
I brought her into the palace thinking maybe she could help
Identifying the Assassin Who Attacked Prosecutor Yoon
Can you see the person who hurt him?
I
Not seen
So you weren't with him at the time?
Yin Jianxiao injured his legs and feet, so I left for a short time
Find him a place to rest.
When he came back, he met with this accident.
We did have a look at his injured ankle.
Found a scrap of skirt
Why are you with him?
I am a mirror maker
Yin Jianxiao mentioned that His Majesty needed new glasses
We were on our way to the palace.
Mirror maker?
What did you say?
Yin Jia came back to life?
How ridiculous is this?
I'm pretty sure he's dead.
Yes, I can testify.
They said the cold body lying on the cart
Suddenly he jumped up and came back to life
- How come...
-That's not all.
His men tried to kill him again.
But he subdued her...
You expect me to believe this nonsense?
He is just a helpless nerd.
I know nothing about swordsmanship
Resurrection is ridiculous enough
What is going on?
They say the blind
Seeing what ordinary people cannot see
That's right
That was the monster from 13 years ago
That sickening stench...
How could I forget?
What should I do now?
Why remain silent?
Are you listening?
Concubine
I am as lowly as an ant, just a blind man
No need to separate with screens
I promise you
I can't see anything
Madam, what can I do for you?
Do you want to sit back and watch the prince become food for evil spirits?
To help Prince Yongin ascend the throne?
Or is it the Queen Mother?
Seems to be very painful
Why don't you just let me help you get rid of that evil spirit?
I…
Yes, Queen Consort.
I know your thoughts very well.
Including those you don't even realize
I heard that the chief guard Xu Zaiyi sent Yin Jia to the Imperial Medical Bureau.
Before he wakes up
Get rid of him
If he wakes up
We're all screwed.
you…
What's going on?
Did it come from inside?
Ouch, what happened?
-What?
-Oh no, what happened?
Clean it up quickly
These precious medicinal herbs...
-Oh my god
- There are also
What should I do?
etc.
How do you...
Are you okay?
Do you know where you are now?
So uncomfortable
My eyelids feel like they are filled with lead
The body is also heavy
Look here, Prosecutor Yin!
Wake up!
I'm sore all over
Still itchy.
Why does it hurt so much?
You just caught a sword wound.
It will definitely hurt!
Really
Disinfect and re-bandage immediately!
-Yes, sir.
This is just ordinary porridge.
What's this?
What's this alluring aroma?
Why don't you eat?
But the wound hurts?
What?
What's this?
What exactly was added here?
What do you mean?
It's just boiled rice
Only these two ingredients
Can it make your tongue leap with joy?
What?
It suits your taste
My taste...
taste…
Oh, I forgot that humans have five senses.
White porridge...
Touch, sight, smell, hearing
And this powerful taste
So even ordinary rice porridge
It can also make the human tongue dance with joy
What are you standing there for? Stop him!
I won't go! Otherwise I'll get beaten again.
He is obviously a dying person.
How did it become like this overnight?
this…
Oh my god, how is this possible?
I understand
He got...
Amnesia
Really?
Amnesia...
Although humans are an inferior race
But the five senses
Especially the taste
It is indeed extremely exquisite!
My thousand years
Just absorbing the essence of various foods
And humans
But can you taste this ultimate delicacy?
Because of a tongue?
These lowly creatures
You deserve to enjoy such delicious food!
I'm so furious.
It's him
Get out of the way!
Damn
We have to take Ruli away before he finds out.
You can stay at my place tonight.
His Majesty will summon you at dawn.
good
What a bad smell
What does this smell like?
Like a burning smell?
But this palace
Why is it so gloomy?
Ruli...
Lord Yin Jia?
This is Ruli
Help me!
grown ups
Hey! Where are you going?
You can't wander in randomly.
Hello!
Where is she running to?
Ruli...
The soul of the master is in the palace
That's right
This side
Coming Soon
Ruli
When you come, I will be in the well
Help quickly...
grown ups!
Got cheated
Damn
Why is this body so clumsy?
Follow me
You should come with me
I am lonely and angry
Hey! Wake up!
Awake…
Awake
Damn
Could it be these eyes that are to blame?
Are you awake?
grown ups?
I am not him
Since he has disappeared without a trace
I'm afraid Yin Jia has already passed away
-Don't be obsessed anymore
- You are wrong
The drowned ghost trapped in the well
Imitating Lord Yin's voice led me here
The drowned ghost knows adults
I am sure that the spirit of the Lord is in this palace.
So what?
I'm going to meet the drowned ghost again
Are you crazy?
Even the experienced witch
There is a possibility that you will lose your life when dealing with a drowning ghost.
There is neither a soul stone nor a guardian angel
You are just a fat sheep in the eyes of wandering ghosts!
The cat cries over the rat...
It's disgusting.
I spent 13 years chasing after you
How can I tolerate you?
Taken away by an unknown wandering ghost?
Ghost howl?
You can't stay here for long
Letting go
Damn
Yin Jia's damn...
Ruined Shell
The “joy” of “happiness”
Can you see this word too?
Can't see clearly
It is the “Huan” of “Huan” color
This young woman is truly gifted.
yes
This lens is a perfect match for me.
Then I will carefully polish this lens and present it to Your Majesty
This lens is ground into a concave shape
This is a concave lens
It is used to correct those who see things clearly at close range.
Glasses for blurry vision at a distance
How can Your Majesty know so clearly?
I have made glasses for countless people.
But no one has ever known the reason
Of course
So I am the king.
I have also read Tang Ruowang's "The Telescope"
After reading this book and understanding its mysteries
This king personally supervised the skilled craftsmen to make...
This mirror
Wait, that’s…
This pair of glasses is very satisfying to me
My eyes are not only clear again
This wonderful device can actually make the mind clearer
Could it be the soul-calming stone?
This is the soul stone.
You have to treat it as your own
This is the Yin Soul Stone
Although the shape of the frame is different
But I was not wrong
How come this thing is here?
therefore…
This king does not need a new mirror
What?
It's my fault.
The king summoned you today.
Because I heard that Lord Yin wanted to bring you into the palace
I'm curious about what's so special about you
Back off
What should I do?
I still have to interrogate the drowned man.
Need to find a reason to stay in the palace
His Majesty
Lord Yin Jia and I have just arrived after a long journey.
With joy in my heart, I only hope to offer my humble art
Presenting a pair of glasses to His Majesty personally
Even though the adults are still alive and dead
I also believe that he shares my heart.
I heard that Yin Jia had woken up last night.
Because the Imperial Medical Bureau only treats royal family members
So he has been transferred to the government hospital for treatment.
I see
This is great news
but…
What do you want?
I venture to ask Your Majesty to at least allow me to offer
Tinted lenses!
How dare you bargain with His Majesty?
I don't know if you are fearless or arrogant.
Please forgive me
His Majesty
The reason why I granted this was because I cared about Yin Jia.
Be careful with your words and actions
Yes, sir.
you
Hello!
Oh my God! My Lord!
Why did you come in person?
Make room for this girl to work for a few days.
Yes, sir.
- This way...
-etc
Can I go get the tools I need?
Will we start work tomorrow, sir?
It's up to you.
His Majesty will surely be pleased to see you.
He has had eye problems recently and is planning to get new glasses.
therefore…
This king does not need a new mirror
Your Majesty is in no hurry to change his glasses
Why did you bring me here, sir?
besides
How come grandma's soul-suppressing stone is here?
My beloved minister was attacked
It is said that the method is clean and neat
I don't think it was the bandits who did this.
We have to find out who is behind this. What do you think?
Your Majesty has
A doubter?
A man who uses the sword rather than words
This prince knew that this great plan would lead to bloodshed.
But he never expected that Yin Jia would become the first sacrifice
So
Why did Your Majesty summon the mirror maker into the palace?
There may be something fishy about this matter
Yin Jia must have a deep meaning in bringing her here at this moment
Who is coming?
Very unfamiliar
How dare you sneak around here?
I…
She looks like a person of extraordinary status.
Why is there a stench of evil spirits on your body?
Could it be left by the drowned ghost?
Unbecoming
It seems that you are determined not to speak
Someone drag her away
- It's the Queen.
I am a mirror maker
The first time I entered the palace, I accidentally got lost
Please forgive me
stop
Are you the person recommended by Inspector Yin Jia?
That's right
Back off
yes
Your Majesty, why did you let her go?
Since he was brought by Inspector Yin Jia
It must be her.
Don't alert the enemy
I heard that Yin Jia had woken up.
Wait for me to confirm it with him personally.
Call her again
It turned out that it was the back of the Central Palace.
Forget about saving the dead souls. It's hard for me to even get close to them.
Could she be a female official?
Deep resentment
I really don't know why
Is Yin Jia really neither human nor ghost?
They say he's crazy
First you have to jump into the furnace
I want to jump off the roof again
He once ran around with a knife in his mouth
Maybe it's not amnesia at all
But crazy?
The official medical department has made such a judgment
But he wasn't that bad when he was with us.
That is to say
Living like this is too pitiful
grown ups!
-What are you going up there for?
-Come down quickly!
-Oh, Master! Come down quickly!
-What is he doing up there?
Please come down quickly, sir!
I tried three times but failed.
Try higher?
Or just close your eyes?
No! No!
Prosecutor Yin!
Come down quickly
Come down
Who are those guys?
It's just nonsense
Brothel?
He is the most upright and polite person.
Where did you say he was?
Listen
He was stabbed a few days ago and his life was hanging by a thread.
I ended up going to a brothel...
Who can believe this?
I thought so too!
But this is the person who was stabbed a few days ago
I heard there was good food and wine there.
He immediately ran out barefoot
What should I do?
Who? My Jia'er?
Sneaking out in broad daylight to get a drink?
- Still barefoot?
-yes!
- His shoes
-Oh my god
Look, the shoes he left behind are still here.
Oh my god...
Lord Yin also ate up all the food rations in the clinic.
The roof was covered with tiles that he jumped up and down...
He stepped on it and broke it into more than fifteen pieces.
Oh my god
So please make compensation
Is this enough money?
Where is that brothel?
That white porridge can't compare to this table of food
Grilled abalone, crab in soy sauce, and cold rice noodle soup
Salted mackerel, cucumber stuffed cinnamon, dried yellow croaker, scallion pancake
Imperial hot pot, stewed pork ribs, chrysanthemum wine, pine needle wine
And fried beef patties
It's a feast!
Another copy of this
This one needs that one and this one too.
What other wine is there besides this?
There are lotus leaf wine, pear blossom wine and azalea wine.
Just hearing the name makes me itch
One pot of each
- Go ahead, go
- It's an adult.
Are you sure the Minister of War will pay the bill?
Our salary can't afford this meal.
How about we sneak away?
What a great idea!
Ruli
Ruli is here!
Who are you, woman?
How dare you attack me?
Who is this woman Ruli?
This is not over yet
Damn
No! She is...
You little bastard
Your mother I
I thought you were going to die
Do you know how scared I was?
God bless you
Thank you for being alive.
Thanks
My son
Thank you so much...
Thanks
Another pot
Let me do it
No need, I've packed it all.
Of course, distinguished guests should stay in a clean room
Oh, I'm not a guest.
Ouch
This house is old
It is the warmest in the hospital.
Sorry to bother you.
Don't say that. It's really okay.
After so many years, I can see people from Longtan Village.
I'm so happy that I can't wait
Oh my god…
You've suffered a lot, haven't you?
You can also learn to be a mirror maker
Ruli, you did a good job
These things recently
It reminds me of what the great witch said back then...
My grandma?
right
I remember it was when Jiaer just turned one year old...
This child
I'm afraid it's hard to live past thirty.
Let's make a substitute sacrifice for him.
(Substitute Festival: a ritual in which puppets are used to ward off disasters on behalf of children)
(Wish you a long life)
(Abundance and Peace)
She was the officiating priest.
After her death
I've been worried
He can escape death.
Maybe it's all because of you
No ma'am, I didn't do anything.
You're wrong.
My Jiaer can survive
It's all because of you protecting me
Thank you Ruli
Almost done, just the last bit left
Sorry ma'am
But that person
Not Lord Yin Jia
(The shrine of my deceased brother and student Yin Jia)
It's all your fault!
You disaster star!
Get out of the way!
Stop it now!
My kids are starving to death.
It’s all this girl’s fault for bringing Jiang Chaoli to our village!
Admit it, you are just cowardly and venting your anger
Before Jiang Chaoli arrived
Our village also suffers from frequent floods, droughts and locust plagues!
These natural disasters are beyond human control.
It never stopped!
so
Why do you put all the disasters on her?
My mother and I are moving to Hanyang
When to leave?
Wait a few days until my bone injury is better before leaving
I want to ask
Would you like to go with me?
Go together?
right
Come with us
You must have had enough of this village, right?
If I'm not going, why should I go with you?
So you plan to continue living like this?
Let them trample on it at will?
Isn't it enough to break a leg?
I will only ruin your life!
I am the one cursed by the river tide, the one despised by the Dragon King
What curse is there?
My leg is injured
I fell accidentally while climbing a tree.
Don't blame you
Come with me, Ruli
Did he really cross the Yellow Springs?
No
It is impossible to do so before the 49th day.
He might still be hanging around his mother.
Don't waste your energy.
I have never seen him in the palace or around it.
You don't have to believe me
Even if I tell you that bean paste is made from beans, you won't believe it.
What? How?
Aren't you afraid?
how?
Do you want me to be your patron saint?
OK
If you can do it
-What?
- You can't do it
You are trapped in this body and cannot move
To escape from that body
You jumped off the roof and into the fire
Running around with a dagger in his mouth
Isn't that exactly why?
That's right.
I don't believe a word you say.
but…
This heart
Still beating
What are you doing
You are the most dignified woman in front of Yin Jia
How dare you touch me like this now?
I didn't touch you
I touched an adult's body.
A warm body with blood flowing
What are you planning?
That's right
Just as you guessed
Do you want to find his soul and return to his body?
This is ridiculous. His lifeline has already been severed.
Then is it reasonable for you to occupy this corpse?
I really miss you, my heart is broken
His face and body are close at hand
But it's not him
The thing I value most in this world is this face
But inside is you, the person I hate the most
This is simply
The worst nightmare
I…
Can't stand you
Don't use his face and voice anymore.
Tarnishing the reputation of the Lord
Before this body is safely returned to you
I will never sit by and watch someone smear his reputation.
OK
Even if you keep saying these vicious words till the end of time
I don't care
Ruli...
I've never met a human being like that.
Coexistence with Heaven and Earth
Natural
A child of this character
Enough to cleanse the curse brought to me by humans
In this case
How could I...
Give up you?
The king ordered Inspector Yin Jia to return to the palace immediately!
So what if he is the king?
The child had just been wounded by a sword
Am I going to be dragged up from my sickbed to do the job?
How do you talk like that!
presumptuous
You have really sharp ears. I was clearly just talking to myself.
I should go wake him up. I'm going right now.
Jia Er! Get up!
The king summons you to the palace
I'm so happy I'm dying of joy
The doctor said it was amnesia
Watch his movements carefully on the road
Is this the legendary floor heating?
Yes
Among the five senses, it is not just the taste that is worth enjoying
Wrapped in warmth...
It's melting.
It's amazing
stand up
I don't want
Didn't you hear?
The king wants you to return to the palace.
He is not my king, so why should I respond to his call?
Do you dare to disobey my order?
What's so scary? He won't live to be a hundred.
now
Enjoy floor heating for me
The most important thing
I said I would not let you tarnish my reputation.
Your persistence is really heartbreaking.
Why do you care so much about the person who tricked you into coming here?
Do you think he brought you here just to make a few pairs of broken lenses?
That stinky guy...
What's wrong with him?
Well, I'll continue sleeping.
What are you hiding from me?
You've been behaving strangely since Longtan Village
You must know
The reason why Lord Yin Jia brought me into the palace
Even if you know
Why should I tell you?
Even if I tell you that bean paste is made from beans, you won't believe it.
I should have expected that.
Asking you is stupid of me
I will find out the truth myself
It's so simple
He is so naive
I don't even want to listen to a word you say
I followed you just to protect you.
Being hit by a wandering ghost
After all, I have been watching you for 13 years
Hear me, shut up.
Everyone is watching us
Don’t ordinary people find it cumbersome to wear these every day?
This crown
All stuck with sweat
And this broken belt
Always wandering around and getting in the way
You...
You can go to the Clothing House now.
What?
Yes, sir.
What? Where are you going?
I'll go with you
where you go?
Don't just stand there and stop him!
-Yes, sir.
Who allowed you to touch me?
Let me go
Let go!
I hope nothing will happen.
Don't resist like this!
Put me down quickly!
Put me down!
open!
I'm going to take that roasted abalone-like thing
Thrown back into the Jeju trench
Put him down now!
What happened again?
His Majesty!
- Lord Yoon Gap...
- I'll tell you later.
What are you doing?
I came here upon being summoned, and he dared to leave me alone?
presumptuous!
How dare you face...
Did you go this way?
Wait here and come back to me!
Why shouldn’t I?
Where did she just say she was going?
The Clothing House, right?
That madman...
Why does he...
You guards
Year of Bingchen
February 6th Xinwei Day
I wish to help a soul transcend
Please have mercy
The Supreme God in Heaven
I pray sincerely here
May you protect my heart from evil spirits.
And wish you...
Caught
The Holy One who speaks the way of justice
May you drive away evil
Give me wisdom
It's out
Jin Huan Emperor Dragon King Emperor
Standing like a mountain in this changing world
May you guide the living beings
Going the right way
Tell me where the adults are.
I will release the rest of your soul
Where is she if she is not in the Clothing House?
no!
You can't leave unless you tell me where the adults are.
Even if I tell you, you won't see him.
Why?
Once you see
No one survived
What does this mean?
Tell me what this means!
He already...
Swallowed by that thing
"That thing?"
Eight-foot ghost
Guang Er
Guanger!
Eight-foot ghost?
It's him
Eight-foot ghost
(Special thanks to: Jin Yongguang)
I will never give up on Master Yin Jia
-grown ups!
- You fell into his trap
He took advantage of you
I don't believe a word you say.
I must revive the master first and then ask him in person.
Don't you want to take revenge on the culprit?
I will help you
As long as you help me
The source of Hachikage's hatred is not in him.
Yin Jia knows too much
Close monitoring is required
What the hell is going on?
I will use my body as bait to summon the eight-foot ghost
Subtitle translation: Zheng Wei