THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
IN ACCORDANCE WITH SAFETY GUIDELINES
Gangcheori, now.
Do it!
Gangcheori!
Damn it…
Is Gangcheori's luminous pearl not enough?
No.
The talismanic iron net is being torn.
Stay back.
Your Majesty. You have to do it now.
Warrior Deity…
Out of the way!
Is it that scoundrel again?
The unknown sorcerer in the palace…
Who is this rascal?
Why must they mess with me every time?
Oh, Warrior Deity.
Warrior Deity…
You will not be able
to leave here on your own terms.
This is the medicine the queen
has been taking recently?
It does not come from the Royal Clinic.
It is secretly brought in
from outside the palace.
- Antaehwan?
Yes, Your Grace.
I secretly questioned
a court lady physician
and she told me it was medicine
prescribed to deter miscarriages.
I hear she also took it often
when she was pregnant with the prince.
The Royal Clinic seems to be
in the dark about it.
I do not know how she is hiding it.
Your Grace?
Summon Pung-san.
Your Grace, but he is--
I am well aware
that he is a vile snake.
However, my son has died.
That child…
and the bizarre way he died…
How am I to accept any of it?
As soon as day breaks,
I shall summon Fortuneteller Pung-san.
This is him.
He placed the talisman
near the Royal Library.
REPORT TO YOUR MAGISTRATE'S OFFICE
IF YOU HAVE SEEN A MAN OF THIS DESCRIPTION
We must find him first
if we wish to expose
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost's accomplices.
We are questioning every court eunuch.
It might not be a eunuch.
Expand the search
to outside the palace as well.
Yes, Your Majesty.
How is the security
at the prince's quarters?
As you have commanded,
It has been reinforced with
additional royal guards and stewards.
I dispatched dependable soldiers
who are skilled at combat.
Anyone would think twice
before trying to enter.
I installed bells
and a fresh talismanic iron net
at His Highness's quarters.
Even if someone manages to break in
and places another talisman for the ghost,
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
will get caught in the net
and the bells will ring
on their own to notify us.
But, where is he today?
It appears he became
a bit fatigued after yesterday.
He is resting at home
because he was feeling unwell.
I see.
But, this eyeglass lens…
Last time at Mount Bugak,
you confronted that ghost
with this lens after stealing it from me.
You also told me
to use this against the ghost
if things went awry this time.
What makes this so special?
That is… a Ghostbane Stone.
Ghostbane Stone?
It is referred to as the stone
of the Dragon King
and possesses mystical powers.
Your Majesty remained safe
from the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
because you kept it with you up until now.
Your Majesty.
May I ask how you managed
to acquire that Ghostbane Stone?
It was…
By chance,
did Shaman Neop-deok present it to you?
Did you say Neop-deok?
I am certain
that female Ghostbane Stone once belonged
to Shaman Neop-deok.
Are you really not familiar
with Shaman Neop-deok?
Shaman Neop-deok…
was cherished by Queen Indeok,
my late grandmother.
I believe my grandmother summoned her
to the palace a few times.
Then…
That shaman gave me this corrective lens.
I did not believe in heretical ceremonies,
but I acknowledged the effort
that kind shaman put into refining it.
Hence, I used it to make these glasses.
But…
how do you know Shaman Neop-deok?
She is…
my maternal grandmother.
What a strange connection we have.
My grandmother was at this palace.
Did she foresee it then?
Did she know the royal bloodline
would be threatened by this ghost?
Is that why she gifted
the female Ghostbane Stone to him?
Unfortunately, this is
the only thing I can do for you
as a lowly subject who sympathizes
with His Highness's predicament.
If you keep this close,
it shall protect you.
I am even weaker than before…
This confrontation was
harder than the one at Mount Bugak.
How…
Damn it.
You claimed Prince Yeongin died because
of the sorcerer under the king's command.
Did you find out who that sorcerer is?
That Examiner Yoon Gap
you mentioned last time…
He was kicked out but returned
to the palace with a young girl.
I hear she has been frequenting
the Queen's Palace recently.
Who is she?
They say she is an eyeglass artisan.
Apparently, the king summons her
to the Royal Library frequently.
An eyeglass artisan?
I should look into that.
I cannot believe that some brat
could hinder the Warrior Deity so…
How dare you try to scheme before me!
Your Grace,
that is not true.
Then, what is the truth?
My son met such a tragic death…
but the king is expecting another child.
You claimed the king had a sorcerer.
You made a mockery of me
with this unverified claim.
Your Grace.
The energy inside the palace
shifted a fortnight ago.
I am certain the figure
who first entered the palace then
to stay by His Majesty's side
is the sorcerer.
A fortnight ago?
Yes, Your Grace.
However, did you just say
that His Majesty is expecting a new member
of the royal bloodline?
The queen has been sowed
with the king's seed.
The Warrior Deity will have fresh prey.
Are you all right?
Yes. I am fine. Just fine.
Should you not have a seeing guide?
Well, I do have a servant,
but something came up
and I could not bring him with me.
Hold on,
you have quite an extraordinary aura
for a young maiden.
Are you a court lady?
No. I am an eyeglass artisan
at the Royal Couturier.
The young maiden
possesses such remarkable talent.
Anyhow, thank you.
Not at all.
That brat must be the one.
She must be.
Is he a fortuneteller?
What are you going to do
with that cursed thing?
Well…
it seems the royal bloodline
is expecting a new member.
I will take that nascent fetus
to create the most restorative tonic
that will heal
the Warrior Deity's injuries.
A soul, not tainted by the grime
of the mortal world in the slightest.
It will be most helpful
in revitalizing the Warrior Deity.
Were you waiting for me?
Is it not obvious?
I am your patron deity, after all.
Because you are worried I might be jinxed
by some wandering spirit?
Yes. You are correct.
Are you feeling all right?
Last time, it seemed like
you recharge in clean, fresh water.
Maybe you should again?
I have already done so.
I see.
Listen, about what happened yesterday…
I guess I thought with your luminous pearl
and my grandma's implements,
we would be able to confront
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost without issue.
I was too hasty and rash…
and it made you overexert yourself.
So? Do you wish to give up
on being my disciple?
What?
You agreed to become my disciple
because you believed
that I could catch
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
However, when the chance arose,
I failed to do so.
Hence, you no longer have any reason
to serve me as your patron deity.
No.
An agreement
between a patron deity and a disciple
cannot be broken so easily.
I still hold some resentment
and contempt for you.
However, I also know
that for many years,
you did whatever it took
to keep me safe.
And you continue to do so to this day.
Am I wrong?
You are correct.
That is strange.
You are right here…
but I sense the aura
of an Imugi over there, too.
Bibi.
My lord, let me pour you a drink.
How nice.
Did you hear that rumor?
They say a ghost was responsible
for Prince Yeongin's demise.
I heard that rumor as well.
But you know, I believe those ghost rumors
have been around since the late king.
Yes.
For the past few years,
rumors of ghosts being responsible
for the sudden deaths of royal kin
have been swirling around
and making their rounds.
My goodness, so the ghosts
are wiping out the royals?
All that stuff
was just uselessly made up
by the court ladies.
Nothing more than silly rumors.
What is Lord Choi Won-u up to?
Well, apparently,
he simply offered
his condolences for Prince Yeongin
and left before even having
an audience with the king.
From what I hear,
he was bedridden from an illness
and did not meet with anyone.
I do not believe you need
to be concerned about him.
My lord, may I pour you a drink as well?
He is a childhood friend,
currently the magistrate of Gwacheon.
He was so desperate
for a chance to meet you
and begged me so incessantly…
Excuse me. I need to relieve myself.
Pardon?
Wait, my lord…
My lord…
Who are you even looking for?
My younger brother.
What? You have a younger brother?
Then, that Imugi aura I detected earlier…
How dare you!
How dare a measly examiner
display such impertinence to me,
the Minister of War!
Is it because you are
an ignorant, lowborn bastard?
Possibly.
Probably.
Why that scoundrel…
Rascal, did you pass
your 60th birthday this year?
What did you say?
You are fine if you did not,
but if you did,
you should be careful here.
One could argue
that I ended up in this body
and was able to welcome
Yeo-ri as my disciple,
all thanks to you.
That is why I kindly offer this advice.
My sword. Where is it?
How dare you insult me like this?
You scoundrel!
Heed my warning.
I am a bit busy
looking for my younger brother.
If you interfere once more,
I will not hold back.
Did I not warn you?
You scoundrel!
My goodness. You were telling the truth.
I thought you were bluffing
with that constant talk of whirlwinds,
but you just released a whirlwind
and blew him away.
That was nothing.
Yeo-ri, I am Gangcheori.
The most malicious malevolent deity
who humans fear the most.
Wait, how far did you send him away?
I am not sure.
Wind can be so unpredictable.
I cannot say.
Based on the direction,
it seems he will be riding the north wind.
Perhaps, he will land by the sea off Jeju?
Gosh!
Why did you hit me?
What now?
He is the Minister of War, a real bigwig!
Did you even consider
the possible consequences?
That man…
is Yoon Gap's killer.
What?
He was the one
who stabbed Yoon Gap to death.
Is that true?
Then, the Kwak Sang-chung
you mentioned last time…
Correct. That was him.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Good job.
Well done!
You should have just blasted
him off to Japan while you were at it.
Where?
Go.
A bit further.
Where?
It came from over here.
Lord Kwak's scream came from over here.
What in the world is going on?
Are you not Examiner Yoon Gap?
What are you…
doing here?
We just heard Lord Kwak scream.
By chance, did you do something to him?
What?
My lord, your jest goes too far.
As if Lord Kwak
with his exceptional combat skills
could even be ruffled
by this wimpy whippersnapper.
Where in the world is Lord Kwak?
A whirlwind just now--
We heard a whirlwind pass through
and the sound of a scream as well.
However, we did not see
a single person in the vicinity.
Right, my lord?
You did not see anybody, either.
My goodness.
What are we to do?
What is going on here?
How will we find him?
He is an Imugi.
There really was
another one besides Gangcheori.
That man is dead.
He killed that man instantly.
What is with that Imugi?
Where in the world could Lord Kwak be?
My goodness.
We must find him.
Look here, my lord.
What has gotten into you?
My goodness. What happened to him?
What is going on?
Wake up.
Why am I…
Open your eyes!
Go and fetch a physician.
Right.
Hear me! Is anyone there?
Hear me!
What is going on here?
Yes, my lord?
Let us hurry. Come on.
Quickly now.
Oh, goodness. My lord.
How terrible.
Oh my…
Who are you?
Me?
I am Imugi Bibi. I'm here to eat you.
Eat? Eat what?
Do not come any closer. Stop!
Stay back! Stop!
I have not been this stuffed in ages.
His belly was full of spite.
Quite tasty indeed.
He ate him.
He just devoured a man.
You have not changed one bit, Bibi.
What?
You see me?
Is that you, Gangcheori?
I just cannot believe this.
So, it is true.
The Gangcheori I know
is really inside this body.
Damn it.
Even when the wandering spirits
at the market street
yammered away about some clueless Imugi
being stuck in a human body, I…
I still had hope that it was not you.
But they were indeed
actually talking about you?
Geez.
Who knew the invincible, lofty Gangcheori
would end up in such a sad state?
Seeing as how emaciated you look,
your hunt for aristocrats
must not be going easy.
Maybe I ate too many of them?
The supply of aristocrats over 60
has been drained in the south.
That is why I have come to the capital.
There are bountiful feasts
all over the capital.
You can eat whatever you want.
How many more do you need?
I need 12. Once I eat 12 more,
that will make 100 aristocrats over 60.
Once I do, I shall ascend
into the sky as a black dragon.
I shall occasionally let you know
how I am doing from up there.
"Gangcheori!"
"The water up here is so nice!
Ascend so we can have some fun together!"
That is enough foolishness.
Come out now.
Where?
Come out of
that smelly human body already.
Do I look like I have a choice?
What?
Are you kidding me?
Do you really not know how?
Do you?
It is so simple.
You need to destroy this body you are in.
Just kill this Yoon Gap
or whatever his name is.
As if there was anything easier
to kill than a mortal.
I need to…
kill this body?
Just jump off a cliff
or stab it in the heart.
It is so simple.
What are you complaining about?
Look. That would be perfect.
Grab it.
Damn it.
Turn it.
Just stab it.
Stab it?
Stop!
Who says you can kill His Lord?
Absolutely not.
It is that brat from before.
You locked eyes with me earlier.
Can you see me?
Yes.
Also,
we are already linked
as patron deity and disciple.
We agreed to keep
this body safe until we catch
that Eight-foot-tall Ghost
and save Lord Yoon Gap.
What?
Gap!
Move it.
Tell her I am sleeping.
I am asleep.
Gap!
I came in to borrow this,
but it seems His Lord is already sleeping.
He is sleeping already?
I thought I heard him talking outside.
Oh, that…
He kept talking in his sleep.
It must have been
a busy day at the palace.
My goodness.
What am I going to do with this punk?
What is the matter?
That expensive medicine I bought for him…
He dumped all of it in the outhouse.
What?
I cannot believe him.
You damn punk!
Do you know how much that costs?
How could you dump
that precious medicine out like that?
You could have just let me take it!
I am so upset, I could die!
I cannot believe you!
How can you even sleep?
This damn punk. How can you even sleep?
Going to the outhouse?
This is hilarious.
The almighty Gangcheori…
is now forced to use
that smelly, dirty outhouse.
That brat from earlier…
She is the one you used
to chase around and obsess over, right?
Are you really going to fight
that pesky Eight-foot-tall Ghost?
Just for that measly human's sake?
I already gave her my word I would.
Gangcheori.
Gangcheori…
Okay, fine.
Once a human with mighty spiritual energy
starts serving you
with great reverence as your disciple,
you get another chance to ascend.
I am also familiar with that legend.
However,
how can you trust those lowly mortals?
You know how fickle they can be.
Bibi.
I learned a few things while living
in this despicable mortal world.
Guess what the most useful thing is.
What is it?
Lying.
Gosh, who knew you were such a jerk?
The most malicious, malevolent deity.
I plan to go with how things play out
for the time being.
And there are so many dishes
I have yet to taste.
Once that girl fully opens her heart to me
and follows me wholeheartedly…
I shall kill this body and escape
to claim her for myself.
Yes, great.
Excellent.
You can just go right for it. Yes.
Hear me, you scoundrels!
Is anyone out there?
Get me down this instant.
Why these scoundrels…
I am Kwak Sang-chung, the Minister of War!
Get me down now! Go on!
Hear me, scoundrels!
Is there truly no one there?
Can someone get me down?
Those wretched lords.
I shall teach them
a painful lesson when I return.
I shall!
Wait. No.
Please.
Please, can someone just let me down?
Anyone, please just get me down from here.
Wait.
Just stay there. Let me step out first.
Damn it. This is insane.
What is insane?
Damn it!
You startled me.
Startled enough to blush like a peach?
What happened?
What is it?
Listen, Yeo-ri--
I mean, Listen, Bibi.
The desire to devour an aristocrat…
Does it make you want
to stare at them all the time?
Does it make your heart race
when they are near?
Does it make you want
to touch them and stuff?
No.
I am too busy gobbling them down.
Who has time for touching?
Are you like that?
That girl, Yeo-ri…
She has finally accepted me
as her patron deity.
But my heart strangely aches
whenever I am near her.
And sometimes,
I think I might want to devour her…
How strange…
What about other mortals?
Other mortals?
Does Lord Yoon Gap…
really live in this village?
Did you think
a low-ranking official born a bastard
would be living in fancy Bukchon?
Goodness.
I should have known.
I guess love that overcomes social classes
only exist in fairy tales.
Gosh, my lady! That is quite an epiphany!
My goodness!
All right. We should return now.
You will be in big trouble
with His Excellency if he finds out.
But still, we need to return this plant.
He may be looking for it.
Another mortal?
Yes.
See if you feel the same thing
about any other human.
Another mortal.
She is another mortal…
but I do not
feel…
anything.
My lord.
This is the plant
you entrusted me with last time.
I came here to return it.
The plant from that damn quack monk?
I do not need it.
Keep it or toss it.
Do as you wish.
Now, I understand…
I do not want to devour her as Bibi does.
Gosh.
I assumed you were staying home
when I did not see you.
What are you talking about?
You expect a patron deity to stay behind?
So, what choice do I have?
I cannot keep my promise to you
and defeat the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
Nor can I leave this body
and abandon your side.
I have no choice but to continue lying
and prolong the time we have together.
It's strange…
Something about His Lord has changed.
He is not the man I first met.
How did he change?
How shall I put it? He seems a bit wilder.
It makes him even more attractive.
Attractive? As if.
He just shoved you aside.
Hey, that was because he was embarrassed.
See?
He even gave me a gift.
Did you not hear him tell you to toss it?
You just do not understand.
His Lord may seem curt on the outside,
but he has a warm, tender heart
on the inside.
Such men are prevalent in fairy tales.
I see. Sure.
What? What is the matter?
What?
Shush.
Is that Father?
What is he doing with such ruffians?
Help yourself.
The Royal Confectionery
is known for its desserts.
Thank you.
By chance,
could I forgo them now
and take them with me later?
Why?
For Examiner Yoon Gap's sake?
No, I would not go that far.
He is waiting for me outside
for he is not allowed
in the Queen's Palace.
Do not worry and help yourself.
I shall have them pack some
for Examiner Yoon separately.
Thank you.
Instead of the yugwa,
you should send him dasik and yakgwa.
They are tastier.
It appears you have
some affection for Examiner Yoon.
Did he treat you well?
Well, what happened was--
I would not say he treated me well.
I find him comical.
I have never met a man like him
in the palace before.
What was that?
Your Highness.
Mother.
A vision?
My apologies.
It appears my stomach is a bit upset.
Your Highness, are you all right?
Perhaps, you should take your leave now.
Yes.
Your Highness, are you all right?
Why are you not leaving?
Your Highness, by chance,
have you dreamt of a nightmare recently?
How do you…
Escort the prince out
and give us the room.
How did you know about that?
Just a moment ago,
I had a vision of Your Highness.
You were suffering from a nightmare.
It has already been several days
since I started having that nightmare.
At first,
I thought it was
just an upsetting nightmare.
However, as the days passed,
the nightmare felt more real.
It felt as if I was
actually experiencing it.
Did you say he spat out
black water from his mouth?
Can you figure out the cause?
Please allow me to inspect
your chambers for a moment.
My goodness!
My lord!
Thank the heavens you are safe.
I would call this divine intervention.
It is indeed a great relief.
What happened to you?
The whole capital was
flipped inside out to look for you.
Where in the world have you been?
And what happened to your leg?
Yoon Gap.
Where is that scoundrel?
Pardon?
There you are!
Why you…
You rotten scoundrel.
You ghastly rascal.
How did you do it?
How did you do that to me?
You came sooner than I expected.
And you are surprisingly…
perfectly intact.
What did you say? Why you…
I will kill you someday.
I will pay you back
a hundred, a thousandfold!
What is all this commotion about?
Your Majesty.
Minister, what happened to you?
And what exactly
did Examiner Yoon do to enrage you so?
This scoundrel.
This scoundrel and his whirlwind…
His whirlwind…
I do not expect you to observe
proper etiquette towards me.
You are not Yoon Gap.
Therefore you are not one of my subjects.
Then, you should have
just kept on walking.
Why did you bring me here?
However,
once you draw attention to yourself
by acting out like this,
I will no longer be able
to protect you or Yeo-ri.
Would that be fine as well?
So, you order us to stop
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost,
but if things go awry,
you will simply play dumb
and leave us to take the fall?
Is that it?
Why this rotten little…
You scoundrel.
You are right.
I am not one of your subjects.
I am…
Gangcheori.
Gangcheori?
As in that wretched Imugi
who brings forth misfortune
wherever he goes?
You refer to
that malevolent deity from legends?
I believe I have heard
of him as well, Your Majesty.
He was on his way to ascend as a dragon,
but he was jinxed when a human spotted him
and he fell back down to earth.
Afterward, he spent
his time tormenting mortals.
That rotten Imugi…
And…
you are him?
It is perfectly clean.
Nothing seems out of place.
What could it be?
May I step up for a moment?
You may.
What is the matter?
My goodness!
Your Highness.
Do you finally understand?
Do you understand who I really am now?
Although I am unsure if feeble mortal eyes
can perceive such things.
Since we will be
spending some time together,
I shall graciously explain it to you.
So,
if the king is here,
I may be a malevolent deity
but a deity nonetheless.
I am here.
Thus, who should observe
proper etiquette toward whom?
But,
what exactly happened
between you and the Minister of War?
From what I heard,
you were present when he went missing.
Were you the one responsible?
Oh, that?
He just kept yammering away,
so I sent him off with a whirlwind.
A whirl…
What?
A whirlwind.
I summoned a whirlwind
and sent him packing.
Blasted him right off.
What? What did you say?
What did you blast off with a whirlwind?
Must I repeat myself?
I hurled that fool into the sky.
But it seems in this human body,
I am weaker than I used to be.
I thought he would land by the sea
off Jeju and we would enjoy some quiet,
but seeing as how he returned
in just a few days,
it appears he did not go very far.
So, you are saying
you made the Minister of War
fly off with a whirlwind?
You? You did that?
Your Majesty.
Something terrible has happened.
Are you saying
this object was discovered
inside the queen's chambers?
What about the queen?
Is the queen all right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
She fainted for a moment,
but the royal physician
said she would be fine.
However…
Since she is with child,
he said she should be careful.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean the queen is with child?
Are you saying Her Highness is pregnant?
Your Majesty, I have sinned gravely!
Her Highness feared
something terrible would happen
due to the Eight-foot-tall Ghost,
so I remained silent on the matter.
Then, this skull…
What…
BONFIRE
What is that?
It was written by the same person
as the last talisman.
Then…
this is related
to the Eight-foot-tall Ghost?
Yes, Your Majesty.
And this talisman…
Speak!
It appears this talisman
targets the baby in Her Highness's womb.
Make no exception
and apprehend every attendant
in the Queen's Palace!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Just a moment.
Please let me inspect it a bit longer.
What are you trying to do?
I cannot just stand by and watch.
How could they target an unborn child?
I will get them.
Do you think you can find out who it is?
The ghost tormenting Her Highness
must be here,
but my powers feel blocked by something.
I must retrieve my myeongdu
from the Royal Couturier.
MYEONGDU: A MIRROR THAT REVEALS
SPIRITS TO A SHAMAN
Stop.
You must be more careful.
What did I tell you?
A myeongdu reveals spirits
and reflects the world
unseen by mortal eyes.
It is how a shaman finds their voice.
You must treat it like a part of your body
and cherish it.
Myeongdu, the mirror for spirits.
With this…
What is the matter?
I suggest you stop there.
His sword is powerful enough
to easily annihilate
and completely wipe out
a wandering spirit like yourself.
He was a drowned ghost.
What?
That makes no sense.
How did it manage to stay
out of water for that long?
It must have been thanks to that talisman.
That is how he managed
to brazenly stay on dry land for so long.
He escaped through this waterway.
We must catch him.
There he is.
That is where he is hiding.
Make sure you catch him.
Grant me mercy so that I may salvage
and guide this spirit to cross over.
Got you.
Are you all right?
What is wrong?
Damn wandering spirit…
If you tell me who instigated it,
I shall spare your life.
I thought you may know something.
Are you suspecting me right now?
Something feels off. My body feels heavy.
She ended up being struck by a curse
in the end.
The queen has similar symptoms.
That vicious drowned ghost
is targeting the unborn child.
Then, will you offer
your son in your stead?
There is only one way to break that curse.
You catch the ghost that placed it.
Yeo-ri will die if we waste any more time.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim