THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
IN ACCORDANCE WITH SAFETY GUIDELINES
RETURN
Yeo-ri.
I had palace attendants swiftly make this,
but…
will this be enough?
Yes.
I need this to break the curse.
My goodness. All right.
- Take it.
- Yes, my lord.
Are you sure you can make it there
in such a state?
I must.
Gangcheori will be in danger
if I do not go.
Then again,
it did seem like that rowdy Imugi
cared for you deeply.
You must go if it distresses you so.
Let us go.
- Let us prepare to leave.
- Yes, my lord.
First, I need to save Gangcheori.
Stand your ground!
Your Majesty!
- Stay back. You will only get in the way.
- But--
I do not need one more victim to save.
That drowned ghost
will appear during the daytime.
Rotten water spreads easier
under the hot sun.
Gangcheori is in danger.
This water has a rotten stench.
I cannot…
I cannot breathe.
A member of the royal bloodline.
Come with me.
You will come with me!
Your Majesty!
Do not just stand there! Take him now!
It is not like last time.
This water reeks of decay.
I cannot breathe…
Imugi, the cocky freshwater sovereign.
Not so cocky now in that mortal body.
How's the taste of rotten water?
Now, I end you!
The curse…
Your Majesty. He fell into the water.
Should we…
What are these?
Consider it a last-resort weapon.
Although I am sure we will not need it.
"Earth overcomes water."
Dirt will bind and trap water.
Dirty wandering spirit.
Let me show you the true power…
of the freshwater sovereign.
Oh, no! Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Are you all right?
What is that on your neck?
I am fine.
However…
Gangcheori!
He has been cursed. I must hurry.
I call upon the guardians
of the Blue-East, White-West,
Red-South, Black-North,
and Yellow-Center…
Please return the curses
from all cardinal directions
back to their origins.
You rotten wench…
Gangcheori!
It looks like the curse was broken.
Why is he not waking up?
Gangcheori.
Wake up.
Gangcheori, wake up!
Wake up already!
Seeing how you are yelling
at the top of your lungs,
it seems you've recovered.
You're alive.
You are alive…
I was worried something might have
happened to you.
The curse…
was broken.
That is impossible.
You must be mistaken.
You were sure even that brat
was struck with the curse.
Then, how could it have been broken?
That wench…
hails from Yongdam Village.
Yongdam Village?
What is so special about that?
How dense and worthless you are.
Did you actually forget
about Yongdam Village?
But that happened a long time ago.
It must be a coincidence--
Coincidence?
You need more than an Imugi by your side
to confront the Warrior Deity
and break the drowned ghost's curse
with such swiftness.
You still think it's a coincidence?
But…
His Lordship did not mention anything.
How could His Lordship know?
Take that deceased spirit
Cleanse the soul and purify the spirit…
You and I
were the only ones
to visit Yongdam Village.
You…
- My goodness.
- Such behavior…
You seem perfectly fine now.
Of course, I am the almighty Gangcheori.
A drowned ghost is no match for me.
Your Majesty,
we should return to the palace.
We must swiftly get
your injuries looked at.
Let us return.
Go on.
Are you all right? Let me see.
I'm fine.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Your Highness,
His Majesty is here for you.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
Her Highness has made a full recovery…
Your Majesty.
Forgive me for worrying you.
I am fine now.
They say the child in my womb
is also healthy.
Such wonderful news.
I was terrified that I might…
end up losing you.
Your Majesty.
Damn wandering spirit.
Do not bother wasting your energy.
Without a single drop of water around,
you will not be able to flee.
Who instigated this?
Answer me.
Or I shall seal you
in that puppet once more
and bury you in the ground.
Go on.
This punk…
Start talking! You wretched scoundrel.
We will not be able to get
this scoundrel to talk.
Seal him in the puppet once more.
I shall bury him deep
in the driest, most barren land.
There is no need
to rush his burial.
I heard you appeared
in the Queen's nightmares every night
to torment her.
But did you know
you are targeting the wrong person?
Seeing your current state,
the cause of your death
must have been drowning.
Instead of retrieving your head
from the water for a proper funeral rite,
an insidious individual placed it
in the Queen's pillow
for the sake of a curse.
Should you not expose them
so they may be punished?
I am sure they made you
a promise of some sort.
Tell me.
I shall grant you your wish.
My wish?
That is right. Your wish.
So tell me.
You need to grant my wish first.
After you do,
I will tell you who that individual is.
He is Bang Mak-dol, an off-site slave
from Goksan, Chungcheong-do.
He says he died ten years ago
due to a flood.
He has agreed to speak
if I deliver his remains to his daughter.
Then, you leave for Goksan immediately?
Yes.
I believe I will be able to meet
his daughter if I visit his former home.
Come closer.
Closer.
So, are you feeling better now?
I am fine now, Your Majesty.
Thank you for bestowing me
those precious medicinal herbs.
No need to thank me.
I will grant you the use of a horse.
Have a safe journey.
Clerk Officer.
You shall escort her there,
she has a rough journey ahead.
I shall do my very best to keep her safe.
Then, I shall take my leave.
All right. Safe travels.
What is the matter?
That queen woman remains reclined,
resting in her bed.
You suffered the same curse,
yet you are sent off
to some faraway place?
Is he just allowed to abuse
the lower class as he wishes?
Watch your tongue. His Majesty
generously provided her with a horse.
Horse? He should have
given her a palanquin!
- I must go back and argue with him.
- I told you I am perfectly fine.
Really?
Your Majesty.
Were you overly affectionate
toward that Yeo-ri on purpose?
Was it obvious?
Just a bit.
That Gangcheori
was steaming from his ears.
My word.
What? What is it?
What is it? Is there misfortune?
My goodness, say something.
Maybe it is because
of those awful rumors about the Imugi?
Not to mention,
officials are dropping like flies.
I am just a ball of anxiety.
A flood has broken out.
The trees are about to be uprooted.
Does that mean…
I am going to die?
Do not worry. I shall save you, my lord.
I shall craft this talisman for you
with the utmost care.
Always keep it with you at all times.
Do not go anywhere without it, all right?
The almighty Imugi is
just a snake at the end of the day.
Hence, it must be stopped
by its gluttonous mortal enemy,
the pig.
Take it back.
I do not believe in such things.
Just accept it for my sake.
I had it crafted by the noble elder
of the Association of the Blind
and even brought one for you.
Do you truly believe
this will make a difference?
We live in strange times.
Our colleagues
are dying one after another.
Almost as if someone is aiding the king.
Whether it is a ghost or an Imugi,
it is better to be safe than sorry.
Keep it with you.
Can I help you?
Is this the residence of Bang Mak-dol?
Yes. He is my father.
But he passed away a long time ago.
What is this?
They are your father's remains.
What?
What do you…
Father…
Please forgive me.
My father ended up like this
as he tried to save me.
Please forgive me.
My dear Kkeut-sun…
Kkeut-sun…
Hey.
We granted your wish,
now honor your promise.
I am beginning to get hungry.
Hey, Lady Shaman.
My daughter's heart has been shattered.
Can you lend me your body
so I can just tell her a few words?
That is a bit…
We pull you from the roaring river
and now you want to rob us?
This is not what we agreed upon!
Then, what?
Do you want my baby, my poor Kkeut-sun,
to live with that sorrow forever?
How can you be so heartless?
To hell with it!
If you refuse,
these lips will remain sealed for good.
What a rotten scoundrel…
I will beat you up
and teach you a mighty lesson.
Do you promise to answer our questions
if I let you briefly borrow my body?
I will tell you everything!
Every single little thing I remember!
Do you know how exhausting
being possessed can be?
And you just offer yourself up?
Did you forget your body is mine--
Just for a brief moment!
I just need to tell her one thing.
A very brief moment.
Do I just enter now? Yes? Now?
Do I?
You are entering nothing…
It worked. Golly gee!
Already?
That damn brat…
Have you lost your mind?
That is why I told you not to go!
If you had just listened to your father,
we could have avoided this mess! Well?
Father?
Father, is that you?
Yes, it is me.
Who else would I be?
Anyhow!
You just never listened
ever since you were a kid.
You just had to walk into the flood--
Then, what about you?
You would have yelled at me again
if I lost that fishing net!
And what about you?
You should have reeled it in
when I told you to!
My goodness.
Look at this little one.
Who does he get his handsome looks from?
Look at you, Kkeut-sun.
You even commendably birthed
this strapping lad.
Father!
She is a daughter!
Oh, a daughter?
She looks exactly like you
when you were a baby.
Wait.
Father!
Kkeut-sun.
It was not your fault.
It was just my fate. All right?
And on my ancestral rites table,
can you just place
a dried persimmon for me?
Father!
Father…
Dried persimmon and what else?
What else do you want to eat?
That will be enough.
Oh, Father…
- My sweet puppy…
- Father.
You better have a happy life.
Do not cry for me anymore.
Father…
But…
what is this "dried persimmon"?
A blind man?
Yes. He could not see.
After being swept away by the flood,
my skull that had been rolling around
the bottom of some still river water
was caught by a fisherman's net.
And that blind rascal
was delighted to find a spirit
with a bitter grudge
and bought it off him.
- And who was that man?
- Let me see…
His name was…
Yapper, that scoundrel!
I heard someone call him that.
- Yapper?
- Yes.
Then, the Association of the Blind
held me captive for all those years.
Only recently,
that blind rascal took me out
and told me
he would let me see my daughter
if I brought him royal blood.
The Yapper…
A character of your magnitude is rare.
Your spiritual energy is
certainly more enticing
than the energy of that lowly Yapper.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost
definitely mentioned that name before.
The blind Yapper…
Who could it be?
Gosh. It has been over ten years
since I have been to the capital.
I do not know where anything is.
If I knew I would be here so soon,
I would have asked that Yoon Gap
where his house was beforehand.
I mean…
Master?
Master!
- Master--
- What are you doing, old man?
You cannot just pick up and eat
what does not belong to you!
Does it look like
I am running a charity here?
My goodness. My apologies.
My master was a bit hungry.
I will pay you for it.
Here.
I would appreciate
a discount on the rice cakes.
I only came to the capital because
you told me you managed to acquire all
the books that book peddler had bought up.
But what is this?
The book I am looking for is not here!
My lord,
I am just as frustrated.
Exactly which book are you looking for?
How can I find it if I do not know
what I am looking for?
Search again.
You must acquire
all the books that scoundrel
has ever touched, looked at,
or even walked past in the capital.
Is that how you do business?
I don't need your business!
Are you all right?
Yes.
You rotten scoundrel!
You better scram this instant!
Is there something up there?
I don't see anything.
- Do you see anything?
- Nothing but air.
I don't see anything.
Who is that fellow talking to?
Here you are, Master.
I was worried
how we would pay for the rice cakes.
Thank you for your generous offering.
Not at all. I owe you a great thanks.
I do not know why such things
have been happening to me recently.
There is no smoke without fire.
Pardon?
I managed to chase it away for now,
but it seems you partook
in the formation of a deep grudge.
I am afraid I do not understand.
Not even in the slightest.
You must face your sin and repent
to guide the bad energy out
if you do not want this to repeat.
I take refuge in Amitabha.
May Avalokitesvara show us mercy.
Master, let us go now.
Here we go.
What?
We must swiftly return
and report back to His Majesty.
She is in no state to ride a horse.
Go on ahead if it is so urgent.
What are you talking about?
We need to catch this Yapper.
He must know
that the curse has been broken now.
We need to hurry back.
Do you even know how you look right now?
You were already weak
after that curse a few days ago.
And you even let
that trifling wandering spirit in today.
This will not do. I shall go on ahead.
Do you think the name Yapper
is enough to find him?
The Association of the Blind
should know something.
You get some rest.
Yes, my lord. Don't let me keep you.
Such great magnanimity you possess.
Did you already forget
his curse almost killed you?
Being possessed is beyond draining.
Why would you offer yourself up?
He put us through that hell,
just so he could scold his daughter again?
How pathetic.
He is not pathetic in the slightest.
Mortals do not even live to be 100.
That daughter of his will die
and join him in just a few years.
Why was he being so fussy?
What? What now?
Do you not understand?
The fact we cannot even live 100 years
makes the grief that much more poignant.
Just because you consider
fleeting mortal lives to be lowly,
do not call the love
between a father and daughter…
lowly.
My grandma said…
that everyone in the world
was pitiful and tragic behind it all.
I was hoping I would never find out
what she was feeling
as she lived
that foolishly obstinate life…
Noble Elder.
Burn it all.
Yes, sir.
With the curse broken,
who knows what
that drowned ghost will blab about?
They will soon investigate
the Association of the Blind.
Move it!
My goodness!
- Goodness me!
- What is going on?
Wait. Stop. Why are you doing this?
Hold on. What is going on?
My word.
My lord,
what brings you
to our squalid corner of the world?
Apprehend all the fortune tellers
in the Association of the Blind!
That is a royal order!
- Yes, sir!
All the fortune tellers
will be dragged out.
Investigate every corner of that place.
You must find evidence.
My goodness!
Please, spare me, my lord.
Who are you?
I am just a mere servant here.
I swear I do not know anything!
My lord! I swear I do not know anything!
My lord.
- My lord!
- Take him to the State Tribunal.
- Yes, my lord.
- My lord…
Announcing His Majesty!
I, your lowly blind subject,
offer my humblest greetings
to Your Divine Majesty!
Do you know someone called Yapper?
Your Majesty, did you say the Yapper?
I have never heard
of such a name before, Your Majesty.
If I find that you speak
even a single lie,
you will deal with the harshest
of consequences.
Why would this pitiful creature
ever lie to His Majesty?
Then, it is true you have been frequenting
the Queen Dowager's Palace?
Answer me!
When did those visits start?
Are you asking when Her Grace,
the noble and exalted Queen Dowager,
began to show this pitiful creature
some favor, Your Majesty?
Let me think…
Yes.
It began when the late king passed,
during the Year of the Water Rabbit.
The Year of the Water Rabbit?
Her Grace married into the royal line
at the most tender age of 17
and experienced the greatest tragedy.
You must be aware
of it as well, Your Majesty.
That heinous evil spirit.
Your Majesty must be careful as well.
If you do not,
Your Majesty will not be able
to avoid great misfortune.
I thoroughly searched
the association grounds,
but I failed to procure any evidence.
I questioned the other fortune tellers,
but none were familiar
with this Yapper character.
Unbelievable…
Will this be all right, Your Majesty?
The Queen Dowager is involved.
Yeo-ri would not have spoken carelessly.
One of them must be the Yapper.
Imprison all of them
and continue the interrogation.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
- Two soups with rice.
- Coming right up.
I feel much better after some warm food.
- Bring out one more.
- Coming.
- No, that will not be necessary.
- All right.
Why? I can easily finish another.
Stop eating already.
Do you know how much this costs?
I might not have enough…
You will end up with terrible regret
if you are stingy with your patron deity.
- We are done here. Let us go.
- What?
What?
Take care.
You are going back now?
My stomach is full and I feel renewed.
There is no reason to delay.
My word.
You want to ride a horse
through the rain this late?
Not a chance.
Why is it raining all of a sudden?
My goodness. Look at it come down.
It looks like a passing shower.
We can go when it stops.
Why…
are you looking at me like that?
How am I looking at you?
You are looking at me as if I were
someone you longed for.
Yoon Gap did indeed have feelings for you.
Perhaps,
this heart races
at a dizzying speed when I look at you
because it belongs to him.
Or perhaps, it is just a cruel joke
being played on me
because I have been trapped
in this mortal body.
Truth be told, I am not sure either.
That is my current state.
What about you?
What do you mean?
I have always been curious.
When you smile at me,
is it for me to see? Or…
is it intended for Yoon Gap?
We need this rain to stop
if we want to leave.
But the rain just shows
no signs of stopping.
Hold on.
You are an Imugi,
a deity that governs the weather.
- Don't tell me…
- My goodness.
Do you think an Imugi can just control
the world's weather as he sees fit?
Even an Imugi has his limits.
Hear me!
I am about to die of thirst here.
Bring me a cup of water!
How dare an imprisoned criminal
give out orders?
Be quiet!
Does a mere constable
dare to speak down to me?
For your sake,
I suggest you go fetch it, unless
you want to be cursed in your sleep.
All right?
Water.
Damn it.
Noble Elder, what is to become of us?
You just had to go after
that wretched queen.
Look at this mess we are all in.
Noble Elder,
you should come up with a plan.
- Yes.
- Yes, please think of a good one.
Did you forget who we were?
Anyone who is anyone in the capital
has benefited from our association
at least once.
Buddhist temples are not allowed
in the capital
and shamanistic rituals are only permitted
ten li past the city walls.
No matter what anyone says,
we fortune tellers have managed
to survive all these years.
Am I wrong?
- Sure.
- You are right. Yes.
No one will be able to touch us.
Your Majesty, you cannot.
The orison of the blind
is not some ploy that seeks
to harm the people.
Your Majesty even showed benevolence
to the lowly slaves.
Without evidence, how could you imprison
the blind fortune tellers, the vulnerable
and destitute members of our society?
What are you saying?
Someone has committed
an unspeakable act of the mystical arts
against the Queen.
Yet, you suggest we just let them go
because we should pity their blindness?
The Chief State Councillor is right.
The Queen was in mortal danger
because of that incident.
If there is any truth to the allegations,
rationale dictates that
they should be properly investigated
to expose their crimes for all to see.
However, all of you suggest
the association be freed
as if you had all conspired together.
Your Majesty.
Do you believe the Queen Dowager
utilized the association
to bring the Queen into harm's way?
I have yet to clarify as such.
Your Majesty.
I hear the blind fortune tellers visited
the Queen Dowager to recite scriptures
for the late Prince Yeongin.
How is that, Your Majesty?
Did that help clear the air for you,
Your Majesty?
They sure love to quote
the words of Confucius and Mencius,
but all the scholar-officials of this
nation secretly nudge their wives
to have talismans and hexes crafted
to ensure their good fortunes.
If we open our mouths,
their depraved secrets
will spill out one by one.
Should we be shaking like a leaf?
Or should they be?
It's clearly them.
Where in the world could he be?
Grilled Abalone.
If you have phlegm, just spit it out.
Must you do that?
Stop calling me Grilled Abalone.
I am the Head Eunuch.
You should address me as such.
I may have been
explicitly and overly irritated
about your conduct and manners recently,
but that was because I did not know
who was actually in your body.
You lacked the knowledge of etiquette
and propriety of the mortal world.
Now, I truly understand
where you are coming from.
Thus, that is enough
of that abalone business.
And just address me
as "my lord" or "Head Eunuch."
Do you understand?
Good.
Then, I shall see you around.
Tell Yeo-ri I am hungry
and to wrap it up so we can go home.
- Head--
- There we go.
Grilled Abalone.
Grilled Abalone!
Are you saying you were unable to find
the blind fortune teller named Yapper?
That's right.
We even questioned
the slaves at the association,
but no fortune teller had such a name.
Besides his name,
did the ghost give you any other clues?
Because he was also sealed
for all those years,
he did not know much.
Forgive me for my shortcomings,
Your Majesty.
No.
You have saved my family
several times already.
You saved the Prince and the Queen.
You also saved the baby
in the Queen's womb, did you not?
I thank you.
About your maternal grandmother…
Did you say her name was Neop-deok?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Did she ever mention
that she visited the palace?
No, she did not.
Not even once?
My grandmother passed away
in the Year of the Water Rabbit.
I was just a child when she passed.
The Year of the Water Rabbit…
Shaman Neop-deok died
in the Year of the Water Rabbit?
Yes. In the fifth month of the year.
How did she pass?
I asked you how she died.
It was an accident.
She fell into the sea during a ritual.
Your Majesty.
You may leave now.
My goodness. Do something.
I cannot believe this.
So clumsy.
What are you mad about now?
I also heard the news.
They failed to locate Yapper.
He managed to kill a prince
of this nation without hesitation.
Did you think
they would get him after one try?
They will find him soon.
Do not be too discouraged.
Yeo-ri.
Yeo-ri!
I went through hell catching that damn
drowned ghost because you asked me to.
I dealt with foolish mortals
even when they disgust me.
I did all that for you.
What could you possibly be mad at now?
Why are you treating me so coldly?
You are right. You did all those things.
However,
that was all
so I would accept you as my patron deity.
In order for you to ascend as a dragon.
And that is our deal.
Yes.
Thus, I am trying my best
to keep that promise.
I will also keep that promise,
no matter what.
I will properly serve you
as my patron deity,
and until the day you ascend as a dragon,
I shall pray with both hands and feet.
However, that is as far as I go.
I will do just that and nothing more.
Thus, you should do just
as much and nothing more.
Whether I am fatigued or not,
or whether I drop
my eyeglass chest or not,
do not meddle yourself.
Do not look at me like that either.
I am certain there is an instigator.
How else could they move
in such perfect unison?
However, it cannot be the Queen Dowager.
This is not how she operates.
Your Majesty.
You should release the members
of the Association of the Blind.
Chief State Councillor!
I, too, wish to punish the one responsible
in the most merciless way.
However,
there is no definitive evidence
to convince the court.
I put you in charge of that investigation
to find that very evidence.
In no way, am I trying to side
with the Queen Dowager.
If someone had conjured a nasty hex
against the royal bloodline,
then, the biggest victim
with the deepest wound
would be the Queen Dowager.
Her influence in the court
is quite formidable.
I fear this may lead…
to vicious backlash.
Your Majesty,
the Association of the Blind members
were just released
from the State Tribunal.
Are you certain
we should release them like this?
That is why evidence…
As of today, I am sure of it,
more than ever.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost has a puppeteer.
But who could that be?
Investigate the association further.
I must catch the Yapper first.
Hey, grab me that towel.
It appears I have made a grave mistake.
Handing over of towels
is not a part of our deal. Our deal…
does not go that far.
I have committed a terrible breach.
I am truly, terribly sorry.
- Move.
- I am so sorry, I could die.
Move.
She could have just walked around me.
She just had to…
Grandma.
I…
was smiling at him.
I was looking at the man who killed you
and smiling.
I thought I was just confused.
I really believed that was why…
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Did Gangcheori really kill Neop-deok?
Hey, you were eavesdropping?
You were latched on to the Queen Dowager.
Why are you here now?
You promised to buy me new shoes
and you did not.
Thus, I will latch on to you
and torment you
with steadfast persistence.
Fine.
I hear you.
Can you just leave me alone now?
Leave now.
I will buy them for you tomorrow morning.
I am in no mood
to deal with you right now.
Hold on.
But how do you know my grandma?
Because I met her.
I told you I was older than your grandma.
Do you just not listen to me?
You met her? At the palace?
When?
So, that was…
Let me think.
Right. The fourth month
of the Year of the Water Rabbit.
That was a month before she passed away.
Was she really at the palace then?
That's what I said.
She came to the palace,
then left with some members
of the royal family.
So I followed them.
I hid nearby and saw everything.
Neop-deok and the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
made a mess in some temple courtyard.
What did you just say?
Ma'am, where did Gang…
I mean, where is Lord Yoon Gap?
He just left for some errand.
Did you not see him?
What is the matter?
I just remembered an urgent errand.
Please go ahead and sleep.
Where are you…
My goodness.
What if a night guard catches you?
In the end, Neop-deok was able to
overpower the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
But I am pretty sure that ghost ended up
going after her to get his revenge.
The more I learn about a maiden's mind,
the less I know about it.
She is charming me
with her smile one moment
and bringing forth a blizzard the next.
The midwinter northern wind
has nothing on her.
Charming who? You?
As if you were mortal?
It is just a figure of speech.
Then, you can just stop here.
Just stop being that brat's patron deity.
What?
Do you regret it?
What are you talking about?
Back then, when you told that brat…
you killed her grandmother.
Geez. I told you no.
My goodness.
You cannot seek an audience
with him at this hour.
I must see His Majesty now.
It is regarding the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
Eight…
Did something else happen?
So…
what brings you here this late?
Your Majesty.
In the Year of the Water Rabbit,
the year you ascended the throne,
was the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
at the palace?
Was a member of the royal family back then
possessed by the Eight-foot-tall Ghost?
That is a private matter
of the royal family.
I cannot give you an answer.
No. I must know.
I must know when
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost first appeared
and who was responsible for its grudge.
I must.
Please, answer me, Your Majesty.
If you refuse to tell me the truth,
I will no longer be able
to assist Your Majesty.
Fine.
It was here.
During those horrific times…
Even back then…
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost was here.
That damn evil spirit…
took hold…
of the late king…
my father.
I believe that damn evil spirit…
also killed my grandmother.
It was not Gangcheori.
It was the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost
killed my grandma.
Draw me a hot bath first.
My body stinks
after rolling around in that filth.
Yes, sir.
Yapper, you scoundrel!
My goodness! My lordship!
My goodness…
Please show me mercy, my lordship.
I know things
did not turn out well this time.
I am terribly upset about it as well!
Even in the afterlife,
I will not forget the great kindness
you have shown me
when you saved me this time.
But, you do not need to worry.
The Warrior Deity has a plan.
He has a brilliant plan to catch
those rascals and heal
all his injuries in one swoop.
Wait. You cannot.
No!
My lordship, you cannot!
Wait, my lordship! My lordship!
Please stop, my lordship!
Please stop!
Please stop, my lordship.
My goodness… No…
That will anger the Warrior Deity.
My lordship, you cannot…
My goodness. My lord…
I could not care less
about what a ghost does.
I pulled you from that nasty market
where you conjured hexes with the ghosts
of the children you starved,
and brought you all the way up here.
After making a complete mess
of everything,
you still seek out the Warrior Deity?
Who do you serve? Do you serve that ghost?
Or do you serve me?
Of course, I serve you, my lordship.
I will stay loyal
to your lordship until my dying breath.
My lordship. The month grace period
you granted me last time is not over yet.
I promise I will end
the prince's life by then.
Fine.
If you fail to take care of this by then,
I shall end your life with my bare hands.
My lordship!
That damn eyeglass artisan!
The wench who ruined everything!
She is of the same bloodline
as that shaman.
She shares a bloodline
with Shaman Neop-deok!
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM YOUNG-KWANG
Why did you not tell me
that it was the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
who killed my grandma and not you?
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
Why would you tell Yeo-ri that?
It appears you were worried about her.
I am certain they like each other.
If we can just briefly hold
that Imugi captive,
we can easily take care of that Yeo-ri.
Every nobleman over 60 had
the same talisman with them.
I cannot summon the wind?
I have your mother.
If you wish to save her,
come to the abandoned house.
What is the meaning of this?
Save me, Gangcheori. Please.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim