THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD ACTORS AND ANIMALS WERE FILMED
IN ACCORDANCE WITH SAFETY GUIDELINES
Stay back.
Stop him!
Keep His Majesty safe!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty…
Queen…
Queen.
My Queen!
Apprehend him!
You cannot, Your Highness.
Mother!
Please, Your Highness…
Hear me! Summon a royal physician!
Summon a royal physician immediately!
The Warrior Deity…
has finally devoured
the unborn baby of the Queen!
I just do not understand
what is going on here.
I am able to touch them without trouble.
Both stones. The King's and the Prince's.
It is faint, but it smells of alcohol.
Someone poured alcohol
on the Ghostbane Stones.
Thus, the Eight-foot-tall Ghost
was able to attack the Queen
despite the fact that
she was holding the Ghostbane Stone.
No, that is not possible.
They were both very strict
about who they allowed to come near.
Your most trusted could be behind it.
Wait, hold on.
Hand it over.
Was it you?
The Prince's Eunuch Lee
already confessed as well.
Were you really behind this?
Head Eunuch, please spare me.
Please forgive me.
He held my family captive
and threatened me. I had no other choice--
I cannot believe you.
You fool!
I took you under my wing
and raised you to be a eunuch…
It appears I have been raising
a wild beast.
I committed a heinous act of treachery
to His Majesty because of you.
You have tainted the honor of all eunuchs.
Take him away.
My lord. Please.
Head Eunuch! Please forgive me!
Your Majesty.
My shortcomings are deserving of death.
What does that mean?
Tell me you can heal her.
Tell me you can heal her right now!
I will not ask you to even save
the baby in her womb.
So, just save…
Just save the Queen, at least!
She has already lost
too much blood, Your Majesty.
This cannot be.
I refuse to accept this.
Tell me what I must do.
Tell me…
What must I do?
Please save her…
Your Majesty.
My Queen.
Mother.
Your Majesty.
I am…
beyond saving now.
No.
Do not say that.
Please do not say such things.
You cannot leave me.
You cannot leave me like this, my Queen.
Please…
Please forgive me…
for departing first.
Our…
Our Gwang…
Please…
Mother…
Mother!
Your Highness…
Mother…
Mother!
My Queen.
It is my fault.
I should have checked
before the passage rite.
I was a fool.
It is not your fault.
We never stood a chance
against the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
He upended a passage rite
that was prepared with the utmost care.
A maniacal, wicked spirit.
Her Highness.
Her Highness has ascended
with royal grace!
May Avalokitesvara show us mercy.
Her Highness has ascended
with royal grace!
Your Highness.
Her Highness…
Your Highness…
You scoundrel.
You…
You said if I just poured
alcohol on those things,
I would become the Chief State Councillor.
But look at this mess.
My steward suddenly went insane
and wielded his sword against the Queen.
Are you trying to get me killed as well?
How did you even know about this place?
I would be left in shambles
if you suddenly disappeared.
I had you followed
after our previous meeting
to uncover your hideout.
You have wasted your time.
You only hastened your demise.
What?
Are you sure
no one followed you all the way here?
Apprehend all of them!
Yes, sir.
Wait. I am innocent.
It was not me. I am innocent.
I did not do anything.
Is this the only way now?
But that means…
I could end up dying.
Hey! Everyone!
My goodness. Did you all hear the news?
They caught the scoundrels
who did that to the Queen!
I hear the interrogation hall is
in a frenzy right now.
My goodness.
Those rotten scoundrels.
I do not know anything.
I was only deceived by this man.
Please spare me, Your Majesty.
As soon as day breaks tomorrow,
behead them all.
Do I make myself clear?
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty…
You are no better than a beast!
Did you never fear
the judgment of the gods?
Judgment?
Give me a damn break.
I was struck by that damn divine judgment
the moment I was born.
Lowborn by birth
and cursed by blindness.
If all those years of being treated
less than a maggot
were not divine punishment,
then what is?
That would not even come close.
I promise you this.
You will end up suffering
the most excruciatingly painful death.
You should not be so cocky.
You are not even a threat
to the Warrior Deity now.
After all, he possesses
a luminous pearl, just like you.
You…
and that brat you care so much about
will soon be done for.
I should kill you!
That is enough.
Even His Majesty held back
from slaying him.
Gangcheori.
Stop right there!
My goodness. Look who it is.
Why, it is Her charming Grace,
the Queen Dowager.
You dared to trick me
into offering up my son as a sacrifice?
You committed that vile act
against the ever-gentle Queen
and used me
to defy the King?
Why did it have to be me?
Why did you target me?
That was because you, wench,
looked like the most terrified,
cornered rat.
What did you say?
Toying around with a terrified wench
in the palm of your hand
requires no effort at all.
Why, you scoundrel!
Your Grace. He is to be beheaded shortly.
Please try to remain calm.
Let us go.
Your Majesty.
These objects were delivered
by Eyeglass Artisan Yeo-ri.
A talisman that wards off ghosts
and eastern peach branches.
Your Majesty.
You cannot continue to refuse your meals
and reside in the royal library all day.
Your Majesty.
I am the one who deserves death.
So please,
look after your sacred body.
Please look after your sacred body.
Your Majesty…
I will get you some more.
But she never drinks tea.
Why?
Does it look strange?
A pearl necklace on a pig's neck…
is what I was afraid of…
but it suits you quite well.
Do not be too disheartened…
because I am keeping my distance.
It is just that…
if I embrace you as I would my own child…
I would feel so sorry for my poor Gap.
I am aware.
Do not burden your heart.
Mortals are lowly creatures
and they sometimes behave revoltingly,
but they can also be charming at times.
I am certain…
that was thanks to mothers like you
who so tenderly looked
after their children.
Is Yeo-ri making a fresh batch of rice?
This is indeed caragana.
Did the plant I gave you flower?
Well… the plant is currently
with someone else.
However, I did see the buds
before they bloomed for myself.
Is that true?
Did that caragana actually bloom?
May I ask why you respond so?
What is so special about that caragana?
Well, the thing is…
Examiner Yoon Gap.
They say if the caragana blossom
is consumed,
one will be able to hold out
until the luminous pearl
is completely drained
while confronting
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
Does Gangcheori know about this?
Gangcheori…
what exactly are you planning to do?
Your Majesty.
Hear me.
Is anyone there?
Hear me!
You…
You must be the scoundrel.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost.
You should have just killed me instead.
Why would you kill her?
I attempted to ask for your forgiveness.
With my sincerest intention,
I sought to atone.
Then, why…
Why would you kill
someone completely innocent?
She was beautiful and ever so gentle.
I understand your grudge runs deep,
but where does it end?
Tell me where it ends!
Why must I suffer so
because of the sins
of my ancestor long past?
His sins are not mine.
Do you say they are not your sins?
You do not know anything.
You do not know how I died.
How my family,
my kin,
and my neighbors
all met their demise.
You know not
of the vow I made with my last breath.
What could you possibly know?
You spent your life in these gilded halls,
draped in silks
and veiled behind the palace walls.
You do not know anything!
Seon-u…
Run. Hurry.
Cheers to Commandant Cheon
of Yongdam Village!
Cheers!
With the military exam behind him,
we should call him the deity of warriors!
The Warrior Deity!
Yes, of course.
He is the Warrior Deity, indeed!
Cheers to the Warrior Deity
of Yongdam Village!
Cheers to Yongdam Village!
It is my fault.
It is all my fault.
Everyone died because of me.
I will never forgive you.
I shall make you pay, even in death.
King…
I shall…
slaughter every member of your bloodline.
I shall never forgive you.
For all eternity!
Did you say these are not your sin,
but those of your ancestor?
This royal dragon robe you wear
was woven with the bloody sacrifices
of the villagers of Yongdam,
my family, and me!
The very throne your ancestor secured
through sacrificing our lives…
is where you sit, is it not?
However, I am sure you remained oblivious,
satisfied about what a sage king you are.
You must have prided yourself
on being a benevolent king
who embraced all his people.
Your very existence is a sin.
That blood only flows through your body
because it was saved
with our wretched, fiery deaths.
And yet, you shamelessly proclaim
that you are utterly without blame?
My grudge shall not be extinguished
until every last drop
of blood from your lineage…
has been eradicated from this land.
No…
You cannot…
Please…
I will let a part of you remain conscious,
so prepare your eyes
to fully bear witness…
what happens to your son,
that insufferable Imugi scoundrel
who always got in my way,
and even that wench, Yeo-ri.
You shall witness
how they all meet their demise,
just as I had met mine.
You cannot. No!
I was wrong.
I was wrong!
Please.
Please!
Are you all right, Your Majesty?
My goodness.
After all, he possesses
a luminous pearl, just like you.
You…
and that brat you care so much about
will soon be done for.
Oh, you scared me.
Sulking in utter desolation
is only making that ugly face uglier.
What?
Follow me.
What? To where?
I was sure it was around here somewhere.
What are you looking for?
There it is.
Welcome.
We will take this.
Sure. That will be three jeon.
Three jeon…
Come here.
Finally, somewhat acceptable.
What is?
You finally look somewhat acceptable,
after covering up some of that ugly face.
What? I'm taking it off.
No.
Your sacred patron deity
just bestowed this upon you. How dare you?
Make sure to wear it every day.
Maybe you will tremble
a little less with that on.
You always speak like that.
Just say you wanted to buy it for me.
Was calling me ugly necessary?
Well… I guess it is warm.
Wait, but you cannot squander
your salary again like last time.
Bring every last bit to your mother.
After I graciously used
my pumpkin taffy money to buy it,
must you nag like that?
But maybe…
I might like that one a bit more.
Which one?
This one? Or this one?
No. On a second look,
I think this one is the prettiest.
And you did choose this one for me…
You are still the fairest mortal
I have ever known.
Hence,
it breaks my heart.
Where are you taking me?
It is almost the first full moon
of the lunar new year.
It looks like people added wish papers
to be burned with the moon hut.
You could not care less about it
in Yongdam. What has gotten into you?
It was not that I did not care.
I just stayed away
because they were nasty and petty.
They used to shoot dirty looks
if I ever approached them,
worried I would end up
jinxing their holy wishes.
Seeing how angry you are now,
you must have had a wish
you wanted to write down.
I did.
I was so sick and tired of being alone.
I wanted to wish for someone
to share meals and tender warmth with.
I wished for it with all my heart.
That was it.
Are you trying to keep it a secret?
You will jinx me. Go over there.
Traditionally, they burned
moon huts with wishes
as a way of wishing on the Big Dipper.
However,
despite having
your patron deity right here,
you wish to pray
to some stars far, far away?
Who knows if it will ever be granted?
It might be granted if I wish hard enough.
The Big Dipper up there might.
So, what did you write down?
You will only jinx it.
Unbelievable.
Wait, what is that over there?
What?
What are you talking about?
No. All the way over there.
That?
Yes.
I heard…
Pung-san was scheduled
to be beheaded today.
Proceed with the execution!
He smiles?
Stop!
His Majesty commands
you to stop this execution at once!
Your Majesty,
did you just give a command to…
Your Majesty.
Why are you stopping their execution?
Those two, An Seok-ju and Pung-san,
assassinated Her Highness, the Queen.
They did not kill the Queen.
The ones who led me to perform
that heinous, heretical ceremony,
Examiner Yoon Gap
and Eyeglass Artisan Yeo-ri,
killed the Queen.
That is not true, Your Majesty.
They were merely trying
to aid Your Majesty.
Were you also an accomplice
in the assassination of the Queen?
Most certainly not, Your Majesty.
How could I ever dare--
Carry out my royal command properly!
Stop the execution of Noble Elder Pung-san
and the others immediately.
Apprehend Examiner Yoon Gap
and Eyeglass Artisan Yeo-ri,
and behead them immediately!
This is a royal command.
Apprehend Examiner Yoon Gap
and Eyeglass Artisan Yeo-ri.
Yes, sir.
Who is Yeo-ri?
What's going on?
My goodness!
Yeo-ri.
They could not have gone far.
Find them.
I already searched over here.
Search that way.
Yes, sir. Let's go!
My lord, what is going on?
Why is His Majesty coming after us?
His Majesty has changed.
He was definitely lost
in melancholy just before,
but he suddenly experienced
a surge of energy and gave the order.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost
has possessed him.
With the Ghostbane Stones gone,
there is no reason
for him to bide his time.
Come to think of it,
I detected on His Majesty
the stench that once came
from the Prince's quarters.
His Highness is in danger.
If His Majesty is possessed,
the Prince will be his first target.
However,
I cannot just openly defy His Majesty's
royal command to save His Highness.
That is Your Majesty in appearance only.
What will happen
when he is no longer possessed
and he finds out he killed his son
with his own two hands?
Considering his lofty character,
he is bound to give in to insanity.
We will be at Choi Won-u's residence.
Bring the baby Prince there.
What did you just say?
He stopped Pung-san's execution?
And he also commanded
for Examiner Yoon Gap
and Eyeglass Artisan Yeo-ri
to be apprehended?
Yes, Your Grace.
I heard Pung-san was
summoned to the palace.
How could the King give out
such an absurd command
if he has not gone mad?
Your mourning robe…
Your Majesty.
Have you already forgotten
what kind of creature he is?
He used a wicked spirit
to kill the Queen
and my son, Prince Yeongin!
Yet, you stopped his execution
and even summoned him to the palace?
Answer me, Your Majesty!
It has not even been a few days
since the passing of the Queen.
How could you change out
of your mourning robe already?
Did you forget
what the Queen meant to you?
You are much too noisy.
Shall I behead you as well?
What did you say?
What did you just…
You…
What could you possibly do
as you shake like a leaf?
I have no intention
of killing you as well.
You are not of his bloodline anyway.
However, if you act foolishly…
you shall lose your life as well, wench.
Your Grace!
Your Grace.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
how could you treat Her Grace--
I do not want to hear it.
You two shall also leave my sight at once.
Unless you have a death wish.
And end the state mourning
for the Queen this instant!
Your Majesty.
But…
Your Majesty…
Your Grace!
Are you all right, Your Grace?
Who goes there?
Are you not that eyeglass artisan?
Can you please invite us in?
What are you saying?
What do you mean His Majesty
is possessed by an evil spirit?
He stopped the execution
of the Queen's assassins,
Lord An Seok-ju and Noble Elder Pung-san,
before calling for our arrest.
Royal Guard Seo Jae-il
also mentioned His Majesty
suddenly started acting strangely.
Yes…
It does indeed seem strange,
based on what you told me.
However, I cannot just blindly believe
what you two tell me.
Something else could have happened before
to warrant His Majesty's actions.
I cannot welcome
an unnecessary misunderstanding
by taking you two in
when you are on the run.
I will not report you to the state troops…
but you must leave at once.
Have you already forgotten
your daughter was once possessed
by that book merchant's vengeful ghost?
The same thing is happening right now.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost,
the vengeful ghost of Cheon Geum-hwi,
has now possessed him.
Yet, you still do not believe us?
You…
Your tone and conduct last time
at Yongdam Village was quite irritating,
but I held back
because His Majesty let you be.
How dare you refer
to His Majesty in such a manner!
It is "His Majesty"!
You dare refer to him as "that King"?
Damn it.
Let us go, Yeo-ri.
We are talking to a wall here.
I hope you do not kick out the baby Prince
once he flees and makes his way here.
What did you say?
Wait. Hold on…
Father, these two saved both you and me.
This is no way to repay them
for their kindness.
You may stay the night. However,
leave once day breaks.
Take them off.
Stop it.
Come now.
Shall I do it for you?
What is wrong with you?
Take them off already.
I told you I am fine.
They do not hurt anymore.
I saw you wincing as you walked.
That is enough already.
I will take care of my own ankles.
We are coming in.
Sure. Come in.
It is late and I could not ask them
to prepare a feast.
I had them prepare something light.
Thank you, my lady.
And for welcoming us earlier as well.
We would be lost right now
if we were turned away like that.
You are the one who saved me.
I, also…
am someone who knows
how to repay kindness.
Yes, I am sure you are.
But…
this room is quite small.
Will you be all right?
I had them prepare another room.
You should stay there, my lord.
Your meal is waiting
for you there as well.
It is not small at all.
This is even bigger than our house.
I should help you with a hot compress--
Stop. Enough.
The Eight-foot-tall Ghost
has possessed His Majesty?
Are you sure
that is what Imugi Gangcheori said?
Yes, my lord.
But what are you two doing in here?
Why are you not in the Grand Hall?
We were kicked out.
Pardon?
Way to brag.
How ridiculous.
His Majesty… I mean,
His Eight-foot-tall Ghost Majesty
has already figured out
that we had our suspicions.
How is this just in any way?
We were kicked out
after a lifetime of service
to have Sang-deuk, that traitor,
and the steward who stabbed Her Highness
serve His Majesty.
I cannot believe this.
What should we do about this?
Yeo-ri and Imugi Gangcheori were worried
about His Highness, the Prince.
What? His Highness? Why?
They said
the Eight-foot-tall Ghost's first target
would be His Highness.
Are you asking about the caragana blooms?
Yes. Do you have any more?
I came here today specifically
to acquire some more.
Providing more will not be an issue,
but you must tell me
what those blooms exactly are.
I am observant in my own ways.
Just like how Yeo-ri is not
a mere eyeglass artisan,
I had figured out your lord
was not just a mere examiner.
I am sure the caragana
that bloomed in the middle of winter
is not just an ordinary flower.
So please, answer me.
Is that not the least amount
of etiquette you could show me
after I took care of it this whole time?
You are right.
To protect the one I wish to keep safe,
I need that flower.
By "the one you wish to keep safe,"
do you mean Yeo-ri?
What are you doing here?
It is nothing.
By chance, can I borrow
some yellow soil and salt?
To do what with them?
How much do you need?
As much as I can get.
I suspect they will come in handy soon.
Open them!
Where is that damn Prince?
Your Grace, where are you going?
First, to my quarters.
Once His Majesty realizes
His Highness is missing,
that is where he would go next.
How is there not
a single place to hide the Prince
in this vast palace?
Your Grace.
Did you look into it?
Yes, she was speaking the truth.
The Capital is crawling with state troops
looking for the two of them.
Your Excellency, it is Mak-geum.
What is it?
Your Highness!
My lord.
We have confirmed His Highness is residing
at Lord Choi Won-u's residence.
How did you know
His Highness would flee in advance?
When drive hunting, the prey
are bound to look for hiding spots.
I am sure that brat
and that rotten Imugi are there as well.
I shall hunt them all at once.
No! You cannot!
Please!
Why, this is…
Her Grace's dragon-head hairpin,
is it not?
She asked me to deliver this to you.
To ask you to keep me, the Prince, safe.
His Highness was able to make it out
safely, thanks to Her Grace's assistance.
Then, is His Majesty
truly possessed by an evil spirit?
You refused to listen to us.
Now, do you believe us?
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
there is great trouble afoot.
State troops are gathering outside!
Your Highness.
You will be all right.
Get the boy out of here with Yeo-ri.
I will buy you some time.
No.
I shall step outside.
Look after His Highness.
Open these gates.
His Majesty awaits outside!
Knock down the gates.
Your Majesty.
What brings you by to my residence,
this early in the morning?
Your Majesty.
Now, I finally know who you are.
Your cowardly ancestor
was there as well.
Your Majesty.
Just as your ancestor had done,
remain quiet and do nothing.
If you interfere once more,
I shall slay you first!
Let us go.
Halt!
Go on ahead.
Step back, all of you.
I will take care of this Imugi myself.
The whole nation is
in the palm of the Warrior Deity.
What happens to us now?
Must we continue running from Father
who remains possessed by an evil spirit?
You are the most important to me.
So, let us run away, Gangcheori.
Do you mean it?
I have sworn an oath to always be ready
to give my life for His Majesty.
I can no longer stand by
as that dirty, evil spirit continues
to occupy His Majesty's body.
Where is Yeo-ri?
You must be safe.
You…
I am here, under the command
of The Ten Kings of the Underworld,
to escort you to the afterlife.
Follow without protest.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim