Mr. Ling Yizhou is suffering
from traveler's diarrhea.
Let's give him some time.
Mr. Ling Yizhou is suffering
from traveler's diarrhea.
Let's give him some time.
Mr. Ling Yizhou is suffering
from traveler's diarrhea.
Let's give him some time.
Traveler's diarrhea?
Mumu.
-What?
-There's no more shampoo.
It's on the bottom half of the shelf.
I can't find it. Can you get it?
Fine, I'll get it for you.
A towel?
-It's mine.
-Whose?
-Mine.
-So you're...
Naked.
Mr. Fu,
I heard you were college classmates
with Ling Yizhou.
That was a long time ago.
Why would you bring that up, Mr. Jin?
I'm always cautious
when choosing who I work with.
I'm worried
that you won't be able to do it
because of your friendship.
You must be kidding, Mr. Jin.
He was born into the Ling family
with a silver spoon in his mouth.
And I...
I'm just an ordinary person. I'm nobody.
With such different backgrounds,
do you think we'd still be friends?
That's true.
He has been able
to live luxuriously off of his family.
Recently, he's even had the time
to go on a show with an actress.
He would never be able
to manage the company well.
In my opinion,
you're much more capable than him, Mr. Fu.
Take this
and get everything done.
Don't worry.
Once you're done,
I'll definitely fulfill
the promises I've made to you.
This is a serious matter.
I only have this one chance.
It's now or nothing.
Mr. Fu.
You won't let me down, will you?
I won't.
I'm finally home.
I'm so tired.
Hello?
Xia Lin, are you home yet?
I just got home.
Good.
Romantic Departure has been receiving
good feedback since it aired.
Your popularity has gone up.
Really? That's great!
I'll tell you more later.
Get some rest today.
Okay. I know, Ms. Jiang.
Who is it?
-Hello.
-Delivery for Ms. Xia Lin.
Pidan. Is it from the producers?
I don't know.
-Can you bring it in for me?
-Sure.
Thank you.
-Just leave it here.
-Okay. Here you go.
Okay. Thank you.
Pidan, this is your new home.
Go look around.
What is this?
Did you get the dog yet?
I did.
Thank you, Mr. Ling.
Pidan, don't move.
Let me take a photo.
Don't move.
Sales of outdoor home appliances
related products
have gone up from 3 percent to 7 percent.
Are you free tomorrow?
Let me treat you to dinner
to thank you for Pidan.
Sure. You can decide the time.
-Is it this office?
-Yes.
Mr. Ling, let me explain.
The company received an anonymous tip
that there has been unfair competition
in international information affairs
under your supervision.
Foreign investors
are quite unhappy about this
and have asked to investigate the matter.
If the accusations are true,
they are demanding
to fire the CEO immediately.
Or else they will pull
all their investments.
So...
Let me see.
"The board has decided
that you will be suspended
for the next 30 days
to be investigated
by the Internal Audit Department.
The matter will be handled by Fu Weining."
I am Fu Weining.
"Before the investigation is concluded,
you must not participate
in any decision-making procedures,
including..."
This is quite a long list.
Anyway, you must leave
this office right now.
Sure.
Wen Li, let's go.
Why is it so hot here?
I didn't expect that we'd meet like this,
my dear classmate.
Fu Weining,
you haven't changed at all.
Being too aggressive
might hurt yourself.
You haven't changed either.
As arrogant as ever.
I won't go easy on you
just because we used to be classmates.
Why hasn't Ling Yizhou replied to me yet?
What does he usually do at this time?
What's wrong with me?
Why am I missing him all of a sudden?
Hello, Ms. Jiang.
Hello, Xia Lin.
Our proposal for I Cannot Hug You
went through.
The director really likes you. You're in.
Okay. Got it.
What's wrong?
You don't sound happy.
It's nothing.
I'm probably just too tired from filming.
I'm still adjusting.
Don't worry. I'll start preparing.
Also, Ms. Jiang,
thank you for being with me
through these hard times.
Thank you for your hard work.
No need to say that.
You've worked very hard.
They start shooting soon, so be prepared.
Got it.
Don't worry, Ms. Jiang.
Come on.
Let's go.
Keep an eye on them while I'm not there.
Let me know if anything happens.
Yes, Boss.
By the way, Boss,
should we tell Ms. Xia about this?
Of course not.
-You can go now.
-All right. You get some rest too.
Sorry, I just saw your message.
Did something happen today?
It's nothing.
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
Okay.
I have some good news to share with you.
-Good morning.
Good morning, Xia Lin.
Why are you so early today?
I woke up early. The traffic was smooth.
What about you?
How does it feel to be back on set again?
I feel energized and ambitious.
Really?
You haven't been acting for a while.
You should watch how I do it
and learn from me.
Of course.
I'll make sure to pay attention
to the best actor, Chu Yan.
I won't get you in trouble.
Good.
You better not embarrass me.
Of course not.
Both of you are like best friends.
Don't get it wrong.
It's never what you see.
It's all an act.
So you'll grab her
and come in from the river.
-Okay.
-Make sure there's tension.
-Okay?
-Sure.
Wait.
We're all in this together.
So don't pull any petty moves on me.
If you really hate me,
please just keep it inside.
Bottle it up for two months
so that we can finish shooting.
Then we'll be able
to get rid of each other sooner.
You can live your life
and I can live mine.
What do you think?
Guys, you must make it look real, okay?
Xia Lin, act like you're panicking.
This scene is kind of dangerous,
so let's get it done the first time.
All right.
I understand, ma'am.
-Be safe.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Stand by, everyone.
-Move to the left a bit.
I wonder what spell you cast
to make Ling Yizhou propose to you.
Now, you even got Chu Yan
to give you a lead role.
You're such an ultimate sham.
Move the PAR lamp to the left.
Slow down. To the left.
Let go of me. Just tell him you like him.
-Why are you doing this to me?
-Come here!
He's mine.
You can't steal him from me, you bitch.
I'll teach you not to mess with me!
Help!
-Xia Lin's acting is amazing.
-Help!
-If Zhen Baohui didn't tell me about it,
I would think this is real.
-You can scream all you want.
-Help!
-I already cleared the area.
It's just you and me here.
Help!
-Save her!
-Hurry!
-Hurry up!
-Save her!
-Hurry.
-Here.
Hurry.
-Get her up.
-Careful.
-Slow down.
-Are you okay?
-Hurry up.
-Xia Lin, are you okay?
-Should we get a doctor?
-Have you called an ambulance?
-I'm fine, ma'am.
-Get her inside.
-Hurry up.
-Slow down.
-Careful.
-Here.
-Are you okay?
-Careful.
You know what you did.
Don't bring
your personal emotions into this.
If you do that again,
I'll have to teach you a lesson.
What are you looking at?
Get to work!
Ms. Xia just swallowed some water.
She isn't hurt.
Who's investing in this film?
China Entertainment is the only investor.
-Contact their boss for me.
-Yes, Boss.
By the way, the board suddenly
decided to switch suppliers
which has caused a problem
with Lingshi Technology's chip production.
It will affect our delivery dates
for the second half of the year.
This won't do.
Book a Monday flight ticket
to the UK for me
and arrange a meeting with Benjamin.
I'll talk to him myself.
Okay.
Get some rest, Boss.
Xia Lin.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Let's go.
Okay, make the arrangements.
Yes, Boss.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's wrong?
Someone was following me.
Probably a reporter.
You should be careful too.
I'm not a movie star.
Why should I be careful?
If they get photos of you
having fun without me,
even your fiancée
won't be able to help you.
Then I'll have to help myself.
Get down.
-What's wrong?
-Paparazzi.
-Where?
-Get down.
-Are they still here?
-Yes.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
Just a slight cough.
It was windy on my way here.
-Are they gone yet?
-No.
Ling Yizhou, were you pranking me?
We are in a private room.
Who would be taking photos?
Me.
Let's order now. I'm hungry.
Get me the cold medicine in the car.
What would you like?
Anything.
You can go now.
Drive safely.
Is there anything you need to tell me?
No.
I haven't filmed for so long.
It was very exciting today.
There's nothing else.
It's getting late. You should go now.
You...
A goodbye kiss?
Seriously?
There's no need to keep acting.
What?
There's paparazzi.
-Where?
-Over there.
-There.
-Where?
Okay. You can go now.
Boss, I got the information.
They sent the stalker.
Send more people to protect Mumu.
Make sure they are discreet.
-Don't let Mumu find out.
-Okay.
Ms. Xia.
Hello, my name is Meixi.
-I have the supporting role of Wu Feifei.
-Come closer.
Wu Feifei. Nice to meet you.
-What about Zhen Baohui?
-Okay. Good.
I'm not sure about the details.
-Careful.
-I think Baohui wasn't feeling well.
So she backed out.
-Come closer.
-I just got notified yesterday.
-That's good.
-Okay, Ms. Xia.
-I'll go say hi to the others now.
-Okay.
Okay. I look forward to working with you.
Thank you.
-Mr. Chu.
-Hi.
Here.
What is it? You seem to be in a good mood.
What? Is it my turn to shoot?
Not yet.
About Zhen Baohui...
Thank you.
-Zhen Baohui? Who's that?
-What's wrong?
I got it.
-Try it again.
-It was nothing.
-But be careful, okay?
-Okay.
I know. So what is she...
Chu Yan, get over here!
The director is asking for me.
I have to go.
-Go ahead. Don't piss her off.
-We're good.
-Piss her off?
-One more.
Just one side?
That's impossible.
That one is broken. Be careful.
He's ridiculous.
Ms. Jiang. Here, have a seat.
No need for that.
I asked around.
The investors switched out Zhen Baohui.
I know.
You know who did it?
Chu Yan, right?
Chu Yan?
I don't think so.
Stop thinking about that.
I think it's a good thing.
Everyone can get along now.
Ms. Jiang, are you leaving soon?
I came here to keep an eye on you.
You get into trouble when I'm not around.
What if something like yesterday
happens again?
It won't.
You're drinking this too?
It's quite popular now.
All the actresses are drinking this
Baiyinian meal replacement powder.
I heard that it's nutritious
and can help you lose weight.
I'll buy some later and give them
to everyone on set on your behalf.
That's a good idea.
Okay. Keep reading your script.
I need to give this to the director.
It's her birthday today.
Okay.
They said one of the investors
didn't like Zhen Baohui,
so they replaced her.
An investor
who could easily replace her...
Chu Yan, who do you think it is?
Since when do you like to gossip?
Get my car.
Okay.
That's her.
Yuyuan, have the driver turn on
the air-conditioner.
Okay.
How do you feel?
I think it went great. What do you think?
-You're doing well.
-Xia Lin.
Good work, guys.
Ms. Xia, hello.
This is...
You...
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Fu Weining.
I'm a legal consultant at Lingshi Group.
I'm in charge of the investigation
of Ling Yizhou's misconduct.
Ling Yizhou's misconduct?
It means that
he has done something wrong.
Ms. Xia, would you like
to have tea together?
Excuse me.
I don't think we're that close.
I'm sure that you would like
to know more about Ling Yizhou,
wouldn't you?
It's so hot today.
I'll go with you.
Come on.
Something has happened to Xia Lin.
Get here quick.
It's so hot.
Aren't you...
Aren't you hot?
Tell us what you want.
I guess Ling Yizhou hasn't told Ms. Xia
what happened yet.
He has been accused of accepting bribery.
He has been suspended for investigation.
That's related to his work.
I don't need to know about it.
I guess you don't know
Ling Yizhou very well, Ms. Xia.
Ling Yizhou is my future husband.
I think I know him better
than anyone else.
Ms. Xia, do you know that there are
two things you can never look at directly?
One is the sun.
The other is the human mind.
The former will hurt your eyes,
the latter will hurt your heart.
The human mind...
The more trustworthy
it seems to be on the surface,
the darker and more despicable
it is in the shadows.
Can you talk in a way we can understand?
If you want me to say it directly...
Ling Yizhou isn't as honest
and trustworthy as you think he is.
If you continue to be with him,
you might get in trouble yourself.
I hope Ms. Xia can cooperate
with our investigation
and tell us what you know.
I have nothing to tell you.
Ms. Xia, I thought I was being very clear.
This could affect your career in showbiz.
Make the right decision.
Mr. Fu, I'm Xia Lin's manager.
I'm in charge of her career.
In my opinion,
you have no right to comment
on Xia Lin's career at all.
You're such an annoying manager.
Thank you. That's what everyone says.
This is the last time.
Ms. Jiang.
Would you like to get a drink together?
I'm on my period.
I can't have cold drinks.
Wen Li.
We'll drive Ms. Xia home first.
Yes, Boss.
Mumu, if he comes to you again,
just tell me.
I'll handle him.
You've been suspended?
It's just an investigation.
It will be fine.
Why didn't you tell me?
It wasn't necessary.
"It wasn't necessary"?
Aren't we partners?
This is a serious matter.
What happens to you affects me too.
Why wouldn't you tell me about it?
Mumu, I'm their target.
I don't want my affairs to affect you.
You can just live your life normally.
Ling Yizhou, you think that
I can never help you in any way, right?
That's why you don't tell me anything.
Or do you think I don't have the right
to face things together with you,
the chairman of Lingshi Group?
What about you?
You didn't tell me
that you fell into the water.
Aren't you the same?
You...
Mr. Wen, stop the car.
Stop the car.
Don't you think he's being ridiculous?
Kind of.
But...
Mr. Ling was trying
to respect your wishes.
Jia Fei.
Which side are you on?
On the other hand,
I'm curious why you're so mad.
Why wouldn't I be mad?
I thought you said you were just acting.
Why would you be mad?
I...
I'm just getting into character.
So you're already preparing
for the role of a fiancée.
Come here.
What?
Look at your small face.
Your skin looks terrible.
Those dark circles under your eyes...
The wrinkles...
You do look like a tragic lead actress.
Do I really look that bad?
Are you still
the optimistic Xia Lin I know?
Come here.
Let me put an eye mask on you.
Then, I, the experienced
love story screenwriter,
will analyze what's going on for you.
You and Ling Yizhou have the same problem.
Whether it's a relationship in a script
or in real life,
you must support and help each other.
You've been single for so many years.
That's why you're used
to deal with everything yourself.
That's why you never tell him anything.
As for him,
he's used to being in charge.
He's also a male chauvinist.
That's why he always deals with problems
without you knowing.
He wants you to live your life happily
without having to worry
about this.
But it makes me feel like
he doesn't trust me.
See?
If you feel that way,
he probably feels the same.
Did you know that Lingshi Group invested
in this new film you're shooting now?
Mr. Ling ordered them
to replace Zhen Baohui.
He did?
How do you know?
I heard...
The producer told me.
At first, there was only one investor,
China Entertainment.
Zhen Baohui had talked to them
about replacing you.
But then,
Lingshi Group invested more money
and beat China Entertainment.
I heard that Zhen Baohui
acted very unprofessionally on set.
Her acting was very awkward
and she had a bad attitude.
So they just replaced her.
Feifei.
Do you think I was too mean to him today?
I guess my analysis was quite accurate.
I need to take notes.
This might be useful.
Should I apologize?
Feifei.
Can you stop writing
about other people's love stories?
You should think about yourself too.
I know.
When you were on
that reality show last time,
didn't Inglemirepharm's give you
a set of skincare products?
Yes, it was Inglemirepharm's.
I'll have my assistant
give you some next time.
Okay.
What should I do?
That's good.
Start preparing for the next scene.
-Good work, guys.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Let's add a new scene.
We'll have someone
throw the ball at Xia Lin.
Chu Yan, you'll block it for her.
That's good.
Chu Yan, are you all right?
Are you okay?
It kind of hurts.
I think I need
your fan to heal my injury.
Sure. I'll let you borrow it
for ten minutes.
Ten minutes?
Do you think I'm only worth ten minutes?
I need at least 20 minutes.
I think you're doing just fine.
Hey, let me lean on you.
-You're fine.
-Look at my arm.
Why are you late?
You haven't changed either.
I'm not expecting a raise.
Fine.
How is she?
Everything is normal.
Give me the phone. I need to check Weibo.
MR. LING, LOOK AT YOUR WIFE
SWEETEST COUPLE
MR. LING, DO YOU GIVE THEM YOUR BLESSING?
I thought you said everything's normal.
What is this?
The crew responded
and said it's just for the show.
I've made a decision.
I don't want anything to do with you.
Let's stop seeing each other.
Wen Li.
Get me the car. We're going there now.
Boss.
I just had some wine with a client.
I'm kind of...
I feel dizzy.
So you can't drive?
I could drive...
But it's against the law.
It's fine.
I'll drive.
Boss.
I can get you a designated driver.
Your salary this month...
In a bit,
Chu Yan will stand
in front of Xia Lin like this.
Xia Lin, you need to act shy and say...
"What are you doing?"
-Okay? Get it?
-Yes.
-You have to act cool, okay?
-Okay.
Let's try it.
Okay.
Five, four, three, two...
What are you doing?
You get it, right?
Ma'am,
it's a shame you didn't pursue acting.
I would if I were prettier.
Why would I be a director?
-Come on.
-Yes.
Ma'am, Mr. Ling is here.
He wants to treat everyone
to afternoon tea.
Mr. Ling?
Hello, Ma'am.
-Mr. Ling, hello.
-Hello.
Thank you for the afternoon tea.
It's no problem.
It's hot outside.
Have some cold drinks to cool down.
Xia Lin has one more scene.
-How about you wait inside?
-It's fine. I'll watch from here.
Just pretend like I'm not here.
Stand by, everyone. Get ready!
Just do your job.
Xia Lin, keep your head up!
I can't see your face.
Sorry, ma'am. Let's try it again.
Again.
Five, four, three, two...
Xia Lin, what are you looking at?
Look at the man in front of you.
Again!
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Again!
I'll give you one minute.
Get yourselves together.
Xia Lin.
What flavor was your bubble gum?
Strawberry.
Mine was durian.
What will happen
if the flavors mix together?
Show some respect.
I'm an actress.
Really?
If you're an actress,
why were you so nervous
about doing a kiss scene?
I've never done one
with strawberry and durian, okay?
You're silly.
Hurry up.
Are you guys ready?
-Yes.
Get ready.
Five, four, three, two...
Good!
It's a wrap.
Thank you for the drinks, Mr. Ling.
-Thank you, Mr. Ling.
You can have
some of my lemon mint green tea.
What? This isn't the one I usually drink.
That place went out of business.
Why do the places I like
always go out of business so soon?
It's probably your own problem.
Mumu, are you done?
That was the last scene.
-Let's go home then.
-Okay.
We're here.
Get some rest.
Bye then.
I'll wait for the elevator with you.
Okay.
Aren't we partners?
This is a serious matter.
What happens to you affects me too.
Why wouldn't you tell me about it?
What about you?
You didn't tell me
that you fell into the water.
Aren't you the same?
You...
-I'm sorry.
Do you want to come up?
Sure.
Mumu.
Isn't this apartment too big for you?
No. I have Pidan.
Pidan?
-Pidan.
-Pidan, you scared me.
I thought you weren't afraid of dogs.
I'm not. I just need some time
to get used to him.
This is your chance then.
Pidan wants to play with you.
Pidan.
Do you think you should be here right now?
Go play. Go on.
Good dog.
Mumu.
I was actually hoping
that you'd come live with me.
What?
You know the situation right now.
Even though it's about my job,
Fu Weining is trying
to get to me through you.
If you move in with me,
at least I can protect you.
I don't want anything bad
to happen to you.
I know you're worried about me.
But I'm fine living by myself here.
Besides, it's so easy
to get in touch nowadays.
You don't have to worry about my safety.
Mumu, I hope you can think about it.
By the way, last time...
I was kind of mean to you.
I know it's not that you don't respect me.
We're actually quite alike.
We don't want to cause each other trouble.
So, I'll start trying to talk to you
about my problems more.
You should too.
So that we can be better partners.
Mumu.
I'll do what you say.
I also hope you understand
that nothing you do
could cause me any burden.
I like dealing with your problems for you.
Your presence in my life
has made it more interesting.
Mumu.
I like having you by my side.
I can feel your warmth in my heart.
Sometimes, I think you're a thief.
Because...
Everything you do
steals my attention.
Who is it?
I need help!
Get up. Hurry!
-Hide somewhere.
-Why should I hide?
Jia Fei is here. Hide!
So what if she's here?
Please, just hide.
No. Jia Fei will definitely go
into the room.
Over here. Hide. Hurry up.
-Everyone knows we're engaged.
-Please, just hide.
Hurry up. Go.
Don't say anything. Please.
Coming.
What's going on?
Why did you change your passcode?
I forgot to tell you about that.
By the way,
was that your voice I just heard?
Yes. I was practicing my lines.
It's a new character.
Why would you do that?
Get me something to drink. I'm thirsty.
Okay. Wait a second.
Linlin.
-Are you out of drinks?
-I have some. I'm coming.
Here.
Why are you here?
I'm here to see Pidan.
Didn't you say Pidan is here?
I thought I would come to see him.
He's asleep now.
He has a bad temper.
He doesn't like to be woken up.
By the way,
how's it going with you and Mr. Ling?
Mr. Ling and I...
Who would that be?
No!
No matter who it is, I'm not here.
Ms. Xia, is Jia Fei here?
She said she...
Jia Fei is not here.
Are you looking for her?
No.
Mr. Ling said you're sick.
He had me bring you some medicine.
Do you need anything else?
No. I don't need anything at all.
I'm not sick. I don't need medicine.
Is there anything else?
Well,
it was pretty hot on the way here.
I think I have a heatstroke.
Could I have some water?
-Come in.
-Thank you.
-Please.
Have a seat.
Who could that be?
Chu Yan?
Hi, Xia Lin.
Xia Lin.
I saw that you weren't feeling well.
-What are you doing?
-I brought you some medicine.
Thank you.
What did you mean by your message?
It meant what it meant.
Why do you mean
by "let's stop seeing each other"?
Is Pidan here?
Pidan is asleep.
He has a bad temper.
He doesn't like being woken up.
Your phone is ringing.
I...
Okay.
It's all your fault. What should we do?
Get up.
Aren't you going to offer me a drink?
I'll get you a new one.
Wait a moment.
By the way, Xia Lin.
In episode 17,
I don't know what to do
with the crying scene.
Whatever you say.
You should do what you think.
Move. Out of the way.
I just don't know
if I should cry loudly or quietly.
I think both works.
You should do what you think.
So what if he sees me? We're engaged.
It's a contract engagement.
Don't do anything rash. Move.
-Move.
-I won't.
Xia Lin, what was that?
That was Pidan.
Pidan is awake.
Pidan is awake now.
Where is Pidan?
There.
Tell me. What's going on here?
-I'm here for Jia Fei.
-I'm here for Xia Lin.
He's here for water.
So you've been playing hide-and-seek here?
That's right.
Feifei, Wen Li, what's going on?
That's right, Wen Li.
Why didn't you tell me
that you know Ms. Jia?
I have a meeting to go to.
I'll get going now.
You guys have fun. Bye.
Boss.
It's late now. You must be tired.
You should get going.
It's not too late. I'm not tired.
-We have a lot to do.
-We'll talk next time. You should go.
Go.
Go home. It's late now.
Right, Yizhou.
I didn't drive today.
You should drive me.
Drive me home.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go.
We'll get going.
Wen Li.
Was I rude to Mumu?
Boss.
- I think--
-Never mind.
Why would I ask you?
You don't have a girlfriend.
I do good deeds all the time.
How could I be pregnant?
It should be...
Could it be...
Let me reward you then.
Subtitle translation by Sophia Zhang