LOCATION: SUWON, GYEONGGI-DO
TIME: 11 A.M.
-Hello, Netflix.
-Hello.
What's "dong" in English? Oh, "bronze."
-"Mi." Beauty.
-"Mi."
-Bronze and beauty.
-"Sae." Bird.
I'm Defconn,
the host of "Bronze Beauty Bird."
This is the Hip Newbie.
Hip, hip.
Nice to meet you, everyone.
How have you been, Netflix Club members?
The club that we'll be observing today
is a gathering of global friends
who met in Korea.
It's a friendship-making club
with foreigners.
-Hi!
-Hello!
-Oh, hi!
-Hi!
THE FOREIGN MEMBERS BASHFULLY GREET THEM
Nice to meet you.
Can you introduce yourselves?
-Your foreign crew.
-My foreign crew?
I'm the leader of Fake Buddies.
EDGAR / LEADER
This is our group. We hang out,
we meet both foreigners and Koreans,
and we just mingle together in Korea.
Please slowly, slowly.
NEWBIE WAS TOTALLY LOST
We're just a group that hangs out.
FAKE BUDDIES
SOCIAL CLUB WHERE YOU CAN MEET
PEOPLE OF VARIOUS NATIONALITIES
AND VISIT PLACES IN KOREA TOGETHER
Fake Buddies?
So, friends that aren't real?
We are not friends
when we meet for the first time.
We're on a journey to become real friends.
As we meet again and again,
we become real friends.
Okay. Translate for us. Go on.
…UHH…
GIGGLE
Oh, boy. I'm in trouble today.
Translate.
Leader,
can you speak Korean?
-Yeah, I can.
-Korean, please.
-You can speak Korean?
-I'm from Busan.
FELT A TWINGE OF BETRAYAL
Oh, sir.
MIN JI-HONG / BUSAN, KOREA
I'm Korean.
-What the heck?
-I'm pure Korean.
You're a native of Busan,
but you formed a group
consisting of foreigners.
How come?
I wanted to make some foreign friends.
Here comes his dialect.
I looked around various groups.
Those other groups were fun,
but they were mainly for language exchange
and just partying for the day.
I'd say, "See you next time."
-It didn't work out.
-I never saw them again.
SO HE MADE A CLUB
Can the members introduce themselves?
KIM / CHICAGO, USA
Michael Jordan!
-Chicago Bulls!
Six championship rings!
A JORDAN FANATIC
MEETS A CHICAGOAN
SHAI / ALABAMA, USA
AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEACHER
ZOE / AUSTRALIA
I'm a YouTuber!
HAPPY TO SEE HER
And…
Can I guess your name?
Antonio.
BASELESS GUESS OF HIS NAME
Your name is Antonio.
FRANK / NOT ANTONIO
FRANK / NEW JERSEY, USA
-New Jersey!
Oh, so hip!
What's your job?
MY ANTONIO IS ACTUALLY A DOCTOR
How long have you lived in Korea?
You like Korea so much
that you visit often?
THE AUSTRALIAN AGREES
THE AMERICAN AGREES
SO DOES THE KOREAN
HAIM / ISRAEL
Israel's "Wailing Wall."
You understand?
I know it because I live in Korea.
A lot of people told me,
"Hey, Wailing Wall."
A COMMON RESPONSE FROM KOREANS
My mom went to the Wailing Wall.
When her church people visited Israel,
they all went to the Wailing Wall.
HAIM HAS NO PROBLEM UNDERSTANDING
They're all like, "Father, Father!"
They go on a pilgrimage to Israel.
ANDREA / TRINIDAD AND TOBAGO
Caribbean?
GLAD TO HEAR A WORD THEY RECOGNIZE
JULIETTE / FRANCE
Bonjour.
-We've used up all the English we know.
-Okay.
Can you ask them why they came to Korea?
When I first came here…
CAN'T BELIEVE MY EARS
Can you speak Korean?
I'm sorry.
You speak so well.
I first came here to study,
but I loved Korea so much
that I came back.
-You sound like a baby.
-Doesn't she sound cute?
The teachers always say,
"You're so lovely, Shai!"
I love it.
You're so cute!
Thank you.
How old are you?
I was born in 1999.
SHAI AND SI-AN ARE THE SAME AGE
And the professor that I'm close with
gave me my Korean name.
-It's Kim Hye-seong.
-Hye-seong.
-Kim Hye-seong suits you so well.
-Like a shooting star.
Oh, my.
How long have you been learning Korean?
-It has been three years now.
-Three years?
-She speaks so well for three years.
-She does.
-We can't speak English well in that time.
-I know.
How was your English
while you were in school?
I almost used profanity just now.
CULTURE SHOCK
-I apologize.
-You spoke rough English.
-Yes, I did.
-You spoke rough.
You learn bad words first.
-That's how you learn English fast.
-That's true.
In my case…
ADVANCED LEVEL KOREAN SPEAKER
"In my case…"
You're Korean, aren't you?
In my case,
it's kind of a long story,
but I'll keep it short.
So fascinating.
I've been interested in Korea
since high school
because of its pop culture.
Especially BoA and Girls' Generation.
-I was of that generation.
-Girls' Generation.
At the time,
I realized that I just had to go to Korea.
-So it's because of BoA.
-That's right.
Thanks to BoA.
There are many like him.
-Many people come to Korea because of BTS.
-Right. K-pop.
Then, who is the life of the party
in this club?
-Right here.
-Yes.
-One, two, three.
THEY POINT TO FRANK
-Really?
-Frank.
How does he liven up the atmosphere?
-I dance.
-Dance?
THE DOCTOR WHO DANCES
-Then--
-Show us.
My butt
HE JUST GROOVED A LITTLE
BUT IT LIVENED UP THE GROUP
I go clubbing.
I like to go clubbing.
Which dance club do you go to, Frank?
-In Hongdae.
-Hongdae.
Hongdae. Yeah.
Doesn't Kim liven up the mood too?
When she drinks a bit of alcohol, yes.
He's right.
-I'm a boozehound.
-A boozehound?
How much do you drink?
Three or four?
-Soju?
-Yes.
Meat, soju, meat, soju, meat, soju.
WITH KOREA'S SOUL FOOD,
4 BOTTLES OF SOJU ARE EASY
-Meat, soju, meat, soju?
-Yes.
AFTER THAT IS THE CLUB
-To the club in Hongdae.
-Hongdae people.
-They're so excited about clubbing.
-They are.
THEY'RE BASICALLY "CLUB BUDDIES"
Ji-hong, what is our schedule for today?
-Today will be a K-culture day.
-Okay.
We'll tour the whole Suwon area.
-It's awesome here.
-Yes.
Let's go. Shall we follow his itinerary?
Isn't it so pretty?
There are places like this everywhere.
They made access points
around the fortress.
Raise your hand.
-Raise your hand.
-Ta-da.
RAISING THEIR HANDS HIGH
-You don't really have to do it.
-This is fun.
-How adorable.
-We're like kindergarten students.
-Si-an, are you going to a club in Suwon?
-I'm excited!
EXCITING "FAKE BUDDIES" PICNIC
Do you know any K-dramas?
-K-dramas?
-Yes.
-I've watched them.
Lovely Runner.
-Lovely Runner.
-Do you know Lovely Runner?
He said he liked her there!
-That's right! I know!
-You know that place?
-Do you like Byeon Woo-seok?
-Yes!
-Byeon Woo-seok!
-Me too!
-Lovely Runner.
-Yes, Lovely Runner.
There's a scene shot here.
Right. It's when he says he likes her.
-That's right.
-It's that place, isn't it?
Sol, I like you!
Sun-jae!
SUWON IS FAMOUS AS A FILMING LOCATION
-This is it.
-Is it Lovely Runner?
They sell Sun-jae and Sol's umbrella.
They sell Sol's umbrella.
Isn't it nice that you can
explore new places
-when you gather like this?
-Yes.
-Right.
We went to the Mud Festival too.
-In Boryeong?
-Yes, Boryeong.
You put mud on yourself?
-The Mud Festival is amazing.
-I want to join too.
Where was the best place you went to?
The place you really liked.
Wolmido.
-Wolmido?
-Wolmido!
The Disco Pang Pang tagada.
Did you like that a lot?
-It was really scary.
-Was it scary?
NEXT IS THE FRONT YARD OF A HANOK BUILDING
Are you all ready?
-They play ddakji in Squid Game.
-Yes.
Has anyone tried it?
MOST OF THEM HAVE TRIED IT
-Yes, I've tried it.
-Yes, I have.
-But I'm not good at it.
-I'm not good.
We're not good at it.
Let's compete in teams
and the losing team
must get a forehead flick.
Introduce your team, please.
Suwon's known for its wang galbi.
-Suwon Wang Galbi!
-Suwon Avengers!
I'm Tony Stark of Suwon Avengers.
WE CAN'T LET THEM BEAT US
What?
Let's do side dish names
for Suwon wang galbi.
I'm Kimchi of Wang Galbi!
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO BE?
Why kimchi?
Why is that the only thing
that came to mind?
Listen carefully.
First of all,
when you flip
all of your opponent's ddakjis,
-you win.
-Okay.
-Let's go, Hye-seong.
-Go, Hye-seong.
-Come on, Shai.
Hye-seong is fierce! She's our ace!
The new star Hye-seong
that appears like a shooting star.
-Go, Hye-seong.
-Hye-seong.
-Okay. Nice.
Good.
-You can get it.
-You got this!
You got this.
ANDREA CAME TO GET IT
Oh, no.
No, you can't do that.
Leave it.
HYE-SEONG IS SENSITIVE
ABOUT THE DDAKJI PLACEMENT
IT'S A CLEAN FLIP
SHE'S A HIDDEN MASTER
-Okay, good job.
-Well done.
Good job.
2 WIN IN A ROW, USING THE SAME TRICK
-She's good.
-She's a pro.
-She plays so well.
-She really plays well.
I need to go at this point.
I'll go.
-Tony Stark.
-Go, Tony Stark.
-You can do it.
-You got this.
TONY TO SAVE THE DAY
Tony.
You can't do it.
Tony can't do it.
BETTER PRONUNCIATION THAN USUAL
TONY CAN'T DO IT
I think she'll do it.
HER INTIMIDATING POWER
So close.
You're too good.
I tried this in the States.
-In the States?
-Yes.
At King Sejong Institute.
She tried this in the States.
She's a hustler.
They've all done it.
-All of you?
-Go for it.
Go for it?
-She must be confident.
-Go for it.
REGAINS HIS KOREAN PRIDE
DEFCONN BEATS THE FOREIGN ACE
You're out.
-Okay, I'll try.
-Host versus host.
KIMCHI'S HERE FOR REVENGE
Have a taste of Kimchi!
-Kimchi slap.
THESE FOREIGNERS EVEN KNOW
ABOUT THE KIMCHI SLAP
Uh, wait.
KIMCHI WASN'T SO SPICY AFTER ALL
It's okay.
-It's okay!
-It's okay.
Gosh, why is this so difficult?
SUWON WANG GALBI'S ZOE IS UP
Darn it!
Darn it?
-What?
-A foreigner just said…
What's going on?
Hang on. That foreigner just…
Didn't she say she was from Australia?
Do they say that over there too?
HYE-SEONG COACHES HER
1. CLOSE YOUR FINGERS
-Hye-seong, you're good.
-And get lower.
2. LOWER YOUR POSTURE
-She has a technique.
-She's the coach.
Hye-seong is better than me.
SADLY, SHE FAILED
Hey, meat and alcohol.
Meat and alcohol.
-You got this.
-Meat and alcohol.
HER TECHNIQUE WORKED
SUWON AVENGERS WIN THE DDAKJI MATCH
You're holding two of these, right?
The team that gets the most inside wins.
SUWON WANG GALBI
ATTEMPTS TO REGAIN THEIR GLORY
You've done this before.
SO CLOSE
HARD TO GET EVEN ONE IN
That was so close.
SUWON AVENGERS TRIES IT OUT AS WELL
Oh no.
The wind?
NEITHER ONE OF THE TEAMS HAS SUCCEEDED
Juliette, relax.
AWFULLY CLOSE
-Give it more speed.
-Yeah.
A little more speed.
SHE DID IT
SUWON AVENGERS WINS
Juliette! That was awesome!
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
GETTING READY
TO GET FLICKED
Game dummies.
THE DUMMIES THAT LOST TWICE
We can't end it like this.
Double or nothing.
No, one more game.
Then, pay for our meal.
Let's try jegichagi.
Okay. Let's do this.
Tell your teammates how to play jegichagi.
-Yes.
-Okay.
I have to teach my teammates?
-You…
-I have.
You have?
Teach us.
SHE SHAMELESSLY LETS HER BE THE COACH
I'm exhausted.
A SIMPLE AND CLEAR EXPLANATION
SHE PUTS IT INTO
PRACTICE IMMEDIATELY
-Hey.
-You're so good at it.
-That's right.
-You have to bounce it.
-Give it a bounce.
-She's right.
Here I go.
FRANK SILENTLY MAKES STRIDES
THEY FINALLY HAVE SOME HOPE
-We got this.
All right. Let's go, everybody.
SI-AN GOES FIRST
We can do it.
-Two.
SI-AN DOES 2
She did so well earlier.
EDGAR GOES NEXT
-Three.
-Three?
You have to do it now!
OKAY!
NUMBER 4 ZOE
Two. Two!
-Two!
-Come on. It's two.
DO I LET THEM HAVE IT?
Come on. It's two!
-She did two.
-You did well. Good!
Fine, okay.
You did well.
I thought I only did one.
-You did two.
-Really?
Okay. Juliette is up.
Juliette.
Relax.
-One.
-Hang on.
-Next.
-Slowly.
ANDREA GOT 1
-Okay. Two!
-Two.
THE CORNERED NEWBIE STEPS UP
SHOW US WHAT YOU GOT, TONY STARK
-Your shoes are a bit…
-My shoes are
-not good for this.
-They aren't.
What size do you wear?
-Your feet.
-My shoes? I'm 285 mm.
Come on.
Let me try on your sneakers.
CHANGING SHOES TO WIN
-The right shoe.
-Oh, the right one.
-Here.
-Hey, these shoes are nice.
-One, two, three, four,
-Two, three, four,
-five, six, seven,
-eight, nine.
NOW THAT'S OUR TEAM'S LEADER
NEWBIE GOT 9
That was really awesome.
THE SHOE WAS VERY EFFECTIVE!
-You're really good.
-I got it.
How many more do we need?
How many does
Frank have to do for you to win?
-Six.
FRANK NEEDS TO KICK IT
AT LEAST 6 TIMES
Frank is the best on our team.
You didn't know that, did you?
There's a reason why he wore those pants.
Those shoes are made for jegichagi.
It's as if the jegi is drawn to it.
There's a reason
why you put your hair up, Frank.
FRANK ONLY GOT 1
Weren't we on break?
THE RESULT IS HARD TO BELIEVE
SUWON AVENGERS WINS 3 OUT OF 3
It's time to flick your foreheads
and for you to treat us to a meal.
-All right.
-Very well.
Let me see whose forehead is good.
This one is perfect.
NEWBIE SEARCHES FOR HIS PREY
Should I put a dent in this? Should I?
Who wants to volunteer?
Who wants to experience it?
-Want me to flick your forehead?
-I'll go.
Frank? Why?
Why?
STANDING TALL
LOWER YOURSELF BY STICKING YOUR BUTT BACK
-Twerk.
-No twerking.
Stand.
WOBBLING
That sound…
Are you okay? Are you okay?
NOT OKAY
You know…
Oh, it turned red.
-It's red.
-It's red. Look.
It's red, isn't it? Yes.
I'm okay.
He has a red mark.
He's marked forever.
This is the Korean style
of flicking the forehead.
-It's party time.
FRANK WILL REMEMBER THIS
But I'm okay.
NEWBIE IN THE CLUB SCHEDULE
14:30 WRAP-UP GATHERING
You all like makgeolli, don't you?
-Yes.
-We love it.
Kimchi pancake, potato pancake,
spicy sea snails and noodles,
and tofu kimchi.
Napa cabbage.
Haim, you like makgeolli, don't you?
Do you shake it? How do you drink it?
Let me show you how I do it.
-First…
-He's going to show me?
LEARNING HOW TO DRINK
You go like this.
He learned the proper way.
Follow him.
THE KOREAN LEARNS
FROM THE ISRAELI
But be careful.
Shake it.
PLUS POINTERS FROM THE AMERICAN
-My favorite is Jipyeong Makgeolli.
-Jipyeong?
-My second favorite is Horanggi Makgeolli.
-Horanggi Makgeolli?
I don't even know those.
-Cheers.
When I say "This member,"
you say "Remember."
This member.
-Remember.
-Cheers.
-Yeah.
THEY ALL DRINK COMFORTABLY
BUT THE TWO AMERICANS DRINK
IN THE MOST POLITE WAY
-Wow!
-It's delicious.
-It's rich.
-Nice.
HYE-SEONG GOBBLES UP
HER PACKED CABBAGE BOSSAM
You eat so well. You're so cute.
Did you always like Korean food?
-Yes.
-I love it.
What's your favorite Korean dish?
Mine is bossam.
Bossam.
-Bossam?
-Bossam.
I love it so much.
-Have you been to Dongdaemun?
-Of course.
-It's so good.
-Isn't it? Your eyes got so big.
I tried beondegi there too.
-You know how to eat beondegi too?
-Yes.
Beondegi?
-What about you, Kim?
-I like dak-galbi.
-Dak-galbi.
Cheese dak-galbi.
-Cheese dak-galbi.
Pork belly or dak-galbi? One, two, three.
-Pork belly or dak-galbi?
-One, two, three.
-Pork belly.
-Soju, meat.
-Soju, meat, soju, meat.
-Soju and pork belly.
-Yes.
What surprised you the most
when you came to Korea?
-The hurry-hurry culture.
-Hurry-hurry?
When I order something from a restaurant,
-it comes out fast.
-Yes.
You eat fast and leave fast.
Yes, that's right.
Koreans eat
food that is still boiling hot.
-While it's still boiling?
-Right.
-Gukbap.
-They eat it immediately.
I always have to wait for 10 minutes.
-You wait until it cools down?
-Yes.
It's so hot that I can't eat it.
In Korea, you eat it
as soon as it arrives.
-That's right.
-You eat immediately.
KOREANS EVEN DRINK UP
THE LAVA-LIKE GUKBAP
-They eat it immediately.
-It's really a superpower.
When I go for dinner with my colleagues,
our vice principal would eat fast
and say, "We have to get going.
Shall we go to the second round?"
-So we had to go.
-Exactly.
First, second, third, fourth round.
-We don't have that abroad.
-That's right.
You don't?
We would eat in the first round.
Drink alcohol and something light
for the second round.
-Then, go home.
-That's right.
But here, you eat in the first round,
drink in the second round,
do noraebang in the third round,
and eat again in the fourth round.
-You keep going.
-You know it so well.
You're practically Korean.
Do you have any life hacks
that you picked up living here?
There aren't any subways in my country,
so I had to learn a lot.
-The subway?
-Yes.
If you really want to sit,
you have to stand in front of
an elderly person in hiking gear.
Then, when they get off
at Dobongsan Station
or Bukhansan Ui Station,
I can get a seat.
AN OBVIOUS DESTINATION
Since they get off at Bukhansan.
It's a good tip when you're over there.
That's a great tip.
-Kim's great tip is she really likes apps.
-Apps?
Naver Pay, Kakao Pay, Coupang Eats,
-Coupang, the Daiso app,
-Coupang is good.
the Olive Young app. All the apps.
Right? They're good.
-Coupang is the most important.
-I love Coupang so much.
She's the queen of Coupang.
Me too. I'm the queen of Coupang too.
It's so fast.
Do you use Naver Pay
at convenience stores?
Yes, I use the CU app.
Wow. I don't even use that one.
-Yes, the CU app.
-You have the CU app?
It's because you can save
on the two-plus-one deals.
-That's right.
You can manage your coupons.
She knows more than me.
-You know so much about it.
-Yes.
-There are some that I didn't know.
-Me neither.
The two plus one deals.
If you don't want to take
all of them in one day…
-There are rewards points.
-…you can save it for the next day.
Give me another one, please. Another tip.
-I'm the one who has to learn.
-Give me another tip, please.
Is there anything
that you want from Koreans?
-Something you felt while living here.
-Something you'd like them to do.
I'd like to talk to them,
but they'd avoid me
and say, "I don't speak English."
And on subways,
they wouldn't sit next to me.
-They're afraid to speak English.
-So I'd say,
"Please have a seat, ma'am."
-Then they sit?
-In Korean?
-They sit immediately.
-You see? That's how they are.
-I wish they'd feel comfortable around me.
-If they could be more at ease…
There's a Korean drinking game.
Do you know the APT game?
OF COURSE WE DO
The loser has to drink this up.
-Bottoms up.
-The loser has to chug it.
-Let's go.
-APT APT APT APT.
A A A, P P P.
NEWBIE FREESTYLES THE MELODY
23rd floor!
23RD FLOOR!
-Okay, let's go.
-23rd floor?
-Wait.
-First floor.
Second.
-Third.
-Fourth.
BUILDING A 23-STORY APARTMENT
-20th.
-Show us.
-21st. Sorry.
-21st.
-22nd.
23rd?
Zoe!
ZOE MUST DRINK THE PENALTY DRINK
Not me, not me.
-Zoe, Zoe, Zoe.
-Wait.
-Zoe, Zoe.
-I can only drink this much.
-I don't think she can do it.
I don't think she can do it,
so I'll do it for her.
-Really?
-Wow!
SHAI VOLUNTEERS TO TAKE THE SHOT
She knows how it's done.
Hye-seong is so cool.
Can you really do it?
I can drink five bottles of soju.
I'm fine.
EXPLODING WITH AWESOMENESS
That's right. She drinks
five bottles of soju. This is nothing.
Then, you have to grant her wish.
Tell us your wish.
Just be happy.
TOUCHED
Just buy a hamburger?
-Hamburger.
-Buy a hamburger.
-Be happy.
Live happily.
-Buy her five hamburgers.
-Got it.
-At any time.
-Five? Okay.
She agreed to the burgers.
Here I go.
TIME FOR SHAI TO DRINK THE PENALTY
-Shai! Shai!
SHE DRINKS INCREDIBLY FAST
SHE CHUGS IT IN ONE GO
Wow! You're amazing!
Your English skills are a secondary issue.
If you just want
to interact with foreign friends,
you'd enjoy this.
They always seem
to be willing to learn something new
and have an open mind.
They're so cool.
FAKE BUDDIES
SEOUL, GYEONGGI
1. DANCE IN THE CLUB
2. K-CULTURE LOVERS
3. REAL BUDDIES
LOOKING FOR NEW CLUBS
CONTACT US
FOR NEWBIE TO JOIN YOU
Subtitle translation by: Ilyoung Kim