''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Nature, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫  Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds, six paths, nine heavens; A promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness, I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE 33]
You won't do this without reason. I'm sure you have a favor to ask.
Tell me.
What's the relationship between King Bailing and God of War?
Are the tribulations of the God of War
somehow connected to her relationship with King Bailing?
Honestly, I don't believe it, either.
But everyone in the heavens believes so.
I have no choice but to believe it as well.
Her love turned into hatred?
I don't think she's a person like that.
Don't worry. King Bailing is only concerned about the three realms.
He won't snatch away your woman.
This is too hard. How do I solve this?
I can't solve it!
The hair didn't change at all.
Did I overthink?
Yu Sifeng wasn't a demon after all.
Maybe the demon in Qingmu Town
is connected to the demon in Mount Buzhou.
That demon has a malignant aura surrounding it.
It's not an ordinary demon.
Thank you, Sect Leader.
You wouldn't have been hurt if it weren't for Xuanji.
I should thank you instead.
You're too good
for Xuanji.
By the way, Sect Leader,
I just remembered that something fell out of the demon's body
when I fought him on Mount Buzhou.
The demon wanted to harm Xuanji and the rest.
But I don't know what exactly he was up to.
That's why I want to revisit the altar on Mount Buzhou.
Maybe I can find some clues.
You're injured now.
You shouldn't overexert yourself.
I think we should send our spirit beast, Hong Luan, to check it out.
You should go on a retreat and recuperate.
That's a good idea.
Sect Leader, sorry for the trouble.
[Shuoyang Hall]
Master!
- Master!  - What's wrong?
Why are you so anxious?
Some demons from Tianxu Hall are gathering at the base of our mountain!
And Sixth Junior is there as well.
What?
Don't worry.
Everyone will appreciate what you did in the future.
I don't know why,
but I feel uneasy.
I don't know what Wu Tong put inside this box.
We should be careful.
Master.
You scum!
How dare you come back!
- Master. Aunt...  - Shut up!
You traitor! You betrayed us and joined Tianxu Hall!
I don't have a disciple like you!
Minyan, how could you join the demons?
You better kowtow and apologize to your master right now!
Master. Aunt Yinghong.
I'm not here to beg for Master's forgiveness.
I'm here to represent Tianxu Hall today.
What did you say?
Say that again?
Master, please calm down.
Don't think that you don't need to worry about us
because you got back Linglong's primordial spirit.
Actually, you only got half of it back.
Half of it?
What do you mean? Explain yourself!
Linglong is still unconscious, right?
You should think of the reason why
and cooperate with our superintendent.
Only by doing so will you be able to save Linglong.
Sixth Junior, what do you mean by that?
- What do you mean by that?  - Explain yourself!
Everyone has their own ambitions.
Everyone, you all don't need to be angry.
How dare you say that?
You came to my sect when you were eight years old,
and I raised you until you became an adult.
But only now did I finally understand what your ambition was.
Fine. Hero Zhong, why are you here?
Do you want to threaten me with Linglong's primordial spirit again?
Hero Zhong, you better accomplish the mission our superintendent gave you!
Master,
our superintendent commanded me to send you a gift.
As the leader of the Five Great Sects,
we hope that you won't create trouble for us anymore.
And we'll reward you for your cooperation.
How could demons such as you order Shaoyang Sect around?
Min Jue?
- Second Senior!  - Senior!
- Min Jue!  - Senior!
You beast!
How dare you harm your fellow senior!
Master!
Minyan, are you okay?
Impossible!
Master, I didn't kill Second Senior!
You know I wouldn't do this!
I don't know why he's dead!
I thought he was still in the cell! How could this happen?
Master, you must believe in me!
I didn't expect myself
to raise an ingrate like you.
Today, I'll slay you for justice's sake!
We have no time for explanations! Let's go!
- Where are they?  - Where are they?
I didn't expect them to possess the Teleportation Charm.
- Minyan.  - Second Senior!
Minyan.
Why didn't you let
my master kill me?
Both of us know that Min Jue's death has nothing to do with you.
It's Wu Tong!
He killed Second Senior!
He did it on purpose!
- And I actually became his accomplice!  - Minyan!
- Minyan!  - He died because of me!
Second Senior is dead because of me!
I deserve to die!
Zhong Minyan,
you can kill yourself if you want to!
But what about Linglong?
Who will save her?
Who will retrieve her primordial spirit?
We still have many things we need to accomplish.
You need to pull yourself together.
We still have many tasks to complete.
If not, your second senior will have died in vain.
You mustn't spoil our plan because of your impatience.
Wu Tong,
I will seek my revenge.
You will pay for this!
You two have finally returned.
What will you cook today?
Hurry, I'm starving to death.
Food is the only thing that's on your mind.
It's a secret.
You two have finally returned. Something huge has happened.
We received a notice from Shaoyang Sect.
How could this happen?
Second Senior is dead? And Sixth Senior is the murderer?
Sixth Senior has been kicked out of Shaoyang Sect.
Impossible. I don't believe it.
Sixth Senior is a kind person.
He wouldn't resort to such despicable acts!
I'm sure there's something behind this.
The spirit beast of Sect Leader Chu sent us a letter.
Father said that Sixth Senior has joined Tianxu Hall.
He wants us to be careful,
and he wants us to return to the sect earlier.
He even said that...
He said we only brought
half of Linglong's primordial spirit back from Mount Buzhou.
And Linglong is still unconscious.
We were cheated by Wu Tong.
This Wu Tong...
In order to exchange for Linglong's primordial spirit,
five of us went into Mount Buzhou, yet only two of us came back.
Sixth Senior even joined Tianxu Hall because of this.
But in the end, we still couldn't retrieve Linglong's primordial spirit.
Although we didn't completely save Linglong,
she would've been dead without the primordial spirit you brought back.
Ting Nu, please make some Birth Candles for me.
I want to enter Mount Buzhou once again.
I want to save both Linglong and Sixth Senior.
It's not that easy to make Birth Candles.
We need rare ingredients to make them.
I'm afraid Dragon Scales are too hard to find.
What should we do then?
I...
Teng She.
Teng She, come here.
Aren't you a heavenly officer?
You can help me enter Mount Buzhou, right?
Please take me there, okay?
I can enter that place with no difficulty.
- Bring us there then.  - Sure.
Wait! We have a problem.
Now, I'm your spirit beast,
and you're a useless mortal.
Because of that, my powers are restricted and I can't enter Mount Buzhou.
You!
How about you chop off your arm?
I'll be free by then and I can help you enter Mount Buzhou.
Fine. You can chop off my arm
if it means that I can save Linglong and Sixth Senior.
Wait! I have an idea.
The pieces of primordial spirit can sense each other.
Teng She, you should be able
to bring back the rest by using the primordial spirit residing in Linglong's body.
You know quite a lot.
But only I, the great heavenly officer,
am capable of powerful feats as such.
This is great. Let's return to Shaoyang Sect immediately.
Okay. Let's go.
What's for dinner tonight?
Here.
Fill my cup.
My Lord,
we've sent your gift to Shaoyang Sect.
What?
It's such a big gift.
Didn't your master ask you to stay for dinner?
Oh, I almost forgot.
You've been kicked out of Shaoyang Sect.
Now, everyone knows that you belong to Tianxu Hall now.
You will never be able to return to Shaoyang Sect.
Reward him with some wine!
After you drink this,
you should just work for me with all your heart.
Naturally, I won't treat you badly.
Minyan!
Wu Tong!
What? You can't continue your act anymore?
You're far worse at acting than me.
In the past, when I worked for our leader,
I always followed his every order and acted obediently.
I would never let him notice that it was all an act.
But you?
Why?
What do you mean?
Why did you kill Second Senior?
He's no threat.
And he has never offended you!
I didn't kill your second senior.
Don't stare at me like that.
My beloved Linglong
was the one behind your second senior's death.
Me?
Did you forget?
You gave Chen Min Jue the poisonous glutinous rice cake
yourself last night.
Why are you staring at Linglong like that?
Are you perplexed? Are you raging inside?
Or are you wondering why your beloved Linglong became like this?
You don't even understand her well.
You don't even know what her favorite food is.
Come, let me help you out.
Someone!
Give Minyan your favorite glutinous rice cake.
Go.
Brother Wu Tong, why don't we just forget it?
I'll treat glutinous rice cake as my favorite food, okay?
Are you trying to disobey me?
North Superintendent, although Minyan committed mistakes,
he doesn't deserve to die.
North Superintendent, please give him another chance.
Brother Wu Tong.
Zhong Minyan, you're getting more stupid.
Do you think I will poison you?
I don't want my audience to die on me, you know?
But you better listen up.
I hate it when people touch my stuff.
You better not come up with tricks under my watch!
Linglong is mine.
If you do something you shouldn't, I'll send Shaoyang Sect more gifts.
By then, it'll be more than just Chen Min Jue.
Come, let's go.
Stinky woman, I'm the best heavenly officer there is.
How dare you make me do such cowardly things?
We still need to save Sixth Senior after we retrieve Linglong's spirit.
If my father knows about this, he won't let us leave Shaoyang Sect.
We can only use this path. Hurry!
Zhong Minyan, accompany me to the gate of Fenru City.
I'll visit Shen Shu and Yu Lu.
I'm talking to you. Why aren't you responding?
I know.
You're angry at me because of your senior's death.
But you can't blame me for this.
I didn't know that glutinous rice cake was poisonous.
Just forget it. It's only one death.
There are so many disciples in Shaoyang Sect.
I'll capture another guy and let him accompany you, okay?
Scram.
Zhong Minyan, you better know what's good for you.
No one has ever spoken to me, Linglong, in that tone.
Don't call yourself Linglong in front of me!
You're not Linglong!
You don't even deserve to mention her name!
Stop!
Explain yourself then!
What do you mean by I'm not Linglong?
All of you told me the same thing!
Although I don't understand your words, I'm not stupid!
That person you spoke of, how is she connected with me?
So what if we look exactly the same? Why am I inferior compared to her?
Fine.
Since you want me to speak,
I'll tell you everything.
There's only one Linglong in this world.
And that Linglong is in the Shaoyang Sect.
It's more than a coincidence that you look exactly the same as her.
Wu Tong made you because he couldn't obtain her.
Wu Tong stole Linglong's primordial spirit.
He extracted half of your primordial spirit
and insert half of Linglong's primordial spirit into your body.
He made you his puppet.
And you will only adopt an appearance
and a personality that suits his liking!
You're wearing red because that's Linglong's favorite color.
Wu Tong is treating you well
only because he wanted the real Linglong.
You're not a flower demon, and you're not Linglong, either.
You're just a monster that resembles no one!
One's heart is the hardest to imitate.
You only have Linglong's appearance
and her demeanor.
But you're not her!
No matter how willful the real Linglong is,
she always has a kind heart.
A person like you, who aids evil, will never become her!
Impossible.
Everything you said was a lie.
They're not real! I'm the real Linglong!
You're lying to me!
Am I lying to you?
If so, why did you cry when I was hurt?
Why did you space out when you saw my dagger?
Why do you feel familiar with every word you said to me?
Am I lying to you?
Or is it because the Linglong inside of you is trying to remember me?
Tell me!
Fine!
All of you are up to no good!
I'll ask Brother Wu Tong to kill you right away!
Fine.
Go now.
Ask him to kill me right now.
This is better.
You don't need to find out the truth.
Just do your part and be his puppet.
And lose your own identity in the process.
Scram!
Here.
This is the place where I first grew up and cultivated.
I saved you because you were destined to be mine.
I have a name for you, as well. You will be Linglong.
What are you doing? Let me go!
- It's not there.  - She's not Linglong.
How is it?
The clone looks exactly like her, doesn't it?
Even you don't know who the real Linglong is, right?
You're wearing red because red is Linglong's favorite color.
Wu Tong treats you well because he wants the real Linglong!
I remember now.
Yellow is my favorite color.
Yellow is my original color.
Everything here was familiar to me.
But now,
it feels like I'm in unfamiliar territory.
Don't tell me it's because
I'm not the original me anymore?
What if Brother Tong doesn't like this?
I'll just change it back.
Brother Wu Tong.
Brother Wu Tong, what's on your mind?
Our leader asked me to prepare some troops for him.
Tianxu Hall will hold a major operation soon.
I was wondering if I should help him.
What's wrong? Do you need anything?
Look.
When did you change your clothes?
Do you like it?
If you don't like it, I can change it back.
As long as you like it.
Really? So, are you saying that I can wear anything that I like?
Brother Wu Tong, are you saying that I can choose my own appearance?
As long as you're happy.
- I...  - Linglong...
I'm busy now.
Go out and play.
Second Senior, I still owe you a drink.
We were going to finish this wine and listen to your story together,
but I didn't expect you to leave us just like that.
Minyan, you traitor.
I will definitely capture you
and make you confess in front of Second Senior.
But I still don't believe that Minyan is behind this.
First Senior, you're still defending him even now?
You saw Second Senior's body when they sent him back, right?
If Minyan joined Tianxu Hall because he didn't have a choice,
he should've returned to us when Tianxu Hall asked him to come here!
I think this is a huge blow to Master.
We should go and visit him.
Sorry, Second Senior. It's all my fault.
I didn't manage to save you.
They should've taken me instead of you while we were there.
Xuanji, I know it's boring to stay here and recuperate.
That's why I brought you something.
Second Junior, you're willing to give Xuanji your favorite treasure?
My junior is so chivalrous.
I should reward her for that.
Don't worry.
I will find out the truth and avenge you.
Linglong!
Linlong, we've found a way to save you.
When you get better, we'll find Sixth Senior together.
Please wait a little longer.
Teng She, come and examine Linglong's condition.
I'll make you some Snowflake Beef.
I just need to resummon the other half of her primordial spirit, right?
No problem. Just watch.
What's going on?
Again.
You!
Someone kept boasting that he's a heavenly officer.
I think your powers are weaker than your boasting skill.
- Stupid rat snake, shut up!  - You're a snake as well!
Wait! Logically, her primordial spirit will return to her
if I try to summon it, no matter how far away it is.
Unless...
Unless what?
Unless her primordial spirit is trapped within another body.
It'll be troublesome if that's the case.
Let me see what's going on by examining her primordial spirit.
Brother Wu Tong told me that I'm not a puppet.
Brother Wu Tong likes me for who I am.
He said I can do whatever I want to.
I'm too lazy to bother with you.
It's Sixth Senior.
What's wrong?
Sixth Senior.
I heard his voice!
Sixth Senior, I'm Xuanji.
What did you call me?
I can hear you.
Sixth Senior, I'm Xuanji.
Xuanji? What's going on?
We tried to resummon Linglong's primordial spirit,
but we heard your voice instead.
Where's the other half of her primordial spirit?
It's inside the flower demon who looks exactly like her.
It's no wonder Wu Tong treasures her so much.
Sixth Senior, did you stay in Tianxu Hall
in order to find the other half of her primordial spirit?
I don't believe that you're joining them of your own accord.
And I don't believe that you killed Second Senior.
Since it has come to this,
Xuanji, you're the only person who still believes in me.
I will find a way and retrieve the remaining half of her primordial spirit.
And I'll apologize to Master.
Dumb mortal, do you think you can retrieve it without any problem?
You need the Soul Bell, you know?
Soul Bell?
Since Wu Tong can steal Linglong's primordial spirit,
it means that he has the Soul Bell.
Minyan, try to steal the Soul Bell from him.
We'll meet up in Mount Buzhou.
So what if you manage to steal it? You need to know how to use it.
Teng She, stop beating around the bush.
Just tell us if you have the solution.
I'll make you sweet and sour fish as well.
Kid, turn around.
- What is this?  - The Sun Moon Charm.
After I draw that, I can detect you within a proximity of 2.5 km.
We can't just bring her wherever we go, right?
As long as you're able to steal the Soul Bell,
I can retrieve the other half of her primordial soul outside of Mount Buzhou.
We should act in haste. Let's go to Mount Buzhou now.
Sixth Senior, please be careful.
Okay.
What happened just now?
Nothing.
Wait! I felt like I was trying to say something.
Oh right! Didn't you let me use a mirror
that could show me my past lives?
Can you show it to me again?
Only half of it went inside?
It's hard indeed using another body.
So, this wasn't my true look after all.
You saw everything? You know what's going on now?
Brother Wu Tong replaced half of my primordial spirit with Linglong's.
And my primordial spirit was left at the place I trained at.
Where's the place?
It's at...
Give it to me!
It's no use even if you take it back.
But we can help you.
Help me? Do you think I don't know what you are plotting?
You just wanted Linglong's primordial spirit, right?
- I won't fall for it.  - Yes.
We're trying to retrieve her primordial spirit.
But don't you want to be yourself?
It's a win-win situation. So, why not?
Are you afraid that Wu Tong won't like you
if you return to your past self?
It's not that!
Brother Wu Tong likes me. Not that Linglong.
Fine, I'll do it then.
I'll prove to you that Brother Wu Tong likes me.
And I'm not a replacement of that Linglong.
Fine. But now, we lack something that could extract one's primordial spirit.
We need Wu Tong's Soul Bell.
I saw that bell before.
But Brother Wu Tong doesn't allow me to touch it.
Will you return my primordial spirit if I steal the bell for you?
Yes.
Fine. I'll steal the bell,
but you must keep your promise.
- It's a deal then.  - See you in three days.
And we'll help the primordial spirits to return to their bodies.
Okay.
Hurry!
Xuanji!
Sixth Senior, we're outside of Mount Buzhou now.
How's your progress?
Everything is going well. Wu Tong will go on a retreat tomorrow.
That flower demon promised us that she'll steal the bell for us.
And she'll help us in retrieving Linglong's primordial spirit.
Minyan, once you acquire her spirit, try to find a way out.
We'll meet you at the altar outside.
Okay. Wait for my good news.
Brother Wu Tong,
I can't bear to part with you.
You're missing me already?
It's only for one day. I'll be back soon.
The back of the mountain is cold. This shirt is too thin for you.
You should change your shirt.
It's fine. I won't be cold.
I'll be angry if you catch a cold.
Look at your temper.
You're angry over this?
Fine. I'll listen to you.
How is it?
Are you happy now? Is it thick enough?
Much better.
I'll leave now.
Here.
The Soul Bell. I've finally obtained it.
Brother Wu Tong will return tonight.
You better be quick if you want to escape.
Okay. We'll start now.
They're here.
Teng She, we have the Soul Bell.
What should we do now?
Teng She.
Xuanji.
Hurry up!
Wait.
Wait! Didn't you say you would return me my primordial spirit?
What should I do now?
Don't rush me! We'll do it one by one!
I need to extract the primordial spirit in your current body.
Don't worry. I'll keep my word.
I know. Actually, you're not evil.
You should leave Tianxu Hall
after you retrieve your own primordial spirit.
It's hard for you to acquire a human form.
Find a peaceful place and find a person who truly loves you.
Don't be too full of yourself.
I did all this because of Brother Tong.
After you retrieve Linglong's primordial spirit,
we will be unrelated.
None of you can tell me what to do.
Are you done or not?
I'm going to cast my spell now.
Kid, stand beside that demon.
Okay.
Spirit Transfer!
Linglong, I can finally bring you home.
Minyan, you mustn't delay this any longer.
Her primordial spirit needs to return to her body immediately.
Okay.
What about her?
Stupid.
Just do the same thing I did just now.
Use the Five Elements Spell and find the correct position.
The flower demon's element is wood. Use water element for the spell.
When her primordial spirit returns to her body, she'll become her original self.
Do what you did?
Teng She, I don't understand at all.
Why don't you do it again?
Teng She?
- It's cut off?  - Cut off?
Teng She, can you try to detect them again?
I don't know what's going on. Maybe the charm fell off.
Anyway, I've given him the instructions. It's an easy task.
Let's just wait here.
Teng She?
Teng She? This is bad.
How did the charm disappear?
- I can't remember the things he taught me.  - It's fine.
It's fine. I remember them.
Ruo Yu, it's lucky that I have you.
Let's return her primordial spirit to her body now.
Wait! We need to let her do something for us.
What are you doing?
Her primordial spirit is not in her body.
I can use the Jade Flute to hypnotize her and steal the spirit keys.
Did you plan for that long ago?
Now that Wu Tong isn't here, no one will be able to stop Linglong.
This is a rare chance.
You're using her!
This is our reward for retrieving her primordial spirit.
We can ask for her help if we want the spirit keys.
We mustn't use her to our own advantage!
A gentleman wouldn't do this.
A gentleman?
You severed one of your senior's arms in order to join Tianxu Hall.
Is that what a gentleman would do?
Minyan, did you forget what your master told you?
You can do everything it takes to retrieve the spirit keys.
Besides, the flower demon won't be in danger.
We've sacrificed so much for this.
If we don't retrieve the spirit keys, your second senior will have died in vain.
Miss Linglong,
this is forbidden ground. So...
We mustn't mess with Miss Linglong. We'll die if she gets angry.
Miss Linglong, please.
- She did retrieve them for us.  - What is this?
This...
This is the Flying Dragon Seal, a treasure of Lize Palace.
I'm sure the spy stole this together with the spirit key.
I can take this back as well.
But why is there only one spirit key?
The spirit keys of Fuyu Island and Xuanyuan Sect were stolen as well.
There should be three spirit keys here.
Don't tell me they hid the other two keys in a different place?
It's our miscalculation, but now we've alerted them.
Let's leave first.
Okay. Return her primordial spirit to her body.
- We'll leave after that.  - Okay.
- Who's there?  - Let's go!
Let's go!
Where is Sixth Senior?
Let's check it out.
Everyone, listen up! I'm sure they're still around!
- Hurry!  - Go!
I'll distract them. You leave first.
Ruo Yu, we'll leave together!
- Xuanji and the rest are at the altar.  - There are too many enemies.
If this continues, both of us will die.
I'll wait for you in Qingmu Town.
Ruo Yu!
Sixth Senior!
- Sixth Senior!  - Xuanji! Sifeng!
Go and save Ruo Yu!
Ruo Yu?
Teng She, go and save Ruo Yu.
We'll escape with Minyan for now.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫