''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Destiny, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫ Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds; Six paths, nine heavens, a promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness, I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE 17]
Please come in.
Hero Yu, Madam needs to see you.
Please proceed to her chamber.
Now?
Yes.
Madam is sincere about this.
She said she needs to discuss something with you.
Okay.
Please.
A true gentleman always strives to improve his knowledge
and his moral standards.
With a solemn posture and a generous heart,
it shows his high rank.
A true gentleman will never be forgotten.
Madam, Hero Yu is here.
You may go now.
Yes.
Greetings, Madam.
I wonder what the matter is?
Was my song beautiful?
Why are you staring at the ground?
Everyone said that I'm the most beautiful woman in the world.
Look. The flower and I, which one of us is more beautiful?
This scent...
It's the Serpent Perfume of the Zitong Cult.
What cult?
I don't know anything.
Madam, where did you get this?
Do you want to know?
You must promise me one thing then.
The wine that you brought has a potent aftertaste.
But I can't manage to recreate the same taste no matter what I do.
Can you tell me the secret behind that?
- Let me go!  - Qing Rong!
- Qing Qi!  - Qing Rong! What happened?
Qing Qi, you came just in time.
I originally wanted him to teach me how to brew wine,
but he was trying to violate me.
Kill him for me.
If not, I'll be too ashamed to live in the world.
Madam, you're framing me.
You animal! How dare you try to violate my wife!
My Lord, I will never do such an outrageous act.
I saw it for myself! How dare you deny it!
Prepare yourself!
Uncle Dong Fang, what are you trying to do?
He tried to violate my wife! I'll kill him no matter what!
That's impossible! Sifeng wouldn't do that!
Don't try to find excuses for him!
Qing Rong is gorgeous.
Every one of them has been eyeing her.
He was staring at Qing Rong during the feast.
I knew he was eyeing her,
but I didn't expect him to commit such an audacious act!
- Uncle Dong Fang, calm down!  - My Lord.
I'm not willing to argue.
Please think about this in a calm manner.
Many disciples of yours were chased out because they disrespected Madam.
Who do you think is the problem here?
My Lord, you are always upright and honest.
But why are you so muddle-headed and letting someone to manipulate you
when it comes to this?
- Qing Rong.  - You believe in him instead of me?
- No!  - You're useless to me.
- Never find me again.  - Qing Rong!
All of you, scram!
Qing Rong, wait for me!
How did this happen?
Sifeng, I'll dress your wound.
- I'm fine.  - Let's go.
Does it hurt?
You would've been framed if I didn't pass by.
Madam Dong Fang is really something.
Why was she acting like that?
You never saw what happened,
yet you said I was framed?
Do you believe in me that much?
Of course! I know your character the best.
Even if Madam Dong Fang is really gorgeous
and you do have feelings for her,
you'd handle it accordingly.
You wouldn't commit such an audacious act.
Have feelings for her?
Chu Xuanji, it's meaningless to me
no matter how beautiful other women are.
Don't you understand?
Is it because disciples from Lize Palace cannot marry?
You still don't understand?
You removed my mask.
From now on, I don't need to wear any mask anymore.
I've broken the rules.
That means I've forsaken Lize Palace.
So, it's okay for me to marry someone.
But you said Lize Palace wanted to disown you
because you broke the rules.
You should return to Mount Shaoyang with me.
Why can't you understand what I'm trying to say?
If I do return to Mount Shaoyang with you, what identity will I hold?
You'll be my friend!
Since young, my father told me that
we must help our friends out as much as possible.
So, he'll let you stay there.
Wrong.
We'll be peers then.
You're still wrong.
I'm still wrong?
What is it then?
I know now.
You'll join the Shaoyang Sect
and become one of us.
As long as you join our sect, you can stay with us officially.
But you'll become my junior if you do so.
Clearly, she doesn't understand what a relationship is.
But why was she the only person who could remove my mask?
Never mind. Let's get down to business.
Sit down.
Xuanji, seems like we need to stay here for some days.
We need to solve Master Dong Fang's problem.
After that, we can find Minyan and Linglong.
Because Master Dong Fang has been bewitched by his wife.
So, it's true that Uncle Dong Fang was bewitched?
Yes.
During tonight's feast,
I gave Master Dong Fang the antidote with the Tasteless Wine.
Xuanji, your family is close to Master Dong Fang.
Have you ever heard of news regarding his wife?
I remember that when I was young, my father told me that
there was a cult on Mount Zitong.
They always captured young women in order to brew their concoctions.
That time, Uncle Dong Fang went to destroy the cult
and he saved the only surviving girl in the cave.
He brought her back and made her his wife.
If they captured young women,
it's impossible for the cult to leave them alive.
How could a young and weak woman manage to survive the ordeal?
You're saying that...
Madam Dong Fang belongs to the cult.
If not, how would she know how to use the Gu Poison of a cult?
When someone is bewitched, they'll become hot-tempered.
Such impudence! I have the same rank as your father!
How dare you disobey me!
Why is the wine tasteless?
In the end, they'll lose all control and they'll be manipulated.
The condition will become worse during a full moon night.
In the end, if Madam casts the last spell,
Master Dong Fang will become her puppet.
Fuyu Island is in danger.
When will the next full moon appear?
- The day after tomorrow.  - The day after tomorrow?
You're finally willing to see me.
Why are you only willing to meet me
during a full moon night?
Listen, you mustn't drink with someone else next time.
Tell me if you want to drink.
I can accompany you.
I can drink with anyone I wish.
If you're not willing to accompany me, I can leave right now.
Wait! Qing Rong, don't joke around.
Why would I do so?
I'll be very happy whenever you want to see me.
Stop acting like this, okay?
I've prepared some wine for you.
Come, drink it.
Thank you.
Let me play a song for you.
- You can skip the song.  - No.
I feel like playing it right now.
I didn't know you were into playing songs.
There are many things that you do not know about me.
That's right.
We've been a couple for so many years,
yet you still remain mysterious.
I first met you in that cave.
After one glance,
I knew I couldn't forget you.
From that day onward,
I swore to the heavens.
You'll be my most precious in the world.
What a joke.
I almost gave up on becoming a cultivator.
Even becoming an immortal can't compare to the times when we're together.
I really think that
I'm the happiest man in the world.
Because I got to be together with you.
What about you? Qing Rong?
We have been married for more than a decade.
How I wish you wouldn't play your song tonight.
So, you knew everything.
Uncle Dong Fang was so kind towards you.
Why are you trying to harm him?
Tell me.
Tell me why you're doing this.
If I'm not mistaken, you weren't captured by the cult,
you're the leader of the cult.
After your cult was destroyed, you had no way to escape.
That's why you pretended to be pitiful in order to save yourself.
Master Dong Fang is intelligent.
Maybe he knew the truth all along
but he still tolerated you.
Why are you trying to harm him?
Qing Rong, I've put down the past.
Why can't you just forget about the past?
What a joke!
You eliminated my entire cult.
How could I forget that?
And you all.
Your so-called righteous sects have slain many people as well!
Why can't we do the same thing when you are doing it?
You are just bullying the weak by using righteousness as an excuse!
Not only that,
you even locked me up on this island.
I can't go anywhere.
You treat me as your pet
and you want me to feel grateful for that?
I wanted you to know
what it felt like to have a fate worse than death.
It's a pity that you discovered my plot.
But it's fine.
I've had enough of living like this.
You can do anything you want.
Master, let me kill her on your behalf
in order to appease your hatred.
Just let her go.
Qing Rong, no matter if you believe it or not,
I've been keeping you on Fuyu Island in order to protect you.
I didn't expect you to misunderstand me this badly.
Just leave.
I've lost today.
You can take my life.
Qing Rong, what are you doing?
You asked me to leave?
I'm homeless now.
Where else can I go?
It's better if you kill me.
Qing Rong, of course, I'm not willing to let you leave.
But you're suffering here,
so how could I force you to stay by my side?
Actually, I'm just worried that
you only care for my appearance.
I'm afraid that one day when I grow ugly and old,
you'll be reminded of my true identity.
Don't you understand my love for you?
Even if you want me to die, you can just tell me to do so.
I'm willing to die for you.
I don't want you to die.
Do you believe this?
I'll give you the antidote even if they're not around.
Of course, I do.
Qing Rong, I know you still love me. Am I right?
Of course.
I have your child.
How could I bear to kill the father of our child?
- Are you speaking the truth?  - Yes.
I always thought you didn't like children?
Silly boy.
Qing Rong.
I don't wish to see them.
I only want to be with you alone.
Okay. All of you, leave.
Come.
But...
Everyone, I hope you can keep that a secret.
Uncle Dong Fang, I...
I've gotten to the bottom of this.
My wife was just pranking me.
It's not a good thing if people know about this.
Hero Yu, it was a misunderstanding.
Here, I'll apologize to you on behalf of my wife.
Master, Madam almost killed you.
Are you really going to let her off?
I've taken the antidote. I'm fine now.
She's very pitiful as well.
Moreover, a couple shouldn't have any overnight feuds.
You will understand this soon.
You two, just treat it as if you two haven't been here.
Master Dong Fang, don't worry.
We won't tell anyone.
Thank you.
Master Dong Fang is still very confused.
Tomorrow, when he feels better,
we'll ask for permission to leave the island.
We'll find Minyan and Linglong after that, okay?
But do you think Madam was really pranking him?
- I don't think she's pranking him.  - You don't know anything,
yet you're not as ignorant as I think.
I don't understand what she's trying to do.
Does she love or hate Uncle Dong Fang?
She wants him to live, yet she wants him to die.
Uncle Dong Fang is pretty weird as well.
He wants her to leave, yet he wants her to come back.
A relationship is between two persons.
It's hard for outsiders to understand what's going on.
If you get into a relationship, you'll experience both good and bad.
Sometimes, it's sweet. Sometimes, it's bitter.
It's unpredictable.
I think Uncle Dong Fang is quite pitiful.
Madam Dong Fang is evil,
but he's still trying to protect her.
Even the kindest person will be disliked by someone.
Even the evilest person will be loved by someone.
As long as they're willing, they won't think they're pitiful.
Instead, they'll feel satisfied.
Anything that has to do with feelings is difficult.
It's more difficult than my training.
I don't want to encounter something as troublesome as that.
Sifeng?
Sifeng, why are you standing here?
I was thinking that the night scenery is beautiful.
I heard that Master Dong Fang has hidden some top-grade Flower Wine.
Why don't we steal some of them?
Steal? It's not good to steal.
But why not?
We did him a huge favor.
Stealing some wine isn't a big deal.
- You have a point. Let's go.  - Let's go.
What a pity.
Dong Fang Qing Qi almost became my puppet,
but the two rascals spoiled my plan.
That Yu Sifeng, he was actually unfazed by my beauty.
And I didn't expect him
to recognize my bewitching spell.
We don't have much time.
I can only think of other ways.
Don't tell me you're going to leave?
You promised me that you'd leave with me.
And that,
you'll leave with our child, too.
So many flower petals!
They're so beautiful!
Xuanji.
Sifeng!
This vat of wine smells the best.
[Pure Flower Dew Wine]
It's so fragrant!
This is Pure Flower Dew Wine.
We must let it settle down before we drink.
Sifeng, I knew you were the best.
You can overcome any obstacles in the world.
Actually, there is one thing I cannot overcome.
Are you willing to help me out?
Your affairs are my affairs.
Tell me. How can I help you?
The thing that's been troubling me
is hidden within the bottom of this wine jar.
You'll see it after we finish the wine.
I heard that the sea view on Fuyu Island is great.
Why don't we enjoy some wine by the sea?
Sure. Let's go.
Yu Ning? Pian Pian?
How could the two of you do this?
That's the only jar of Pure Flower Dew Wine.
And you got to it first.
How about we share the wine?
Sure. Sifeng, we won't drink it by the sea then.
Let's drink it in the wine cellar.
We came without notice. Are we interrupting you guys?
Of course.
Not at all. The more, the merrier.
Sifeng, let's go.
It's meaningless if we drink it like this.
Why don't we play Rock-Paper-Scissors?
What do you think?
Sure. But we need to lay down the rules.
Those who win can take one sip.
Those who lose can only stare in silence.
I'll definitely take the first sip.
Me first.
Sifeng won.
Sifeng, that's enough!
You're more of an alcoholic than me.
You finished half of the wine in one sip.
- Who's next?  - Me.
Sifeng won again.
You!
Take it easy.
Although the Pure Flower Dew Wine is sweet when you drink it,
it has a huge kick.
You're something. There's only a little bit left.
I'll play with Xuanji next.
Sure.
I won!
You won.
It's mine now.
You drink it.
Oh no, the words have become solid inside the wine jar.
They can't be removed.
[You don't know that I fancy you.]
But I won the match.
That wine is mine.
The moonlight is intoxicating indeed.
I can't drink this.
There's a heart inside. Look.
It's true.
There's a heart indeed.
Xuanji, look.
There's nothing inside though.
I don't see anything.
Let's go. We didn't manage to drink.
I'm tired now. Let's go.
Let's go.
Why are you leaving?
Sifeng, why are they leaving?
It's good that they're gone.
Troublemakers.
Sifeng, are you drunk?
I'm not drunk.
You're the one who's drunk.
Me? I haven't had one sip.
It's all because of you.
Dumb Xuanji.
Okay, I'm dumb.
You're drunk. We should return early.
Come.
You're not allowed to go.
My problem hasn't been solved yet.
What problem?
You are my problem.
Xuanji, you always ignore everything
and try to drill yourself into my heart.
You make me feel uneasy.
And I always dream about you.
Tell me. What should be your punishment?
You feel uneasy?
And you always dream about me?
Sifeng, I haven't seen you for four years.
I always dreamed about you, too.
Does this frustrate you?
You feel that way as well?
You don't need to answer me yet.
Listen to my heart.
You can answer after that.
Why is his heart beating so fast?
Don't tell me he's sick?
This...
Sifeng, why is your heart beating so fast?
Are you sick?
Let's find a physician.
There's a window on top. We can exit from there.
♫  Throw away the paper parasol, the pain of yearning, when it was just a dream  ♫
♫  Continue this journey to tell you slowly  ♫
♫  Who can be fine after groveling so many times?  ♫
♫  Heaven has also struggled over it, ♫
♫  causing all beings to suffer along, too  ♫
♫  I thought I could pretend, pretend not to love you ♫
♫  Because I thought I didn't want, want to hurt  ♫
♫  Yet the passing years were so turbulent,  ♫
♫  things change with every passing second  ♫
♫  Every single drop of yearning I feel is clear  ♫
♫  Who cares how absurd it is?  ♫
♫  As the autumn winds blow, see that the geese have embarked on their journey  ♫
♫  It's only a step away  ♫
♫  Even if love is an abyss I will still jump into it  ♫
Sifeng.
Sifeng, why are you ignoring me?
Speak to me.
What are you doing?
Xuanji, you should know that
you have to be responsible for me once you removed my mask.`
I removed your mask. Of course, I need to be responsible for you.
Is that so?
♫  It's only a step away, even if love is an abyss,  I will still jump into it  ♫
It's too fragrant.
Sifeng, this...
What's wrong with you?
The flowers are too fragrant.
They're irritating my nose.
Smell this.
Smell this. Isn't it fragrant?
- Am I right?  - It's pretty fragrant.
Stop fooling around!
You're bad!
Chu Xuanji, do you know what this is?
Sifeng, you drank too much.
This is Fuyu Island's Love Stone.
It fell from the heavenly realm a few hundred years ago.
As stated in the books,
if two people, who are fated to be together, approach this stone,
the stone will glow.
What has it got to do with us?
I want to try this with you.
It's fake. Stupid rock.
I'm going to smash it.
Sifeng, don't do that!
This belongs to Fuyu Island. We shouldn't touch it.
Just ignore the stupid rock. It'll be bad if someone saw you.
Hurry, let's return.
Let's go.
Sifeng.
Sifeng, you're awake?
Here's some hangover soup. You should drink it.
I'll drink it by myself.
It's fine.
What sound is that?
I think someone came to the island.
Is it Linglong and Sixth Senior? Let's have a look.
Deputy Chief?
What a coincidence.
Greetings, Deputy Chief.
What did I say before you left?
Our master has such high expectations for you.
But the mask couldn't hold you down.
You found a way to remove the mask.
The little girl is all grown up now.
I almost couldn't recognize you.
You're so lucky.
Did she remove the mask for you?
Are you going to blame Sifeng again?
I removed the mask. It has nothing to do with him.
You should come at me.
Miss, you're not from Lize Palace.
I don't dare to approach you.
But... did you really remove the mask?
Of course.
Yu Sifeng, I want to congratulate you.
You're the first person who managed to remove that mask in Lize Palace.
What do you mean by that?
Sifeng was injured. I was afraid something might happen to him.
That's why I removed the mask.
Good. Very good.
There's an old rule in Lize Palace.
If someone can remove that mask,
Lize Palace will not try to make him stay.
Yu Sifeng, it seems like this is your happy ending.
But you need to return the mask to Lize Palace.
You need to give an explanation to the palace master.
Where's the mask?
Deputy Chief, I lost the mask while I was fighting the Purple Fox
in Mount Gao.
You lost it?
What is this then?
The mask is crying.
That means your curse hasn't been dispelled.
That's a different story.
Yu Sifeng, you should return and explain it to our palace master personally.
Deputy Chief, I still have many questions left unanswered.
Please give me more time.
I will try to solve everything.
Sorry, Xuanji.
I can't accompany you to find Linglong and Minyan.
Wait here. Those from Shaoyang Sect will pick you up.
You mustn't go on your own.
Must you return?
I'll follow you then.
I'm worried about you.
This is my personal matter.
Don't worry. I'll be fine.
I'll surely return for you.
Xuanji, let me tell you a secret.
It's really difficult to be a human.
But you...
You're the reason why I'm willing to become one.
Ruo Yu, return with Yu Sifeng.
Yes.
Wait.
What else?
Listen. I'll pick up Sifeng at Lize Palace in a few days.
Miss, don't you know the rules of Lize Palace?
No women are allowed in Lize Palace.
I'll wait outside then.
And I want you to promise me that Sifeng won't be harmed.
Don't think that everyone in Lize Palace has a mild temper.
Yu Sifeng is a disciple of Lize Palace.
Anything he receives has nothing to do with you.
I'm not as mild-tempered as Sifeng.
If you can't promise me that,
- Sifeng will stay behind.  - Stay behind?
On what basis?
Do you know what you need to do after you remove the mask?
I know. I need to be responsible for him.
I removed the mask. I'll be responsible for him.
How? Tell me.
You need to marry him.
Are you willing to do so?
Deputy Chief!
I need to marry him?
So, Sifeng meant we must get married?
So, that's the problem.
It's my fault. I didn't understand him completely.
Miss Chu looks unhappy with that.
I agree.
If marrying him is the only way for him to escape punishment,
I'll marry him.
Sifeng, you've done so much for me.
It's okay.
I can do this for you.
Miss Chu, if you do so willingly,
the mask will become a smiling mask.
But it's not smiling.
Stupid mask! I've agreed to marry him!
Why aren't you smiling?
- You're not doing it willingly.  - Nonsense!
Deputy Chief, please give Xuanji and me some time.
I've given you ample time.
Take him away.
Don't touch him!
I don't understand.
How could you let a mask decide someone's fate?
That's the dumbest rule I have ever heard of.
Today, I'm going to destroy this stupid mask.
The mask was made by the bark of the Kunlun Tree. It's tough.
How could she destroy it without any effort?
Dingkun Sword?
Why does she have the Dingkun Sword?
Now that the mask is gone, you have no way to punish Si Feng.
The mask was destroyed.
That adds another level to Yu Sifeng's misdeeds.
I won't let you take him away!
What? Are you trying to attack me?
Xuanji, calm down.
You've offended me too many times.
Don't blame me for disrespecting your father.
You're just a mantis. How dare you try to stop a cart!  (T/N: Chinese idiom - to overrate oneself and attempt something impossible)
Brace yourself!
Deputy Chief!
Xuanji!
Xuanji?
Spell of Tranquility, calmness among all else, return to tranquility.
Xuanji!
Deputy Chief, what exactly happened?
You actually ignored your status as an elder
and fought against your junior.
Sect Leader Chu's daughter
forced me to release Sifeng with the Dingkun Sword in her hand.
I was taken aback.
Are you talking about the divine weapon
which fell into the human realm?
Deputy Chief, you misunderstood her.
That sword was given to her by my master.
Although it's made from rare materials,
- it's not a divine weapon.  - That's right.
Xuanji's cultivation is just ordinary.
I'm sure she wouldn't be able to master a divine weapon.
Fine. You already said it.
I'll treat it as my mistake.
Okay, let's skip that. We should get back to business.
Everyone knows that the Destiny Pearl is in my hands now.
But the disciples that I've sent to Xuanyuan Sect haven't returned yet.
No one knows exactly what happened.
The most important thing now is the spirit key within the Destiny Pearl.
Spirit key?
Why am I in the dark?
Deputy Chief, we're in a plight.
I hope everyone can be honest and not hide anything from each other.
1,000 years ago, the heavenly realm sent four spirit keys
to the four righteous sects.
Fuyu Island, Lize Palace, Xuanyuan Sect, and Dianjing Valley Sect.
Each sect holds one spirit key.
And they're hidden within each sect as a treasure.
According to Xuanji's news, Tianxu Hall knew about that fact long ago.
And they're aiming for our spirit keys.
Yes.
After all this time, the demons aren't weak and feeble anymore.
They've become a huge threat.
It's fine if they just want to save Wu Zhiqi with the spirit keys.
I'm just afraid that they're after something more.
I heard that they wanted to revive the Devil Star.
The Devil Star?
What a joke.
I think it's impossible as well.
The Devil Star was vanquished 1,000 years ago.
How could they revive it?
It's just their wishful thinking.
But, speaking of which, we need to be more careful with the spirit keys.
How about this?
We'll formulate a plan after Dianjing Valley Sect's sect leader gets here.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until  you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫