''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Nature, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫ Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds; Six paths, nine heavens, a promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness, I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE 24]
The demon clan has been running amok with a long list of crimes.
They even attacked Fuyu Island in the light of day.
They killed our fellow disciples and took our treasure.
The world is in a perilous position right now.
As cultivators,
we should destroy those demons to uphold justice for the people!
Am I right, everybody?
Yes!
But the demon clan is very cunning.
They can take the shape of humans. They are impossible to guard against.
If we want to defeat them, we have to check our own people first before checking the others.
Today, a disciple of Lize Palace, Yu Sifeng,
colluded with the demons in Tianxu Hall to bring chaos to the world.
He should be killed.
But we cultivators are always fair and square.
We won't kill an innocent without solid evidence.
So, we'll use the Demon Whip to prove his identity.
If he can take three whips from the Demon Whip,
he can prove his innocence and he'll be pardoned.
If he reveals his true demonic form under the whip,
we'll punish him on the spot without mercy!
Punish him on the spot without mercy!
Demon Whip!
Senior! Senior!
Senior, Sifeng is not a demon.
You can't accuse him wrongly. Please let him go.
He sent a spirit beast to kill our disciple in Tianxu Hall. He was caught red-handed.
We are here to test his real identity. Other things are unimportant now.
Sifeng sent Little Silver Flower to Tianxu Hall because of me.
He wanted to get the Mirror of Origin to help me restore my six senses.
So, he has nothing to do with Tianxu Hall.
Whether or not he's colluding with them, you can't vouch for him.
We'll find out after three whips of the Demon Whip.
- Senior!  - Xuanji!
Stop fooling around.
Sifeng!
Sifeng! Sifeng!
- Sifeng.  - Sifeng!
Aunt Yinghong, let go of me!
Sifeng!
Please stop hitting him with the Demon Whip.
Yu Sifeng, tell me!
Are you a demon?
[LONGYIN]
I already
said it many times.
This is just the answer that you want.
No matter what I say,
it'll be useless.
Two more whips.
Come on.
Okay.
No! Sifeng!
Sifeng!
No!
Stop!
Sifeng!
Sifeng! Sifeng!
You already hit him twice.
If he's a demon, he would've shown himself.
If you keep hitting him, he'll die!
Sifeng! Sifeng!
Master, please spare him.
Yes, Sect Leader. He has already been beaten twice.
But there's no trace of a demon at all. How about we stop?
I'm afraid that he'll die if you hit him again.
[LONGYIN]
My fellow sect leaders, what say you about the third whip?
We promised to give him three whips.
How can we just stop?
Even if he's not a demon, he's still harboring a demon.
If he doesn't hand in the demon, continue to whip him.
Since it has already been decided, let's not hesitate anymore.
Deputy Chief, what about you?
Lize Palace has never been biased.
It'll be bad if others talk behind our back.
If you want to whip him, go ahead.
Tell us.
If you tell us, your life will be spared.
If I tell them about it, they'll know your secret.
Your uncontrollable power
and they'll treat you as a weird person again.
One... One more whip.
No such thing as worth it or not.
Just willing or not.
Dingkun Sword!
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path Nature, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫  Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets ♫
[LONGYIN]
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness,  I will not forget our promise  ♫
Xuanji.
No.
Dingkun Sword!
I won't allow you to hurt Sifeng!
What happened? Xuanji broke the Demon Whip.
Xuanji.
Chu Xuanji?
Could it really be you?
Demon Whip. My Demon Whip.
Sect Leader Chu, there must be something wrong with your daughter.
Valley Master Rong,
I'll settle this for you.
Xuanji, are you looking for death?
Come down now!
Without Sifeng,
whether or not
I live or die,
it doesn't matter.
Here.
Don't think that you'll be safe just because the Demon Whip is broken.
Let me tell you. Dream on.
I'm going to interrogate you with Hell's Nail.
I'll torture you for as long as it takes
until you admit to your crime.
Master!
Who dares touch my disciple?
Valley Master Rong, you are really determined to attack my disciple.
We didn't know that you were here.
- Sorry for not welcoming you properly.  - Don't be so pretentious.
If I was late any longer, my disciple would be dead.
- Ruo Yu.  - Here.
- Bring Sifeng back first.  - Yes, Palace Master.
Sifeng. Sifeng.
Let's go.
You weren't here. So, you didn't know that
your disciple was being suspected of colluding with the demon clan.
Are you saying that he killed a demon to silence it?
Look at this.
This demon was trying to escape after killing it with this secret weapon
and he ran into me on the island.
The poison on this demon's hand is indeed the one used to silence the demon.
You are really fantastic.
Do you really think that Lize Palace is useless?
Don't be mad.
Even if your disciple is not responsible for killing that demon,
he sent his spirit beast to Tianxu Hall to kill our disciple.
He was caught red-handed.
Bring him here.
Is this the dead disciple you mean?
Take a good look at him.
Is he dead or alive?
Minyan, take a look at him.
How is this possible?
Aren't you dead? I saw it myself.
That day, I fainted after being stabbed.
But I woke up after that and I was lying on a mass grave behind the mountains.
This is the secret art of Lize Palace.
You can stab the Qi acupoint to fake death.
My disciple taught this to his spirit beast
so that his spirit beast could escape Tianxu Hall
and save this person's life.
The funny thing is, all of you elders are so ignorant.
You are so self-righteous and requite kindness with enmity.
You accuse my disciple as a murderer!
Take him away!
Valley Master Rong, your Hell's Nail is amazing.
There's no need to target me.
I'm not the only one who suspected Sifeng.
Since the misunderstanding has been resolved and we didn't kill your disciple,
do you want me to atone for it with my life?
Palace Master, we wrongly accused Sifeng over a false testimony.
I sincerely apologize to you.
I don't need your apology.
I just want to ask. Who insisted that my disciple was a demon?
Stand out!
What is it?
Nobody dares to admit it?
Do you think that Lize Palace can be easily bullied?
Fine.
If you won't say it,
I'll use Dianjing Valley's Hell's Nail to force all of you to testify.
Dongfang Qingqi, how long are you going to keep quiet about this?
Master Dongfang, so you know
who the one is that wrongly accused my disciple.
Brother Dongfang,
since this incident stems from Madam,
we need to ask her in detail.
Bring Madam here.
Yes.
So, it's Madam Dongfang. Good.
I want to hear your testimony again.
Madam, who is the demon?
Who is the demon?
You are the demon.
He is the demon.
I am a demon.
- All of us are demons.  - Qing Rong.
So, all of you tortured my disciple because of a word from this crazy lady?
She said that all of you are demons.
So, should I put all of you into prison
so that you can have a taste of Hell's Nail?
Palace Master, Qing Rong has been quite absent-minded lately.
Please don't blame her.
Don't blame her?
Master Dongfang, your wife almost killed my disciple.
Now, she's acting crazy?
I think she's the most suspicious person to have colluded with the demons.
You don't dare to interrogate her because of Master Dongfang, right?
Fine!
I'll do it.
Palace Master, please have mercy on her.
You had no mercy when you tortured my disciple.
- I won't have mercy on your wife, either.  - You...
How dare you.
- Qing Rong!  - Brother Dongfang!
I want to see what answer I can get when
the Hell's Nail that was used
on my disciple is used on Madam Dongfang.
Tell me! Where is the demon of Tianxu Hall hiding?
Mount Buzhou.
I just know that they are at Mount Buzhou.
Do you hear that?
The answer that you want is inside Madam's head.
And you just tortured my disciple for nothing.
All of you are really a bunch of useless beings!
Let's go!
Qing Rong.
Bear with it.
Why is it so painful? Why is it so painful?
Look. It's just a nail.
I already took it out. It won't be painful anymore.
But I...
But it's really painful.
I beg you.
Please find him
and ask him why he lied to me.
I love him so much.
- Qing Rong!  - Why?
Qing Rong, why do you have to torture yourself?
Why do you have to be so foolish?
I am foolish.
But so are you.
You are foolish, too.
Both of us are foolish.
Qing Rong!
Qing Rong.
Qing Rong. Qing Rong.
Qing Rong!
It's really rare for you to come and find me so late at night.
Are you here to have tea and catch up with me?
Are you feigning ignorance with me?
You know Sifeng's identity better than anyone.
But you just allowed them to torture Sifeng.
Are you trying to go against me?
So, you are talking about Yu Sifeng.
You've wrongly accused me.
Those sects are already suspecting Lize Palace.
It was a disaster. If I sided with him,
Lize Palace would have looked too suspicious. Right?
Moreover, it is just a Demon Whip.
No matter how they whip him, he won't turn into a demon. Right?
Let me warn you again.
If you destroy Sifeng,
I'll destroy you.
Xuanji.
I won't allow you to hurt Sifeng!
Chu Xuanji,
are you that person or not?
Sifeng, are you feeling better now?
Just some minor injuries.
But you look
worse than I do.
I misunderstood you.
I feel guilty as your friend.
This is not your fault.
You saw Little Silver Flower hurting someone with your own eyes.
If I were you,
I would be suspicious, too.
Even when you were suspecting me,
you still risked your life to save me.
It's all because of Xuanji.
She believes in you and kept on trying to find a way to save you.
She even risked her life for it.
Sifeng, I grew up with Xuanji since young.
There are things that I see more clearly than you do.
Xuanji really treats you differently.
This is the first time I saw her being so violent.
She was even ready to oppose my master.
She never did that before,
and it's because of you.
I can see that you are really special to Xuanji.
I just think that you should know about this.
So, I came to tell you about it.
I hope that you can recover soon.
I won't disturb you anymore.
Xuanji! You...
Everything I did today
is out of my own willingness.
Dingkun Sword!
Without Sifeng,
whether or not I live or die,
it doesn't matter.
Things that Xuanji did are enough to prove everything.
But I was still hung up about those non-essentials.
Yu Sifeng,
you were really barking at the moon.
Why were you so foolish?
Do you know how upset I would be if I really
harmed you with my own hands today?
This is a very powerful bead.
Keep it with you to help you recover and as protection.
From now on, don't risk your life for unimportant people anymore.
All right now.
Rest earlier.
King Bailing, this is bad!
This is bad!
Heavenly Emperor invited you to attend Xi Wangmu's Yaochi Banquet together.
I racked my brain
trying to find various reasons to help you put that off.
King Bailing, you better discard this mortal body and
let's go back to the heavenly realm.
I still can't go back yet.
King Bailing, you...
Xuanji has been affected by feelings in the human realm.
She doesn't even listen to me now.
Love is worrisome.
Love is scary.
If she continues, she'll lose control, become tainted,
and fall into the evil path.
I can't leave her behind right now.
I have to break this ill-fated relationship that she has with him.
King Bailing, God of War is very willful.
She won't change her mind.
Especially something to do with feelings. You know her best.
If you use force on her, she might create some huge troubles again.
Have you forgotten about what happened 900 years ago?
Ever since she destroyed her own life pillar,
she started to turn evil until she committed that grave crime.
You are right.
She is very willful.
She was like that in the past.
And she is like this now.
Maybe I should've let things run their course.
Forget it.
There are so many ways in this world.
I can use other ways to help her reincarnate.
If she wants feelings, I'll use feelings to help her reincarnate.
- King Bailing.  - As long as she can be safe in this life
and keep the three realms in peace,
anything can be done.
King Bailing, are you going to...
Yesterday, my master sent me a broken scroll of Sentimental Tactics.
He said that Heartless Tactics can no longer suppress the secret ground.
Since the Heartless Tactics doesn't work,
I'll study the Sentimental Tactic together with her.
That's why you gave the love flower to Xuanji.
So, you are trying to seduce her with a love token.
Are you really doing this just to break this ill-fated relationship of hers?
Si Ming,
I had only one goal when I descend to this mortal world.
To bring her back.
I know.
My master found these broken scrolls a few days ago.
He understands the mystery of turning Heartless Tactics to Sentimental Tactics.
He hopes that Junior Xuanji and I can go back to Xuyang Peak to practice it
so that we can protect the secret ground with greater power.
Good.
This is a good thing.
Senior Heng Yang is always worried that
he took the wrong path in this life and couldn't reach Nirvana.
Now, you and Xuanji can help him get this off his chest
and protect the secret ground at the same time.
This is really killing two birds with one stone.
But...
the cultivators of Sentimental Tactics
should be connected with each other and share weal and woe together. (good and bad times)
I know a lot of seniors in Xuyang Peak who became couples after
training in Sentimental Tactics together.
Then, you and Xuanji...
Sect Leader, Junior Xuanji and I
have been training together day and night.
And we've developed feelings towards each other.
Junior Xuanji is naive and innocent.
I'm willing to take her as my partner and protect her forever.
I hope that we can have your blessings.
Of course, I'll give you your blessings.
Even the Love Stone approved of your ties with her.
It means that both of you are a match made in heaven.
Besides, since young, Xuanji has always been different from others.
She needs someone
to take care of her and guide her.
If that person is you, I'll be ecstatic.
I really want to bring both of you together.
When are you going to ask your master to come and propose?
To show my sincerity,
I'll go back at once to Xuyang Peak to invite my master to Fuyu Island
so that we can set this engagement in front of all sect leaders.
Good.
Great.
Xuanji.
Sifeng, you are awake.
Are you okay?
Don't simply move around, Sifeng.
I'm fine.
I asked you to not move. Lie down. Hurry up.
- Okay, I won't move.  - Lie down.
I'm really okay.
But you even dared to stop the Demon Whip.
Now, I can't let you go even if I want to.
You crazy girl.
By the way, I heard that
I'm just a broken vase.
Aren't you the one who said it?
My feelings now are broken again like that vase.
I just want Sifeng to smile at me and tell me that
he's fine.
I don't know which part of me is like a vase.
Stop it. I...
How can Sixth Senior do this?
I said those things in a moment of desperation.
How could he tell you all about it?
So, it meant nothing.
No. Of course, you are more valuable than a vase.
It was just a metaphor.
Although that metaphor is not that accurate, I want to say that,
of course, Sifeng is valuable, too.
He's more valuable than a vase and...
Sifeng, I... I'm too dumb.
I can't speak well and I can't use a good metaphor.
You are so smart. Can you teach me how to talk?
Looks like I really need to teach you how to talk.
Or else, I'll eventually die in your hands.
There is...
something that I want to teach you.
But it's not about talking.
It's about...
teaching you how to fall in love with me.
Do you want to learn that?
Is that very hard?
No.
It's like sword fights and spells.
You do it step-by-step and one at a time.
Can I learn that too although I have no six senses?
Of course. Everyone can learn that.
It might take longer for you
but I will teach you patiently.
The important thing is you have to want to learn it.
I'll learn it if you want to teach me.
Good.
Then, you have to listen to me carefully.
For your first lesson, I don't want my name in that book of yours.
- Why?  - Because there are too many people in it.
And I don't like sharing.
But...
I want to be...
deeply ingrained in...
the most important part of your heart forever.
Xuanji,
do you understand?
Linglong?
Linglong.
You cherish Xuanji the most.
Now, Hao Chen is willing to love Xuanji for his whole life.
If you knew about this,
you would be ecstatic, right?
Why are you here, Elder of Constellation?
I'm here to pass down the lord's order.
The lord's order? Go ahead.
He needs to confirm the validity of a clue now.
He wants you to find a person with a celestial eye at once.
How will there be a mortal with a celestial eye?
Even if there is, where can I find him?
Are you joking with me?
That person is called Liu Yihuan.
As for where to find him, it'll be your problem.
But let me tell you...
Our lord is running out of patience.
You.
Pick it up for me.
Wait.
Who asked you to walk there?
- Crawl over there.  - You...
Hurry up. Hurry up and crawl.
Hurry up.
Come over here.
Good boy.
Linglong.
How dare you call my name?
Do you really not remember your past?
We've known each other for a long time.
The past?
You mentioned the past again.
Guards!
Bring him back and punish him again.
I don't want to be punished.
Not only do I want to punish you,
I'll ask Brother Wu Tong to punish you himself.
- Let's go.  - No, Linglong!
I don't want to be punished!
No!
Look at you now. You look so pitiful.
I am pitiful.
But you don't even know who you are right now.
Aren't you as pitiful as I am?
So baffling.
Brother Wu Tong!
What is it, Linglong?
Nothing. Just a disobedient slave who spoke some nonsense.
Brother Wu Tong, play with me.
I'm looking for a person named Liu Yihuan now.
I don't have time to play with you.
Find another person to play with you.
Liu Yihuan?
I think I've heard this name before.
Where did you hear it from?
The little demon in the prison.
She said that her father is Liu Yihuan and can use the celestial eye.
Really?
I don't need to make any effort at all.
So, Liu Yihuan's daughter is right here with me.
This is so interesting.
Master.
I've already read your message.
Xuanyuan has fallen
and two spirit keys have been taken away.
Tianxu Hall is so lawless right now.
The worst thing is,
the demon clan has already found out that the Devil Star
is inside Shaoyang's secret ground.
The closer the two stars are,
the weaker the barrier of Shaoyang's secret ground.
The demon clan will not let go of this rare chance.
I'm going to initiate Xuyang Peak's Protector Formation at once.
I can't let the demon clan cast their greedy eyes on the Crystal Lamp.
Master, to initiate the Protector Formation of Xuyang Peak,
we'll have to use the strongest power in Xuyang Peak.
Besides, this formation will feed on your cultivation
until you wither and die.
So what if I sacrifice myself to protect the secret ground?
But protecting it and eliminating the demons is a long battle.
If you sacrifice yourself, how many people can become your successor?
You've read the broken scrolls that I sent you before this, right?
I found them in the library.
Heartless Tactics and Sentimental Tactics are actually the same.
They are separated into two because of different understandings
between different cultivators.
If we put our heart into it,
we can turn the Heartless Tactics into the Sentimental Tactics.
Unfortunately, I was too late.
I can no longer find someone who can connect to me
and practice the Sentimental Tactics with me.
I sent those broken scrolls to you
because it's not too late for you.
I have only you and Xuanji as my disciples.
If both of you can practice the Sentimental Tactics together,
even if I pass away, I'll have successors to fuel
the Protector Formation of Xuyang Peak.
I understand what you mean.
I'm willing to inherit your aspiration.
Back then, you kept on persuading me to take Xuanji as a disciple.
Now, it looks like both of you are really fated to be together.
Moreover, from what I can see,
both of you have spent four years together at Xuyang Peak.
I'm sure that both of you can succeed in mastering the Sentimental Tactics.
You are right.
If that's the case, please propose
a marriage proposal to the sect leader for us to be engaged.
And please be a witness for me
and Junior Xuanji in front of the four sects.
We can show them Shaoyang Sect's determination to guard the secret ground.
Okay.
I'll go to Fuyu Island with you.
Yes, Master.
Sifeng, are we viewing the moon now?
We are viewing the moon and continuing the lesson.
We are not done yet?
Do you think that my lessons are that easy to learn?
What else do I need to learn?
What you need to learn now is, if others treat you well,
what are you going to do?
If they treat me well, of course, I'll treat them well, too.
Since I'm teaching you to love me,
you have to differentiate between how you treat me and others.
For example, if a man compliments that you are beautiful
and wants to travel with you, what should you do?
- I should agree.  - No. You should hit him.
If a man compliments you, it means that he likes you.
And since you've chosen to love me,
how can you travel with him? So, you have to hit him.
Another example.
If a man invites you for food and gives you presents,
what should you do?
- Food? Of course, I have to agree.  - Wrong.
You have to hit him, too.
Why will a stranger give you gifts? There must be an ulterior motive.
So, he deserves to be beaten up.
I should hit him?
Now, the most important question.
If a man is cold and wants to hug you for warmth, what should you do?
I should hug him, right?
Or else, he'll be freeze to death.
Chu Xuanji, you have to hit him, too.
I have to hit him again.
There are so many ways to get warm, why does he have to hug you?
Besides, remember this.
This is very important.
Besides me, you can't let another man hug you,
and you can't hug another man either. Understand?
Sifeng, this important point sounds very strict.
Of course.
This is an important question.
Of course, I need to be strict about it.
Okay, next question.
If one day, your father asks you to stay away from me...
I'll hit him.
No.
You are right. Not every question has only one answer.
Xuanji,
your father is an open and above-board person.
If he gives you this kind of order one day,
there must be a reason for it.
But you can try to convince him otherwise,
or meet up with me in secret.
Xuanji, I won't let you down.
Little Silver Flower, why are you hiding here?
Well, you risked your life to protect me.
I'm here to thank you.
My master is still injured. Don't disturb him.
Little Silver Flower, Xuanji did a lot of things to save us.
You should thank her.
Me? I don't want to do that.
After you take the form of a human,
you have to follow human rules.
I don't need you to repay me.
But you have to thank the person who had helped you before.
Actually, it's fine.
Thank you. I'm done. Is it very hard? No need to act magnanimously.
Yanran.
I won't say it again even if you didn't hear it.
If I had known that you were Little Silver Flower,
we could have used the four years to become friends.
It would have been nice.
I've bought your favorite rice cake for you.
- I...  - Yanran.
Xuanji is being kind.
Take it.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until  you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫