''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Destiny, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫ Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds; Six paths, nine heavens, a promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness,  I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE SIX]
♫  The flower petal accidentally kissed your shoulder as it fell  ♫
♫  It's the sun that always causes problems from nothing  ♫
♫  There's a small breeze, a small patter of rain  ♫
♫  As soon as I saw you, I was surprised at the upheaval of my feelings  ♫
♫  How can I hide such chaos in my mind?  ♫
♫  Whether you raise or lower your head, my heart flutters  ♫
♫  Please stop testing me time and time again  ♫
♫  You're so hard to forget  ♫
♫  I thought I could pretend  ♫
♫ pretend to not love you ♫
♫  Because I thought I didn't want, wouldn't want to hurt  ♫
♫  Yet the passing years were so turbulent  ♫
No. I can't let this dummy continue to sleep here.
♫  Every single drop of yearning I feel is clear  ♫
♫  Who cares how absurd it is?  ♫
♫  As the autumn winds blow, see that the geese have embarked on their journey  ♫
♫  It's only a step away  ♫
♫  Even if love is an abyss I will still jump into it  ♫
Don't go. Don't leave me behind.
♫  It's a shadow from a glimpse  ♫
♫  It's an illusion from a relfection  ♫
♫  It's a karma that brings joy  ♫
I never thought that the forbidden ground of Shaoyang Sect would be guarded so heavily.
It has taken me a lot of work.
But no matter how well-guarded it is, I still found it in the end.
Someone has broken into the forbidden ground. Hurry!
This is the ancient Torch Dragon?
I never thought that they'd use the Torch Dragon to guard a Spirit Key.
Darn it. Is Ling Shi trying to get me killed?
The barrier is intact.
I wonder who the one is that broke into the forbidden ground again.
Luckily, you and your master have already reinforced this barrier before this.
Even the curious ones will not be able to get past the Torch Dragon.
I'll lay down a few more Defensive Formations with Uncle Lu Yang
to prevent anyone from getting near to this place.
Shi Feng from Xuanyuan Sect wins.
How did Xuanyuan Sect become so powerful this year?
It's quite strange.
Sifeng! All the best, Sifeng! You have to win!
Wu Tong, remember this.
I made the exception to accept you because you looked so sincere.
If you can't come first this time, you can leave us.
I'll definitely get first place.
All the best, Sifeng! Sifeng, defeat him!
Sifeng!
All the best!
Great!
It's a spell again!
I remember that I already said this the last time. Spells are not allowed.
I can forgive you the first time, but a second time is unforgivable.
Wu Tong, you already broke the rule just now.
I think this round should go to Yu Sifeng from Lize Palace.
You useless thing! Good-for-nothing! Are you that incapable?
If you can't come first, you can leave us.
Master, I still have other skills.
Sect Leader Chu, let me compete again.
Yu Sifeng did not defeat me. I didn't lose.
You broke the rule and you still want to compete. You have no shame.
Does Dianjing Valley Sect have no rules?
- You...  - Say no more!
Dianjing Valley Sect has lost in this round.
Master!
Sect Leader Chu, let me compete again!
Tell me. Do you know how to write the word dignity?
- Shut up!  - I...
Forget it. He's so fierce. Let him be.
It's okay. Let me.
Even your master has already asked you to leave. Why are you still here?
Since you like to talk so much, I'll shut you up forever.
Be careful!
Xuanji!
Don't be too arrogant. Try dying.
Stop right there! Don't run!
Chase after him! Don't let him run away!
Stop right there!
How is she?
I've patched up her artery. She should be fine now.
I'll perform acupuncture on her later.
But, Aunt Yinghong, why is she still unconscious?
She was bleeding so much just now.
Linglong, calm down first. Master Yinghong has said that she'll be fine.
Xuanji will definitely wake up.
It's all because of Wu Tong. We have to find Wu Tong to avenge her!
Enough. Stop disturbing your aunt.
Let's go out first.
Aunt Yinghong.
She'll be fine.
[SHOUYANG HALL]
Sect Leader, we were incapable. Wu Tong got away.
What?
Barricade all exits right now. Don't let him get away!
Yes!
Senior Brother Chu, how is Xuanji?
Luckily, she's not fatally wounded,
but we don't know when she will wake up.
Sect Leader Chu, I'm really ashamed for what happened today.
I have a high-quality medicine for wounds that was passed down by our great master.
Later, I'll ask my disciple to send it to her.
Hopefully, it can help with her wound.
It's Dianjing Valley Sect's fault for not educating my disciple well.
That Wu Tong came to me out of the blue.
I wanted to lead him into the light.
But I never thought he would bring such disaster today.
If that's the case, Dianjing Valley Sect will no longer keep him.
Today, I'm going to kick Wu Tong out from Dianjing Valley Sect
in front of every sect here.
From now on, Wu Tong and Dianjing Valley Sect are no longer related.
You are really good at passing the buck, Valley Master Rong.
You might have kicked him out,
but what about the competition ranking then?
To make up for all of you,
Dianjing Valley will withdraw from the competition this time.
It's a form of apology, too.
Although Wu Tong has been kicked out from Dianjing Valley,
he seriously wounded Xuanji and escaped to avoid punishment.
We can't let him off the hook so easily.
No matter where he runs,
I'll definitely catch him and bring him to justice.
Wu Tong is bad-tempered and vicious.
If we let him run loose, he'll be a disaster to the people.
In order to uphold justice, we have the responsibility to get rid of him for the people.
If that's the case, Dianjing Valley Sect will take the lead first.
From today onward, Dianjing Valley Sect, Shaoyang Sect,
Lize Palace, Xuanyuan Sect, and Fuyu Island
will work together to arrest Wu Tong.
If there is any resistance or people harboring him,
they'll be going against us five sects!
[WANTED. REWARD: 500 SILVER]
[REWARD: 500 SILVER FOR WU TONG]
Wait!
Go.
The head disciple of Lize Palace is really kind.
You even withdrew from the Hairpin Tournament for a girl.
Chu Xuanji was seriously wounded by Wu Tong
because she defended me during the competition.
Now, she is still unconscious and her life might still be in danger.
Out of moral responsibility, how can I not show care towards her?
What a noble and honorable excuse.
Yu Sifeng, you are the head disciple that the palace lord has high hope in.
You have to fight for Lize Palace's reputation.
If you don't want to make up for your mistake of losing your mask
by becoming first in the Hairpin Tournament,
so be it.
Is Xuanji getting better?
Aunt Yinghong said that she'll wake up after resting for two days.
Sifeng, take care of Xuanji for us first.
We'll go and fetch the medicine for her.
Let's go.
Xuanji.
Xuanji!
Who are you?
Xuanji, when are you going to wake up?
I'm afraid that I'll have to go back to Lize Palace
before I can bid my farewell to you.
Do you know that if you can wake up and smile,
I'll be able to go through any hardships when I go back?
Hero Yu, you are so kind for coming here every day
to take care of Xuanji.
Thank you for saving the junior sister of our sect twice.
I never thought that there was still a righteous disciple like you in Lize Palace.
Xuanji is my friend. I can't do much.
I just hope that she can wake up soon.
Don't worry. She will.
This is weird. She was so seriously wounded.
But she's almost healed although it has just been a few days.
It's really surprising.
She has indeed recovered very quickly.
We've given her a lot of medicine and supplements
from various sects for the past few days.
They must have helped her recover.
Although she looks fine now, she has lost a lot of blood.
I think she'll still be unconscious for a while.
As long as she is fine. Junior Sister Xuanji is a very fortunate person.
Yu Sifeng.
Deputy Chief.
You still know that I'm the Deputy Chief?
I haven't seen you for so many days.
I thought you'd already forgotten about Lize Palace's rules.
I wouldn't dare.
You need to focus and pack your things, too.
Get ready to go back.
Deputy Chief, the Hairpin Tournament is not over yet. Right?
The game is already set. Xuanyuan Sect got lucky this time.
Lize Palace is really noble. We just gave away first place to others.
Nobody cares about that Hairpin Tournament.
What is it? Are you reluctant to leave?
No. I just think that if we leave like this,
it'll look like Lize Palace is a sore loser.
Deputy Chief, how about we wait for a few more days?
Don't think that I don't know what you are thinking about.
Forget it. You are not my problem.
You are Palace Master's disciple. He'll punish you when you go back.
Your days of freedom will come to an end soon.
I understand that you want to cherish your remaining time.
Xuanji,
in the end, I still can't wait until you wake up.
I don't know if you can hear me.
But I still want to tell you that
it was the happiest thing in my life to have been able to come out
and meet you here.
I'll remember our four-year promise.
No matter how hard it is, we'll meet again.
Sifeng, you are leaving?
The Hairpin Tournament has ended for a few days already.
I can't extend my stay anymore.
Xuanji will be sad when she wakes up with you gone.
The sound of this bell can travel for miles.
Linglong, please give this to her for me.
She can contact me with it when she wakes up.
Don't forget about it.
Don't worry. I'll tell her.
Too bad we haven't caught Wu Tong yet,
or else we could watch him get punished to uphold justice for Xuanji.
I still think that this matter was not handled properly.
Wu Tong is just a normal disciple.
But now, the five sects are working together to make him a wanted criminal.
He should've thought of that when he hurt Xuanji back then.
He has only himself to blame.
I didn't mean that.
Wu Tong is very narrow-minded and he's an extremist.
It's not a good thing to corner him.
Or maybe I'm thinking too much.
Linglong and Minyan, please take care.
- Farewell.  - You, too, my brother.
After Xuanji is awake, we'll go and visit you at Lize Palace.
Bring Yu Sifeng, the disciple who broke the rule in the hall!
[LIZE PALACE]
Yu Sifeng, as the head disciple of Lize Palace and
as the preferred successor of Palace Master,
not only were you not strict with yourself and weren't a role model to everyone,
you even lost your mask outside and showed your real face.
You broke the rule and put Lize Palace in danger.
Do you know what the punishment you deserve is?
The 13 Punishments. I accept the punishments with no objection.
Take away his Head Disciple Token and
send him into the 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion at once.
Wait.
This is the first time he committed this mistake.
Besides, he didn't do it on purpose. He had a solid reason.
This is not a suitable punishment.
When I was cultivating myself two years ago in seclusion,
Sifeng attended to me diligently.
He made great contributions. I haven't even rewarded him yet.
He made a mistake this time but his merit offsets his fault.
As for his reward and punishment,
they've cancelled each other out.
Palace Master. Based on Lize Palace's centuries of rules,
if a disciple loses his mask and shows his true face outside,
he has to be sent into the 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion.
Even though he made a contribution,
you still have to discuss it first with two other palace lords and four elders.
How can you just cancel out the punishment like that?
Looks like Palace Master is being biased towards his own disciple.
What is it?
Are you saying that his merit for helping me out in my cultivation
is not enough to cancel out the punishment for losing his mask?
Losing his mask is not the only rule he broke.
He was very close with those disciples from Shaoyang Sect.
And his relationship with that Chu Xuanji
is not just a simple friendship.
He even withdrew from the Hairpin Tournament for her
and let Lize Palace lose the chance to become the head of the five sects.
Where does this rumor come from?
Impossible. This is not true.
Profound sentiments of friendship.
I think he said it himself.
Yu Sifeng, do you still remember?
Yes, I do.
My feelings for Xuanji are indeed more than friendship.
I don't want to lie.
Yu Sifeng!
I think you've been possessed by an outsider.
Say it. Say that you are sorry.
You have been bewitched because you are young and ignorant.
Say it! Say that you are sorry!
He won't say it.
Palace Master, a disciple of Lize Palace can never fall in love with a woman,
and can never have a wife and family.
As the Head Disciple of Lize Palace, he lost to temptation
and was influenced by an outside woman. He destroyed his own future.
He has broken many rules. His punishment cannot be canceled.
Palace Master, he has to be sent into the 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion!
Shut up!
What kind of a place is 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion?
Since ancient times, how many came out alive after going in?
Moreover, Sifeng is a rare talent
that only appears once in a blue moon.
Don't you know that?
I still want to teach him well
and let him bring pride to Lize Palace!
If he goes through the 13 Punishments and dies inside it,
who will be able to lead Lize Palace in the future?
Palace Master, if he can't survive the 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion,
how can he be the rare talent of Lize Palace?
If you really want to be biased,
we won't be able to enforce the rules of Lize Palace in the future.
Shut up!
Palace Master, the rules of Lize Palace are set by our great ancestors.
Palace lords need to discuss with the elders before any decision is made.
Palace Master has no right to make the decision alone.
I'm getting a headache.
Terrible headache.
I can't discuss this further today.
Take him into the prison first and we'll discuss it on another day.
Palace Master, we have to make a decision eventually!
Palace Master, it'll be hard to convince everyone if we do this!
Take Yu Sifeng into the prison first.
A decision has to be made eventually.
How long can he delay this?
Eldest Brother Liu.
Little Phoenix.
What happened?
You brat.
I was still hoping that you could bring some wine for me.
Now, you are locked up by those two monsters as well.
No. You are the best disciple in Lize Palace.
Your eccentric master dotes on you the most, right?
It's not his fault.
I'm the one who took off my mask and broke the rules.
Mask again. I can't believe Lize Palace.
Why are they always so violent about one mask?
They always say that only the disciples in the palace are your family.
Actually, this is just an inhumane place.
But you always followed the rules by the book, right?
Why did you take off your mask?
Did it fall off by itself or someone took it off?
Something is wrong with you.
Wait.
Eldest Brother Liu, this is...
Spell of deceit.
I've been here for so many years. Of course, I have to do something.
Let me tell you. I've cleared a path through all the prison rooms here.
Look.
The prison of Lize Palace is built on the Kushui River
and the bottom of it is surrounded by bitter water that we can't survive in.
It looks very well-guarded, but it's not.
I've dug a secret tunnel that I can escape in.
Nothing is too hard for me.
So, you always sneaked out to see your daughter.
You can sneak out but you continue to be locked inside here.
It's for your daughter, right?
I heard that the old palace master once forced you to make a vow
on your daughter's life.
That's why you have been stuck here for decades.
Yes. If it wasn't for Yu'er...
Don't talk about me. Let's talk about you.
What happened to your mask? Who took it off?
Was it a boy or girl?
Is she beautiful?
You are getting shy.
Come. Let's drink while we talk.
Here.
Take it and drink it.
Oldest Brother Liu, since young, whenever I saw you in prison,
you would always trick others to drink in order to uncover the others' secrets.
That part of you has never changed.
But you are the only one who will tell me about the outside world.
You always said that
human feelings are troublesome and complicated.
But they are also the most beautiful.
I think... I understand now.
Little Phoenix,
you always look so cold.
But I know that you are the most open-minded person.
You look a little bit like me in the past.
You met a girl you like, right?
No. If you had just taken off your mask,
based on your position in the palace and how defensive your master is,
your master would definitely do everything he could to cancel your punishment.
But it'll be troublesome if you had really admitted that you like someone.
I don't think you'll be able to escape the 13 Punishments.
When that time comes, even your master can't protect you.
You haven't admitted this to those old-fashioned men, right?
I can't lie to my master.
And I cannot deceive my own heart.
LIttle Phoenix, you are quite smart usually.
Why are you acting dumb at a time like this?
Do you know what kind of place 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion is?
I know. I broke the rules. I'm willing to be punished.
What do you know?
Let me tell you. In that 13 Punishments Tower of Oblivion,
all 13 floors are full of vicious beasts, monsters, and evil spirits.
Devilish formations that erode the soul and heart.
The one who is punished has to climb from the bottom to the top to be able to survive it.
All these years, those who could survive it are few and far in between.
Are you courting death?
Even though it's rare, it's not impossible.
You are a fool. You are betting with your life.
This won't do.
How about this?
You should just escape from the secret tunnel that I dug out.
Don't ever come back to Lize Palace anymore.
I can't leave.
If I leave, I'll become Lize Palace's traitor.
I'm indebted to my master.
Even if I have broken the rules,
I can't escape in fear of punishment and bring shame to him.
Moreover, if I just run away, am I going to hide and run forever?
- Little Phoenix.  - Don't worry, Eldest Brother Liu.
Since there's a way out from the 13 Punishments,
I'm going to escape using that way.
I really don't know what to say to you.
Linglong, don't worry. Xuanji will be fine.
But she has been unconscious for so many days.
How can I not worry?
What should we do now?
I'm so hungry.
- Xuanji, you are awake!  - Xuanji.
- Xuanji.  - Little Six, keep an eye on her.
- I'll call for someone.  - Okay.
Xuanji.
Sixth Senior Brother.
You are finally awake. You scared us.
Thank you, Sixth Senior Brother.
What did you say?
Aren't you the one who pulled me out from the water that day?
I was so scared when I fell that day.
I thought I was going to die.
Luckily, you pulled me out. Thank you.
No. It wasn't like that.
That day...
- Master.  - Father.
Xuanji.
Aunt Yinghong.
Senior Brother Hao Chen.
Xuanji has recovered. No need to worry now.
See? I knew that she would be fine.
It's good that she has recovered.
I really can't believe you!
You don't practice hard usually. That's why you couldn't react in time!
You made us all worry.
I'm sorry, Father.
Father, Xuanji did it to save me. If you want to scold someone, scold me.
Sect Leader Chu, Xuanji was very courageous this time.
She stepped forward bravely when danger hit. You should compliment her.
Junior Sister Xuanji, how's your wound? Do you feel uncomfortable?
You've recovered well,
but your wound is quite deep.
Weren't you afraid when the sword flew towards you?
I didn't think that much.
I just didn't want Linglong to get hurt.
Dummy. I'm tougher than you. A sword wound is nothing.
Don't do this again in the future. It's dangerous.
Enough. Say no more. Recuperate well.
Take care of her, both of you.
We'll be leaving first then.
- Xuanji.  - Linglong.
Where is Sifeng? Why isn't he here?
You've been unconscious for many days. The Hairpin Tournament has already ended.
I was unconscious for so long?
I thought it was just a dream.
- So, Sifeng has left?  - Yes.
He came here every day to take care of you but you didn't wake up.
In the end, he couldn't drag it out any longer.
So, he went back to Lize Palace.
I'm too useless.
I was unconscious for so long just because of a sword wound.
I couldn't even bid farewell to him.
It's all right. We can still meet him, right?
- Junior Sister Xuanji.  - Junior Sister.
First Senior. Second Senior.
What is it? Aren't you happy that we are here to see you?
Of course. I'm very happy.
Xuanji, you've really changed my mind about you.
You risked your life to take a sword for Linglong. You were so brave.
You don't have any strong points usually but you are so unselfish in a critical time.
How could you say that?
Xuanji, we know that you will be bored while recuperating.
So, we brought you something.
Second Junior Brother, you even gave the treasure you got when you roamed the world to her?
Our junior sister is so unselfish. Of course, I have to be magnanimous, too.
Xuanji, I still have a lot of treasures. I'll show you later.
Are you worried about Xuanji?
Yes. Xuanji is so slow when it comes to her training.
How can I not worry?
She has never known what danger is since young.
She has escaped from death so many times.
Although it's already very lucky that she can grow up safely
and I shouldn't ask for more,
just like how her mother took care of her
and kept her by her side all the time when she was still alive,
accidents can still happen.
And her mother couldn't take care of her forever, either.
From now on, I really don't know how to educate her.
So you are always so strict towards her
because you want her to know how to defend herself from being bullied
and being able to save herself in a sticky situation.
Right?
Actually, regarding Junior Sister Xuanji,
my master has different opinions from yours.
My master can see that she is a talented person.
So, he asked me to request your permission
to let her be my master's disciple.
Really?
I wouldn't joke about it.
Although my master always stays at Xuyang Peak in order to
reinforce the barrier of the forbidden ground,
he always talks to me about matters in Shaoyang Sect.
Although her six senses are not developed
and her personality is different from others,
she never loses her pure heart.
Xuyang Peak will suit her well.
And it's suitable for her to learn the Heartless Tactics.
Senior Heng Yang is considered
the most cultivated person in Shaoyang Sect.
Of course, he has his own view.
If she can really enter Xuyang Peak
and become Senior Heng Yang's female disciple,
she must be blessed from her past life.
So, you agree with this suggestion?
It'll be my honor. An honor.
When Xuanji is feeling better after a few days,
I'll summon her and tell her about this great news at once.
Okay.
Xuanji, listen to me. Although Master looks so strict,
he worries about you the most.
The five sects are working together to catch Wu Tong.
The five sects are working together?
- Isn't that awesome?  - What's so awesome?
So many people are looking for him, but they still can't find him. Right?
If I see Wu Tong, I'll poke a hole through his shoulder as well.
Let him have a taste of what it feels like.
Linglong, don't be so rash.
Look. I'm fine now.
Just let Wu Tong go.
Don't provoke him anymore.
I think Wu Tong is narrow-minded and cruel.
If he can injure me, he might even kill someone one day.
We better stay away from him.
Why do you sound exactly like Sifeng?
Because Sifeng told me the same thing.
He told me that
if we tie ourselves to a despicable man, we are the ones who will suffer in the end.
I think Sifeng knows a lot of things.
I'm sure that he's right. Let's just take his advice.
I am your sister but you never take my advice.
What happened during the Hairpin Tournament?
Sifeng withdrew from the competition for you.
In the end, Senior Brother Shi Feng from Xuanyuan Sect
won the competition and got the hairpin.
Talking about this Hairpin Tournament...
Xuanyuan Sect is like a new force on the rise. A dark horse.
Xuanji, you didn't see
how proud those people from Xuanyuan Sect were.
They just acted like the master of all five sects
and started to order us around.
But Sifeng could have won.
Because of me, he...
Father, you are looking for me?
Senior Brother Hao Chen.
Did I cause trouble again?
Xuanji, do you know that everyone was very worried about you
when you were wounded?
It's my fault for being too useless.
I made everyone worry about me.
Then, do you want to improve yourself
so that they won't have to worry about you again?
Of course. I want to become more powerful.
Then, I'll be able to protect the important people around me.
Junior Sister Xuanji, do you want to come to Xuyang Peak to train together with me?
- Xuyang Peak?  - Yes.
Uncle Master Heng Yang is willing to take you as his disciple.
He's willing to train you personally.
Uncle Master Heng Yang?
I...
I'm so stupid.
But he still wants to take me as his disciple.
Has he become silly from age?
Don't be so mannerless.
It's your blessing that Uncle Master Heng Yang
is willing to accept you as his disciple.
I know. That's why I said
that he should accept an extraordinary disciple like Senior Brother Hao Chen.
Not a dummy like me.
How do you know that you are not extraordinary?
You are different from others.
Your six senses are undeveloped.
Actually, that's your inborn talent, too.
It's something that others don't have.
Having no six senses... is a good thing?
Since God has already chosen a path for you,
no need to doubt yourself.
You just need to find the right way and train hard.
I believe that you'll be able to achieve something great.
Sifeng said the same thing, too.
Can I really become someone who's more powerful?
Senior Brother, I'm willing to go to Xuyang Peak to train together with you.
Xuanji.
Xuanji. Xuanji.
Sifeng, I am Linglong.
The sound of this thing can really travel for miles.
Linglong, how is Xuanji now?
I'm sorry. I forgot to tell you that Xuanji is fine now,
but she was summoned by my father now.
I'll tell you when she comes back, okay?
Good.
Linglong, tell Xuanji that after she is done, to send me a message.
I'll wait for her.
Don't worry.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫