''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Destiny, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫ Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds; Six paths, nine heavens, a promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness, I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE 11]
Kunyin Pill...
I should be able to make it myself.
I'm almost there.
Burn with Zhuyu Grass.
I've seen it before.
Where is it?
[KUNYIN PILL]
This is it.
Master.
Help me, Master.
Ling Shi!
Sect Leader.
Where did you get this evil pill manual?
My disciples have become like this because of it!
Sect Leader, I was wrong.
This has always been a trap!
They said this Kunyin Pill could increase one's skills.
And it's true.
But unexpectedly, if one doesn't keep taking it, he'll die!
Who are they?
Tianxu Hall.
It's that bunch of evildoers at Tianxu Hall! I fell into their trap!
- They want to covet the spirit keys.  - You...
My disciples are in deep water because of you!
Leave. You're no longer part of the Xuanyuan Sect!
Sect Leader! Please give me a few more days.
I'll definitely produce the Kunyin Pill.
Our sect will be saved then.
Otherwise, Tianxu Hall will attack our sect in three days.
There's no way we can resist them!
- Shut up!  - Master!
Sect Leader, it seems Tianxu Hall is coming for the spirit keys.
For now, our disciples are being controlled by the Kunyin Pill.
I think we should ask the other four sects for help.
Since our sect has taken the pill,
how can we ask for their help?
But we can't bow down to evil.
We can only solve this problem by fighting to the death.
Ming Di, get ready for war.
[Cloudless Breeze Hall]
Linglong!
Linglong, let me explain, please.
- There's nothing to explain.  - Can you stop being so stubborn?
Yes, I am stubborn.
Linglong!
She runs around whenever she's mad.
Kid, why are you here alone?
- What's wrong?  - Sister, I live on the mountain.
My father is sick. I came down to pick some herbs.
But I can't go back because I've sprained my foot.
Father must be very worried, but it hurts so much!
Don't cry. I'll get you home, okay?
You're not a bad person, are you?
Father said there're demons who trick children
by turning themselves into beautiful sisters.
I'm not a demon. I'll take you home, okay?
Come.
You're quite heavy.
Anyway, where's your home?
It's in the forest ahead.
That's a demon spirit.
Linglong.
Linglong. Wake up, Linglong.
Something's wrong with this rain.
Linglong, let's get out of here.
Yu'er, someone's trying to seize my prey.
That gives us one more prey.
Minyan!
Chu Xuanji.
What?
Have you recovered?
It's time to set off for Xuanyuan Sect.
Sifeng, I've got a stomachache.
I can't get up. Let's not go to Xuanyuan Sect today.
We'll do it tomorrow.
You can't feel pain, can you?
I'm not feeling well
and I feel weak.
Sifeng, since I can't get up,
let's just go there tomorrow.
Are you not feeling well?
All the more reason why we should go there.
Let Sect Leader Zhu Shi check on you.
We can't delay it.
I'm not going!
Sifeng! Sifeng!
- Sifeng.  - What's the matter?
I saw Linglong and Minyan had gone out in the early morning.
I thought they'd be back very soon.
But it's already noon and they aren't back yet.
What did you say? They've been out since this morning?
Sifeng, did something happen to them?
Let's go look for them.
Shaoyang Sect is really something.
He was hugging you yesterday night,
and he's run away with your older sister this morning.
Sifeng, I think we should stay out of this.
Let's settle the problem of the Aoyin Band first.
No, I don't find this urgent at all.
Ruo Yu, which direction did they go?
They went in the direction of the forest, the west of Longshu Town.
Forest?
Are Linglong and Sixth Senior in there?
Sixth Senior left this secret mark with his Cangming Sword.
Is Linglong with him? Are they in danger?
This is a strange place. Let's look separately for them.
Sifeng, are you all right?
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
It's not me.
Why are we back here?
Are we going around in circles?
Sifeng.
What's wrong, Sifeng?
Yanran.
Ruo Yu.
What's going on?
Sifeng. Sifeng!
The four idiots have taken the bait.
Let's take them back and feed on their blood.
Sifeng!
Wake up, Sifeng.
Sifeng.
Sifeng. Sifeng!
What do I do?
Let's try Sifeng's Antipoison Pill.
It should be okay to have one.
This doesn't seem to be it.
This should be it.
♫  Back then our love did not end  ♫
♫  We are able to encounter again in this life;As we journey through this mortal affairs  ♫
♫  As we journey through this mortal affairs  ♫
What are you doing?
I gave you water and medicine.
Here's what happened, Sifeng.
You got caught in the rain in that forest,
and you lost your consciousness and couldn't wake up.
I found this Antipoison Pill with you.
I thought you'd get well by having it.
Don't get mad, please.
I'm glad that you're up.
You gave me this?
Isn't this the Antipoison Pill?
It's not.
This is the Truth Pill.
It took Lizhe Palace hundreds of years to come up with one.
How could you waste such a precious thing?
Did...
Did I give you the wrong pill?
Will it affect you?
You fool.
Of course, it'll affect me.
- Then... This...  - Fool?
Is the Truth Pill starting to take effect?
Oh no!
I'm in trouble.
You're right.
I'm a fool.
And I always cause trouble for you.
That's why you're avoiding me.
No. I've never seen you as a burden,
and I've never thought of avoiding you.
In my heart,
I've always wanted to be with you.
Really?
- Then why did you...  - Forget about the past.
I'm telling the truth.
Don't you know what you gave me?
I...
I gave you the Truth Pill.
Are you telling the truth, Sifeng?
Yes.
I'll answer your questions with truths.
From now on, stop talking to me.
Sifeng, why can't I talk to you?
Because you don't want to tell me the truth, do you?
Did you lie to me?
That's right. I wasn't telling the truth.
Chu Xuanji, don't go too far.
I won't.
I just want to know
if you meant it when you said that you don't want to see me
and refuse to be my friend?
That's not the truth!
Ever since I met you,
I've been lying to myself.
I want to see you so badly.
You're my most important friend and I don't want to lose you.
I knew it. You haven't changed, Sifeng.
But, Sifeng,
why did you say that we should stay away from each other?
If you ever fall in love again,
the Lover's Curse will grow in your body.
There'll be three Green Feather marks on your wrist.
Whenever you get hurt by love,
each Green Feather mark will turn into a Red Feather on your chest.
When all three Green Feather marks turn into Red Feather marks,
your blood will flow backward. And you'll die.
Because...
Because... Because I...
I...
Because of what?
Say it.
Sifeng.
Because...
Go ahead.
Say it, Sifeng. I want to hear the truth.
Because...
Because it's none of your business.
Sifeng, has the pill's effect gone away?
Why so soon?
I should've asked you more questions.
That's very inappropriate of you.
Was it inappropriate?
Now that I know the truth, you can't lie to me anymore.
I think we should be concerned about the others.
The rain in the forest is probably strange.
It makes one lose consciousness.
It gives one a hallucination and makes him succumb to them.
Maybe it's because I wasn't born with six senses.
This rain doesn't affect me.
Who's that?
Xuanji?
Sifeng?
I knew it. Demon spirits wait for humans to lose their will
before capturing them with the blood vine.
Linglong, that's smart of you.
You kept yourself out of the rain with this farmer's hat.
Do you know the whereabouts of Minyan and the others?
I can't find Little Six anywhere.
And I don't know what this demon spirit is up to.
But I saw someone being hanged upon a tree.
Judging from his outfit, he seemed to come from a nearby village.
It seemed that he was hanged to death without any struggle.
Are Sixth Senior, Ruo Yu, and Yanran in grave danger?
He's hanged on a tree with a vine.
Did you see anything else on the tree?
Nothing at all.
Sifeng, do you have any clue?
The vine.
The bewitching rain.
That reminds me of something.
- What is it?  - Jialuo blood vine.
It can release a kind of bewitching rain
which gives humans hallucinations.
It then wraps itself around them and drinks their blood.
It eventually bears Jialuo blood fruits.
The fruit can make a cultivator powerful.
Someone is coveting blood fruits.
That's why he planted the blood vine.
That means they're going to drink Little Six's blood.
- What do we do?  - Don't panic.
Linglong, we can't delay anymore.
Let's make some farmer's hats first.
They can keep us dry. We'll go look for them afterward.
Do you remember you once told me that you'll dote on me,
love me, and adore me?
I do.
Do you remember you told me on our wedding day
that I'd always be your only one?
I do.
But now you're lying to me! You're hurting me!
- Are you an unfaithful man?  - Yes.
Since you know you're unfaithful, what should you do?
I should take my own life.
Fine, do it here then.
Your daughter is here, Father.
Father.
Your daughter is here.
Daughter? But I don't have a daughter.
Don't you remember, Father?
You gave me away to the hunter family when I was born.
On my fifth birthday,
I found out that I'm not their biological daughter.
That's why I looked forward to celebrating my birthdays with you
and receiving a birthday cake from you.
But you never came.
For my seventh birthday,
I got myself a piece of birthday cake with the apricots that I picked.
But the hunter's child bullied me.
He seized my cake and threw mud on it.
He called me a parentless brute.
I cried for help.
But everyone stayed out of it.
And I saw you peeking outside the courtyard.
I cried out loud for your help.
But you're like others.
You just stayed out of it.
Do you remember it now?
I do.
Do you deserve to be my father?
I don't.
Then tell me, what should you do?
I should take my own life.
Do it with this scarf then.
Little Six!
Little Six! Little Six!
It's not him.
We must find Sixth Senior and the others now.
I remember this tree.
We went this way. Why are we back here?
Is it a hallucination?
It's not. Because the trees are moving.
Moving? How could the trees be moving?
- This...  - There's only one tree that moves.
It's called the Migu tree.
I read about it from the Demon Manual.
Jialuo blood vines and Migu trees grow together.
They reinforce and resist one another.
Are these all Migu trees?
No, there's only one.
There's only one Migu tree every hundred miles.
This forest is just its imaginary root
and the real Migu tree contains spiritual power.
The blood vine covets the power.
Thus, it wraps its root around the real Migu tree.
The blood vine loves blood.
Let me lure it here with my blood.
I have spiritual powers, too.
Surely it'll drag me to the real tree.
You just remember where I'll be dragged to.
That won't do.
I know you're eager to save them.
I've got an idea.
Look over there.
Those are rain butterflies.
We just need to make the Migu tree bloom
and let the rain butterflies smell the flowers.
They'll lead us to the main tree.
And we'll get rid of the root of the blood vine and save them.
But it's obvious that the tree isn't blooming.
That's why the rain butterflies are all here.
The Migu tree has a special characteristic.
It loves songs. They make it bloom.
Their spiritual powers are not bad.
The blood fruits smell nice.
This should do.
It worked.
Xuanji, here.
- You're up.  - Linglong, great. You're all right.
Of course, I'm all right. I saved you after all.
Can you get up?
Both of these blood fruits are wasted.
Pay with your lives!
Watch out, everyone!
Watch out!
Linglong!
Sifeng!
Let go of Sifeng! Come at me!
Sifeng.
Sifeng. Wake up, Sifeng.
Sifeng! Wake up.
Are you all right?
Sifeng.
Sifeng! Sifeng! Wake up!
You shouldn't be here. Why don't you wake up?
What are you afraid of?
Why don't you look at me?
Are you afraid of me?
Sifeng, look.
I'm here. Wake up and you'll see me.
Sifeng, I'm here to save you.
I'm right here!
Sifeng.
I'm all right. Use the Five Elements Spell to summon the Golden Touch.
Dragon Cut!
Whenever you get hurt by love,
each Green Feather mark will turn into a Red Feather on your chest.
When all three Green Feather marks turn into Red Feather marks,
your blood will flow backward and you'll die.
Sifeng.
We're saved.
Yes, we're saved.
Xuanji!
- Linglong!  - Sifeng!
Are you all right? How are you?
- Xuanji! Are you all right?  - Linglong!
- I'm okay. - Did... Did you...
This isn't the place to talk.
We'll deal with those demon spirits first. Let's go.
Demon spirits are formless. Quickly use the Demon Slayer Charm.
We're in the middle of nowhere. Where can we get the charm?
I have it.
It's you! Your formation has killed many!
I'm going to kill you in the name of God!
Please spare her!
Who are you?
Wait! This is my friend.
Eldest Brother Liu, what's wrong with you?
Little Phoenix, it's a long story.
It's all her fault. Admit that you're wrong.
It's none of your business!
None of my business?
If I hadn't saved you from the bad guys,
you'd be hiding from me, wouldn't you?
And they controlled and made you hurt people again.
If I hadn't gotten here in time, you'd be dead by now!
You're so annoying, Old Man!
I'm a good-looking and charismatic young man.
And you called me an old man?
Eldest Brother Liu, is this Yu'er?
Sifeng, who is this Eldest Brother Liu?
Why is he on this demon spirit's side?
We're from the same sect. He's my senior.
Little Phoenix, you need not cover up for me.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Liu Yihuan, the abandoned disciple of Lizhe Palace.
I see.
Eldest Brother, what's your relationship with this demon spirit?
This is my daughter.
Her name is Yu'er.
Your daughter?
She's a demon spirit.
You seem very young. She doesn't look like your daughter.
- Did you...  - Don't misunderstand me.
It's just that I take good care of myself.
As for Yu'er, she's really just half-demon.
She had an accident some time ago
and she died and became a demon spirit.
She's a naughty and immature kid. I apologize.
Anyway, an eye for an eye.
Your daughter has killed many people. She should be executed.
That won't do!
She's died once. She can't die again.
You gave birth to her with a demon.
That's irrational of you.
And it's wicked of you that you let your daughter hurt people.
You're so irrational and wicked.
Even though you're a friend of Sifeng, we're not going to help you!
That's very rude of you, Miss!
Moreover, she didn't mean to hurt them.
Look.
Do you see it?
This... This is the charm used to control demon spirits.
Someone is controlling these demon spirits.
They're forced to do evil and grow Jialuo blood fruits.
Yu'er, tell me. Who forced you to do this?
I'll teach him a lesson.
Say it.
- I'm not going out!  - What's wrong?
Help me, please! Help me, please!
What's going on?
Someone has summoned her back.
I can still smell the aura of those demon spirits.
They're not far from here. Let's go after them.
Let's go!
The blood fruits have all been used up.
Give me yours.
There're some troublemakers in the forest.
They've ruined the blood vine.
Please have mercy on me and give me some time.
What did you say?
Give you more time?
Who would give me mine?
If there's no blood fruit, I'll use you to cultivate my pill!
Over there!
Let me go!
Help!
Help! Help!
You...
It's Elder Ling Shi of Xuanyuan Sect.
Don't you ruin my plan!
My pill. My pill!
As a sect elder,
how could you control the demon spirits and kill the innocent?
You've gone astray!
It's too late. There's no blood fruit left.
There's no blood fruit left!
He won't tell the truth because he's been bewitched by evil.
We're juniors.
- There's none left.  - There's nothing we can do.
Instead, we should let Elder Zhu Shi interrogate him.
That's a very strong demonic aura.
Watch out, everyone!
Xuanji, are you all right?
Sifeng, you're bleeding.
Just a small scratch. It's nothing serious.
- Sifeng!  - It's nothing serious.
Sifen, why do you risk your life for her?
Lu Yanran, stop talking nonsense.
I'm worried about you!
Why do you risk your life for Chu Xuanji?
- I...  - Little Six.
Little Six, don't scare me!
Or I'll tell Father on you!
Wake up, Little Six!
Don't scare me!
Minyan,
you frightened me.
Linglong...
were you crying for me?
No.
The wind made my eyes water.
We feel the same way about each other. Why don't you admit it?
You must have injured your head.
That's why you mistook me for Xuanji.
I, Zhong Minyan, only care about Chu Linglong.
I'm not apologizing.
You feel the same way about me. Why don't you admit it?
We care about each other.
Can we stop lying to ourselves?
You confessed to my sister
and now you're doing this to me. Are you making fun of us sisters?
If you let Xuanji down, I'll kill you.
Linglong.
Xuanji, let's make things clear today.
- I...  - Min Yan.
You should think before you say it.
- What do you mean?  - You've upset, Xuanji.
If you don't care about Xuanji's feelings, I won't forgive you.
Eldest Brother Liu,
are you all right?
Yu'er is all right.
That's Xuanji.
You're stubborn, indeed.
Sifeng!
Sifeng, why is everyone upset?
Why did Linglong fight with Sixth Senior again?
You really live up to your name.
I've heard and seen it all.
They're upset because of you.
- Eldest Brother Liu.  - I...
This is an urgent situation.
Let's find Yu'er's charm stone first.
That's right, Old Man. Stop minding other people's business.
Yes, the charm stone.
It's an explosion. Surely it'll still be in there.
Let's go.
Sifeng, I...
Eldest Brother Liu.
This is it. The charm stone that controlled the demon spirits.
Yes, this is it. Break it and Yu'er will be free.
Wait.
This demon spirit has hurt many. We can't let her go just like this.
A demon spirit was born a demon.
According to the rule of five sects, we can't just let her go.
Yu'er made the mistake because she was forced by Elder Ling Shi.
Now that Ling Shi has runoff and other demon spirits are dead.
There's no reason for us to kill Yu'er. She's one of the victims, after all.
Sifeng is right.
Demon spirits made up of the remaining spiritual power of demons.
They've died once.
If we kill them again, there's no way for them to turn good.
I don't see it as a righteous act.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
''Lover's Curse'' - Singer: Ayanga and Yu Kewei
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until  you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫