''Colored Glass'' - Singer: Liu Yuning
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stablizing the earth, the dragon enters the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven  ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path; Nature, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫  Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart;  I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds; Six paths, Nine Heavens, A promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness,  I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE NINE]
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
You're wearing this mask because of me.
But don't worry. I'll find a way to remove the Lover's Curse Mask for you.
I told you before. This was my decision.
Eldest Brother Liu, you don't need to blame yourself.
To become emotionless and focus on my training is a good thing as well.
How is that a good thing?
Our training is hard enough by itself.
But now, you have to force yourself to be emotionless as well.
That'll make your life meaningless, you know?
It's not a good thing.
It's fine. Don't worry.
I'll definitely find a solution for you.
By the way,
come out now.
Come out.
I'll return you your spirit beast.
Ascending the Heavenly Realm was tough indeed.
Little Silver Flower, you were naughty.
Thank you, Eldest Brother Liu.
Why are you thanking me?
Okay. I'll leave now.
Xuanji, are you done with your training?
Linglong, isn't this the bell Sifeng gave you?
I'm sure you kept in touch, right? How is he doing?
Senior Brother Hao Chen confiscated
everything I had when I went to Xuyang Peak.
That's why I didn't contact him for four years.
You didn't contact him at all?
Xuanji, before Sifeng left, he wanted you to contact him once you woke up, you know?
Besides, even if he did confiscate everything,
you could still write him letters.
Write letters?
I was busy with my training every day.
I never thought about that.
You're too heartless. Did you forget him already?
And you never contacted me as well after you went to Xuyang Peak.
I would've severed my ties with you if you weren't my sister.
Linglong, how could that be? I missed you so much.
But I think it's fine if I keep you all in my heart.
Besides, sisters and our friends will stay with us forever. Right?
Initially, I wanted to finish my training
as soon as possible so that I could meet up with you sooner.
The same goes for Sifeng as well. We made a promise.
We'll train together once I leave the mountain.
That's why I didn't contact him for four years.
That doesn't matter, right?
But, Xuanji, you need to maintain your relationships.
No one will wait at the same spot for you.
I thought you would've learned about other things besides your training.
I didn't expect you to still be a blockhead in relationships.
Linglong, will Sifeng be angry because I didn't contact him?
Will he ignore me?
About that, I can't say for sure.
I'm sure he won't do that. Sifeng must be very busy in Lize Palace.
He needs to train as well.
I'm sure he forgot about this due to his busy schedule.
It's fine. I'll find him immediately after we leave,
and the four of us can roam the world together.
I'm sure it will be fun.
Have some fruit wine.
Great wine.
Xuanji, I didn't ask this before because it was inconvenient.
Did you find any shards when you went to Xuyang Peak?
It's fine. Maybe we can find them when we roam around.
Sixth Senior, I'll stop finding them.
Senior Brother Hao Chen told me that everyone has a different purpose in life
and I should treat it as such.
I should be protecting the Crystal Lamp
instead of searching for shards of the Mirror of Origin in order to recover my six senses.
What if I become obsessed with it?
Is that so?
Did the strange power appear again during your training?
That's good. We won't look for it then.
Oh right, Sixth Senior Brother! I have some good stuff for you.
There's an immortal tree on Xuyang Peak. Its fruit is delicious,
but it only bears fruit once every five years.
That's why I've saved some for you, Linglong, and Sifeng.
You little glutton. You actually saved some for us?
Not bad at all. Seems like my efforts were not in vain.
You're unlike your sister at all.
I have no idea what she's thinking about.
Minyan!
Linglong is going to dance with a fellow male disciple!
Sixth Senior Brother, what about this?
Xuanji, your senior doesn't like to drink and eat fruit.
I'll take them for myself.
I...
Hall Master, after the failure of Shadow Demon in Shaoyang Sect,
we've planted spies in the four sects successfully.
But due to Shadow Demon's failure
and to avoid any further suspicions, I think we should
stay in the shadows for now.
We should wait for the right time to grab the Spirit Keys.
We still need to wait? How long do I need to wait?
Hall Master, we...
Who's there?
You didn't manage to locate
the God of War and the Devil Star all these few years,
and you didn't obtain the Spirit Keys as well.
Wolf, aren't you too merciful?
Isn't that the reason you got nothing done at all?
Wu Tong, do you think you have the right to speak in this place?
Our Hall Master is keeping you here
because he just wanted you to tell us more about the Five Great Sects.
Just be a good dog.
When you're a dog,
you shouldn't just come out and bark like this.
Tianxu Hall only appreciates capable people.
Those who get nothing done should just keep quiet.
Wolf, what do you think?
I just didn't want to reveal our true strength too soon.
Hall Master, I just wanted to avoid casualties
from dealing with the Five Great Sects.
The demon tribe has been training in secret for 1,000 years.
Your strength is much greater than the Five Great Sects.
If they aren't willing to cooperate with us,
it's the best excuse for us to execute them without mercy.
Why should we hide?
You're just trying to get your revenge against the humans who had driven you out.
Wu Tong, don't try to manipulate us due to your personal hatred.
It's precisely because of that.
Only a human knows how to force another human to submit,
to manipulate and destroy them.
Hall Master, why don't you give me this chance?
I'll destroy the Five Great Sects and obtain the Spirit Keys.
Hall Master, Wu Tong is just a dog who has been driven out from its shelter.
We mustn't trust him.
But this pathetic dog managed to find out that the Xuanyuan Sect is lying to you.
- What?  - Someone!
You were misled by Xuanyuan Sect's spirit stone all along.
One of the Spirit Keys was actually hidden inside the Destiny Pearl.
You didn't know about that.
Tell us.
Yes!
The Spirit Key is hidden inside the Destiny Pearl in our sect.
But only Sect Leader Zhu Shi knows about
the location of the Destiny Pearl.
Wolf, you chose the wrong person to threaten.
Instead of threatening those who are loyal to the sect,
isn't it easier for you if you threaten the weaklings in the sect?
Darn it.
Hall Master, please give me a chance.
Let me obtain the Spirit Keys for you.
We've been hiding for too long.
It's time to create a scene so that our prey will be attracted.
Wu Tong, from today onwards,
you'll be the Chief of Mount Buzhou's hideout.
The Five Great Sects can't reach Mount Buzhou.
You don't need to fear anything.
You don't need to fear the Five Great Sects.
You can use any method to obtain the Spirit Keys.
Yes, Hall Master.
Tianxu Hall has been in the shadows for too long.
It's time for us to make an entrance.
Greetings, Master and Deputy Chief.
Sifeng, you've mastered your skill.
I'm very relieved to hear that.
You were always the most talented.
As long as you aren't distracted and focus on your training,
I'm sure you'll be the leader of the Five Great Sects.
You'll take over Lize Palace sooner or later.
Master, your effort wasn't wasted.
It's good that you forced him to choose this mask.
Yu Sifeng, you mustn't disappoint your master
and repeat the same mistakes.
Let bygones be bygones.
Just forget about them.
I'm just reminding him.
Although the Lover's Curse Mask can render him emotionless
and stop him from having any feelings,
if he faces a situation where he can't control himself
and feels for someone,
a Lover's Curse will form and he'll be done for.
You only talk about useless things.
Sifeng, you do understand the purpose of the Lover's Curse Mask. Right?
By getting rid of emotions, it will save us from unnecessary trouble.
That's good to hear.
And you must remember that
outsiders are just like mirages.
Your only home is Lize Palace.
- Yes, My Lord...  - I'm not finished yet.
All of you mustn't risk your lives for an illusion
that you cannot hold and create unnecessary trouble.
- Yes, Master.  - Yes, Master.
That's enough.
Let's return to the main point.
- Deputy Chief.  - Regarding leaving Lize Palace for training.
Do you understand what to do? Once you exit the palace tomorrow,
you should never break the rules.
I've received letters from Shaoyang Sect.
They stated that some demons are causing trouble outside.
Coincidentally, you will leave the palace soon.
Investigate the matter as well.
Those demons have nothing to do with us.
They can't reach Xiyang on either side.
If they want to create trouble in Zhongyuan, just let them be.
Senior Brother, you're ignoring everything except for our sect,
but you must respect the other sect leaders as well.
Since we belong to one of the Five Great Sects.
You make the decision.
Investigate the matter.
Yes.
Xuanji, you have the Transmission Charm with you.
Do you know your task when you leave the mountain?
- What's my task?  - Silly Xuanji.
Senior Brother Hao Chen wants you to write letters to him.
But Senior Brother Hao Chen, we'll be busy when we leave.
She'll think it's troublesome,
or maybe she'll forget about it.
Remember to write letters to me.
You're pure and innocent. You haven't recovered your six senses.
The outside world is complex and chaotic.
I was reluctant to let you go,
but I have to abide by the rules.
If not...
So, after you leave,
you need to report to me every single detail.
First, you can reflect on your progress.
Second, I can know your progress as well.
Do you understand?
Yes, Senior Brother Hao Chen.
You must be careful.
You two must remember this.
After you two leave the mountain, you must deal with situations
according to your own capability.
You two mustn't be reckless.
Xuanji, remember to listen to your sixth senior brother.
Linglong, you must control your temper as well.
Father, I know that.
It's the first time you two are leaving here.
Your father is worried.
You must remember his words.
Yes, I'll remember them. I'll leave now.
You!
This child...
Father, Aunt Ying Hong, Senior Brother Hao Chen.
Don't worry. We know what to do.
Master, Aunt Ying Hong. Don't worry.
I'll take good care of them.
Linglong, wait for us!
Linglong! Wait for me!
This is so beautiful! We finally left the mountain!
This is too beautiful!
Senior Brother Hao Chen, we had another uneventful day.
Today, Sixth Senior Brother ordered a dish that was not tasty
at a restaurant on Mount Mengxi.
It's not delicious?
Fine, we won't order that tomorrow.
We can save some money as well.
This is great!
We'll go to Xishu tomorrow. There are many delicious foods over there.
There are pork trotter jelly, cold noodles, and peppered chicken.
You're going to finish our money soon.
We can only depend on Sifeng in Lize Palace later on.
We've been out for seven days,
but there are no demons to be seen.
I don't feel like a hero at all.
Look at the letters Xuanji wrote for Senior Brother Hao Chen.
I'm so happy today. I've eaten a lot today.
Okay, we've finished our mission for today.
- Let's go.  - Okay.
Senior Brother Hao Chen, we had another uneventful day.
Today, Sixth Senior Brother ordered a dish that was not tasty
at a restaurant on Mount Mengxi.
It's lucky that the vegetables were delicious.
I'm happy today.
Where are we? We should ask someone.
Excuse me.
Sorry for the interruption.
Judging by your attire, I'm sure you are cultivators.
Do you know how long it will take for us to reach Mount Shaoyang?
Mister, are you going to Mount Shaoyang because there are demons around?
Yes.
We came from Wangxian Town.
Demons are wreaking havoc in our town these days.
They cried in the middle of the night.
All of us were too afraid to go out.
This situation has lasted for three months. This can't continue on.
After that, a wandering priest told us that
Shaoyang Sect is famous for slaying demons.
That's why we're trying to seek their help.
Wangxian Town?
We need to pass by there before we reach Lize Palace and Xuanyuan Sect.
We can meet Sifeng after we slay the demons.
This is great! We finally have demons to slay!
Mister, we have decided to slay the demons for you.
But...
You three are... ?
We're members of the Shaoyang Sect.
This is our name tag.
Mister, please tell us more about the demons.
We will try our best to help.
I think you are too young.
These two ladies look very fresh and innocent.
I think you shouldn't sacrifice your lives for this.
I think we should seek your master's help instead.
- Goodbye.  - Wait!
Mister, wait a minute.
We may look young, but we're famous in the pugilist world.
Especially this girl.
She may look weak and feeble,
but she can slay dozens of demons at one go.
Dozens of demons?
- They're pretty good.  - Sixth Senior Brother,
since when could I slay dozens of demons?
You defeated Shadow Demon and his clones, right?
That's a different matter!
This is a rare chance. We should grab hold of it.
I'm her senior.
As for her, she's not important.
Little Six!
We came down the mountain in order to slay demons.
You don't need to travel far to seek help.
Since that's the case, please help us out.
In Wangxian Town, there's Mount Haiwan.
On that mountain, there's a grass called Zhuyu Grass.
And only our town has that grass.
But the strange thing is it can't be planted.
It can only grow on its own.
But three months ago,
some of our townsfolk went to pick some Zhuyu Grass.
But all of them were devoured by demons.
After that, some brave youngsters went up the mountain as well.
But they never came back.
Mister, do you have any idea what the demon looks like?
The demon always assaulted people from the back.
That's why nobody has seen their true face.
I have a grandson who only learned how to speak recently.
Two days ago, he said he saw a demon that cried.
It cries, it has two huge talons, and it can fly as well.
But he's just a child. I don't think we should treat this seriously.
It has wings,
and it cries as well?
Isn't that scary?
Linglong, look.
From the Demon Manual, a demon who cries and has wings.
- It is a Quru Bird?  - Quru Bird?
But it doesn't state that the demon likes to eat Zhuyu Grass.
Is it possible that someone is behind this
in order to obtain more provisions?
Since that's the case, we must act now.
Let's check it out.
We must be cautious later on.
It's just a Quru Bird.
Since it likes to eat, I'll give it a taste of my power.
I'm sure there are more than one of them. We must be careful.
Even ten of them won't scare me away.
It's really desolate here.
Of course. There are demons roaming around.
The Zhuyu Grass is pretty fragrant.
Linglong, it's such a waste since Zhuyu Grass is delicious.
Xuanji, it's dirty, you know? Why are you eating it?
- Linglong, it's delicious. Try it.  - No way.
- Sixth Senior Brother?  - I'll skip this time.
Silly girl.
Linglong, look.
The cuts are uneven.
I don't think this is caused by something sharp.
It looks like it was ripped.
You're right.
Look here.
Seems like we're facing a tough demon.
Little Six, why are you so timid?
- You're afraid of this?  - You!
I smell a demon.
Watch out!
- It's the Quru Bird!  - It has escaped!
Let's chase after it!
What a strong demonic scent!
I smell that, too. It's thick and disgusting.
It stinks!
It's dark down there. We don't have a clear view.
- Xuanji!  - Linglong, be careful!
Linglong, are you okay?
I'm fine. You must be careful.
- Little Six!  - Linglong!
Linglong, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Be careful!
- Xuanji!  - Xuanji!
Sifeng?
Sifeng!
- Xuanji!  - Xuanji!
Xuanji!
Why are you bleeding?
I'm fine.
Silly girl, you're not fine.
I'm Ruo Yu from Lize Palace.
Greetings.
Sifeng will return later, right?
Miss, Sifeng is...
We're his friends. This is great.
I didn't expect to see him here.
You said you were his friends?
That is bizarre.
What's bizarre?
I heard that the members of
Lize Palace weren't supposed to make friends with outsiders. Right?
But Sifeng is different from others.
- There are no exceptions.  - Sifeng is an exception.
Sifeng!
Did you capture it?
The Quru Bird fled because it was frightened.
It fled?
It's all because of you three!
- You!  - Save your breath.
Ruo Yu, let's go.
Sifeng!
Sifeng, is this really you?
You got yourself a new mask.
I almost couldn't recognize you.
I thought my skills would've been better after four years.
I thought I could protect everyone.
But I didn't expect you to improve this much.
You saved me once again.
Quru Birds hunt in groups.
We need a tactic to hunt them down.
Next time, you better prepare yourselves.
Don't create trouble for other people.
Sifeng, my brother, long time no see.
Sifeng, it's been four years since we have met.
We wanted to find you in Lize Palace.
Let go! All of you, stay away from Sifeng!
You're rude! Who exactly are you?
That is none of your concern.
Please calm down.
She is Miss Lu Yanran from Dianjing Valley Sect.
She was separated from her friends.
That's why she's traveling with us.
- We...  - We're not here to save you.
We prepared an ambush for the demons.
We were waiting for them to return to their nest.
But you just came and went all out on them.
And that messed up our plan.
How would we know you had a plan?
You speak as if this is our fault.
Wasn't it your fault?
Sifeng, since we didn't manage to find their nest,
we should return to our inn and rest.
Sure! Where are you staying? We can stay together
and we can travel together afterward.
We're not going on the same path.
Miss Xuanji, first, we need to help Miss Lu find her friends.
So, it's inconvenient for us to travel together.
Please forgive us.
Save your breath. Let's go.
Sifeng, are you leaving us?
We missed you.
And we've finally met after so long. Please don't leave.
That's right. Why are you leaving us?
Sifeng, are you angry at us because Xuanji
didn't contact you at all?
Yes. Linglong said you must've been waiting for my news.
Sifeng, I'm sorry. It's my fault.
- But the Transmission Bell...  - No.
I lost mine as well.
It's a useless item.
That's good. I knew it.
Sifeng, you were so busy.
There's no need for us to contact each other, right?
- Since we'll meet anyway.  - I'm busy, indeed.
I won't waste any time here.
- Sifeng!  - Everyone, farewell for now.
- Xuanji!  - Xuanji!
- Xuanji, what's wrong?  - Xuanji!
What's going on?
Xuanji was poisoned.
Wait, Quru Birds aren't poisonous.
Sifeng, seems like Miss Xuanji has a serious injury.
We...
Are we going to leave them, for real?
Sifeng, I heard that your sect are experts in neutralizing poison.
Are you really going to ignore her?
Little Six, will Xuanji be fine?
But the Demon Manual stated that Quru Birds aren't poisonous.
How did this happen?
You're right.
That's why we suspect that someone is manipulating them
and the manipulator must've applied poison to their talons.
We would've captured that demon if it weren't for someone.
But in the end? We're stuck here because of them.
Such bad luck.
What do you mean by that? Sifeng is our old friend.
We will travel together sooner or later.
And we still have plenty of things to catch up on as well.
You can leave if you don't want to stay.
You are thinking too much.
Sifeng has nothing to catch up with you.
Didn't you see that? He ignored you just now.
- You!  - To me, you are here because the Quru Birds are too strong
and you wanted to seek Sifeng's help to defeat them.
- You!  - Some people are useless by themselves.
That's why they want to seek help from Lize Palace.
I–
What?
Stop it now.
Sifeng.
Sifeng, don't leave.
Sifeng, don't leave me.
I have just neutralized the poison.
You better not move around.
Sifeng, I know you're angry.
I was too dumb.
When I went to Xuyang Peak for my training with Senior Brother Hao Chen,
he confiscated the Transmission Bell you gave me
because he didn't want me to be distracted.
And I didn't think of other ways I could use to contact people.
That's why I didn't write one letter to Linglong nor Sixth Senior Brother.
Linglong was very angry with me.
You don't need to explain that to me.
It's fine even if we didn't contact each other.
Sifeng, why are you still trying to leave?
We wanted to find you in Lize Palace initially.
Isn't it a great thing when we meet each other here?
Why are you still insisting on leaving?
Why must we stay together?
Because we made a promise.
The four of us are going to travel together, right?
So childish.
Is that so?
But after that, I realized that
nothing is permanent in this world.
Same goes for a friend's promise.
Sifeng, I don't understand.
- Initially...  - I did promise you
that I'd find the Mirror of Origin with you initially.
And I will keep my promise.
I obtained one shard by accident.
Here.
Sifeng, I didn't mean that.
And regarding the Mirror of Origin,
I don't need it anymore.
Senior Brother Hao Chen said that I will become obsessed
with desire and greed if I search for it.
It's not good for my training.
So, I promised Senior Brother Hao Chen that I wouldn't search for it anymore
after I leave the mountain.
But Sifeng, I still need to thank you.
So, you don't want to recover your six senses anymore.
I was born without them.
I think it's fine even if I don't recover them.
They don't seem that important to me.
The current Chu Xuanji isn't that bad anyway. Am I right?
The human heart is indecisive and unstable.
I've witnessed it for myself.
Sifeng, what did you say?
Since it's useless to you,
that means we don't need to meet anymore.
Farewell.
Sifeng!
Sifeng, don't leave us!
- Sifeng!  - Xuanji.
Xuanji, why are you here?
Sifeng, did you neutralize the poison?
She can move after some rest.
You may leave after some time.
We'll handle the Quru Birds. Let's go.
- Wait, Sifeng!  - Sifeng.
What do you mean by this?
Aren't we your companions?
That's right. I thought we were going to capture them together.
There's no need for this many people. It's troublesome.
That's not the point.
Sifeng, I thought this was a happy occasion,
but why are you treating us like the plague?
You're trying to avoid us.
Sifeng, what's wrong with you?
Sifeng, there's no need for explanations.
Let's go.
Sifeng!
What's going on? Why are they approaching us?
There are so many of them!
There are too many of them!
Set up the barrier!
Why are there so many Quru Birds?
Didn't you say someone was manipulating them?
They're still not leaving even after the barrier was set up.
I'm afraid they're trying to trap us here.
You won't be trapped if you're capable enough to break through.
Hero Zhong, you're quite skilled
but it's hard when you have two amateurs around.
Stop looking down on us!
You can leave if you're that capable!
We'll deal with the birds and the demon once Xuanji recovers her strength.
Miss Lu, it's fine. We can escape by ourselves.
Silly girl, she's not saying that out of concern!
These Quru Birds all came out of their nests.
And their talons were coated with poison. It's too risky to try and break through.
Sifeng, what do you think?
We'll just destroy their nest then.
- Are you going to use that?  - We must deal with the mastermind first.
It's better for us to end this quickly as well.
Sifeng, what are you doing?
He's going to cast the secret spell of Lize Palace, Soul Chaser.
It can detect the location of the culprit behind this.
Inside the palace, among the stars,
chase the cursed soul, with the speed of the wind.
Search!
- Sifeng!  - Sifeng, are you okay?
To the west, there are ten caves.
Take the middle cave and you'll reach a valley.
The demon manipulating the birds is located there.
I've injured the demon and he can't move around.
You can go and capture him.
Sifeng, we'll let them go since they wish to capture it so badly.
Your breathing is a mess. You need to recuperate.
- I'll stay here and guard over you.  - No need.
That demon is quite powerful. All of you should go.
- But what if something...  - Stop wasting time!
If the demon flees, I'll blame it all on you.
Be careful then. Send us a signal if you're in danger.
Let's go.
- Sifeng, you...  - Xuanji, let's go.
I...
Sifeng, are you okay?
Why are you here?
I've thought about it. I can't leave you alone here.
I'll stay by your side until you get better.
No need.
Sifeng, you mustn't rush the recovery process.
Don't move. It's dangerous for you to activate your energy by force.
Sifeng, why is your breathing getting more and more unstable?
Do you feel uncomfortable? Are you in pain?
Why are you sweating so much?
This won't do. I need to transfer some of my energy to you.
- But your mask...  - Don't touch it!
- I want to help you.  - You're helping me by not touching it.
I knew it. Sifeng is still angry at me for not contacting him.
What should I do to appease him?
Oh right! What did Sixth Senior Brother do every time
he made Linglong angry?
Sifeng,
why are you sweating so much?
You'll catch a cold.
Here.
What are you doing?
Sifeng, I'm wiping away your sweat.
You'll catch a cold like this.
I'm not trying to scold you, but you're not taking care of yourself.
You can't do anything without me around.
My sweat is gone.
Sifeng, this dried fruit is very sweet.
I can't even bear to eat it. I kept it especially for you.
Try it.
Chu Xuanji, what exactly are you trying to do?
I... I'm trying to make you happy.
I'm trying to coax you.
Please don't be angry anymore.
Please don't hold it against me.
Sifeng.
Isn't this funny?
Sifeng, please smile.
You'll get younger when you smile.
Sifeng.
Chu Xuanji, that's enough.
Isn't this funny?
Never mind. I have another trick.
Sifeng, let me tell you a joke.
Listen closely.
Once, there was a phoenix who tried to attain nirvana.
Guess what happened in the end? Listen carefully.
It overheated!
Isn't that funny?
Sifeng, isn't that funny?
It's funny, right?
Answer me.
It's not funny?
I have another trick up my sleeve.
Sifeng, look.
I've hidden a treasure in one of my hands.
Take a guess. If you're correct, I'll give you the treasure.
You think it's this hand, right?
You're wrong. There's nothing inside.
Are you done?
Sifeng, don't be angry.
Although you're wrong, I hate it when our Sifeng gets angry.
So, even though you're wrong, I'll still give you the treasure.
Are they nice?
Sixth Senior used this trick every time Linglong was angry,
and he succeeded every time.
I like Sixth Senior.
Minyan?
You like Minyan?
Chu Xuanji, listen carefully.
I'm not angry.
You can stop your silly acts.
Sifeng, you're not angry?
Why are you acting like this then?
Why did you change so much?
You don't want us to be your friends anymore?
Do you hate me now?
The disciples of Lize Palace weren't supposed to have friends anyway.
There's nothing for me to like or hate.
Four years is a long time.
It's normal for people to grow and change.
There's no need to dwell on the past.
No, you weren't like this in the past.
We had plenty of things to talk about in the past, and many things we could share.
You taught me many things as well.
Sifeng, you even told me that
meeting me was the best thing that had happened in your life.
Although I was asleep, I did hear what you said.
I was rash then. I never think before I speak.
You mustn't hold it to your heart.
- It's meaningless.  - It's not.
The past you and everything you said,
all of them were meaningful to me.
I don't want our relationship to change.
Sifeng, I don't want to lose you.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫