Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  Explore the universe  ♫
♫  The sword brings forth a sandstorm  ♫
♫  Grasping the mortal's view through the sword's sheath  ♫
♫  Ask for the path through the maze  ♫
♫  Measuring the distance of Heaven and Earth  ♫
♫  Ruling over the wind and all creations, small and great  ♫
♫  My tears are as clear as colored glass  ♫
♫  Mercy, taking up arms prepare for war  ♫
♫  Stabilizing the earth, the dragon enters  the mountains and rivers  ♫
♫  Don't test me, enemies will not be forgiven  ♫
♫  Look at the degree of resentment on this path;Nature, Nirvana, how many cycles of reincarnation?  ♫
♫  Borrowing a few lives of sorrow and joy to refine my heart; I'll be brave, I'll love, be satisfied without regrets  ♫
♫  Numerous love tribulations, struggling against the three worlds, six paths, nine heavens; A promise till death do us part  ♫
♫  Even if I drank from the river of forgetfulness,  I will not forget our promise  ♫
[LOVE AND REDEMPTION]
[EPISODE 30]
Brother Tong!
If you dare hurt Minyan,
then I'll kill your beloved flower demon.
She's just a flower demon. You can take her life.
If I can create one Linglong,
then I can create many copies of her.
Brother Tong, save me!
Sixth Senior!
This is bad! Our Birth Candles were used up!
You know how to enter this place by using that item?
You are quite capable as well.
It's a pity that you don't have much time.
Now, half of your soul is in Mount Buzhou
while half of it is in the human realm.
Let me see how much power you have left.
Take them down!
This demon actually has a malignant aura?
It has tremendous power.
It isn't an ordinary demon.
He's aiming for Xuanji,
but he didn't extinguish Xuanji's Birth Candle.
What is he plotting?
Stop!
Let's stop fighting.
I admit my defeat.
Sixth Senior?
We don't have much time.
I want to exchange conditions with you.
Tianxu Hall wants the spirit keys, right?
As long as you're willing to give me Linglong's primordial spirit,
I'm willing to betray the Five Great Sects
and become your subordinate in Tianxu Hall.
I'll help you obtain all the spirit keys.
No! Sixth Senior, you mustn't do that!
Linglong wouldn't want you to do this!
What else can we do?
She can't afford to wait any longer.
Wu Tong, you're just angry over what happened in the past.
I'll stay here, and you can do whatever you want.
If you want me to be your dog,
I will.
Linglong, this man really loves you.
He loves me that much even though this is our first meeting.
Why don't you dig out his heart to see
if he's sincere or not?
That's a great idea.
I'll make you pay for your threats in the past.
Stop!
Brother Wu Tong?
Seems like he's sincere.
Why don't we let him stay and let him witness our love?
Isn't that more interesting?
I'll do anything for you as long as you return
Linglong's primordial spirit to us.
It's not that easy to get what you wish.
You want her primordial spirit? Fine.
Exchange it with another life.
Someone!
Second Senior!
Wu Tong, you scum! Do you think I'm afraid of you?
Kill me if you dare!
Fine. I'll grant you your wish.
Zhong Minyan, if you want to retrieve Linglong's primordial spirit,
you need to show some sincerity.
Kill him in front of me.
Sixth Senior, you mustn't do so.
If you can't kill him,
you won't be able to retrieve Linglong's primordial spirit.
Zhong Minyan, I'm an impatient man.
Minyan, it's a trap.
Don't believe him.
You mustn't do so.
I will surely save Linglong and Second Senior.
Do you think you can go back alive?
Look at how much time you have left.
Zhong Minyan, this is the Black and White Ring.
It's made from Xuanyin Steel and Mingyang Stone.
We need to wear this in order to stay in Mount Buzhou.
Will you be my dog in exchange for Chu Linglong's primordial spirit?
Or will you let both Chu Linglong and your second senior die together?
You make the choice.
- I'll stay.  - Sixth Senior!
Second Senior,
I'm sorry.
I can't save anyone
if I don't do this.
No.
No!
Second Senior!
You want me to kill my senior?
I can't bear to do so.
But I had cut off one of his arms.
That's enough, right?
I've hurt my senior.
I can't turn back now.
You believe in me now, right?
Fine.
I see your sincerity.
Here's Linglong's primordial spirit.
Xuanji!
Second Senior!
The Birth Candles are dying out. We should return soon.
What's going on?
Brother Wu Tong!
So, their Birth Candles were bound by the Binding Formation.
Their Birth Candles have extinguished,
and they can't enter or leave the place.
They will perish in Mount Buzhou.
If Xuanji dies there, it means she will fail her tribulation.
I mustn't let her die in Mount Buzhou.
God of War, you're powerful indeed.
It's a pity that you can't use your powers here.
You won't be able to escape, no matter how hard you fight.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything.
Someone else didn't want you to escape.
He has cut off your means of escape.
The Birth Candles have been extinguished.
Mortals can't last long in Mount Buzhou.
You can only stay here until you perish.
Zhong Minyan is smart.
He made the right decision to survive.
No.
I mustn't die here.
I'm willing to surrender to Tianxu Hall as well.
- Ruo Yu!  - Ruo Yu.
Don't try to persuade me.
I've lost my mask.
If I return to Lize Palace, I will face death.
Staying here is a better option.
At least I can still survive.
This is pretty interesting.
You want to stay? Fine.
You need to follow his steps.
Kill your own to show us your sincerity.
Kill them and retrieve the primordial spirit.
Ruo Yu, don't fall for it!
They want us to kill each other!
You are on the verge of death.
You should play your last act for me before you die.
Here.
Every man for himself.
Don't blame me for this.
Ruo Yu.
Sifeng! Sifeng!
Sifeng!
- Sifeng!  - Xuanji.
Sifeng! Sifeng!
Don't scare me, Sifeng!
You'll be fine, Sifeng!
Sifeng!
We'll definitely escape alive!
I will kill everyone who dares to hurt you!
Sifeng!
Sifeng, wake up! Look at me, Sifeng!
Sifeng, this can't be!
We're home now, Sifeng!
We're out, Sifeng!
Don't cry.
Sifeng!
Sifeng! No!
I'm here!
No!
Sifeng!
Please don't scare me, Sifeng!
Sifeng.
Sifeng!
Sifeng! Sifeng!
Please don't scare me, Sifeng!
Sifeng.
Sifeng!
No!
Look at me! Please don't scare me!
Senior Hao Chen? Please save Sifeng!
Senior, please save him!
Senior!
I beg you!
Xuanji, what exactly happened?
Where's Minyan and the rest?
Father.
Sifeng!
- Sifeng!  - Sifeng!
Aunt Hong, how's Sifeng?
How is he?
The person who struck him clearly wanted him to die.
The sword pierced his heart meridian.
Ordinary people would've been dead.
Sifeng survived due to his many years of training.
But he's just a human.
His heart meridian was pierced. It'll be hard for him to survive.
Now, the qi in his body is dissipating.
We can't stop that.
I'm afraid that he can't last for long.
This can't be. Sifeng, that can't happen.
Sifeng, this is not real.
- This can't be!  - Don't touch him!
You were the reason behind this!
Sifeng would never take the risk
in Mount Buzhou if it weren't for you!
He would've never been injured if he hadn't blocked the attack for you!
If you can't save him, I'll bring him back to Lize Palace.
- Sifeng!  - No!
He mustn't move in this condition.
Sifeng!
What should we do?
Don't tell me I can only watch him suffer like this?
What if I reverse my Yang Jue Skill and use it to protect his heart meridian?
Will he be saved if I do so?
You mustn't!
You can activate the Nine Cycles Spell
by using the Heartless Tactics in conjunction with the reverse Yang Jue Skill.
But it is very risky.
If anything goes wrong, your blood will flow in reverse.
Not only will you not be able to save him, but you'll also die as well.
What do you mean?
Sifeng is in this condition because of Chu Xuanji!
Why aren't you letting her do so when she has a way to save him?
Xuanji, our fate is predetermined.
- You mustn't force it.  - I will force it!
I will save him! Even when the possibility is close to nothing!
It's best if I can save him,
but if I can't save him, I'll die together with him.
Xuanji, stop messing around!
Don't stop me!
I'll do it.
I'll use the Nine Cycles Spell to save Yu Sifeng.
Hao Chen, you–
I'm better at Heartless Tactics and Yang Jue Skill compared with Xuanji.
It's more stable if I do that.
Senior Hao Chen, you don't need to do this.
You don't want me to save him?
Are you asking me to witness your death?
Yu Sifeng, it's fine if just you die like this.
But you've caught Xuanji in your love web.
If anything happens to you
and Xuanji harbors anguish because of this,
even a million deaths are not enough for you to atone for it.
Today, I may save you,
but next time, I'll show you my true colors.
Senior Hao Chen, how's Sifeng?
You've sustained internal injuries.
Why didn't you tell us before you did that?
Senior Hao Chen, when did you get hurt?
While I was searching for you, I saw a suspicious demon at the altar
and I was struck by his malignant aura.
But it's fine. I know my own condition.
Xuanji, Hao Chen was hurt because of your reckless actions.
- Sorry, Senior. I—  - I said it's fine.
You don't need to worry.
It's just that the attributes of
Lize Palace and Shaoyang Sect are different.
The Yang Jue qi that I've sent to him can only stay inside his heart meridian.
It can't travel through his entire body.
I can only continue this when his body accepts it on its own.
Wait? We still need to wait?
How long can Sifeng last?
Will this method work or not?
Xuanji, if my qi can't travel through his entire body,
then there really is no other way.
If a strong spirit energy is protecting his heart meridian,
we may be able to force the qi to travel through his body.
There are Pagoda Trees at the base of this mountain.
If we can find a 10,000-year-old Pagoda Tree
and create medicine out of its roots,
Sifeng will be fine after he consumes it.
Yes. Xuanji, take care of Hero Yu.
You need to transfer your qi to protect his heart meridian every five minutes.
I'll follow you.
Hao Chen, you need to recuperate.
You mustn't hurt your own vitality because of this.
I won't be able to give an explanation
to Senior Heng Yang if anything happens to you.
Xuanji, take good care of your senior.
Let's go.
I'll go as well!
Yu Sifeng isn't that great.
He's not worth sacrificing your life for.
Xuanji, I told you before.
You don't know much about relationships.
How could you entrust your future to a stranger like him?
Senior, I may not know much, but I know enough.
Sifeng is the person that I want to spend my life with and never part in this lifetime.
If he leaves me behind, I would rather die.
You're trapped by your relationship.
No class at all.
This is the most despicable
and ignorant act.
Sifeng is the person that I want to spend my life with and never part in this lifetime.
So stupid!
It's no wonder you fail your tribulations every time.
If I don't help you,
this will continue forever.
Sifeng, please hang in there. I beg you.
The medicine is here!
Chu Xuanji, help him up!
We didn't find any 10,000-year-old Pagoda Tree.
We'll see what a 1,000-year-old Pagoda Tree can do.
How is it? Is it working?
No.
The spirit energy is weaker than Senior Hao Chen's qi.
We can't protect his heart this way.
No. I must find it.
Even if there's no 10,000-year-old Pagoda Tree,
I'll find a 10,000-year-old immortal fruit or something.
Sifeng.
Sifeng, hang in there.
What if they can't find anything useful?
What should I do then? Should I submit to fate?
No, I don't want that.
Sifeng, you have to overcome this.
Sifeng, I believe you can overcome this.
Please get better soon.
I didn't expect my Love Flower to have so much spirit energy.
Maybe it can save Sifeng.
Its spirit power has protected your heart meridian.
Sifeng, you must hang in there.
You must get better soon.
My King, according to my observation,
there is spirit energy from the heavens surrounding Chu Xuanji.
I wonder what happened?
It's because Xuanji used the Love Flower to save Yu Sifeng.
Yu Sifeng wasn't supposed to live.
I gave the Love Flower to Xuanji in order to get rid of her anguish,
but she actually used it to save an outsider.
Doesn't she understand the purpose of Love Flower?
She doesn't understand, indeed.
My King, are you angry because she used an immortal item?
Or are you angry because she used the Love Flower that tied your fates?
What a load of nonsense.
Are you still trying to joke around?
What tied fates?
I'm just angry because she's stupid, and she doesn't know what's good for her.
That's why Yu Sifeng is able to lead her by the nose.
But Chu Xuanji has recovered her six senses
and she fancies another person.
My King, if you let her continue her peaceful life,
if her anguish doesn't develop then there's a huge possibility that
she may be able to return to the heavens.
Are you asking me to let them be together in this lifetime?
No! I mean, that isn't suitable at all.
But My King, mortals have a short lifespan.
Even if she is to be together with Yu Sifeng in this life,
it will only be temporary.
When she returns to the heavens,
she'll understand that life is but a dream.
By then, she can stay by your side
and continue her relationship with you.
How dare you say that!
You want me to let Xuanji and an outsider decide her fate?
Impossible!
She belonged to me in the past,
and she'll only belong to me and the heavens,
no matter if it's the present or the future!
Since I've come down to guide her,
I will make sure nothing goes wrong in this lifetime of hers!
Xuanji has disobeyed me many times because of this Yu Sifeng.
I mustn't let him stay by her side.
I need to sever
this ill-fated relationship for her!
Father,
this is Linglong's primordial spirit.
We managed to save her.
Where's Minyan?
Sixth Senior?
He...
Sixth Senior was left behind in Mount Buzhou
and he became Wu Tong's subordinate.
Father, did you give Sixth Senior a secret mission?
He... He severed Second Senior's arm
and he wants me to tell you that he'll accomplish his missions.
What? What do you mean by that?
I didn't say anything like that to him! Why is he...
Why did he do that then?
Xuanji, don't you believe in me?
I-It's not that.
It's just that... just that, he...
he...
Maybe Minyan was used by Wu Tong and the demons.
That's why he betrayed our sect.
Or maybe...
that demon who brought you there was the traitor.
The demon worked together with Tianxu Hall to deceive you.
Impossible. Purple Fox died in Mount Buzhou.
It's impossible for her to deceive us.
What about the disciple of Lize Palace who entered Mount Buzhou with you?
What about him?
Ruo Yu?
Sifeng!
It's him.
He was the one who hurt Sifeng.
He was the one who hurt Sifeng!
I told you before.
I told you not to act recklessly.
But you wouldn't listen.
Mount Buzhou is a place unknown to mortals.
But you insisted on going there.
In the end, everything has become a mess.
It's fine.
It's a lesson for you all.
Now, you know you should think twice before you act.
As for Sifeng, you don't need to worry about him.
Hao Chen has never boasted his abilities.
He won't do things that he's not confident in.
Do you know that your Senior Hao Chen only risked himself
to help an outsider for your sake?
Hao Chen is passionate about you.
And you two were a perfect couple.
But you insist on...
Father, Sifeng and I love each other,
and we promised to never leave each other.
So, I will never marry anyone except for Sifeng.
I've told Senior Hao Chen about my feelings.
Father, I hope you can understand me as well.
Fine.
Get up now.
I know that Yu Sifeng is your benefactor.
We'll talk about this in the future.
I need to patrol the area
and set up the Thousand Bells Formation in order to detect demons.
By doing so, the demons won't be able to create trouble.
Sifeng, how do you feel?
Sifeng.
Does it hurt?
Sifeng!
The mortal's method doesn't work indeed.
It will only cause him harm as the spirit energy is too strong around his heart meridian.
Sifeng, I'll undo two of your seals below your rib-cage.
If not, you will die.
Little Silver Flower, no!
Sifeng. Sifeng!
Are you afraid that Xuanji will know that you're a demon
after I unseal them?
But if I don't unseal them, your blood won't flow.
And they won't be able to save you no matter what they do.
Don't worry.
The spirit energy inside your heart is very powerful.
It will suppress your demonic nature.
Listen to me, okay?
Please listen to me!
Sifeng!
Sifeng, how do you feel?
Do you feel better?
Sifeng! Why is this happening?
Why couldn't it suppress your power?
The thing that Xuanji gave me
clashes with the spirit energy
within my body.
Why is this happening?
Sifeng, you mustn't force yourself!
Oh right, Palace Master once told me that
I need to undo your Dragon Crystal Seal when you're in danger,
and let you consume human's primary essence.
Sifeng, I'll bring you some humans.
Wait for me!
Little Silver Flower! Come back!
Sifeng, don't overexert yourself!
I know you don't want to do this, but I have no choice.
Sifeng!
Give me the Dragon Crystals.
I won't give them to you!
Your life will be in danger!
Go and find...
find Brother Liu.
Hurry and find Brother Liu!
Sifeng.
Aunt Hong, I'll bring this medicine to Sifeng.
Be careful. It's hot.
Why is the door sealed with a spell?
Sifeng?
Sifeng!
Sifeng, are you awake?
Sifeng, talk to me!
Sifeng, open the door!
Sifeng!
I smell a demon! Why is there a demon here?
Father!
A demon has captured Sifeng!
I caught its scent! It's heading toward the forest!
Let's go!
Where's the demon?
Xuanji, do you know where they're located?
It has a faint scent. It's hard for me to locate it.
Let's split up and search.
Okay. Let's split up.
Yu Sifeng, why are you here?
Sifeng!
Xuanji, did you have a clear look at that demon?
No.
This is strange.
Why didn't the demon kill Yu Sifeng?
Why did the demon escape after it brought Yu Sifeng here?
Senior Hao Chen, that's enough.
Let's take Sifeng back.
Fine. I need to cast Nine Cycles Spell to stabilize his heart meridian for now.
Let's go.
That demon's purpose just now is inexplicable.
Yu Sifeng had received spirit energy from the heavens.
He should be fine, yet he's extremely weak.
What exactly is going on?
By casting the Nine Cycles Spell, I can travel around in his body
and understand what's going on.
Strange.
There's nothing wrong with his body.
He's like an ordinary human.
Wait, something is hidden within.
Demon Poison?
Senior!
Xuanji, don't come near me!
Be careful!
It's Demon Poison!
The poison is affecting Hao Chen!
I'm afraid his body will be taken over!
What should we do? He's casting the Nine Cycles Spell!
If we force him to stop now, the poison will enter his body!
Let me try!
No! The poison is too strong!
Ting Nu? Brother Liu?
Ting Nu, please save Sifeng!
I can neutralize the poison.
Wait!
Demon, how dare you come here!
Father, although Ting Nu is a merman, he has helped us many times.
He was once an immortal medic in the heavens. His medical skills are superb.
- He's our friend.  - Nonsense!
We're cultivators! How could we work together with demons?
Old guy, you're stubborn indeed!
What's wrong with demons?
Many kind-hearted demons are much better than evil humans!
This is an emergency, you know?
It'll be too late if you don't allow my friend to help.
Father, please let Ting Nu save them!
They can't hold out for long! Ting Nu, please save them!
Sect Leader, this is an emergency.
Why don't we let him try?
Besides, he won't be able to do much with us around.
The poison has been neutralized.
Sifeng!
Wait, this merman... It's him?
Strange, I tremble with fear when I look at him,
but I have never seen him before.
Your injury isn't serious,
but there are residues of the poison inside your body.
You better go on a retreat and recuperate for a few months to detoxify the remaining poison.
No!
I haven't captured that demon yet.
Senior, I'm afraid the demon won't return anymore.
You need to recuperate. Demon Poison is a big deal.
He Yang, bring Hao Chen back to Shaoyang for his recuperation.
- We'll take it from here.  - Okay, come.
Sifeng.
Sifeng!
Ting Nu, what's wrong with Sifeng?
Sifeng's condition is more complicated. Yihuan, I need your assistance.
Xuanji, you can wait outside with the rest.
- I—  - Don't worry.
I'll do my best to return a healthy Sifeng back to you.
I—
Sifeng, I'm going to reconstruct your heart meridian.
I need you to stay awake
and bear the pain.
Thank you.
It's done.
Little Phoenix, you managed to survive this ordeal,
but who knows how many ordeals are waiting for you in the future?
You better not injure yourself anymore.
Okay. I'll seal his Demon Point right now.
Yihuan,
we should use the Dragon Crystal Seal on him
when he is fully recovered.
Fine.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by Destined ♥ Love Team @ Viki
♫  There is overabundance of joy in this world  ♫
♫  Waiting for me to grow up, to capture the wisdom  ♫
♫  There is overabundance of confusion  ♫
♫  When you look at me, you'll understand  ♫
♫  I look forward with expectation to be disappointed  ♫
♫  Time and time again, faith is broken by destiny  ♫
♫  Each and every sound is me  ♫
♫  With all that I am, my love will never reach your silhouette  ♫
♫  You don't know where you're going until  you've been heartbroken  ♫
♫  Concealed feelings deep in one's heart  ♫
♫  The longing to return home is a cherished desire  ♫
♫  My time has not been wasted  ♫
♫  When love becomes deeper, betrayal becomes deeper  ♫
♫  I blindfolded myself to see things clearly  ♫
♫  Before embracing, one must learn to let go first  ♫
♫  The experience of an agonizing bone shaking pain  ♫
♫  Like hands, like feet, like you, I can't be without  ♫