♪Stars twinkling, your wish comes true♪
♪Stars shower tenderness on the summer♪
♪Stars make faces, twinkling, twinkling♪
♪Every moment is worth remembering♪
=The Dark Crown=
=Episode 32=
I can't believe it either,
so I came here after I got the news.
What happened to you?
Why would he agree to marry Mi Kerui?
Yu Lou.
Don't be sad.
Something must be wrong.
Youting never liked Mi Kerui.
Even if he can't remember you,
he won't choose her.
Don't... Don't be sad.
I'll figure it out, okay?
Forget about the food.
Let's go.
I'll take you home.
Come on.
Youting?
Why are you...?
Don't touch her!
Yu Lou is uncomfortable.
Shouldn't you...?
Don't touch her!
Stop yelling!
Who did this to her?
Listen, Youting,
why do you want to marry Mi Kerui?
How can you forget Yu Lou?
Not your business!
Youting.
You hate me, don't you?
I thought you forgot me.
Why are you doing this?
Our relationship
has nothing to do with you.
Liao Youting.
I don't understand
why you're doing this to me.
Yu Lou!
Nan, I didn't get the chance.
Liao Youting took Yu Lou away.
Never mind. I have another plan.
(Congratulations! They're engaged!)
They're engaged?
You fooled me.
Then don't blame me
for killing
Liao Youting too.
Huh.
(Nurse Station)
Youting carried you to his car
after you passed out.
He was creaming your name
like he was crazy.
I've never seen him like this.
I thought he'd stay,
but
he left.
Yu Lou.
Youting said you needed to
stay away from him for your safety.
Do you know what it means?
For my safety?
Yes.
I asked him,
but he didn't answer.
Is he going to
get engaged with Mi Kerui?
It's on the news.
I don't think he'll change his mind.
Yan Lan.
Do me a favor.
Mr. Liao.
(Yan Lan, Yu Lou (Date))
Who let them in?
Your families are friends.
Mr. Yan can definitely get in.
Miss Yu...
Mrs. Liao didn't tell her,
but Mr. Yan insisted.
We couldn't stop him.
I'll pick up Grandma.
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
I told you not to wear black.
Why didn't you listen?
It's your sister's engagement party.
How can you dress like this?
She's even worse.
It's like she's having a wedding.
Look, Mrs. Liao
is also wearing a black dress.
Shanshan, check on your sister.
No! You go!
I... What can I do?
I'm not her real mother.
At least you're her sister.
She's going to marry Mr. Liao.
Be nice to her.
It'll benefit you, right?
Benefit?
Mom.
No wonder Mi Kerui
always says I'm stupid.
Like mother, like daughter.
- You...
- Don't argue.
Do you really think Mi Kerui's marriage
will benefit us?
Listen,
she's never treated us like family.
She hates
both of us.
If she gets what she wants,
we'll no longer be
a part of the Mi Family.
What are you talking about?
At least I'm your father's wife,
and you're his daughter.
Even if Mi Kerui is against us,
your dad will defend us, right?
When we were rich,
he cared about me.
However, since we lost money,
he's looked at me
with disgust.
As for Mi Kerui,
she knew Mr. Liao was a heartless man...
♪When I cross the sky and find you♪
♪All the sights along the way make sense♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)