♪Stars twinkling, your wish comes true♪
♪Stars shower tenderness on the summer♪
♪Stars make faces, twinkling, twinkling♪
♪Every moment is worth remembering♪
=The Dark Crown=
=Episode 5=
I bought it for you.
Me?
If it's OK, I'll leave first.
You're the best thing ever happened to me.
I wish you all the best.
Best thing ever happened.
Is this a love confession?
No wonder she was nervous.
(I thought I would be locked up again,)
(not expecting him to let me go.)
(Did I change his trajectory?)
(Most Important Person)
What did he do again?
Most important person?
(Mi Kerui, Second Daughter of Mi Group)
- ♪I left my home to save Li♪
- She is better.
That's nice.
- Amazing.
- ♪But I became the Principal Graduate♪
Well done.
♪I'm wearing the red robe♪
Very good.
Look at her figure.
Amazing.
♪I rode my horse in front of the palace♪
Kerui, come here.
Come to Grandma.
(Old Lady, Liao Youting's Grandmother)
Kerui knows I love opera.
She's been studying it since childhood.
Who could compare to her?
Kerui, I remember your wishes.
Grandma.
(Mi Jianguo, President of Mi Group)
Mrs. Liao,
that's what Kerui should do.
We will be family sooner or later.
She'll serve you with more care.
Sure.
(Liu Shuzhen, Liao Youting's Mother)
(Liao Wenge, Liao Youting's Father)
I wish
Youting will marry Kerui soon.
Isn't Youting here yet?
He's busy. He can't make it.
Grandma, everyone,
I need to go change.
I'll be back in a minute.
OK.
What a good girl, right?
What are you doing here?
There's no point in coaxing the old lady.
You can't even see Mr. Liao.
It doesn't matter.
We have plenty of time.
You can lie to yourself,
but Yu Luo is probably with him now.
You don't know what a temptress she is.
There is nothing strange about having
a few women around an outstanding man.
You'd better keep an eye on Chen Yihao.
He's never seen the world.
Don't let him be seduced
by the temptress again.
We're doing well.
He's talented.
Look, he designed this bracelet for me.
What do you think?
It's no worse than an Italian designer's.
I'm glad you like it.
Don't you remember what day it is?
I even set it as the door password.
Today is our one-year anniversary.
Oh.
At home?
Alright.
Come back early. I've got you a surprise.
(Scum.)
(He doesn't want to let anyone go.)
Bye-bye.
Mi Shanshan?
Yu Luo, I'm warning you.
My sister is Mr. Liao's fiancée.
You better stay away from him,
otherwise, you will be in trouble.
Is that all?
OK, you have my word.
Then do me a favor, too.
What?
Tell your sister to keep an eye on him
and don't let him pester me.
It's annoying.
Don't talk nonsense.
You must have seduced him,
- so he...
- Mi Shanshan,
I think you are funny.
Last time,
it was Chen Yihao.
Now, it's Liao Youting.
Whoever I'm with, your family
will take him away from me, right?
Bullshit.
Who do you think you are
to compete with us?
I'm warning you.
Don't ever mention Chen Yihao again.
OK.
I'll just pretend he is dead.
I won't mention him again.
You don't have to curse him.
Come back early.
I've got you a surprise.
I just spoke in anger.
Actually, I've given up on him.
Because I found
that he really loves you.
I guess his door password
will no longer be 0606.
- 0606?
- Yeah.
- What does it mean?
- It's today.
Today is a special day.
Don't you know the password to his door?
Have you never been to his place?
So what if I haven't?
Yihao is a decent man.
He doesn't just take girls home.
But I've been there.
He said it was cozy to date at home.
You can make the first move if he doesn't.
But when it comes to surprises,
you're not as good as me.
Who says that?
I'm going to surprise him tonight.
Alright, if you can,
change 0606 to your anniversary.
I'm going now.
I'll get you out of his world forever.
Good things come in pairs.
You look great in this.
Do you like it?
Yes.
You should wear it again.
OK.
- Bad guy.
- Don't move.
Sit well.
Yihao.
Don't move.
Shanshan.
What are you doing?
Temptress, get down!
I thought you messed with me for Yu Luo.
Turns out it was about yourself!
Shame on you to steal your friend's man.
Yihao and Yu Luo broke up.
Why couldn't I?
Shameless woman!
Shame on you!
I will kill you!
Stealing my man,
- who do you think you are?
- Listen to me!
Listen to me!
Yihao!
She did seduce me.
I had a few drinks today.
I didn't expect to see her in that.
Why are you doing this to me?
I even brought you a gift.
I brought you the plan you wanted most.
Shanshan, listen to me.
You know
I'm not a bad guy.
I didn't touch Yu Luo in three years.
I just had a few drinks today.
Get out of here!
Get out!
Fine, I'll get out.
Shanshan.
(Nurse Station, Two days later)
You can leave after a rest.
Abortion doesn't require hospitalization.
Luo.
Yueru, don't move.
You look pale.
The surgery must have hurt.
I'm fine.
Why didn't you tell me about your pregnancy?
Aren't we best friends?
I heard it was a miscarriage.
Where's the father?
Why isn't he here with you?
Forget it. I don't want to mention it.
Luo, how do you know I'm here?
Yihao told me.
I don't know where he heard it from.
It isn't appropriate for him to be here.
So I didn't bring him.
I think
you broke up with him.
- Why...
- That's expedient for making money.
You know he wants to start a business.
In fact, we're doing great.
He said he'd always love me.
He'll marry me when he's successful.
Yueru, don't worry about me.
We will be happy.
Don't worry. Eat this orange.
♪When I cross the sky and find you♪
♪All the sights along the way make sense♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)