♪Stars twinkling, your wish comes true♪
♪Stars shower tenderness on the summer♪
♪Stars make faces, twinkling, twinkling♪
♪Every moment is worth remembering♪
=The Dark Crown=
=Episode 28=
Liar, why didn't you call me
when you missed me?
You're a big liar. It's been 100 days.
What about you?
Do you miss me?
No.
Then why did you come?
I wanted to know
if you were working hard.
After all, you're my kept boy.
I need to be responsible.
If your group loses too much money
due to the incident,
I'll make money and keep you.
Don't worry, I can handle anything
but you.
Well,
now that I'm your kept boy,
am I supposed to do something?
Like what?
What...
What do you want?
You tell me.
Youting, I brought...
Oh.
Well,
I'm busy. Goodbye.
Why didn't you lock the door?
Why should I?
Who dares to come in?
Besides, I didn't know she was coming.
Don't move.
Get back to work.
I'll wait for you at home.
At home?
Xijingyuan.
See you tonight.
♪I'm going to cross a distance♪
♪And fly to you♪
♪Watch the sun rise and fall with you♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪Close my eyes tightly♪
♪I can't sleep when thinking of you♪
♪Your smile is sweet and adorable♪
♪Can't get you out of my head♪
Mom.
When will you recognize me?
Look,
Mom is much better.
She had porridge today.
But she still can't speak.
Don't worry.
She'll get better.
Listen,
when I sent some cakes
to Youting's office,
I saw him kissing Luo.
They got back together.
Wow.
Don't mention Yu Lou
in front of her, okay?
What?
I'm sure Luo didn't push her.
Think about it.
It's a big hotel.
Why is there no surveillance
at the place she fell?
Someone must've planned this
for a long time.
I invited Luo right before the banquet.
She didn't know anything about it,
so it can't be her.
But it can't be Kerui either.
She cares about Mom.
You're always prejudiced against Kerui.
I... Well,
I don't like her,
but I'm not saying she did it.
If I had evidence, I would...
Wait.
Hello, who's this?
What?
Youting!
How could I fall asleep?
What time is it?
It's almost 1:00 a.m.
Why didn't he call?
What took him so long?
Hello?
Miss Yu, I'm Li Shang.
Li Shang?
Mr. Liao had an accident.
He's in the hospital.
(Nurse Station)
Youting!
Mr. Liao went to City Hai for a meeting.
He wanted to come back earlier.
It was dark,
and he...
Why are you so silly?
You could tell me you were busy.
Luo, don't worry.
The doctor said
he'd be fine.
He's sleeping because of the anesthetic.
He'll wake up tomorrow.
What's the point of crying?
Give him a break.
He's been upset lately
and busy with making up
for the group's losses.
It was fatigue driving, so...
Stop saying that.
Who'd have thought this would happen?
Youting, I'm here with you.
I won't argue with you anymore.
I won't leave you again.
I'll be a good girl.
I'm not crying.
Just take a break.
♪When I cross the sky and find you♪
♪All the sights along the way make sense♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)