♪Stars twinkling, your wish comes true♪
♪Stars shower tenderness on the summer♪
♪Stars make faces, twinkling, twinkling♪
♪Every moment is worth remembering♪
=The Dark Crown=
=Episode 15=
Yueru,
how come Yueru is here?
Yueru, why are you here?
Are you here for me?
I didn't expect that
only you care about me at this moment.
Yueru, the Mi family is chasing me for the debt,
and there's also Mr. Zhang.
They forced me with knives.
I'm desperate, Yueru.
Yihao,
do you still love me?
Of course! I do!
Please, don't leave me, okay?
Fine.
As long as you love me,
I will never leave you.
Yihao,
you know what?
I've never been after a good life with you.
I really love you.
I fell in love with you the first time I saw you.
But at that time, I didn't dare to get close to you.
I had to take Yu Luo as an excuse to get close to you.
Only in this way
would you pay more attention to me.
Yu Luo,
I should never have let her meet you.
It's the thing I regret the most.
Without her, you wouldn't have become like this.
But, have you realized that?
I'm the only one who truly loves you.
Yu Luo will harm you,
Mi Shanshan will harm you,
but I, Yueru, won't!
Yueru,
I know you are the best to me,
but I borrowed a lot of money.
Please help me, okay?
Okay.
Don't be afraid.
I'll help you.
Go and sleep with Mr. Zhang.
Didn't he give you a lot of money?
He will surely give you more if you do that.
Yueru,
please!
Fine.
I'll help you.
Yihao,
I really love you.
I love you!
(Wang Yueru was arrested for intentional homicide)
(and received legal punishment.)
Wang Yueru killed Chen Yihao.
I didn't expect it would end like this.
My plan
was to make Chen Yihao go bankrupt.
He's greedy,
and this was his punishment.
But Yueru...
How could she get caught in his grip?
After all, she had been pregnant with his child.
How could he do such a thing?
For money,
he really dared to do anything.
So, for ending up like this,
he can only blame himself.
I'm the one who caused all this.
Not at all, they brought it upon themselves.
Luo,
actually, I'm so scared.
When I think of how you used to trust Chen Yihao,
I'm so afraid that you would be in Yueru's position.
Thank God, you haven't been hurt.
Don't blame yourself any more.
(But how could I really escape?)
Luo,
everything has passed.
Up so early again?
Well,
with your boyfriend in such a big trouble,
how could you sleep?
With one less brother- in- law to support me,
I might also lose sleep, right?
Mi Kerui,
does his death make you so happy?
Whether he dies or not is none of my business.
I'm just sorry that our money
has been emptied by you two jerks.
Us two?
You must have said the same thing to dad,
trying to make him drive me out of the house,
trying to make him completely disown me.
Who can you blame for what you've done?
Oh,
remember to take your mom with you when you leave,
so that she won't take the scolding for you.
In your dreams!
If anyone has to leave, it shall be you.
Mi Kerui,
don't count your chickens before they hatch.
If Mr. Liao doesn't want you,
you are nothing in this family!
Mi Shanshan,
I will surely let you know
that the family can't do without me!
Hello?
♪When I cross the sky and find you♪
♪All the sights along the way make sense♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)