♪The left bank lights♪
♪Are still faintly lit♪
♪The dream you mentioned♪
♪Is still bumpy♪
♪Don't know much about love
when we were young♪
♪Don't have to be perfect♪
♪My heart is warm when you're with me♪
♪We talk and walk together♪
♪The moment I exchange stories with you♪
♪Watching you, waiting for you♪
♪Makes me happy too♪
♪How many people have come♪
♪How many people have left♪
♪Perhaps only by appreciating our love♪
♪Will it become silent and leave a mark♪
♪We once loved♪
=I Am The Years You Are The Stars=
=Episode 8=
The most important thing
about Korean style makeup
is the highlight.
With a correct highlight,
you'll get that dewy look.
Look, just like me.
Just like this.
Apply it gently to have that natural look, see!
Very natural.
(Serial novel, Ms. Luosifen)
[*Luosifen is a rice noodle dish with river snails.]
(and Mr. Coffee's Love Story.)
(Ever since parting ways with Ms. Luosifen,)
(Mr. Coffee would often think about her.)
(Perhaps it was because their encounter
was too special,)
(or maybe it was because
the Luosifen was too smelly.)
(For the next few days,)
(the coffee shop smelled of Luosifen.)
(The second time they met)
(was half a year later.)
This is the place.
(Ms. Luosifen,)
(who just became the co-writer of a TV series,)
(brought her friends to the store to celebrate.)
Scan the code to order your food.
Miao,
you are the first from our dormitory
to get a screenplay writing role for a TV series!
It's a web series and I'm just the co-writer.
My name is at the end of the list.
But it's a long series!
36 episodes!
I'm still stuck with writing web movies.
You guys only see the glory
and not the hard work I've put in.
Party A bought the rights to a script,
which was a total waste of money.
Aside from the names in the series,
we couldn't use any lines from the script.
Our team had to write
an entire new story.
It was so exhausting.
I'm planning to switch jobs
and become a web novel writer.
That's not bad at all!
If your novel becomes a hit,
you can earn so much more than a screenwriter!
I hope so.
Here's your order.
Thank you.
Not bad, right?
I told you guys it would be good.
It looks so delicious!
It looks so pretty.
I want to take a picture of it!
Thanks.
Are you done?
Waiter!
I'm done.
What is wrong with you people?
I ordered the same shaved ice,
but the toppings are completely different!
Yeah!
The co-owner made their order especially for them.
Please enjoy your meal.
Miao,
is something going on?
Does your boyfriend work here?
When did you get a boyfriend?
I don't have a boyfriend.
Then what is going on?
Tell us the truth!
Confess!
Thank you.
My friends are just talking nonsense.
They always make fun of me.
I wish it were true, to be frank.
Did you come here
to make our relationship official?
It's okay.
I don't mind.
Girlfriend.
Why haven't you been here
since that day?
I...
I was busy writing screenplays!
Do you address all your female customers
as your girlfriends?
How could you think of me like that?
I only said this to the girl
who asked for hot water
while we were closing shop.
Let's end our conversation.
(Ms. Luosifen)
(ran back to her seat happily.)
(Even though I looked calm,)
(my heart was beating like a drum.)
(I told myself,)
(doing this)
(would only result in two outcomes.)
(She would think of me as a pervert)
(and stay away from me.)
(Or)
(maybe she would like my little tricks.)
We know we're wrong.
We'll go outside to eat our food!
Yeah, Yueran.
Don't tell on us, please.
We'll go right now.
I won't report you,
but you have to share it with me!
This...
Let me try it!
My healthy meal has no salt in it
and tastes awful!
Hand me a new pair of chopsticks.
Here, here!
Here you go.
It smells so good.
Here's some water.
Yueran,
you look so much prettier than before!
Tan Yueran!
Look at the camera!
I'm warning you,
I'll report you!
I'll report you for eating in the lab!
Go ahead!
Have fun with that!
Here!
I can't believe Tan Yueran let out a smile!
Yueran,
something's not right.
Are you dating someone?
I have someone I like.
If you guys treat me to a meal,
I'll let you guys see him.
Are you serious?
Alright, I'll take your word for it.
This meal is on me.
Okay.
Then it's a deal.
You two pay for the meal,
I'll pay for the coffee.
You have my word.
That's settled then.
Young Master.
An apple a day
keeps the doctor away.
Even if I don't eat apples,
doctors will still stay away from me.
Young Master,
why don't you go down there and check it out?
Someone is in a bad mood over there.
She looks troubled.
I heard
one of her colleagues
got fooled by an innocent looking wench.
It also seemed like she had something to do it.
That's why she feels bad.
How do you know this?
Well,
it's pretty normal for a girl
to share secrets with me.
I'm just too charming.
Right?
Here.
For me?
Would I feed this to the turtle?
So what's up?
I heard a friend of yours got fooled
by an innocent looking wench.
Do you have a crush on that guy?
Firstly,
I'm not upset about that innocent looking wench.
I'm upset because the organ recipient
is illegally looking for organ donors.
Secondly,
I don't like him.
I just think he's pitiful.
Thirdly,
I have a feeling this is not
the end of the matter.
But I don't know what to do.
You think there's something wrong
with the organ recipient?
Yeah.
Can I capture her?
Capture her?
What do you want to do?
You are so capable.
Can you investigate someone for me?
I can do it
as long as you move out.
Well, forget it then.
You have absolutely no sincerity!
Don't you know sincerity
is worth its price in gold?
It is!
But Grandma Dao offered me ten times its worth!
I'll give you double of that.
You don't even have an ID
or a property certificate!
How can I trust you?
This again.
Your eyebrows are too thick.
Your eyebrows are too thick!
I'm saying,
if you help me look into
Tan Yueran's matter,
I will
give you a full body massage
and a facial care!
How does that sound?
A full body massage and a facial care?
What was your previous occupation?
What are you thinking about?
I'm a professional!
If you don't want a full body massage,
then I guess I have to pay with my body.
That is unnecessary.
Just give me
a traditional Chinese therapy.
Deal!
What would you guys like to drink?
- We have to scan a code, right?
- Let me see...
Yeah.
Just order one for me.
Anything is fine.
Okay.
Is it the guy over there?
Yeah, what do you think?
He's handsome, right?
He's a barista
and the owner of this place.
Tan Yueran,
you're like a whole new person
after that heart transplant!
Dude,
Tan Yueran is in love.
Can you believe that?
This isn't what's surprising.
What's surprising is
she's sharing this with us!
Stop, you two.
Yueran,
who was the previous owner
of your heart?
That person must be a social butterfly!
I agree!
You guys are so dramatic.
Was I really that introverted before?
No,
you weren't introverted.
You were just autistic!
Nonsense, shut up!
Here you go.
Thank you, thank you.
Please enjoy.
Give it a taste.
This is my boyfriend's handiwork.
It looks delicious!
Cut it out, Yueran.
You're making him shy!
He ought to feel shy.
Quanzhan,
why don't you
message the PhD girl!
You won't run into her
by just walking around like this.
What would I even say?
Just invite her to hang out with you!
Tell her this.
You can say that
you and your colleague are here on business
and it'd be nice if you could meet her.
That's too intentional!
You have to be intentional!
You want her to know
that you came here
just to find her.
If she doesn't want to hang out with you,
then she'll reject you.
But if she likes you,
or has feelings for you,
then she will meet up with you
no matter how busy she is!
Right?
Yeah!
I think you should just call her!
Just call her.
Call her?
Won't I disturb her?
What if she's in class?
What if she's not in class?
If she's busy,
then send a message later.
If she picks up your call, then it's a win!
Wang Quande,
no wonder you have a girlfriend.
Okay, I'll call her.
Hello?
Tan, Tan Yueran.
Wang Quande, who's my colleague,
and I,
we're near your school.
Somewhere nearby.
So I'm just wondering if you're on campus.
I'm not on campus.
I'm getting food with my seniors.
Here's your food.
Thank you.
I sent you some messages on WeChat before.
Why didn't you reply to them?
You're a pretty good cook, Brother-in-law!
Keep up the good work, Brother-in-law.
How about we meet up after I'm done
with my projects?
Yueran, we have to go.
We're leaving now.
Bye-bye.
Okay, goodbye.
Well...
Why did she hang up?
Busy, I guess.
Video games are better anyway.
Thank you.
Your friends called me brother-in-law just now.
I think they have the wrong impression
about our relationship.
Firstly,
how does them calling you brother-in-law
have anything to do with me?
Secondly,
they were the ones that said it.
You should ask them.
Why are you asking me?
Thirdly,
there are two guys at the counter.
How do you know you are the brother-in-law
and I am the sister?
Why are you in such a rush
to put a label on yourself,
Brother-in-law?
See you, Brother-in-law!
Boss,
did you ask me to come here
to look at you make a dress?
I'm just mentally preparing
for the person that's coming.
A person that's coming?
Is someone trying on this dress later?
But you won't finish it in time!
I...
You look pissed.
What? You want to buy the place?
Is it on sale?
You can have it for free
when you get married.
I heard you're going on blind dates.
Well,
I heard you have
a female cohabiting partner.
My apologies.
Always being a step ahead of you.
That's fine.
As long as you die
one step ahead of me, too.
I had been hoping to die
even before you were born.
Whatever. I don't care.
This is what you wanted.
(Tan Yueran, congenital heart disease)
Little Qian Tu is always so efficient.
So that's a deal?
One week.
He's at the photo studio.
Ask the CAO to accompany you.
But don't tell him
I am here.
I'm worried I might go soft on him
if I see him again.
Wise.
I'm off.
I see
you have two faces.
What do I do?
I've somehow ended up
like a person that's very experienced.
Let me see...
Her personal information is here.
Is there anything different?
Not too far off from what you knew.
This person is very introverted
and has congenital heart disease since childhood.
She suffered from extreme social anxiety
(Tan Yueran, congenital heart disease)
and was once suspected to be autistic.
Are you talking about Tan Yueran?
Someone who goes to a funeral home to hit on a guy
and treats everyone to milk tea?
Yet you say she has socially anxiety
instead of a social butterfly?
That I don't know.
This can't be the same person!
Boss.
Can I try it on?
Just for a little while.
Okay.
♪For a moment♪
♪It's like a long time ago♪
♪Your clothes♪
You look like an actual bride.
Really?
Then I want a picture for memory's sake!
Let me find a spot with good lighting...
♪Deja vu♪
♪I don't recognize your delicate face♪
What is there to remember?
♪You're still young♪
Because I can't get married.
♪And my hair is still long♪
♪Who can tell♪
♪If the dream is an obsession of a lie?♪
If you want pictures, take them properly.
I'll take it for you.
♪If it's there after so long, it will come true♪
Please.
♪We'll meet again♪
♪One day♪
♪But I don't know what year it is♪
♪I'm too sensitive by nature♪
Well? Do I look nice?
Not bad.
Take a look.
It's good, right?
Qian Cheng is here.
Move!
Young Master!
Why did you give me a week off?
How could you use me as a bargaining chip
to trade with my brother?
You don't respect me at all!
Just laugh out loud if you want.
You don't usually laugh like this.
♪I haven't seen you clearly yet♪
♪Fate has withdrawn its favor♪
♪You and I are just an inch apart♪
♪But it's as if we're far apart♪
♪I was born to be alone♪
♪I know that adoration is nothing♪
♪If everything has to return to the ground♪
Nonsense.
Nonsense?
Are you ashamed?
Are you blushing?
♪I'll leave you a love letter♪
Here.
Try our new cake.
It's a brand new recipe.
You're making me the lab rat again.
How can you be so heartless?
I made it especially for you.
Miao is no longer with us.
I don't have anyone else to try my food.
Well?
Is it good?
It's good.
Just the right amount of sweetness.
Oh right,
have you seen the advertisement PowerPoint?
I did.
But
was it Jin Xiaoyu's idea
to do a photo shoot at a funeral home?
No,
it's our spokesperson's idea.
Lin Nuoyan!
I thought it was Jin Xiaoyu!
No worries.
If there's anything you don't like about it,
you can tell me.
We can figure it out.
Or, we'll find someone else.
Li can do the photo shoot as well.
It's just that his camera isn't very good.
Might have to borrow yours.
That way you don't even have to be there.
I think I might as well be there.
Dr. Cheng,
I've been losing sleep,
can you help me?
Come.
Let me check your pulse.
I thought you're an emergency doctor.
You know how to do pulse diagnosis, too?
So you know I'm an emergency doctor!
I deal with loss of blood,
not loss of sleep.
My bad.
Did I say something wrong?
Did I remind you of a bad memory?
No.
I'm not that weak.
But
I think about her a lot lately.
I also met
a girl who's really like her.
That's good!
You know, before Cai Miao passed away,
she wanted me to tell you,
that you have to start anew.
I know.
You told me many times.
But that girl
is really like her.
How do I start anew?
It's okay!
As the saying goes,
if you have a girl around you,
could love be far away?
Take it easy.
Okay.
We've seen everything here.
Is it time to show me
where you work?
We're taking pictures for the association.
You can't take photos of where I work.
I'm not taking pictures.
I'm just curious
about where you go to work.
Just think of it as a learning experience for me.
Professor Lin,
I see you are
a very studious person.
Can I
take that as a yes?
I guess.
I have a job this afternoon.
I need the help. So you can give me a hand.
You're professional after all.
(Makeup Room)
This cadaver
has serious ascites.
This is a liver cancer patient, I think.
Quite the expert, Professor Lin.
The pathology of ascites is complex.
It's usually related to
a disruption in the pressure forces
between intravascular
and extravascular fluid spaces.
But for patients with liver cancer, it's usually
because of the chronic liver cirrhosis
and pressure at the portal veins.
So what do we do about ascites in cadavers?
The decay prevention team
will suck out the liquid.
When in the prone position,
the liquid accumulates
at both sides of the abdomen
while the middle portion
of the abdomen becomes flat.
Tapping on it produces a dull sound.
No wonder people say
hard working girls are the prettiest.
That's you right now.
Mr. Lin Nuoyan,
can we not flirt
under this condition?
(Mu City Municipal Funeral Home)
Sorry to bother you today.
People say that
after going to the morgue,
you can't go home directly.
You should have a meal
or a shower before going back home.
Okay.
Thank you for today.
You taught me so much.
It really broadens my horizon.
Honestly,
I've always been quite interested
in your line of work.
Mainly,
everyone is a little bit fearful
of places like the morgue.
Sure, I study medicine,
but I am also very afraid of death.
We wrestle the Grim Reaper for people's lives.
Death for us
means failure.
Why am I hiding?
Death is like birth.
It's just a journey
in life.
Like airports,
train stations, or harbors.
It's about parting.
My master told me,
the meaning of death
is to teach people how to be grateful.
The reason why I chose here
as the location to do the photo shoot
for the advertisement
is because I watched a movie
called "Okuribito".
Apart from that,
I knew you could help me.
I actually like the advertising slogan
you guys use.
"Live on in another way."
This, to the people who are about to die,
makes organ donation sound like something hopeful.
Congratulations.
You hit your target audience.
I'd rather you not be the target audience.
Especially after seeing your professional side.
I wouldn't want anything bad to happen to you.
An animal in suit.
Stop holding her hand.
Then,
will you contribute to my funeral?
Since you're a professional,
please contribute more.
Sure.
I will.
That's a relief.
I'll head back to work.
If
you need anything, just come by.
Okay.
Let me treat you to a meal if you're free.
Okay!
I'm off.
This is how
you earthlings date, right?
Are you here to see me?
You think too much.
I went to buy flowers, not to see you.
True.
Then what are these flowers for?
To visit your ex?
Does your ex live here?
Wait up, pretty boy!
Where does your ex-girlfriend live?
Why did that perverted professor meet with you?
Like you said, for a date.
Seeing you two together
reminded me of something.
Of how matching two people can be?
I can't accompany anyone.
And you're the same.
To those normal people,
we are abnormal beings.
You still run your mouth like a child
even though you're so old.
You're not afraid of biting your tongue?
Even if I bite my tongue,
I'll heal immediately.
That's why drugs don't do anything for me.
I guess poison wouldn't work on you.
Chen,
I'm here to see you.
He's a guy.
(Grave of Great Friend Chen Zhongshun)
He's my classmate when I was young.
At bootcamp,
we were comrades for a month.
Afterwards he left for the navy
and stayed in Taiwan, China after the war.
His biggest dream
was to go back home.
But only after his death
did I have a chance to bring him back.
(1985, Taiwan, China)
Mr. Chen!
Kid, you're here!
Come, come.
Back in the day,
your grandpa and I
got on the boat from here.
So,
how is your grandfather doing?
He's doing well,
just that his legs are a bit weak.
Everyone's the same.
We're old.
Yeah.
Mr. Chen,
my grandfather wanted me to give you this.
(You told me you love me
and would hold me in your arms.)
(But the time to part has come.)
This old boy, Jiang Baiju,
even at this age,
he still thinks about Chen Mansha.
What?
Have you forgotten about Ms. Chen?
No!
Back in those days, your grandfather and I
often went to Paramount.
The both of us tried to pursue Chen Mansha.
Later on, we joined the army
and went to the frontline.
I joined the navy,
he went to Yunnan and Burma.
We never reconnected
after those chaotic years.
Only until you found me
did I find out that
your grandfather went to America,
got married and had kids.
He also has a good grandson like you.
Unlike me.
A lonely veteran,
staring at the ocean every day,
with a home I can't go back to.
Compared to your grandfather,
(the Man on the Flying Frapere)
I miss Chen Mansha even more.
Mr. Chen,
my grandpa told me
you liked to have fun when you were young.
He misses you a lot.
So he asked me to visit you more often.
Not anymore.
My legs don't work as well anymore.
That's true.
When I was young,
at Paramount,
only I could match
your grandfather's dance skills.
All the girls in Shanghai
knew about that.
Your grandfather
was the Prince of Night Shanghai.
And me,
I was the King of Dance at Paramount.
Since when were you the K...
My grandfather says
you know very few dance styles.
Not nearly as much as he did.
He talks big!
That guy...
But you.
You look just like
your grandfather when he was young.
Like an exact replica!
Really?
Back in the day,
I was more handsome than your grandfather.
I knew more moves than he did.
I was more popular than him.
He was just rich.
All I had was my personal charm.
Personal charm.
With your personal charm,
you wooed the most popular socialite,
Miss Qin Xiangjun!
Your grandfather can't keep his mouth shut.
Telling you kids all this stuff.
What's the big deal!
I'll go to the mainland in two days.
When I'm there,
I'll find Ms. Qin
and tell her how much you miss her.
Please don't!
She's married now.
She has a family now
and lives a stable life.
Don't disturb her.
So you don't want to know where she is?
Forget it.
I can't live with her,
so I shouldn't
disturb the peace.
It's fate.
I accept it.
Don't you want to know
if she's doing well or not?
Kid.
Do you know?
Before getting to know Ms. Qin,
I always believed that
Chen Mansha was the one I was going to marry.
But after I met Ms. Qin,
that's when I knew
chasing a superstar
and chasing after the woman you love
are different things.
I can put up pictures of Chen Mansha
all over my room
and stare at them every day.
But,
I...
I don't dare look at photos of Ms. Qin.
You'll become nervous
when you see the woman you love.
You'll become afraid.
(Grave of Great Friend Chen Zhongshun)
(September 20th, 1999)
(Return to one's roots)
♪I haven't seen you clearly yet♪
♪Fate has withdrawn its favor♪
♪You and I are just an inch apart♪
Your classmate in your youth,
your comrade in bootcamp,
stayed in Taiwan, China after the war.
Were you born during the ROC era?
You're pretty smart, little girl.
What alien language are you speaking?
Shanghainese.
I see you're not so bright.
Who are you?
Old man.
♪It's also forgiveness♪
Ms. Qin.
(Late Father Liu Changman)
♪I'll leave you♪
(Late Mother Qin Xiangjun)
♪A love letter♪
♪But I won't give you♪
♪The pain of the world♪
♪When I understand the depth of love♪
This was your ex-girlfriend?
She was.
But not mine.
Ms. Qin
was the fiancee of Mr. Chen.
They were engaged.
But that dummy Chen
had to join the army.
In the army, I reprimanded
him over this issue all the time.
Who's this?
This is Miss Qin's husband.
Chen
always wanted to know
if Miss Qin was doing well,
but was also afraid to find out.
I guess this is the best solution.
The two of them live two aisles apart.
They'll know if the other is doing well or not.
I mean.
You're making your friend
watch his fiancee
be with another man!
Where's the brotherhood in that!
What about it?
You don't think it's fun?
This is poor taste!
You don't know men.
You don't know how to accumulate good karma.
So old yet so childish!
No grace at all.
You're not going?
♪I'll leave you a love letter♪
♪But I won't give you♪
♪The pain of the world♪
(All of this)
♪I'll never forget it♪
(is the way fate intended.)
♪I keep this body as it was before♪
♪But eternity is more like a bondage♪
(Ms. Luosifen said)
What were you thinking?
Shared bicycles are everywhere,
but you had to ride your own bike.
Now we have to fix the chain!
This is our first date.
Of course I want to bring you around myself.
The shared bikes don't have backseats.
Who knew Hu's bike was this crappy?
Failing at critical moments.
This is the result of trying too hard.
Get up.
I got this.
You can't just shove the chain somewhere.
You have to go like this
and let it catch the chain.
There we go!
You're an expert!
My family owned a repairing shop in the past
and modified motorcycles.
It's nothing
to me.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You wanted to see me fumble?
I just wanted to give you
a chance to show off!
Who knew you are as crappy as the bike?
Then...
Mr. Fu Liang!
Let me get this straight.
I don't need you to be good at everything.
I don't cook, you do.
You don't fix bikes, I do.
In this relationship,
we just have to do
what we're good at.
Does that mean
I should reward you
with the touch of love?
Stop, Fu Liang!
Kitty!
Kitty, kitty!
(You will not be with me my whole life.)
(But I will.)
(I will not grow old with you.)
(But you will.)
Here you go.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
I see you're the only one working today.
It's a Monday.
We don't get a lot of customers.
So the others will come in the afternoon.
(Computer Composition Principles Study Guide)
You study computing?
I study coding.
I can't fix computers.
Relax.
I won't ask you to do that.
But
can you take a look at this?
I went to a volunteer event.
I uploaded some photos just now
and it turned out like this.
There will be another event in two days,
and I need to upload even more photos.
If it turn out like this again,
I would be in trouble!
Sure, I'll take a look.
(Chinese Organ Donation)
This website of yours
is not going to make money.
See?
The design is ugly.
The server is bad.
Did you make it?
I'm only in charge of taking photos.
The website was probably made
by the other two volunteers.
I see.
Give me some time.
She hasn't been looking for Jin Xiaoyu recently.
So the two of us
think it's very suspicious.
I can understand how you feel.
As a volunteer,
as Fu Liang's friends,
the two of you are more alert.
Tan Yueran's interest in the donors
is not something new.
Some time ago,
she complained of not sleeping well.
About this,
I also discussed it with Chief Fan.
Chief Fan says
she keeps dreaming about a guy.
Did she say
what the guy looks like?
It's not some reincarnation TV drama.
How could she see his face clearly?
As a doctor,
once the illness is cured,
it doesn't matter where the drug came from.
But to an organ recipient,
aside from the bodily rejection,
psychologically accepting other people's organ
is the difficult part.
That's why I want to meet
Chief Fan in person to have a chat.
Medicine is science,
but there are always exceptions.
Chief Fan can solve some of them,
but not all of them.
You're also a doctor.
You should know this.
See that little girl over there?
We call her Cutie.
She's only twelve.
She's also a congenital heart disease patient.
When Tan Yueran first moved in,
she didn't like to speak.
Cutie was always following her around.
Later on, Tan Yueran's operation went well
and became much more lively.
Cutie, on the other hand, has become low-spirited
because of her worsening illness.
To see your ward mates getting better by the day,
while you wait endlessly for your organ to come.
She must be in despair.
Even so,
she's still full of smiles.
I guess,
this is fate.
The famous Zen girl.
Chief Zhou,
I can't bear to watch this.
Let's hurry and leave.
If you're so soft-hearted,
how are you ever going to make it
in this line of work?
(No smoking! No yelling!)
I
normally play some...
(Volunteer Checkpoint)
Wang Quande.
Master.
Did you see Jin Xiaoyu?
I think I saw her in the garden
with Professor Lin.
The handsome professor
that delivers body donors here.
No!
I just saw Xiaoyu
taking a stroll with a handsome guy
in the graveyard.
That's not Professor Lin?
Is that so?
She's not answering my calls,
nor replying to my messages.
I searched all over the place
and I still can't find her!
Master,
did you come
because you heard there was a handsome guy?
Of course.
Do you think I'm here to invite her
to play Mahjong with me?
Not answering calls,
nor responding to texts...
Something is up.
Stop talking nonsense.
Go tell everyone to report
on Jin Xiaoyu's location.
- Yes, Master.
Is this what humans are like after death?
You were like this the last time
you were sent here.
You haven't died enough?
I just want a normal death.
The type that would kill me in one go.
I'm lying down here to experience it.
But why are you lying there?
To experience
what it feels like to lie next to you.
Excuse me.
Young girls like you
should date more!
When I was young,
I visited all the big hospitals
looking for help every day.
Even in train stations, I had to do homework.
My master even had some dreams back then.
Telling me about all
the possible futures I could have.
Now, he just wants me
to marry someone that's alive!
Has your master considered
what your potential husband will do
after you pass away?
As a person who is close to death,
I hope my potential husband
can remember the good times we had together
and move on.
He should try to find love again
and live a new life.
But as someone that has such experience,
I have to remind you,
your wish
is only your wish.
Your husband
might keep in his heart
the good times you two had.
But he might not be able to move forward.
Because whenever
he sees something beautiful,
he's reminded of you.
That's why it's difficult to start anew.
Don't look at me like that.
How do you know I'm looking at you
when your eyes are closed?
Jiang Baiju.
In all the years you've lived,
have you truly loved anyone?
My parents.
Aliens have parents, too?
Besides your parents.
I guess it'd be my clients.
To borrow William's words,
every party A
is my true love.
You've never been in love?
Are you impressed?
No way!
Does it not seem that way?
♪For a moment, it's like a long time ago♪
♪The wind blows your clothes,
framing the scene♪
♪I don't recognize your delicate face♪
♪You're still young and my hair is still long♪
♪Who can tell if the dream
is an obsession or a lie?♪
♪If it's still there after so long,
it'll come true♪
♪If we part in this life,
we'll meet again one day♪
♪But I don't know what year it is♪
♪I'm too sensitive by nature♪
♪I hide my anxiety,
so you won't see through it♪
♪If you're hiding it on purpose♪
♪Why should I try?♪
♪It's hard to deal with
a neither-right-nor-wrong answer♪
♪Memories are fading away♪
♪Only a sense of vision leaves in my mind♪
♪I've been walking slowly♪
♪But you're not catching up♪
♪I'm just afraid that the road ahead
is not far enough♪
♪And I'll finish it soon♪