(Joy of Life Season 2)
(Episode 25)
Ling Er?
Ling Er, where are you?
Has she left already?
I sent my men to inquire about it from your residence.
They said you loved perilla soup.
That's why I told them to learn the recipe.
How's the taste?
The Ye family is in charge of the capital's defense.
They'll find you eventually if I vanish for no reason.
You didn't vanish.
You left the capital due to an emergency.
You even left behind a letter.
What letter?
You imitated my handwriting?
Take it away.
Why did you capture me?
I'm worried that you might see Wan Er by yourself
and tell her that Lin Gong's death was related to Fan Xian.
You mustn't be impulsive.
You shouldn't do that if you consider yourself as her friend.
How can they get married if you tell her that beforehand?
You do make it sound nice.
You just want to expose him during their wedding.
Do you not trust me at all?
What do you think?
Don't you think this silk ribbon is too long?
- Yeah. - I think it looks good.
I think it's a first-class top-grade ribbon.
First-class top-grade?
- What do you think? - I think it looks fine.
- Who asked you that? - What are you doing here?
He's looking for me.
- Don't leave yet. - I'm in no rush.
You can continue.
Finish it quickly and come back.
Tell me. What's the matter?
- Father told me to call for you. - I'll find him now.
It's fine. There's no rush. Your affair is more important.
But I'm in a rush.
Father.
Were you looking for me?
It does fit you perfectly.
Really? I'll take this, then.
No. I didn't say that.
My words don't count here.
I can't take it anymore.
When will the preparation end?
It's a major event. We have to be well prepared.
But all of them look almost the same.
What's the difference?
I do agree with that.
Did you do the same back then?
I tried out more clothing than you.
How did you pull through, then?
I endured it.
Why are you sighing too?
I was thinking
that ordinary folks have no chance to try out as much clothing as you.
The thing that frustrates you actually makes other people happy.
Was I wrong?
That's not it.
Are you sure you're Fan Si Zhe?
Could Fan Si Zhe even utter such brilliant words?
I've witnessed too much from my trip to Northern Qi.
Although the Qing Kingdom is considered a strong state,
many of the people are still starving.
So?
So,
I have to make more money.
The more money I earn, the more shops I can open.
It's best if I can open shops all over the world.
Qing, Northern Qi,
even Dongyi City, I'll open shops everywhere.
With all the shops I open, there'll be plenty of job opportunities.
I'm not thinking too far ahead.
I just hope that everyone can make a living.
That's right.
Earning money shouldn't be our only goal in life.
You're actually thinking of that.
I guess you've grown up as well.
Fan Xian,
I called you here because there's something you need to decide.
Your wedding has alerted the entire capital.
Firstly, you're known as the poetic genius.
Secondly, you'll take over the Imperial Treasury.
Thirdly, His Majesty granted the marriage to you personally.
Right now, all officials are waiting for their turn to congratulate you.
Our residence isn't that spacious.
We can't invite all of them here.
What do you think about
the wedding guest name list?
I'll give you a reminder.
Inviting them is easy,
but it's hard to choose who not to invite.
Those who weren't invited might take it to heart.
Who knows when they'll turn against you?
Xian.
Why don't we turn it into an auction?
So, it's inappropriate no matter who I invite, huh?
That's the case.
If so, I won't invite anyone.
It's a wedding. We have to hold a banquet.
We'll hold a family banquet, then.
A family banquet?
Look at it.
The carriage is here.
It's gorgeous.
What a beautiful carriage.
The flower carriage is here.
The flower carriage is so beautiful.
The flower carriage is here!
The flower carriage!
The flower carriage is gorgeous!
What a great scent.
Xian!
- Over there! It's coming! - Be careful.
A huge carriage is coming! It's so beautiful!
They said it was heading to you.
Did you know about that?
If so, I'll go and check on it for you again!
They scattered petals from Xinyang all the way to the capital?
They were scattering the petals 24/7.
Don't they need to rest?
They're doing it by shift.
That's a lot of petals. Can they even fit inside the carriage?
They scatter petals
and pick flowers on their way here.
I don't know how many flowers have been picked.
I was the one who chased her out of the capital.
Now, she's making all this commotion just to give me a wedding gift?
She's Princess Wan Er's mother after all.
She wouldn't be Li Yun Rui if she was a loving person.
- Here it comes. - Here it comes.
Here it comes!
Here it comes! Hurry!
Look at the fresh flowers.
It looks gorgeous.
It's so beautiful.
Look at that.
I've never seen this before.
The flowers smell great.
Who's sitting inside?
I can't even imagine it.
This is my first time seeing this.
What does she mean by that?
(Fan Residence)
Long time no see.
His Majesty ordered you to remain in Xinyang.
You cannot return to the capital without an edict.
I'm going against his order.
I came back in secret.
Now, you can press charges against me if you like.
Why have you returned to the capital?
These are for you.
Don't be afraid.
It's just my congratulatory gift.
You should be taking over the Imperial Treasury
after marrying Wan Er.
These are the ledgers of the Imperial Treasury.
Don't you think it's a sincere gift?
So, you went against the order and came back just to deliver these?
I want to see Wan Er
on the day of your wedding.
She's my daughter.
Her wedding day is the most important day of her life.
I never led such a life before.
However, I hope that she can lead such a life.
I also want to leave her with the most beautiful memories.
Therefore, a ceasefire will take place
between us during the wedding.
What happens after the wedding, then?
Isn't it obvious?
We'll be enemies again.
Have you never considered the fact
that I might not agree to it?
I said it already.
You may press charges against me.
I just want to do the things I desire to do.
I'll handle it
no matter what decision you make.
How long will you stay in the capital?
Depends on my mood.
- Where will you be staying? - Not the Fan Residence.
You better hide yourself well.
Don't you think it's time for you to address me as Mother?
Read it slowly.
Don't read it under strong light. There's no rush.
It's fine.
I'm done reading it.
What do you think?
The founding of the Imperial Treasury cannot be replicated.
It was the greatest shop in the world after all.
It was the greatest shop in history.
It's filled with ingenious ideas.
It has branches all over the world.
And, it's backed by the imperial family as well.
Judging from this,
the ledgers indicate that there was a loss of 20 million taels.
The way Li Yun Rui had handled the business,
she should've been executed for this.
It's not that easy to execute a member of the imperial family.
Aren't you shocked by the sum?
I expected that long ago.
Even if there's no loss now,
it'll incur losses once I take over it.
To you,
these are more than just ledgers.
This is also a trap.
Even if it's a trap, I'll deal with it after the wedding.
You're right.
Your wedding is the biggest event in the world now.
Your mother was looking forward to this day too.
Should I hide these ledgers first, then?
How?
She delivered them to you in a carriage full of flowers.
Why don't we be generous as well?
Generous?
Notify the Eighth Bureau to copy and record the ledgers.
Great timing.
You can use the item left behind by your mother.
(Seventh Bureau, Eight Bureau)
Who will we show them to after we're done copying them?
Those who are supposed to see them will receive a copy.
The Imperial Treasury's reserves are still intact.
Fan Xian is a genius too.
I assume he can cover the deficit
within four to five years.
The ledgers were delivered here under huge commotion.
Those who should know about it
will know about it.
All merchants in the world
pursue profit.
Since they know that the Imperial Treasury has a huge debt,
no one will dare to do business with Fan Xian.
The loss
will only grow.
If there's no turnaround within six months,
he has to give up on the Imperial Treasury.
Six months?
And, a loss of 20 million taels.
Even a deity cannot achieve that.
Unless
someone is willing to help him out.
Has Fan Xian ever expressed explicitly
that he would join your faction
ever since he came to the capital?
Not yet.
It's a huge debt of 20 million taels.
I think it's reasonable for him
to owe us a favor in exchange for our help.
You're saving him here.
Not many people wish to save you.
Many of them want to kick you while you're down instead.
After all, the sum is huge.
Are both of your eyes blurry?
No. Only this eye.
It should be presbyopia.
It's 20 million taels after all.
Aren't you concerned about it at all?
I'll put it aside first. It can wait until the wedding is over.
There's no need to panic.
Regarding the debt,
both His Majesty and I knew about it.
I'm not panicking.
Actually, this isn't the only reason I'm here today.
Wang Qi Nian already told me about the serial killings.
Did you see the culprit's face?
I thought you would seek me out on the same day it happened.
You wouldn't need to tell Wang Qi Nian to make a trip
if we could discuss this case out in the open.
You're good enough to be an official now.
Was it Mr. Wu Zhu?
I don't know.
From Jiangnan all the way to the capital.
All those who saw him were killed.
- What about the past few days? - The capital has been peaceful lately.
It seemed like the culprit had vanished.
If so, I'm sure it's not him.
Wu Zhu has forgotten many things.
What if it happens again?
What if he forgot about you as well?
What if he attacks you?
What will you do?
I'll do something about your presbyopia.
I'll definitely cure it for you.
What if he's the culprit?
What should we do?
Will you be attending my wedding?
It's a family banquet.
That's why I'm inviting you.
I lost my family long ago.
You still have me, don't you?
I'll see how it goes after the wedding.
Is this my wedding gift?
I can't just not attend your wedding and not give you a wedding gift.
That'll be inappropriate of me.
What's inside? You're acting mysterious here.
May you two have a harmonious relationship
and enjoy years of happiness together.
You look so beautiful.
- Mother? - Don't move.
Let me do your makeup for you today.
When did you return to the capital?
I came back in secret.
Did His Majesty not issue an edict?
No, he didn't.
If so, you're going against his order.
Since when did that happen?
This is a heinous crime.
I don't care.
You're getting married.
I'll be committing a heinous crime
if I don't come back for it.
Mother.
In this life,
I only agree with one thing.
What is it?
In the entire world,
I, Li Yun Rui, am the most beautiful person.
Although some individuals are too blind to see my beauty,
that's not my fault.
Who were you referring to?
That's not important.
I'm saying
that because I want to tell you this.
I have to come to the capital
because I have to do your makeup for you.
In this world,
if I allow someone else to be more beautiful than me,
that person has to be you.
And, it has to be today.
You were alone
since young.
You never had a happy life.
Even now, I can't make it up to you.
But today,
let me fulfill my duty as your mother.
Let me send you to the next phrase
of your life.
Mother.
Don't cry.
The makeup is perfect.
Mother,
can you stop competing with Fan Xian in the future?
Look at you.
You're so gorgeous.
As your mother, I've lost to you.
I've done
what should've been done.
Where are you going?
Since I came in secret,
I have to leave in secret.
Wan Er,
I've never led your life before.
I'm envious of you.
Stop right there.
From today onward,
forget about
this mother of yours completely.
I'm very happy
that you were able to come.
Where are we going?
Where else can we go?
Just let them off!
I was worried that you might be worried. That's why I want you to join me.
I don't know any martial arts.
If anything does happen,
you may kill me whenever you like.
Why are the horses still here?
Go over there. Park the carriage over there.
Guys, sorry about this. Please park the carriage over there.
Park the carriage over there.
Park it over there.
Guys, bring all the horses there, okay?
Sorry about this.
This looks so grand.
Yeah.
It looks so grand.
I'm sure it's a major figure.
Yeah.
It does look grand.
What a grand carriage.
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Is this the crown prince?
- Are you... - I'm Wang Qi Nian.
Gift bearers, follow me.
I know what you guys are going to say.
This is a family banquet. You guys don't need to follow me.
- Who else has arrived? - Get out of the way!
The...
Get out of the way!
This is an urgent letter sent by Northern Qi.
- Is Northern Qi invading our borders? - No, this isn't about war.
Northern Qi wrote a letter to Lord Fan.
It's just a private letter.
How could the border army rush here just to deliver it?
The person who wrote this was Northern Qi's emperor.
How could the groom pour us a drink?
It's a family banquet. The customs don't matter.
What's wrong? I'm getting married,
yet you look more nervous than me.
Fan.
Come.
Is Miss Ruo Ruo here?
What's wrong?
Are you trying to act drunk before drinking?
According to the palace,
Ruo Ruo and I will get married after your wedding.
Ruo Ruo doesn't want to get married.
Fan Xian,
that's an imperial edict.
Whether Ruo Ruo and I are willing to get married or not,
that doesn't matter.
But she doesn't want to get married.
What should we do, then?
Don't tell me she wants to go against the imperial edict?
Actually,
I've always had a good impression of Ruo Ruo.
Since that's the case, I should try to know her better.
I'm sure you can rest at ease since you know me well too.
What about Yuan Meng, then?
Yuan Meng?
About Yuan Meng, that was just a ridiculous event in the past.
I never participated in the events
related to Moon Embracing Pavilion.
I trust you.
I've also forgiven you.
However, Ruo Ruo won't be married to you.
Our marriage was granted by His Majesty. Who dares to defy him?
Congratulations.
Your Highness.
- Greetings, Your Highness. - Cheng Ru.
Put the gifts in that room.
Don't touch any intriguing items you see, you hear me?
I came here only for one reason.
I came here to drink with my brothers.
That item,
have you fixed it?
I have.
The emperor of Northern Qi wrote a letter to you. Take a look.
My Lord.
He's urging me to update my chapter.
What does that mean?
The emperor of Northern Qi loves "Dream of the Red Chamber".
Is that all?
There's other news too.
Your Highness, you may read it yourself.
One of the four grandmasters, Ku He,
wants to take
Ruo Ruo as his last disciple?
Isn't Haitang Duo Duo his last disciple?
According to the letter,
she didn't last. That's why he's taking another last disciple.
How is that a valid reason?
The four grandmasters are extraordinary at martial arts.
It's inevitable for their thoughts to be different from ordinary folks.
Send this to the palace and let His Majesty decide it.
I'll get to it right now.
All right now.
Take your seats.
Fan.
Fan,
how did you do that?
Do you still think the wedding between you two will be held?
Judging from the grandmaster's intervention,
I'm afraid the marriage granted to us by His Majesty will be voided.
The four grandmasters are above the imperial court.
Do you think that's a good thing?
It has always been like this.
I was just saying. Don't take it to heart.
Take your seat now. The dishes are getting cold.
Why isn't there anyone on the streets?
You're right. Why isn't there anyone here?
You don't need to keep holding my hands.
Xie Bi An isn't around.
I can only depend on you if an assassin were to attack us.
I feel safer holding your hands.
I can protect you.
But remember that you made me a promise.
You said you wouldn't ruin Wan Er's wedding.
If you don't trust me,
why don't you kill me right now?
Look. I'm alone, and I don't know any martial arts.
It's easy for you to strike me down
and be free of all your worries.
If you dare to speak nonsense during the banquet,
I'll definitely strike you down.
It's a promise, then.
What promise?
It's either you protect me
or you strike me down.
I'll leave my life
to you for now.
Once you marry Wan Er, we'll be considered relatives.
We're a family.
Cheng Ru, I'm not lying.
I have had sleepless nights
because of our brother over here.
The Imperial Treasury has such a huge debt.
What should we do about it?
Your Highness, you're benevolent indeed.
There's one more thing.
I think Northern Qi has high regard for you as well.
But no matter how huge of a debt the Imperial Treasury has incurred,
it's our affair.
We mustn't use money from other kingdoms to fill up that hole.
That's a taboo.
Your Highness, you don't need to worry.
No matter how much the emperor of Northern Qi likes my novel,
he would never pay 20 million taels to me so that I could update it.
No other world would do this.
You're right.
Speaking of which,
what should we do about the Imperial Treasury's debt?
Today's Fan Xian's wedding. Let's not talk about that.
Let's drop the topic. But I'll say one last thing.
Luckily, that guy is under house arrest.
I'm sure the wedding will be chaotic if he's here.
My Lord, Prince Cheng Ze is here to congratulate you.
Luckily, I came here alone.
If not, there would be no space for me.
They're unlike you. At least they fear death.
I fear death too.
But that's not what I fear the most.
What do you fear the most, then?
I fear
a calm and peaceful life.
It's so boring.
You're ridiculous.
Your Highness, Lord Fan
is inviting you inside.
Since it's his wedding, all guests are welcome.
Great. I was worried that he might not let me in.
Your Highness, please.
All of you are here, huh?
Greetings, Crown Prince.
Cheng Ze, spare the formalities.
Wait, you're not bowing to me?
Cheng Ze, you made an appearance during Fan Xian's wedding.
I can see that you're a loyal person.
However, you went against His Majesty's order.
If His Majesty does blame you for it,
Cheng Ze, we brothers will share the blame with you.
Were you referring to my house arrest?
I already requested his permission.
You requested his permission?
It's Wan Er's wedding. I requested permission from His Majesty
to attend it.
That's great.
Cheng Ze, I was worried for nothing.
Sorry about that. I'll punish myself by having a drink.
I'll join you.
This is a rare sight to behold.
I can't believe that such brothers exist in the world.
Here's my wedding gift.
Thank you.
Why don't you check it out?
Initially, I prepared some jewels and accessories.
But when I thought about it, you didn't lack them at all.
I chose a more direct approach.
Here's 500,000 taels.
That's too much.
This is just scratching the surface.
The Imperial Treasury incurred a loss of 20 million taels.
I'm worried for your sake.
You two are brothers indeed.
What was that?
The crown prince was worried about the same thing.
I can never be as benevolent as the crown prince.
Let's consider the common folks' approach.
You taking over the Imperial Treasury is also a major task.
You still need to do business.
But with that debt, it's hard for you to do business.
That's fine. I know many merchants.
They'll have to help you out
for my sake.
- Yes. - Cheng Ze's intention is kind.
But...
Merchants never act if there's no benefit.
If you accept their help today,
what'll happen tomorrow?
All of them will interfere with the Imperial Treasury.
That'll be terrible.
But you see, Cheng Ze isn't like all those merchants.
He's not a materialistic person.
He's definitely a kind person.
Crown Prince, you have excellent insight indeed.
However, we can't just let the Imperial Treasury
crumble under Lord Fan's leadership, right?
That's right.
He's our brother. How can we leave him in the lurch?
But even real brothers
are turning against each other, you know?
What's wrong, Crown Prince?
Do you plan to fork out the money?
It would be a huge deal if I were able
to fork out that sum.
I guess you were wasting our time here.
Fan, if you're free tomorrow or the day after tomorrow,
you can come to my residence.
We can always find a solution to our issues.
Great. From now on, both the Overwatch Council and the Imperial Treasury
will belong to you, Crown Prince.
Cheng Ze, you mustn't crack such jokes.
I dare not act like you.
I don't dare to form factions in secret.
You should consider my proposal as well.
You don't need to join my faction.
It's just a deal. We're just getting what we need.
Yeah. A deal with endless implications.
At least it's better than selling oneself for glory.
I guess my hand slipped again.
Taking one is more than enough.
500,000 taels is enough
for the Censorate to impeach me at least eight times.
I don't want to jinx this festive occasion.
Your Highness, have you ever heard of the term "honeymoon?"
Is it a kind of dessert?
No. That means Wan Er and I will take a break after our wedding.
No official affairs will be entertained.
Your Highness, I appreciate your intention.
But I won't be visiting you.
How can you repay the huge debt
without any help?
Today's a great day. I don't wish to talk about this.
Everyone, this is my first time participating in the wedding ceremony.
The auspicious hour will arrive soon.
Why don't you guys observe the ceremony together
and join in the fun?
The auspicious hour has arrived!
Shouldn't the matchmaker be the one holding the ribbon?
I stole her job from her.
I want to witness this important moment myself.
Two hearts as one,
never apart.
Wan Er, I have something to tell you.
Young Master!
We can talk after the wedding ceremony is over, okay?
No!
I have to tell her right now.
Wan Er,
Father told me to tell you this during your wedding.
What is it?
He told you
to
Take good care of Da Bao.
Okay.
I promise you.
- I'm done. - You're done? Good.
I'm done!
Da Bao, you're done.
- I'm done. - All right.
Shall we begin?