(Joy of Life Season 2)
(Episode 18)
Isn't this the Spring Imperial Examination?
Can't they depend on their abilities?
These are not just names.
They are also the ways of the world.
Oh, Fan Xian,
the tree that stands out
is the one that gets knocked down.
It's good to be knowledgeable,
but it's more important to know how to be tactful.
You'll get used to it eventually.
Have you met Guo Zheng?
You know that too?
Guo Zheng used to be the Chief Imperial Censor.
After Guo You Zhi was imprisoned,
he temporarily took over the role of Minister of Rites.
There are many taboos in the Spring Imperial Examination.
You should consult with him often.
I've met Guo Zheng once, but...
You didn't quite get along.
Uncle, Guo Zheng led the renovation of the examination hall...
It's all according to regulations.
He's been an official for many years after all.
He knows all the rules inside out.
He knows how to use the rules to protect himself.
You will need to learn that too
in the future.
I know you feel uncomfortable about it,
but toughen up.
Once you get through the exam,
your future career prospects are limitless.
The crown prince went to see him?
Sit.
Yes, Your Highness.
After that, Fan Xian went to Chancellor Lin's residence.
So, he's pulling strings.
Your Highness,
we have a few names too.
Should we send a list over as well?
Not this year.
These are all scholars loyal to you.
We'll leave it to luck this year.
The traps are already set,
we can't jump in ourselves.
Do you think Fan Xian will follow the usual rules
in this Spring Imperial Examination?
Who would dare to defy
years of established customs?
He's different.
What others are accustomed to,
he might not be.
Qi Nian.
Yes?
When I first heard about the corruption
in the Spring Imperial Examination,
I was really motivated to eradicate
all the accumulated corruption
and restore fairness for all the scholars.
You truly care about the country and the people, My Lord.
But in just a short while,
the crown prince and Chancellor Lin handed me a list.
What can I do?
To fight against Prince Cheng Ze,
I need the crown prince's support.
And as for Chancellor Lin, it's even more complicated.
I'll be marrying Wan Er after the exam,
making us family.
I don't want to accept what they gave me,
but I can't refuse.
You have no choice, My Lord.
Do you know what Chancellor Lin said to me?
What did he say?
He said everyone is used to it,
and I should just endure it.
If I endure it now,
I'll get used to it in the future.
Everyone is used to it,
so why should I be the one to stick my neck out?
If I do so,
I'll face opposition from all sides,
with swords and knives raining down on me.
Maybe I should just put up with it.
My Lord,
you have a bright future ahead.
Why should I be the one to bear all the troubles?
Why should I face betrayal and enmity,
and live in a world of torment?
Qi Nian,
I'm just an ordinary man.
I'm not that special,
I'm not that brave,
and I'm not that righteous!
My Lord,
as long as you have a clear conscience.
My conscience is clear.
My conscience is clear!
I'm not the one at fault!
My Lord,
no one is arguing with you.
My Lord.
Shi Chan Li and the gang haven't done anything out of the ordinary.
You...
I got it.
I just want to check.
Let him go on his own.
Come, have some food.
Study after dinner.
Wan Li.
Who are you?
Mr. Fan?
Why don't you take a seat at the table?
I brought my own food. It's not polite to take up a seat there.
- What are you... - I'm reading while eating.
Why don't you read inside?
Mr. Fan,
the candles inside cost money.
Out here, it's free.
So, you're a little tight on money.
You're being too polite.
I'm just plain poor.
Waiter,
we'll have a roast chicken, a plate of beef, and a pot of wine.
Sir, aren't you going to sit at a table?
Why sit at a table?
Right here is just fine.
All right.
Mr. Fan,
what are you...
Each encounter is destiny.
Let's have a drink together.
I can't accept this.
Just treat me back someday.
This is not necessary.
I must thank you for this meal.
Gentlemen,
enjoy your meal.
Sir, your dishes are all here. Enjoy.
All right.
Excuse me.
I haven't had meat in so long, I couldn't help it.
This happens all the time.
- Then I... - Go ahead.
When we were in the examination hall, you said
you wanted to become an official.
- Why did we come to the capital? - To become officials.
And why are we working in the examination hall?
Also to become officials.
Yes, I dream of it, even in my sleep.
Is it to gain honor and glory for your ancestors?
No,
it's because I can't stand it anymore.
Mr. Fan, the imperial examination system is unfair.
Officials are corrupt,
people are starving outside,
and the court is embroiled in political strife.
Who in the world doesn't know that?
Yet no one says anything about it.
Ji Chang advised me to endure it,
but I think, if I choose to endure it even when the world is unjust,
what's the point of all these teachings from the sages?
So, Mr. Fan,
someone must break the silence, even if it means shedding blood.
Look, if I were to achieve success in the exam,
wouldn't the bloodshed be more pronounced,
the impact greater,
and the number of people who hear about it larger?
I want to become an official
because I refuse to endure it.
Wan Li, your vision of being an official
would lead you to death.
A dead end indeed.
But Mr. Fan,
I've become a fool
from studying too much,
stubborn in my beliefs.
Please forgive my foolishness.
Wan Li.
- My Lord. - You've worked hard, Zi Yue.
Keep watching the inn for the next couple of days.
You didn't have to say that.
It's my duty.
Qi Nian, let's go.
Back to the residence?
To the Overwatch Council.
You want to go to the Overwatch Council at this hour?
I want to read the inscriptions again.
What did I tell you?
He's always spontaneous.
I heard that.
What can I say?
This is called profound deliberation,
wisdom as deep as the sea.
My Lord, you truly are extraordinary.
Goodbye.
Thoughts of you make one grow old,
time has suddenly grown late,
abandon not the path once chosen,
work harder to earn a meal.
You're in charge of overseeing the copying of the names, right?
When the time comes, take a look at these names for me.
These are not just names.
They are also the ways of the world.
Those listed in this list
will all become useless manuscripts.
Look, if I were to achieve success in the exam,
wouldn't the bloodshed be more pronounced,
the impact greater,
and the number of people who hear about it larger?
Actually, I know it too.
I have no chance of making it onto the list.
All the slots have been filled,
and there's no place left for us.
But what can I do? I'm just a poor scholar.
Fan Xian, you see,
they've traveled thousands of miles to the capital,
the Spring Imperial Examination
is not just an exam for them,
it's like a ray of hope.
These are my favorite phrases.
Get out of the way. You're blocking my light.
They can't afford to pay for candles,
but still want to have light.
Thank you.
When my mother was alive,
she wanted to change this world completely.
It wasn't just changing the world,
your mother also wanted
to change people's hearts.
At that time,
she was like a dazzling meteor,
and also like a blazing flame,
showing the people of the Qing Kingdom a different light.
But she still died.
However,
that light left its mark.
Many people
changed because of her.
Sometimes I often think,
with my mother's abilities,
if she had chosen a different path back then,
she would still have lived well.
Yet she chose to burn everything and leave behind inscriptions.
But now,
there aren't many people who remember her.
Do you think she regretted it?
Absolutely not.
Even until her last moment?
I didn't see her at her last moment,
but I believe Ye Qing Mei never regretted it.
Wasn't she afraid?
She was only afraid
that her light wasn't burning brightly enough.
I never thought that one day,
I would become the one to pass on the flame.
- I want to make some trouble. - Sure, go ahead.
Whatever trouble you cause, I'll take the blame for it.
I can't let you bear the blame every time.
What blame?
I have a better scapegoat.
A better scapegoat than me?
That's right.
The best scapegoat in the world.
Fan Xian asked you to deliver a message to me?
I find it quite baffling myself.
After all these years,
I've never seen Lord Fan act in such a manner.
What's the message?
He requests Your Majesty
to summon him to the palace.
Summon him.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Fan Xian?
Lord Fan!
Commander Gong?
How may I help you?
What are you doing here at this late hour?
His Majesty has summoned him.
Now?
According to protocol,
no court official should enter the palace at this hour.
His Majesty's orders are the protocol.
I'm just doing my duty. Please forgive me.
Your Majesty,
Fan Xian is here.
What is he...
Your Majesty, I heard that you were injured by gunpowder a few days ago.
I've been worried about you.
So, I specially prepared some burn ointment for you.
Also, considering your daily worries over state affairs,
I've also prepared some calming and tonic medicine for you.
Take it after dinner every day.
The burn ointment is for external use.
Is there anything else?
That's all.
You say you were worried,
but why don't I believe you?
I've been injured for several days already,
and you only showed up now.
It took some time to make the ointment.
Also,
if you wanted me to summon you,
why go through such a big hassle to let others see?
Truly, nothing can escape Your Majesty's eyes.
All right, speak up. What do you want to tell me?
Your Majesty, do you trust me?
Just say whatever you came to say.
Your Majesty, are you aware of the corruption
in the Spring Imperial Examination?
Since I took on the role of Central Official,
I've been receiving numerous notes every day.
These notes are filled with names,
and these names
are preselected by someone,
earmarked for success in the exam.
Keep going.
I would like to request fairness in this year's
Spring Imperial Examination.
If you want fairness,
why come to me?
I'm afraid the implications are too deep,
and I alone cannot bear the responsibility.
In the entire Qing Kingdom,
only Your Majesty can weather this storm.
Are you asking me
to be your scapegoat?
Not for me,
but for the Qing Kingdom.
Why do you sound so much like Lai Ming Cheng?
Are you holding resentment about Lai Ming Cheng's death?
Yes.
You shouldn't.
You're quite candid.
For your candor,
I'll be your scapegoat this time.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I shall take my leave now.
Apply the medicine
to me before you go.
His Majesty summoned Fan Xian to the palace?
- At this hour? - If it wasn't urgent,
His Majesty wouldn't have summoned him in late at night.
Are you sure?
Gong Dian saw him with his own eyes.
Even he found it unusual
and relayed the message immediately.
Does he know what was discussed?
Gong Dian said even Eunuch Hou came out.
What was discussed inside,
no one else knows.
Even Eunuch Hou came out.
That's enough for now.
Ask Gong Dian to stop finding out what they talked about.
His identity is crucial.
Tell him that unless it's absolutely necessary,
don't send any more messages to me.
Yes, Your Highness.
I wonder what His Majesty
said to Fan Xian.
Whatever they talked about doesn't matter.
Summoning him late at night and in private...
His Majesty holds Fan Xian
in too high regard.
Your Highness,
I'm really unable to handle this matter.
I hope Your Highness can forgive me.
I heard that His Majesty
summoned you to the palace yesterday.
Yes, that's true.
Did His Majesty give you any orders?
His Majesty
didn't say anything.
He didn't say anything?
I didn't ask anything either then.
Your Highness, everyone will have to rely on
their own abilities in this year's exam.
That's the way it should be.
Lord Qin.
Lord Fan.
I knew you would take this path.
- How? - You don't want anyone to see you.
Doesn't this just prove that we're destined to meet?
Lord Fan, I owe some favors from my time in the military.
I have a few names here,
please look out for them for me.
I'm sorry.
It's just a few people.
Please help me spread the word.
- What word? - This year's exam
will be assessed on actual talents, not background.
I will not take anyone's list.
Did His Majesty summon you last night
precisely for this matter?
His Majesty didn't say anything.
Oh, I see.
Since His Majesty didn't say anything, I'm not guessing anything either.
Uncle, I'm really sorry.
It's just that I must adhere to the rules
regarding the Spring Imperial Examination.
Why did you do it?
I have no choice.
I know His Majesty summoned you to the palace last night.
Now everyone will assume that His Majesty
instructed you to act in this manner.
I know His Majesty.
With his methods,
he would either swiftly eradicate all forms of corruption
like a thunderstorm,
or he would subtly
manipulate behind the scenes.
Even when his plan naturally comes to fruition,
he never lets anyone see through his true intentions.
He would never hastily summon someone in the dead of night,
only to let things end so peacefully.
This isn't His Majesty's way.
You're using him as a shield.
Uncle, you know His Majesty so well.
No one can truly understand him.
Among all the kings in Qing Kingdom's history, he's the most inscrutable.
You're being too modest, Uncle.
Don't change the subject. I'm asking you.
Why did you do it?
Actually, I just want
the Spring Imperial Examination
to be fair and justifiable,
even if it's
just once.
All the officials in the capital are watching the examination closely.
Aren't you afraid?
Of course I am. That's why I'm making His Majesty take the blame.
And I've seen through it, haven't I?
If I were to expose it,
would you be able to deal with it?
Uncle, you're family.
Please leave me a way out.
Why should I spare you?
Because Wan Er won't marry anyone else but me.
If you're gone, Wan Er can always find someone else!
You're right, Uncle. Please calm down.
I don't know if it's fate or doom.
Why did Wan Er have to fall for you?
Well, I'm pretty outstanding, you know.
You want to create a fair system for the Spring Imperial Examination.
What's your motive?
What can you gain from this?
Actually, I understood
what you said last time.
The tree that stands out is the one that gets knocked down.
So, I had thought about
swimming with the tide and doing what others do.
What's wrong with that?
For things I don't like, I could endure them
and eventually get used to them.
But I just couldn't do it.
I couldn't sleep at night.
I'm tormented inside.
There is this word that keeps rolling around in my mind,
and I can't suppress it.
Which word?
Well, unfairness.
That's two words.
"Well" doesn't really count.
We're scholars.
We should be cautious with our words.
I'll be more careful next time.
"Unfairness."
So, it's all about that.
Do you believe
there's fairness in this world?
Not absolutely,
but relatively.
What?
There's no absolute fairness in this world.
Just like some are born into wealth,
while some are impoverished.
Some have sharp intellects,
while some appear foolish.
And the Spring Imperial Examination is meant to provide everyone
with a relative fair chance to change their fate.
If even this one chance is not fair,
how absurd would the world be?
All right.
Let's make things fair
in the capital for once.
Go meet with Guo Zheng again.
I've arranged it.
Ask him about the taboos and regulations of the examination in more detail.
While you want to fight for fairness for them,
don't let yourself fall into a trap.
Fan Xian,
if the world
is truly that absurd,
what are you going to do?
You don't need to answer.
Ask yourself.
Go.
Fairness...
Lord Fan.
Lord Guo, we meet again.
I've been waiting for you, Lord Fan.
Minister Guo, you're well-versed in the rules.
I've come to seek your guidance
on the rules of the Spring Imperial Examination.
Chancellor Lin has told me about it.
I'm not good enough to guide you.
Lord Fan, with your intelligence,
you could've figured it out yourself.
I'm just providing additional information.
I've prepared it for you.
Lord Fan, given your capability,
you're in charge of many tasks
during the Spring Imperial Examination.
Before the exam starts,
there's the task of inspecting the examinees.
During the three days of the exam, you'll need to
supervise and patrol the hall.
After the exam, you'll need to oversee the registration of names.
The Spring Imperial Examination is the most important event in our dynasty,
with numerous rules and taboos.
There are too many to list verbally,
so I've written them all down.
All the detailed rules are included.
As long as you take the time to look through them,
you can ensure there are no oversights during the exam.
How can I repay such a great favor?
- Lord Fan. - Yes?
Come here, go over there.
This pillar...
Straighten it.
- Lord Guo. - Lord Guo.
Lord Sun, the exam is coming. I'm busy.
- I'm busy. - I'll leave you be.
You've worked hard, Lord Guo.
Thank you.
Now I'm just looking forward to seeing you
write your own book and establish your own school soon.
I'll be content then.
Thank you very much, Lord Guo.
- I'll take my leave now. - Goodbye, Lord Fan.
How did it go?
Didn't you hear us back there?
Fan Xian is a highly skilled martial artist. To be cautious,
I didn't dare to get too close to eavesdrop.
That's a pity.
You didn't see the deeply grateful look on Lord Fan's face.
I almost felt bad for him at that moment.
What did you write in that booklet for him?
All the details about the various rules and regulations
of the Spring Imperial Examination.
I can't afford to make any intentional mistakes on written papers.
You did right.
Fan Xian
is very cautious.
However, for significant events like the Spring Imperial Examination,
there are inevitably some rules that shouldn't be written down.
Since they shouldn't be written,
naturally, they had to be left blank.
Please tell His Highness that with me around,
I'll ensure that Lord Fan violates taboos during the exam.
While it might not be a major offense,
it will make scholars throughout the country keep their distance from him.
Aren't you afraid of offending Chancellor Lin?
Of course I am.
But he doesn't have
any leverage over me.
His Highness said
that those were just old and useless ledgers from the past.
After the ban is lifted,
he'll personally come to express his gratitude to you and,
in passing, burn all those useless papers.
Then His Highness
can just sit back and watch the show.
(Fan Residence)
- Are they here? - They're in the room. Everything's arranged.
Nobody saw them, right?
They avoided everyone in the residence.
Don't worry, nobody saw him.
They're starving.
You're back.
I'm back.
Returning from Northern Qi this time
was truly a journey of hardships.
Fortunately, Bao Kun and me are unparalleled duo.
No matter what obstacles we faced,
we cleverly overcame them.
That's how we managed to escape danger
and return to the capital.
You two seem to get along well now.
Heroes appreciate heroes.
Young Master, now that you've returned home in glory,
I must treat you to a meal and catch up.
Let's talk about what to eat.
- I'll treat you. - No, let me.
I'll treat you. Come on, Qi Nian!
Young Master, you sound so energetic.
What should we eat?
I'll treat you.
My undercover diary.
You've worked hard.
He said you called me here to save my father's life?
Here's the thing.
I'm in charge of overseeing the Spring Imperial Examination.
What does that have to do with me?
There are many taboos of the exam that I don't know about.
- I don't know either. - But your father was the Minister of Rites.
You want my father's help?
That's why I asked you to come back.
Your father can only be at ease when he sees you.
You're planning for the exam so early?
Actually, when Prince Cheng Ze proposed I oversee the exam,
I was already preparing strategies to deal with it.
Now, it looks like the timing is just right.
You guys,
- each more cunning than the other. - I'm just being meticulous.
All right, spill it.
How do you plan to save my father?
I'll arrange it.
I'll transfer him to the Overwatch Council's jail in a few days.
Will you still be able to get him out then?
I'm the Chief Inspector of the Overwatch Council, what do you think?
But there's one thing you should know,
your father's accusation of collusion isn't fabricated.
I can save his life,
but returning to an official position
is out of the question.
I understand.
Just keeping him alive is good enough.
I'll talk to my father
and make sure he tells you everything
he knows about the Spring Imperial Examination.
What's this?
A booklet personally written by the current Minister of Rites.
Many of the taboos of the exam are listed inside.
- Then you don't need my father. - On the contrary.
I need your father to go through this.
You're worried there might be traps written here?
It's better to be cautious.
Whether there are traps or not,
let your father judge.
All right.
- Let's go and save my father then. - There's no hurry.
Si Zhe.
Lower your voice.
You've both taken a long trip here.
You must be exhausted.
Take a few days to rest.
Be careful not to let anyone see you.
Of course.
We'll be extremely cautious.
I'm relieved.
Come on.
First of all,
welcome back home, both of you.
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
The odor is a little too strong.
Why don't you two go wash up? You both stink.
- Do I stink? - You're all right.
Come on, I'll rub your back.
Let's go, hurry.
Why aren't there any guards here?
Isn't that obvious?
This is the Ministry of Justice's jail.
You even have authority over here?
I have some tricks up my sleeve.
Since you have such means,
why don't you just get him out today
instead of just bringing him food?
Don't worry.
It'll be easy once he's transferred to the Overwatch Council.
It'll just take a day or two.
Relax, I won't deceive you this time.
You've deceived me several times before.
Bao Kun, why is it every time you speak to me, something feels off?
Off?
I've already washed up.
Just shut up.
Son, I'm here to see you again.
She got another one.