♪How I wish to see you but I can't,
so I close my eyes♪
♪Your voice makes my heart ache
out of longing♪
♪Like the day we met♪
♪The colors are so brilliant♪
♪And warm♪
♪My uneasiness and timidness fade away♪
♪Your warmth makes me brave♪
♪Like a small animal♪
♪I curl up next to you♪
♪So tender♪
♪I often wonder♪
♪what changed everything♪
♪I come prepared with limitless love♪
♪I arrive on time
to see you grow strong♪
♪I'm here to stay♪
♪We face the peaceful
and disturbing days together♪
♪Falling in love♪
♪The world is so sweet♪
♪ Fulfill our unfulfilled promises♪
♪Falling in love you♪
♪Two brave hearts♪
♪Trek through
the highest mountains until forever♪
=Amidst a Snowstorm of Love=
=Episode 11=
I was wondering how you managed
to stay at the top level.
So you've been secretly practicing here.
How is it a "secret"?
It's such a huge place
with so many people.
Here.
Thanks.
Why did you take over
this billiard room?
I made that decision on a whim.
Perhaps, I'm just used to it.
Sometimes, I may be too tired to train.
Just sitting here,
listening to the sound of cues
striking the balls
makes me feel at ease.
Want some?
I'll be chubby.
No, you won't. It's dark chocolate.
One bite?
You're stuffed?
Yeah.
Don't eat my leftovers.
(And he finished it.)
What's wrong?
(Even my parents
wouldn't eat my leftovers.)
What's on your mind?
I'm thinking about
the game.
I don't know the local players.
I don't know what to do.
There's nothing fancy about them.
I'll show you the way they play.
Really?
Of course, I was planning to come back
and practice with you this week.
But I fell sick.
I know the local players.
You're so smart.
I bet you'll get it very fast.
Okay.
Yiyang, we ran out of water.
Can you put us some?
Yeah, we're thirsty.
Yiyang, should we call her
sister-in-law?
I'm Yin Guo. Just call me Yin Guo.
Hello, I'm Zhou Wei.
Hello, I'm Li Qing.
Nice to meet you.
So pretty.
Are you also here for the contest?
Yeah, I play the Nine-Ball.
Nine-Ball?
- I also play Nine-Ball.
- Really?
I'm Xie Yaoyao.
Me too.
This is Mr. Qian.
He also plays Nine-Ball.
Hi, how should I address you?
Yiyang is my coach.
I'm older than the others.
So they call me Mr. Qian.
That will do.
Mr. Qian.
Sister-in-law, how did you know Yiyang?
Yeah.
I...I...
Tell us.
Let's play Nine-Ball.
Alright, I'll train a bit.
If you're available...
Don't you want water?
I filled it up. Come here.
(Storage)
- See you.
- Bye.
Bye, sister-in-law.
Let's go.
Sis, here's your water.
Thank you.
Yiyang is very thrifty.
He always looks
for the chalk that's ending.
But he's putting new ones for you.
Alright, I'll leave you
to train. Go ahead.
The Chinese female players
are the best in Nine-Ball.
When you play games at home,
you're facing the top players.
So don't be afraid of the local players.
They're the ones who should study you.
I know, but it's my first time here.
I just want to play it safe.
I'd prefer to know every contestant
to secure my victory.
Right, there's a senior player
Liu Xiran. Do you know her?
I heard she was from Dongxin City.
I know her.
She's back this year.
You'd better be careful.
She's highly experienced.
Don't underestimate
your girlfriend, okay?
I know.
I've watched all your video clips.
Keep practicing.
I'll come back and pick you up.
Let's have something nice.
What would you like?
No need. Anything will do.
Aren't you hungry?
Just a little bit.
What's wrong?
I want to save you some money.
You're under financial pressure
in business.
Don't be silly.
We can't save money on food.
It's close by. Let's walk there.
Another dish?
I told you not to get
so many dishes. It's too much.
I can't finish my food.
Alright, leave the rest.
Have the lobster.
I'll have the rest.
You're eating my leftovers.
Don't you feel awkward?
Why would I? We're family.
You're just like my brother on that.
He can never finish his food.
I have a small appetite.
Didn't your little brother get adopted?
I kept him for two years before that.
He was in kindergarten
and I was in primary school.
He was such a nice kid.
They often gave out snacks
in the afternoon.
He would always keep
the nice things for me.
He would get a bag
and pack the snacks for me.
The teacher found out
that my brother never finished his food
and would always pack it for home
even though he needed to eat.
So he called his parents.
So you went there.
Who else did he have?
The teacher was startled
when he first saw me.
You must have missed him a lot
after the adoption.
There was no other way. Back then,
I couldn't support him.
Right, I have an interview
in the afternoon.
Go ahead. I'll be fine.
I'll walk around a bit and wait for you
in the billiard room once I'm tired.
Let me take you somewhere.
Wait for me there.
Okay.
Why are we here?
Aren't you going to the university?
I booked you a hotel room for tonight.
My place is tiny.
You didn't sleep well last night.
That's not true. I slept just fine.
No need. It's such a waste.
- Let's go.
- I've paid.
It's under your name.
You check in on your own, okay?
Okay, but no need...
I'll pick you up at seven.
Wait for me.
Is everyone from your billiard club?
Not really.
We're not a developed billiard room.
Yiyang doesn't draw
a percentage of our prize money.
It's our second home.
He's a free coach for us.
So it's profiting from
the external business?
Yeah, from the tenants
of the youth hostels
and some amateurs nearby.
But few and few people
are interested in billiards nowadays.
Ever since he took over this place,
he's been losing money every month.
That's the situation.
(You didn't sleep enough. Take a nap.)
I was still talking and you took off.
Can we go Dutch?
I can't make you pay for everything.
The society values gender equality.
You're giving me pressure.
You're just a student.
And Sun Zhou told me that
you've been digging into your pocket
for the billiard room.
You've been digging into your pocket
(Do you regret dating a poor student?)
(Are you serious?)
I've been a poor student too.
I only managed to win prize money
because of my occupation.
Otherwise, I'd be a poor student, too.
I've been a poor student too.
I only managed to win prize money
because of my occupation.
Otherwise, I'd be a poor student, too.
♪Is it the sunshine calling at us?♪
♪Everything I did, leads to you♪
♪Isn't our fate so undeniable?♪
♪Everything we did, leads to us♪
♪Lovely you♪
♪How'd you steal all my heart♪
♪And through all the years♪
♪You kept it♪
♪Oh, my lovely you♪
(Bank account)
(This is all I've got.)
(2314.09 Euro)
(He didn't even cover
the account info. So careless.)
(3412.21 Euro)
♪Love is what we are♪
(44274.34 Euro)
♪That you and I had been♪
♪Ever did I think, to ever have you♪
♪And kiss you♪
♪Love is so bright♪
(Guo: CNY 202491)
♪So finally, just let me be, your man♪
(Mine.)
(Guo: CNY 202491)
♪Bitter bitter sweet♪
I don't have much as you do.
But it's pure income, at least.
Tell me if you need working capital.
Make sure you do.
♪Bitter bitter sweet please♪
♪My dear♪
♪Love is what we are♪
(Silly girl.)
♪Ever did I think, to ever have you♪
♪And kiss you♪
♪Love is so bright♪
♪And it feels so unreal♪
♪So finally, just let me be, your man♪
(It's only three.)
Who is that?
Didn't you say seven o'clock?
Yeah.
It's seven.
Until I put you
on the train back to Hel,
I won't leave again.
Don't you have an interview?
I'm not going.
I hate to leave you alone.
Why do you smell so nice?
I had a shower before I went to sleep.
Didn't you...
(You're a grown man. Don't you know)
(that girls smell nice
after the shower?)
What?
Not telling me?
Didn't you...
Why are you smiling?
What did you do
to be so pretty?
Sweet-talker.
Tell me, did you have many admirers?
Xiaodong had many disciples
in my secondary school
and forbade them from pursuing me.
So most of them
didn't even dare to talk to me.
I guess I have to thank him for that.
There was only once
that I got scolded for nothing.
An international student had my name
written on the back of his uniform.
I had no idea about it.
But the teacher called me there
and asked to see my parents for that.
My brother went there.
He looked at the group photo
of our class and said,
"He doesn't stand a chance."
"My sister has no taste."
"She only likes good-looking guys."
Thankfully, I look fine.
Or I may not win you over.
So narcissistic.
You know, I'm from
the Seventh Secondary School.
Really?
It's only five minutes' walk
from our school.
Tell me more. I'm curious.
About what?
Your past.
I told you.
Feel free to ask me anything.
I'll answer as much
as I remember.
My parents passed away together.
On a business trip,
a car accident happened on the freeway.
They worked in two departments
of the same company.
My mom would usually stay home
with me and my brother.
But that day,
she decided to go with my dad.
Since you're talking about it,
you've let it go, right?
What else?
Nothing. No more questions.
I was sleeping.
You woke me up. I'm still sleepy.
Let me carry you to the bed.
Compass.
Yeah.
Why are you wearing this?
I was lost after I graduated
from the university.
(I didn't know what I should do.)
(I traveled to an island,)
(passed by a necklace store,)
(and saw this.)
Then why doesn't it have a needle?
Because there's no direction.
I talked to the craftsman.
He said that
once I found the direction,
I could install the needle.
Your phone is ringing.
It's yours.
Mine is not on vibration.
It's not mine. It's yours. Let me see.
Stay put. Let me see.
It's yours. Stop lying.
Talk.
Your PhD application is almost approved.
I changed my mind.
Why? What's wrong?
It's a great opportunity.
It's a pity to give up on it.
Did anything happen to you?
I never decided on it.
That's it. My girlfriend is here.
Why are you changing your mind?
Like I said, I never decided on it.
Are you planning to go back for me?
How do you know?
Don't be impulsive. It's serious.
I know.
Then...
Just kidding.
♪Waste the entire winter♪
♪Paint our holiday♪
♪See the clouds on the mountain
and walk along the seaside♪
♪Chase after the sunrise and sunset♪
♪Spend our time carefree♪
That's it?
♪Create memories
in a season of our lives♪
I'm sleepy.
♪Breathe onto the glass♪
♪I know everything
is going to fade away♪
♪Like the beach washed by the waves♪
♪The surprises and regrets will be gone♪
♪But my heart will be full of blossoms♪
♪I know it won't happen over and over♪
♪Like a shirt kissed by summer♪
♪It's shot in black and white♪
♪But in my dreams,
it's brightly colored♪
♪Spend our time carefree♪
Are you asleep?
♪Call out to you in the wind,
and recall you in my dreams♪
♪Breathe onto the glass♪
You woke up?
Where's my phone?
Don't worry. I'm well dressed.
So, are you hungry?
I woke up because of that.
Let's have something nice.
What's so funny?
Don't you have something else
to do with me apart from eating?
The bus is coming right now.
There will be a tour guide
who will explain everything.
Hey, Lin, you're back!
Yeah, it's me tonight. Let me hold it.
Okay, guys. Get on the bus.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
- Bye.
Stuffed?
Mind your step.
You have work tonight?
Yeah, you're coming with me.
Hop on.
We can go now.
Where do I sit?
Here.
We still have ten people
at the next stop.
Ten?
Where are we going?
We're going on a night tour.
A night tour?
Yeah, it's a tourist route
for both day and night.
I've been a tour guide once,
working with this driver.
So I contacted him when you were asleep
to take the shift tonight.
You've done
so many things as a part-time.
Hello, everyone. My name is Lin.
I'm your tour guide for tonight.
Before we start, I would like to take
a name list first. Thank you very much.
Sydney Garsindon.
Check. Mind the step, please.
Felina.
Philie.
Mind your step, please.
Mary.
Christine. Are you Chinese?
Chris Anna.
Malala.
Thank you.
Okay, mind your step.
There are two people not in there.
(Mr. Lin, you look good.
May I have your WeChat?)
Wait, wait.
Here.
Jessica.
Jessica, nice to meet you.
Thank you.
Mind your step.
Yelena.
Nice to meet you, Yelena.
So that's it.
♪Hello, I never was so sure
to say it out♪
♪But maybe it's too much
to hold it down♪
♪To look away, the night sky♪
♪Hello, you never were
so fond of memories♪
♪It takes forever just to find the love♪
♪To live a life, under the star light♪
♪So would you say it back♪
♪Dive in the direction of us♪
♪And let the starlight out and shine♪
♪It's just you and me♪
We're here.
♪So fight away to find our love♪
Alright, guys.
There are restrooms right over there.
Let's take a five-minute break
before we go.
♪We might've made a few mistakes but♪
♪Love and shine♪
♪The only way
to find ourselves' through♪
♪Love and shine♪
♪No matter how the snow is falling♪
Tired?
A little bit. I'll stay this time.
Okay, wait for me here.
I'll be back after the activity.
It won't take long.
Have some water.
See you.
Okay.
♪Hello, I never was so sure
to say it out♪
♪But maybe it's too much
to hold it down♪
♪To look away, the night sky♪
♪Hello, you never were
so fond of memories♪
♪It takes forever just to find the love♪
♪To live a life, under the star light♪
Thank you.
Done?
Yeah, let me take you somewhere.
It's close by.
Okay.
Cheers.
♪It's just you and me♪
♪There's nothing our faith can't do♪
♪So fight away to find our love♪
Look, so many stars.
♪Love and shine♪
That one is so bright. Did you see it?
Yeah.
♪The only way
to find ourselves' through♪
♪Love and shine♪
♪No matter how the snow is falling♪
Want some?
Why are you always carrying chocolate?
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
Nowhere specifically.
We've visited the famous attractions.
Shall we go back?
Okay.
I need a good night's sleep desperately.
I'll let you sleep.
(Train Ticket)
I'll take you back tomorrow.
I thought we'd
spend the weekend together.
It's fine by me, but not you.
You're distracted here and it may
affect your performance.
I'll accompany you
back to Hel and come back.
Fine.
Are you upset?
No.
Just take me to the train station.
Why would you travel to Hel?
It's too much trouble
to go back and forth.
Just let me accompany you.
Then I can spend
a few more hours with you.
(1 hour 18 minutes)
We're halfway there.
Yeah.
Why are you checking that?
I'm calculating when to get you a cab.
I can get a cab myself.
♪Waste the entire winter♪
♪Paint our holiday♪
♪See the clouds on the mountain
and walk along the seaside♪
♪Chase after the sunrise and sunset♪
♪Spend our time carefree♪
♪Create memories
in a season of our lives♪
♪Call out to you in the wind,
and recall you in my dreams♪
♪Breathe onto the glass♪
♪I know everything
is going to fade away♪
♪Like the beach washed by the waves♪
♪The surprises and regrets will be gone♪
♪But my heart will be full of blossoms♪
♪I know everything is going to change♪
♪Like the beautified image of summer♪
♪The thrills, the joy, the sorrow,
the smiley face covered in sweat♪
♪But my love
is not complete without you♪
♪The bitter and sweetness
spread between my lips♪
♪I still look forward to miracles♪
♪The laughter and tears
both speak of sweet sorrow♪
♪How I wish it all ends
on this very day♪
♪This very day♪