=Veil of Revenge=
What is the password?
One, nine, three, six, one, seven.
It's not relevant to
any of my information.
Of course you can't figure it out.
Do you want to know
how I found out
you checked my bank account?
=Veil of Revenge=
=Episode 21=
This.
But,
you drank that wine.
That wine?
I'd taken the cure
long before I drank it,
so it didn't work for me at all.
So, honey,
what are you going to do?
Zhiren!
It was Chen Yueran
who forced me to do this!
Chen Yueran?
I thought she was
Mr. Chen's illegitimate child.
Guess I was wrong.
She not only wants
to take away my properties
but wants to destroy me.
She impersonated Chen Yue
to freak you out,
so she must know something.
Could she be...?
Then what should I do?
Just act normal.
Don't let her find out anything.
Then...
Then install this on her car.
Did you get the password?
No.
After Li Zhiren passed out,
I tried many times but failed.
He's very suspicious.
I wouldn't dare drug him every day.
Keep looking for the password.
I need you to do
something more important.
I hired someone to cook the books
and put it in the USB drive.
Replace the file in his computer
with this.
I have something to do.
You should go.
How did it go?
I've installed it on her car.
Zhiren!
Are you okay?
Why?
I'll get some water for you.
Are you feeling better now?
Why are you shouting?
I'm not deaf.
Do you want to try again?
Maybe later.
What's this?
Chen Yueran hired someone
to cook the books
and asked me
to copy it to your computer.
She's clever, isn't she?
(Unidentified USB Drive)
(Transacting...)
(Completed. Balance: 0)
Didn't you say it was false accounting?
It's a virus!
What's happening?
Did you conspire with that b*tch
to do this?
- I didn't!
- Did you do it?
- You didn't?
You didn't?
Didn't?
Gave my money back!
My money is gone!
It's all gone! It's all gone!
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)