=Veil of Revenge=
Chen Yueran got everything
because of Gao Lingyu.
If we turn them against each other,
it'll be much easier.
You're right.
I'll get more water.
=Veil of Revenge=
=Episode 20=
Li Zhiren has a foreign bank account.
Get the account and its password.
(Important Document)
Let me help you.
Why do you know this place?
Why are you hiding from me?
- That...
That night,
I was drunk,
so we should pretend
that...
nothing
happened.
Nothing happened that night.
Then the mark on your neck...
What mark?
Well...
It's a mosquito bite.
Why were we
in the same bed
half naked?
You got drunk
and puked all over me.
You wouldn't let me go,
so I had to take off my clothes
and stay with you,
and I fell asleep.
Don't worry,
I won't take advantage of you
when you're drunk.
Yue,
I've fallen in love with you
since college.
You only know I died once,
but you have no idea
what I've been through.
I know everything.
Sorry, Yue,
I investigated you.
I just wanted to know who you are.
I found the plastic surgery hospital
and the apartment you once lived in.
I know what you've been through.
However, if you don't move on,
you can never forget the past.
God has given you a chance to live
and given me a chance to love you.
I don't want to lose you again.
Can you be my girlfriend?
If you don't want to, just push me away.
How did you survive?
That day...
Miss!
(In Surgery)
My face!
Am I disfigured?
Calm down.
Okay. Thanks.
(Zhang Lu, Maid)
If I'd known you'd suffer that much,
I'd never give up and let you go.
It's not too late.
When Li Zhiren is put in jail,
we'll start over.
It's not too late.
Yue,
is there anything I can do for you?
No.
It's up to Zhang Lulu.
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)