Each day felt special and warm
that winter.
And at the end of it, Woo-jae disappeared.
What about me made him choose to leave?
What did I do wrong?
Why did I think
I was to blame all those years?
I'm sorry.
FIRST SOLO EXHIBITION BY JEONG HUI-JU
EPISODE 4
WHAT SHOULDN'T BE LOVED
Woo-jae
really misses you.
I thought you two
had broken up.
You're right.
I should've broken up when you told me to.
I think I turned out this way
because of him.
He totally ruined me.
What are you--
Had I known the reason why he left me…
Had I known where and what he was doing,
I wouldn't have been in this much pain.
I told myself I'd never forgive him.
I made a promise to myself
God knows how many times.
But having resenting him
for all those years…
It's been unbearable.
Forgiving him seems easier.
So I'm going to forgive him.
Because Woo-jae
came back.
Whenever I think of the good times
I've had with Woo-jae,
you were always there too.
We should all get together soon.
-Actually, he's--
-No.
I don't understand.
Even married couples get over each other
once they divorce.
You only dated him briefly years ago,
and he dumped you coldheartedly at that.
But you haven't gotten over him
resenting him all these years?
I don't know how to feel about that.
I had my reasons.
Right. You were always quick to justify.
-I--
-If you're trying
to justify assaulting Li-sa
by giving excuses
about your personal misfortunes,
it's no use.
Whatever your reasons are, it doesn't
change the fact that you hurt her.
Let's not meet ever again.
Am I the only fool here?
If you want to leave, leave on your own.
You can't take Ho-su.
She should've
heard me out.
Hey.
Hi.
Why were you sleeping there?
He wouldn't go to bed.
It wasn't easy tucking him in.
Goodness.
What did you do today?
I was preparing for the exhibition.
It must be tiring working until late.
LEE JU-YEONG
Ms. Gu, here's the video.
Doesn't it look real?
Well, we're not making anything
from scratch.
What do I need to do next?
Isn't it a bit too much
to have a bottle by yourself?
I'm expecting someone.
Another glass, please.
Because Woo-jae came back.
Woo-jae really misses you.
Bullshit.
Li-sa, let's go.
Do you know what this is?
-What?
-This flower.
That's a flower?
What? You don't know either?
When we were living there…
Where?
That place.
You were there too.
You were. I'm sure of it.
What was this flower called again?
Heath.
These wildflowers
bloom once a year in the wilderness.
Isn't it amazing?
Mom, isn't this pretty?
Li-sa, stay here.
Pull over.
I'll drive you to the school gate.
I don't want others to see us together.
By the way, where were you yesterday?
-What?
-Last night.
Mom was in her studio. Where were you?
Well…
You're late.
No, I'm good. I drove here.
What a shame.
You're paying for this bottle.
I didn't know you were married.
You were born on April 10, 1990,
and are married to Seo Woo-jae.
Am I right?
Is that a problem?
Hold on.
Why are you even interested
in my personal life?
I'm not interested in you.
But I am interested
in your husband.
Where have you
hidden him?
Hidden?
That's rich coming from you.
Does she know
what kind of person her husband is?
Probably not.
She'd have left if she did.
How have you endured it
knowing everything?
You've decided to sweep
everything under the rug
and believe you can still keep
living as a good husband and father.
Is that arrogance
or just a delusion?
If you don't stop, I swear…
I'm done.
Why bother arguing
when we're both miserable?
You don't know me enough
to peg me as a miserable person.
Maybe you're not.
Where is Woo-jae?
What'll you do with him if I tell you?
Does Hui-ju know?
I'm not sure if it's a good thing,
but she refused to hear me out.
Why don't you just drink?
I think we'll be here for a while.
PUBLISHING CONTRACT
We haven't published
a fourth-edition essay in a long time.
Are you working on your next one?
You should.
I thought of what our readers
would want to read about,
and I'm stuck.
Of course, they want
to hear about your story.
Really?
I doubt they want to hear
about how I went from rags to riches
by marrying a wealthy man.
I'm aware of it.
I know people gossip about me.
And I won't deny it.
You've made it this far
because you're good.
You have so many fans
who love your paintings.
And I have my husband
to thank for that, at least partially.
I was able to solely focus on my work
unlike others who struggled
to make ends meet.
So I doubt any advice or comforting words
from me will mean anything to them.
It'd be nice to share
those honest thoughts.
I should just write them in my journal.
Then did you ever have a painful--
No, I don't like bringing up the past.
I like where I am now.
We'll hire eight new teachers
for the major courses within this year.
The Office of Education approved it.
Three are internally-selected,
and we'll hire the rest this month.
What about the general course teachers?
We can't dismiss them
due to the teachers' rights.
We're considering transferring them
to schools under our foundation
or sending them to other schools.
In a year or two,
we'll need more teachers.
So let's have them come back after a year.
Yes, sir.
Form a school personnel committee.
And make sure they all sign
the Declaration of Ethical Conduct Form.
I believe Mr. Lee Hyeong-gi
from Taerim Foundation will--
The medical foundation
has nothing to do with our school.
-Please take care of it yourself.
-Yes, sir.
And leave out anyone
who was selected through connections.
But sir, the foundation has already--
The internally-selected teachers
could become a problem.
Please relay this message to Mr. Lee.
But…
You may leave.
Have the residents been signing
the consent forms?
Yes, sir.
This region is commercially depressed.
So they're open to moving
or switching their line of work
if the compensation is enough.
But some are still against it.
How about some coffee?
I look forward to learning a lot from you.
How do you have
such decisiveness and good judgment?
They come from experience.
-Right.
-In other words, you're talented.
Not at all.
I've worked hard to get this far.
Hello.
Let me.
I'll wrap it up then.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
-Drink on your way.
Hey, I thought we were going
somewhere nice, not here.
This hospital's coffee tastes the best.
I wonder why.
You're right.
Gossiping and coffee
go well with each other.
Seeing even the wealthy die eventually
makes you
feel a bit better
about cleaning up after them.
You're right.
Seeing others suffer is so entertaining.
I only stick around
because it's so entertaining
to see you grovel in front of Ms. Park.
-Has she changed at all?
-What do you think?
How terrifying.
Hang in there.
She'll end up in there soon.
I heard their beef pâté is scrumptious,
but they're always fully booked.
You're the best.
And here's what you asked for.
He'll be back in Seoul tomorrow.
I told him I'd give you his number,
so send him a text first.
We must've had good connections
when he was a cop,
seeing how he always gets the job done.
Thanks.
I should thank you.
While I was at it,
I convinced him to come fishing again.
Why did you even break up?
You guys were doing great.
It's simple. We didn't love each other
enough to endure everything.
Are you seriously going
to leave like this?
I haven't been out in ages,
so I have many errands to run.
-Did you call a cab?
-I did.
How's Ho-su? Is he more attached to you?
Not at all.
He's different from kids his age.
He loves his grandma more than me.
At times, I'm afraid
that he'll choose her over me.
Other times, I wonder if I truly love him.
And that thought scares me
more than anything.
Of course you love him.
The fact that you crave his love
and are afraid of losing him
proves that you love him.
Don't doubt yourself. Okay?
My cab's here.
-Bye.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
She looks like one of my customers.
Your customer?
Is it one of your regulars?
No, she just left a strong impression.
-Bye.
-I'll call you.
-Okay.
Right.
Rheumatism?
Apparently, my immune system
fails to recognize my own body
and ends up attacking it.
It's a chronic disease,
so you must take good care of it.
It must've been painful.
At times, pain isn't that bad.
When you suddenly wake up
in the middle of the night…
Have you ever felt that way?
Your limbs feel so stiff
that you can't even move.
You're not aware of your surroundings
and wonder if you're dead.
That's a symptom of rheumatism.
Suddenly, you feel a sharp pain
and realize
that you're not dead after all.
Then you can breathe again.
You feel this pleasure--
It's foolish to enjoy the pain.
Put your arm down.
You're right.
I am a fool.
I won't deny that.
But I'm not evil enough
to enjoy seeing others suffer.
I'm regretting what I did…
to Li-sa.
Can you help me meet with her again?
I haven't been able to see her
since that incident
because her parents wouldn't let me.
I have no ulterior motive.
You told me
I should apologize to her sincerely.
Yes, you should. Before it's too late.
I will.
So that
she knows how to apologize
when she does something wrong.
NEUROSURGERY DR. AN MIN-SEO
My afternoon shift has started.
If it's not urgent…
Were you aware of it?
The children of the hospital directors
who favor you…
Did you know I jumped through hoops
to get them into the art school?
But it all went down the drain.
I oversee all the legal teams
in our foundation.
But your brother considered
his school separate.
You know I'm not well-versed in that area.
Exactly.
Your stupidity is
what makes me look like a fool.
Are you a doormat?
Are you going to waste your life slaving
away for that money-grubbing family?
That's my family you're talking about.
-How could you say--
-Exactly.
Why aren't you sly like them?
You take after your father
and only know how to treat patients.
Right?
Doctor An, your patients
are waiting for you.
I'm the one you'll spend
your remaining life with, not them.
Got that?
Don't be content with your position here.
Climb up the ladder.
Come in.
Hello.
Let's see.
You've gotten much better.
Thank you.
Thanks to your help,
I avoided disciplinary actions.
The more generous Taerim is,
the better the image and value it'll have.
LAWYER LEE HYEONG-GI
MS. GU HAE-WON
HAS SENT A VIDEO
I'll be glad to help again.
I trust that you'll get me rehired.
Turn the handle smoothly
so you won't spill anything.
This is much easier.
-Right?
-Yes.
Wash the portafilter well,
or it'll look like your face.
Come on.
We have a customer.
I can take a break in five minutes.
One cup of coffee, please.
I've never gotten
a brand-new phone before.
I've always used
secondhand or thrown-out ones.
Your dad never bought you one?
What does he do for a living?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Aren't all dads like that?
You never know what they're up to,
and they always drink at home.
I don't have a mom, so don't ask.
RESTORING DATA
Excuse me.
-It's on me.
-Thank you.
Does he know as well?
-Know what?
-That you don't have a mom.
Don't open up to everyone
just because they're friendly to you.
-What?
-About how you don't have a mom
or any money.
Or about your dad drinking every day
and how that makes you feel lonely.
Things like that.
Why not?
Because you'll look vulnerable.
They can pretend to worry about you
and easily win you over.
What's wrong with that?
They're concerned about me.
Because it's terrifying
when those people change.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
How would you know?
You have a husband and are well-off.
Because there was a time
when I had no husband or money
and only a mom who'd drink every day.
I'll clean it up.
Thank you for the phone.
What about this phone?
You can keep it.
Check it when you're bored.
LI-SA'S TUTOR
Hello, ma'am.
Li-sa isn't home yet,
so we should postpone today's class.
It rings, but she's not picking up.
I think she's doing it on purpose.
Where is she?
Who?
Your art teacher.
She was just here with you.
Where did she go?
Where the hell is she?
You skipped your tutoring class
and didn't answer your phone.
-What were you doing with--
-What about you?
Why did you meet with Ju-yeong
behind my back?
-At the cafe this afternoon--
-I told you
that she's a leech.
-It was because you--
-I told you
she sponges off others
to get what she needs!
So why won't you listen to me?
Li-sa.
An Li-sa!
Why won't you answer me?
What were you doing with--
She apologized.
That's it? Did she say anything else?
What else--
What else does she need to say
other than that she's sorry?
Then why would she come
all the way here to see you alone?
Because she wanted
to apologize for what she'd done.
What?
Do you think she hit me
because I did something wrong?
Do you believe that lunatic?
GAMJATANG
I'd like what she's having.
No side dishes, please.
There are no empty tables.
But others will think
that we're eating together.
Is that bad?
I don't mind.
But I don't want that woman
from before to get the wrong idea.
No, she won't be coming here today.
An older girlfriend?
I don't think she's your mom.
Neither.
-Then who is she?
-What about you?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
I have a husband.
BUS STOP
Are you going home?
Your bus.
It broke down
at the three-way intersection.
I see.
It'll take some time.
Hop in. We're going in the same direction.
I'll let you know that I don't usually hop
into a stranger's car.
But today, I'm a bit exhausted.
But I'm not a stranger.
That's true.
That's why you should be more cautious.
Those around you can be
even more dangerous.
I have some stuff to drop off at the bar.
Can I drop you off here?
Sure.
Oh, right. Look.
Don't tell her that you saw me today.
-What?
-My daughter, Hae-won.
Don't tell her.
Okay.
And
thank you.
How long have you been waiting? Hold on.
RICE MEAL
Give me one minute.
Don't like my mom.
I don't.
Then why give her a ride?
Oh, that? You see,
the bus broke down
at the three-way intersection.
She likes handsome men.
They can be scumbags
as long as they're good-looking.
But you're…
Okay.
I'll ignore her from now on.
You seem like a decent guy. That's why.
My mom has gone through some stuff.
People like her
tend to torment those around them.
That's a relief.
There are many
who torment others for no apparent reason.
You wouldn't know why
no matter how many times you wondered
why they're doing it.
Anyway, I warned you.
What? Where are you going?
Didn't you come here to drink?
But I'm not a decent guy.
I believe you. I'm sorry.
If that teacher approaches you again,
then tell me--
I'm going to rinse off now. Get out.
I just did that out of worry
that she'd hurt you again.
I'm sorry for not telling you
that I was meeting--
Get out.
Li-sa, no one can steal me from you.
You do know that, right?
I had no other intentions.
I just wanted
to buy some time.
Born on October 24, 1985.
The resident registration number
is 152831.
His name is Seo Woo-jae.
Correct. Woo-jae.
One more person, please.
Gu Hae-won, born on April 10.
Correct.
Thank you.
Hello.
Where's Min-seo?
She had surgery scheduled this morning.
She should look after her body
before tending to her patients.
Ho-su.
Ho-su, you shouldn't draw on this.
-Give that back.
-You have your book.
-Read this.
-Hey.
Don't worry about my grandson,
and take care of your family.
Your mom called and thanked me.
Must I continue putting up with this?
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
Of course you didn't know. Again.
So Hyeon-seong did it by himself?
Her business fails every single time,
and yet, he keeps giving her money.
That's an illness.
She shamelessly asks for money
and whines about how hard she works.
Tell her to just stay home.
I'm sure you give her an allowance.
-Mother.
-Am I wrong?
You should stop too.
You've done more than enough
for your poor mother.
Most people exchange loyalty
for money, but she…
Goodness, my puppy. Come here.
Goodness.
Let's see.
I'm sure she didn't say that out of spite.
I'd rather she did, to be honest.
Sorry?
It's more appalling
if she's saying such awful things
with no spite.
Don't mind me. I just forgot something.
You should've called.
-It's my phone that I forgot.
-I see.
It must look realistic.
That's what's most important.
BILLIARD HALL
PROTECT OUR PROPERTY RIGHTS
What is it?
I was wondering if you were still open.
I heard this place is getting sold.
Who the hell said that? You should leave.
Are you Lee Ju-yeong's father?
What the hell are you talking about?
BILLIARD HALL
Ms. Gu.
So you're telling me
that if I hold out and don't sign this,
the school plan may fall through?
This entire building will be cleaned up.
It's not part of the school region,
but if any of the stores aren't
student-friendly, it won't happen.
For example, this billiard hall?
Correct.
I wouldn't be able
to move out even if I wanted to.
I put this house up as collateral
for this place.
How could I possibly leave
without a premium?
That's why you should get compensation.
However, you may end up with nothing
if you get too greedy and it's canceled.
So you must listen to me
and sign it after a negotiation.
I trust you.
If I get compensated,
I'll treat you--
You should treat Ju-yeong, not me.
Right. Ju-yeong.
Art school will be pricey
even if she receives government benefits.
That's fine
as long as you're her teacher.
That's my wish as well.
So you should listen to me carefully
and never be rash.
Be patient and look at the big picture.
Okay. I'll do that.
Goodbye.
Did we have to meet here of all places?
I felt like we should.
Six months ago, they moved into a place.
But I don't know
if they're actually living there.
It's not that far,
so you can go check yourself if you want.
Okay.
Is Dong-mi doing well?
Yes.
HOUSEHOLD REGISTER
SELF: SEO WOO-JAE, WIFE: GU HAE-WON
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE
SEO WOO-JAE, GU HAE-WON
Marriage?
We're not having a wedding.
We're just registering our marriage.
They mean the same thing.
There are many ways
for you two to study abroad together.
You're too young to get married.
I found out that there are
many benefits for married couples.
What benefit do you need
when you passed the language exam
and got admitted?
What did he do while you were studying
German and preparing your portfolio?
Does he even want to go?
If you do go, he'll have to study
for the entrance exam,
and you'll have to do
part-time jobs to make ends meet.
Hui-ju.
You'll have to provide
for someone else while studying abroad.
How will you--
You know I have good stamina.
Marriage isn't a dream.
It's your only chance
to dramatically turn your life around.
Just because it worked for you
doesn't mean it'll work for me.
I know how you feel.
But you really don't need to worry.
I'm going to be happy.
Are you here to see the house?
Someone else came by a few days ago.
It's a good apartment.
I see.
Let's begin the shoot.
Look at the camera. One, two.
Good work.
Can I talk to the bride?
I'll take some shots of the bride.
Okay. Here we go.
Okay. One, two.
One, two.
Good.
Put your shoulder a bit forward. Good.
Here we go. One, two.
Move.
Is this what you wanted?
Look at me.
Do you want me to get married like you?
So that we can all be miserable?
Seeing how you came this far,
you don't want to end it with her either.
You're wrong.
I only came because you asked me to.
If you don't want me to, I won't.
Just say the word.
Tell me to stop.
Here we go. One, two.
-Okay. You're done.
-Thank you.
Are you done?
It was so awkward.
I didn't know smiling
was so difficult. My face feels stiff.
You should at least have
some photos, right? You did well.
I don't think I can do this twice.
You look so gorgeous.
You're literally shining.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
Hey, Woo-jae.
I'm going to be happy.
Who are you kidding?
Am I interrupting?
I'm kind of stuck today.
What's up?
I was organizing
some clothes in the bedroom,
and this fell out of your purse.
I was wondering what it was.
Oh, right. I told you before.
Li-sa threw and broke Ju-yeong's phone.
But why do you have it?
She's really something.
I bought her a new phone,
and she told me to go through it
if I got bored. There was nothing.
There was something.
Did you already see this?
Yes.
Don't get the wrong idea. Ms. Gu and I--
I don't.
You look really irritated in that video.
Others may get the wrong idea, but not me.
Should I be relieved or frightened?
Maybe it's for the better. Be careful
not to cause any misunderstandings.
By the way, I wonder why she took that.
Maybe Ms. Gu told her to.
The teacher
who visited Ju-yeong's
and counseled her several times
was Gu Hae-won.
People who aren't well-off
tend to get attached
to teachers who give them attention.
Maybe Ju-yeong's the one who told her
where Li-sa's dance studio is.
What?
Ms. Gu came to her dance studio
to apologize to her.
I was wondering how she found out.
There's definitely something
going on between Ms. Gu and Ju-yeong.
I'll meet with Ju-yeong again--
No, focus on your exhibition.
Leave this to me.
I don't want to cause a commotion
until our school gets approved.
I'll take care of it.
This is under my jurisdiction now.
I'll let you be.
THE MEANING OF SILENCE,
FROM DRAWING TO CARVING
Who's the artist?
I heard that you handpicked him.
You wouldn't know even if I told you.
At least not yet.
I'll introduce you during the reception.
Doesn't it leave
a strong impression despite being bland?
I love it. I truly do.
You know, I used to prefer arts
that were majestic and spectacular.
Ones that expressed anger
towards violence in society
and strived to save mankind through art.
Back in college, I had a crush
on a senior who studied sculpting.
This is what he said.
He didn't even like to see me smile.
He despised laziness.
He said wealthy women who did this
as a hobby could never create art.
He loathed how poor he was
but also used it as a shield.
You must've liked him a lot.
It sounds like you're pining for him.
Back then, yes.
Back then, I believed pitying him
and torturing myself
was considered sublime love.
I'm curious about his work.
It must be so captivating.
He's dead. He was devastated
by this world's lack of understanding.
And he destroyed all his work.
That's why I love your work.
Your purpose is clear,
yet the audience can make
their own interpretations. I love that.
You should've written
the testimonial for my exhibition.
I was turned away
for being such a passionate fan.
Ma'am.
By her.
-This way.
-Okay.
Watch your step.
This must be your first time
attending a reception in a while.
The artist is someone
I am taking extra care of.
This is his first exhibition,
so he must be tense.
And he knows no one in Korea.
He was too sick to work on any
for a while.
Please guide him well.
Sure.
-I see you put in a lot of effort.
-Yes, a bit.
Sir.
I came without any attachments,
but why haven't you put anything aside?
Is this funny to you?
I'm sorry for leaving you all alone.
Does it look like I'm worried
and nervous to you?
All of the things that I missed out on,
I'm going to make it
the way it should have been.
-Hui-ju.
-It's been a while.
How have you been?
Do you know me?
What are you playing at?
What is that you're trying to achieve?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim