Did you go somewhere this late at night?
What is going on?
What have you done to him?
I comforted him.
What?
Mr. An seemed
to be having such a tough time
to the point where
watching him suffer felt awful.
Why did you do it?
You two had a happy marriage
and he really cherished you.
What was the problem?
Your mother-in-law?
You said you could put up with her
as long as he was on your side
no matter how scary she was.
So why?
Shut up and leave.
You were the problem after all.
Your greed.
You wanted to maintain
stability in your life
and satisfy your desires at the same time.
Had you been willing to risk everything,
I wouldn't have hated you as much.
If you were going to steal him,
you should've kept him.
Was he a toy you could toss away
once you were done?
You must have been so happy
when you found out he'd lost his memories.
Blame me for what I did to you.
Just stick to what concerns you!
You don't get to blame me
for what I did to Woo-jae.
That's his business.
And everything between my husband and me,
that's none of your business, so butt out.
Don't use someone else's pain
against them. Got it?
Do you know why betrayal is so cruel?
Because betrayal makes you
endlessly doubt
the person you love the most.
You ruined everyone.
Me, Woo-jae,
and even your husband.
Honey--
He's a man, after all.
You don't think he can't cheat too?
Damn it.
EPISODE 15
BREAKUPS ARE HARDER THAN BEING IN LOVE
Thanks.
Do you remember?
What?
Who brought you home?
Yes.
What happened?
Why did Gu Hae-won bring you home?
Well…
Hyeong-gi…
I went to the building
where Mr. Lee's accident took place.
And I ran into Seo Woo-jae there.
You see, we still have lingering feelings.
I remember that look on your face.
You looked just like this
when you came to the pub looking for her.
You were worried that Hui-ju might come
back to me, but you pretended not to be
and that you were fine.
I'm going to split it with Gu Hae-won.
I'm willing to give up everything I have.
Can you still say that
this is just infatuation and lust?
You must be more worried than before
because Hui-ju…
doesn't need the stability
from you anymore.
Who are you kidding?
You knew that Hui-ju
would abandon you in the end.
That's why you didn't end things with me.
You were a selfish coward.
Stop pretending you're some romantic.
What's going on between you two?
I'm not like you.
I came here to see Mr. Lee.
Where is he? He said he was
meeting you here the last time we talked.
Mr. Lee is severely injured.
-What happened?
-I heard it was an accident.
It was an accident.
And it must stay that way.
We can only find out what happened
if Mr. Lee gains consciousness.
There are no security cameras
in that area.
So for now, Seo Woo-jae's statement
as the witness is everything we have.
You don't believe him, do you?
I doubt that Woo-jae hurt Mr. Lee.
He has no reason
to turn down Mr. Lee's help.
But seeing how he still won't talk…
Hui-ju might have something to do with it.
Is that your point?
We'll know once Mr. Lee wakes up.
I…
I'm not sure if that's what I want…
If I really want to find it out…
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
They say forgiving someone
is like letting go of a prisoner
and then realizing
that the prisoner was actually yourself.
But look at us.
It looks like
you and I are still locked up in prison.
That means
you still haven't forgiven Hui-ju yet.
I was exhausted and desperate for a drink.
Is that all?
Should there be more?
But you didn't have to drink with--
Don't assume
that I'd cheat because you did.
Yes.
His surgery is over.
His post-op condition
is better than expected.
As you all know,
Ms. An is an excellent surgeon.
But it is possible that
he may have a disability
due to the damaged nervous system.
What disability?
There's a loss of sensation and movement
on the right side of his body.
As for his left leg,
some of the nerves are still working.
So we'll see after physical therapy.
But regaining his speech
is a more serious problem.
He can't talk?
What good will a mute lawyer be?
I've finally taught him to be useful.
What will you do?
What do you mean?
I'll help him recover as much--
And look after him
for the rest of your life?
Are you laughing?
How can you laugh right now?
I just remembered why I married him.
He wasn't like you.
But it turned out I was fooled
and tamed by his kind and sweet words
Growing up, you were never nice to me.
So I focused on my studies,
thinking you'd compliment me
if I became a doctor.
What are you talking about?
Why are you bringing that up now?
"You. I didn't give birth to you because
I wanted to, so don't get in my way."
"How can you survive in this world
if you can't even befriend those losers?"
"Aren't you on a diet?"
"You're such a pig."
"How can you even be eating after that?"
Hey.
When I said I didn't want
to marry the man you chose,
what was it you said?
"You'll come to your senses
once you marry an awful man
who beats you for the rest of your life."
Should I continue?
Hey. Why do you still remember those--
Don't "hey" me from now on.
Because you treat me so badly, he also…
I…
forgot I even said those.
She remembers them verbatim.
I think it's been really hard for Min-seo.
What?
The person who was hurt
remembers things much more clearly.
TAERIM HIGH SCHOOL OF ARTS
Mr. Lee is in pretty bad shape.
I need your help
with the foundation for now.
Yes, sir.
And regarding Mr. Seo…
He's appearing in print ads.
And he's accepting all the interviews
from the press and production studios.
He'll also be walking on the runway
for a charity at Fashion Week.
A documentary about his father
will be put together too.
Was it Park Jae-gwan?
The critic we met before.
Why don't we use him again?
He can only critique his art,
not his personal life.
It seems Ms. Lee of Hwain Gallery
has already talked to him.
Ms. Lee is serious
about supporting Mr. Seo.
I haven't seen this before.
I'm trying out something new.
Don't you think it's better
to stick to your style
than to try something new for now?
I'm sick of hearing
how my work resembles my father's.
You're his son. What's wrong with that?
Besides, your father was
definitely an artistic genius.
But no one recognized him.
Because he wasn't flexible like you.
You're different. You will be successful.
I guarantee it.
Come to think of it,
Ms. Jeong knew you better than I did.
At your exhibition, she said…
But even if he wasn't
a good father to Mr. Seo,
I'm sure he was the best father
to the artist within Mr. Seo.
Not only did he pass down his talent,
but also a sense of hunger
that couldn't be satiated.
I'm sure Mr. Seo will prove his worth.
Min-seo.
There's something I must tell you.
Can we talk outside?
Let's talk here.
He can't…
hear us anyway.
What? What is it?
When your husband had an accident,
I was there with him.
That flower comes up a lot
in a novel called Wuthering Heights.
Give it a read.
WUTHERING HEIGHTS
Let me get this straight.
He suspected you cheated,
so he called you there to threaten you,
but he tragically fell?
In other words, my husband is a bastard?
Do you expect me to say that to people?
I could've grabbed his hand
before he fell.
What if you did?
Both of you could have fallen
if you tried to save him.
I can't be responsible for you too.
He told me the building
needed a safety inspection
which was bad for construction.
As long as I'm concerned,
he fell when he went to check up on that.
But…
If that's all, leave.
I'm done listening to you now.
What brings you here at this hour?
I came out for some business,
so I stopped by to see you.
-What business?
-I sold the fishing spot.
Already?
The association wanted to hold out
to raise the compensation.
But it seemed unnecessary.
This is for the better. I should sell it
when I can and get out of there.
When?
Cooking is already
prohibited there at night.
I'll keep it open during the day
for my regulars and start wrapping it up.
Do you think you can stay there
at night all by yourself?
Didn't I tell you? People scare me more.
By the way, what are you doing here?
I wanted to see your kids
if you were at home.
What is it?
Why the long face?
What happened this time?
Gosh. I don't know.
I don't know
what's wrong with me these days.
What is it?
Why can't you ever catch a break?
Thanks.
Once I'm as old as him,
do you think I can let go of everything
and live peacefully?
Do you think he's living peacefully?
His wife's dementia is pretty bad,
so she's in a nursing home.
And his only daughter got a brain lesion
from a car accident as a kid,
so he's been taking care of her.
A caretaker comes
to bathe and look after her for two hours.
For those two hours,
he dresses up and indulges himself here.
The only luxury he has in life.
He's still living because
he can't leave behind his daughter alone.
This is his last place of rest.
Getting old doesn't bring peace.
You do whatever it takes
to find a way to cope.
So if there are things
you can let go, you should do it now.
If you push them to the cliff,
you will fall with them.
I couldn't stop thinking all day.
Where you and Hae-won were yesterday
and what you did
and talked about together.
Hui-ju.
I told you it was nothing--
I'm not saying I'm doubting you.
That's what I did.
So things must have been
really difficult for you.
How could you have been okay?
I wanted to turn a blind eye
when I knew you were suffering.
I was being selfish. I'm sorry.
I will withdraw
from the project with Hwain Gallery.
My family means more to me than my career.
I don't ever want to
make you feel insecure again.
Just let me smooth things out
with the gallery.
I don't want to
cause trouble for the project.
I'd be grateful.
Thank you for being patient.
Go to bed first. I'll be in the studio.
If you find what I have done so far
helpful to the project,
feel free to use my work
without any conditions.
May I ask why you want to drop out
all of a sudden?
It wasn't sudden.
I'm sure you sensed it too.
But still. This isn't right.
If this is about Ms. Gu, I already…
You don't love me. Wake up!
Who are you to judge my feelings?
This isn't love!
This is why I cannot continue
to work with him on this project.
Please stop!
-Giving up
-This is wrong, Woo-jae!
being part of Mr. Woo's last masterpiece
was a huge decision for me.
I don't want to involve the police
or make this public.
As I've been
in the public eye more than him,
a lot more people would criticize me.
Is Mr. Seo aware of this?
No.
You're the only one
who watched this footage.
What do you want me to do?
I know very well how much you care
about this project and how hard
you've been working for it.
I don't want to ruin this project either.
I'm indebted to Mr. Seo for something.
So I will let this incident slide.
But please make sure
he never does anything
like this again in the future.
Can you guarantee that
you will never bring this up again?
Get in.
Weren't you following me?
Yes, ma'am. So are you saying Li-sa has--
The wounds.
She has a lot of wounds on her thighs.
Did you know about them?
I know that she's gotten hurt often lately
because she's careless and clumsy.
No.
I think they are self-inflicted wounds.
I think you should check up on her.
Then where's… Where is Li-sa now?
She called in sick and hasn't come
for a few days. Didn't you know?
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
HUSBAND: SEO WOO-JAE
Are you divorcing Ms. Gu?
Yes. Did you follow me
to find out about that?
Why'd you tell me about that book?
Did you even read it?
It was very long and boring.
I didn't understand it at all.
Love is hard to understand.
That's not love.
They keep saying they're miserable.
So you did read it.
Two nights ago,
you were at my house, right?
You met my mom, didn't you?
Why?
Do you seriously not know?
Or are you trying to see if you're right?
You read the book.
You really don't know
why two people would meet?
Where are you?
Get in the car.
-He--
-Stop talking. Get in.
Why were you with Li-sa?
What are you plotting?
I never intended to meet her.
She came to me.
Cut her some slack.
It was something like a book club meeting.
Why are you here?
I moved here.
I told you. I'm divorcing Hae-won.
But why here of all places?
The unit was available, and I want
to remember more of our good days.
It's the same passcode.
Come anytime you want.
The police couldn't find
Mr. Lee's cell phone.
He said he needed to tell me
something about your husband.
Did you take his cell phone?
No.
There might be something in the phone
that other people shouldn't see.
I don't know where it is.
And I don't want to.
Gosh.
Did you do this to yourself?
Why? What's the problem?
We give you everything
you want and ask for.
You have everything.
Why are you doing this?
It's all because of you!
Everything that happened
with Mimi, Ju-yeong,
and Ho-su is all your fault!
I saw everything.
I saw it that day.
You left Dad and me there.
And I saw you with that man!
You didn't see anything. I told you.
You're mistaken. Why won't you believe--
Yes! That's why I pretended
I didn't know anything about you two!
Then you should be careful!
Why do you keep seeing him?
What if Dad finds out?
Do you like that man more than me or Dad?
Li-sa.
Please book me an appointment
with Dr. Jeong for next week.
One moment.
Dr. Jeong will be leaving
the hospital next week.
I'll make you an appointment
with another doctor.
What are you talking about?
Are you running away?
You didn't ask me for permission.
I didn't sign off on it.
How dare you try to run away
from me behind my back?
That's not true. Right?
It's not, right?
Tell me it's not true! It can't be.
Tell me you're staying!
If you cared even a bit about Jeong-seop,
how could I…
No. How could you leave?
You can't run away
to live your own life.
You just can't, you bastard.
You bastard!
Please stop.
Why do you keep butting in?
You don't know anything.
Do you know what he did to Jeong-seop? He…
Yes. Your son
was Dr. Jeong's friend.
Yes. They were friends.
They were friends. But why…
Why did only my son die?
Why did only my Jeong-seop have to die?
I'm sorry.
How could you do this if you're sorry?
Jeong-seop would think it's so unfair
seeing you enjoying your life
when he's dead!
You bastard.
Is that how he would think?
What?
Do you think he would want his friend
to live a life of suffering forever?
Was that the kind of person he was?
Stop it.
She's right.
Ma'am.
Did you send her off safely?
Yes.
But if this ever happens again,
just let it go because
she has the right to do that.
How do you endure it?
I'm not enduring it,
I'm just waiting
for her anger to die down.
-For how long?
-I don't know.
I can only imagine
how deep her pain must be.
What was that about going to America?
An internship.
An opportunity to study more
on physical therapy came up,
But I don't know if I should go.
You should go.
I also had an opportunity once,
but I lost it.
I pitied myself for losing the chance
and regretted it a lot.
So, don't regret it and go.
You also…
You also have regrets,
so you should start over.
It's already too late for me.
Mr. Lee's surgery went well.
Once he regains consciousness,
he will tell the police what happened.
Is that okay with you?
Hui-ju was there that day too.
Does that change anything?
He fell because he wasn't careful.
That's a fact.
I sent over the paper again.
Let's end this quickly.
You'll be better off that way.
Better?
Who are you to judge what I want?
Then what is it that you want?
What do you gain from this?
If you're holding onto me
out of fear and loneliness, stop.
You always had a lot of people
who cared about you. And you still do.
Don't act like I ruined your life.
If you do, you're disrespecting them.
If you don't let go of me,
we will only keep
hurting each other like this.
It's better to be lonely alone
than be miserable together.
Remember what I told you?
For us, a divorce means
either your death…
or mine.
Do you still want that?
Ho-su and Li-sa are staying
with my mom today.
What on earth happened?
Li-sa didn't tell you anything?
Tell me what?
She stopped talking to me a long time ago.
What's going on?
Li-sa is harming herself.
What do you mean?
I had no idea.
I'm her mother, but I was so blind.
I found out when her teacher told me.
I knew that Li-sa was acting strange.
But why didn't I
try harder to look into it?
What did her teacher say?
There must be a reason behind it.
I have no idea.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know
how I'm going to face Li-sa now.
I just don't know, honey.
You will have to face her.
She's our daughter.
We must take good care of her,
so things don't get worse.
Ms. Gu!
There's someone inside,
but she's not answering.
Please open the door.
Ms. Gu.
Ms. Gu!
SLEEPING PILLS
Seeing how you're here,
I guess Hae-won is fine. I was worried.
Worried?
If you were worried,
you should've gone right away.
Why did you call me?
Were you just going to let her die
if you couldn't reach me? Were you?
Then I would've gone to her myself.
She wouldn't want me to, though.
That doesn't matter.
Even if you're going to divorce her…
shouldn't you have gone to her
once you knew her life was in danger?
You went there in my place.
At least,
I realized something from all of this.
Now I know how useless
and harmful you are to Ms. Gu.
And one more thing.
That I shouldn't let
someone like you come close to my sister.
At one point in your life,
these amazing two women both loved you.
How did you turn into such a loser?
Ms. Jeong is withdrawing?
Artists from other fields
will be participating
to take up where Ms. Jeong left off.
No. Let me go and see Ms. Jeong.
No. That is the gallery's job.
You should only focus on your work.
This project will proceed
as planned without her.
And I'll make it successful.
Mr. Woo is the pillar
of Korean architects. I can easily
find artists who want to join
his last exhibition.
Exactly.
I'm asking why Ms. Jeong
wants to drop out of this great project.
You want to be successful. Right?
Then distance yourself from her.
She wants you to succeed.
I'm certain of that.
So stop causing trouble.
And only focus on your work.
Why did you
-call me here to tell me--
-Because…
I'm the CEO of Hwain Gallery
in charge of protecting you.
Ms. Jeong has
many powerful people around her.
I don't want to cause trouble with her.
I'll take him inside. You can go home.
Ho-su.
Are you okay?
I want to play.
What the hell are you doing?
I just played with him.
I'm glad that Ho-su still remembers me.
Dad!
I cut his umbilical cord,
comforted him when he cried at night…
fed him baby formula,
and watched him take his first step.
What were you doing in the meantime?
You crazy bastard.
Do you want the paper
that says he's not your son?
A piece of paper
doesn't mean anything to me.
It doesn't change the fact that
I was the one who raised him
before you took him away from me.
Ho-su, let's go inside.
Ho-su.
What happened? Why am I here?
Why? Did you ask me why?
Why didn't you tell me?
When did you break up with that jerk?
You guys had just gotten back together!
I told you he'd do it again.
Only the first time is hard.
If you know that,
why do you live like this?
So learn from my mistakes!
This is so frustrating!
I didn't ask you for much.
I only asked you to outlive me.
That's all I want!
Gosh. Stop yelling at me.
You're hurting my ears.
And you're totally wrong.
I'm not going to die.
I couldn't sleep, so I took
some sleeping pills. Why the fuss?
Fuss?
You ended up in the ER
and scared the crap out of me.
I'm making a fuss?
Sorry.
I shouldn't have taken them with alcohol.
I won't do that again.
Who's that guy?
Guy?
The guy who carried you to the ER.
What guy?
Didn't you bring me here?
Look at you.
The drugs haven't worn off yet.
I rushed there
after getting a call from him.
You were totally out of it.
And I couldn't find your husband.
And I was losing it too.
If it weren't for him,
I would've been admitted too.
He seemed boring and pale,
but he was such a sweet guy.
And he's nice and tall.
A girl has to meet someone like him.
Look at your asshole husband.
I forgave him because he was good-looking.
See? Look what he did.
Since this happened,
you should divorce him right away
and date this guy. Okay?
No.
I can't. So don't bring it up again.
Ms. Gu.
Right.
I was on my way out to buy abalones
to cook porridge. My goodness.
Hey, your teacher is not well.
She must stay home to recover.
Keep an eye on her.
You're in charge.
Gosh.
You're not well? What's wrong?
I'm okay. I feel refreshed
after getting some sleep.
Are you done with your exams?
Did you do well?
I aced them.
And I got this.
SEOUL FAMILY COURT
NOTICE FOR HEARING
PETITIONER: GU HAE-WON
MINOR: LEE JU-YEONG
THE DATE OF THE RULING
HAS BEEN SET AS FOLLOWING
Give me ten big abalones.
Sure.
Give me big ones.
Going up.
The flowers are beautiful.
I like roses too.
I heard that flowers
in subtle, pastel colors
are popular these days.
But I still think
bright, colorful flowers are better.
Colorful like those.
Who are they for? Your wife?
She must be so happy.
The doors are opening.
NAME: KIM SO-YEON
So-yeon.
I'm here.
I'm sorry that I took so long.
I just heard what happened--
I'm sorry.
I'm really…
My wife spent
all my retirement pay, savings,
and money from our home equity loan
on a patch of land without telling me.
She was scammed.
After keeping it from me
for a while, she fell ill.
There was nothing we could do.
However,
I was too busy chasing
after those frauds to mourn for her.
Excuse me.
You need to take your abalones!
Jeong-yeon!
Was it not her?
Ho-su.
What did you do with that man earlier?
He's really good at building sandcastles.
He built everything I asked for.
You're still here.
You left work early because
your wife is sick. Why are you still here?
You told Mr. Choi to prepare
his admission documents
for a school in England.
Should I have asked
your unconscious brother-in-law?
That's not what I mean.
Then what do you mean?
Jeong-hwan only wants
to study just like his mom.
Ho-su will get everything
including the hospital.
I'll give everything to you, Ho-su.
Mom.
I don't expect anything
from any of you now.
I raised you wrong.
Everything you have all came from me.
You and your sister are so ungrateful.
All right.
Ho-su, why don't you have one of these?
There.
Open wide.
There you go. Good boy.
You'll get only the best stuff from me.
Eat a lot, so you can be a healthy boy.
Ho-su won't turn out like you.
The hospital is running smoothly now.
So I'll take care of him from A to Z
and raise him right.
When will you stop being so greedy?
Let this go and make peace--
Change too suddenly and you die.
Are you praying for my death?
Mom.
You weren't even sure if he was your son.
Your wife might've been sleeping
with some guy for years.
How can I trust you to raise my grandson?
Can't you just drop it?
Drop what?
Li-sa, when did you--
I called her over. Your wife is not well.
I doubt that she'll feed the kids.
Let's go.
Come on. Not you too.
Ho-su still needs us.
Your mother can look after him.
But he still needs his parents.
She keeps coddling him,
so he won't even come to his mom.
I'm not against him going
abroad to study. Let him finish--
Seo Woo-jae was here.
He was with Ho-su
at the playground in front of the house.
I can't be there every time
to see if he's here or not.
And it's not a bad idea
to learn their culture early on
like my mom said.
It'll be okay if we visit him there often.
We've done that for Li-sa,
so we won't make mistakes this time.
I'll get going then.
Take care.
I'll be back soon. Don't worry about me.
-Bye. Good luck.
-Bye.
-Take care.
-Go back inside.
IN FRONT OF TAERIM HOSPITAL
You won't be working at the hospital now?
I've been meaning to call you, actually.
I heard what you did.
Thank you for taking me to the ER.
Are you okay now?
Totally.
It was nothing.
I had a hard time falling asleep.
I mean it.
If I was miserable to death,
I'd kill the people who made me
miserable. Why would I die?
I wasn't scared of death.
Seeing how much pain life brought me,
I wondered if the afterlife
would be better than living.
That's what I thought.
But when I saw you unconscious…
I didn't care about that anymore.
I kept praying.
"Please don't let her die."
I ran to the ER like a madman.
Gosh. It was really scary.
Don't ever do that again.
If you have trouble sleeping at night,
call me instead.
I know you're uncomfortable around me.
But I'm not asking you
to do anything with me right now.
Just…
Just let me help you.
Let me do that little by little.
I don't feel uncomfortable.
I feel comfortable around you.
And that's the problem.
MONEY SPOILS ART,
CONGLOMERATE'S HORRENDOUS COMMERCIAL ART
RISING SCULPTOR SEO WOO-JAE
PRACTICALLY SELLING HIMSELF AS ART
MONEY SPOILS ART,
CONGLOMERATE'S HORRENDOUS COMMERCIAL ART
JEONG HUI-JU BOUGHT MY WORK, I'M HONORED
FROM PUPIL TO RESPECTABLE ARTIST
So you're accusing me of paying off
these reporters to write these articles?
Didn't you?
That's too bad. Unfortunately, I did not.
I wouldn't buy off this many people
just to bring you down.
I'm not that interested in you.
And I have no time for it.
Would your pride have been hurt less
if I was behind these articles?
You seem disappointed.
I knew it.
You should have known your place.
No matter how hard
Ms. Lee tries to help you,
you see, one's character…
is bound to surface eventually.
Stop whining like a baby here,
and go focus on your art more.
Come in.
He's just leaving.
Have a seat.
The father's parental rights
to provide shelter, educate,
and designate the place of residence
along with the rights
regarding childrearing will be restricted.
The court designates the petitioner
as the guardian of the minor.
And the guardian will be responsible
for the following obligations.
This is absurd!
That school director was right about you.
You set me up!
So you could take the money!
You talked Ju-yeong into this!
You did that to steal all of my money!
How could you do this to me?
How could you?
I didn't expect to see you here.
I'm glad you are here.
How dare you show up here?
I was curious about his recovery.
I want him to gain consciousness
more than anyone.
And I have the right to be here
because after all,
I'm a witness to the accident.
Once he wakes up, the lies you told--
At least your husband
will believe it was an accident.
No. He will have to
because what he did was worse than this.
It was unfair that
you wasted three years of your life.
And I have new evidence
regarding your accident in Ireland.
Why do you want to help me?
Because helping you will help me.
He made me lie in bed
unconscious for three years.
That's the kind of man your husband is.
Hui-ju, you are living with a monster.
He'll be here soon. You should go.
I have no reason to avoid him.
Discussing how
he'll compensate me for the years I lost
sounds good too.
Then let's talk about this outside.
You said that back then too.
You told me to leave Ho-su
and get out for a while that day.
If I knew I would lose you and him,
I wouldn't have done as you said.
I should've held out.
You didn't lose anyone.
I decided to leave you.
Then come back to me.
Come back to me with Ho-su.
The three of us can start over.
Bring Li-sa too if you want.
I'm different now.
I'll support you.
I'll be successful.
More successful than your husband.
Where's Mr. Lee's cell phone?
I know you took it.
There's something in it, isn't there?
That's why you remembered
to take it even when he…
HYEON-SEONG
Get out. Let's talk outside.
Let's talk outside. Please?
I'm on my way up.
Are you still in the room?
Please.
Why are you out here?
Why didn't you go in?
I didn't want to go in by myself.
It's bad. He's still unconscious.
Is Li-sa's therapy over?
Oh, my. She should be done soon.
I'll go check on her.
I'll go too.
We should work on this together.
She's our daughter.
You won't do it without Ms. Jeong?
Come on, don't do this again.
This is an important time for you.
This is a great chance
to fix their prejudice.
Exactly. That's why
I must do it with Ms. Jeong.
This was a joint project.
If she drops out,
what will people say about that?
How many more times must I tell you?
You must distance yourself
from Ms. Jeong to protect yourself.
Exactly. I asked you several times
why that's the case.
You don't love me. Wake up!
If you approach her again,
I won't be able to stop her.
If this video reaches the public,
your career is over before it even starts.
This isn't what it looks like.
Of course you'd say that.
It's not!
Right. I don't know
what happened between you two.
What's important is that people will
only believe what they want to.
And people will believe
Ms. Jeong over you.
This is a lie!
That's not true! It's a lie!
It's not true.
That's a lie.
I lived here only briefly,
but I still have a lot of stuff to pack.
It was so easy to start.
But breaking up is difficult.
Why do we always make the same mistake?
What brings you here anyway?
I know I don't deserve it,
but I'm here to ask you for a favor.
Please stop Woo-jae.
He will listen to you.
Remember what you told me?
That I would destroy myself
because of my victim mentality.
You were right, as you can see.
And I can now understand
that you will not crumble
no matter how hard I try.
It was impossible to achieve something
only out of hatred and resentment.
But Woo-jae isn't like me.
His feelings for you,
whatever they may be…
He firmly believes that it's love.
It's your responsibility
to cut off his obsession with you.
Hae-won.
You said…
you would never break down like me. Right?
I will be watching you to see
if you can do what you so proudly claimed.
Why'd you come?
Ms. Lee called me.
She's worried about you.
She doesn't know that we broke up.
SEO WOO-JAE
GU HAE-WON
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
Should I tell her?
Hui-ju came to me.
A proud woman like her asked me for help.
She asked me to stop you.
That's how disgusted she must be by you.
Do you still not see it?
She abandoned you. Completely.
If things worked out for you two,
I would have only hated you.
But now I pity you.
I don't hate you. I pity you.
Does it hurt?
Is it painful?
Is this what they call karma?
There really must be a God.
Seeing how you get to feel the way I felt
after all of my efforts
to get it through to you.
I'll file the form.
Li-sa.
Let's order food for dinner.
We should do it before Mom gets back.
What should we eat?
When is she coming home?
Well, she should be here pretty soon.
We can order it now.
Chicken. I want fried chicken, Dad.
Make sure to order soda too.
Chicken? Sure.
Is Ho-su really going to England?
Why?
But I don't want to go.
Are you going too?
Dad, you too?
-What about Mom?
-Don't send him abroad.
He's going to school.
You studied there too.
Ho-su doesn't want to go.
Why did you let Grandma decide?
-We can discuss it later.
-Is it because of Mom again?
Woo-jae. Hold on.
Woo-jae, don't do anything rash.
Wait.
Woo-jae!
I can't let you go like this.
Hui-ju…
If I can't have you,
nobody can have you.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son