[English subtitles are available]
[White Cat Legend]
[Episode 1]
During the reign of His Majesty,
the Emperor traveled to Shendu
and all nations came to the court.
During prosperous times,
there will always be turbulence.
Fortunately, there is the Court of Judicial Review
to be in charge of all prisons
and uphold justice.
Unexpectedly,
three years ago,
[Court of Judicial Review]
the Minister of Judicial Review was assassinated and died.
With that, the Court of Judicial Review has been on the decline.
The situation got more chaotic...
Right now,
there's even a rumor going around about a demon cat
murdering people in Shendu.
Sir, come in.
Come and play.
Good!
Let me accompany you.
Sir.
Let me hug you.
Why did it stop?
My Lord,
it's time to cross the bridge.
Go then!
My Lord.
Th-This is a little strange.
My Lord,
there's something wrong with the horse too.
How about
we go back to the pavilion first?
Why is the fog
so strange?
It's none of your business.
Go inside.
The night curfew is coming.
I'm on duty tonight.
It's just fog.
Go!
Okay, My Lord.
Gu!
Wait for me.
I don't believe it.
Gu.
Gu!
My Lord.
Don't leave me alone.
What are you doing out here?
Go back.
You...
Wait for me!
Wait!
Thank you.
Don't close it!
Good!
Amazing.
[Chen Shi]
Bravo! Bravo!
One more.
Excuse me.
Steamed buns.
Fresh steamed buns.
Sir, one please.
Okay.
Here.
Good!
Buns.
Thank you.
Give me some food.
Give me some.
This wild cat
is bigger and prettier than mine.
Little girl,
are you okay?
Did you get hurt?
It's getting dark.
Why are you still playing outside?
What's your name?
Don't fall down.
Shendu is amazing.
Even this young girl
runs faster than I do.
My money...
My buns!
Little girl!
That little girl is a thief!
Stop!
You thief!
Look.
Good!
Get down.
Don't block me.
Don't block.
Get down.
Make way.
Stop!
Excuse me.
Stop! Stop!
Let's go.
Wild cat.
What are you doing here?
What is this?
It's so beautiful.
It's so fascinating.
Who left this here?
What is this?
It's... blood?
You're quite powerful.
What does this mean?
[Go]
Gosh. You can write?
But...
But I'm illiterate.
What is this?
Wild cat...
Well...
You're quite something.
Wild cat.
Wild cat!
You...
Take care.
Come again if it was good.
It's late. The shop is closed.
Come again next time.
Madam,
have you seen
a little girl?
I didn't see her.
She's right there!
She not only ate my buns,
but also stole my money.
Little girl, you...
Look at you.
I was wondering where your bun
came from.
Did you take his money too?
Forget it.
Madam.
She's so young.
You can't
steal again.
Especially not money.
Got it?
Give him the money.
Sir,
our shop is closed.
We aren't going to receive other guests anyway.
I'll serve you a bowl of good wine
as an apology to the little girl.
No, no, no.
Don't stand on ceremony.
No need.
Who is it?
The shop is closed. We are not–
Of course we are still receiving guests.
We can't turn you away.
Sir,
you are so magnificent.
Where are you from?
Please have a seat.
Have a seat.
Come on.
Sit.
I am the Prince of Persia.
A friend from afar
is not easy to take care off.
This is
the Prince of Persia from afar.
He will be attending
Meng Chun ritual in a few days.
If you don't treat him well,
you won't be able to afford it.
If you want to cover it up,
just don't speak.
This official's Mandarin
is really...
unique!
Really?
So I have a chance
at getting level 8 in Mandarin?
What does that mean?
Keep a low profile.
This is a royal secret.
Don't ask.
Prince, you must be tired from the long journey.
I'll serve you some good wine.
Well...
Prince, we still have a long way to go.
What are you doing?
Where are you from?
Golden hair, high nose.
Your eyes...
Why
is it yellow?
Haven't you seen a foreigner?
There are all types of people.
Don't make a fuss.
But I'm just curious
how your hair grew.
It's curly.
Why is it like this?
Just look, don't touch.
Sirs, here.
Good wine is here.
It's cold outside.
Drink some wine to warm your body.
Here.
Drink it.
Drink, gentlemen.
Sir,
is it cooling outside?
Yes.
Then
stay where it's cooling.
All right.
Sir, it's fine. Drink it.
Madam!
I have something to tell you.
There's a garment among
the grass outside. Whose is it?
It's my old clothes.
I was going to throw it away.
Maybe
a stray cat brought it back.
But there's blood
on the clothes.
What's going on?
There are many stray cats nearby.
A few days ago, I was chased by a stray cat
and got scratched several times.
Sirs, please drink.
It's fine.
Warm yourself up.
That wild cat
looked quite sensible.
How could it scratch you?
Madam.
Wait a minute.
Let me look for something for you.
Madam,
before I left the village,
I brought this.
Thinking it might be useful some day.
It can heal cat stratches.
This is for taking, and this is for applying.
It's common for cats to scratch and dogs to bite in my village.
Use it as soon as possible.
Young man, you look like a good man.
I won't hold you up.
I'll be on my way then.
Take care.
Okay.
No, no, no.
What now?
One more thing.
Go ahead.
Fireworks.
What fireworks?
Isn't there fireworks
in the clothes at the door?
I didn't know what it was at first,
so I set it off.
Madam.
They have knives on them.
I'm afraid they are robbers.
Why is Shendu
so messy?
None of you can get out today.
You little wench.
I am the judge of the Court of Judicial Review,
Alibaba.
I am the judicial commissioner of the Court of Judicial Review, Sun Bao.
I'm here to investigate the case and capture the culprit.
[Sun Bao] [Alibaba]
Surrender now.
The Court of Judicial Review?
What? Are you scared?
Where are the people you kidnapped?
Where are you going?
I'm not a bad person.
I know you're not.
You have to be the witness.
If this case is solved,
you'll get a share.
Isn't that your daughter?
What daughter?
She's just a thief I use
to lure in customers.
Don't move.
Useless!
Put down the knife.
You want to be a hero?
I'll kill you first.
Put down the knife.
Wild cat!
Bastard!
Don't move!
[Shangguan Qin]
[Hu Si]
Is this how
the two of you solve cases?
Vice Minister Shangguan.
Wh-Why are you here?
Look at your outfits.
You look nothing like
an official of the Court of Judicial Review.
This is nonsense.
I...
Vice Minister,
don't scold him.
He can't stand it.
Today is really a bad day.
We're just following orders.
You set off
the Court of Judicial Review signal fireworks
at the gate too?
At least you're not that stupid.
You know how to leave yourself a way out.
Take them all away!
Wild cat?
Cat?
Chen Shi.
Listen.
This is the Court of Judicial Review
where justice is upheld and evils are punished.
You have to tell me the truth.
If you lie,
I will not forgive you!
I told you everything.
I didn't lie.
You were the one who kept smacking that–
You're still saying you didn't lie?
You said cats can write?
It's true.
I don't know what word it was.
But it just looked like it...
Looked like what?
I'm illiterate.
So it just looked like it.
There's no lie in this.
What word was it?
I just remember it was something like...
Like...
Like!
[Go]
Madam,
it seems to be a word "walk."
I don't need you to tell me that.
According to you,
the Court of Judicial Review signal fireworks
was also set off
by this wild cat?
Madam,
you finally believe me!
Ridiculous!
Please calm down, Madam.
Wang Qi,
I was going to hold you accountable.
What's wrong with them?
Madam is great in every other aspect
except the fact that she likes to smack the gavel too often.
She broke four pieces this month.
You are right.
Does Vice Minister Shangguan
like to listen to loud things?
I'll buy some firecrackers in Meng Chun in a few days–
Madam,
I received reports last June
that foreigners went missing
in Shendu.
I suspect
someone is hiding in the markets
to chose outsiders
to harvest from them,
hide them, and sell them off.
They kill people and steal goods.
It's unforgivable.
I...
received a tip-off.
The perpetrator is highly likely
to be a pair of male and female bandits.
To solve this case,
I made a detailed
and thorough plan.
As expected of him.
He's good at making up stories.
Go on.
According to the information I gathered
of the missing before they disappeared,
I have basically confirmed the area they went missing in.
It is somewhere in that alley.
So I decided
to lure the snake out of its hole.
Cui Bei.
Tell me about it.
[Cui Bei]
Yesterday morning,
we held a meeting at Mingjing Hall.
Wang Qi said,
"Sun Bao, Alibaba,
in order to solve the case,
go be the bait."
Alibaba said,
"Why don't you go?"
Sun Bao said, "Exactly."
Wang Qi said, "I...
have to stay to deal with
Vice Minister Shangguan–"
Vice Minister Shangguan
is wise.
You can't stand even a single grain of sand in your eyes.
Cui Bei.
I told you not to note down useless things.
Madam.
This is my plan.
First, let Sun Bao and Alibaba
disguise as rich fat sheep,
luring the male and female bandits to take action
while I take both of them down.
You said I'm a prince?
You wish!
I asked you to act as
the Prince of Persia.
As for Sun Bao...
You can act as...
a servant of a prince.
Servant?
As for Cui Bei,
you can act as a study partner.
Me?
Are you sure?
On October 8,
Hu Si escorted a criminal to Mingjing Hall.
I was washing my inkstone at the hall.
My fingers slipped
and the inkstone hit Hu Si.
Hu Si was in a coma for three days.
The criminal was crushed by Hu Si
and fractured his arm.
He still hasn't recovered yet.
On the 5th of this month,
Alibaba invited you, me, and Sun Bao
to visit Zuixian Residence.
I just left the Court of Judicial Review...
It was really strange.
It's already winter now.
Yet it suddenly started raining so heavily.
It was raining and snowing.
And went on for two to three days.
Even the water level in the moat has risen.
Alibaba and I
were drenched
and had a high fever for days.
Wang Qi was fine though.
Don't mention this anymore.
I feel cold whenever I mention it.
I was thoughtless.
Cui Bei.
You don't have to go.
You're so capable
of bringing disaster.
You may very well
never come back.
You might die
with those bandits accidentally.
In that case, Alibaba, Sun Bao,
a prince, and a servant,
it should be enough.
Having me to disguise as a prince
is ridiculous
and would bring harm.
You have money anyway.
You can buy a set of nice clothes
and get the chance to enjoy being a prince.
What's wrong with that?
Soon,
the Meng Chun ritual is coming.
Who knows?
Some foreign princes might come
to join in the fun.
Foreigners are always fascinating.
These human traffickers
can't help themselves but take action
when they see such fat sheep.
Besides,
the assessment is coming.
Don't you want to make a great contribution
and let Mingjing Hall
get noticed by Vice Minister Shangguan?
Also, Alibaba.
Think about it.
You wearing a whole set of clothes
that of the Prince of Persia...
What are you talking about?
Why isn't he charging us?
Persian people are welcomed here.
And he treats us like brothers.
The boss is nice.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
Wait, you...
I...
I've paid.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
This way.
Apprehending two major criminals
and showing up in front of Vice Minister Shangguan...
How mighty would that be!
I'm willing to do that!
I'll cooperate.
Madam,
although this plan is simple,
it's still a success.
If it's really a success,
would there still be a need for me
to clean up the mess for you?
In any way,
we still caught the suspect.
Wang Qi.
This is not easy.
This is the first time
Mingjing Hall has solved a case.
Yet you want to take credit?
Of course.
No, no...
But in my opinion,
this case,
If it weren't for this...
Chen Shi.
If it weren't for Chen Shi,
and that cat,
I'm afraid it wouldn't get cracked.
Vice Minister,
you can't say that.
Although that cat
helped us a lot,
this...
But to crack this case,
it required my flawless
and detailed plan.
I still have my suspicions about this case.
If what Chen Shi said is true,
that he was accidentally involved,
could a cat do so many things?
That wild cat is really something.
I've never seen such a magical cat.
No matter how powerful it is, it's still a cat.
Did you catch it?
-In the prison.
Madam,
it's in the prison.
All right.
Throw him in it too.
Okay, huh?
He is a good man.
But he is a good man.
He's a good man.
I really am not–
Wang Qi!
Madam,
why?
A cat can solve cases, write,
and can do so many things.
If this Chen Shi isn't making stuff up,
there must be someone who has ordered him to do so.
I suspect...
No.
There must be something wrong here.
Something wrong?
What can be wrong?
I'm telling the truth.
Madam, I...
The two of them can be the witness.
Yes.
We can be witness.
Can I believe your words?
It's been two years.
Mingjing Hall
hasn't solve any proper case.
Just as the Meng Chun ritual is about to come
as well as the Court of Judicial Review's official assessment,
and that people are about to be dismissed,
you solved a case.
Who knows if
there's something up your sleeves.
Although these two criminals
have been arrested,
it'd be difficult for you Mingjing Hall
to claim this credit.
I advise you
don't do such things
and focus on serious things.
The Court of Judicial Review
don't keep people who do nothing.
Madam,
this is targeting us.
What did you say?
Madam, please investigate it clearly.
Fine.
Take him away then.
-Yes.
Let's go.
I'm the witness.
Go.
What's that sound?
It sounds so creepy.
I don't know.
I don't want to know either.
Don't ask me.
It's that wild cat.
The wild cat?
Go in by yourselves.
Wild cat!
Where are you?
This... This wild cat...
Wild cat!
It's me, wild cat.
Don't be afraid. It's me.
Wild cat!
It's me, wild cat.
Why did this wild cat become so fierce?
It got drugged by the human traffickers.
Don't be afraid, wild cat.
Friend...
Come here.
What's wrong?
My hand!
Sorry.
We'll release you immediately
as soon as there's a result to the case.
He's making the act become real and mistaking good with bad.
He has no choice.
This is the only way.
Officer,
why are you locking me up?
Friend.
Are you a good person?
I am.
That's good.
As long as you are a good person,
whether you are being locked up or not
won't change this fact.
Right?
Don't worry, the Court of Judicial Review
won't wrong a good person
nor let go of a bad guy.
Sun Bao!
Let's go.
That makes sense. Just lock me up.
Sun Bao, be careful.
Well...
My apologies.
I've never seen
such a fierce cat.
What if it keeps shrieking like this?
Officer,
why don't you lock us up
together?
I'll be the wild cat's companion. How's that?
Okay.
Let's go.
[Court of Judicial Review]
Madam.
The male and female bandits
have been interrogated.
It's true.
Very well.
Since Wang Qi and his men's words were true,
the case can be closed.
As for the rest,
you can deal with it.
It will be considered a merit too.
Got it. I understand.
We can't let those rascals at
Mingjing Hall take the credit.
In that case, I...
Mingjing Hall
was founded by the former Court of Judicial Review.
It was once glorious.
It's just unfortunate that
after the minister of the previous Court of Judicial Review left,
most left or retired.
They now don't have a leader.
If it wasn't for that incident...
[Li's Residence]
Take him down!
A bunch of idiots joined it.
They aren't proper enough to even appear on the court.
By the way,
is the cat they brought back
locked up?
Yes.
I suspect this cat
is related to another strange case.
You mean the Demon Cat Murder Case?
That's right.
Vice Minister, to be honest,
I've heard
many rumors recently.
But what's actually going on with the
Demon Cat Murder Case?
Ten days ago, at midnight,
a trembling woman was found
by the moat.
Who's that?
It's midnight,
why are you wandering around?
There's a demon...
What did you say?
There's a demon!
Demon cat...
The demon cat is killing!
The demon cat is killing...
Since then,
the Demon Cat Murder Case started to spread.
But
we can't conclude that it was
a demon cat that did the killing
just because of what she said.
At most,
it's just an official who went missing.
I'm not done yet.
Two hours later,
at Zhuque Gate...
[Zhuque Gate]
Help!
The gate guard found a body
on the rooftop of the gate.
It was the official who went missing
on the bridge, Marquis Yu.
Sir!
Wild cat!
[Integrity; Prudence; Diligence]
It's all in vain.
Alibaba!
Stop saying such
annoying things here.
Who would have thought
this is how Vice Minister Shangguan deals with this case?
Besides,
when Vice Minister said to lock up Chen Shi,
you didn’t say a single thing.
In front of Vice Minister Shangguan,
you are the judicial commissioner of Mingjing Hall.
I'm just a judge.
You are the person in charge of this case.
As you're replying to Vice Minister Shangguan,
if I interrupt,
it'd be inappropriate.
I shouldn't look
nor say anything.
All right, Baba.
Now you're putting me in the front.
And you, Cui Bei.
You usually don't say anything.
Why did you take a jab at me
when you decided to open your mouth?
I was just telling the truth.
Fine.
I’m a generous man.
I can’t afford to get mad for nothing with you.
Look at it now.
Not to mention we won't get the credit for this case,
an honest man was wronged too.
Where is Sun Bao?
Why isn't he back yet?
Listen.
Sun Bao
is only tall
but doesn't have guts.
When he's met with problems,
he only knows to pray to gods and buddhas.
He's the most unreliable.
Today, Chen Shi said
that cat can write.
Maybe
Sun Bao went for fortune-telling again.
He's stubborn and does the opposite of what he speaks.
He's as strong as a cow yet as timid as a mouse.
This is also the truth.
Wild cat.
We can't bite.
You are drugged.
Don't be afraid.
It's me.
Wild cat.
We even set off fireworks together.
Do you remember?
All right.
It's okay to bite me.
Don't be afraid, wild cat.
Don’t be afraid.
Who can escape the guards of Zhuque Gate
and hang people on the city gate
without making a sound?
Madam.
In that case,
it's really a demon cat killing?
No matter who the murderer is,
as long as we can solve this strange case
and give the court an explanation,
it'd be a great merit.
But if we can't solve it,
the Court of Judicial Review,
including you and me,
won't be able to take responsibility of it.
So remember,
you must keep an eye on
the human and the cat.
If one of them is missing,
you'll be responsible.
Yes.
Don't worry, Vice Minister.
I will complete the task.
This is...
You...
You're awake?
Who are you?
I'm from the Court of Judicial Review.
But I came a little late.
You haven't seen me before.
The Court of Judicial Review?
I remember now!
Wasn't I
in the Court of Judicial Review?
They also
locked me up...
Oh right!
Why am I here?
Where is the wild cat?
Don't shout.
You mean that cat?
I let it go.
From now on,
I'll take over your case.
It’s finally my turn.
[Li Bing]
Your name is Chen Shi?
Me? Yes.
[Court of Judicial Review]