[English subtitles are available]
[Jun Ji-hyun]
[Ju Ji-hoon]
[Sung Dong-il]
[Oh Jung-se]
[Cho Han-chul]
[Joo Min-kyung]
[Go Min-si]
[Jirisan]
[The show is an adapted fiction based on
stories of National Park Rangers.]
[All characters, events, regions,]
[organizations depicted in the show
are fictitious.]
[Commander! Clouds are on the ridge!]
Leave the valley! Move!
It was raining, right? Be careful.
I found it!
Who are you?
[The murderer's out to get you.]
[I think the murderer has something
to do with the incident.]
[Kim Jin-deok]
-Did something happen back then?
[-Flooding is a natural disaster.]
[It has nothing to do with crimes.]
[-Are you okay?]
-Let's go down. Quick.
-This bedrock area is safe.
-Don't lie.
That's what they said then, too,
but the whole building was swept away.
What are you saying?
[You mean Dowon Valley in 1995?]
[The ones who had stayed all died.]
I can't reach Yi-gang.
Help!
[1.5km from Mujin Valley,
on the southwest cliff.]
Any support team available?
Dong-hyup, get ready to go up with me.
I'll go.
[Episode 13]
You...
You're my life.
We're from national park!
Hello?
Over here.
-Hello?
-I'm right here!
Over here!
Have you seen Yang-sun?
No.
-Have you seen Yang-sun?
-No.
[Ranger]
My goodness.
We can just walk down and take the bus.
Please get in. You have a lot of stuff.
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
Get home safe!
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[Ranger]
Hurry, come help.
Okay.
Did Yang-sun go to the main station?
-She mobilized.
-What?
[I'll shoot the line thrower.]
[Grab the rope and tie it to the tree!]
Is that her?
I'll cross first.
-I need to go grocery shopping.
-We brought a lot.
[Commander, we're at the cliff now.]
Good job.
[How is she?]
A mild injury, but she's all right.
I'll bring her down right away.
[Okay. Keep the walkie on at all times.]
Yes, sir.
[Yang-sun! Come down safely!]
Okay!
So cool, Yang-sun!
This is Yang-sun's first dispatch.
I'll save her more food.
You have to put this on.
-Can you get up?
-Yes.
Grab my shoulder and get up slowly.
Grab my shoulder.
Lift your right foot.
-Thank you.
-The other one, too.
Be careful!
Oh, no.
[Please, no!]
Lee Yang-sun.
Yang-sun!
Lee Yang-sun!
-Yang-sun!
-What happened?
Follow them! Quick!
Yes, sir.
[Yang-sun.]
[Haedong Ranger Station,
Jirisan National Park]
[Anyone there? Answer me!]
[Haedong Ranger Station,
Jirisan National Park]
[Yang-sun, can you hear me?]
[Yang-sun!]
[Answer me!]
-What? Is there an accident?
-Hush.
[Lee Yang-sun!]
Yang-sun!
[Commander.]
What happened?
Yang-sun fell.
[She got swept away in a stream current.]
If she got swept away
from the southwest cliff,
she'll come down this way soon!
Gu-yeong!
Bring ring buoys!
Lifebuoys.
Yang-sun!
Yang-sun...
Commander, it's started again!
Yang-sun!
Yang-sun.
Jeong Gu-yeong!
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
[Weather Forecast - Cheonwangbong Peak,
Daily Precipitation]
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
Main Station.
How's the situation?
[Over 100mm of rain has poured down
southwest of Cheonwangbong.]
[It's worse than yesterday!]
Yang-sun.
Yang-sun!
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
Seo Yi-gang.
Withdraw.
[Seo Yi-gang!]
[I said, withdraw!]
Yang-sun.
Yang-sun!
-Yang-sun!
-[Going to the valley now is suicide!]
Yang-sun!
Let go of me!
-What was that?
-Gosh.
Yang-sun...
Yang-sun!
-Gu-yeong. No.
-Gu-yeong.
Yang-sun.
Yang-sun!
Yang-sun...
No way...
Yang-sun.
No way!
[Emergency Rescue Operation]
Yang-sun.
What am I going to do now?
-There's no way...
-Yes.
What do I do?
What am I going to...
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[Condolences]
How did it go?
We've recovered the bodies of
the deceased who died on the bus.
But no sign of Yang-sun yet.
Rescue divers have asked to withdraw.
It's been days already.
Most of the water has drained out.
She could
already be carried away into the sea.
Let's wrap up...
the search.
[Keeping citizens safe, Damsung Police]
Hey.
[Drunk driving causes nothing but tears.]
Are all of these from the river?
Yes.
How's Gu-yeong holding up?
Oh, you know...
Bring the lost article folder.
[Lost and Found Log book]
[Daily Log,
Haedong Police Substation]
This photo...
Oh, this?
It was my high school graduation.
But what's wrong with Yi-gang's grandma?
No one except Yi-gang has noticed.
I'm surprised you did.
[Damsung High School]
[Congratulations, Class of 2002]
Guys.
Have you seen Yi-gang?
I haven't seen her.
Have you guys seen Yi-gang?
Yi-gang's grandma!
Oh, you guys are here.
Where's Yi-gang?
I met her at the train station earlier.
She said she's going to Seoul.
What?
-I'll see you again.
-Goodbye.
On two!
I'm starving.
This girl...
She could've taken a photo with me
before she left.
Don't move.
Dad, over here.
Here we go.
Hello, sir.
-Officer Kim.
-Yes?
You should talk to Yi-gang.
Why? What's going on?
I cannot imagine how tough it is
for her to arrange a funeral alone.
So I suggested a joint funeral,
but she's as stubborn as an ox.
She insists on doing it alone.
[Condolences]
Yi-gang...
If you want to pay your respects,
come back later. It's not ready yet.
How are you feeling?
Let me help.
You need dishes, right?
Go away.
I'll do it alone. So go.
Please don't do this.
Please stop hiding
and pretending you're okay,
like you used to do.
When things get tough,
you can talk to me.
It's your fault.
If she hadn't gotten on that bus,
nothing would've happened to her.
If she hadn't gotten on that bus...
If it weren't for you...
She was all I had...
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
Go. Please.
Just leave.
[Condolences]
[Gamnamu Restaurant]
[Album]
[You brat.]
Won't you prepare a ritual table for me
when I die?
Stop saying that.
Gosh, what a pain in the neck!
Grandma.
Grandma, I'm sorry...
[Condolences]
I'm here camping. Don't worry about me.
What a great tent.
It's so easy to build.
Here.
You don't want coffee?
How about some tea then?
It won't take long. The burner's amazing.
They have no idea...
what happened here a few days ago.
But that's our job.
Remembering what happened here.
Who climbed that mountain,
what they'd gone through.
How scary the mountain is.
Or how comforting it can be.
Who made what kind of sacrifice
to protect the mountain.
We must remember it all.
Yang-sun's last moment was remarkable.
She was the most amazing ranger.
I feel like a real ranger now.
Take me to your training more often.
I want to see many other places.
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
[Mount Jirisan Final Flood Report]
[Date: August 28, 2019]
Hello.
Is there anyone else?
Boss and Il-hae are on patrol.
Gu-yeong...
and Yi-gang are still on vacation.
Right.
What brings you here today?
Well...
Could I see the daily log
during the flood?
What? The daily log?
We're investigating the cause
of the bus accident.
That bridge was in danger of collapsing,
so we'd blocked off that road.
It's a mystery that the bus went that way.
The driver may not have seen
the warning sign
because of the heavy rain.
The sign was on the ground by the road
like the bus crashed into it.
But since there were
no security cameras around,
we can't tell what exactly happened.
Rangers were working
near the mountain at the time,
so I thought maybe we can find witnesses
if we know who was there.
[Mount Jirisan Final Flood Report]
The daily log is not completed yet.
I see.
Please call me
when it's ready then.
So...
What route
did the bus take
to get to the bridge?
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
[Detour, Do Not Enter,
Collapse Hazard]
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[It wasn't an accident.]
[That man...]
[He killed them.]
[It's all my fault.]
[I should've stopped it.]
[I should've done
whatever it takes to stop it.]
[Only if I had stopped it,]
[they would still be alive.]
[Because of me...]
[They died because of me.]
Good morning, sir.
Are you all right?
Tell me if this is too much.
I'll find you another spot.
I tried to leave here.
[I've always wanted to leave this place.]
[That's why I've envied the ones
who left here.]
[But when I actually tried to leave,]
[there was no place to go.]
I want to stay.
My mom, dad, and grandma.
They're all here.
So I'll stay here, too.
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
Summer disaster prevention period
ends today.
Many trails and facilities were damaged
during the flood.
Pay special attention to patrols,
including flood recovery work
and detour guidance.
And Bidam Shelter's lacking a staff.
You know working at a shelter is tough.
You'll be taking turns
for the shelter duty.
But if there's a volunteer,
I'll consider the one first.
I'll go.
I'll go, sir.
One of the line throwers is broken.
Ropes and harnesses are
all in a bad condition.
Let's make time to fix them.
Okay.
[Repair Team Workshop]
Are you leaving?
Yes.
Take care.
Thanks.
I'll see you.
[Jirisan National Park,
Ranger]
[Jirisan National Park
Haedong Ranger Station]
Whatever, just take this.
What's this?
Ghosts are supposed to come
from the north today.
[I'll find out who the murderer is.]
[I will, for sure.]
[When I catch him, then...]
I don't have anything else to offer you.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry for this sudden visit.
But why are you here?
I want to ask you a few things.
I heard
these two were close
to your late husband.
Yes.
They always drank
or went to the mountain together.
They were like brothers.
And they...
ended up passing
around the same time.
Did anything happen among the three
when they passed?
Like a fight
or an argument?
Never.
They always boasted about
how they never once fought
since childhood.
Were they friends from childhood?
Yes. They grew up in the same village.
He lived there before we got married,
so I only heard stories.
He said it was up the mountain...
[Haedong Village Volunteer Rangers]
Here it is.
Black Bridge Village...
Yes. That was the name.
[This was my hideout when I was little.]
We called it
the Black Bridge Valley Shelter.
-Then...
-That's right.
This is my hometown.
[Kim Sol]
[The person you're trying to reach
is unavailable...]
What brings you here on your day off?
You know,
Black Bridge Village...
Why did it suddenly disappear?
Why do you ask?
I want to know what happened back then.
Why do you want to know?
I'll explain later.
-Leave!
[-In 1991,]
-Stop it!
[-a cable car business was carried out]
[in that village.]
[And many unfortunate events]
[-happened in a row.]
-We won't ever do as you say.
Leave.
Unfortunate events?
What happened?
In here.
[Someone put a dead animal
in the community well.]
Who would do such a thing?
[And some residents lost their lives.]
People died? Why?
There were tragic accidents...
What is it?
[And there was a suicide, too.]
What on earth was going on
in that village?
We only clean things up,
so it's hard to know the details.
Also,
we didn't even live in the village.
In the end, the cable car business
went down the drain.
Later, the national park conducted
a migration project
and the village closed down at last.
But who put the dead animal in the well?
You'll...
regret this.
[At the time,]
Yang Geun-tak, who was pushing
for the cable car business,
was the prime suspect.
Isn't that the man
who came recently
for the cable car business?
That's right.
But no one found out who actually did it.
Is that all?
That's all I know.
Then...
Is there a way I can find out
who lived in the village?
It was too long ago so I don't remember,
but there should be
the migration project record
at the main station.
[Mount Jirisan National Park Office]
[Document Room]
[Black Bridge Village
Migration Project Report]
[List of residents eligible for
Migration Project]
[Choi Il-man, Lee Jong-gu,
Kim Jin-deok...]
[Hyeon-su's father, Kim Nam-sik.]
[Lee Jae-geun]
[Yang-sun's grandfather.]
He must have put the bomb
in the trap on purpose.
-It could've been for a different reason.
-What?
He could have put it there to kill him.
[Seo Geum-ja who died at
Yangseokbong Peak in 2017.]
[Lee Geum-rye]
[It wasn't the flood.]
[All those who died till now had lived]
[in Black Bridge Village.]
[But...]
[Yi-gang's grandmother
isn't from the village.]
[So why?]
In 1991, a cable car business
was carried out in that village.
And many unfortunate events
happened in a row.
[Cable car business...]
Who put the dead animal in the well?
Yang Geun-tak was the prime suspect.
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[The people on the bus
weren't the target.]
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
[Yang Geun-tak...]
[He was the target.]
[Wildlife Ecology Evaluators
for Mount Jirisan Cable Car]
The cable car business
and Black Bridge Village...
What really happened back then?
[Heo Jin-ok]
Yi-gang.
Her pulse is too weak.
She has serious hypothermia.
We must hurry up
and get her to a hospital.
[Heo Jin-ok]
Hello?
Oh, park ranger?
How are you doing?
[Mount Jirisan National Park Office]
[I never got to thank you properly.]
I need to ask you
some questions in person.
Could you spare some time?
[I was planning on visiting
the mountain tomorrow anyway.]
[I'll call you when I get there.]
Okay. Thank you.
[Messages]
[Black Bridge Valley at 3]
[Warning: Bear Frequenting Area]
[At 3 o'clock...]
[the murderer will be here.]
So what's the evidence you can use
to prove who the murderer is?
I don't know yet.
But it'll be here somewhere for sure.
Here?
Is there really evidence here?
You two have been
suspicious from the beginning.
You're hiding something from me, right?
I also want to ask
what Yi-gang asked you earlier.
What?
The day Da-won died.
Why were you on the mountain?
-Something came up.
-Okay.
So what was that something?
I went to see Yang-sun.
You told me to remember things.
Even if everyone forgets,
I should remember her.
[Bidam One. An SOS report from
Magpie Hill, Deokseoryeong.]
[The victim feels severe pain
in the chest]
[from their pre-existing heart disease.]
[Any ranger close enough to make it?]
Magpie Hill is twenty minutes from here.
Haedong One.
Currently at Black Bridge Valley.
We're 20 minutes away. We'll mobilize.
[Helicopter's on its way. Hurry up.]
I need assistance.
I'm fine. Just go.
They sent a helicopter,
so it shouldn't take long.
Call me if anything happens.
[Endangered Species Restoration Center]
Hurry up!
Will Yi-gang be all right by herself?
Let's rescue the hiker first
and quickly head back.
Hurry!
Yi-gang...
Yi-gang is on the mountain.
[Jirisan]
[The murderer was trying to
kill someone today, too.]
[I think you were the target.]
I always saw a ghost light
before something bad happened.
[Please keep this a secret from others.]
[No one seems to have touched
the lost articles there.]
[The murderer did.]
[Are you a stalker?]
Someone might die there tomorrow.
[I should stop before then.]
What brings you here?
Someone made a false report.
[Are you going to kill him, too?]