Let's go for round two!
Let's take a picture!
Here we go!
One, two, three!
-Make a funny face.
-One more!
-One, two, three!
-Huh?
-What?
No...
Run!
Hey, what are you doing?
Get them!
Hey, stop right there!
Jeez.
Hey, stop!
Hey, to the left!
Stop right there!
Go down! Quick!
Hey, this thing's on.
-Where are they?
-Find them!
Hey, hurry up!
Are they gone?
-Woo-min.
-What?
Never mind.
Jeez.
Woo-min.
Date me.
-Guys! Woo-min!
-Woo-min, Ji-eun!
-Ppyoji! Where are you?
-Where did she go?
Hey, never mind, I was just kidding.
Where are you guys?
Okay.
Let's date.
Woo-min.
-Ppyoji!
-Woo-min!
Look at them! This is crazy!
-What is it?
-Look at them!
Oh, my God!
I said I only love you
Instead of all the words I had prepared
I'll always be by your side
I promise you as I look into the sky
-Woo-min!
THE POP-UP SHOP AND THE TAILOR SHOP
How about one more bead?
Excuse me, Mr. Jo.
To work on this sample,
our entire staff
had to work overtime for days.
All the designs you gave us
had to be handmade.
Oh, thank you for your hard work.
Mr. Jo.
I've been running this bag factory
in Seongsu-dong for over 20 years.
Let me give you some advice.
Mr. Jo, your designs are, how do I put it?
Delusional.
You need to make things you can sell.
It's way too different
from the conventional designs.
There's a limit
to straying away from tradition.
I bet this won't sell.
The production cost is similar
to Chanel or Vuitton.
Am I wrong, Mr. Jo?
It's not Mr. Jo.
It's designer Joseph Jean, sir.
What's the difference?
We all put our name on the line
for our business.
Don't you agree, Mr. Jo?
He's Mr. Jo, so I call him that.
See! He's not complaining!
Anyway, Mr. Jo,
if it takes this much work,
we won't make a lot in a month.
Mr. Jo, if you're too stubborn
about your design,
you'll end up going under. So, Mr. Jo-
"Mr. Jo"!
How many times did I hear that?
How dare he decide if it'll sell?
He only made one sample. Such a show-off.
What? It strays away from tradition?
Screw that!
Fashion is about change and evolution.
Esther, what else did he say?
-High-end, sir.
-Highland?
He wouldn't know what high means.
Has he been to Eilean Donan Castle?
What does he know about the Highlands?
Joseph.
Not highland, high-end brand.
That's enough.
He said my design is delusional!
Bosh!
I've never seen a purse like this
in my entire life.
Combining various materials,
with the structure, with the volume.
Not just anyone can do this.
You like Alexander McQueen, right?
This would put him to shame.
Yours is something more than high-end!
Don't give up
on your creativity for money.
Just do what you want to do.
Whatever that may be.
Then the world will recognize
how you shine.
Ma'am, if we look at the price point,
the purse's cost-performance ratio
is too low for MR. JOSEPH's clients.
Then make it a special edition.
But what happens if it doesn't get sold?
It'll be a total humiliation.
I hope people will get to see
this piece in some way.
Like a pop-up shop?
"A pop-up shop"?
You mean a flash retailer?
It will depend on how we do it,
but it's a good idea.
Excuse me.
Hello, Producer!
Congratulations, Mr. Lee.
Congratulations.
Thank you for coming.
It's a great flagship store
that suits the brand image.
I look forward to your support.
Oh my, hello. It's an honor.
I can't believe
I'm meeting you in person, Ms. Ahn.
Will you escort...
You're here, too, Ms. Hong.
How sentimental those colors are.
You just noticed that now?
Woo-min.
This is the photographer
for today's event, Ji Woo-min.
He'll be taking your pictures, too.
We meet again. Nice to see you here.
Yes. Hello.
Do you already know each other?
Let's get started.
Oh gosh, these look so good.
Mr. Lee looks so amazing!
I heard you have great retouching skills.
Please take extra care of the photos.
Sure.
Mr. Lee, the photos look great.
Well, you're perfect in every way, so...
-Great work.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I'm just doing my job.
Excuse me, but I have to ask.
Sure, go ahead.
I heard you and Ji-eun broke up.
I wonder why we keep running
into each other lately.
Yes, we did initially.
How do I say this...
It was like a test, so to speak.
When I was with her,
I felt she was different
from other women I'd dated.
But I just needed to be sure.
I thought about it,
and only after we broke up,
I realized that I was right.
So, I'd like to start over.
Shouldn't you apologize first?
You're indeed a good friend.
Thanks for the advice.
I was about to do that.
You and Ji-eun are close friends, right?
May I ask for your support?
I want to do things right this time.
I don't think I can do that.
I'll do my best retouching these.
Is it true
Thierry Henry is coming to Korea?
New World International invited him,
begging him to come.
And he wouldn't even listen.
Even when they held Asia's first store
launching event in Shanghai,
he never left his atelier in Paris.
So why now?
And secretly, by himself?
I know you two have been best friends
since your days at ESMOD.
That's news to me.
I heard that because of his visit,
every luxury hotel in Seoul is getting
cancellation or reservation calls.
And you'll find out
in Cheongdam Daily soon.
These hotels have no manners.
Ms. Ahn, you're the one arranging
Thierry Henry's visit, right?
Why are you handling that alone,
when you're so busy?
If you report this to Cheongdam Daily,
the agencies will start lining up,
so that they can host him.
I mean, it's Thierry Henry.
The chief designer of EARLAINE,
the brand that women all over the world
covet the most.
A Korean adoptee
and a European fashion icon.
That's right. Thierry is coming to Korea.
Oh my!
What an honor.
As one of the leading
fashionistas in Korea,
I can't express how honored I am.
Do you know anyone
who can manage his accommodation?
Who would say no to accommodating Thierry?
Everyone's trying to make connections
and launch EARLAINE in Korea.
It's a different matter.
We need someone to work with discretion.
Someone who can keep it quiet.
-Thierry Henry?
-Hush!
That's right, one of the most famous
Koreans in the world
alongside BTS and Son Heung-min.
Thierry Henry.
He's Korean-French, to be exact.
His designs are always sold out,
and wherever he goes, he becomes
the gossip that are just as shocking.
With no manners, no mercy, no sense,
he's mean, picky, and finicky...
All right, I get it.
He even came second in Tabloid's list
of the rudest celebrities of the year.
That amazing Thierry Henry?
Was he second place, not first?
Come on, Ms. Oh.
So are you in or not?
Just say "goodbye" to him?
-Can I do that?
-You...
You'll have to say bye to me first.
Thierry's visit to Korea is personal
and has nothing to do with EARLAINE.
He doesn't want this to be news in Korea.
He doesn't want any public attention.
He'd like no one to know about this.
Can I ask him for an autograph
or a picture for my Instagram?
No.
Of course, absolutely not.
His likes and dislikes are clear,
but they differ from time to time.
He has mood swings too.
When he gets too passionate,
he does unpredictable things.
But that wouldn't happen this time.
His visit will be extremely private.
Take good care of him.
Thank you for your trust, Ms. Ahn.
Excuse me, Ms. Ahn,
does Thierry have a particular reason
for coming to Korea?
He wants to buy a suit.
A custom-made suit.
Do you think this makes any sense?
I guess there's
a world-class tailor in Korea,
who's good enough to attract him.
Ppyoji, this will be
your most glorious moment
in your life as a fashionista.
Of course I respect him,
but I only want to see him
in magazines or the media. He's scary.
He's one of the most creative people
I know in fashion.
He's only known through gossip,
but he actually does
many anonymous charity work.
He takes 40% of his income
and gives it back to society.
Everything from refugee issues
to starvation, and the environment.
To some, he may be a respectable person.
But he's also a complete menace to others.
But that might be just gossip, made up
by those who can't do their jobs right.
Hey, what's so funny?
He's been chuckling all along.
What is it, Woo-min?
Guess who just followed me on Instagram?
There's a campaign
with Dynamic Metropolitan as the theme.
It's a global event held by THE Q.
They want photos by street photographers.
That's why I'm looking
for suitable candidates on Instagram.
WOOMIN_J
FOLLOW
It's an honor.
Want to give it a shot?
You mean, THE Q?
Yes, of course. Thank you!
I'll DM you.
Let's sit down. I ordered for you.
Did you ask me for lunch to nag?
Nagging is for people
who actually listen, Seon-ho.
I'm a troublemaker now?
You ruined a trunk show,
and it made headlines.
So the answer is yes, of course.
The last two scheduled shoots
got canceled.
I'll admit my attitude
wasn't professional as a model.
I deserve punishment.
It seems you messed
with a pretty powerful woman.
Did I? So does that mean
I'm out of work for a while?
Will you apologize?
I have nothing to apologize for.
Good for you, then, Seon-ho.
A powerful woman, huh?
I'm craving champagne.
You brought your company card, right?
Let me order some.
You don't want
Thierry Henry's visit to hit the news.
What?
No way.
You know nothing.
On YouTube, they say,
you have to dress up to accommodate him.
Welcome, Thierry! Hello!
I'm from AUDREY...
Wait, excuse...
Oh gosh!
-Go!
-Okay, you should go.
MS. AHN
Jeez.
And then there he was,
looking so charismatic.
He had such a unique aura.
Pardon?
You want to speak with him?
The staff member you saw the other day.
She's taking good care of him right now.
Did something happen?
Well, Ms. Ahn,
by any chance, is Thierry allergic to...
No, I mean...
Does he have a trauma with flowers?
Were the flowers pink?
Gosh, how did you know?
Sometimes he panics
at the sight of the color pink.
I guess that's
how much he hates the color.
Thank you.
You saved me from all that pink.
Hello, let me introduce myself again.
I'm Pyo Ji-eun, from AUDREY.
Your Korean's very good.
Anything making you uncomfortable?
I was desperate for this
during the flight.
FINE DUST
VERY BAD
How nice.
So nice!
That hurt.
Passing through!
Are you having fun?
TOFU
-Do you mind taking our...
-One, two...
-Here you are.
-Thank you.
Who is it?
Come on, it's too early.
You have to help me.
Be my driver for a few days.
-Driver?
-Yeah.
Am I your husband? Or your boyfriend?
Neither, but you're my best male friend!
I'm not unemployed anymore.
I've got a job now.
I already asked Mr. Do to excuse you.
I checked you have no plans this week.
He told me you're all mine.
Where are we even going?
I haven't even washed my face yet.
No time. Do it in the car.
What is this? Did you get a new car?
I rented it. I'm doing a one-man
escort service because of Ms. Oh.
"One-man escort"?
I'm escorting Thierry Henry all by myself.
Hey, your hair's a mess. Do something.
Do I really have to wear a suit
while I'm driving?
Dressing up is a must
when escorting Thierry Henry.
Well, you sure have a nice figure.
By the way, you seem like
you've changed a bit lately.
Something feels different.
No, I've always been the same.
What? Do I look more handsome?
It's not that.
Well.
Don't lose this.
You got it?
How much is the pay?
Oh no, Mr. Driver, we're out of budget.
METROPOLITAN RAILWAY MAP
You said I was a driver. So why am I here?
He wants to take the subway.
But I can't drive a train.
I thought you said people can't find out.
All the people passing by
are staring at him.
I wonder why he wants to go
to Cheongnyangni Station by subway.
Well, don't be curious.
Don't ask questions.
Just do what the man wants.
That's the point of this escort mission.
Thierry.
I'm good, thank you.
Just try one.
What is it?
It's spicy.
-Spicy?
-It's spicy!
-Hot!
-It's hot?
He says it's hot!
-Not this one?
-Here!
-Hot! It's Hot!
-It's hot?
Hot!
-I'm sorry.
-Run!
EXIT
I'm sorry.
PLATFORMS
It's unique and pretty.
Are you launching
a purse line this season?
It's not that.
I just came up with the design.
When is the release date?
If it's Joseph's first purse,
I should be the first customer.
I'm not producing it.
We can't afford the production cost.
I'll just display samples
at a pop-up shop.
For my customers.
A purse that not even loyal customers
of Joseph can purchase.
A purse you can't buy,
a design you can't have.
What's the point of that?
I know.
You came up with a great design,
and yet you'll take away the chance
to buy it just because it's expensive?
You have to try everything.
That's more like you.
Oh, this one is good.
I like this too.
That pose is too much.
It's only a local brand.
Seon-ho!
Let's take five.
Okay.
Why are you so surprised?
What are you doing here?
You shouldn't be here.
Why not? I can't come to the studio
I used to shoot at?
Didn't Mr. Gang tell you?
That I got cut off? Yeah, he did.
I just came to see you.
God, I was worried.
Anyway, who are they?
They don't look like models.
-Influencers.
-Influencers?
Twenty K.
Thirty-two. Forty-one.
And this one's, 70K.
Look who's here!
Did you have to look for yourself
that the influencers replaced you?
Ma'am.
What do you think? Do you feel threatened?
If we just take a few pictures with them,
and they do Instagram postings
for purchase orders,
I'll be in business 24 hours a day.
The sales from your magazine shoots
is nothing compared to them.
So you're a saleswoman?
Ye Seon-ho, you may be a famous model,
but in the fashion industry,
people always flock to what's new.
So, all the things you have
could also mean you're outdated,
don't you think?
How many followers do you have?
Come on.
You will go somewhere, not me.
Us?
My friend Ahn Nam-hee prepared
a beautiful Korean meal for me tonight.
I'm on a diet.
Also, I'm not familiar with local food.
What was that thing we ate earlier?
Tteokbokki?
Yeah, that one, I was so shocked.
That's why I'm done eating today.
Sorry, we didn't mean...
I don't want to disappoint my friend,
so you should go there
and help me enjoy
that delicious feast from here.
-Did you get what he meant?
-Yup.
He'll just enjoy with his eyes.
What?
So spicy, I hate you! But you're cute.
It's so tasty.
Is it good?
Look how pretty that is!
It's hot!
Thank you!
Wow, the food looked and tasted great.
But I can't eat another bite.
Here, your paycheck for the day.
Are you still seeing that guy?
Who? Nam-jin?
Wow, this is so good.
What does it matter to you
if I'm with him or not?
Well, you broke up, so I was wondering
if you still had feelings for him.
I certainly misunderstood him.
He tried to take me as I am,
but I thought I had to change
who I was to better fit him.
So that was difficult.
Why? You worried
I'll start seeing him again?
No.
I'm just curious as a friend.
Maybe he's a great guy,
and I just didn't think
to look deeper into him.
If he turns out to be a bad guy,
you'd better have my back as my friend.
Why should I?
You have Seon-ho, too.
Seon-ho fights way better than me.
No way.
When our class lost at soccer
on sports day, things got scary.
I bet she even made some of the boys cry.
That's my friend Seon-ho, indeed.
And then she insisted to play
in the next game herself,
in a boys-only match.
But she's not a boy!
That's crazy.
She's really something, isn't she?
Ji-eun.
Hey, Nam-jin.
We're surely running
into each other often.
Did you have a meeting
around here or something?
Yes, I had dinner
with my college professors.
We had some drinks as well.
Looks like it. Your cheeks are red.
Just a few drinks.
I know a good place for a walk nearby.
If you're okay,
would you like to go with me,
and have a talk?
Oh, sure.
Woo-min, you should go on ahead.
No.
You have to transfer twice
on the subway to get home.
I'll wait.
I'll take her home.
Hey, I'm not a kid. I can take a cab.
I say mean things sometimes,
but I'm grateful for you, friend.
If it weren't for you,
I would've been exhausted today.
See you tomorrow, Woo-min.
Let's go.
Ji-eun.
Yes?
What is it? Did I forget something?
Go home early.
Go on, Woo-min.
I should apologize,
so that I can ask you to start over again.
Apologize?
I broke up with you back then
because I wanted to know more about you.
To see if you were dating me
because you needed me,
or because you liked me.
So, have you found an answer?
I know for sure that you didn't date me
just because you needed my help.
You mean
you're not so sure
whether I liked you or not?
Will you give me a chance
to figure that out?
It's so weird to see you
being so forward like this.
I like you a lot, Ji-eun.
I'm sure
I'll figure it out soon with your help.
Thank you for being honest with me.
I thought about it,
and only after we broke up, I realized.
So, I'd like to start over.
I want to do things right this time.
PHOTOGRAPHY BOOK
CHAT
SIGNED BY A FAMOUS DESIGNER? WHO?
I'LL TAKE IT IF IT'S FREE
JOSEPH... WHO'S THAT?
WHO'S JOSEPH?
Shoot, no one's buying.
Huh?
What's this?
Next.
Thank you all for today.
We'll contact you individually
regarding the results.
You didn't like any of them?
Maybe just this one?
And the male models?
I want someone completely new.
Never-seen-before kind of new.
That way, it won't draw
attention away from the bag.
Should I search on Instagram?
I've got your DM.
Do you need a model for a pop-up shop?
Nice to see you here, sir!
Let's see your walk.
All right!
What are those old photos
he keeps looking at?
Why does he keep tracking down
the places in the photos?
What if he didn't come here
for a tailored suit,
but actually to find his birth mother?
He's retracing the steps
he used to take with his mom.
He does seem a bit sentimental,
and hesitant, too, from behind.
GYEONGGANG STATION
GYEONGGANG LOUNGE
It's been a long time
since trains ran at this station.
Now, they run rail bikes here.
Sorry, Thierry, I think
you should take off your glasses.
Lots of young people come here.
They'll recognize you.
I'm Thierry Henry.
I'm just being who I am!
But you said you wanted to come here.
-Wait, isn't that...
-It's him!
-Wow.
-Hey, take a picture of him.
Hey, who's that? What?
Excuse me,
did you just take pictures?
Please delete them.
I was taking pictures
of him, Thierry Henry, not you.
Nonsense, that's my uncle.
Look, I was right!
-See?
-It's his glasses!
-You're wrong.
-That's him!
No pictures, please. Please delete these.
My niece, let's go.
That's him, right?
-It's him, it is!
-For real?
Oh my gosh, ouch!
That hurt!
Wait, please, you can't take pictures.
No pictures!
No! I'm her uncle!
He's my uncle! My uncle!
Thierry, it's okay.
We checked everyone there
and made them delete the photos.
We asked them not to upload
the pictures online.
So...
I really don't know what to do.
He just changed his schedule, saying
he wants to go back to Paris right away.
Isn't that good if he's leaving
earlier than scheduled?
I have no idea what kind of escort
I'm doing right now.
He sobbed all the way back from Gapyeong.
No matter how much I comforted him,
he wouldn't stop.
He hasn't even mentioned
anything about getting a suit.
So, you're just going to let him go?
My guess is,
he's looking for his mother,
his birth mother.
If that's the case, I'd like to help him,
but I'm hesitant to bring that up.
You seem to be having
a hard time with this, Ji-eun.
So I went to see Ms. Ahn.
She gave me this.
What is this? An old magazine?
Read it.
VINCENT CHA
THIERRY HENRY'S ESMOD CLASSMATE
I think
it's not his birth mother, but his...
Welcome, how can I help you?
Well.
We're here for a custom suit.
We're having dinner
with both of our parents.
It's for a special occasion.
This way, I'll measure you first.
I didn't know
there was a tailor shop here.
I saw in a magazine article
that you graduated
from a famous design school in Europe.
I didn't graduate.
Why? It must've been
difficult to get into.
The desirable way's
to cut your pants at the point
where your ankle bone shows a bit.
-Will that be okay?
-Well...
Yes, that sounds good.
Everyone prefers
ordinary things like this, right?
My father did, too.
Anything different from everyone else
was something he couldn't accept.
So I'm here in Korea.
You must've been sad.
That must've been your dream.
Still, I got my father's tailor shop.
And I've been making
suits for his old customers
and their children for happy occasions,
hoping that I could help
make them a little happier.
I wonder what kind of happiness
I'll get from this suit.
You wear a suit
on meaningful days of your life.
I think you might be my last customer.
I'll sew each
and every knot for your suit,
so that you can look
perfect at the dinner.
"Last customer"?
Tailored suits aren't popular anymore.
Off-the-shelf suits are good and cheaper.
Custom suits take days in the making.
They're only popular
among a few loyal fans.
We're closing down.
HAE-JUN TAILOR SHOP
CHA HAE-JUN
I was thinking you'd need
to change your return flight again.
No, this is good enough for me.
I just wanted to check
some things out for myself.
That's enough for me.
But if you go like this, I'll be so sad.
This was the best I could do
while sticking to the rules you told me.
They're closing down soon.
This is the answer I can give you.
I won't be rescheduling.
127-34 BOGWANG-DONG YONGSAN-GU
I'm learning how to tailor suits.
I mostly just sow on lapels,
but I'm enjoying what I do.
Whenever I think of you,
I go to Seoul
and buy a French fashion magazine,
and that's the one thing
I enjoy doing the most.
The peaceful view of the Han River
from the subway train,
eating spicy tteokbokki
while waiting for a train,
and standing at a small
but scenic train station...
That's when I feel alive.
Thierry, I think I'll have to stay
and live here, just like this.
This letter is for us
to let ourselves free
from the promise we made
on the padlock we left at Pont des Arts.
When you threw your key into the Seine,
I didn't. I guess I wasn't ready.
I want you to unlock
that padlock and be free.
HAE-JUN TAILOR SHOP
Welcome.
When you're done with the suit,
please send it to this address.
I don't think that'll work.
Customized suits require a fitting.
You'll have to come to see me again.
Pop-ups are usually about leaving
an impression that lingers on.
When people at the pop-up shop
see the bags on display,
what would they think?
Their first impression would be "pretty."
And it will linger on,
making them want it, maybe?
Then should we give
people those impressions?
That lingering impression...
Esther, get the design sketches.
Let's go by scooter.
Why are we going to the fabric market
in Sinseol-dong all of a sudden?
We'll make tote bags
with my design sketches on them.
Joseph!
Joseph, I like you so much!
Bosh. I like you too, Esther!
Now, that's more like Joseph.
This pop-up seems like a sign of promise.
You release the design,
promising that
it will be released one day.
Right, I'm making a promise to the world.
It's not like I can do it at the moment,
but I'll make it happen someday.
-Well, I hope your fans are patient.
-Gosh, seriously?
As long as it's not too late, Joseph.
Where's Woo-min?
This is a historical moment.
Today's an important day for Woo-min, too.
Thierry, what is he...
Thierry? Holy cow!
How come Thierry's here with you?
For the EARLAINE launch.
I've been interested in it.
With Ms. Ahn's help,
I was able to have a meeting with him.
One of his conditions
for the meeting was to bring him here.
-Nice to meet you.
-Me, too.
Hello.
Hello, Seon-ho.
You said he freaks out
at the mere sight of pink, right?
It's like Ms. Ahn mentioned,
"it changes from time to time."
Hello, everyone.
Oh my, that bag?
You're crazy!
I'm about to be a bad guy.
I'm gonna snatch it!
This is mine!
Now, let me introduce to you, Mr. Joseph!
Joseph!
Look this way!
Thank you! Wow!
Aside from these two,
please send me the rest my way.
Sure.
Thank you.
But it's not up to me
to get them published.
-Good work.
-Thank you.
I felt like Thierry was isolating himself
behind these tall, solid walls,
and now he's overcome them.
I'm so happy for him.
He showed his true self to you,
because you did a great job.
As the saying goes,
sincerity is often met with sincerity.
I like that.
I hope the same goes for my sincerity.
How about it?
I want something more than casual dating
with you this time.
An official date.
I want to sincerely convey how I feel.
My hand's cold.
Are you going to leave me hanging?
Please?
I HOPE THIS IS THE PERFECT SUIT
FOR THE PERFECT BOYFRIEND
I didn't know this place was so pretty.
Too bad it's just a pop-up shop.
What's with the look?
You look like you've got
a lot on your mind today.
I'm just tired.
I had a guest to escort, you know.
The pop-up runs until next week.
Why did Woo-min insist on
meeting us out here this late?
All of us together.
Today's the opening day.
He's being a loyal friend.
Wait here just a sec.
I've got to call my dad for a bit.
Sure, I'll wait here.
You're pretty today.
Your makeup's great.
What's with you?
Hey, Woo-min.
What's up with you?
Did you go to a wedding?
You're all dressed up.
Are you falling for me
for looking so handsome?
You must've not looked in the mirror.
Which part is handsome?
Look around and take pictures, too.
This is Joseph's pop-up shop
that even Thierry Henry fell in love with!
Do you remember this necktie?
Have you kept it?
I...
I'd like to go back to how I used to feel.
Let's stop being friends.
Don't you know how I feel?
You were never just a friend.
I've always seen you as my girl.
Let's start over, Ji-eun.
Ji-eun.
Do you think I'm a joke?
Did you think I'd be happy
if you asked me to start over?
Let's just stop being friends.