♫  All I want is you and me  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫  First close your eyes, and feel my breaths  ♫
♫  Not allowed to escape  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫ Hurry and listen carefully the sound of heartbeats ♫
♫ Just waiting for you to say okay ♫
♫ Tell me your secret ♫
♫ I just want you to stay ♫
♫ Experience with you ♫
♫ This and that feelings ♫
♫ Just come to me right now ♫
♫ I’m crazy, really can’t wait ♫
♫ No need to be that clear-headed ♫
♫ When I am with you ♫
♫ I am almost engulfed ♫
♫ You are beautiful as if you are not real ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫  First close your eyes, and feel my breaths  ♫
♫  Not allowed to escape  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫ Hurry and listen carefully the sound of heartbeats ♫
♫ Just wait for you to say okay ♫
[HIStory 5: Love In The Future]
[Chapter 6]
Hai Yi. I'm falling for you.
I said... I'm falling for you.
♫ Driving on a sleepless raining night ♫
♫ Aimlessly driving ♫
♫ Just driving ♫
♫ Discovering the memories about you and me ♫
♫ Have scattered in every corner ♫
♫ Every corner ♫
♫ (I thought...) The painful wound has already healed ♫
♫ (I also thought...) Pretending I don’t care ♫
♫ I’ll be better, will have a normal life ♫
We'll be getting off work soon. Where are you?
Are you not coming back?
I'm leaving the office now.
Are you coming back for dinner?
Hai Yi, reply to my messages!
What are you busy with?
Even if Hai Yi doesn't accept my love confession,
with his personality, he would talk back viciously.
Why did he just disappear like that?
Momo's advice is not helping at all.
"It's always darkest before dawn," huh?
I only see darkness in my life now.
Kid, why are you here alone?
Where are your parents?
Did you run away so your parents can't find you?
I didn't run away.
It's late now.
It's dangerous to stay outside alone.
I know the way home.
Do you like it?
It's a lucky bracelet.
Here. You can have it. You know what?
People with a lucky bracelet have magic.
Make a wish in front of it.
Your dream will come true.
I wish I can find my dad.
The kid who was lost back then was Hai Yi!
I didn't expect fate to bring us together again.
I can't believe that I am falling for that little boy I met.
Well... I need to find him.
Hai Yi.
Hai Yi? Sorry. Sorry
[Location of Surgical Patients]
Hai Yi.
Aunt.
How's he doing? What did the doctor say?
It's a *myocardial infarction.
(*heart attack)
He went into the operating theater a few hours ago. He's still in surgery.
I-I don't know...
Don't worry. You dad is a strong man.
The medical field is very advanced now. He'll make it through.
Right. He'll make it through.
It'll be fine.
Dad... You must persevere.
I still have so much to talk about with you.
[63 Yunyi Road]
Transferring to voicemail. Charges apply after the beep.
Please hang up if you don't want to leave a message.
Is he working overtime?
Huai-en...
I've changed my door-lock's passcode to your birth date.
You can use it to enter whenever you want to see me.
Tap with your finger, swipe a keycard, or enter the passcode.
[0520]
Hello, Huai-en. Did you call me?
Yes. I brought some late night snacks to surprise you,
but you are not home.
Sorry. The Chairman...
What happened to him?
Nothing. An urgent company matter came up.
I have to handle it.
Where are you? Are you in my flat?
Yes. Is everything okay with the company?
It should be fine.
It's just that I don't think I'll be leaving soon.
I'm not sure what time I'll be home.
It's all right. You didn't make me come here.
I'm going home now.
No way. It's late.
I would be worried if you go home alone.
Get some rest in my room when you're tired.
- I'll be home as soon as I can.
- It's all right.
I can go home alone.
I don't want to pressure you.
Listen to me.
All right.
I will sleep in your room tonight.
You promise me something too.
Make sure you also get some rest.
Well... Good night.
Good night.
Huai-en.
I'm so glad that you came to see me.
- Bye.
Love you.
- Are you Hai Yang's family?
- How's my dad?
The patient suffered a myocardial infarction. We couldn't save him.
We tried our best. I'm sorry for your loss.
Bro—...
How could you leave us without any last words?
It's way too sudden. How are we supposed to cope?
Hai Yin...
Get up.
Poseidon Department Store was everything to Hai Yang.
There has to be a new chairman.
We have to decide the next chairman as soon as possible.
Managing Director Liang.
Gather all the board members for an urgent meeting tomorrow.
Yes, Sir.
Hai Yi, where are you?
I don't even know where you're from or where you live.
Hello? Hai Yi. Where are you?
Hello?
Hello...
Hai Yi, why aren't you talking?
I'm fine.
Where are you? Why aren't you home yet?
A company issue came up.
"Company"?
Are you still at the office?
I won't be home tonight. Don't wait for me.
That's all.
Wait. I—... Hello?
Something is wrong with Hai Yi today.
Dad...
Don't sleep anymore.
Xiao Yi!
Daddy.
Daddy, I thought you didn't want me anymore.
How could I not want you?
It's fine. It's fine.
Xiao Yi, I couldn't find you after the phone call.
Don't ever run away again, understand?
You scared me to death.
I'm Xiao Yi.
I didn't run away.
I'm right here.
Stop sleeping, okay?
Would you wake up please?
Wake up.
Sorry to wake you.
It's all right.
Did you solve the company matter?
What's wrong? Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I promised to set up a meeting with you and Chairman.
I don't think I can make it happen.
It's all right. I'm not in a rush.
I just came back from the hospital.
Chairman... passed away.
What did you say about the chairman again?
It was a heart attack. They couldn't save him.
[Poseidon Department Store]
Hai Yi?
Chairman, we'll do our daily routine in the afternoon.
Some other people will join us.
That really is Hai Yi.
Board members, thank you for being here despite your busy schedules.
My older brother has just passed away. It's been hard for us.
However, we need someone to lead Poseidon Department Store.
Today, I'm going to make an announcement.
His son will inherit the business.
Hai Yi will be the next chairman,
and lead the Poseidon Department Store.
Hai Yi has never been involved in our company's business.
It will severely stress him if he suddenly
becomes the chairman right now.
He's just a kid who knows nothing about the business.
Are you joking?
I heard that Mr. Hai has been abroad for a long time,
just spending money and enjoying life.
Are you sure he knows how to run a company?
Vice Chairman Wu, do you have a better candidate in mind?
Of course I do. Managing Director Liang is very experienced.
He helped Chairman run the company for years. To me,
he's the best candidate for this job.
Good idea.
Yes. The board can only be at ease
if the Poseidon Department Store is run by Managing Director Liang.
Board Members, thank you for the opportunity.
I'm afraid I can't take this job.
I think the most important thing to do now
is to help Hai Yi make arrangements for the funeral.
Poseidon Department Store was everything for Hai Yang.
He will only rest in peace
once we decide on the next chairman.
Board members.
Here's the will from my brother.
In the will, it clearly states that if anything happens to him,
Hai Yi will be the next chairman of Poseidon Department Store.
So Chairman has made the arrangements already.
We should respect his last will.
[Will by Hai Yang]
Board members,
I promise I will do my best,
and follow in my father's footsteps.
I will lead the Poseidon Department Store to a prosperous future.
As you all know,
besides Poseidon Department Store being everything to Hai Yang,
it has also been everything to me.
Emotionally, of course I'd like to respect Chairman's last will.
Rationally, however,
choosing the next chairman is not a joke.
I have an idea.
I suggest that Hai Yi
be the interim chairman for the next three months.
Meanwhile, he should compete with Managing Director Liang.
The one with the better performance gets to be the next chairman.
Hai Yi, will you dare to take the challenge?
Yes. Good idea. I agree.
It's reasonable. I agree too.
Vice Chairman, this is disrespectful to my brother.
Fine.
I accept the challenge.
Brother Zhe-ni. You haven't had breakfast, right?
I bought you a club sandwich and a hot latte.
Let me know if you need anything else.
Director, why are you suddenly so nice to me?
You even got me breakfast.
If there's anything you want to say, just say it.
You're scaring me.
Don't say that. You sound like I've been treating you poorly.
It's the first time you've been so nice, though.
Just say it.
I was just wondering... our new chairman...
what he plans to do with me.
The "new chairman"...
Do you mean Hai Yi?
Yes.
Are you talking about the guy
who always comes to work with me?
Exactly.
I had my doubts about it before.
Our new chairman has such a unique charisma.
He intentionally pretended to be junior staff.
If you've found anything I did offensive,
please bear with me.
Having said that,
I was strict with you for the sake of the company, right?
Please say something nice to the new chairman for me.
I have to catch a plane early tomorrow morning.
What do you want from me?
Xiao Yi, come on. Sit here.
No. I'm good with the couch.
You should know what I mean.
I do. I told you I want to live my own life.
Why do you force me to inherit the business?
It's the family business that I've been working for.
You'll have to inherit it someday.
As I grew up, I never felt your fatherly love.
You spent all you time working.
The only time you took me to celebrate New Year,
you lost me because you got a work call.
Do you really think I care about our family business?
Xiao Yi, I told you it was an accident.
All right. Forget about that incident.
Have you ever believed me
when I've said Wu Chang-shan is not a good man?
He has worked hard with me his whole life.
- Don't say pointless things if you don't understand.
- Right. I don't understand.
In the end, you don't even believe me.
Why do you want me to inherit the business?
I'll choose my own life.
All right.
You can make your own decision when you are strong enough.
But listen, Poseidon Department Store is your responsibility!
I don't want that responsibility.
I'll show you I can still survive without your financial support.
Dad...
How could you leave me like this?
Why did our last conversation end like that?
Hai Yi.
These are for you.
[To nine-year-old Hai Yi]
[Happy 15th Birthday to Hai Yi]
"Hai Yi, happy 15th birthday."
"I promised we would go camping for your birthday."
"I did not keep my words because of work again."
"I'm sorry."
I didn't know he remembered my birthday every year.
Of course he did.
He was too busy with work and didn't know how to express himself.
He never made it to give you these gifts.
He always complained to me about missing a lot of your growing up.
I thought he didn't love me nor care about me.
Silly boy.
What father would not love his own child?
Your mom was from a rich family.
She chose to be with your dad
regardless of her family's objection.
She gave up everything
and started a business from nothing and suffered with your dad.
She even disowned your grandfather.
It was unexpected that she would get sick and die young,
and that made your dad the bad guy.
He tried so hard to establish Poseidon Department Store,
and to make it successful,
because he wanted to do something for your mother
and pass the family business to you.
In the end, this made him a failed father.
He really did love you.
Know that.
Aunt...
I'm so angry.
I'm so angry at myself. Why did I always go against him?
If I had known I would never see him again...
I miss him so much.
Let it all out. You'll feel better.
Aunt...
Thank you for telling me everything.
I will do my best to fulfill his last wishes
and protect the Poseidon Department Store.
Great.
That cunning man Wu Chang-shan is treating you like this.
The most important thing now is to stabilize the company.
Stay focused.
Your dad will surely look after you from Heaven,
just like he did before, and silently protect you.
You can do it.
Thank you, Aunt.
What do you mean?
Someone protested at the food court.
You said you would punish those who didn't do their jobs.
I would like to take responsibility and resign.
You've worked here for a while, and you've worked hard.
It's just a small incident, yet you would like to quit.
This is not your style.
I—
I made a big mistake.
I don't think I should work here anymore.
Are you talking about always setting up Lin Huai-en?
You haven't given me a good explanation about that.
Why are you always targeting him?
Answer me.
I—... I'm jealous of him.
That's why I wanted to teach him a lesson.
Lin Huai-en is new to the company.
There's no conflict of interest between you two.
Why are you jealous of him?
Because I like you.
I've liked you since the first time I saw you.
I've kept it to myself over the years,
and hoped that you would love me back someday.
After Lin Huai-en came into the picture,
I couldn't take it anymore because you're so nice to him.
Who is he?
Tony...
Love is always inexplicable.
I appreciate that you like me,
but I can't do anything about it,
because I'm already in love with Lin Huai-en.
I can't have anyone else other than him.
I see.
Please accept my resignation.
This is what I can do for Lin Huai-en.
You—
There are some changes within the company.
I need someone to fight with me.
Your performance has always been outstanding,
and I trust you very much.
I really hope that you can stay.
Although we won't be lovers,
I hope we can be work partners from now on.
Are you willing?
I'm willing. Thank you Managing Director.
I'll definitely work harder.
Sir—... Wait.
Sir, you can't come in without an appointment. Sir.
It's okay. You can go back to work.
Hai Yi, why did you lie to me
and hide your true identity?
How have I lied to you?
You've never asked me.
No? You could've told me yourself.
We've lived together for a while.
I didn't even know who you were until someone told me.
You are my friend because of who I am,
and not my family background, right?
Of course! I did want to earn money from you at the start,
but later I truly—... wanted to be your friend.
Then what's the problem?
I even told you I time-traveled,
but you still don't believe me.
It's not like that.
I just think you don't need the details
because you might leave anytime.
So...
Am I just a passerby in your life?
I can't control your thoughts.
Everyone has secrets in this world.
I haven't done anything wrong to you.
Fine.
From now on, we are no longer friends.
Why can't you understand my situation now?
Chairman, here is an urgent document.
Is he coming for me? Is he here?
Darn it, Hai Yi.
He hasn't come for me at all.
What should I do?
I can't just go back to him and cry like a girl.
Dai Zhe-ni, you are so stupid!
Why were you so impulsive?
You even said, "We are no longer friends!"
Hello, Sam. I saw them.
Okay.
What should I do?
I even blocked my last way out.
Don't rush it. It's not that bad.
Are you sure? When I think about Hai Yi and I being strangers from now on,
I'm heartbroken.
You just have to explain your misunderstanding, talk to each other nicely and you'll be fine.
But he's not even looking for me.
Or should I go to him first? Make it less awkward for him?
No. You must endure it.
He chose to hide it. For a thing this big, you shouldn't give in.
He should come and explain and apologize to you first.
What if he never comes?
Then, it's a test for him.
Just make sure you never give in.
But when two people fight,
one of them has to give in to solve the problem.
Besides... I was the one who started the fight.
If you always apologize first whenever you fight,
you know what, you will be dominated.
As one saying goes, "Have no regrets when you love someone to death."
You'll have to listen to him all the time.
Love should be given unconditionally, right?
You can't just give in.
You need to know how to exit the situation.
But I haven't even confirmed my relationship with Hai Yi.
[Cartoony World]
Don't worry.
At least you've confirmed it by looking at each other.
Trust me.
Are people's mindsets 20 years later
really different from my generation?
I should probably listen to how modern people think.
All right. Momo, I'll entrust my happiness to you.
No problem. Leave it to me.
Please explain.
These are just some photos of work events. What's wrong?
I'm not surprised that Wu Chang-shan protects you,
but how could you collude with Luquan Group?
Chairman, "collude" is too much.
Luquan Group provides our E-commerce platform. Is anything wrong with that?
I know that Vice Chairman Wu and a few board members
would like you to be the chairman.
It's obvious that he's gathering backup for you!
You're just imagining things from the photos. You're overthinking.
You know whether or not I'm "overthinking."
If I really needed the support of Luquan Group,
it would be quickest to simply date Lu Si-chi.
You guys are no longer together anyway.
How would I know if you are a double-dealer?
My dad trusted you so much in the past.
Liang Wun-sen, I'm warning you.
You are the managing director of Poseidon Department Store.
If I find you colluding with Luquan Group, I'll surely punish you severely.
Even if you are the chairman now,
you can't insult me like this without any proof.
As long as I work for Poseidon Department Store,
I won't let something like this happen.
♫ Driving on a sleepless raining night ♫
♫ Aimlessly driving ♫
♫ Just driving ♫
♫ Discovering the memories about you and me ♫
♫ Have scattered in every corner ♫
♫ Every corner ♫
Shall we play over there later? It looks cool.
It's Hai Yi.
Don't pick up the phone.
Why not? He's finally calling me.
At least, answer after he waits for 20 rings.
"Twenty"? What kind of plan is that?
I'm your adviser. You know nothing.
Seventeen...
Hello? Aunt, yes.
Nineteen...
This Hai Yi is not sincere enough.
Wei Se-mo! What a stupid idea!
♫ The falling rain has bad intentions ♫
♫ Completely leaving no room ♫
♫ Abruptly reminding me of the past ♫
♫ The rain sounds are foreshadowing  ♫
♫ Constantly reminding ♫
♫ Describing how powerless I am ♫
♫ Just don’t be depressed, don’t be submissive ♫
♫ Be courageous, but the memories fail me ♫
♫ When mentioning you, I become powerless ♫
♫ That word and sentence, I think of it but don’t say it ♫
♫ Even the input method doesn’t forget ♫
♫ How cruelly ask me to forget you? It’s you ♫
♫ The messages are organized over and over, but still not clean ♫
♫ The sceneries outside are stacked into shadows ♫
♫ Longing becomes an illness, the senses are numbed ♫
♫ Engraved in memory, every single drop ♫
♫ I overestimate myself to provoke you ♫
♫ I’ve used all my efforts to love in this life ♫
♫ Please let me be a fish in my next life ♫
♫ Always have a seven-second memory ♫
[Soundtrack]
"That’s What I Want, Getting Closer And Closer To You" by Ozone
"You Are Everywhere On My Mind" by Andrew Tan
"Still Remembers" by Andrew Tan