♫  All I want is you and me  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫  First close your eyes, and feel my breaths  ♫
♫  Not allowed to escape  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫ Hurry and listen carefully the sound of heartbeats ♫
♫ Just waiting for you to say okay ♫
♫ Tell me your secret ♫
♫ I just want you to stay ♫
♫ Experience with you ♫
♫ This and that feelings ♫
♫ Just come to me right now ♫
♫ I’m crazy, really can’t wait ♫
♫ No need to be that clear-headed ♫
♫ When I am with you ♫
♫ I am almost engulfed ♫
♫ You are beautiful as if you are not real ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫  First close your eyes, and feel my breaths  ♫
♫  Not allowed to escape  ♫
♫  That’s what I want, getting closer and closer to you ♫
♫ Hurry and listen carefully the sound of heartbeats ♫
♫ Just wait for you to say okay ♫
[HIStory 5: Love In The Future]
[Chapter 2]
My brain is cruel.
Why didn't it allow me to see the end of my dream?
Ho Bo-wei...
Are you an idiot?
Now it's already too late to think about a way to go back,
and you are thinking about kissing?
And with a guy!
Are you insane?
Sorry. The number you dialed does not exist.
Please check it and dial later. Thank you.
This number has not—
Grandma doesn't live there now.
How would she keep her number?
[Super Massage Chair]
Grandma. Leave it to me.
Leave it to me.
I'll massage you when we get home.
It's okay.
It's been a long day for you, too.
I insist.
How about I give you a massage first, and you massage me after?
Sure.
You give me a massage first, and I massage you after.
No.
I've got to find a way back.
Hi, Sam.
Check someone's background for me.
Dai Zhe-ni.
"Dai" as in wear, "Zhe" as in philosophy, "Ni" as in Nietzsche.
Okay.
My head is throbbing.
If I drink two bottles of wine in one go,
maybe I can go back after I wake up.
It was a really bad idea.
[Hai Yi]
- How are you doing?
- Great.
- Is everything okay?
Amazing. Brilliant.
It's good to know you didn't mess up the place.
Come on. I am perfectly aware of the situation.
You got me a place to stay. I surely will cherish everything here.
I'll get straight to the point. I sent you some information about Lu Si-chi.
- Take a took.
- Okay.
The only child of Luquan Group. 26 years old.
Master of Arts in Communication. The University of Chicago.
An advanced degree! She's highly educated!
Come on.
She is a candidate for my future wife.
Of course she has to have some prerequisite skills.
Wait. I can find the same information online, too.
How am I supposed to approach her with only this information?
What else would you like to know?
What's her favorite food?
Does it even matter? Wagyu beef.
Wait. She likes Taiwanese abalone too.
Right. Next question.
What's her favorite alcohol?
I love whiskey.
All girls like... red wine.
You are her boyfriend.
How could you not know her favorite drink?
Never mind.
Next question. What's her favorite perfume brand?
I know this one. It's Chanel.
Because I bought her one.
You bought her one. Does she have to like it?
Does she use it?
Hai Yi. She's someone that you are desperate to see.
However, it seems like you don't even know her well.
- Are you sure she's the one?
- Hey!
Dai Zhe-ni, I'm technically your boss. Mind your attitude.
Just go find her!
I see. I'll definitely find her,
but I need to do some more research about her.
I don't care how you make it happen. I only care about the result.
All right. I'll make it happen as soon as I can.
About the fee...
Don't worry about the fee, but you have a week to find her.
No problem. One week.
- Please pay me in cash.
- In cash? No problem.
If you can't find her in a week, you have to pay me double as a penalty.
Deal.
Brilliant.
I'll be back to 2000 in less than a week.
The penalty will be none of my business.
I'm not an idiot. Don't take advantage of me.
Brother Fu-de. I'm Dai Zhe-ni.
Thanks for the help. I couldn't find you here anymore.
I just wanted to tell you that I have a place to live now. I hope you can come and stay with me.
Please contact me after you see this note.
[Poseidon Department Store]
- Hello, Managing Director.
- Good morning, Managing Director.
Good morning, Managing Director.
I'm sorry, but you'll need to take the next elevator
- All right.
- Wait.
Get in here, Lin Huai-en. I need to talk to you.
The person who came in last, please get out.
I'm sorry.
[Measures to Prevent the Pandemic]
Managing Director.
You said you needed to talk to me, right?
I did.
I just simply wanted to let you in the elevator.
You stood in front of everyone. Why did you let them go in first?
Don't ever do that again.
I see. Thank you, Managing Director.
He seems to enjoy listening to music.
I wonder what he's listening to.
The door is closing.
Come in.
Managing Director, are you looking for me?
Yes. Have you eaten breakfast?
Perfect.
A very popular breakfast restaurant wants to open a branch in Poseidon Department Store.
I need someone young to try their food.
Sure. No problem.
Come and eat up.
Right here?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Darn it. Why do they always bully me?
Darn it.
Why do they always bully me?
Darn it. Why? Why?
I hate them all.
They all bully me.
Oh.
You like to talk to a tree hole too. Just like me.
I'll give you some advice.
Instead of getting angry alone...
make yourself stronger...
so that no one will bully you again.
Because that's how I grew up.
Thank you, Big Brother.
Good luck. You will grow up nicely.
All this money is mine.
It seems like Hai Yi is a rich guy.
[Hai Yi]
What a good show!
After 22 years, the world has become this.
Too bad I still can't find any information about my grandma.
We are not celebrities, after all.
The internet was not common back then.
It's okay.
I'm going to take this knowledge back to 2000.
[The Inventor of Communication Softwares in 2000]
As long as I get this knowledge back to 2000,
I'll be rich overnight!
I have to remember all these social media softwares.
[Queen's Shopping Season]
♫ If this is a dream, I really don’t want to wake up ♫
♫ If you are scared, do you want to hold my hand? ♫
♫ Let me help you absorb all the troubles ♫
♫ Sometimes you think too much ♫
♫ Sometimes I want to escape with you ♫
♫ I want to give you happiness when you are with me ♫
♫ What happen between us can’t be hidden anymore ♫
I am hired to do a job.
Time to work.
Lin Huai-en, why don't you go and have lunch?
I'm not hungry, Manager.
Have a seat. Let's have a quick chat.
What happened, Manager?
Nothing.
This morning, Director Liang asked you to go to his office.
Yes. Managing Director treated me to a lavish breakfast.
I'm still very full.
Managing Director treated you to breakfast?
Not really.
He said a popular breakfast restaurant
wants to open in our department store.
He asked me to try out their food,
because he needed advice from someone young.
I see. Nice.
No popular breakfast restaurant is wanting to open in our store.
Did Sen Sen ask me to hire you because he likes you?
You seem harmless,
but in fact, you are vicious.
Manager, what's wrong?
Nothing. By the way,
we are about to launch the brochure for the anniversary sale.
Who should I leave the task to?
I'll do it. I haven't done it before.
But you don't have much experience.
Manager. I can do it. Don't worry.
Okay. Go now.
I'll text you the address of the printing factory.
Call me whenever you have a question.
Okay. Thank you for giving me this opportunity.
Bye, Manager.
I will keep you away from the office as much as possible,
so you won't have a chance to approach "my" Sen Sen.
[JJ and Lu Si-chi are friends now.]
She's sure is from a rich family.
No wonder Hai Yi was dumped.
Here's some fruit for you.
You should start to find her, shouldn't you?
I have started.
I know everything about Lu Si-chi now.
- However...
- "However"?
However, if I don't disguise myself as a rich guy,
I won't be able to reach those who are close to her.
So?
So I need you to be my fairy godfather.
You want more money.
I need money for the disguise.
Let me tell you something. Money can't buy true love.
But without money, true love will be extinguished.
Okay.
Buy whatever you need. I'll reimburse you.
Nice. I don't normally raise my rate in vain.
You know what? Take it as an investment.
- For what?
- For our business.
You see, with the experience of finding Lu Si-chi,
we can start a detective agency together,
helping others to solve their problems.
You're overthinking. Do I need to buy a cow when I want to drink a cup of milk?
No, no, no.
I'm very sensitive to any potential chance to make money.
Trust me.
If you can find Lu Si-chi, you can start any foundation or corporation.
No. No need to be that complicated.
You'll be Chairman. I'll be the *CEO.
(*chief executive officer)
We'll be business partners.
Whatever. Do as you wish.
The vendor expects to see the sales report tomorrow. I'll leave it to you.
Huai-en, it's my three-month anniversary with my boyfriend today.
I need to submit the monthly report tomorrow. I'll leave it to you.
♫ Day by day, I suddenly discover ♫
♫ That strong but invisible line ♫
♫ Lost in time ♫
♫ Foolishly unclear, pretends to be cool and loves to be jealous ♫
♫ Then I discover the unbelievable change  ♫
♫ I like to have you by my side ♫
Thanks for the sponsorship, Poseidon Department Store.
Here's the first song I composed. I hope you like it.
I hope it cheers you up.
I'm going to university next year.
I'm one step closer to working at Poseidon Department Store.
I'll do my best.
I'm waiting for you, right here.
Managing Director?
Why are you still at the office?
I should be asking you that.
It's late. Why are you still at the office?
I'm still working.
Are you covering for someone else again?
Since you don't know how to reject them,
you have to be responsible for all these jobs now.
Yes. I will make sure I get them done.
Thank you, Managing Director. Bye, Managing Director.
I didn't say I'm leaving.
Two people working together will be faster.
Money can't buy true love.
But without money, true love will be extinguished.
- I vote for the pink one.
- What about the black one?
- No.
- The black one is a limited edition.
You can only pick one.
- I want both.
- Sorry, Sir.
Your card has been declined.
What?
That's impossible. Okay. Try this one.
Okay. Thank you.
The card machine must be broken.
Have you made up your mind?
- Still both of them?
- Sorry, Sir.
This one has been declined too.
What?
What's wrong?
I dreamed of my deceased grandma last night.
She said we are not suitable for each other.
Let's break up.
What?
I'll get this bill.
Lu Si-chi, what do you mean?
Hello.
Hai Yi. She's someone that you are desperate to see.
However, it seems like you don't even know her well.
Are you sure that she's the one?
There's no love between me and Lu Si-chi.
I didn't expect it but although Dai Zhe-ni is young, he sees it clearly.
It's been a while.
- It's been a while.
- Happy Birthday, Peter.
- Thank you, Shan.
- Happy Birthday.
Shan.
Hi.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Hey, Peter.
- You are...
- I'm JJ.
Don't you remember me?
JJ. Hello.
- Happy Birthday.
- Thank you.
I've invited many friends today. Just help yourself.
Sure.
Jen, you are even more beautiful now.
May, let's grab some drinks later.
I don't know who he is.
- Let's play a game.
- Sure.
Guys, this way.
Let's go.
Ladies and gentlemen, come over here!
Here comes the climax of the night.
Come on. Follow me,
Yeah!
Hi, gorgeous. Even though you are sitting in the corner,
to me, you are the star in the room.
I'm allergic to red wine.
- Are you tired?
- Why's that?
Because you've been running around in my head for a while.
You must have a small brain. It only takes me two steps to finish walking.
Peter.
Si-chi.
I've memorized so many pick up lines nowadays, but they didn't work.
- Your turn.
- Bet NT$20 (US$0.66).
All right. I'll do it.
More...
Hai Yi told me that she likes red wine.
[Poseidon Department Store]
Come in.
Managing Director, are you looking for me?
Yes.
Would you like me to try those pork chops?
I don't want you to try them. I would like you to eat them.
Come on. Join me for lunch.
I don't think it's appropriate.
The colleagues may start gossiping.
I don't mind it, but to you—
This is not what you should worry about.
Cut the pork into small pieces and feed me.
Why didn't you reject me?
If you don't reject me, I assume that you agreed.
See? You should reject something unreasonable.
Oh, that's what you meant.
Otherwise, what do you think I'm saying?
Lin Huai-en, I know you are kind-hearted,
but you can't only be kind.
If you never reject them, they will assume you don't have boundaries.
I see. Thank you,Managing Director. I'll keep it in mind.
Eat up now. The food is cold.
All right.
I'm Ms. Lu's boyfriend. Leave it to me.
Who are you?
I'm your Facebook friend, JJ.
Don't you remember me? We just met each other at Peter's birthday party.
I don't care if you are JJ or YY. I don't know you!
I'm not interested in knowing you.
Excuse me. What are you guys doing? Why did you let a random person in?
I'm so sorry. Sir, you need to leave.
Don't say that. We can be friends.
Sir, you need to leave.
Keep laughing.
- Just keep laughing!
- My stomach hurts.
I felt ridiculous when your ex-girlfriend ignored me like that.
To be honest, I... I've never seen her like that.
We should never judge someone by appearance. She's such a snob!
Am I really an unobtrusive person?
I don't know about that, but you certainly spent quite a lot on your disguise.
I'll deduct the cost from your salary.
I did my best!
That Lu Si-chi has set her standard too high,
and I am not really a rich guy.
Those who have capability find solutions. Those who don't find excuses.
What about you? She dumped you with such a ridiculous excuse.
You must have run out of money, right?
I... It's none of your business.
You didn't get your job done. It's fair for me to cut your salary.
How could he leave? We haven't finished talking.
Can you be that arrogant when you're rich?
[NT$95,500 (US$3,150)]
No way. It's not a good deal.
I've got to find a way back, before I lose too much money.
It didn't work at the place where I woke up.
Let's try it where I have an accident.
All packed and ready.
These are going to make me rich after I go back to 2000.
Without Hai Yi,
I wouldn't have had money and these things.
But I'm leaving without finishing my job.
Will Hai Yi miss me when I'm gone?
I hope he understands after he reads my messages.
It doesn't matter. My grandma is unwell, and I need to take care of her.
Dai Zhe-ni.
Brother Fu-de. What are you doing here?
I'm surprised to see you here, too. Right?
I dropped my gourd bottle off the bridge.
I can't find it. Would you help me?
A gourd bottle?
Jump. It's your chance to go back to 2000.
Wait. Sir, please don't do something stupid!
Let go. It's none of your business.
Brother Fu-de, tell him to let go.
Whatever has happened, please don't commit suicide.
You don't get it. Let go of me.
I get it. There is hope as long as you are living.
Dai Zhe-ni?
Lin Huai-en?
It's the third time we've met today.
I think we're friends now.
You can talk to me if you need help.
I will try my best to help you.
I don't think anyone can help me with this.
How do you know without telling me?
If you realized that you were in a different world
when you woke up one day,
what would you do?
Are you talking about a game,
or is it a movie?
Right.
It would be nice if it was a game,
because there would be a second chance.
I don't know what exactly has happened to you,
but you need to take care of your grandma, right?
Please don't kill yourself.
Can I add you on LINE?
You can talk to me whenever you feel upset.
[Grand Crystal Hotel]
Daddy. Daddy.
I'm leaving.
Daddy!
I'm leaving. I am leaving.
Daddy, Daddy.
I'm leaving.
[Message from Dai Zhe-ni]
"Very quietly I take my leave,"
(*from the Chinese poem, "Saying Goodbye to Cambridge Again")
"as quietly as I came here."
Hai Yi, it was nice to meet you.
Thank you. I'm leaving.
- Hello.
- What did you mean by those messages?
Nothing.
I wondered if you remembered that poem, "Saying Goodbye to Cambridge Again".
What bridge? Are you crazy?
You're the one who is crazy.
Why aren't you sleeping in the middle of the night? Are you checking on me?
Yes. I am checking if you are messing around with some girl.
What girl? You are out of your mind.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I don't have time for that. I don't even have enough time to make money.
What if you had time?
Why do you ask this all of a sudden?
Nothing. I can't sleep. I was just chatting.
If I had time...
I would have to meet someone I liked first.
What's your type?
I...
I'm going to sleep now. Don't stay up too late.
He even called me.
He must care so much about my messages.
No matter what, he has helped me a lot.
I have to finish my job before I go back to 2000.
Where is my mobile phone?
Where did I leave it?
Gosh.
If I have to buy a new phone, I'll need to *eat dirt this month.
(*no money left for food)
After I bumped into Dai Zhe-ni yesterday,
I went back to the office to work overtime.
Right. I must have left it at the office.
Lin Huai-en.
Managing Director, why are you here?
- Is this yours?
- Yes.
Why is my phone with you?
You left it in the pantry room.
I decided to bring it to you in case you needed it urgently.
Wonderful. Thank you, Managing Director.
Thank you.
Let's go. I'll drive you to work.
Okay.
Seat belt.
Be gentle.
Thank you.
It's only been a few minutes, and you've already thanked me a few times.
Is this still working?
♫ Please don’t appear in my dream ♫
♫ I just want to think that you’ve never come ♫
♫ You have been torturing me in my mind ♫
♫ Make me impulsive and make me fall ♫
♫ If I understand I shouldn’t have all these ♫
♫ I shouldn’t have held your hand ♫
♫ Like the breeze blowing lightly ♫
♫ From now on, all the pain and love don’t remain ♫
♫ If you are just a passerby, tell me first ♫
♫ Don’t make me wait with expectation ♫
♫ Love is a struggle, I am getting puzzled and puzzled ♫
♫ My emotion is out of control, like the withered flower ♫
♫ The falling leaves, are they lonely too? ♫
♫ They are on the ground for so long and no one picks them up ♫
Hi. We finally meet in person,
CEO.
I don't think I've ever allowed you to stare at me unscrupulously like that.
Why are you out here?
It's because quarantine is over, of course. Bring my luggage in.
How is it going? Have you got used to your new job?
I have. My colleagues are nice to me now.
Really?
Yes.
I see. If you encounter anything you don't know how to reject, just message me.
Sure. Thank you, Managing Director.
Did I just thank you again?
Have you eaten?
Not yet. I was desperate to find my phone and left the house right away.
I knew it. Remember to grab something to eat later.
Managing Director. Would you drop me off in front of that convenience store?
Why? Do you need to buy something?
Not really. I would like to get out of the car earlier
in case my colleagues see me and cause you trouble.
All right.
See you at the office.
See you. Thank you, Managing Director.
He's way too cute!
It's late. Why are you still here? Are you going to sleep on the couch with me?
What? Can I not?
Of course, you can. This warehouse belongs to your friend.
Don't you need to go home?
No. No one expects me to go home anyway.
Why do you have so many questions? Should I give you a report?
No. You're my boss. You can do whatever you like.
What's that smell?
Stinky tofu? Is it smelly? I'll go and shower then.
It's all right.
What's your plan about Lu Si-chi?
You are not in quarantine anymore. Just go and see her in person.
I can't.
Why not?
It's none of your business. Just do it for me.
I was very confident indeed.
After I talked to her a few times, I realized that she's totally unapproachable
unless you have a rich-family background.
Pretend that you are this rich guy and try to talk to her.
Is he famous enough? What do I need to wear?
Nice outfit! I'm going to try this on.
Stop staring at me. Turn around.
I was not looking at you. I was looking at the outfit.
All right.
What do you think? Is it nice?
It's thundering!
♫ The falling rain has bad intentions ♫
♫ Completely leaving no room ♫
♫ Abruptly reminding me of the past ♫
♫ The rain sounds are foreshadowing  ♫
♫ Constantly reminding ♫
♫ Describing how powerless I am ♫
♫ Just don’t be depressed, don’t be submissive  ♫
♫ Be courageous, but the memories fail me  ♫
♫ When mentioning you, I become powerless ♫
♫ That word and sentence, I think of it but don’t say it  ♫
♫ Even the input method doesn’t forget ♫
♫ How cruelly ask me to forget you? It’s you  ♫
♫ The messages are organized over and over, but still not clean ♫
♫ The sceneries outside are stacked into shadows ♫
♫ Longing becomes an illness, the senses are numbed ♫
♫ Engraved in memory, every single drop ♫
♫ I overestimate myself to provoke you ♫
♫ I’ve used all my efforts to love in this life ♫
♫ Please let me be a fish in my next life ♫
♫ Always have a seven-second memory ♫
[Soundtrack]
"That’s What I Want, Getting Closer And Closer To You" by Ozone
"If You Are Just A Passerby, Don't Stay For Me" by Diiton
"Still Remembers" by Andrew Tan