Wanna stop by the store?
- I know it's cold, but ice cream would...
- Ouji.
I want to have sex with you.
Erm...
Oreo.
Come here, boy!
Sorry to bother.
- It's fine.
- No worries.
Let's just get home, yeah?
Okay. Yeah.
Dragging me by the arm?
Can it be? Can I expect something tonight?
Should we open a bottle?
- What's up?
- How do you make tea?
Tea?
First, you have to brew the water.
Right. The water.
Tea?
Am I... being rejected right now?
Listen.
I was equally as happy, you know?
To hug you and all.
I just felt awkward saying it.
The thing is...
I actually love you, Haru.
I know we married on the fly,
and got the order all wrong, but...
Haru?
I'm so relieved.
I feel so happy right now.
I...
I've been waiting to hear those words...
All this time.
Ouji, I...
I love you, too.
I'm sorry.
[Episode 5]
[Heading out to a meeting]
Their mini album will be released
after the concert.
We'll decide the number of songs
at a later date.
As for next year's agenda...
Marriage ain't so easy after all, right?
Huh?
At least, that's what your face is saying.
What's that supposed to mean?
Quit making assumptions.
On the brink of a divorce
after you were caught cheating?
Hell no.
Yeah, I don't think that's it.
Ouji's changed ever since he married Haru.
It's like he's mellowed out.
That'll help improve our image.
Right? Coincidence or not, I'll take it.
Haru's got a compelling power like that.
I know.
Huh, you're actually serious about her.
I said, quit making assumptions.
We have to. You won't tell us a thing,
even after two decades of playing together.
Then you two know Haru as well as I do.
You're asking about our thoughts on Haru?
Well, I remember she'd wait for us
after shows and before recordings.
She was a groupie, or practically a stalk...
Haru isn't...
She isn't like that.
We're considering solo activities as well.
And you, Tanaka?
Ouji.
I think that individual
works for a tabloid magazine.
I've seen them around before.
Seriously? What a pain.
Guess the party's over.
Hamburger steaks, huh? My favorite.
Holy cow, that's good.
Let's just get married.
WHAT?
That hurts... Why?
Wait, this is real?
Of course it's real.
Hey, no more crying, okay?
Ow, ouch.
Welcome back!
I'm home.
Good night! Sweet dreams!
I do actually love her.
Your expression says otherwise.
- Huh?
- Yeah, why the dissatisfied look?
I'm not dissatisfied, it's just...
I love her.
Which is exactly why it's not so simple.
Ouji. I think you're overthinking it.
This is your first crush,
and your first marriage.
Of course you're confused.
- Well...
- If you love her, take it a step at a time.
If only I could.
What, so you just wanted to brag?
Man, I want to get married, too.
Your first step is to quit four-timing.
[Keiko Kotani]
I'm serious about all of them!
[Can we meet later today?]
Trash. You utter scumbag.
- Haru, are you hungry?
- Huh?
Was my stomach growling?
No, but there's a taco rice truck out front.
How about it?
Sorry, but I'm grabbing lunch
with some friends today.
Ah, I see.
I'm free to grab a quick coffee, though.
I finished writing my draft early today.
Inspiration's flowing?
Yeah. I overcame a hurdle of some sort.
Oh? That's good to hear.
Should we get going?
No, let's shelve it for another day.
I'd rather try it out with you.
If you insist.
Didn't realize you were
such a fan of taco rice.
You could say that.
Wow.
[Ouji]
Sorry, I'll be late tonight.
Haru. It's a bit creepy seeing you
grinning in the streets like that.
Roger!
- Fuyumi!
- There you are!
Thanks for waiting.
Drinking while the sun's still up?
Yup. I already finished work for the day.
Wait, that can't be the only reason
you're beaming.
Haru, you haven't told her yet?
I thought she'd be a bit exasperated,
hearing me gloat.
Already am.
Thought so.
Okay, here me out.
- A hug...
- A confession...
And then another hug?
Yup.
Cheers!
Your drink must taste all the sweeter, Haru.
Such pure love at your age... Savor it!
Thank you two for always listening.
Then I bet you're raring to go home tonight?
No, Ouji says work is keeping him late today.
Gosh, I'm a bit miffed after all!
I know we did things in the wrong order.
But now that we've reaffirmed our feelings,
I feel absolutely fulfilled.
I suppose order doesn't matter after all.
Sure, he still lacks a sex drive.
But it doesn't seem like
such an obstacle anymore.
We'll overcome that wall, together.
You're grinning wide. Cute!
I'm sure Akina's thinking love is pointless
without the sex, though.
No, I think it's a wonderful development.
- What?
- If you're certain he loves you,
then maybe you can hold off on sex after all.
Huh? Who are you?
What did you to do our Akina?
Let's just say I met someone
who changed my mind.
What?
- A platonic love?
- Wow...
I didn't realize platonic feelings
were contagious.
No, I don't feel a platonic love for him.
And we've done everything but go all the way.
- Erotic as that may sound.
- Woah.
Anyway, I sort of understand how you felt
when you first met Ouji.
Let us both enjoy our time together.
He made me think, "he's the one"...
Type of relationship be damned.
I see.
To think even Akina would find someone.
So what's he like?
Is he a foreign dude?
His face sort of looks like it.
He kinda gives "K-pop idol" vibes...
No, a boxer.
You're confusing us.
More importantly,
his mannerisms are to die for!
He's usually the courteous type, except...
What's the matter, Akina?
I hate being the only one who's feeling it.
I want to make you feel good, too.
- Huh?
- We're allowed to go halfway, right?
I'm confident in my skills.
I'd be tempted to stay,
so that'll have to be a "nope" from me.
What? What is it?
Give us an example.
He'll drop the courtesy, without warning.
Why is that so effective?
I get it!
You do, Fuyumi?
I love getting a glimpse
of their true colors.
- It makes my heart squeeze!
- I'm the opposite.
I love the professionalism
of keeping an appropriate distance.
"Professionalism"?
- It's just an example.
- Nicknames are great, too.
Going from "hey you",
to a cute nickname? It's the best!
Sounds like a player. Sorry, can't relate.
Don't get rational on me now.
Going from "Ms." to first name basis
is what gets me.
Name-calling in bed is pretty great, too.
Our preferences are all over the place,
but we're ultimately charmed
by these people, huh?
Personally, I'm fulfilled
just hearing your stories.
Do our stories entertain you?
Yes, they're almost too stimulating.
Jeez...
[An article next week will report a scandal]
[between a stage play actor and our staff]
What happened?
Fuyumi?
[Apparently, his partner's a makeup artist]
[An article next week will report a scandal]
[between a stage play actor and our staff]
Is everything okay?
Someone at the elementary school
was afflicted with food poisoning.
I-I'm sure Chizuka is fine, but...
I'm sorry. I need to go hear the details.
- Okay.
- Don't worry about paying.
- Hurry.
- Sorry, thank you.
Take care!
[Shota]
[Please give me a call]
[Have you heard?]
[About the article]
I shouldn't leave any evidence.
No, it's too late now.
[Delete message]
[Shota]
Shota?
Fuyumi...
Did you hear the news? About the article.
I did. An affair. Could it be...
I wonder how we were found out.
What?
We always met at my place, right?
We never went in at the same time, too.
And I made sure to keep
an appropriate distance at work.
- That might be it.
- Huh?
We may have acted too close.
What should I do?
I'm sorry.
Shota, I...
I'm so sorry.
Don't apologize, Fuyumi.
I'm the one who fell for you first.
But I'm the adult. I work backstage.
No more of that, okay?
I want you to see me as your equal.
If the article is published,
I'll say I insisted on pursuing something.
Tell them you couldn't turn me down.
Why would you...
Because I want to protect you.
Though I may be younger,
I'm a man, first and foremost.
My manager's calling.
I'll text again if I learn something new.
Okay.
I'm sorry I got worked up.
Chizuka was fine, as are the other kids.
Thank goodness.
Seriously, she looked so worried
when she left.
She really is a mother, isn't she?
She sure is.
Alright. Now that we know Chizuka's okay,
how about we go for karaoke?
I've had enough secondhand happiness
for the day.
Besides, I have plans.
But I still have lots to share...
Wait, is it a date?
With Mr. Eros?
You could say that.
You're poking fun at me like an old man.
If we've got extra time afterwards,
care to join me for a drink?
Sounds good. But will we have extra time?
So long as I don't feel too good.
Then it seems we'll have no time after all.
Confident, isn't he?
Huh?
[Heading out to a meeting]
Welcome home!
Ouji?
What's wrong?
Haru.
I'm sorry.
- Ouji?
- Let's break up.
[Preview]