Something's wrong.
The parts have been replaced.
What?
There is wear on the surface,
and signs of intentional damage.
It was done very cleanly.
No wonder you insisted on inspecting the car again.
It's truly hard to guard against an inside job.
Hello?
Hello.
Is this Mr. Bai Tianyu?
I'm a representative from Haojie Finance.
Your brother, Liu Yaqi,
borrowed 30,000 yuan on our platform.
It is three days overdue.
When will you settle this?
Okay, I got it.
Where are you going?
Stop right there.
It seems you know you did something wrong, right?
Let go. I didn't do anything.
Where are the parts?
Put them all back.
What's going on here?
I don't know what you're talking about. I have things to do.
If you leave today,
don't ever come back.
Don't think that just because you stole the parts from Mr. Dong's car,
no one will know.
No way.
They actually swap parts.
Could it be a shady shop?
This is too much.
Little girl, don't talk nonsense in public.
How am I talking nonsense?
Um.
I...
Did I hear that right?
Was she just talking about my car?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
I happened to be passing by and wanted to pick up my car.
Your car...
You probably can't pick it up today.
Why?
Then...
So what she said is true.
My car just needed an oil change.
I am the owner.
You changed the parts without my permission.
Do you know what kind of car that is?
Can you afford to pay for it?
What kind of behavior is this?
It's a violation, illegal,
and theft!
Let me tell you.
As long as I, Dong Dawei, am in Lucheng,
your shop won't survive here.
Got it?
He is also a victim.
Why are you only mad at him?
Alright, stop talking.
Fine, let's not argue.
Let's go.
Take me to see the car.
I will never go to his place to fix my car again.
Yes.
Tianyu, listen to me, let me explain.
I really didn't mean to do it.
I just did it because I...
Why did you bring up Yaqi changing parts
in front of so many people?
If I hadn't refunded them and fixed the car again,
do you know how serious the consequences would be?
But I really just wanted to defend you,
so I did that.
I don't need it.
Then,
just consider me being a busybody, okay?
Forget it.
Brother Meng.
Um,
can you lend me some money?
I'm a bit tight on cash lately.
You'll have to find another way.
It's fine.
Let's keep in touch.
Okay.
Tianyu has gone too far.
You can't be blamed for this.
You were just trying to protect him.
He's so inexplicable.
I can't explain it to you anyway.
Hello.
I'm Gao Chenyang from Lu University's Design Department.
I was just watching.
You're painting the outer wall of the animal shelter.
Can I join you?
Sure.
Why are you staring at me?
Is there something on my face?
No.
Junior sister, I was drawing a rabbit just now.
I think you're as cute as a rabbit.
I drew it based on your face.
Look at me.
What small animal do I look like?
Sorry.
I have no interest in observing you.
Who cares to observe you?
Thank you.
Junior sister,
if it's convenient for you,
could you leave me your contact info?
No need, senior.
What I mean is,
next time if I see stray animals,
I want to contact you right away.
Let's keep in touch.
Goodbye, senior.
Goodbye, junior sister.
He likes you.
Don't be ridiculous.
Otherwise, why didn't he observe me?
That's too much.
I have to talk to him when he gets back.
Yaqi.
Did you take out an online loan this time,
chase girls,
or go gambling?
Tell us yourself.
No.
I just invested in some stocks with friends
and accidentally lost money.
I didn't know how to tell you,
so I...
All day long,
it's either stocks
or lottery tickets.
Can't you learn from your brother
and work dependably?
Are you planning to be a good-for-nothing your whole life?
It's enough to have him in the shop.
I wanted to try other options.
That's why I...
What options?
What kind of option is this?
You don't learn the good things,
and instead learned to steal and sell parts?
If your brother hadn't told me,
did you ever consider the serious consequences?
Yes, I was wrong.
But is that woman totally faultless?
If it weren't for her,
would we have lost so much money
and so many customers?
If our store goes bankrupt one day,
it will be all because of that woman.
You're fighting me over a woman.
You're so gutless now
that you need a woman to take the blame, right?
If you don't learn a lesson now,
your life is ruined, you know?
You've taken all my benefits my whole life
and kept me under your thumb.
So what if I cause a little trouble?
Aren't you able to handle everything?
I just want to make you miserable.
I...
Really.
This kid.
Tianyu,
don't take it to heart.
If you like that girl,
go for it.
Don't let yourself regret it.
We are not in that kind of relationship, Dad.
Let me push you back to bed first.
I still have a car to repair.
Hurry up.
If you don't compensate us today, no one will have a good time.
No,
we already handled this compensation yesterday.
Besides,
we really can't give a refund.
I'm really sorry.
You can't give a refund? Is that it?
Go get the car out for me right now.
The whole street knows about this.
Who would dare to get their car repaired here?
Exactly. Yeah.
No, listen to me.
Give me my car right now.
Did you dismantle our parts
and sell them?
Yeah! Compensate us!
Give me my car.
You ruined my car.
No.
Refund our money.
Just listen to my explanation!
Listen to me explain.
I've repaired everything that needed fixing.
Do you expect me to take it all apart again for you?
We have no idea what parts you used.
What if they're illegal?
What nonsense are you talking about?
We just want to take our cars back.
What kind of place...
What are you doing?
...is this? What's going on here?
We just want our cars.
You can take your cars,
but we can't refund your money.
You can take them to any repair shop
for inspection.
If you can prove there's a problem with our work,
we'll compensate you tenfold.