Well, take whatever you like.
It's on me.
We just came in to get out of the rain.
Why buy flowers?
This is for you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I just felt coming into this shop
and not picking anything is awkward.
Here.
What's going on?
Are you allergic to pollen?
Why didn't you say so earlier?
I just found out myself.
Don't tell me
no man has ever given you flowers.
You...
I have always received gold bars.
Who is as stingy as you?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Donate 5%
to support animal protection.
Are you crazy?
This is Su Wan's project, right?
You're being ridiculous.
I just want to discuss it with you.
After all, it's not a bad thing, right?
Right, Dad?
Dad, talk to him.
I think it's good.
Everyone is responsible for helping stray animals.
Then I'll sign it.
You're a hopeless romantic.
Keep it a secret.
I can't.
I have a big mouth.
Beg me.
I'm so sorry.
I'm late. Sorry.
It's okay. Sit.
How did you know today is my birthday?
This is a surprise I prepared.
A surprise?
I made it myself.
You are so amazing.
You can race and repair cars.
And you even make cakes.
Have a taste.
This is so cute.
Is this little girl me?
Yes, it's you.
The candles are so pretty.
Make a wish.
Come on.
I hope we can be happy every day.
I hope he can spend many birthdays with me.
Happy birthday.
What I want to say is,
whether you are sad or happy in the future,
I will always be by your side.
Actually, to me,
as long as you are here,
every day is the happiest.
Oh, right.
And this.
What is this?
Su Wan, you caused such a big mess.
Come home right now.
What is it? Why the rush?
Sorry, Tianyu.
I have an emergency and have to go.
I'll take this with me.
Take the cake back and eat it.
I have an emergency. I have to go.
Then... Then...
Where are you going? Let me take you.
It's fine. No need.
I'll explain it to you later.
Big news! Big news!
Something big happened at our school.
Everyone,
Did you check the school forum?
Abusing animals under the guise of protecting them.
I heard the president of that animal association is named Su Wan.
This person is so inhumane.
People like this will get punished sooner or later.
We must kick her out of Lucheng University.
Get out here now, you involved party!
Su Wan.
It seems they adopted animals
for abusive experiments.
You said Sister Su Wan is the president of the Animal Association.
Could it be...
She wouldn't do such a thing.
But Sister Su Wan really has psychological issues.
And didn't she cause the death of...
Don't talk nonsense, little girl.
My sister is perfectly fine.
She likes animals so much.
Impossible, impossible.
But,
if others believe this is true,
what should we do?
There must be something wrong with this.
I will find evidence to prove Su Wan's innocence.
Doudou, wake up.
Don't scare me.
Doudou.
Dou...
Don't.
Su Wan,
the food is ready.
Come out and eat.
Su Wan,
can you come out?
come out.
How is it? Still not answering?
Don't be discouraged.
Dad, I'm going out.
Okay.
Su Wan is inside.
Su Wan.
Brother.
If I had known Su Wan would cause you so much trouble,
on her first day at the garage,
I would have kicked her out.
Brother.
Is it necessary to go this far for Su Wan?
It's one thing to neglect the store's business,
but you also spend money everywhere gathering information.
What are you after?
This matter,
you didn't do it, did you?
You suspect me?
It's fine if you favor Su Wan,
but don't slander my sister.
Give me your phone.
Brother.
Give it to me.
What is this?