[English subtitles are available]
I don't know what to do when I see Yang.
I think you should keep a distance.
It's my reason
when I say I couldn't stay with you.
I have a crush on you.
I like you too.
Someone like Phumjai.
He's a good man. You shouldn't hurt him.
Why do you keep pushing me to go to Tammy?
I told you I like you just to test you.
I wanted to see how loyal you were to Tammy.
I'll prove it to you.
Boss,
didn't Phumjai take only one day off?
Why didn't he come to work today?
He'll be here soon.
Boss,
the canned pineapple will expire next week.
What should we do? There's one box left.
One box?
Yes.
Where is Phumjai?
Phumjai took a day off yesterday.
Where did she go?
I don't know.
How could you not know?
My brother went missing
because of you.
He hasn't been home for two days.
I can't get in touch with him.
Isn't it because of you?
-What's going on? -I know.
Then tell me.
If you don't like me,
just tell me.
Tell me you don't have any feelings for me.
Why?
Why did you stop?
You want to test my feelings, right?
Fine.
I'll prove it to you.
I have no feelings for you.
Even now,
no matter how many times you kiss me,
I won't have feelings for you.
I understand.
The person you have reached is not available.
Please take care of the store.
Tell me if Phumjai calls.
Boss.
Boss, where are you going? Aren't you taking an umbrella?
Hey, Tammy, are you with Phumjai?
No.
What's wrong?
I don't know where Phumjai is. No one can reach him.
If Phumjai calls you, please tell me.
No matter how many times you kiss me,
I won't have feelings for you.
I understand.
Shit.
Did I sleep all day?
Yes, Tammy.
You finally picked up. Where have you been?
I was looking for you.
Really?
Where are you? What's wrong?
I got caught in the rain, so I'm not feeling well.
Hold on.
Phumjai, open the door for me.
Okay.
What did you buy?
Eat up and take your medicine.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
You had to do all this because of me.
Don't think like that.
Friends should help each other when they're in trouble.
Then why are you alone?
Well, I just want to be alone for a while.
I was caught in the rain,
I wanted to stay here for a night.
I didn't know I'd sleep for a whole day.
Tammy.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Well.
Have you ever dated Yang?
Did Yang tell you?
Actually, I didn't want to hide it from you.
But Yang begged me.
Also,
I thought it'd been so long.
Why didn't Yang ask you to tell me?
He probably
didn't want you to think I was bad.
Then
why did you break up at that time?
There were many reasons.
But mainly,
I had many pursuers.
And Yang was busy.
And we quarreled a lot.
We had no choice but to break up.
In that case,
let me ask you.
Although I like you very much,
I don't love you that way.
I'm sorry, Tammy.
Actually,
it's good to be frank.
Also,
it's good to be loyal to yourself.
So,
we can still be friends, right?
Sure.
When you told me you like someone…
I like someone.
I've never had such feelings
for anyone.
Is that Yang?
How do you know?
Actually, I've been suspecting it for a long time.
But I didn't expect you to like Yang.
Only Yang has been so obvious about it.
What obvious?
That he likes you.
It's not true.
He doesn't like me.
Trust me.
I can't be wrong.
He has been so obvious.
Stop coming to Phumjai.
Don't hurt a good person.
And about the video,
how would you like to edit it?
I think it's good.
Okay.
I don't know where to find him.
Tammy.
I beg you.
If you can contact Phumjai, or if you know anything about him,
tell me.
Go get some rest.
I think the medicine is working.
Okay.
Hmm.
Get some rest.
Thank you.
Qi'er, Tag.
Where did Phumjai go?
Yeah, I don't know.
I hope nothing bad happens.
That's right.
I hope he'll be fine.
Bless him.
Okay.
-Boss, where are you going? -Please take care of the store.
Oh.
Boss.
Boss, aren't you bringing a raincoat?
Where is he rushing to?
Hello?
I found Phumjai. He's fine. I'll explain to you later.
Wait.
Oh.
Yang called and said he found Phumjai.
Then we can rest assured.
Yes.
But I'm still worried.
Is it Yang?
Hmm.
Why are you here?
Oh.
Wait.
Why did you get soaked?
Worry about yourself.
You don't have to wipe it for me.
Can you do it yourself?
We are all worried about you.
I almost called the police.
You're crazy. How's the shop?
Just
go back and look after the store.
Don't worry about the store.
Your business is more important
now.
Let me make some porridge for you
and I'll go back.
What's going on between you and Phumjai?
Since you like each other, why don't you talk about it?
Phumjai is a person who is loyal to his feelings.
During the day, he told me
he had a crush on someone.
Are you going to let it go?
You told me
if I knew anything about Phumjai, I should tell you.
So I have a request too.
Don't break his heart.
Be careful. It's hot.
Thank you.
I made you uncomfortable, did I?
Why would I?
I wasn't thinking about anything.
You told me
you had no feelings for me, didn't you?
I'm the one who made you uncomfortable.
I'll get going.
Call me if you need anything else.
Okay.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Yes.
Hey.
Hello. Hello.
How are you?
I'm fine.
You can speak Chinese so well now.
Tell us how you can learn it so well.
Because I have a good teacher.
Yes.
Only these?
Tag.
Yes?
What are you doing?
These foods are about to expire.
Brother Yang asked me to throw them away.
Oh.
Why not sell them at a discount?
Brother Yang.
Can we sell them at a discount?
How much should we lower the price?
How about
we give an 80% discount?
We can still get 20% of the original price.
If we throw them away, we get nothing.
Okay.
Let me help you.
How are you?
Give it to me.
Let me help you.
Phumjai.
How is it?
Did you catch a fever because you went on a date with Tammy?
Well...
Uh...
When Tammy is here, ask her yourself.
Oh, you have a girlfriend now.
Brother Yang, let me help you.
Oh.
This is heavy.
What's going on with you?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
Hello, welcome to Little Sun.
Tammy.
I told you that you don't have to come.
How can I not come? I want to know if you really recovered.
I bought donuts for you guys.
Hey, donuts!
Guys, have some donuts!
Thank you, Tammy.
It's so nice of you, Tammy.
-Thank you.
I'll start eating now.
And...
I'll start eating, too.
These donuts are good.
Brother Yang, have some donuts.
No, thanks.
I'm not hungry.
Try some. They're good.
Oh.
I'm glad you knocked on the door this time.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Do I look not okay?
So in the end,
what happened
between you and your partner?
Well...
Nothing happened.
Anyway,
he doesn't like me.
I know that now.
Are you sure?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm fine.
I feel good.
Phumjai.
Yes?
I'm your brother.
You think I can't tell?
You're not okay.
You can tell me
anything.
I promise I won't scold you.
You usually have no motivation?
I see you fool around with Bojji every day.
I have motivation every day.
But today I've got more of it
because you trust me.
Wish the business of Little Sun will thrive.
Wish Brother Yang can be my partner forever.
[Wish the business of Little Sun will thrive]
Forever.
That day,
I was going to tell him that I would pick him.
Say it. Say you have no feelings for me at all.
No matter how many times you kiss me,
I still have no feelings for you.
How could he do that to me?
I didn't say anything.
I think
it would be better if I stay alone.
Because I'm always thinking about him.
When I'm around him...
It's okay.
I still have feelings for him.
Why?
Why did he reject me?
Why did he not have feelings for me?
What should I do?
Welcome to Little Sun.
Work hard. Go.
Okay.
Why are they so cheap?
Oh.
They're about to expire.
Phumjai.
I'm going to eat at the secret restaurant in the alley.
I heard the food there is delicious.
The food at this restaurant is really good.
Unfortunately,
not many people know it.
Maybe its owner thinks the quality of the food
might be lower if she serves too many customers.
How can that happen?
The restaurant is not run by her alone.
If it's too busy for them, they can get more people to help them.
Maybe it's for some personal reasons
and no one else can help.
Have you ever tried to tell others your problem
before you make a choice for them?
Here's your food.
Thank you.
Okay.
Sir, what would you like to order?
So delicious.
I want the same as his.
It's sold out. He got the last one.
Would you like to try something else?
We serve many foods. You can take a look at our menu.
Okay.
See?
Good food won't wait for you.
If you don't get it quickly, you'll starve.
Listen.
I talked to Phumjai.
I want him
to withdraw his shares in Little Sun.
But
don't worry.
I'll find you a new partner as soon as possible.
Have you decided what to order?
You've read this menu.
Do you want to see other menus?
Hey, munchkin.
What are you doing here?
Do you need me to do anything else for Phumjai?
What?
Phumjai is not in a relationship now.
But if you keep protecting him,
when will you admit that I'm your boyfriend?
Hey, munchkin.
What happened?
I just don't know what I am to you.
It's...
I feel you are just using me.
Hey, it's not like that, munchkin.
I feel you don't love me as much as I love you.
I'm tired of it.
Munchkin.
Don't say that.
Anyway, I didn't tell anyone about us.
Actually, this is good for both of us.
When we break up,
we don't need to tell anybody about it.
Munchkin.
We were not a real couple from the beginning.
When we break up, it's like nothing ever happened between us.
Don't say that, Munchkin.
Munchkin.
Munchkin. Munchkin.
Huh?
Brother Yang.
Can I talk to you?
What's up?
Well...
Phojai told you that I'm going to
withdraw my shares in the shop, right?
Well.
You know what happened
between me and Tammy.
It's over.
It really is.
I have no reason to continue to run the shop now.
But
don't worry.
Phojai will find you a new partner as soon as possible.
Then...
I'm going to pack up.
Good luck.
Phumjai.
If canned pineapples have expired, will you just throw them away?
What?
Tell me,
is our relationship
coming to an end?
If I'm no longer a shareholder of this shop,
our relationship will come to an end.
But you're still a shareholder.
Does that mean our relationship hasn't come to an end yet?
Well...
I'm a little confused.
But I'll say
you're right. It hasn't come to an end yet.
I'm sorry.
Please don't leave me.
What's the reason for me to stay?
You know what?
On the day when we went on a date like a couple,
I prayed to Buddha
that the business of our shop would thrive
and that you would be my partner forever.
When you disappeared,
I realized how important you were to me.
I want to be with you.
I want you to cook instant noodles for me.
I want you to knock on my door.
I want you to ask me to teach you Chinese.
I want to sit down and watch Tammy's live stream with you.
I want to look at you when we eat together in the evening.
I want to go on a real date with you.
I want to be with you when you're sick.
When everything is fine,
I want to be the one who will take care of you.
I want to call you
boss.
You know what?
This is the first time you've said so many words after I met you.
If you promise me that no matter it's good news
or bad news,
you'll tell me everything,
I will stay.
I promise you.
Then,
I'm not going anywhere.
Let me put my things away.
Thank you.
I should thank you, too.
I know you don't need to learn Chinese now.
But I want to teach you a sentence.
Let's
be a couple.
Does that mean
"Can you be my boyfriend?"
Yes.
You asked me
what I would do
if I met someone I like.
If...
What's going on, Brother Yang?
I
will do this.
Didn't you
give this necklace to Tammy?
This belongs to you.
How can I give it to someone else?
Something must be going on
between the two.
After we close the shop today, let's play baseball.
Okay.
Brother Yang.
If you don't pay me back one million today,
you'll have to work here
until you can pay off the debt.