[English subtitles are available]
Mr. Yang, have you found a Thai partner?
I don't know anyone here.
I want to learn Chinese. What can I do?
I can teach you
and make you feel you are born to learn Chinese.
Let go of me. I didn't do it.
If you want to be my fan,
you should have your own business.
How can I have my own business?
Can you help me find a partner or not?
There's someone who is interested.
Hey! Stop it.
You two, shake hands and start your business.
I hope your business will thrive.
Hey.
There are no customers now.
Teach me Chinese.
Yi (one).
Er (two).
San (three).
Si (four).
Stop.
Everyone knows these easy words.
Teach me some other words.
Lao Ban (boss).
It means a business owner or a boss.
That's all for today.
What?
That's it?
I hope you can remember this word first.
Lao Ban.
Because you
should call me Lao Ban.
No way.
I'm the Lao Ban.
I have more shares than you do.
So?
Wait, let me remind you.
According to the contract we signed,
-I hold 51% of the total shares.
-But you didn't invest money.
But I have more shares than you do.
Uh.
Welcome to Little Sun.
Yeah.
Where is the subway station?
Go straight,
and turn left. Then you'll see it.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Bye.
It's okay, guys.
Today, she only asked for directions.
But next time, she might come back and buy something.
You're right.
Smile, or the customers won't come.
[Love in Translation]
♫I don't understand why it has to be you♫
♫I used to be calm but you came and made me feel anxious♫
♫I don't want to see you♫
♫But you are making me feel anxious♫
♫I don't know♫
♫When my heart will tell me the answer♫
♫I know♫
♫My heart won't tell me any new answer♫
♫The most important is my feelings for you♫
♫Love can be expressed without words, what matters is that you know I love you♫
♫As long as you are with me, I don't need words of love as love is not a language♫
♫When we are staring at each other, we can be sure of each other's love♫
♫As long as we love each other♫
♫Love is not a language, by staring at each other, we can be sure of each other's love♫
♫As long as we love each other, we don't need others to explain our love♫
[Love in Translation]
Welcome to Little Sun.
-Hello, Mr. Rookie Businessman.
-Hello.
Odo!
I miss you!
I miss you.
Tag.
Hey.
Phumjai.
Who is she?
Oh, that's Qi'er. She works here.
So cute.
-Huh?
Nothing.
I just passed by, so I want to say hello to you and visit your shop.
What about you, Tag?
Why are you working here?
Me?
I just...
Have you seen anything weird?
No.
Yang seems to be a good guy.
Keep an eye on him.
I think he's suspicious.
Okay.
How about Phumjai?
Phumjai?
He's quite happy.
As long as a customer comes to our shop,
he'll be very happy for long.
But I think
if the shop goes on like this,
they won't be able to run the business for long.
-What should we do?
-Listen.
In the beginning, take photos of the shop and post them on social media.
Let people know what you are selling.
And promote a few selected products that sell well.
Munchkin.
Anyway, please help me take care of Phumjai.
Okay, I will.
Don't worry.
You're the sweetest.
Give me some energy.
Let's go.
He's my good friend.
He volunteered to take pictures to promote the shop.
Really?
Yes, I've got a new idea.
What is it?
We can select five or six products in our shop
and promote them. Do you think it'll work?
Hey.
Good idea.
Man, you're smart.
-Of course.
-You're smart.
You are not like Odo.
What?
Odo is not a real friend.
He's never helped me.
In the future,
I might come here often.
Hey.
We're here, bro!
Odo, I'm here!
Yeah, I mean...
How about I come to help you and be your partner?
That'll be too much. Is that necessary?
Of course it is.
You and your partner always fight.
Hey, this is good.
I'll take it now.
Hey.
-What's up?
-Let's have a meeting.
Okay.
Let's think about how we can increase our sales.
Where is Phumjai?
Phumjai?
Where is he?
I'll go find him.
Guys.
Hey!
What are you doing?
This is Tammy's display board.
I want to use it
to decorate our shop.
If her fans see it,
they'll immediately come to our shop and buy stuff.
What the heck are you thinking?
-It's useless.
-Stop!
What's wrong with you?
We can take photos of it and our shop
and use the photos to promote our shop online.
I told you. If we use the picture of Tammy to promote our shop,
our sales will definitely go up.
Don't fight.
Drag them apart.
Calm down, boss.
I think
we can try Phumjai's idea first.
It might work, right?
Yes, boss.
Let's give it a try.
Yes.
Calm down.
Okay.
We'll try his idea.
Tammy, are you okay?
Just now,
someone was trying to hurt you.
I'll always protect you.
Where should I put it?
This one?
Yes. Is it okay?
If it's a product recommended by Tammy,
we can put a picture of Tammy next to it.
These are all her favorites.
So I came up with this good sales plan
to promote some selected products
with the hashtag #TammyLikesIt.
I'm sure her fans will come to our shop to buy stuff.
You remember everything Tammy likes?
It seems that
you really like Tammy, right?
So,
when did you
start to be so crazy about her?
Tell us.
The thing between me and Tammy
happened three years ago.
That day, I was in a bad mood because I had a fight with my brother.
[Excuse me.]
[Is this Charoen Krung?]
She asked me for directions.
But I didn't really know Chinese.
[Charoen Krung.]
Talking with her was like talking with a mute.
[Yes.]
We also used several English words.
[It's very delicious.]
Good. Good. Good.
I quickly forgot about the fight with Phojai and offered to be her guide.
[Want to try some?]
Okay.
I want to go there.
[This way. This way.]
Okay.
[Thank you so much.]
[I couldn't make it without you.]
No one
had ever looked at me with that much appreciation.
And no one had praised me like that.
Food review.
[I love it.]
After the trip,
Tammy went back to China.
If you liked her that much, why didn't you keep in touch?
Well...
I was so excited. I forgot to ask for her contact info.
And then?
Then Tammy became a KOL in the next year.
I went to see her.
You know what?
It was because of that trip that Tammy wanted to learn Thai.
Oh.
She wants to visit Thailand again.
She's sweet.
Did she tell you that?
Or is it just your imagination?
Well, it's possible.
It's the same now. I get to talk to her by leaving her comments.
We
can communicate
-with each other again.
-What a surprise.
If she can speak Thai, why are you learning Chinese?
Why don't you talk with each other in Thai?
Because Tammy said a lot of people tried to chase her.
Those who can pass the first test
must be able to speak Chinese.
If Tammy agrees to talk to a person,
she will reply in English.
So if I want to chase her,
I have to learn Chinese first.
That makes sense.
Let's get back to work.
-Hey, guys.
-What's up?
What's up?
Tammy uploaded a short video with the hashtag #TammyLikesIt.
-Where?
-Here.
It's true.
She's so sweet.
Phumjai, give her a reply.
Right. Let me thank her first.
-Tell her.
-say "thank you" to her.
What language should I use?
Here.
Please type "Thank you" in Chinese.
I'm serious.
All right, guys. Our shop is going to be a popular one.
Alright.
We'll have a lot of customers.
Tammy likes it. Tammy likes it.
Hello.
Guys.
We've got an order.
What?
Go on.
What would you like to order?
The customer wants to buy all products
labeled #TammyLikesIt.
See? I told you. That's a great promotion plan.
Okay. Anything else?
The customer wants to pay a deposit
of five thousand baht.
Is it convenient for you to transfer the money now?
He said yes.
-Thank you.
We'll pack the products and deliver them to you as soon as possible.
Thank you.
-Bye.
Then,
go pack the products and deliver them.
Do we have enough time to deliver them today?
-Oh. right.
-Right.
Tag, let's pack the products.
Tammy likes it.
And this.
What else?
Are you looking for an assistant?
Oh, it's him.
It's late. Hurry up.
Tammy, you're outside for so long.
It's hot.
I brought you inside, so you feel cooler with the AC.
Oh.
But even if you were in the sun for so long, you still look pretty.
I need to thank you, Tammy. If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't be selling so well.
Thank you.
A customer wants them all.
What do you want to eat? I'll go...
[Piengjai Rawichotpitak]
This is the last box.
There's no more, honey.
Dad, Mom.
Oh.
Wow!
What did you order?
Aren't they from Little Sun?
Did Phumjai ask you to buy them?
Hey, it's not like that.
Oh.
Wait.
It's too late, honey.
Thank you, Tammy.
Hey.
Come here.
Phumjai.
Phojai, what's up?
Why did you ask Mom and Dad to buy from your shop?
What are you talking about?
Are you saying you don't know about it?
There are a lot of packages sent from your shop in our house.
Did Mom and Dad
order them all?
I...
I really don't know that the big order was from them.
Phumjai.
In the end, you still asked our parents for help, right?
You said you wouldn't ask your family for help.
Have you forgotten what you said?
Have you ever kept your word?
In your eyes,
I am such a bad brother, right?
Why have you never trusted me?
I hope
you won't be a bad influence on my brother.
My idea
didn't work.
I'm sorry.
Do you have plans after we close the shop?
Well...
No.
What would you like to eat?
Let's go eat together.
Okay.
I can help you with the marketing plan.
Why didn't you tell me about that?
I told you everything.
But I really don't know about that
Gosh.
Since the shop opened,
has my brother ever paid attention to his work?
Yes.
He paid attention to Tammy's livestreams.
Munchkin, I didn't mean that.
I mean, has my brother ever paid attention to running the shop?
Is he doing okay?
Are people in the shop nice to him?
Is his partner a good guy?
Alright.
Don't worry about it.
I'm helping you take care of him here.
Don't you
worry about me at all?
Huh?
I always worry about you, Munchkin.
Hey.
It's so good.
Is this
the food you like?
Yes.
Try it.
It's delicious.
No.
Open your mouth. Try some.
Hey.
Fine.
I'll try it
Open your mouth.
Please feed me properly, okay?
How is it? Is it good?
It's good, right?
It's been a stressful day.
Thank you for bringing me here.
I brought you here to talk about work.
Oh,
the marketing for the store, right?
Yes.
But...
before we talk about that,
there's one more thing.
In the future,
you
must call me brother.
What?
I'm older than you, you should call me elder brother.
What the heck?
If I call you brother,
what will you call me?
I'll call you "you".
What? It's not fair at all.
Hey.
If you call me brother,
I'll think about your marketing plan.
Really, Brother Yang?
Are you really going to?
Tell me what you're planning to do.
Let me tell you,
I'm full of ideas.
I want to promote the store so that everyone knows about it.
Through online channels, social media.
What are you babbling on about?
This is a global era.
The social media is getting bigger.
We must make our supermarket widely known.
In other words, we need to reach out to young people.
If our shop gets famous,
I'll be more motivated to work.
And you wouldn't be motivated otherwise?
I see you play with Bojji every day.
I'm motivated every day.
But today, I'm even more motivated because
you, Brother Yang, trust me.
Brother, you know,
since I was little,
my family has never trusted me.
They never trusted me to do anything.
When I was young,
my parents wouldn't even
let me ride a bike.
So I...
still don't know how to ride it to this day.
I'm someone
who doesn't know how to do anything.
Let me teach you.
You'll teach me how to ride a bike?
Give me your hand. Hold it. What are you afraid of?
Is what you just told me true?
Yes.
Slowly.
Okay.
Lift your legs up.
Don't be afraid of falling.
Keep your balance. Then lift your leg.
OK. Lift your legs.
Keep your legs up and turn right.
Right, right.
Go straight.
Hold tight.
Okay, hold tight.
Turn.
Slowly. Watch the road.
Watch the road.
Okay.
Turn around.
Ride properly.
To the left.
Ah, Brother Yang.
Brother Yang.
Are you okay?
Turn.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay.
Brother Yang.
I can ride now, Brother Yang. I can ride now!
Be careful.
I can ride now.
Great!
Ride faster.
Oh.
Hey.
Isn't it too fast?
Brother.
Ride well.
Hey.
- Brother Yang.
- Be careful!
- Brother Yang!
- Stop! Stop!
Are you okay?
I'm going back to the supermarket.
Don't stay out here until late.
You're not trying to ride to Lhasa,
understand?
Ride...
Bicycle.
Ride a trend.
I've got to tell Brother Yang now.
Brother Yang.
Brother, I got it.
When you teach me Chinese,
can't you just teach me pick up lines?
Yes.
I'll teach you later.
That's great.
Well, then...
Brother Yang, do you have a girlfriend?
No.
Why do you ask?
Oh.
I was hoping you could help me get girls.
Will this work?
Hey.
I'm hungry.
Do you want to eat something nice with me?
Spicy instant noodles?
Well...
You're off topic again.
Didn't I tell you to memorize the words and wait for me?
I'm just hungry, Brother Yang.
My stomach is growling.
I haven't eaten anything since I got off work.
If I'm hungry,
how can I memorize these words?
So many words.
Fine, I'll eat.
I'll have some too.
Okay. Two packets.
Here are your noodles.
Clean up the table. It's heavy.
This is yours.
This is mine.
Open it for me.
Hey.
Tammy is live.
Let me watch the livestream.
Hello, you're here again with Tammy,
the Chinese girl who loves Thailand.
You're here again with Tammy, the Chinese girl who loves Thailand.
Today is very special
because today I'm celebrating the fact that I've reached 300,000 subscribers.
I'm going to have a special show - 50 facts about Tammy. Yay!
Great!
Let's start with the first question.
The first question.
What color does Tammy like?
Blue!
What color do you like?
Green, Brother.
The second question is, which animal do I like more, dogs or cats?
I like...
Cats!
Dogs!
Did you guys get it right?
For the third question.
My favorite food
is Thai food.
But it can't be spicy.
She said she likes Thai food too.
But it has to be non-spicy.
But
everything I like is spicy.
Oh, there were 49 facts.
I haven't got the same answer to a single question.
We've come to the last one.
How is it? Are there many people who got it right?
The last question is
my favorite sport.
Brother Yang, listen carefully.
My favorite sport is...
Baseball.
Baseball...
Hey.
Don't tell me that she likes it.
No.
Tammy doesn't like it.
What?
But I...
I like it.
Brother Yang, do you like baseball too?
From what I heard,
You and Tammy have
nothing in common.
Can you keep it going?
It's okay.
Although the 50 facts didn't match,
there may be
a 51th fact
or a 52nd fact
or other questions that match.
Okay.
Come and learn Chinese.
I'm full.
Can you read this word for me? I don't know how to say it.
Do you remember the words you memorized last time?
Yes, Brother.
Hello.
How are you?
What about goodbye?
Hello bye.
Let's go.
Clean it up.
But the word
- But you haven't looked at this word...
- Hello bye.
I'm so proud.
Brother Yang!
Tammy replied me.
What should I reply?
Oh, Tammy.
Brother Yang, please help me reply Tammy.
Reply her!
Brother Yang!
Tammy replied me in English.
It means I've passed the first test.
Can I invite her to the supermarket?
Are you sure?
Yes.
Tell her for me.
If you get the chance, please come to my supermarket.
Like that.
[The cafe you recommended is awesome.]
Tammy, we can meet now.
Tammy.
Hello.
Qi'er, can I help you?
Oh.
Yes.
Tell me.
I can help you with everything.
In that case, can you
move further away from me?
It's uncomfortable.
Oh.
Your angry face is so cute.
No.
Please
keep it for when we're far away.
Keep it in your heart.
Dear customers,
please follow me.
Here, a whole shelf.
All these products are the ones with #TammyLikesIt.
Thank you.
I followed Tammy's livestream
- and saw a lot of comments on delicious food.
- Yes.
I saw the video of Tammy replying with a funny poster.
I wanted to try it too.
You have to try. You're in the right place.
All the products here sell very well.
It's almost sold out. Only one box left.
I want this.
Your "ride the trend" plan
is very effective.
Of course.
Our store's sales went up quickly.
What?
Don't just stand there.
Another new order?
Pack it up.
Okay.
You're still up?
Today,
you haven't taught me Chinese yet.
Oh.
Wait for me. I need to work.
Little things, when combined together,
can create something special.
Even though we don't like the same things in those 50 facts,
there may be
a 51th fact,
or a 52nd,
or other questions where we match.
Don't jump to conclusions.
If you really don't know,
don't think you can't do it.
If you haven't tried...
Well,
in the end,
how is it?
Hey.
When did I fall asleep?
If you're sleepy,
go sleep in your own room.
Come here.
I wrote this for you.
Go back and read it.
Thank you, Brother Yang.
Welcome to Little Sun.
Hello.
Tammy!
Phumjai.
[Director: Phadung Samajarn
Worawut Thanamatchaicharoen]
Tammy, do you remember,
we met three years ago.
Was that you?
Yang.
Brother Yang, Tammy said hi to me.
Brother Yang, do you think she's asking me out?
Obviously, she's talking to a lot of people.
I won't allow her to lie to Phumjai.
She may not be as good as you think.
As long as she didn't push me away,
I'm very happy.
This might be a good starting point, Brother Yang.
[Watch Love in Translation on the iQIYI app and iQ.com official website]