(Loading)
(Dungeon Pass)
(The Truth)
=The Truth 2026=
(All persons, backgrounds,
and descriptions are fictional)
(Settings and actions are setups)
(All photos and videos)
(are authorized)
(Safety measures were taken
during shooting. Don't try this at home)
(Parental supervision required
for underage viewers)
(Enter game)
(1996, An Residence)
We're going back to 2016.
Okay, come on.
Let's go.
All changed.
I don't know what kind of place
we're in right now.
Anyway,
their uniforms look really nice.
Exactly.
Yeah.
(Fancy uniforms)
Let's go.
Come on.
I'll take the rear.
I'll cover the back in the daytime.
(Housekeeping Supervisor, An Xiaoning)
(Housekeeper, An Xiaowen)
(Housekeeper, An Ke)
(Nanny, Jin Xiangyu)
(Security Guard, An Xiaoding)
(Personal Bodyguard, He Jiahuan)
Breakfast.
I made this for you this morning.
I'm the nanny.
Wait.
Are we allowed to eat
such a fancy breakfast?
Right.
Aren't we supposed
to serve someone today?
I'm security.
Shouldn't I go outside?
Where
are we? I want to know.
The An Residence in 2016.
Technically, it should be March 25.
But everything here
looks different from what we saw.
(Now)
What day is it?
What year are we in?
Butler!
Who are you to call the butler?
He's your boss.
You're just a security guard.
No.
You're just housekeeping.
He's a bodyguard.
You're a bodyguard?
I'm a personal bodyguard.
(Personal Bodyguard)
He's here.
The butler.
Wait.
Why do you look so old?
(Why has the butler aged?)
Didn't you all ask for leave?
Why are you back again?
These uniforms actually suit you all.
Our boss
had them custom-made for you.
What do you think?
They look good.
I think they're great.
Really great.
A little too fancy.
But what's the boss' surname?
The boss?
I'll tell you in a bit.
(Who exactly is the boss?)
Same place, different people.
Same place, different people?
I told you to leave this painful place.
But you insisted on coming back.
Didn't you?
Yeah. Wait.
What year is it now?
It's 2030 now.
2030?
What?
It's 2030 now.
2030?
We wrote 2016.
Why did we
travel to 2030?
Write 2016.
Right.
These are everyone's
staff medical reports.
Thank you.
Okay.
I forgot something.
I need to grab something.
Okay.
Let's check the medical reports.
Let's see.
(Tui City Medical Center
Physical Exam Summary)
Why did you read all of them?
What gives you the right?
He's the detective.
(My bad)
(Personal bodyguard and detective)
Okay. Let's
read our own reports.
Okay.
Patient: An Ke.
Age: 58.
(Patient: An Ke)
Findings.
The patient looks young,
but both arms
show frequent unconscious swinging.
(Unconsciously swinging)
According to the patient,
while swinging, he's sure he can hear
butterfly wings flapping.
An Xiaoning.
Age: 57.
Usually calm. Loves working out.
But she's obsessed with strawberries.
Dandong strawberries.
(Perfect local match)
I'm 60.
(Patient: Jin Xiangyu)
Often yells in her sleep,
"I want to be chairwoman!"
and scares people.
I'm 39, right?
(Patient: An Xiaowen Age: 39)
Exam shows
the patient looks super young.
(Trying not to smile)
I'm 37.
(Patient: An Xiaoding)
All indicators are excellent.
He easily switches into dance mode.
The more he moves, the better he looks.
He Jiahuan. 37. Male.
His mind and body are starting
to feel middle-aged and weak.
You're drained.
You're weak.
(Quickly takes two bites to recharge)
Based on Tui City's latest tech,
the Super CTT scan shows
the patients once inhaled
Red Bone Poison.
It has permanently
left dark red deposits on their bones.
I have them too.
We inhaled this stuff.
Red Bone Poison.
(All four inhaled Red Bone Poison)
I have An Yi's medical report here.
He's 79.
(Patient: An Yi Age: 79)
The exam year is 2030.
(Exam year: 2030)
(An Yi lived until 2030)
He's still around.
Still alive.
Not dead.
Exam shows
the patient is totally fine.
But the patient said
he'd inhaled Red Bone Poison before.
After checking,
the amount was small.
According to Tui City's latest
Super CTT scan,
whether before or after death,
it would never
leave red deposits on his bones.
Red Bone Poison.
After death, it leaves
dark red deposits on the bones.
An Yi.
Whether before or after death,
(An Yi, An Xiaowen, An Ke,
An Xiaoning, An Xiaoding)
it would never leave red
deposits on his bones
First, that body isn't An Yi.
And in 2030,
he had a medical report.
Right.
He was still alive.
It wasn't him.
Then whose body was it?
The victim was someone else.
(Current case recap)
(Victim: An Yi)
(The case keeps moving backward)
(Place of death: Unknown)
(Time: Mar. 24-25, 2016.
Exact time unknown)
(Cause of death: Unknown)
At that site,
only those four kids
would get marks after inhaling it.
(Permanently leaves dark red deposits)
There was only one bottle
of Red Bone Poison in the world.
That means
that body
belongs to one of those four kids.
So it's one of the four of us.
No, wait.
But you're all still alive now, right?
Maybe someone switched identities.
(Someone among the four
switched identities)
(Who might switch identities?)
The year is 1996 now.
Mr. Ding,
hi.
Hi.
I'm An Xiaoding too.
It's 2030 now.
It forms permanent dark red deposit.
I think there's one possible
It goes like this.
So
maybe the person who died
was someone from 2030
who traveled back to 2016.
Because we
went from 2016 to 1996,
then to 2030 now.
That proves
time travel exists here.
That means
other people can also travel to 2016.
I killed myself.
Or I killed
one of you three.
Right.
Is this a parallel universe?
So cool. A parallel universe.
I killed myself.
(An Xiaoning's theory:
The killer used a parallel universe)
How exactly did that person
travel there?
There's one more clue.
The halo color.
It's different.
The first time,
it was from 2016
to 1996.
(First time travel: 2016 to 1996)
The light changed.
Red to white.
(Red, white)
Then from 1996
to 2030.
2030.
(Second time travel: 1996 to 2030)
It was
white to green.
(White, green)
2016 was red.
1996 was white.
2030 was green.
(Theory: The light color
is linked to the year)
So the first time we saw
that thing, it was...
Green to red.
In 2030,
someone
went back to 2016, when we
first saw the light.
(2016: red, 1996: white, 2030: green)
So,
the masked person An Yi saw
was someone from the future.
That means
that puppet person may be
the killer who came back from 2030.
(Theory: The killer came back from 2030
and pretended to be the puppet person)
If someone came from 2030,
what did they come here for?
(Why did the masked person return
to 2016?)
Well...
Listen. The boss will be here soon.
The boss?
Who's the boss?
You'll know soon.
Come on.
Come with me.
Wait.
I still have a question.
Aren't we a rich family?
Yeah. Why?
(Why did everyone's
identities change so much?)
When I count three, two, one,
we say, "Hello, boss."
Okay.
Remember that.
Boss.
Don't look so serious, boss.
(Welcome her with smiles)
Pai?
Wait.
She took over.
Speak.
What?
Paishan Glass Factory
(Paishan Glass Factory)
has grown ten times in value?
(Chairwoman Pai)
Good.
Our global coverage is up to 80%?
Thanks for telling me.
Our...
(All our assets are gone)
The glass dynasty...
The An family...
(An Glass Factory)
(Paishan Glass Factory)
Mr. Ke.
I'm housekeeping.
The An family's heir.
I'm the housekeeping supervisor.
The An family's heiress.
I'm housekeeping.
From Wang Tech.
Bodyguard.
Mr. Ding.
I'm security.
The current Mrs. An.
Nanny?
(The rich-family sequel
has been rewritten)
No wonder we ended up
with these identities.
(Other people's success
hurts even more)
By someone else's...
Someone else's...
One, two, three.
- Hello, boss!
(A total role reversal)
Those uniforms look pretty good on you.
Yes.
Getting used to the work?
- Yes.
We need time.
After falling from the top,
it's a little...
It's easy to go from simple to rich.
Going from rich
to simple is pretty hard.
Difficult.
Exactly.
(Missing our glorious old selves)
You'll get used to it.
Are you used to it?
Climbing up step by step?
Very used to it.
Watch your mouth.
Even though this is Pai Mansion,
and even though you're my
security, housekeeping, and bodyguard...
Madam.
You're all my babies.
(Not that "baby")
We're all your babies.
Not bad.
As long as we live well together,
nothing matters more.
Sure thing.
Boss' happiness comes first.
Right.
(Ding)
Ding.
(Excited Jealous)
(Jealous)
There's more?
(Special treatment)
(Ding)
(Security Guard Ding)
You know what to do.
(Housekeeping cart key)
(That familiar..)
Housekeeping cart.
Ding!
Make sure you keep that key safe.
A token of love.
Right, butler.
The banner you asked me to make
is done.
Hope it helps.
Helps us?
Us?
(What help do we need?)
Looking for our children.
(Ever since you left in 2026,)
(Mom and Dad have been worried sick.)
(We sold everything to find you.)
(Our children,)
(An Ning,)
(An Wen,)
(An Ding,)
(An Xiaoke,)
(please come home.)
Wait.
Our children
went missing?
(2030. Why did their
four children disappear?)
Get back to work.
Butler, walk with me
in the back garden.
Of course.
You two aren't together, right?
I couldn't accept that.
No.
Good.
Don't worry.
Okay. Take care, boss.
(A very responsible security guard)
These
are your four children.
They disappeared four years ago.
They've been gone since then.
I have a really scary thought.
Go on.
What if the four kids traveled back?
Could they?
Check the age.
What age?
What if right now,
one of you four
is actually a kid?
No.
No way.
I'm so mature.
He was born in January
2016.
(An Xiaoke, born January 2016)
In 2026,
(Missing in 2026)
he was ten.
No way.
(Child replacing
the real person ruled out)
Why would a kid run away from home?
(No clue at all)
Let's check the car key.
The car Pai gave us.
What's inside?
Your BMW.
Bring it over.
(Cleaning cart)
I wanna drive this.
(The little car he's wanted
for 14 years)
Isn't this it?
Here.
The evidence is right under your butt.
I'll do it.
(An Xiaoke's little bag)
Go ahead.
(Finally riding his beloved little car)
Okay.
Stop.
(Little car experience voucher used up)
Come on.
Search it.
(Extending the ride on the spot)
There's one here.
An Xiaoning,
take yours.
Whose is this?
(An Xiaoding's bag)
This is An Xiaoding's.
See what's in this cabinet.
An Xiaowen.
(An Xiaowen's bag)
This is...
(Wig)
Running...
Running away from home.
(Running away from home)
Next, I'll check.
(Detective vibes)
I wanna see hers.
(Respectful)
Sure.
I wanna see yours. Hurry.
(Photo of the four kids)
This is where they were last seen.
Four kids.
Emo punks.
Wearing wild emo wigs.
This.
They even made some curse sign.
There's writing on the back.
Runaway squad of four.
Cool departure pic.
Even four grains of sand
can sting the world's eye.
We're gone. Don't look.
You won't find us anyway.
(An Ning, An Wen, An Ding, An Xiaoke)
Then they labeled the four kids.
Explain this.
Why do you have this?
I honestly don't know.
(Why is the four kids' photo
in An Xiaowen's bag?)
I also have a key
that opens that door.
Staff lounge 201.
An Xiaoke's stuff.
Someone wrote something here,
"If you keep crying,
I'll throw you out."
"I'll make you a kid nobody wants."
"Talk back and I'll beat you to death."
"Look at you. What even are you?"
"You'll make me die of anger one day."
Then below that,
someone else wrote,
"Being threatened
and scared was painful,"
"but if he hadn't been so strict,"
(2016)
"I wouldn't be where I am today."
"Those words were useful."
"I hope An Xiaoke"
"becomes as outstanding as me."
You psycho!
So you also...
So you inherited your dad's style too!
Exactly.
You actually picked up a stick?
Another monster.
No way.
What do you mean, no way?
Do I look like that kind of person?
Totally.
Spill it.
(Come clean)
Look.
The words written on the first line,
the ones written in pencil,
(If you keep crying,)
I wrote that when I was a kid.
(I'll throw you out)
It's like a diary entry.
My dad,
An Songqiu, used to treat me like that.
Exactly.
When I was a kid, my dad
used scare tactics
and physical punishment.
Even though growing up like that
was a bit painful,
I ended up
becoming a super
successful glass artist.
I achieved a lot of things
I never could've imagined before.
So looking back after making it,
even though
that kind of upbringing was painful,
maybe there was a method to the madness.
(Can't help but grab a stick)
Wait.
Don't hit me just yet.
I feel like the educational method
that actually works
is scaring them,
not beating them.
(An Ke's parenting style: Scare tactics)
So you became an upgraded version.
The upgraded version means
nobody gets hurt.
Whether it's hitting or scaring,
it's all abuse.
Gaslighting.
That's not true.
It really isn't.
What gives you the right
to be so confident?
You creep.
(Begging for mercy)
I'm good at begging.
I'm good at backing down.
Alright, shut up for a second.
You three aren't saints either.
True.
I suggest
the rest of you share
(Waiting to see what happens)
how you raised your kids.
Fine, let's see what you've got.
(A box inside An Xiaoding's bag)
Say goodbye to domestic abuse.
What?
(The box in An Xiaoding's bag)
He can't go through what I went through.
I wrote that back in 2016.
I cut up all the black balls
they used to hit me with.
(Chopped-up golf balls)
Because I went through that,
I didn't want my kid
to suffer through it too.
So when An Yi told me
to hand the kid over,
I gave a hard no.
No way. I have to raise my own kid.
I want him to be happy,
joyful,
and free.
(An Xiaoding's parenting style:
Free-range)
Your head is in the right place.
Total respect.
Right.
Some people...
Some people's morals are totally warped.
(This isn't what I expected)
Alright, let's look at Ning's stuff.
Ning has an envelope.
(An envelope in An Xiaoning's bag)
(An Xiaoning's Excellence Plan)
Now this is interesting.
This one is all about scheduling.
(Morning, Noon, Night)
An Xiaoning's excellence plan.
Morning jog,
golf,
news analysis,
math, abacus, second language,
table manners, negotiation skills.
Suffocating.
(Finally caught you)
And then it even says,
"I want him to be free and happy."
"Not chained down
by the pressure to be perfect."
"I can't let him go through
what I went through."
You're the suffocating type.
(Didn't you notice something's off?)
Double standards.
Yeah, you're not violent.
But you're totally suffocating him.
You guys are completely mixed up.
I'm An Xiaoning.
My kid's name is An Ningzai.
(An Xiaoning's Excellence Plan)
(The one being suffocated
was An Xiaoning)
Oh.
Right.
Good point.
He's absolutely right.
My bad.
You guys are terrible detectives.
Okay.
Next up,
I'm going to give
a two-hour presentation.
Take a seat, everyone.
Alright.
(An Xiaoning's life story presentation)
Here's the deal, guys.
An Yi,
who is my dad,
set up this whole life plan
for me when I was a kid.
He wanted me to be highly successful.
(Physical and mental awakening)
From 6PM until night,
(Depth and breadth of core academics)
18 hours in total,
(Social etiquette and practice)
he packed my schedule completely full.
(Arts, technology, and leadership)
(Father-son book club, value guidance)
(Family meeting)
If I didn't get it done,
(Daily reflection journal)
he would yell at me.
Are you a total loser?
Just non-stop roasting me.
And when I didn't perform well,
he would hit me with a golf club
and
a brown
golf ball.
(Just like An Xiaoding,
An Xiaoning was also physically abused)
It was just pure torture for me.
It felt awful.
I was already six-foot-one back then.
He was only like five-foot-eight,
but
he completely controlled me.
And because he had
all the keys to our house,
he'd often sneak into my room
while I was sleeping
to check on what I was doing.
Sneaking in while you're asleep
to check on you?
Yeah.
So after I grew up,
I told myself one thing.
I absolutely have to...
Grow to six-foot-three.
That was my first goal.
My second dream
was to leave the An family for good.
Since I've always loved glassware too,
I wanted to start my own brand,
Ning's Glass Works.
And let me tell you,
the success I have today
is entirely self-made.
(Self-made certificate of honor)
(Ning's Glass Works wins
Top Brand Award for 6th straight year)
(Impressive)
Even if our family goes downhill,
he's still the most successful one.
Respect.
So back then, when An Yi
told me
to bring my kid over,
I was like, hell no.
There was no way
I was letting him raise my kid.
I just wanted my kid
to have a childhood nothing like mine.
Yeah.
(An Xiaoning's parenting style: Healthy)
Why do you have this?
I honestly don't know.
I want him to be happy,
joyful,
and free.
I just wanted my kid
to have a childhood nothing like mine.
I feel like things
are starting to take a weird turn.
This isn't looking great
for me right now.
Did you think everyone was like you?
(This is bad)
How come I feel like...
Say goodbye
to domestic abuse.
No, look.
You're saying goodbye to domestic abuse,
but I was never abused.
Scare tactics don't count as abuse?
You were never abused?
I'm ready to lock in the killer.
(Authoritative)
What counts as domestic abuse?
Emotional abuse is the worst.
Nobody can handle the silent treatment.
Alright, fair enough.
But I do have one question.
If you guys are all
(Grit teeth)
such amazing parents,
then why did your kids run away?
Let me tell you why.
It's because your kid
kidnapped ours.
Exactly.
I raised my kid so well.
Your kid is the bad influence.
They got corrupted by your parenting.
Okay, I admit it.
Things aren't looking great
for me right now.
But I'm sure
there's gonna be a plot twist.
By plot twist, you mean
finding out none of us
are good people, right?
Pretty much.
(Waiting for a plot twist)
My clue here says something
about a staff lounge.
Alright.
We need to go there.
Wait.
I want to take another look
at all your stuff.
See if there are any critical clues.
Maybe I can find that one
ultimate piece of evidence.
(Back at it searching
for the "ultimate evidence")
Wow, nothing.
(Already walked away)
The guy who feared being scared
became the one scaring others.
Give him the key.
(Fatherly love)
What?
Don't.
Let's go.
(Grip tightly)
(Main hall)
I suspect one of the four of us
isn't really themselves.
I was thinking the same thing.
It's not like I killed myself.
But it could be
that I went back to kill someone
and got accidentally killed.
Right.
(Who is from 2030,
the victim or the killer?)
Open it.
Rock and roll.
This is creepy.
(New scene unlocked: Staff lounge)
Let's check it out
zone by zone.
(Splitting up to search for evidence)
Plenty of clues here.
(What big discovery did he find?)
(Cool)
(Equally cool)
(Showing off the cool gear)
(A man's joy, Jealous)
My sword and shield.
Come on, let's attack him.
(Check out the team's daily routine)
(at 12 PM every Fri)
Why?
(Father and son ganging up on Uncle Ke)
(Righteous detective)
That's for hitting the kid.
(Father and son ganging up on Uncle Ke)
(Uncle Ke utterly defeated)
I think this one is way cooler.
This is cooler.
(Gearing up with something new)
Let me do it.
A zombie?
Like this.
(Son turning into a zombie)
Why?
Why is it so short?
Not bad.
Hold this.
You hold this.
(Self-defense weapon +1)
Someone's after you.
(Continuing to search for evidence)
(Hey there, detective)
(You're so random)
Why are there four canisters of oil?
(Focused on the case)
(Four canisters of liquid)
No idea.
(An Xiaoding's storage area)
(An Xiaoding)
When the security guard shows up,
the bad guys behave themselves.
Is this mine?
What are you...
Are you trying to burn...
(You're suspicious)
You're trying to burn someone alive.
I'm gonna burn everyone to the ground.
(Act tough)
(Watch your back)
There's a laptop here.
Coming.
(Blank note, pencil, laptop, phone)
Let's check this area first.
Don't touch my laptop.
(Don't touch my laptop,
Password required)
What's this?
(Found a blank sticky note)
Should we shade it with a pencil?
It's blank.
A pencil.
Should we use a pencil
to shade over it?
Really?
There it is.
Dad's laptop password is 0108.
My phone was connected
to his laptop before,
so now I can use his laptop
to scroll through my phone.
You guys should try this too.
(Don't touch my laptop)
(Laptop successfully unlocked)
You can access your phone
from the laptop?
How do you do that?
It's the iPhone Mirroring feature.
You can directly view
the contents of any previously
(iPhone Mirroring feature)
connected phone on the screen.
(Entering the password)
Let's take a look.
They have a group chat called
"Escape Our Parents".
Does my kid want to escape me too?
(Vent here!)
This group was created by An Ningzai.
(An Ningzai's first message
after creating the group: Vent here!)
An Xiaoke said...
My dad is so terrifying.
He freaks me out
over the smallest things.
He thinks Grandpa's
parenting style was great.
He assumes because I look obedient,
it means he's doing a good job.
But he has no idea
that I cry myself
to sleep every single night.
And then,
An Dingzai said...
My dad told me before
how he got beaten up so badly as a kid
just for breaking a bowl.
But when I literally just
accidentally broke one of his teacups,
he grabbed a pair of chopsticks
and whipped me.
You...
You lied.
(Fighting violence with violence)
(Gentle)
I told you guys from the start.
(Here comes the plot twist I wanted)
He beat me while yelling,
"Don't do this again."
He only wrote that once.
Okay.
(Too excited)
I just want to emphasize.
You're too into it.
(He beat me while yelling)
I just want to emphasize.
Am I really like that?
I'm so jealous of An Ningzai.
He has never
been hit at all.
(Proud)
Don't celebrate just yet.
An Ningzai replied.
Wait, An Ningzai replied.
Don't celebrate yet.
My dad doesn't hit
or yell at me,
but he constantly talks
about escaping his childhood home
and starting from nothing.
So compared to what
he went through, my complaints
are absolutely nothing.
When I say I'm tired,
he goes,
"You're not."
You're not.
When I feel like crying,
(Clapping back)
he says,
"What is there to cry about?"
What's wrong with that?
I can't even say that?
How else are you
supposed to raise a kid?
He doesn't yell at me,
but every time he finishes talking,
I feel like it's all my fault.
That's textbook gaslighting.
Because my kid is a picky eater.
I told him
how I barely had food back then,
and that he should
be grateful for what's on his plate.
He shouldn't complain.
That's too self-centered.
Man, I actually just read up on this.
You're invalidating the kid's feelings.
No,
I've never invalidated him.
I'm just sharing my perspective.
I'm telling him
how tough it was for me back then.
So is your parenting style
just spoiling them?
How would you teach him then?
I'd tell him
that I didn't get to eat
all these back then.
I barely had food back then.
Okay.
And I stop there.
Exactly.
I stop there.
That's what I said.
I don't push it any further.
Alright.
We don't need to argue about this.
(Upholding justice)
You added that extra line.
You shouldn't complain.
I guess
only Wen's mom is different.
His mom doesn't hit him,
and she doesn't drop
those guilt trips either.
The biggest bombshell is about to drop.
(Waiting for the next plot twist)
(The chat log hit the bottom)
That's it?
I really am
a good mom.
I raised him so well.
Yet you're saying
I'm the killer.
That's enough.
So An Wenzai
had nothing?
No.
No dark past.
No dirt.
No way.
Let's go.
Let's go check out Wen's evidence.
Come on.
Wen, the janitor.
(An Xiaowen's storage area)
(Found a box)
A family should always stay together.
Three locks.
(Lock 1, Lock 2, Lock 3)
This is a girl.
This is a baby.
(4-digit passcode)
This is
(Dad, Mom, Kid)
a guy.
Dad, Mom, and kid.
Birth dates.
Year and month.
(Passcodes might be birthdays)
What's the kid's birthday?
You don't remember your kid's birthday?
(Totally immersed in the role)
My son's birthday is January 28th.
0128.
Your birthday is...
0528.
Mine is 1230.
(All locks unlocked successfully)
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's see how you raised your kid.
(Tablet)
Let's check it out.
What is it?
Tuibao.
(An Wenzai x AI Tuibao chat log)
Good evening, Wen.
Did anything fun happen
at school today?
First place in the physics competition?
Congratulations!
But you don't seem very happy.
Your typing speed
is a minute and thirty seconds
slower than usual.
Whenever you won
an award before, you used to talk a lot.
Dang it.
How do you get me better
than my parents?
They don't give a crap
about me at all.
Are you afraid of being lonely?
I'm not afraid of being lonely.
What scares me is
having a mom and a dad
but living like an orphan.
No matter what I do,
my mom just says,
"It's your life. You decide."
He,
am I wrong?
You always reply to me.
Compared to those two people
whose blood runs through my veins,
you feel more like a real human.
What's his zodiac sign? A water sign?
He's so insecure
and craves affection.
This kid needs a reality check.
(Even the uncle can't stand this)
What a brat.
I gave him enough
freedom.
Right. Giving it didn't work.
Neither did restricting it.
Kids get spoiled
either way.
You have to use this.
(Understand An Yi,
question An Yi, become An Yi)
(Snap into character)
All first-time humans.
Why should I give in to him?
(Love that twist)
Well said.
Who isn't someone's child anyway?
Right.
Leave this to you.
No.
Say no to violence.
Then leave it to his dad.
(Shifts into "bad dad" mode)
How can you be like this?
What gives you the right
to judge others?
Don't you think this
whole situation was caused by you?
(Dad)
Even now,
you're still blaming others.
Did I give you too much
freedom?
(Immersed in "bad dad" role)
You took that freedom...
You're an absent father.
(The absent father)
What do you have to say?
I'm busy
every single day.
I have
(Stay in character)
365 people to take care of,
(Classic absent father line)
and 365 things to deal with.
How am I supposed to handle this?
Fine.
Very well.
I still have another suitcase here.
(An Xiaowen's suitcase)
And a phone.
(An Xiaowen's phone)
This chat history
is
between me
and the Taobao AI shopping assistant.
My child is three years old.
Please help me
find safe, affordable toys for him
for the 618 shopping festival.
The AI assistant replied.
I've found several
building blocks
that help develop creativity.
During 618,
they're also 15% off.
Love is like
building blocks of patience,
one piece at a time,
building a castle in his heart.
From childhood to now,
I've bought things for him
every 618.
That shows I care deeply about my child.
What's in the suitcase then?
What's the password?
Because we
wanted to give the child
more love,
we added one to each digit
of his birthday.
More care,
more happiness.
So I added one to each of them.
I already opened it.
(Notebook, card, stone)
A notebook and a card.
Tmall 618 commemorative card.
Every good item
you choose for your child
quietly shapes his world.
From Tmall, quality and value.
This notebook...
(An Wen's growth diary)
It records every little moment
of my son's life.
This was given to me
by He Jiahua.
Even though our son is gone,
I will always be with you.
I'll come back as soon as work is done.
Don't forget to accept
the gift I bought you
during Tmall 618 Festival.
After the child went missing,
He Jiahua prepared
many surprises for me.
I wrote back, "I'm glad you're here".
It was really warm.
What do you like?
I'll
arrange everything
for you and the child.
Have you emptied my cart already?
Of course.
It's Tmall 618 Festival.
I can have
the Taobao AI shopping assistant
recommend gifts for you.
I'm sure
we'll find something you love.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I actually
love chatting
with the Taobao AI shopping assistant.
It always knows exactly
what I want.
It's so convenient.
What is this?
Tell me.
(A blood-stained stone)
(Interrogation tension)
This goes back to my
painful childhood.
Go on.
Our dad
was a control freak.
If I did something wrong,
he would hit and scold me.
Until one day, something changed.
I got sick.
And he became unusually gentle.
After that, I thought
maybe being sick was
the only way to get
love and freedom.
This stone was used
for self-harm,
right?
Yes.
So your fragile act in front
of me
was all fake?
Kind of.
I do like acting weak.
Fake.
Everything is fake.
What's even real anymore?
In the An family,
sincerity matters least.
Every family has its problems.
(Sudden emotional shift)
Yeah.
There are still some boxes left, right?
Yes.
There's a cabinet below.
Let's check it.
(Box)
(Ning's notebook)
That's the text.
Let me
read this.
Today marks 1,000 days since the child
went missing.
We sit again
on the front steps,
sleepless through the night.
For the past 1,000 days,
we've kept asking the same question.
Not how he got lost,
but how we
pushed him away, step by step.
I followed my dad's way.
(If you cry, I'll throw you out)
Only results matter. Not process.
Crying is useless.
Fear is weakness.
(Ke uses threats to teach courage)
Only surviving makes you strong.
I thought I gave him everything.
I gave him enough freedom.
Later, I realized
that what I gave him
wasn't what he needed.
(Not an orphan, but lived like one)
It was what I never got as a child.
I wasn't loving my child.
I was loving the child
(Wen lives through her child)
inside me who never grew up.
I kept thinking of that fairy tale.
I thought
the worst ending was
the rabbit being eaten by the wolf.
But the real worst ending
is the rabbit growing up
and becoming the wolf.
Every time I hurt him,
I hated myself.
Because his fear looked
(Ding passes fear down through fists)
just like mine as a child.
What I said most
wasn't "I love you".
It was,
"Do you know
how hard I've worked for you"?
Those years weren't easy.
I raised him
to be sensible and understanding.
I used his good behavior
(Ning buys gratitude with guilt)
to justify my own suffering.
We never understood
how love became this twisted.
Later we realized love
didn't change.
We just were never truly loved.
Unprocessed trauma doesn't disappear.
It just gets passed on.
The child became our proof,
our compensation,
our outlet,
and our mirror.
Everything but himself.
It took us 1,000 days
to admit this.
But by then, the child was already gone.
(They call
their unhealed wounds "love,")
(yet every careless embrace)
(leaves the child hurt.)
I think we need
to be objective here.
We can't say
these parents
were
completely
wrong.
But in parenting,
there has
to be balance.
Everything needs limits.
You went too far.
Yes.
(All four have problems in parenting)
In 2030,
someone went back
to 2016,
when we
first saw the light.
What was he trying to do?
It took us
1,000 days
to admit this.
But by then,
the child
was already gone.
I know now.
So going back to 2016 means going back
to when the child was born.
Start over.
Do it again.
In 2030,
we want to go back to 2016,
fix
who we were,
continue
their lives,
and raise
the child.
So...
Among the four of us
in 2016,
one person died.
(The charred body belongs
to one of them in 2016.)
(An Xiaoding, An Xiaowen,
An Xiaoning, or An Ke.)
So,
now,
one of us present here
is actually our future self from 2030.
(Theory: Someone from 2030 traveled
back in time to save their child.)
(Returned to 2016, killed their
younger self, and took their place.)
(Who among us is the version from 2030?)
Our objective now
is to determine which one
of us is actually from 2030.
Yes.
That makes sense.
(The detectives agree
with the deduction)
But there
is another question.
Where is An Yi?
(Where is the 2016 version of An Yi?)
We should return
to 2016 and look for him.
Right.
Our original
objective
was to travel to 2016
and investigate the crime scene.
We accidentally ended up in 2030.
Therefore, we should
continue with our plan and proceed
with the investigation.
Let's go.
Everyone,
why are we in the wrong year?
You wrote "2016"
on the paper.
On a blank sheet.
Just write "2016" yourself.
Didn't we all use blank paper?
Maybe it needed paper
of a different color.
When we traveled to 1996,
we also used blank paper.
(Family curse victims:
An San and An Si)
Maybe it's not the color or the writing.
Could it be the paper's production date?
(A bold theory emerges)
(Production date: 1996)
(Theory: Time travel requires
paper from the target year)
The paper's production date.
Yes.
That means
the paper we took
was manufactured in 2030.
(Discarded paper from the archive room)
Just write "2016" yourself.
(Paper produced in 2030)
The person who traveled
from 2030 to 2016 used
that sheet to make the journey.
That is why it was left on the floor
for us to find.
And that is why
we ended up in 2030.
What we need now
is paper from 2016.
(Theory: Only paper from 2016
can send them to the past)
Can these be torn open?
(The action-oriented
investigator gets to work)
Tui City Gossip Weekly.
Gossip Weekly.
The Former Owner's Villa.
I'll gladly take it.
Mr. Pai revealed
a story to the reporters.
After years cleaning the An residence,
someone broke
through the first-floor fireplace
and uncovered a hidden wine cellar.
A large collection of aged wine
was found inside.
Even the An family
didn't know it existed.
So once we return to 2016,
we should look for the cellar.
But first, we still need
the paper from 2016.
Let's keep searching.
What's this?
A remote control.
It's a payment code.
Collection code.
An Glass Corporation.
(Glass Inspection Device)
Fully traceable glass tracking system.
Earlier, we found a piece
of broken glass,
didn't we?
Be careful.
There may be glass shards.
His head was covered in broken glass.
Let's use this device to scan
the glass from yesterday's
crime scene.
Scan the glass.
Right.
Okay.
Footprints belonging to your son.
Isn't this from 2016?
This one.
(2016)
Okay.
I think we should go
check the time-travel
location now.
Let's go.
Go.
Return to the past.
(Rest and recharge)
(Rest resets battle fatigue)
(Recharging restores energy)
(To survive long,)
(rest and recovery as passive skills)
Just attach it here.
Alright.
Okay. Formation.
(Will they successfully return to 2016?)
(Paishan Glass Factory)
(An Glass Factory)
(An Family Villa,
March 25, 2016, 4PM)
We're back.
Let's find the wine cellar.
We're really back.
Back.
(Jin's room. He Wen's room.
Abandoned archive room)
We're really back.
Even the curtains are a different color.
Table is gone as well.
First, I need to restrain
Pai before she
gradually takes...
Over our family's assets.
We've been nurturing a threat
in our own home.
Pai!
Come out!
(Main Hall)
(Wine cellar behind the fireplace)
Kick it open.
I'll do it.
(Experienced)
Lift it.
(Clearing the hidden passage)
(New area unlocked: Wine Cellar)
Who has been tied up here?
(Who was tied up in the wine cellar?)
What?
Grandpa. My grandpa.
An Yi.
(Why is An Yi here?)
He's still alive.
He's unconscious.
He doesn't seem to be in good condition.
Don't wake him.
Let him rest.
(Overwhelming sense of justice)
You deal with your
dad yourselves.
Should I handle it?
Don't act rashly.
(Bloodline awakening)
Should I handle it?
Or someone else?
Either way, if we do it,
no one will ever know.
(Looks around)
(Torn paper fragments)
What does "two...
(Impossible to piece together)
sufficient for death" mean?
(What does "two... sufficient
for death" mean?)
What?
Nothing.
Let's keep it.
Yes.
An Yi.
Are we sure
we don't need to wake him up?
Let's ask him something.
Yi.
(Attempts CPR)
Press his philtrum.
Any water?
Splash some on him.
(Returning a favor)
Can someone pull his beard?
(Pressing his philtrum
and splashing cold water)
See if he reacts
(Pulls his beard)
Tickle him.
(Tickling)
He's still not waking up?
Try mouth-to-mouth?
If this fails...
(No. Absolutely not)
Then forget it.
Let's leave him unconscious.
(Let him stay unconscious)
(Searching his belongings)
(Potential clues)
He has one of these.
One is broken.
(Same glass inspection device)
The other one still works.
He was investigating the glass as well.
(Why was An Yi
carrying a glass inspection device?)
Wait.
There's a phone.
There's a phone here.
(Phone)
Wait.
Let's check
the notes.
Through that archive room,
I saw everything.
That symbol
was never a curse. It was a plea.
A plea for all of this
to finally come to an end.
I don't want this cycle to continue.
In this world,
there is still time
to change everything.
The reformed version of myself
will give my child
the childhood they deserve.
One of the four
of us traveled back.
Yes.
Someone wanted to change everything.
Our deduction was correct.
Yes.
It's correct.
I'm going to search
this phone thoroughly.
I understand your situation.
This is a video consultation call.
Many times,
when we are mistreated
as children,
we grow up
hoping to become different
kinds of parents.
Yet when we become parents ourselves,
we often
end up treating our children
the same way our parents treated us.
This is known
as intergenerational trauma.
So in 2030, he consulted
a parenting specialist?
Did the child die?
What does he mean by returning to 2016?
What does he mean by replacing him?
Sir,
what are you talking about?
I don't understand.
Perhaps his child died.
That may be what
drove him to take such drastic action.
(The child dies)
No.
It's like this. Let me explain.
I'll reenact it.
(Support)
(The audience takes their seats)
Imagine it.
(2030 Therapy Session Reenactment)
(Fully immersed)
This is intergenerational trauma.
You must end
(Expert)
this behavior
if you want to save your child.
(Expert No. 2)
Yes. Your child needs to feel secure.
(2030 Therapy Session Reenactment)
You're right.
Then
I need to return to 2016.
I need to replace my former self.
I need to become him.
Did the child die?
What does he mean by returning to 2016?
(Expert No. 3)
What do you mean?
Replace whom?
Who exactly are you replacing?
Call disconnects.
It's you.
That's right.
Yes.
This part.
(Outstanding acting)
Either you've perfect acting,
(I love to hear it)
or it happened to you too.
No way.
(Otherwise,)
no one could portray it so convincingly.
Exactly.
(I'll take that as a compliment)
What?
What's this?
There's something else here.
What is it?
(A plastic bag)
There's a piece of paper.
(A note hidden inside the bag)
Disinfection Record.
March 22, 2030.
Clothing disinfection completed.
That means someone brought
a mascot costume back
from 2030
and had it disinfected before traveling.
Wait.
I'm the security guard.
(Security guard)
What are you?
I'm the janitor.
(Janitor)
Then we're finished.
(Security guard)
You're the janitor.
(Cleaning Supervisor, Housekeeper,
Janitor, Bodyguard)
I'm the janitor.
I'm the murderer.
(Cleaning Supervisor,
Bodyguard, Janitor)
You're the supervisor.
If that's the case, then the killer
must be one of us.
Cleaning supervisor.
(The killer is one of the janitor,
Ning, Ke, and Wen)
I think this confirms
one thing:
Someone returned from 2030...
While wearing the mascot costume.
Yes.
Use the inspection device on the glass
to obtain the following
data.
(An Glass Corporation,
Fully Traceable System)
Contact the inspection officer
for procurement.
We haven't checked the glass yet.
Right. Let's do that.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Thank you.
(With "Xin" as the caregiver)
Let's scan
the glass.
Does anyone have a pen?
It's fine. We'll remember it.
Three, two, one.
Identification number:
BLASQTS
6230D6202YPH
Write that down.
Let me find a pen.
BLASQ
(Mnemonic method)
(Charcoal)
Got it. I have a pen.
Quickly.
Glass identification number:
BLASQTS
(Original Handwriting)
N6230D6202YPH
(Glass batch number obtained)
Call the inspector.
(Inspector's phone number)
Hello.
You have reached the newly established
(An Group Quality Traceability System)
An Glass Group
(Manufactured on March 23, 2016)
Quality Traceability System
I didn't expect to receive
our first
call so soon.
How may I assist you?
Check an item.
We'd like to trace a piece of glass.
Please note the serial number.
Serial number.
Certainly.
BLASQ
(Reviewing it mentally)
NTS62306202
YPH.
One moment, please.
I've found it.
The manufacturing process for it
was highly unusual.
Only one piece
in the entire batch
was successfully produced.
(Unique piece)
What does this
part look like?
What is it for?
It became a large decorative mirror.
(The unique glass was crafted
into a decorative mirror)
It was placed in the An
family courtyard.
The courtyard?
Outside?
Thank you.
Goodbye.
We must search the courtyard.
Let's go.
(Wine Cellar. Main Hall. Courtyard)
There's a piece of glass outside.
(Beep)
It's raining?
Infrared Thermal Sensor.
(Infrared Thermal Sensor)
Press here
to view the historical records.
(View Historical Records)
I pressed it.
The interface appeared.
Please log in.
hongwaixianguanliyuan
houtai.com
(Pull)
Don't pull it. Tear it.
It's been pulled out.
You...
We'll look at it later.
Take it.
Put it in your pocket.
Okay.
He, grab an umbrella. It's raining.
What?
(Mirror fragments)
This is the broken mirror,
right?
(The shattered mirror)
There's blood.
Yes.
(The fragments are stained with blood)
That means
this was the primary crime scene.
(Current case summary)
(Victim: Unknown)
(Location of death: Courtyard)
(Time of death: Between March 24
and March 25, 2016. Exact time unknown)
(Cause of death: Unknown)
His head was violently...
Struck against this.
I understand now.
Because the two people looked identical.
One acted as a reflection.
Yes.
For example, this person is the victim.
I stand behind
the mirror.
Copy their movements.
As if seeing themselves.
Yes.
Then, at an unexpected moment,
I strike them.
A perfectly casual murder.
Right.
It's quite an ingenious method.
Let's investigate further.
Be careful.
(Scene Investigation)
The leaves are the same
species, aren't they?
Right.
Is it?
I've found a crucial piece of evidence.
A leaf.
(The leaf found in the courtyard
matches the one found on the body)
That doesn't seem
particularly significant.
Can we restore
these fragments?
You've used your restore card.
Use the Restore Card.
And just like that, my card is gone.
Don't worry. He still
has a Copy Card.
Can it restore?
Just let it try.
It can.
If it actually works,
I'd like to see it,
(Always willing to experiment)
alright?
Okay.
Use the Copy Card.
(Copy Card)
Copy the Restore Card.
(Copy Card: Copies any skill
card used by another player)
(Restore Card: Restores one clue)
Use the Restore Card
on the mirror.
Alright.
Alright?
I can't believe I doubted that.
Why don't I believe this?
Is this real?
The players have used the Restore Card.
(Restore Card, restore a clue)
Restore a clue.
It's restored.
(The mirror has been restored)
It actually worked.
Impressive.
Wait.
Then what are these?
(Additional glass fragments)
Why would repair leave extra shards?
(Why are there extra fragments?)
All fragments in this section
must be restored.
But besides this intact
piece of glass...
There's something additional.
These fragments clearly
do not belong to the mirror.
Wasn't this glass
supposed to be unique?
Then why are there
extra pieces?
Do they form another object?
Or were they always broken?
(What exactly are these fragments?)
Let's scan them.
Good idea.
Scan them.
They said only one piece
was produced.
Correct.
But we don't
know whether more were made later.
Yes.
We don't know.
Wait.
I'll call them directly.
Hello.
I didn't expect
to receive a second call so soon.
How may I assist you?
Hello.
We would like to trace
another piece of glass.
Please note the serial number.
The serial number
is BLASQTS
6230D6202YPH
It's the same.
Same piece.
You're tracing
the same item.
(The extra fragments
share the mirror's origin)
You told us
that only one piece
of this glass was produced.
Yet it seems we now have two
separate objects made from it.
Allow me to check.
Alright.
She can check this too.
Can she also tell us
who the murderer is?
It seems she can find anything.
I've found the record.
After the unique mirror
was manufactured,
some leftover material remained.
Leftover material?
(Is that right?)
Really?
Quite literally, edge scraps.
Mr. An used
those scraps to create
an exquisite glass box
and took it home.
(A shattered glass box
is found at the crime scene)
This item was never
recorded.
So these fragments belong to a box.
Could you tell us
its size and appearance?
Can we look into it?
I'll need to look into that
and send the information to you later.
Thank you.
I went to see Mr. An.
I tied him up,
and grabbed a glass ornament.
(He Jiahuan's theory:
while restraining Mr. An, the killer)
Killed him in one blow.
(Using the glass case
as the weapon)
Why would he go
to Mr. An's place,
take that item,
and kill him?
(What special role did
the glass case play in the murder?)
This clue is leading us
to investigate Mr. An.
Will he wake up?
Today, we forced him
to stay awake for a while.
(Bloodline Awakening +1)
All right, no problem.
There's one thing
we haven't investigated.
(Unresolved question)
What was it again?
(Two... sufficient for death)
Sufficient for death"
And that infrared
monitoring website.
(Log in to view infrared records.
We have not checked it yet.
Right.
Come on.
Let us find a computer
and take a look at the website.
Here, let me check the URL.
Found it.
Yes.
It's this.
This is it.
This one.
(Scanning Range)
Scanning range.
The management system
requires real-time monitoring.
Okay.
Take a look.
(Real-Time Monitoring)
Historical Records.
(No signs of life detected)
March 25.
From midnight until 3PM,
no signs of life were detected.
No one entered.
(No one entered the courtyard
on March 25)
So the time of death must have been
before midnight or after 10PM.
Yes.
(Estimated time of death:
March 24, 10PM-12AM)
Between 10PM.
and midnight.
A two-hour window.
Yes.
Okay.
I think
we need to review the timeline.
Reconstruct the timeline.
(You seem suspicious)
Why are you so nervous?
Why is your face red?
No, our timelines just overlap.
Then I will go first.
After everything ended
at 10PM on March 24,
I went straight back to my room.
(An Xiaoding's timeline:
Returned to room at 10PM)
Two minutes after I got back,
my dad came over.
(10:02PM Ning arrived
at Ding's room)
He wanted to talk to me.
We talked until midnight,
and then the conversation ended.
In your room?
(12AM Conversation ended)
Yes, in my room.
Yes.
After everything ended at 10PM,
I returned to my room.
(An Xiaoning's timeline:
Returned to room at 10PM)
Then I thought,
a son suddenly appeared
in my life today.
I should talk to him,
catch up on the years we lost.
So I walked over.
It took two minutes.
(10:02PM Ning arrived
at Ding's room)
We talked until midnight.
(12AM Conversation ended)
(An Xiaoning and An Xiaoding's
timelines overlap)
They're each
other's alibis.
(The two corroborate
each other's whereabouts)
Yes.
What about those two minutes in between?
(10PM - 10:02PM No alibi)
A lot can happen in two minutes.
Two minutes is 120 seconds.
Exactly.
It is possible.
I admit it.
(Both had a two-minute
window to commit the crime)
I do have a small observation
regarding his testimony.
Could his suspicion
be considered slightly lower?
Because he was the passive party.
Someone else came to him.
(Jin Xiangyu finds
An Xiaoning more suspicious)
The person who actively
went to see someone else
would
attract more suspicion.
Yes.
Right.
In that journal, you were writing
in the first person.
(From Ning's journal)
You were the one
with the deepest regret.
(An Xiaoning had the strongest
motive to return to 2016)
That is an interesting point.
(Possible likelihood of being
the killer: An Xiaoning - An Xiaoding)
Okay.
Let me explain my timeline.
After the investigation ended yesterday,
I also returned to my room.
I got back
around 10PM.
(An Ke's timeline:
Returned to room at 10PM)
After thinking things over
for about two minutes,
I decided
to call
Jin and He,
my honey
and son.
(10:02PM Called Jin Xiangyu)
(He Jiahuan came to the room to talk)
I wanted to talk to them.
Then,
I quickly
asked them to come over.
We talked
until midnight.
(12AM Conversation ended)
However,
I only invited the two of them.
I didn't expect
Wen to show up as well.
In the end,
it became
(An Xiaowen arrived uninvited)
a discussion among four people.
At 10PM,
I heard Dad mention
that he would announce
the heir the next day.
I felt
very uneasy about it.
So I wandered around
the estate for a while.
Why were you wandering around?
Why didn't you go see your husband?
My husband and mother-in-law
had gone to pick out gifts.
I wandered around.
(An Xiaowen's timeline)
for about two minutes.
(10PM Wandering
the old residence)
As I approached Uncle Ke's room,
(10:02PM Encountered Jin and He)
I ran into the two of them.
(12AM Conversation ended)
(The timelines overlap)
(Mutually corroborated alibis)
So, in other words,
everyone had a two-minute period
when they were alone.
(An Xiaoning, An Xiaoding timeline)
(An Ke, An Xiaowen timeline)
(10PM-10:02PM Every suspect
was alone for two minutes)
Two minutes.
(How could the killer act
in such a tight overlap of time?)
Then...
That proves one thing.
You had the longest window of time.
The rest of us only had two minutes.
(An Ke had the longest
period without an alibi)
You spent two minutes making the call.
They'd still
need time to get
there after answering.
If I were the killer,
and I wanted to commit the crime,
would I have had to murder
(Live-streaming the murder process)
while making
that call?
That would be quite impressive.
Come on over.
Exactly. I would not even be worried.
I would
just keep talking
on the phone.
Come see me.
(Managing a phone call
and a murder at the same time)
That sounds...
Surprisingly heartwarming.
Honey.
Honey, I missed
you so much today.
Both of you,
come over and talk with me
about what happened today.
Would I really be that calm?
Did his voice sound
unusual during the call?
There did seem
to be some heavy breathing.
He sounded
out of breath.
Honey.
(Laughter)
(The investigators burst out laughing)
I think I have an idea.
My thought is this.
What
this information tells
us is that
(12AM-3PM on March 25,
no signs of life were detected)
from midnight until 3PM,
no one committed the crime.
Right?
Right.
So,
anything and everything
that could
have happened
took only two minutes.
(Did the killer commit
the crime within two minutes?)
Did they killed someone and
dumped the body in just two minutes?
No way.
How...
(Ruling out the feasibility)
No way.
How could you possibly
kill someone over there,
and then
move the body all the
way here in two minutes?
I don't think it had to happen
in those two minutes.
Maybe they killed someone
during those two minutes.
Then hid the body,
and dealt with it later.
(How did the killer commit
the crime within 2 minutes?)
Wait.
He's alive.
He's actually alive!
That's terrifying.
Bro.
Dad.
Don't ask me anything right now.
I have a massive headache.
Headache.
I need to go rest in my room.
(An Xiaoding makes a hasty retreat)
Okay, go rest then.
(What happened to An Yi?)
(Message incoming)
She just sent me that image
of the glass piece.
Product info:
Golden Years Glass Mirror Box.
Manufacturer:
An Glass Group.
It can be opened.
It holds
one liter...
Is it one liter?
Yeah, one liter.
This box holds more than one liter.
Up to here is one liter.
This box fits two liters total.
(Total capacity: 2L)
But...
Right.
Hold on.
I think this ties back
to that note.
"Two. Enough to die."
(Did the glass box
connected to the note?)
Two liters
of what would be stored in a glass?
If you smell the glass,
can you pick anything up?
Of course not.
It's been washed out by the rain.
Who says?
None of us have actually smelled it.
How do you know
there's nothing to smell?
(Detectives zeroing in)
I was just assuming.
Let me go smell it then.
I'll go check.
(Father-son sniff squad, activated)
Not leaving any stone unturned.
Alright.
(Super sniffer: online)
If you can actually smell
something, that's impressive.
(Sniffing intensifies)
I'm telling you,
my nose is razor sharp.
I can instantly tell
what something is.
Go ahead, smell it.
(Watch how Dad work!)
There really is a smell.
Not joking.
For real?
For real!
There's definitely a smell!
Right?
(Scent identification in progress)
It's just my gloves.
Hold on.
No, smell this one.
That's just the smell of the gloves.
Because...
Just smell your left hand.
Smell your left hand.
(A hand thoroughly marinated in glue)
Same smell, right?
(Going for a bigger sniff)
Two liters of blood.
(Blood?)
Why would it be blood?
Two liters of blood.
(Why would the glass
box smell like blood?)
Find anything?
Let's bring this back.
Does it smell?
Just smell it.
It smells like blood.
Blood.
So two liters of this.
That would be enough
to kill someone, right?
But wait.
Why would it have
to be filled with this?
Hey,
what if it's like this.
Say I have this jar,
and if I just hit you with the glass,
you'd probably survive.
But if I fill it with
two liters of water...
(Theory: the glass box was the weapon)
One hit. You're done.
Agree?
Let's sit down.
Alright.
So maybe the killer was in the room.
He filled the glass box with water,
then dropped it from above
to kill someone below.
(Dropping object from height?)
That way they could
stay in the room
and fake an alibi.
That's possible.
But could they even aim that well?
That'd have to be incredibly precise.
Yeah, I think so too.
That accurate?
Drop it from above
and fake the alibi.
A leaf.
Are these the same leaves?
Yes.
Is that what you're saying?
There was glass
all over the victim's head.
The leftover shards
were crafted by the chairman
into that elegant glass box.
(Scan range)
12AM to 3PM,
no signs of life detected.
What if
I never had to move the body at all,
because I never had
to go to the courtyard?
(No need to go to the courtyard
to dispose of the body?)
After ten o'clock,
when everything ended,
(An Xiaoning's theory)
everyone
(10PM Everyone returns to their rooms)
had just returned to their rooms.
(10:02PM Gathering in each other's rooms)
One of us four
got knocked out
by their past self.
Drugged
or
(Identity swap across time)
knocked out instantly,
then stashed anywhere.
Then I open my window,
look down,
spot the glass box,
and throw it.
(Smashes the glass)
After that,
I, An Xiaoning,
check the time
and noticed two minutes have passed.
I immediately go find my son
and say,
"I want to talk."
That's
how you build your own alibi.
And then?
Hypothetically,
I chat with him until midnight,
then go back to my room.
Except I don't really go back.
(An Xiaoning's theory: the crime)
I go back
(10-10:02PM Identity swap)
to deal with the body.
(Hide the body)
How, exactly?
(12AM Chat ends)
I burn it.
(After everyone returns to their rooms)
Drag it there.
(Drag the hidden body to
the fireplace and burn it)
Hold on.
There's one issue.
The body
must have been in the courtyard,
because there were leaves on it.
(The victim may have been in
the courtyard before death)
And the victim's head
also had glass on it.
So I think the body
must have passed through
the courtyard at some point.
But,
the infrared scan
detected no signs of life there.
The leaves
and the glass on the head
were planted to mislead us
into thinking the courtyard mirror area
(Courtyard wasn't the primary scene?)
was the primary crime scene.
I think we should
go back and verify
whether that's really the
primary crime scene.
Let's go check the...
I think
we should take another look
at the walls around there,
specifically the second floor.
There was something hanging there.
Okay.
Is there any of rope?
Like rope hanging down
from the second floor?
Would there even be rope here?
This...
What's this?
What's this clip for?
You're the janitor
but no idea what this is?
It's for picking up trash.
You're also a janitor?
I'm the janitor.
I'm the security guard.
(The proud owner of a
very long dream stick)
Is there anything on the tree?
Surely they didn't mess with the tree.
What's this?
Ribbons?
Is it?
I don't think so.
Every tree has one.
It's not.
Is that it though?
Probably not.
We're not staying on this side.
This side would be.
Because this is 107,
and going that way the numbers go up.
Ours are 202 and 204.
That's so far.
(He Wen's room area)
(An Er's room area)
(Jin Xiangyu and An Yi's room area)
What's this?
This is
a drone?
Is that a drone?
A drone!
(Drone)
Let me...
Let me thread this.
Should we just knock it down?
Catch it.
Yeah, give it a nudge.
Just a nudge.
Got it.
Good.
Watch your hands.
Ultra-quiet drone.
Max load: under five kilograms.
There's fishing line tied to it.
(Fishing line attached
to all four rotors)
Isn't that blood on it?
(Blood found on the drone)
It smells like blood.
"Two. Enough to die."
There's fishing line tied to it.
Max load: under five kilograms.
It flew over carrying something.
They used the drone
to carry two liters of blood over,
then
shattered the glass
to fake the scene as
the primary crime scene.
(Theory: drone carried blood weapon)
They flew it over.
(Smashes the courtyard glass)
So the glass box
was filled with blood.
Right.
And doesn't losing
two liters of blood
mean certain death?
Yes.
(Fun fact:)
How long to drain two liters of blood?
(An adult's total blood volume is
approximately 4-5 liters)
(Losing more than 50% at once
(approx. 2-2.5 liters))
(is typically fatal)
Doesn't matter.
It could be drained slowly,
because the body
never needed to go to the courtyard.
Right.
They wanted us to believe
the victim died in that instant.
All to manufacture an alibi.
Exactly.
(Current case summary)
(Victim: unknown)
(Location of death: unknown)
(Time of death: 2016.3.24,
exact time unknown)
(Cause of death: unknown)
There's still one thing
we haven't confirmed.
How did Master end up
inside in the first place?
(Why was An Yi in the wine cellar?)
We definitely need to ask An Yi
what happened when he came face to face
with the killer in that wine cellar.
Yes.
(Rest and recharge)
(Resting resets battle fatigue)
(Recharging restores energy)
(To go the distance in the dungeon,)
(treat rest and recharge
as passive skills)
Alright.
We just
gathered a lot of evidence.
Time to discuss
and start
cracking this case.
(Focused interrogation:
10-minute time limit)
(Goal: detectives initiate a trial)
(targeting a designated suspect or NPC)
(for a 10-minute timed interrogation)
(to advance the investigation)
Let's recap
what we know so far.
We're fairly certain
there is someone
from 2030
who, after years of abusing their child,
had a change of heart.
At some point, they learned
about
a way to travel through time,
so they wanted to go back
to 2016,
the year their child was born
to make things right.
Their plan, most likely,
was to kill their past self
and take their place
with a new identity,
to raise their child all over again.
So they traveled back from 2016,
March 25th,
at 9:50 PM, arrived here.
(Security guard: "Sir, a strange
green light appeared in the lobby")
We still can't pinpoint
the exact time and place
the killer committed the murder.
But what we know for certain is,
(Killer's timeline)
everyone went back after ten.
(10PM Everyone in their own rooms)
And everyone had a two-minute window
(22:02 Ning goes to Ding's room)
without alibis.
(Wen, Jin, and He head to Ke's room)
That was the window for the crime.
In those two minutes,
we're almost certain
the one thing they
definitely could have done
was swap identities.
(10-10:02PM Identity swap)
Exactly.
But it's not confirmed
they killed anyone yet,
because from 10:02 to midnight,
(10:02PM-12AM Alibis established)
they were busy building
(12AM Everyone returns to their rooms)
a rock-solid alibi.
Right.
Another thing we need to consider
is we assumed the body's
primary crime scene was
the ground-floor courtyard.
And that courtyard,
(Scan range)
from midnight to 3 PM,
(No signs of life detected)
had absolutely no
living presence
detected in it.
That's actually
part of the alibi too.
Exactly.
And the evidence we just found
actually supports that theory.
We found a drone
in the tree.
A drone.
And on the drone
it says it's
max load is under five kilograms.
That's just enough to carry
the glass box we found.
And inside the glass box
were two liters of blood
(Golden Years Glass Mirror Box,
An Glass Group)
They set up a
blood-and-mirror crime scene
in the courtyard as a fake crime scene.
Before that,
they also placed
prepared glass shards on the body
along with leaves found nearby
to mislead us into thinking
the primary crime scene
was the courtyard.
Meaning
the victim, from start to finish,
never left this villa.
(So where exactly was
the primary crime scene?)
(Current case summary)
(Victim: unknown.
Location of death: inside the villa)
(Time of death: 2016.3.24-3.25)
Now that An Yi's recovered,
(Cause of death: unknown)
he's awake.
Let's question him.
You're having a meeting?
A meeting.
Have a seat.
Should I sit here?
Obviously.
Where else would you sit?
I'm grabbing my golf club.
You criminal.
Let me ask you.
You were supposed to be
asleep in your room at ten.
So why were you moved to
the secret wine cellar?
I don't quite remember.
Do we need to beat it out of you?
(Reverse "education")
No confession without a beating.
I only remember it's after midnight,
but I can't recall the exact time.
Okay, so tell us what happened
after midnight.
I heard something
rustling downstairs.
I went down to check,
and I saw a puppet.
(An Yi's timeline)
(After12AM: sees puppet
in the ground-floor lobby)
It was rummaging through the cabinet
downstairs.
Then it knocked me out.
When I woke up,
I was tied up in the wine cellar.
So after midnight,
the puppet was active.
(The puppet was active after midnight)
(Noted)
Do you have any memory of
what happened to you
while you were in the wine cellar?
You were knocked unconscious.
How could you possibly know
what happened while you were out?
Of course we know.
When we got hit...
When you hit us,
we were wide awake for all of it.
We all remember...
Hold on.
Let me answer this first.
Unless I was dreaming,
being knocked out means
I'd have no idea how I was
dragged to that place
and tied up.
(Solid logic, gotta admit)
So before midnight,
after ten,
what were you doing?
Before midnight...
After we left your room
and locked the door,
what were you doing?
Tossing and turning. Couldn't sleep.
You were just lying in your room?
Yes.
Doing nothing?
(An Yi's timeline)
(21:57 After everyone left,)
(An Yi stayed in his room)
I saw the puppet at my bedroom door.
(Sees the puppet again)
It appeared when I first
got back to my room too.
When did you get back?
Around 9:51.
(An Yi's timeline)
At my bedroom door,
(21:51 Sees the puppet in the hallway)
there's a mirror, right?
(21:55 Calls everyone to his room)
A flash
(21:57 When everyone left, An Yi stayed)
of a very pale figure went past it.
(12AM Sees the puppet again
in the ground-floor lobby)
Can you confirm it was the same puppet
as the one you saw downstairs?
Should be the same.
Same one.
(Confirmed: same puppet)
Alright.
There's a wine cellar
in our house downstairs.
Besides you, who else
knows about it?
The wine cellar? I don't know.
You don't know?
Right.
That was my first time
in that wine cellar.
(Tui City Tabloid)
Ground-floor lobby reveals
(Interview: The Comeback Queen)
a secret wine cellar with a punch.
The killer knew,
why?
Because they came back
from 2030.
Exactly.
(The killer, from post-2030,)
(knew the wine cellar existed)
So, they knew about the wine cellar.
So after knocking him out,
they locked him in the cellar.
Right.
Are you the only one who knew where
(The 2L glass mirror box)
was that glass box of yours?
Or...
That glass box.
The two-liter one.
That glass box?
Yeah, where did you put it?
That glass box
was in the ground-floor lobby.
You didn't know?
Right there in the lobby cabinet.
I thought everyone
in the An family knew.
It was out in the open.
It wasn't a secret, after all.
(All suspects knew where
the glass box was kept)
Okay, there's something I want to ask.
Go ahead.
About how you treated us growing up,
what do you have to say for yourself?
Fair enough.
How exactly did I treat you?
Ruled by the stick.
(Don't pretend you've forgotten)
When I was young,
you called me worthless every day.
(An Xiaoning's excellence plan)
You made me
follow a schedule you set
for me every single day.
And if I didn't meet your expectations,
you'd hit me with a golf club.
What do you think about that?
What do you say?
(I deserve an answer)
But look at you all.
You're all still here, aren't you?
Are you physically unwell in any way?
Or what?
Physically we're all doing great.
Psychologically, not so much.
Psychologically how?
Every aspect of their
psychology is messed up.
All four of them.
So these psychological issues
are what caused them
to behave the way they did?
Why would they act out like that
if not because of
the damage you did to them as children?
Are you mixing these two things
together now?
Of course.
Can you even separate them?
This is the wound
from my own upbringing.
I simply used a different
style of parenting.
Wasn't that for your own good?
Strict teachers make great students.
Strict fathers raise filial sons.
Shall I give you
an example?
Go ahead.
Someone cheated.
(Don't go throwing mud)
Don't bring up my affair.
(He didn't know beforehand)
Was it even an affair?
Before I married you,
I had no idea
she came with a "bonus".
She came with "extra baggage".
Am I even talking about that right now?
Jin Xiangyu,
then tell us!
Who is that child's real father?
That child's father...
Do you dare say it
in front of everyone?
Step up.
That's not right.
When I was with him,
you were nowhere in the picture.
(Hold on)
How dare you!
Wait a second!
(Can't wait even a second)
How dare you!
(Voice cracking with rage)
You had problem hitting people,
but you stay silent about that?
Did I say anything about that?
(Things getting chaotic)
Is that what I asked you?
(Sit down and cool off)
I'm talking about when you hit the kids!
Why are you coming at me?
Alright,
it's fine.
It's okay.
Okay.
You should say something to him.
You two went first.
Go get him.
(This detective
desperately needs backup)
I raised you all this way
because I wanted you
to amount to something.
(Let me collect myself)
I owe everyone an apology.
Not for the way I raised you,
but for bringing a woman
like her into your lives
during the busiest chapter of my career
as your mother.
Don't hit an old man.
That's it.
So it wasn't your fault.
Because my mom never once stopped you.
Right, she never stopped you.
Never said anything either.
(Changed your tune, huh?
Forgot about your ex-mom?)
I genuinely want all of you to succeed.
I want you to look at things
on a bigger scale.
This isn't just about
our individual families.
This is about our entire clan.
Get out.
(Leave now)
(Don't come back)
Nobody asked you.
Get out.
Someone drag him out.
Someone help!
She cracked,
honestly.
How much time is left?
Our detectives are losing it.
(If you push me, I get fluffy)
I'm filing for divorce when I get back.
Meeting adjourned.
An Yi mentioned
he saw the puppet rummaging downstairs.
I'll go check
if there are any missed clues.
Okay.
I was
clearly
standing up for them just now.
I was right there,
putting myself on the line,
and not one of you...
You four...
(Awkward smiles.gif)
Nothing.
I wanted to back you up,
but he said
you didn't have a leg to stand on.
You really didn't.
Anyone who went through that
would be hurting.
On that particular matter,
(Yi)
he really did suffer.
Yi?
You two get along now?
Wait.
Yeah, An Yi.
He's your friend now?
An Yi really did go through a lot.
Right?
You pulled a neat
disappearing act there.
Never mind them not helping.
Someone tries to help,
and you shoot them down.
You had no ground
to stand on. Don't help.
For real, no ground at all.
(Cinderfella can't be trusted)
Something familiar's turned up.
What is it?
"Knockout drops."
(10ml syringe: "Knockout drops")
And there's also a tube
of blood.
(Why are there syringes
and knockout drops here?)
It's obvious.
Step one.
Step two.
(An Ke's theory on the murder steps)
Step three leads to dead.
(1. Sedate the victim)
(2. Draw/drain the blood)
(3. Death by blood loss)
The blood-drawing tool
basically confirms that
after sedating the victim,
they started pumping out the blood.
Collecting it up to two liters.
About the method of draining the blood,
for example,
if I used another method to drain it,
blood could spray everywhere.
But drawing it slowly this way...
(Theory: using a syringe
prevents blood from splattering)
If they drew it this way,
only a hundred milliliters at a time.
This syringe only holds ten milliliters.
They'd need over two hundred draws.
Wait.
(Two hundred syringes)
Two hundred syringes.
Good grief.
What does that tell you?
It tells us
the blood-drawing process
would take a very long time.
(The killer needed ample
time to draw the blood)
Drawing that much blood
would definitely take a long time.
Right.
So it had to be after midnight.
Yeah, after midnight.
(Current case summary)
(Victim: unknown)
(Location of death: inside the villa)
(Time of death: 2016.3.25, 12AM-3PM)
(Cause of death: blood loss)
So,
whose child is Ding?
He is
my child.
(Father-son relationship confirmed)
And you are...
I'm your father's daughter.
No...
Before blood, you are...
His daughter.
Then I'm his son too.
We all grew up under him.
So to speak.
(Family breakdown)
(An Xiaoning, An Xiaowen, An Xiaoding
were raised under An Yi)
(An Yi's brother: An Ke)
I wasn't raised by him.
I'm his little brother.
(Neither was raised under An Yi)
We were both raised by An Songqiu.
Suddenly being
reminded you're his equal
made me realize something.
If they came back through time,
they might have killed themselves,
or possibly the father.
(Jin Xiangyu's theory: killing oneself
or An Yi share the same motive)
Because they were
beaten by An Yi as a child,
and now their own child
has suffered because of them.
So, they travel back,
not only to kill their past self,
but also to take out their
father while they're at it.
Right.
But since we're equals,
An Yi has no power over me.
I'd just knock him out
and leave him somewhere.
(Jin Xiangyu's theory: An Ke
has no motive to kill An Yi)
He bears no real hatred toward An Yi,
so he just loosely
tied him up and left him there.
Right.
One tug and it comes undone.
(Suspect list)
(Defense)
I believe none of us
would ever accept
committing patricide.
Even if you had
every reason in the world
to despise your own father.
Fair point.
Otherwise yesterday's
victim wouldn't be An Er,
it'd be An Yi.
Exactly.
(Suspect list)
Agreed.
Right.
But you've thought out your wording.
I think that's clever.
Because right now
we have no more leads.
(Let's work from motive)
Let's try working from motive.
In 2026, my child
left me.
I was devastated.
But my husband
is still with me in 2030.
I wouldn't want to go back to 2016
to change any of that.
I mean,
as long as my husband
is there, that's enough.
(An Xiaowen's defense: husband in 2030)
I have no reason to go back.
(No urgent reason to return to 2016)
I don't think that holds up.
Because going back to 2016
means you could start over
with a better life with your husband.
All I'm saying is,
in 2030,
I still have someone to lean on.
I get what you mean.
Actually, that point lines up well
with something I've been thinking.
It connects.
Which is
all four of you
have different kinds
of "violence" in your parenting.
Right?
(All suspects used some form
of "violence" in parenting)
So what's the difference
between the four types?
One,
straightforward physical violence.
(Physical violence)
Physical violence.
You?
You are...
(Emotional violence)
I'm the intimidation type.
Emotional intimidation.
You're actually neglect violence.
(Neglect)
I'm cold neglect.
And he's
belittlement.
(Psychological violence)
I told him he's not good enough,
and will never measure up to who I was.
When it comes to being capable
of actually killing their own past self
and wanting to make amends
for their mistakes,
the most likely candidate I'd say
(Physical violence)
is the physical violence type.
Because there's
real physical capability.
People who don't usually get physical
find it very hard to cross that line.
Right, and there's another thing.
In his testimony,
he was very reluctant to admit
he'd ever been violent.
Because I went through it myself,
and I don't want my
child to suffer the same.
Good bye!
Domestic violence.
So could this mentality
actually means
they deeply despise the part
of themselves they can't control?
(He Jiahuan's reason
for suspecting Ding)
(An Xiaoding repeated the very behavior
he hated, leading to self-loathing)
(and physical violence aligns
more with the act of murder)
Right.
Possibly.
They want to destroy their former self.
Yeah, when they see themselves,
that hatred just
wells up naturally.
(He Jiahuan's suspect)
Wait.
But we all did things
we didn't want to do
if thinking about it that way.
You all just found different ways
to express the same thing.
Right?
We all ended up doing it anyway.
Let me put it this way.
The others believed
they were doing the right thing.
But,
you knew you were doing wrong,
and you did it anyway.
Right.
(Actions contradict beliefs)
You said he can't control himself.
Which means that loss of control
could extend to committing murder.
And also,
the reason I think
physical violence could be relevant
is that type might be more likely
to actually carry out
the act of killing.
Can't control himself.
Hand, don't do this...
These aren't my hands.
These are the devil's hands.
I see where you're going.
Let me then lay out
the 10PM logic.
(Ding's rebuttal)
If I were the killer,
wouldn't I be actively seeking out
an alibi for myself?
(Rebuttal: who sought out an alibi?)
Right?
Right.
Wouldn't I have proactively reached out,
gone to someone else's side and said,
"I didn't do anything"?
Yeah, exactly.
But I was just staying in my room.
(No alibi actively created)
After ten,
I was in my room.
My dad was the one who came to me.
Fair enough.
That alone is enough
to reduce his suspicion.
Definitely.
Reduced suspicion.
Right, agreed.
I think there's still one key question.
Who was most likely to
have swapped identities
in those two minutes?
(Key question: who had the
best chance to swap identities?)
(Key question: who was most vulnerable
to being killed in those two minutes?)
That's actually a good angle.
Just focus on those two minutes.
Basically,
who could have been killed at 10:02?
Right.
(Key question: who was most vulnerable
to being killed in those two minutes?)
Let's fully reconstruct
how the swap happened
in those two minutes.
Actually, it's simple.
Let me walk you through it.
(Timeline breakdown)
From midnight to 3 PM,
(Killer's crime window: 12AM-3PM)
that entire window was available.
Right.
Exactly.
Because from 10:02 to midnight,
(Killer's crime window: 12AM-3PM)
during that time,
(Killer's alibi window: 10:02PM-12AM)
the killer thought
they were building a foolproof alibi.
Because they believed
the courtyard could be
faked as the crime scene.
Which means
the killer only needed two time slots
to do two things.
First,
from 10PM to 10:02PM,
(Killer swaps identities: 10PM-10:02PM)
swap identities.
Then stay put.
After that,
establish an alibi
at 10:02PM.
So just look at from 10PM to 10:02PM,
(10PM-10:02PM movements)
who could've done this.
First, Ding
(An Xiaoding: stayed in his own room)
don't have a chance.
He didn't reach out to anyone.
So I think
his suspicion can be ruled out.
(Suspicion cleared)
(Currently most suspicious)
(10PM-10:02PM: Xiaoding: stayed in room)
What about me?
(Ke: called Jin and He come to his room)
I called you two.
(Ning: went to find An Xiaoding)
Ning went to find his son.
(Wen: wandering the halls)
Wen was wandering.
(Ran into Jin and He)
Just wandering.
Honestly,
"wandering" is a bit thin.
She didn't proactively
seek anyone out either.
(Comparatively less proactive)
Yeah, slightly less suspicious.
But she still needed someone to see her.
Right, she's still under suspicion.
(Suspicion ranking: An Ke, An Xiaoning
> An Xiaowen > An Xiaoding)
So,
if we're going to vote right now,
do we have a consensus
that it's one of these three?
My range is down to those two.
Either her or him.
(An Ke's suspect list)
Both Ning and I
better fit the criteria.
Right.
The two of us are
(Both were equally proactive)
equally proactive.
But her "wandering",
that really throws me off.
Sounds so flimsy.
Right.
So flimsy.
Because take Ding as an example,
"I just sat there.
I didn't go to anyone."
That I can accept.
But if you tell me you were wandering,
how do I know
you weren't on your way to find someone?
Right?
Or what?
Wen, explain yourself.
(Hard to be convincing)
This whole "wandering" story.
(Wen's rebuttal)
Alright.
Here it is.
Let me explain why I was wandering.
He and his new mom
were in our room picking out gifts,
so you couldn't go back.
Right.
So I couldn't go back to my room.
Then she's actually safer,
because the killer wouldn't
know where she was.
What do you mean the killer
wouldn't know where she was?
If I wanted to replace her identity,
first, she couldn't go back.
Her room is shared with him.
But you two were together.
He couldn't replace me.
I was wandering the halls.
He couldn't replace her,
because he didn't know where she was.
(An Xiaoning's theory:)
Right?
Could that be it?
(The puppet couldn't know
An Xiaowen's exact whereabouts)
That checks out.
So who do you think it is?
(An Xiaowen's suspects:)
I think it's one of those two.
(An Ke, An Xiaoning)
Of those two,
(Xiaowen believes Ke is more suspicious)
his suspicion is higher.
Because killers
are usually on edge.
I'd be afraid something
at the crime scene
might have slipped through.
(Working from the killer's mindset)
The killer wouldn't leave their room.
Once they've handled everything
from their room,
they'd stay hidden inside.
Where's safest?
Their own room.
Whereas Ning
left his room.
So,
he doesn't seem nervous
about what's in his room.
(An Xiaoning's doesn't act guilty)
He was fine going to other's room.
I think actively seeking someone
out makes you more suspicious.
Okay.
(An Xiaowen believes:
the killer is An Ke)
My top two
are these two.
(An Xiaoding's suspects:
An Ke, An Xiaowen)
(An Xiaoding's suspect list)
Wen and Ke.
Right.
One was wandering around outside.
That's very suspicious to me.
For me,
(Ruling out An Xiaoning)
His motive makes complete sense.
As my new dad,
coming to find me
about two minutes in.
I think that makes total sense.
That's your angle.
That's his starting point.
That's my thinking.
Okay.
Let me add something.
If you're going by the logic
of who sought out
who that night,
I was also looking for my wife and son.
(An Ke's counterpoint: he share
the same motive with An Xiaoning)
But I tend to side with him here.
When looking for your wife and son,
of course it's easier
to just go to them.
Why would you call them
on the phone to say,
"Hey, you two come over."
"I miss you both,"
"please come."
That seems a bit...
(Rejected)
Got it.
I get his motive now.
He wanted to build an alibi,
but was also worried the victim
might wake up.
He couldn't relax.
So he'd need to make sure
the body stayed somewhere
no one would find.
Where? Right underneath you.
(An Xiaowen's theory: after being
sedated, the victim was in An Ke's room)
Is that it?
So under that sofa we're sitting on,
there was a body.
That's wild.
Ke, that's insane.
That night, maybe we
were literally sitting on top of a body,
just chatting and laughing.
My point is the same.
(Ke's second rebuttal)
If you're using
so-called "guilt"
to cement my suspicion,
first, are you sure the
body was under the bed?
Okay, but if I were guilty,
would I invite four people into my room
to sit right on top of a body?
That'd take serious nerve.
Wouldn't that make me
the opposite of nervous?
(An Ke's counterpoint: if guilty,)
(you wouldn't invite people
to the crime scene)
And Ning,
you said Wen was wandering,
and the killer wouldn't
know where she was.
But what if the killer
had already arrived at 9:50?
Right.
At that point,
if they were watching
us from the shadows,
there's no way they wouldn't know
where their target was at all times.
(An Ke's counterpoint 2:)
They'd follow her.
(The killer would tail the target)
Track her.
Say I'm Wen.
I'm here tonight.
Right now I'm on the second floor.
I arrive through the portal and watch.
Okay,
you're heading that way, right?
Same logic.
After knocking them out,
where would you put the body?
Seriously, if it's An Xiaowen,
where would she put it?
Anywhere.
Because
no one expected anyone to die,
so say by the glass door.
The body could literally be anywhere.
That I agree with.
(An Ke's prime suspect)
Are you voting Wen?
Yes.
Who are you voting?
I think it's those two.
Definitely those two.
Alright, let's vote.
(Can they name the killer?)
Whoever proactively sought someone out
was probably trying hard
to establish an alibi.
So I think
the one who stayed in their room,
An Ke,
is the most suspicious.
(Voting window: An Ke)
I am An Ke,
and I cast my vote...
(Voting window)
I think his and Ke's
suspicion is the highest.
My vote goes to
(Voting window)
If someone
from 2030
came back to 2016
to
kill their past self,
my vote
goes to...
I'm voting...
Ke is most suspicious.
Because
if the crime happened in the room,
they could stash the body
right there in their own room,
(Voting window: An Ke)
then deliberately call people in
to their room
to immediately
establish an alibi.
(Voting complete. Case archived)
No deduction needed for travel,
save more with Tongcheng.
Now, brought to you
by Tongcheng Travel, moment of truth.
In today's case,
the suspects are:
An Xiaoning,
An Xiaowen,
An Xiaoding,
An Ke.
After deliberation,
three suspects
received votes.
(Three of the four
suspects received votes)
The three suspects who received votes
are:
An Xiaoning,
An Xiaowen,
An Ke.
(An Xiaoding received 0 votes)
If Ding was
actually the killer,
then
we should just quit.
If Ding's the killer, he'd be a legend.
Zero votes and escaped scot-free.
Zero votes and free. That's untouchable.
The ultimate mastermind.
It's me.
The suspect with the most votes is
An Ke.
All players who voted for An Ke,
please stand up.
That many votes!
(An Ke received 4 votes total)
(Voting segment)
My vote
was
Ke.
(An Ke)
Just now during
the case breakdown,
when I
mentioned
Ding's
form of violence was
the most direct.
Meaning
that
he used physical violence.
So, at the time I thought
he'd be
more likely to kill.
But then I thought about it.
If he wanted to kill his past self,
he must have had
a deep, deep hatred
for who he used to be.
It was probably just
in that one moment
when he came face to face with himself,
that he thought,
"Why haven't you changed?"
Something like that.
For the other three,
by 2016,
they had already realized
what their father did to them was wrong.
Ke is the most unique one.
Faced with his father's
way of raising him,
his way of dealing with the abuse
was
to
run away and grovel.
Me?
I rarely got hit,
because I was good at begging for mercy.
I knew when to back down.
I'd admit fault.
He thought
that was the right way to handle things.
And
although he
survived that way,
he still ended up doing well,
I thought there was
nothing wrong with it.
Although growing up
like that
was painful,
I went
on to become
a highly successful glass artist.
(Vote: An Ke)
When it turns out
his child
left him,
he would definitely
feel a deep rejection
toward his 2016 self.
An intense disgust.
So at this moment,
only Ke
would have a genuine,
real motive
to kill
his 2016 self.
(Vote: An Ke)
I've given Ning
my good-guy pass.
So, the suspect
comes down to either
Wen or Ke.
I think whoever
would most want
to go back from 2030
to the past
would be someone with
nothing holding them back.
And the one with the
least to lose is An Ke.
Ning.
My reason is
he didn't want anyone in his room.
That could be because his own room
was where he hid the body.
I'm casting my vote
for An Xiaowen.
In my opinion,
her movements
at 10PM and 10:02PM
are the most suspicious
of all suspects today.
(Voting results)
(An Ke: An Xiaowen, An Xiaoding,
He Jiahuan, An Xiaoning)
(An Xiaoning: Jin Xiangyu)
(An Xiaowen: An Ke)
It was me.
So, did everyone get it right?
Did this case end in success
or failure?
(Is An Ke the real culprit?)
The suspect has been identified...
Hold on.
Or not?
(Not yet!)
or not?
Hold on.
The suspect
has been identified.
(Unlock the detective team's
best moments early)
(At every Tuesday noon,
Dungeon Unlocking)
(Case resolved: culprit identified!)
(An Xiaowen, An Xiaoding,
He Jiahuan, An Xiaoning)
(The culprit)
Give us a smile!
I was the only one
who didn't vote for him!
Clueless detective.
(Stumbling)
You guys are incredible.
I gave it everything I had.
It was tough.
So tough this round.
(The lone-wolf culprit)
Maybe that's just how it goes.
Now we'll reveal
the key evidence everyone missed.
The label on the dry-cleaning bag.
The label on the dry-cleaning bag
had some imprints on it.
(Sterilization log)
You can rub a pencil over it
to reveal the text:
"At 58,
I'm saying goodbye to this world."
The culprit wrote this
as a farewell note
when deciding to leave 2030,
and the writing
transferred onto this label.
In 2030,
only An Ke is 58 years old.
(Age: 58)
So it was?
(Uncover the story behind the scenes)
(At every Thursday noon,
Dungeon Archiving)
You can draw that.
So next time,
we'll have to rub every
piece of paper with a pencil.
Did you know about this clue?
I did.
He knew
fools like us couldn't find it.
I should be ranked number one
from the bottom.
No, I'll be last place with you.
Yeah.
Only two people
got a Golden Key yesterday.
So we're both tied for first now.
Golden Keys will be
distributed in the game lobby.
(Game lobby)
Please claim your reward
from your first game dungeon,
part 1 and 2.
You have earned golden keys.
Two of them.
(Player Zhang Linghe: Golden Key ×2)
(Player Ding Chengxin: Golden Key ×2)
Are these Golden Keys
actually gold?
(Player Liu Yuning: Golden Key ×1)
Alright.
The number of Golden Keys I have
wouldn't fit
in one basket.
Right?
I'd need to walk
a whole lap around this place.
(Schrödinger's Golden Keys)
(Teaching Ke: world-class
mime performance)
Okay.
Too many.
Won't fit.
Alright, all collected.
What?
(Ding dong)
It should've been an empty drawer.
Why do I have a Golden Key?
I'm really touched.
(Limited-time player settling up)
When I was scared to tears,
sweet Jin
stayed right by my side and kept saying,
"Don't be scared,"
even though she was terrified herself.
Scared to tears.
Hurry.
It's okay. I'm scared of the dark.
It's okay.
Okay.
We're good.
Close your eyes.
It's fine.
We left you behind.
Sorry.
Don't look.
I've got you.
We're right behind you.
(Soothes)
We're safe now.
Everyone else did great too,
but I want to give
my personal MVP award
to Jin.
Help me pass this to her.
Pass along my love.
An Xiaowen.
(A gift from the limited-time player)
(Gifted keys aren't counted in rankings)
You're such a good friend.
(Can only be used to redeem Skill Cards)
An Xiaowen,
thank you so much.
Golden Key distribution complete.
(Golden Key leaderboard)
(Zhang Linghe, TNT-Ding Chengxin:
Golden Key ×2)
(Liu Yuning, Wang Yuwen: Golden Key ×1)
(Jin Jing, Zhou Keyu: Golden Key ×0)
Dungeon World Two is loading.
Matching a limited-time player.
Players, please enter
the transit portal.
Welcome aboard the
Tongcheng Travel Time Tunnel.
Entering the dungeon world.
I am your guide,
Tongcheng Travel's Fei Ermeng.
Please collect your
exclusive dungeon passes,
change costume and transform.
Get ready to go!
Just investigate with confidence.
I've got you covered!
Let's go together with Tongcheng!
(Player Liu Yuning, online.
Character "Ning Bubble" claimed)
(Player Jin Jing, online.
Character "Jin Cardashian" claimed)
(Player Zhang Linghe, online.
Character "He Yiwei" claimed)
(Player TNT-Ding Chengxin, online.
Character "Ding Pudding" claimed)
(Player Zhou Keyu, online.
Character "Ke Coffee Bean" claimed)
(Limited-time player Sun Qian, online.
Character "Qian Jinding" claimed)
(Dungeon Two loading)
(Now that you've made it
through Dungeon One,)
(what thoughts and
feelings are you left with?)
An Ke's upbringing
actually resonates with me
on some level.
When I saw all those notes An Si,
(Little bro, don't be scared. Dad says)
Ke's brother
(the bad wolf comes if you don't sleep)
left behind for him,
(But I'll chase it away)
I thought of my own brother.
(Little bro, don't cry.
I will protect you)
I've always been really
close to my brother.
In so many moments of growing up,
facing challenges,
and not knowing what to do,
it was often my brother
who was there with me.
He was the one who stayed by my side.
(Footage from the internet)
Keep going!
But he's not exactly someone...
I can't say he struggles
to express himself,
actually he's very expressive.
But he'd never really say things like,
you know,
"I'll always be here to protect you."
or "I'll be there for you."
He just showed it through actions.
by genuinely showing up for me,
or finding real ways to help me.
So seeing An Ke's brother, An Si
treat him the same way.
It immediately reminded me
of my own experiences.
Honestly,
I don't have any
weaknesses in the daytime.
My only fear is the dark.
When I was little,
my dad was always busy.
He worked at the company
and always stayed late.
He'd go out for work
dinners and not come home.
And my mom was a big mahjong fan.
So as a kid,
after I'd fallen asleep,
my mom would
quietly
sneak upstairs to play
mahjong with the neighbors.
Little me would wake up.
And the house
was completely dark.
Nobody home.
I called
my mom so loud
but there was no response.
I was terrified.
From that point on,
I was scared every night.
(Footage from the internet)
My cats and dogs
are for company.
Like my dog,
as long as it slept next to me,
and I could hear
its steady breathing,
I felt completely safe.
(Have you ever made it
up to your younger self?)
The way I made it up to my younger self
was by completely changing
who I was.
As a kid, I never talked.
Very introverted.
Always shut away in my room.
Hated having my photo taken.
I really hated it as a kid.
But actually, it wasn't
that I totally disliked it.
I think kids,
teenagers especially
are in this awkward phase.
They actually really want something
but are too embarrassed to show it,
so they do the opposite.
But as an adult,
I want to be someone who's honest.
I no longer hide
what I truly love.
I no longer pretend to be
a cool girl.
In the An family,
every child grew up
being
put down.
And as kids,
they grew up thinking
their father
or mother
was supposed
to raise a child like that.
Harsh, crushing, and threatening.
We also came to realize
that An Yi
was a victim himself,
(An Songqiu)
because he was raised
by An Songqiu the same way.
He simply didn't know
how to love someone
without hurting them.
Looking back at how I grew up at home,
there was a big difference
between how my grandpa raised my dad
and how my dad raised me.
My grandpa's generation
was a lot stricter with
my dad's generation.
My mom and dad were
"more progressive"
with me,
more free-range
in a way.
Maybe it's because my dad,
through how my grandpa raised him,
recognized some of those issues.
So when it came
to raising me, he'd
already made changes.
So in the future,
if I ever have my own kids,
if I get that chance,
I'll think carefully about
what kind of parenting would be better.
Growing up, An Xiaoding
was regularly
abused.
He lived in constant fear.
(Ding, just remember)
I think those experiences
(Bowl is expensive, don't break it)
are what made him grow up to be
(An the wolf always swatted the rabbbit)
picky, short-tempered,
and vain.
But all those flaws,
they're
more like armor
he built to protect himself.
True growth,
I think,
isn't doing what An Xiaoding did,
carrying that pain and fighting
the world with it.
It's learning
to let go of those fears inside,
to face the pain honestly.
Like talking to someone he trust,
or learning healthier ways
to express his emotions,
or
(Find better ways to express yourself)
seeking professional help.
I think
even though the past can't be changed,
we can still
gradually take back
the steering wheel
of our own lives.
In reality,
there are
many parents
trapped in the same cycle.
They were hurt as children,
and without realizing it,
they pass that same
experience onto
their own children
exactly as they received it.
And that keeps the pain
cycling through generations.
Let our children
have a childhood
they don't have to spend
a lifetime healing from.
What would you say to your younger self?
I'd tell them:
"You're going to be amazing."
"You'll become a big star."
"Millions of people will love you."
"So, keep holding on to
everything you believe in."
"Love everything you love."
I'd say something like that too.
That's touching.
Wen.
Ding.
Ke.
Ning.
All four of them
treated their own children
the same way their parents
once treated them.
They thought it was right.
But in reality,
their love carried a lot
of generational trauma.
They thought they
were loving their kids,
but that love
often ended up causing
a different kind of harm.
Before becoming a parent,
take time to look back at your own past.
What generational trauma do you carry?
What wounds have you lived with?
Be kind to yourself.
Gentle.
Give a real hug
to the part of you that was hurt.
A child is the author of their own life.
What that means is
they get to decide
where their story goes.
As parents,
we can't just decide
what's good and what's right,
(Dr. Chen Haixian, Zhejiang University)
and turn their book of life
(Bestselling psychology author)
into your own book.
You can't take from your child
the right to author
their own life.
(Dungeon Two preview)
Starlight Cafe.
With my three gold cards in hand,
today
I
am getting coffee.
Coming to this cafe every day
make me feel so lucky.
I'm spinning.
Being here together,
we're all
like family now,
so we'll just refer to each other
(Bait in the cup)
as family.
I've noticed the cafe customers
are all loaded.
For the next step,
I have a new idea.
She's calling us out.
Who's coming with me?
I'll top up her card.
We're clean,
inside and out.
As for you lot,
that's another story.
(Eyes in the walls)
Go take a look
at what he's been up to.
This must be the boss'
secret back office.
There are cameras in there.
We've all been
recorded without knowing.
You changing in here
is all caught
on camera!
Running VIP group service,
and spreading those videos around.
Who cares about a dead person,
as long as there's money to be made?
What is this?
Wait! What is this?
(Something's off inside)
This cafe
is far more sinister than you think.
To get rich,
first go crazy!
Do whatever it takes and push forward!
Financial freedom is not a dream!
This isn't one of those
stereotypical compounds!
It's violent,
wild and empty!
Talking nonsense!
Isn't this a scam?
Own you.
Control you.
Crime.
Slander you.
Prey on you.
Don't you realize
you've all
already been hired?
You.
And you.
We're all scum.
When I find that person,
I'll kill them.
I did something bad for you once.
You have no spine.
No heart either.
So I'm the killer.
To reel in high-value clients,
you have to play hard to get.
Like this.
We lay low.
So who is this person?
Why are they helping us?
(VIP or victim?)
(Dungeon Archives)
I am the killer,
(2030, An Ke)
An Ke from 2030.
(SVIP, every Thursday at noon)
I'm a time traveler.
(VIP, next day at noon)
I use the advantage of knowing
the future to build a perfect scheme
and clear my name.
(An Ke age 58 / An Ke age 44)
Kill him.
Replace him.
It's the only way out for young Ke.
Protect the child.
Expose the curse's lie.
Little train.
(Truth Clubhouse)
(SVIP, every Friday at noon)
I'm clearly the boss.
(VIP, next day at noon)
Right?
(All employees)
They're all my employees.
How does the wedding march go again?
(Best man singing along live)
(Zhou knows his stuff)
Showing off the waist, right?
The waist is here.
(Truly all legs from the neck down)
"Little bunny, open up"
"the door!"
(Volume up)
Open it for me!
(Bon appetit)
(Truth Supply Station)
I'm not investigating next episode.
(Spot on)
Am I big brother to you?
(Big Daddy)
(SVIP, every Sunday at noon)
(VIP, next day at noon)
There's also a new big bro!
(Xin, big bro)
Yeah. Second bro!
Bro!
Second bro!
(Good boy)
Come on, bolder.
Bolder.
(Dungeon Unlocked)
Bubbles dissolving in coffee.
(SVIP, every Tuesday at noon)
Is that a heartbeat you hear,
(VIP, next day at noon)
or a specialty blend?
Coffee is just a cover.
It falls right into my
hands. Does that count?
Life tastes flat.
Lucky for you. You've met me.
He Yiwei.
This cup is pudding coffee.
You're the extra sugar I added.
My cool level is minus eight degrees.
Crowns may fall,
but the golden top never does.
(Door of Truth Season 4:
airing schedule)
(Dungeon NPC guide)
(Photographer He, played by He Jinghao)
(Butler Wu, played by Wu Bi)
(Janitor, played by Hu Lanying)
(Pai, played by Pai Xiaoxuan)
(Ms. Pai, played by Pai Xiaoxuan)
(An Yi, played by Lin Tan)
(An Er, played by Zhang Xuzhen)
(Puppet, played by Dai Siqi)
(Security Guard, played by Zou Zhihao)
(Dance troupe, performed by 0-DOG)
(Emcee, played by Gong Yingjie)
(Aunt San, played by Wang Gege)
(An Songqiu, played by Chen Xuming)
(Young An Xiaoding,
played by Chen Yujin)
(Young An Xiaowen,
played by Ma Shangqing)
(Young He Jia Huan,
played by Wang Yumo)
(Crazed mother, played by Huang Jin)
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪