=Push the Door Truth Clubhouse=
(An Glass Factory Behind-the-Scenes)
Ding, teach us your hottest move
(Shimmy)
from your latest social media.
(Highlights)
Son, come on.
(Show us what you got)
Show time!
(Ding's Dance Class is in session)
One, two, three, four
(Looking good)
five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two.
Three-da, four-da
That's it.
The An family has An Yi,
An Er, An San.
Actually I'm the hidden An San.
Anshan?
More like Tieling!
(Epic pun)
(Ding's quiz time)
What do you call a god's mount?
(Think about it)
A god's mount...
Baby!
Pokemon?
Yeah, then I'm a Digimon!
(Heir battle, live)
Quick, stand next to Dad!
Dad's favorite son.
(Is this fair?)
Just the three of them?
What about us?
They're a family.
(Don't force it if you don't fit in)
Aren't we family too?
(Mind has stopped working)
Because we are the real family.
(Daily favoritism battle)
Sorry about that.
Why are you always like this?
Am I wrong though?
Stop arguing,
Mom and Dad.
Let us show you
(The uncles are about to serve)
what the uncles are made of!
It'll definitely look like this.
Your beard fell off.
(Don't say it)
(Emergency image management)
(Who owns the meal card rules)
If you have no points,
and you want to eat, just tell me.
Say "Ning,
I want to eat."
(Ning covers everyone's tab)
Let me treat you.
It's fine.
I've got my dad here.
Your dad's got zero points too.
(Meal card: hot commodity)
Your dad...
(Meal card holder #1)
Only we two get to eat.
(Meal card holder #2)
Everyone else has to beg us.
You two are the only ones eating?
(Tears of envy dripping
from the corner of mouths)
(An family heir squad:
poster shoot in progress)
(An Glass Factory: WELCOME)
I figured you'd all go to bed early.
I tried to.
But I can't.
(Can't fall asleep)
I was in bed by eleven.
But I just couldn't sleep.
(Pre-trip jitters)
(Old friends reunite)
Famous Linghe!
Quick!
(The Truth S3 EP05, "Who's Thinking
of Me", The Famous Linghe)
(Ning speaks)
Let's go.
Come on everyone.
Time to work.
(Instantly in motion)
Stand over there.
(Mother-son bonding)
Let me stand with my son.
(Mommy)
Mommy!
You're the youngest generation today.
Not really. We're the same gen.
You're my little brother.
(Master of mishearing)
Your perfume smells so good today.
(Taking a sniff)
Smells amazing.
Brother-in-law, I switched to a new one.
You know what it is?
Fig.
You know what you smell like?
(The Truth S3, Push the Door
Truth Clubhouse EP6, Staff)
Like those sweet-smelling tomatoes.
Really nice.
(Sold)
Looks like we both have the same taste.
(Very refined indeed)
Ning, you look like Monchhichi.
This is totally Monchhichi.
The hair.
What Monchhichi?
This is more like
a rock boy vibe.
(Rock boy)
Liu Xiaobei.
A bit, yeah.
(100% match)
Yours feels more expensive though, why?
Because I'm elegant.
(Elegant)
(I'm also elegant)
Everyone, look more elegant.
(Instantly ready)
More elegant.
That's a bit of a stretch for me.
(Of course not)
Look elegant.
(Am I not elegant enough?)
Not mean.
(Signature Jin Jing)
She looks like a stereotypical stepmom.
(Ouch)
The classic villain type.
(Instantly serious)
Zhang Linghe, could you
tilt your head just a little?
(Suppressing laughter)
He did it on purpose.
(Only Ning gets me)
Alright, look over here.
Everyone.
Three, two, one.
Good.
Jin Jing, move a little closer to Ding.
(Baby steps)
A little closer.
Isn't that a bit too close?
He's still so young.
You're his mom. That's fine.
Mind your own business.
(Thoughtful Ning)
I was just worried you'd feel awkward.
(The calm before the An family storm)
Everyone get ready. We're starting.
That's too many people.
(So many people)
(Ding is shook)
(Nervous)
(Heavy footsteps)
Butler, why do you keep
fobbing me off with this junk.
(Cramming lines)
(Inspecting the furniture)
(Getting ready)
He and Wen, hurry up.
We're waiting on you two.
(Me?)
No, I mean them.
Son, don't be nervous.
(Caring mommy)
Mom won't say a word.
I'm so nervous.
(Really nervous)
(Cutesy version)
Butler,
why do you keep fobbing
me off with this junk?
Butler,
(Cold version)
why do you keep fobbing me off with this junk?
Does this show require brainpower?
(Wen face)
You just need to bring a brain.
(That simple)
Just bring a brain?
Then I'm out.
(Her own worst roast victim)
♪Meeting again♪
(A man lost in the music)
(Acquiring meal card)
Your meal card.
Do you have a meal card?
You don't have one.
You don't have it?
Stick with me,
and you'll eat like royalty.
As long as you don't vote against me.
(Winning hearts)
Just do what I say.
She's my wife.
(Hello, I'm right here)
You're here
flirting...
Trying to pull that on me?
(Forgot something?)
You have a wife...
I forgot.
You're stepmom.
Got a wife and forgot your own mother.
(Mother-in-law is still a mother)
What's your deal with Uncle Ke?
(Wen's instinct)
Uncle Ke?
Are you two connected in the game?
(Popcorn mode)
They definitely are.
We're not.
Probably not.
(Sure bro)
Uncle Ke.
So who's in this? An Yi, An Er...
(Wen wonders)
Why isn't he An Wu?
He is An Wu.
I'm the fifth.
(No contradiction)
Then why is he called An Ke?
Fifth in the An family, but named An Ke.
The An family has An Yi, An Er,
An San, An Si, then An Ke.
An Ke has four older brothers.
What about An Liu, An Qi, An Ba?
(So easy to remember)
An Yi's real name is An Tiezhu.
Bet you didn't know that.
Actually I'm the hidden An San.
Anshan?
(Anshan?)
Anshan? More like Tieling!
You're from Anshan.
Your name's Amino Acid.
(Amino Acid)
Amino Acid.
So what should I call you?
Xiangyu.
Call me Mom.
(Going by seniority)
You gave me a crystal bracelet.
I'll return the favor later.
(999 pure clarity)
That's real crystal?
That's clearly pure glass.
(100% glass)
Pure glass, this is.
I thought they'd make
glass walnuts
or something.
Let me clear out your shopping cart.
Buy it.
(Instantly in character)
You gotta deliver it like a CEO.
Like, "Your shopping cart,"
(Crisp delivery)
"I've cleared it out for you."
(CEO playbook)
Yeah, exactly that vibe.
Ding, give it a try.
(Anticipation)
(Everyone waiting)
Your shopping cart.
I've cleared it.
(Fell for it)
More like a campus romance drama.
(Staring)
You try one.
I can't.
(Improvising)
That "I can't" just now.
By age, Keyu is
- the old...
- youngest
the youngest.
But highest in seniority.
Which month in 2002?
(Curious)
May 2002.
Taurus?
Yep.
2002.
How old does that make you?
Twenty-four.
Are you even an adult?
(Gen Z shook)
Aren't you also a Taurus?
I'm Gemini.
You're Gemini too?
Okay, give it back to me.
That's my prop.
(Reclaiming the glass bracelet)
This is my prop.
Mine.
What?
(But you said you'd give it to me)
Actors need something to work with.
This is my anchor.
(Looking him up and down)
Why is this
thing so long?
(Waterfall tie)
It's the look.
The idea is that when he's seated,
we can step on it so he
can't stand up.
No, I'm waiting for
someone to lead me by it.
Like this.
(Ready and waiting)
Who's going first?
Me, I'll go first.
Go for it.
Off you go.
Back straight. Look sharp.
So strict.
Head of the family.
(Best big bro in Tui City)
I'm kidding.
Just talk more to loosen up.
I'm getting the energy going,
Once we start filming,
I'll go quiet.
(Time to crack the case)
Keep each other on their toes.
No.
We're about to
find out who the killer is.
(Suddenly serious)
So who's the killer?
(Just asking like that?)
I guess
it's him.
She does this every time.
(Used to it)
Every single time.
I say it's him.
You know why?
Nobody's even died yet,
and I'm already the killer.
Haven't even killed anyone.
(To be fair)
You can't know until someone acts.
What do you think?
(Curious)
Am I right?
I think it's you.
You think it's me?
Ning, not again.
You're doing this to me again.
(Happy to tease)
Detectives are always the good guys.
The detectives
can't possibly kill anyone?
Impossible.
But that doesn't mean they
know everything,
you get me?
He could also be totally...
(Clueless)
A bumbling detective.
Exactly.
He can't kill,
but what he says
isn't necessarily true.
(Spoken from experience)
Got it.
So who's the detective today?
Me.
You're the detective?
Alright, my turn to act.
I've got a ton of lines
Go get 'em, old pro.
(Watching Ning head off)
When we do our scene,
everyone has to watch?
(Strike a pose first)
Right.
I probably won't be able to see it.
Looks like you're up next,
then Ding, then me.
You two are last, right?
Are you nervous, Ding?
(Pep talk mode)
If you mess up, just do it again.
What else can you do?
That's just life.
Okay, I'm off.
(Ms. Wen arrives)
(He Jiahuan enters)
(Ding cramming his lines)
Why did you suddenly start dancing?
(Wiggling)
Aren't I going to teach you all a dance?
(Exclusive: An family heir
publicly declares war!)
The Full Press Conference.
(An Glass Factory: WELCOME)
Who will ultimately take
the helm of the An family?
Alright everyone.
Let's get ready,
so we can start shooting!
Okay.
Sure.
(Ready)
Let's start.
Alright, let's wait over there
for now.
Okay.
Who are we waiting for?
Waiting for the wind.
(Only Mommy gets it)
Alright.
First up, Mr. Ke.
Mr. Ke?
They even let him go first?
(Who's talking behind my back?)
Mr. Ke!
Who are you to call him Mr. Ke?
(Bold)
(Excuse me?)
(Mr. Ke enters)
Mr. Ke.
The way you talk
sounds more CEO than
your own brother-in-law.
No, I'm not.
(Brother-in-law, hear me out)
Who taught you that?
(Sweet-talking An Xiaoding)
Brother-in-law taught me well.
(A little embarrassed)
(Fully professional)
Looking great.
Give me some artist's vibe.
An artist's vibe.
Artistic...
Right, do your own thing.
Beautiful.
(Watching the show)
(An-Glass-Artist-Ke)
(Instantly breaks character)
(New approach)
Let's try melancholy.
Melancholy.
(Let's see it)
(Blue mode: activated)
A melancholy feeling.
Melancholy engaged.
(In character instantly)
Cinematic face.
(How'd that change again?)
Cinematic?
Alright.
(Switches mode instantly)
Like reading a novel!
A picture book!
(Realist school · cinematic)
Now, let me interview you.
The public has always been curious
about the An family inheritance.
Yes.
So Mr. Ke, why
have you chosen not
to compete this time?
(Waiting for your answer)
I have always been
a person who seeks
nothing from this world.
I simply love glass.
(Pursuing art)
I don't care for the family fortune.
A true artist.
Yes, a true artist.
My aspirations
go beyond these shallow...
these shallow...
(these shallow)
Hypocritical.
So what are your aspirations?
My aspiration is
to make even more beautiful glass.
(Still shallow)
You'd better be.
(Applause?)
Mr. Ke!
Great.
Thank you, Mr. Ke.
You can wait on the side.
Sure.
Alright, next.
Our second group,
Mr. Ning
(Grand entrance)
and Ms. Wen.
Am I shooting with my brother?
And Mr. He.
Come on...
Come on, all three of you.
I thought it was my brother.
(Instantly in professional mode)
The young ones.
(Fully Jin-mersed)
Let the kids have their moment.
Very nice.
Can you give us
a heart sign?
A heart sign.
(Love bodyguard)
Honestly,
when I look at Ning and Wen's faces,
I get upset.
Why?
(Still in character)
Reminds me of An's ex-wife.
Mr. Ning,
why is it that
you chose not to compete?
(Sharp eyes)
Reporter,
you are the first person
bold enough to ask me that.
And the last
who ever will.
(That's my brother)
So commanding.
I'll only say this once.
I
don't need to stand
on a giant's shoulders.
Because I
am the giant.
(Giant)
I think the An family fortune
is best left to my
sister and her husband.
That's the best outcome.
Well said.
(Speaks to my heart)
What?
(Furious)
What's wrong?
He's completely ignoring me.
And you are?
Who are you?
I'm your mother.
I'm your stepmother.
Fine, Stepmom.
(Letting it slide)
(Not listening)
So, Ms. Wen,
with two handsome men
standing beside you,
if your brother and your
husband both fell into the water,
who would you save first?
My husband would save my brother.
If my husband and my brother
both fall in the water,
they will stand up
and realize the water
only reaches their shins.
(Long legs save lives)
(Smooth answer)
Fell into a puddle.
Exactly.
Good.
Now, Ms. Wen
and Mr. He,
I hear you two
have a very powerful campaign slogan.
Campaign slogan?
(You know it right?)
What is it?
(I don't)
Between us two,
there will definitely be one
giant of the An family.
(That's literally my line)
Right.
Is that even a slogan?
That's just a sentence.
Just a normal sentence.
(Sharp)
(Not taking any rebuttals)
Okay then, same.
Let's wait
on the side.
Thanks.
(Commanding entrance)
Let's go.
Mommy.
You stand in the middle.
Stepmom, showing us those
skin-tone leggings, huh?
(Little tease)
Can you fix my ankle area?
(Very warmth-conscious)
Because I'm wearing two pairs of socks.
You could never buy
(The Truth S3, Tui City Mansion EP3)
any natural-looking skin-tone leggings.
(Already un-recommending it)
Girls,
just give up.
Ma'am, look at that confidence.
You're clearly set on
securing the chairman.
(Already mine)
Of course.
That's all mine.
What about Mr. Ding?
My mom's right.
It's like comparing
top-grade cashmere against a garbage bag
in terms of value.
Right?
(Cashmere)
PS: cashmere.
Garbage bag.
Understood.
(Garbage bag)
But right now,
these two sides are already
going head-to-head.
(All-out rivalry)
Three, two, one.
Let's do a classic
stereotypical villain face, shall we?
(Inspired)
He's elegant.
Why?
(Born to perform)
He's elegant?
He's always been
cashmere, this way.
You want him to look
stereotypically evil?
He's a little prince.
How did he become a villain?
(Noble mother and son)
Dad! Daddy!
Hello, honey.
Mr. An,
let's take a family photo with Mr. Ding
and Madam.
Sure.
(Can't wait)
Honey, come here!
Ding!
Ding, come here!
Come stand next to Dad!
Dad's favorite son!
(Hehe)
Just the three of them?
What about us?
They're a family.
(Uncle dropped some words)
(They were indeed words)
Aren't we family too,
uncle?
(Proudly)
Because we are the real family.
Sorry about that.
Why are you always like this?
I like being like this.
(You just don't get me!)
Am I wrong though?
Stop arguing, Mom and Dad.
(Insisting again)
We are the real family!
(Mood shift instantly)
Don't film that last part.
(A happy family of three)
Mr. An
and
Mr. Ke take one shot together.
Sure!
(Is that Ke?)
Bro, come on!
(It's An Er!)
Bro!
You startled me.
No need to be scared.
(Comforting Ding)
Are you always this jumpy?
They scared me.
The lights aren't even off yet.
That was a bit much.
Let us show you
what the uncles are made of!
It'll definitely look like this.
Your beard fell off.
(Helpful Ke)
(Protecting the uncle's dignity)
Then let's all
snap one together.
Together?
How do we stand?
No!
A blood son stands next to his father.
Outsiders should step aside.
I'm an outsider? I'm his brother!
Okay you two, seriously...
I'm standing here as his daughter!
So what? You say...
Ning!
I just don't like her.
(Still going)
She looks exactly like your ex-wife.
Alright.
Enough arguing.
(Proudly)
Tall, slim, and beautiful.
Okay, stop arguing.
Let's just take the photo.
Fine, my son has spoken.
Let's do it.
Fake it for the camera.
Gotta look good
for the camera.
Done.
Instantly pulled a face.
We look like this during the photo.
And just like that, we're done.
(Mr. Ding's Dance Crash Course starts now!)
(Mr. Ding's original choreo goes hard)
(Getting into it)
(Music cuts out)
(Beat memorized)
A true dancer carries the music inside.
Good.
(His own rhythm)
(Deep in practice)
(Fully mastered)
Come on, Ding.
(Son's brilliance)
Son, come on.
(A mother's pride)
Show time!
(Big bro speaks)
Ding, teach us
your hottest move
(Shimmy)
from your latest social media.
(Shy)
Everyone's watching me.
(Anticipating)
(Anticipating, proud)
(Staring Ding down)
(Intimidating)
So where should we look at?
(Mom loves me most)
Let's turn around then.
(Ning being Ning)
We'll watch it online.
(Phone)
What, you're watching videos?
(My adorable son)
I'll just teach you directly, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's go.
(Ding's Dance Class is in session)
(This is..., Correct)
One.
(Shuffling)
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five, six,
(Slowly smiling)
seven, eight.
(Dedicated teacher)
Okay, once more.
Sure.
One, two, three, four.
(Getting the hang of it)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Cheeky Ding)
Two, two.
(Teasing Ding)
Three-da four-da.
(Pout)
(Thinking while doing)
(Going with the flow)
(Continuing the class)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(New move incoming)
Okay. Center left.
Center left.
One, two, three, four.
Three, four.
Center left.
(Ke studying hard)
One, two, three, four.
(Double guns for the answer)
Five and six.
Seven and eight.
That's it.
Can everyone remember it?
(Of course!)
Let me run through it again.
(Eager to learn)
I'm a bit slow.
Come.
(Continuing)
One.
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Apple doesn't fall far)
Two, two.
Three and four. Five, six, seven, eight.
(Ke getting smoother)
Three, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Then, just vibe with it.
Wiggle however you want.
(Already cracking up)
Okay, got it everyone?
Let's go.
More or less.
(Full confidence)
Guaranteed.
(Mother-in-law's orders)
He, give it a go.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
(Mildly triggered)
I am at least...
Who are you to tell him what to do?
(Caught in the crossfire)
(Enjoying the show)
(Soft approach works better)
Okay, you ask your husband.
Then you do one.
(Now that works on her)
(Graceful decline)
We're doing it together, as a couple.
(First run with music)
(Sneaking a peek)
That's so fast!
So hard!
(Patient Ding)
This is already the slow version.
It's still so hard.
(Ning is stumped)
(Doing it on his own)
(Ding coaching)
(Ke focused)
Good.
- This is hard.
- This is fast.
It really is hard.
There's a mirror.
Let's go.
(He is confident)
(Second run with music)
(This mom is speechless)
So cool!
Wait,
during your dance just now, you did this
lip-bite thing.
Do we have to learn that too?
(Bite)
You don't need too.
(He is curious)
Show us.
(Savage)
He got an ulcer.
(An Xiaoding's warm reminder)
It has a "woo".
(Woo)
You can freestyle.
(An Xiaoding's trick. 1. Woo)
After that,
(2. Sway)
you sway.
Then open your palms.
(3. Open palms)
Open palms.
(4. Finger guns)
(5. Point)
Then point.
Make it look cooler.
(6. Go left, middle, and up)
Left, middle,
(Joining the lesson)
and up.
(7. Draw an X)
One, two.
(8. Sway to your liking)
Then just sway however you want.
Show off your charm.
(Immerse)
Sway freely.
(Just keep swaying)
(Charm)
Show off your charm.
What is it?
(Brutal comment from Jin)
Is your collar too tight?
Just sway.
Okay.
Bring it on.
(He can do it)
I think we
(He has mastered it)
mastered it.
You got it? I don't believe you.
Come on, do one solo for me.
There's no way.
No way.
Show us.
(He's translator)
He wants a solo.
You want a solo, right?
Do it now, hurry.
(Threatening)
Quick. Or I'll vote you tonight.
(Ding wants to watch)
He, satisfy our curiosity.
(Ning backing him up)
Do a solo dance.
(The mood is here)
I'll count the beats for you.
We'll start now.
Get ready.
One, two, three, go.
(Third round with music)
Lead the dance for me.
(Thoughtful dance leader)
(Pursing his lips)
Not bad.
(Happy)
(One-to-one teaching)
You need to sway more.
(Swaying mode activated)
(Self roast)
Like a folk dance.
(A familiar He who loves solo)
(In need of premium one-on-one lessons)
Teach me.
(An Xiaoding demonstrating)
Wave.
My back can't handle it.
Ning.
(It's your turn)
I can do it.
I'm good at this now.
(Instant battle face)
Where did that move come from?
Can't I add my own?
(Whoever gets the meal card
rules the world)
(Welcoming a new day)
Hello.
Hi.
How did you sleep?
Not bad.
(He Jiahuan enters)
Dressed so formally under your pajamas.
Not bad.
Handsome.
Are you some kind of noble?
(Tui City noble)
Yes.
It looks very expensive.
(Gets the meal card)
It's useless to take it.
He didn't earn a single point.
So food has to be exchanged with points?
(Fully understands the rules)
Yeah.
If you don't have points
and want to eat,
just tell me
that you're hungry,
and I'll treat you to a meal.
(Oh no. I don't have a meal card)
It's fine. I have a "dad".
He has zero points too.
(Stay tuned for "Push Supply Station")
Now only Ding and I have points.
(Waiting to be fed)
Morning.
(Zero-points Dad is here)
How did you sleep?
(Not ideal)
Not great.
I keep dreaming for no reason.
Nightmares?
Really?
Yes.
You're the murderer.
You must be feeling guilty.
I'm the detective.
Not the murderer.
(Heartbroken)
Everyone's here.
(The king of meal cards arrives)
See?
That's why we're father and son.
Of course.
No. I meant we both have glasses on.
I think only the three of us
look like we're in night robes.
(Pajama party)
Mine too.
Yours is a night robe too.
But theirs.
Do you wear that to sleep?
Doesn't mine look like one?
Mine's a nightgown.
(Let me see)
Doesn't the pearl dig into you
when you sleep?
(Genuinely curious)
I like it.
(Doesn't understand, but respects it)
I just calculated.
I think only the two of us have points.
Why though?
Really?
What I meant is
only we get to eat.
They have to beg us.
(Holding all the power)
(Bro won't let me starve)
So only you guys can eat?
(Jealous)
You're too skinny.
I gained weight.
So thin.
(Stepping back for a better look)
I was skinniest around New Year's.
You mean going from 2025 to 2026?
Zhou Keyu, do you think you're fat?
You two are basically the same.
But he still
called you skinny.
(Secretly pleased)
Where is Ning?
Oh.
(I'm here)
What's this here/
(Healthy tea)
How do you say healthy in English?
Healthy.
Healthy?
That's it?
My English is self-taught.
I mostly speak really colloquial stuff.
The things you told me
this morning are mostly
technical terms.
Psychology,
right?
Psychology.
What, are you going academic now?
(Surprise)
You know English?
Can you communicate
without problems?
Yeah, basically.
I'm jealous.
(A skill everyone envies)
Very fluent.
He's my second English teacher.
(The unforgettable pun returns)
Look more panicked, you guys.
Don't we look panicked enough?
(Director Ning is here)
Let's act a little more panicked.
Don't make it look like we're
at the amusement park.
Okay.
(Joins in instantly)
They really got a crane.
It really is.
Yeah.
200 tons.
(The lucky survivor)
I survived.
Should I look outside,
so I don't feel so dizzy?
No.
(Sharing her experience)
Don't look.
(Curious about outside)
Just spread out your focus.
(Wen never moves)
Don't just stare at it.
Actually, we can see
the layout of the set.
You're right.
We already saw
another set.
(Observing carefully)
The rooftop warehouse.
Rooftop warehouse's there.
(Ning, the announcer, reporting live)
We've arrived at the warehouse.
We'll get on the helicopter.
Seriously?
There's a helipad outside.
Where's the helicopter?
The helipad's next to it.
(He is sharp-eyed)
It's just a helipad.
(Won't believe it)
That doesn't mean there's a helicopter.
Helipad?
(Where is it exactly?)
No.
That's not a helipad.
You're overthinking it.
That's the show's logo.
The spinning thing.
(So that's what it was)
(Suddenly reminiscing)
Do you know
what is one chicken and one chicken?
Do you know what is one chicken
and one chicken?
One chicken and one chicken.
What's next?
Yeah. What's next?
A punchline.
(Confused +1)
One chicken and one chicken.
What?
(Confused +2)
What is it?
I forgot.
I totally forgot.
Me too.
(Dead memories resurfacing)
Like button.
Smash the like button.
Fam, smash the like button.
That's so old.
(Definitely an old meme)
I'll explain it when we get back.
(Wen has more jokes)
Memorizing memes at home every day.
(Meme king)
There's another magical one.
What does a god ride?
A god's ride?
(Thinking)
(Enjoying the show)
Baby.
Pokemon?
Might as well say digital camera too.
This door isn't open.
Door's locked.
So cool!
Handsome.
Great job!
Careful.
Move inward.
(Worried)
Careful.
Hang in there.
(The An family's only hope)
There's a lock.
You guys are locked in.
What do we do?
We're not all
climbing out like this, right?
Push one more person up.
I think
why don't
we two
send Ning up first?
No problem.
Ning, help pull the girls from above.
Is that okay?
Sure.
I'll come back to help.
Okay.
ALright.
It's easier this way.
Three, two, one.
Lift.
Go.
Careful.
That's a seriously long stretch.
Okay.
That works.
Yeah.
Wait a sec.
I'll go find some boxes
for you to step on.
Use the boxes as support.
That works.
Right, we can just stack boxes.
Exactly.
Can we step on these boxes?
Yeah.
Pass them up.
I'll catch them.
No problem.
Okay.
Yep, just like that.
Alright.
(This area is dangerous.)
Move aside.
Coming through.
Good stuff.
Careful not to cut your hands.
Okay.
Got it!
Hold it steady.
That's enough.
This is enough already.
Need more?
I'll help support it.
Do I need to step here?
Okay.
I'm gonna jump, alright?
Ready. 3, 2, 1.
3, 2, 1!
Nice.
(Insane arm strength.)
Amazing!
Okay.
Wait, I can grab more boxes too.
I'll look for more.
No rush.
Wait a second.
(Boiler Room)
It's done.
Awesome!
Ding, you're amazing!
Had to be you, Ding.
You literally...
Pried the door open.
You found pliers?
He forced the lock open.
That's impressive.
(Current state
of the An family tea party:)
(more snacks than dignity.)
What's this?
Signal flare.
We're supposed to signal for help later?
If we call for rescue later,
is a helicopter actually coming?
Seriously?
(Let me see.)
(There's really a helicopter?!)
This is for real?
I feel like we're gonna fly out of here.
Really?
What do you mean?
Okay.
We're taking a helicopter.
(Curious baby mode.)
A helicopter.
(Perfect hand gestures. Only missing the helicopter.)
The helicopter's here!
They're coming to rescue us.
(Already excited.)
Really?
Really.
Maybe.
We're actually riding a helicopter?
I've never ridden one before.
Seriously?
Have you?
Focus on solving the case first.
(Business first.)
There are so many gloves too.
We probably need these.
Maybe we have to wear gloves
to pull this thing.
Right.
Is the helicopter really picking us up?
There's actually a helicopter?
Can a helicopter
even fit this many people?
Yeah.
Two people can hang outside.
Nice.
Like those super cool action scenes.
The ladder drops down
(Aerial stunt performer)
and we just hang there like this.
Then Ning hangs outside like this.
So cool.
That's basically James Bond.
James Bond-Ning.
(James Bond-Ning.)
James Bond-Ning!
Butler.
How about arranging some food
for us first?
I can't cook.
Tell Pai to make us something.
Where's Pai?
(Seriously asking.)
Pai is exactly where she belongs.
Where Ding and He Jiahuan are.
(Where Ding-baby and He Jiahuan are
is where home is.)
It's raining outside.
We'll bring everyone some food.
Take a little break.
Delicious.
Let's share some.
(Being polite.)
Seriously, let's share.
No sharing.
Seriously, let's share it.
Just hurry and eat.
Let's share.
Bro, no need to be...
No need to be polite with me. Eat.
(Dominant CEO Ding)
Why are you pulling
the domineering CEO act on me now?
You're really acting like a CEO with me?
This is so good.
Give him one too.
I already asked him earlier. He said no.
You asked already?
I'm not eating it.
You must eat it.
You want water?
Who's feeding you?
You definitely look like someone
from the Electro team.
I didn't do anything.
Today he's acting like a CEO.
Alright, you mother and son
can stop pretending now.
I seriously didn't do anything.
(Trying to prove innocence.)
You did absolutely nothing?
I did absolutely nothing.
(I don't believe you at all.)
(Completely absorbed in food.)
This really is delicious.
(Foodie Wen)
Black sesame flavor.
(Strong food-exploration spirit)
What even is this?
(Expert Wen activated)
Black sesame pork floss sponge cake.
Where did you buy this?
(Just one more bite)
(Taste Buds of Tai City)
Delicious.
I swear there was only one earlier.
Why is there another one now?
Ning secretly put one back.
Last night I offered you one
and you refused.
Now suddenly you want it?
(Strong recommendation)
Try a bite.
Break off a piece.
I'm not trying it.
(Controlling nighttime calories)
(Do not disturb)
(To fall in love with it is Ke's destiny.)
This thing is incredible.
Right? It's so good.
Amazing.
So delicious.
I hate this kind of food the most.
And you think it's amazing?
Then you two aren't compatible.
We could never live together with him.
Our zodiac signs just don't match.
(Claims not to like it,
yet keeps quietly eating.)
You two actually
have pretty compatible zodiac signs.
Really?
Yeah.
Capricorn, Capricorn, Taurus.
Pisces.
You're a Gemini, right?
What about you?
Capricorn.
Yeah, we're all...
(The Earth-sign detective squad.)
We're all earth signs.
A whole pile of dirt.
So earthy.
(Very "earthy")
You're all earth signs.
All dirt.
(All "earth.")
No wonder
your detective squad only has...
Only has straight people and no weirdos.
Our squad has no weirdos.
Exactly.
As if this group
isn't weird enough already.
You all count as "straight", right?
You're analyzing us
through sketch-comedy logic now?
Mm-hmm.
(Completely exposed)
Now I suddenly
want to study sketch comedy.
Mm.
What does "straight people" even mean?
What's a straight person? A weirdo?
(Tips: "straight person" and "weirdo" are common comedy duo archetypes.)
No point hiding it.
(The "straight person" represents the normal perspective and reacts to the weirdo's absurdity.)
Just say things directly.
(As the emotional outlet for the audience, the “weirdo” acts silly and absurd,)
that's how Amazing Night explains it.
(using exaggerated nonsense to create conflict and punchlines.)
You watch Amazing Night too?
Who's your favorite?
(Pretty easy to guess, huh?)
Smooth.
Very smooth.
(I'm very satisfied.)
A little bit of humor.
Bam bam. Two punches.
(All soldiers of comedy.)
You're really not eating any?
Want a sandwich?
(He showing concern.)
Butler.
(Nobody leaves empty-handed.)
Eat one.
I'm good.
Seriously, I'm good.
(Thanks for the concern.)
I already ate earlier.
We specially hired
a Michelin five-star chef
(Fully energized and ready to perform)
to make these sandwiches for us.
These are all from that place, right?
(Immediately joins the bit)
Exclusive supply for our family.
What does that have to do with you?
No, we're a wealthy family, brother.
(Don't forget your identity.)
We're rich.
Right, aren't we...
(Forcefully trying to save face.)
We don’t really share a bloodline anyway.
(Too immersed in the role)
We're a wealthy family.
What?
(Uncle, why are you like this?)
What's that got to do with our family?
You've played poor guys
for so long you got used to it.
Have you ever played
a rich person before?
(Sincerely asking)
Yes.
I have.
Really?
(What kind of joke is this?)
Yeah, I've played rich people before.
Show us your "rich guy" vibe.
(Random passerby exits.
Mr. Ke makes his entrance.)
(Breaks character in one second.)
(This is hilarious.)
Rich people are like very West Coast.
Give us a rich-person laugh.
(Life is hard.
Mr. Ke now performing for money.)
Honestly Ning feels more
like a rich guy.
(Me again?)
(Ordering dishes already.)
A rich person's laugh.
(Evil wizard mode activated.)
How scheming.
That one's actually accurate.
(Performance perfectly delivered.)
You can hear the calculation in it.
The moment you hear it, you know.
(Big wedding special)
Our dance king.
(Next Episode Preview)
(This side is fully prepared.)
(Ready to start anytime.)
(Fully hyped.)
Come on, little train.
(Fully immersed in the chaos.)
You guys are having way too much fun.
(Start dancing.)
Wedding march.
(Comes with built-in soundtrack.)
(The old-school artists insisting
on handmade effects.)
(Easy work, easy work.)
It's a small scene only.
(We're all family here.)
Say it already.
(The accent has completely taken over.)
Just say it.
You can tell at a glance
I'm the boss, right?
(Everyone else are employees.)
They're all my staff.
(Relaxed fit.)
I'm dressed like this
and you still want me
doing silhouette shots?
(I get you.)
Put your arm around the waist like this.
(I get you too.)
Trying to show off the waistline, right?
The waist is over here.
(From the neck down, nothing but legs.)
(Behind-the-scenes
of the robotic-style poster shoot.)
(Fully in character.)
(Serious & Refined & Upright & Cold)
(Elementary school fight.)
I'm the one who gets to inhale first。
(As expected,
Wen is still the composed one.)
Let's go.
(Tiny mouth, deadly poison.)
Get up or you'll never catch up.
(Every word cuts deep.)
What were we aiming at again?
(Still savoring the moment.)
Shoot the pig butt!
(Shoot the pig butt!)
(The obedient younger brother.)
Can it recover itself?
(The sister with ideas.)
Just use it.
(The battle-ready big brother.)
Try it and see.
(The imposing uncle.)
Just let it regenerate.
(Time to play.)
Want to mess around with it a bit?
They're all
inside the control room right now.
(What do we do?)
(Never expected this.)
(Anticipating)
Give me a world-shattering high note.
(The whole village's last hope.)
(I'm not ready yet!)
(High-note showdown.)
(Completely stunned.)
(Volume up.)
(Adjusting method.)
♪Little bunny, be good♪
♪Open the door♪
(Open up!)
(Volume up.)
Open it for me.
Open.
(The Truth Season 4 Viewing Calendar)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪