=Dungeon Unlocking=
(An Glass Factory)
Previously,
An Er's murder case came to a close.
And the truth behind
the 1992 poisoned glass case
finally came to light.
The poisoned glass incident?
That was An Er's doing.
That night,
An Yi called everyone together
and said he would settle the matter
of the group's next chairman
the next day.
Tomorrow at 3PM,
meet me in the second-floor hall.
I'll announce the next chairman there.
As everyone headed back to their rooms,
(Ah!)
A puppet emerged from the dark.
(Night Vision)
Then, it disappeared without a trace.
It's okay. It's gone.
But the next day,
An Yi was nowhere to be found.
Why isn't Mr. An down yet?
Wait, where's that smoke coming from?
Smoke began to spread,
leading everyone to its source.
There, by the fireplace,
they found a charred body.
Why is there a burned body here?
Who is it?
Beside it was a strange symbol.
An X and a circle.
The An family's...
curse.
(The An family has a curse)
Whenever a puppet appears,
someone in the An family dies.
(An Glass Factory)
Dark and unsettling.
Full of unanswered questions.
That puppet in the hallway last night...
Was it truly the An family curse,
or was someone pulling the strings?
And the body in the fireplace,
could it be An Yi?
(A strange light appears)
A light flickered in the dark.
What secret is it hiding?
What else
is the An family keeping buried?
Door of Truth: Chapter One
is now unlocking.
(Loading)
=Case Two: Oh No, Not the Puppet=
(All players logged in)
(An Xiaoding, An Xiaoning, Jin Xiangyu,
An Xiaowen, He Jiahuan, An Ke)
(Jin Xiangyu, Detective,
Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile. Name: Jin Xiangyu, Age: 46)
(Identity: Wife of An Yi,
Occupation: Group CFO)
(Skill Card: Soothing Card)
Innocent.
(Jin is not playing around)
Family curse?
Please. I don't believe that nonsense.
Three people did this together.
I've got it figured out.
Trying to destroy evidence?
That was me.
Get ready for handcuffs.
He even found that?
Then can you find out who the killer is?
You really think
you can act all righteous?
Who are you to judge anyone?
You have your own abuse problem.
(In command)
I'll name the killer right now.
Meeting.
Sit.
I'll get my golf club.
Why would they go this far?
Because of what you put them through
when they were kids.
Exactly.
How are those two things separate?
He never yelled at me.
But every time he spoke,
I felt like it was all my fault.
You, get off here.
Nobody asked you.
Get off here.
(Voice box on strike)
Drag him down.
Somebody!
(Top detective has arrived)
I found the key evidence.
All of you had
(They are cornered)
that firm decision
to keep your kids away from An Yi.
That points to these four suspects.
Didn't they all inhale it?
Didn't they all forget?
Maybe one of them didn't.
So that person kept the memory.
And waited until they were grown.
Was that
the (confidential)
or was it him
(confidential)?
So the time of death was between
(confidential)
and
(confidential).
He's still suspicious.
If you smell
(confidential),
can you tell?
Can we ease up on his suspicion?
He didn't make the first move.
Someone came to him.
(Confidential)
Then she gets a fresh start
with her husband.
Her son and her wife...
It'd be easier for her
to visit both of them.
So why would she call and say,
"You two come over"?
(Can Jin Xiangyu pin down the killer?)
(He Jiahuan, Detective,
Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile. Name: He Jiahuan, Age: 24)
(Identity: An family's son-in-law
Occupation: Glass production line chief)
(Skill Card: Rewind Card)
(Detective He takes charge)
As the detective on this case,
you four...
Over there.
(Don't suck up)
Who said you could stand there?
Lock them all up.
What?
Who?
She's my mom.
My personal bodyguard.
I'm the detective.
Butler.
I want hers.
(Forced smile)
Sure.
(Detective gets priority)
I want yours. Hurry.
Try it.
I'm out of strength.
Don't be scared.
He Jiahuan, I'm out of strength.
(Confidential)
Explain this. Why do you have it?
Enough. Stop talking.
You three are no angels either.
That's full-on mind control.
Liar.
I can't believe this is who you are.
Look.
I'm busy all day, every day.
Every single day of the year,
I've got someone to worry about.
So that sweet,
helpless act
was all fake?
You creep.
(He is fuming)
Hi.
(Gentle big-bro mode activated)
You're so handsome.
So are you.
I want to be that handsome someday.
You will. You'll be even more handsome.
What's wrong?
Say what's on your mind.
(A breakthrough strikes)
I have a very,
very bold theory.
When An Si died,
this may have been
(confidential)
the cause.
I could've made up
(confidential)
on the spot.
This
(confidential)
was there to cover up my crime.
Very possible.
Then this would be
(confidential)
He
(confidential).
Could it have held poison?
You're only staying in the room.
If someone in that room managed to kill
(confidential)
and then tried to make up
for what they did,
I think physical attack
is more likely.
Not only could he physically
carry out the murder,
but there's something
in his statement too.
He was actually very...
So with that mindset,
could we read it as him saying,
(confidential).
(What did He Jiahuan notice?)
(An Xiaoning, Personal Stamina Points)
(Name: An Xiaoning, Age: 43)
(Identity: An family's eldest son
Occupation: Antique trade mogul)
(Skill Card)
Exactly.
As the detective on this case,
let me say a few words.
Since when are you the detective?
(Scared)
Next,
(Get ready! He's got material)
I'll be giving a two-hour speech.
Please sit.
Back then,
I was already six-one.
He was only five-eight,
but he still controlled me.
So when I grew up,
I told myself one thing.
I had to grow to six-three.
That was rule number one.
Can we act it out?
(Dad spoils his kid)
(Born to dance)
(Little demon child)
(So young, so innocent)
Boss, stop being so bossy.
You clueless people.
I'm An Xiaoning.
My kid is An Ningzai.
You're an outsider.
Why are you making a scene?
Come look at me.
This kid needs a lesson.
That's what happens
when kids get spoiled.
You clueless detectives.
(Sharp-eyed Ning)
Here's one possibility.
When
(confidential)
was moved here,
the ankle got snapped.
Which caused
(confidential).
This one's fresh,
but this one's old.
Which means
he'd been beaten for a long time.
He didn't run for days.
So why (confidential)
did he run that day?
And now that we know he's dead,
that proves one thing.
Someone else is in this house.
That body
is (confidential).
There's one thing left to figure out.
It's (confidential).
Who's most likely?
(Confidential)
is just a body.
That's the best part.
First, she couldn't go back.
She shared a room with him.
But you two were together.
(Confidential)
because he doesn't know where he is.
(How will An Xiaoning
find the hidden clue?)
(An Xiaoding, Personal Stamina Points)
(Profile. Name: An Xiaoding, Age: 23)
(Identity: An family's eldest grandson,
Occupation: Glass ambassador)
(Skill Card: Copy Card)
(Who created Chaotic Ding?)
I'm not scared anymore.
Really?
Follow me.
Okay.
(Taking the lead)
Go.
Pull it.
(Night Vision)
What are you doing?
(Helping with eyes closed)
I want to pull too.
Just pull it open.
We'll know once we try.
(Chengxin approves)
Ding, you're brave.
Come on. Let's go.
I'll cover the back.
(Impressed)
I'll go last in daylight.
Why am I such a coward?
I can't stand myself.
I'm actually amazing.
(Amazing Ding)
Dad, are you proud?
I have three awards.
(Proud dad)
That's incredible.
An Xiaoding has no kids now.
I have a kid.
So do you.
I have a kid now.
What's it to you, son?
What's it to you?
How dare you talk back?
Your dad is asking you a question.
Answer honestly.
I'm rebellious now.
I don't want to answer.
Rebellious? Fine.
Pick it up.
Why are you crying?
(Night Vision
Ah!)
(Ah!)
(Uneasy)
Will he come alive? No, he won't.
(Back to work)
Look. His head is covered in glass.
(Ding gets a ding!)
If he was burned, why is it
(confidential)?
Didn't they say this glass
only
(confidential).
Then why would it
(confidential)?
I don't think
it was just those two minutes.
Those two minutes may have been
(confidential)
for cleanup.
Got it.
His motive makes perfect sense.
As my new dad,
it makes sense he'd come over
to find me
around the two-minute mark.
If I were the killer,
wouldn't I be trying hard
to build myself an alibi?
Right.
Wouldn't I reach out first,
walk up to someone, and say,
"I didn't do anything"?
Exactly.
But I was actually right there.
(Confidential)
That alone should be enough
to make him less suspicious.
Right.
(Can An Xiaoding clear his name?)
(An Ke, Personal Stamina Points)
(Name: An Ke, Age: 44)
(Identity: An family's fifth uncle,
Occupation: Glass artist)
(Skill Card)
(An Ke goes all in)
Turn off the lights.
I'll open the door.
Then I'll go in
(Taking the lead)
and check for danger.
If it's safe,
I'll call you in, okay?
(He really did it)
You've grown up.
It's okay. I'll go.
(Charging in)
(Staying safe)
Don't be last.
(Human shield)
This is terrifying. I can't look.
It's okay. I'll go.
What's going on?
What now?
We've been together for two days.
You still don't know me?
All I did
was break one of his teacups.
He grabbed the chopsticks
and whipped me.
He hit me and yelled,
"That'll teach you".
It only says that once.
Don't you think
you caused all this?
Mind control.
(Let me explain)
That's not what happened.
I swear it's not.
(confidential)
We're done
with domestic abuse.
I'll show you what abuse means.
Fine. I admit it.
Things don't look great
for me right now.
But I believe
there's still a twist coming.
(Classic An Ke logic)
From 0:00-0:15.
nobody could have done anything.
Whatever happened,
whatever it was,
it had to be in those two minutes.
If I were the killer,
and I wanted to strike,
would I really do it
while I was on the phone with them?
The two of us were equally proactive.
More or less.
But his
(confidential)
just doesn't add up to me.
It's way too flimsy.
How do I know
you weren't on your way to meet someone?
Right?
Or something like that.
If you're trying
to use my so-called guilty behavior
to pin this on me,
are you sure the body was in
(confidential)
Okay. If he was watching us
from the shadows,
then there's no way
he didn't know where his target was.
But where would he hide the body?
It could be anywhere.
Right?
(Can An Ke see through the lie?)
(Profile. Name: An Xiaowen, Age: 25)
(Identity: An family's daughter-in-law,
Occupation: Glass division head)
(Skill Card: Lights Out Card)
(Sweet Wen, lightning-fast brain)
What kind of pun is that?
It's like
the Nine of Clubs
and the Nine of Hearts.
Try "living it up".
See if that works.
No H.
Pair of nines. You guys are amateurs.
(Pair of nines. You guys are amateurs)
(Confidential)
Right.
The pun queen.
Dad taught me that.
Never forgot it.
(Raw handwritten style)
Okay, I've got a pen.
Hurry.
He's our child.
You were never there to raise him.
(Absent father)
I raised him this well,
and you still have comments?
You killer.
(Night Vision)
Pull.
(Pull)
Stop pulling.
It's already open.
Seriously, we're done pulling.
(It has been pulled)
Your turn.
No.
Say no to violence.
Give it to his dad.
Come on.
Why am I such a coward?
I can't stand myself.
(Gentle sister mode)
It's okay. That's just a fear response.
It has nothing to do
with being manly.
Ding, you okay?
(So thoughtful)
Want to hold this stick?
It's okay. You hold it.
You're all his babies.
As long as the boss is happy.
Even if our family has fallen,
he's still the best of us.
(Sharp Wen catches the details)
His left foot is injured.
So the puppet probably wasn't
(confidential)
That means there
was another puppet.
Yesterday, on the floor,
(confidential)
which means we
What about the two-minute gap?
You can do a lot in two minutes.
Only that journal is in first person.
You're the one who regrets it most.
So he may have been at
(confidential)
Exactly.
He threw it down from above.
(Confidential)
Then he could
(confidential)
fake his alibi.
Because killers
usually panic.
I'd be scared of the crime scene,
or something I missed.
(Think like the killer)
He wouldn't leave
(confidential),
so you'd have to make sure
it stayed hidden
somewhere no one would ever check.
Where?
Right in your
(confidential)
(What did An Xiaowen find?)
(Dungeon Bonus Station now
open for a limited time)
(Dungeon Bonus Station Rules)
(Limited-time challenge quests
refresh regularly)
(Clear the challenge to unlock
surprise rewards)
(Come refresh your Buff collection!)
(This round:
everyone on duty wins rewards)
(The Truth)
Welcome to the Dungeon Bonus Station.
Okay.
(Can't wait)
Soap and Lollipop Challenge.
(Soap and Lollipop Challenge)
Follow the command
and do the right action.
When they say "lollipop",
smell the soap.
When they say "soap",
lick the lollipop.
Finish the director's commands
within one minute.
(Swap: switch items between hands)
Five mistakes max
(Commands reversed)
to win.
Start.
(Soap. Lollipop)
Soap.
(Savoring it)
Lollipop.
(The soap is edible)
Soap.
(Handled with ease)
Swap.
(Swap: switch items between hands)
Switch hands? Okay.
Soap.
(Lollipop. Soap)
Lollipop.
(Actually pretty tasty)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(I'm the lollipop)
(Mistake +1)
Soap. Sorry. Go.
Swap.
(Game on)
Lollipop.
(Soap. Lollipop)
Soap.
(Hesitated and blew it)
Two mistakes.
(Mistake +2)
Wrong.
Swap.
Soap.
(Lollipop. Soap)
Lollipop.
(Soap)
Three mistakes.
(Mistake +3. Still clueless)
Swap.
Soap.
Lollipop.
Congratulations.
(Challenge complete. Three mistakes)
(Applause for Ning)
(Soap. Lollipop)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Locked in)
(No sweat)
Soap.
(Lollipop)
Wrong.
(Mistake +1)
(Soap. Lollipop)
Soap.
(Eyes on it)
Lollipop.
(Handled with ease.)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Panic mode)
(Mistake +2)
Okay, this is actually hard.
Aren't we supposed to swap?
No more swapping.
(Swap items only)
Just swap them.
(Jing wants the challenge)
Let's make it easier.
(Lollipop. Soap)
Lollipop.
(Now at 0.75x speed)
Soap.
(Smell)
(Lick)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Getting the hang of it)
Soap.
Lollipop.
You got it.
Thank you.
(Challenge complete. Two mistakes)
Congrats, you passed.
That's sour.
(Sour)
Way too sour.
Start.
Soap.
(Soap. Lollipop)
(Instant reaction)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(No problem)
Lollipop.
Reverse.
(Reverse)
Reverse means
(Commands reversed. Items stay put)
when I say soap, it means soap.
When I say lollipop, it means lollipop.
(He gets it)
Got it.
(Lollipop. Soap)
Reverse.
Soap.
(Loading)
(Loaded)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Unbothered)
Reverse again.
Soap.
(Soap. Lollipop)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Too easy)
Lollipop.
Congratulations, you passed.
(Challenge completed. Zero mistakes)
That's sour.
(Sour)
Why is it so sour?
Let's go.
(Ready)
Soap.
This is too easy.
(Easy)
Soap.
(He's in the zone)
Lollipop.
(Speeding up)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Fast reaction)
Soap.
(Soap)
Swap.
Hold on.
(Brain buffering)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Mistake +1)
(Smell)
Lollipop.
(Getting smug)
Soap.
(Wait, what?)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Soap)
(Still lollipop)
Lollipop.
(Mistake +1)
Nope. Wrong.
(Trying to exploit the game)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(No, the video is not at 0.5x speed)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Calm and steady)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(No, the video is not at 0.5x speed)
Swap.
(Taste test complete)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Back to normal speed)
Lollipop.
Soap.
Congratulations, you passed.
(Challenge completed. Two mistakes)
That was brutal.
That was way too easy.
Lollipop.
Soap.
(He's got this)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Almost fell for it)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Fully in control)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(That's all?)
(No pressure)
Too easy.
You can switch hands now.
Still easy.
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Trapped in the soap universe)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Too easy)
Soap.
It's not over yet.
Time's up.
(Comfort zone unlocked)
Congratulations, you passed.
(Challenge completed. Zero mistakes)
Your challenge starts now.
(Soap. Lollipop)
Lollipop.
Soap.
(Xiaowen is locked in)
Switch.
Lollipop.
(Lollipop. Soap)
Soap.
Lollipop.
Switch.
Soap.
(Mistake +1)
(Her mouth slipped,
but her hands were right)
Keep going.
Soap.
(Keep going)
Lollipop.
Soap.
Switch.
Lollipop.
(Calm under pressure)
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Getting the rhythm)
(Mistake +1)
Switch.
That's only two, right?
Should I slow it down?
Soap.
Lollipop.
(Still composed)
Switch.
Lollipop.
Okay, time.
(Challenge completed. Two mistakes)
Two.
It's actually chocolate. Totally edible.
Nice and creamy.
(Have a taste)
(Pretty good)
(Success)
(Pick one reward. Snack Boost)
(Utility Boost)
(Squishy Boost)
What does "Hype Myself Up" even do?
Some kind of squishy.
Then I'll take that.
I'll take Hype Myself Up.
(Liu Yuning chose Hype Myself Up)
Squishy Boost.
Utility Boost.
Snack Boost.
Obviously,
Crispy Meat Bites.
This one.
(Jin Jing chose Crispy Meat Bites)
You can pick one.
Choose one from these three, right?
I'll go with food.
Power-Up Mints.
(Zhang Linghe chose Power-Up Mints)
I want this.
It feels like a rubber chicken.
(Ding Chengxin chose Guess Who)
Sure.
Okay.
I want this one.
(First choice. Still thinking)
I'll take the Power-Up Mints.
Feels more useful for me.
(Zhou Keyu chose Power-Up Mints)
Only snack fiends pick food.
(Offended. Food is out)
The Make-It-Up Machine sounds useful.
(Make-It-Up Machine?)
(72 Transformations?)
What's 72 Transformations?
I'm curious about four and six.
(Wen is curious)
What's 72 Transformations?
I'll take 72 Transformations.
(Wang Yuwen chose 72 Transformations)
(Liu Yuning: Hype Myself Up)
(Jin Jing: Crispy Meat Bites)
(Zhang Linghe: Power-Up Mints)
(Ding Chengxin: 72 Transformations)
(Wang Yuwen: Guess Who)
(Zhou Keyu: Power-Up Mints)
(Rewards delivered)
What's this?
(Spotted it first)
What is this? An heir?
(Still hunting clues)
The prop.
(Built-in sound effects)
Ding, come here.
(Come here)
(Who called me?)
(Snacks right here)
(Magic prop)
This is my prop.
(Show off)
Yeah.
Here. Take it.
(Sharing snacks)
(After searching)
There's nothing here.
(Just supplies)
Why is there a...
That's what I won yesterday.
(Oh, right)
Your squishy, right?
(Hand it over)
(Hehe)
Okay.
(Rewards on the case)
You're the absolute worst.
(Feeling fully protected)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪