(The Truth premier: Where dreams begin)
Apartment No. 11, here we come!
(The Truth Season 2: Chase your passion)
The Truth.
(The Truth Season 3: Embark on a new journey)
The Truth Season 3.
(The Truth Season 3: Team-building gate)
We're here!
(When is Season 4 coming out?
I'm so bored.)
(Changsha, 24 March, 2026)
(I'm here. It's Ding!)
Welcome, Ding Chengxin.
(The season's guest lineup is incredible!)
Hi, everyone.
I'll wow you all!
(Liu Yuning, I missed you!)
(When will it air?)
What is that?
(When are they filming?)
Gave me a scare.
Is this The Truth?
(Live broadcast signal interrupted)
(For the full version,
please see "Prologue: Logging In")
Welcome, player.
(Player: Liu Yuning. All-rounder leader.
Top-tier strategist.)
Jin Jing.
(Player: Jin Jing.
Social butterfly. Master empath.)
Zhang Linghe.
(Player: Zhang Linghe. Hardcore STEM
problem solver. Logic expert.)
Ding Chengxin.
(Player: Ding Chengxin. To be unlocked.)
Zhou Keyu.
(Player: Zhou Keyu. Fearless wildcard
with unexpected charm.)
(Game Lobby)
Welcome
to the large-scale open
live-action social deduction game,
"Push the Door"
(Large-scale open live-action
social deduction game, Push the Door")
Here,
you can fully immerse yourself
(Truly free)
in a free world.
(Explore)
Go places you've never been before.
(Unknown areas and "uncertain events")
This is it.
Wait.
(Explore scenes and unlock new spaces)
(Gather evidence)
Search the corners nobody checks.
(Gather clues and reconstruct
the details of the case)
Use the Lights On Card.
(Skill Card)
Use Skill Cards
(Source)
so you don't have to tough it out.
It's fine.
(Time Extension Card: Extend certain timed segments)
I have a Time Extension Card.
(Lights Out Card: Lights-off once)
Everyone, please close your eyes.
(Soothing Card: Calm an NPC's emotions)
Soothing Card.
(Eliminate some wrong answers)
Elimination Card
Wait.
Friends.
(Stamina points)
Collect stamina points.
(Random stamina spots appear throughout the dungeon)
If you run out of stamina,
(Stamina points can be exchanged for food)
you can't eat anymore.
I want to eat.
I'm your brother.
But I'm younger.
Please.
(Side quests are triggered)
Help them
(by players or assigned by NPCs)
and gain their trust.
(Increase NPC trust or earn other rewards)
Then the rest will be easier.
(Accept the File Sorting Quest?)
He has too many files.
(Yes / No)
Please think of a way.
(Accept the Groom Rehearsal Quest?)
Just stand in for the groom.
(Accept the Puppet Guard Quest?)
You must protect it.
(Accept the Hit Single Act Quest?)
I am Li Fei.
I have no backbone.
Neither pleased by external gains,
nor saddened by personal loss.
(Side Quest success)
(Trial)
Be nice.
(Detectives may start trials)
(to interrogate suspects for 10 minutes)
You won't lose out.
(Push the deduction process)
What are you doing?
We're working.
I don't know what you're saying.
Stealing is not a very good word to use.
Who exactly is the child's father?
What?
(Main Quest)
But everything above was a setup.
(Find the clues. Uncover the truth)
Above all, complete the main quest
and find the culprit.
I found the key evidence.
The culprit's locked.
It's you, isn't it?
You're not a good guy.
I am a good guy.
What does it have to do with me?
Also,
remember to stay alert.
The murderer might not be a player.
Watch out for the NPCs.
He must die!
He deserves to die!
Kill him.
Serves him right.
If there's no evidence,
I think this question is too much.
Alright then.
(Loading...)
The door is right here.
Come push it.
(Loading...)
(Dungeon access pass)
(The Truth)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Gentle reminder)
(All characters
and stories are fictional.)
(The special actions and scenes
are scripted scenarios.)
(Consent has been obtained
for photos, audio,)
(and videos used,
including AI-generated content)
(Safety measures are taken during filming.
Please do not imitate.)
(Minors should watch
under guardian supervision)
(Enter Game)
The first dungeon is loading.
Limited-time player, Wang Yuwen.
Match successful.
(Wang Yuwen,
first dungeon limited-time player)
Please enter
the transit portal.
(Player Ding Chengxin is online
Role: An Xiaoding)
(Player Liu Yuning is online
Role: An Xiaoning)
(Player Jin Jing is online
Role: Jin Xiangyu)
(Player Zhang Linghe is online
Role: He Jiahuan)
(Player Zhou Keyu is online
Role: An Ke)
(Player Wang Yuwen is online
Role: An Xiaowen)
(Dungeon: The Battle for the Heir)
(An Xiaoding, An Xiaoning, Jin Xiangyu,
An Xiaowen, He Jiahuan, An Ke)
(Welcome to An Glass Factory)
(Mr. Wu, Butler)
Welcome to the An family,
a glass family whose products are
the most transparent,
yet whose stories are the most opaque.
Today, you only have one mission.
It is to shoot the cover of a magazine
for the members of the An family.
This way please.
The set is ready.
You may all come down.
(An Ke, the fifth son)
This is Mr. Ke.
The youngest son of our founder,
(Butler Mr. Wu; Photographer; Cleaner Pai)
An Songqiu.
That makes him the youngest uncle.
I've worked in this household
for 20 years
and have never seen him
make a mistake.
Don't worry.
You have me.
So he's the legendary
dreamy uncle.
Mr. Ke,
the items you requested are all here.
Mr. Ning.
He is
(An Xiaoning, the eldest grandson)
the eldest son
of the chairman and his late wife.
The eldest grandson
of the An family, An Xiaoning.
Mr. Ning,
your wife has returned
to the country with your child.
What?
She's back?
Yes.
Here.
Hand this to her.
As long as she carries my bead,
no one will touch her
in the detective circle.
Yes.
Ning.
Uncle Ke.
How are you?
Not too bad.
As the largest glass family,
I specially made a glass bracelet
for you.
I hope you like it.
Alright, Uncle Ke.
Thank you.
Quite solid.
(An Xiaowen, the granddaughter)
This is
the only daughter of the An family,
An Xiaowen.
She is the daughter of the chairman
and his late wife.
The whole scene feels different now.
It hurts.
(He Jiahuan,
son-in-law of the An family)
Darling, why didn't you wait for me?
That's her husband.
Heir to Wang Tech,
He Jiahuan.
Why is it swollen?
Who hurt you?
It itches.
Then take a shower.
Mr. Wu!
Yes, sir.
Pull all surveillance footage
in the area right this instant!
I want to know
which mosquito
hurt my wife.
But it already flew away.
Then find out
where it came rom.
Was it the bushes at the gate?
It's getting cold.
Time to let that landscape company
go bankrupt.
Every bump on your face
means one mosquito
must die in this world.
I've long disliked He Jiahua.
Let's beat him up later.
Me too.
He's too handsome.
Tmall 618 Festival.
Continue.
Big discounts on selected items.
Tmall is the best.
I'll clear your cart
for you.
Buy them.
Come.
Let's go.
Isn't this...
Ding.
Uncle Ke
and
And Ning.
Ning?
I customized two rings for you both.
Glass rings.
I hope you two can stay together
happily
forever.
Forever.
(Butterfly)
An Xiaoding is impressive.
(An Xiaoding, the youngest grandson)
He's wearing luxury from head to toe.
Mr. Wu.
How are you still bringing me
this kind of cheap stuff?
I've said it many times.
I can't wear this kind of fabric.
I only accept two things.
Top-grade Italian cashmere
and a spoiled life.
He's throwing trash everywhere again.
He's been spoiled.
He's so spoilt.
I've been sick of An Xiaoding too.
(I equally dislike every guy)
Ding,
come help me.
(Jin Xiangyu, the matriarch)
The current An family madam,
Jin Xiangyu,
and her son who is the youngest grandson
of the An family,
Coming, Mom.
An Xiaoding.
What I love most
is sugar-free cola from Italy
and my son who shines like crystal.
Here.
Quick!
Hurry!
Come on.
She moves quick like a descending fairy.
So fast.
Alright.
Everyone's here.
Yes.
I also prepared gifts for you two.
Uncle Ke got gifts for you two.
A shattered butterfly.
(An Ke, played by Zhou Keyu)
You two may guess
what it signifies.
Such perfect artistry suits me.
Is this customized?
Yes.
(I only accept custom-made items)
From where?
How dare you question your uncle?
Speak humble.
Fine. I'll ask then.
Where was it made?
Italy.
Alright.
Keep it safe, Ding.
Okay.
Hi, honey.
Dad.
Mr. An.
This is
The chairman, Mr. An Yi.
General Manger, Mr. An Er.
(Chairman, An Yi
General Manager, An Er)
Okay. Uncle Er.
Dad.
Yi.
Today,
I hope everyone
can stay focused.
Alright.
Once the photoshoot is over,
I will announce
the candidate
for the family's
next chairman.
I think the family's assets
should be handed over to my sister
and her husband.
Well said.
I only love glass.
I do not love inheritance.
(An Xiaoning and An Ke give up
inheritance rights voluntarily)
Master,
the magazine
created something
called the Factory Groove.
We hope everyone
can stand in the center of the stage,
and we'll film three rounds.
I think the idea is great.
The family
should dance together.
Come on.
Er, you should join too.
Join in the fun.
Okay.
I won't be joining in
with my cracking bones.
Okay.
I need to get some rest.
Get some rest.
Alright.
Be careful.
Take care.
This isn't our last meeting, right?
Honey.
Don't worry.
Come on.
Let's stand in our
assigned spots.
I picked number three.
I picked number five.
Uncle Er sits over there, right?
Yes.
I also like to show
a different side of myself.
Bring it on.
I'm number two.
Then I'll be number one.
Okay.
(1. Jin Xiangyu, 2. An Ke,
3. An Xiaoning, 4. An Xiaoding)
(5. An Xiaowen, 6. He Jiahuan, 7. An Er)
Let's dance.
For the first round,
we'll film the Factory Groove dance.
Get ready.
(Factory Groove filming. Round 1)
Three, two, one. Start.
Move it.
Very good.
Next one. Get ready.
Here.
Keep it up.
Show your confidence.
Be confident.
Here.
Okay.
Show time.
Alright.
Ready.
(Watch this.)
You're so handsome.
(Uncle Ke rocks)
(He used to sing and dance
back in the day)
Let's look
at Ning's.
Start.
(Applause)
So handsome.
It is Ding's turn.
Ding.
The true dance king.
Ding,
bravo.
Come on.
(Watching secretly)
(Practicing secretly)
(Not even close to Ding)
My sister somehow danced
like she's frail and sickly.
Not bad though.
I'm a natural.
The trump card is here.
(Trump card)
Trump card.
Let me see.
Let's see.
Let's see how my darling dances.
(Let me see the trump card)
(Ha)
(Half a beat slow)
He missed
the first beat.
Depth charge.
My back.
(Threw his back out)
What's wrong?
Back?
Your husband's back
is done for.
He hurt his back.
(Camera focus)
Leave the rest to me.
Er.
He even got the camera movement.
Alright.
For round two, we'll shoot fixed poses.
Everyone just strike a pose.
Okay.
(Factory Groove filming.
Round 2: Fixed poses)
Very good. Beautiful.
So beautiful.
So cool.
For the third round,
we'll shoot transition movements.
(Factory Groove filming.
Round 3: Transition movements)
Very handsome.
Good.
That's it.
Keep it up.
Mr. An Er,
we're about to shoot.
(Doesn't budge at all)
He doesn't look that good.
What's wrong?
Did he fall asleep?
Mr. An Er?
Something's off.
Mr. An Er.
Mr. An Er?
Stop filming first.
Er.
Stop filming now.
Uncle Er.
Er.
Mr. An Er.
Mr. An Er!
Er.
Uncle Er.
Wake up.
Uncle Er!
Is he dead?
Call 911.
He's dead.
What should we do?
Stop filming.
Quick.
Tell your crew to stop filming.
This is our family's matter.
(Main Quest)
(Main Quest triggered)
Push the Door Online here.
The main quest has been activated.
(Objective: Find the clues. Reveal the truth)
Players,
(Players must investigate and piece information)
please find the cause of An Er's death
(to identify the suspects)
Lock onto the suspect
(to catch the culprit.)
and uncover the truth.
Push the Door Online here.
The main quest has been activated.
=Case 1: My Family Is a Total Mess=
What's happening?
Dad.
What's wrong with Er?
Er is dead.
Er.
Er!
I didn't do it.
This is a disgrace.
What a disgrace.
How could this happen?
(Dad's so terrifying)
No one is allowed
to speak a word of this.
You may leave first too.
We will handle
the family's matter ourselves.
According to Tui City's customs,
a basket should appear
at a time like this.
Crack the case with The Truth.
Big budget savings with Tongcheng.
This is your investigation partner,
Tongcheng Travel.
Bringing everyone
a powerful clue-searching tool
to help you sort through the clues.
To uncover the truth,
we'll set off with Tongcheng.
Ke
and
Ning.
You two haven't been home for two years.
Yes.
You only arrived
at 9 o'clock today morning.
That's right.
You two
must have nothing to do with this.
I'd like to trouble you two
to lead everyone
and uncover
the truth behind Er's death.
We will.
(Player status upgraded:
An Xiaoning and An Ke are detectives)
(Relationship: Jin Xiangyu
and An Yi: Married (second wife))
(An Yi & An Er: Brothers
An Er & An Ke: Brothers)
(Jin & Ding: Mother-son, An Yi
and An Xiaoning: Father-son (first wife))
(An Xiaoning & An Xiaowen: Siblings,
An Yi & An Xiaowen: Father-daughter (first wife))
(An Xiaowen & He Jiahuan: Married)
(Mr. Wu: butler. Aunty Pai: cleaner.
Magazine photographer)
Honey, why don't you go rest first?
This is a tragedy.
Why don't you lump me
in with the innocent people too?
Enough.
That's enough.
Culprit.
Stop acting innocent.
Still pretending.
Both of you.
What?
Why would I hurt my family?
You're the only outsider here.
(Outsider)
He's an outsider too.
He's on my side.
That's right.
We're a loving couple.
And you?
(Trying to intimidate)
Vicious woman.
Fine.
Very well.
Enough.
Everyone,
members of the family.
Today,
Uncle Er has unfortunately passed away.
The crime scene
(Case summary. Victim: An Er)
was in
(Place of death: An family second-floor hall)
the second-floor hall.
The time of the incident.
When was it?
The platform spinning segment
officially started at 10 o'clock.
So
(Timeline summary)
he crime must have occurred sometime
(The Factory Groove started at 10AM)
after it started moving.
(Time of An Er's death)
The exact time is still unknown for now.
Yes.
That's right.
Now, let's take a look
if there are any suspicious clues
on Uncle Er.
Uncle Er,
(Crime scene investigation)
forgive the disrespect.
(Players must carefully investigate
the scene and collect evidence)
(Objective: Reconstruct the case)
Check what's in his pockets.
Here.
(Push the Door Online reminder:
In real crime scenes,)
(only professional forensic personnel
may touch or move the body)
(When examining a corpse,
the scene should be sealed off)
(Gloves and shoe covers should be worn
to not contaminate or damage evidence)
It's empty.
(Restrict the area
and station officers to guard it)
(Prevent non-personnel from entering)
(These actions are for the show only.
Please do not imitate)
It's a needle.
(Needle)
A shot fired straight through my heart.
It's a needle.
This should be
a poisoned needle.
Yes.
Because he was right by us.
So only a silent method
like this could've killed him
without us noticing.
So he died because of this.
Yeah.
So the cause of death is the needle.
It's too shallow
to have killed him by bleeding.
It's probably poison.
(Possible cause of death:
Poisoned needle wound)
(Starting off on hard mode already)
(He Jiahuan, played by Zhang Linghe)
When was he
stabbed by the poisoned needle?
(When was An Er poisoned?)
For the first round,
we'll film the Factory Groove dance.
He was still dancing
during the first round.
(Factory Groove round 1 filming)
The second round was fixed poses.
(Factory Groove round 2 filming)
We'll shoot fixed poses for round two.
When he held that pose,
he had no expression.
Maybe
that was his pose,
but he got injected
during the sin.
Is that so?
The people next to him
are the most suspicious.
There's no way a needle
could fly that far.
That would take insane force.
(He Jiahuan. Jin Xiangyu)
(Caught you)
(So what?)
(Bold)
(An Xiaoning, played by Liu Yuning)
But I think
there are some tools
that can shoot needles out here.
It's not I think so too.
done by us.
Because he was facing the front.
Yes.
(Everyone was facing forward just now)
He was facing the front.
It's possible
a mechanism was set up.
Because our positions
were pre-selected.
Yes.
So the killer knew where Uncle Er stood.
(Theory: The killer set up
a needle launching device in advance)
I think we should search the hall
to see where could
the launch be from.
I think it should be positioned lower
because he was sitting here.
Yeah.
(Search area: Below the horizontal range
of the poisoned needle)
I think these potted plants
are suspicious.
Could there be something here?
What about under the table?
Could it be hidden in the flowers?
(Leaving no corner unchecked)
Wait.
Here.
A crossbow.
(Found the crossbow)
Careful.
A repeating crossbow.
Careful. It might shoot again.
It won't.
(Scared)
This should be the weapon.
Laser sensor zone.
Laser?
Laser.
(Laser sensor zone)
The poisoned-needle launcher
is triggered by laser
Laser it for six seconds
to fire the crossbow.
It can only be used once.
(A poisoned-needle device
that requires laser activation)
But there's no laser here.
He should have some kind
of laser pointer.
They shone it here,
and reflect it over there
for six seconds.
(How did the killer use the laser
to trigger the crossbow?)
Let's search for a bit more.
(An Xiaowen, played by Wang Yuwen)
I think the mirrors are the key.
You're right.
Why are there so many mirrors here?
They must be used for reflection.
(Did the killer use mirrors
to reflect the laser?)
What phone is this?
Whose phone is it?
I'm a photographer.
(I'm a photographer)
(There's no password!)
(Staring eagerly)
(Photographer's phone. March 24, 2026. 3:47PM)
Please check the set.
(Magazine shoot group chat)
(March 24. 9:59AM)
Laser. A green one.
(Laser reflection point)
Look.
This is 10:04AM.
He caught the laser beam
and bounced it off the glass.
(Theory: crossbow triggered through laser reflection)
So the victim's time of death
is 10:04AM.
Yes.
(Current case summary. Victim: An Er.
Location: An family second-floor hall)
(Time of death:
March 24, 2016 10:03:25AM)
(Cause of death: Poisoned needle wound)
We need to find that laser pointer.
Right?
(Where did the laser come from?)
Yes.
We can find the laser pointer's spot
through how it was reflected.
Do you know where it was reflected from?
(All the poles have reflective mirrors)
Let's check
the photos again.
Just search the stairs.
(Searching the reference object:
the stairs)
There's a staircase here.
The white sofa.
(Confirmed shooting angle)
It should be shot from this angle.
Why is the laser inside the staircase?
(Player's view)
The mirror is facing the tree.
(Mirror facing out. Photographer's view:
Mirror facing inside)
Which mirror is facing inward?
There's another way.
What if I bring some glass,
or this can...
This can be removed.
It can be removed.
(Jin Xiangyu, played by Jin Jing)
I can't, Ning.
I can't remove this one.
(Cannot be disassembled)
I can't take this one off either.
So only this can be removed, huh?
Yeah.
So it means the mirror was turned around
before the victim faced the crossbow.
Who was standing here?
Me.
(Don't tell me it's you, Ding.)
Ding.
You too.
Oh, me too.
(Filming positions: An Xiaoding.
An Xiaowen. Removable mirror)
So either one of you
can turn it around.
Ding,
how care you kill Uncle Er?
I did nothing.
(Innocent)
Uncle Er treated you so well.
I've always been nice.
I believe my son.
He's innocent to the core.
We'll tentatively mark them
as the main suspects for now.
(Is the murderer either An Xiaowen
or An Xiaoding?)
There's another clue in the picture.
What is it?
From the angle of the laser
reflected through the glass,
we can find where
the laser point originated.
(Find the location of the laser
through the reflection point)
Do we have a laser pointer?
We can try.
(and the needle's point of firing)
Look into the basket.
(Laser pointer)
Check from the source.
(Tracing the needle's trajectory
to lock onto the laser's origin)
Where did it reflect to?
(Laser point)
Up there.
The ceiling.
We'll check upstairs.
Anything there?
Nothing.
(No laser device found)
Let's check everything.
Found it.
Got anything?
Bingo.
A laser pointer.
A custom one.
The beam is super dim.
Barely visible.
But it shows up on reflective surfaces.
And it has a mount.
Mounted where?
It's a suction cup.
(Where was it mounted?)
Here, maybe?
Anything under there?
Yeah, it sticks.
Magnet. See?
You're smart.
See?
Yeah.
That's the spot.
(Crime reconstruction: laser, mirror
reflection, poison needle launcher)
(Shocked)
Yes.
Unreal.
He had help.
What do you mean?
Look.
The villa was searched before filming.
(Security)
Nothing suspicious.
Start filming now.
So the laser
was planted after filming started.
I didn't say this downstairs.
The first photo
on this phone
was taken at 9:59 a.m.
The mirror faced out.
By 10:04 a.m.,
the laser dot was there.
Meaning
the laser and the mirror were set up
(Laser set, mirror moved)
after filming began.
(Both happened after filming began.)
Since the death,
no one went upstairs, right?
None of us.
(10 a.m. to now: no one alone)
We were dancing and filming.
So this thing
showed up upstairs after 10 a.m.
Says who?
The evidence.
Got it.
Right?
Right.
So an accomplice did it.
Exactly.
While he was dancing downstairs,
someone was setting up the laser.
Then who controlled it?
The butler, Aunt Pai.
After they took Master away,
they disappeared.
Right.
That wasn't goodbye, was it, honey?
(Was it a team job?)
What?
Aunt Pai.
Let's go downstairs.
Aunt Pai, after Master left,
did you go upstairs?
Absolutely not.
That sure?
Nothing in this world is absolute.
Yeah.
Why are you so sure
it was absolutely not?
I like being absolute.
You do?
Where were you at 10:05 a.m.,
Aunt Pai?
(Reached out, then pulled back)
(Caught the whole thing)
What were you grabbing?
I was cleaning.
Obviously.
She's acting shady.
She kept watching him.
Were you trying to take something?
(In front of this detective?)
(Dodging her eyes)
What?
The brooch?
This one?
It belongs to Mr. Ding.
It's mine.
Yours?
No...
I mean...
(What's with the stalling?)
It's simple.
I really...
(Think before you talk)
I love
custom designer pieces.
It was from a suit.
Uncle Er
loved this brooch.
It was custom.
So I gave it to him.
Then why
would Aunt Pai take it
to return it to you?
(Talk!)
You two in on this?
No.
She set the launcher upstairs,
and you moved the mirror?
Even if the tie clip is Mr. Ding's,
it proves nothing.
I don't think Mr. Ding
is suspicious.
(What does that mean?)
Sounds like a setup.
A setup?
Trying to pin this on me?
What?
(Framed in plain sight)
(Staring)
(Watching him go)
(Definitely eavesdropping)
It's fine. Let's pretend.
Pretend, Ding.
I need to tell you something.
Ding.
(Huh?)
I put what you left
in the car.
(Too scared to turn)
Where's the key?
Under the tray.
Don't worry.
No one saw.
Where's your car key?
What?
(Keeping his distance)
Stop.
Talk.
(The pressure is on)
Mr. Ding,
talk.
Brat, talk.
Leave him alone.
What's in the car?
There's nothing between us.
(So scary!)
He never gave me
a custom gown.
What?
(This kid!)
And he definitely
didn't write his name on my arm.
His name.
(Ding)
What?
(This is huge!)
(His name)
(There's more?)
So you're my daughter-in-law.
Ma'am, don't say that.
Aunt Pai.
What are you saying?
Nothing.
Butler, is this how you manage Aunt Pai?
She's after my son.
Come on. Work to do.
Ding,
keep that key safe.
(Car key)
Honestly,
you look more suspicious now.
This should clear me.
Right?
I doubt it.
Come on.
Let's check the car.
Take a look, okay?
To the garage.
I'm innocent.
They all say that.
Garage opening.
There.
Mr. Ding's car.
(No way that fits)
Is that the car?
That's the car?
The cleaning cart.
Try it again.
(Cleaning cart)
Let's drive it in.
You try.
Turn it on.
(I got this!)
This moves it forward.
Here. Forward.
Careful.
Okay.
Turn.
(It started!)
Slowly.
Get in.
Sit up front with me.
Make way! Princess coming through!
(CEO vibes: one-hand steering)
(Cool, smooth, effortless)
(Make way! Mr. He is coming through!)
(Enjoying it)
This is fun.
I wanna drive.
(Tempted job)
Next.
One by one.
(New bonus scenes every Sunday at noon)
(Back to business)
Come on.
(Fun's over. Back to the case)
The Truth Weekly.
The An family power struggle.
Money queen Jin Xiangyu
controls the cash.
She controls our money.
(Profile: Jin Xiangyu)
(An Glass Factory CFO)
(Money queen: controls the cash)
Tech guy He Jiahuan
holds the core.
Core as in chips.
The whole factory system
depends on him.
(Profile: He Jiahuan)
(An Glass Factory Tech Lead)
(Tech guy: holds the factory's core)
Second Uncle An Er
plays the long game
and holds power.
(Profile: An Er)
(An Glass Factory power holder)
(Second Uncle: power player)
Three sides go to war.
Four people play nicely.
The four of us
are all peace and love.
(Not involved. Just waiting to inherit)
Based on this paper,
you two
look more suspicious.
You've got motive.
(He Jiahuan and Jin Xiangyu look worse)
(Motive: power struggle)
Anything odd
in this trash bag?
(Goal: find clues and solve the case)
(Search the scene and collect evidence)
What's in the black bag?
(Black trash bag)
Shredded stuff.
(Shredded envelope and files)
Whoa, this is bad.
(Shredded to bits)
An Er.
(An Er)
Who tossed it?
(Who tossed the black bag?)
My baby.
What's this?
My baby?
Is there a package inside?
(Black wallet)
There's a phone too.
(Note and phone)
Who's this?
Looks familiar.
Ding.
You're looking shady, Ding.
(Innocent)
(Detective mode)
Ding, I found your phone
on the living room couch.
I kept it for you.
Your cutie pie.
(Innocent)
(Frozen)
Cutie pie?
You and Aunt Pai have a thing?
Ding.
(Ding, how do you explain this?)
I'm being set up.
His chat with his cutie pie,
also known as
(Ding and Aunt Pai's chat)
that cleaner from earlier.
(Ding's panicking)
(Hugging himself)
Mr. Ding,
the gown you bought for Ma'am
ended up in my cleaning cart.
Where are you?
I'll bring it to you.
Ding, what was your reply?
Read it yourself.
Too embarrassing. I can't.
(What's going on?)
(Take it: Ding's raw alarm vocal)
Girl, this is for you.
You deserve it.
(Smooth, Ding)
(My boy is grown)
I gave her two things.
A dress.
And...
a bag.
(Mr. Ding, is this bag for me too?)
Come.
Read it out loud.
The embarrassing part.
(Mommy's listening)
Of course, girl.
A woman like you
shouldn't be carrying a cleaning bag.
I care about you.
So care more about my business, too.
(Hehe)
Is that something you'd say
to your cleaner?
That doesn't sound right.
Why are you being so blunt?
Your business?
What business?
I never said that.
I just meant,
if she hears anything about me,
tell me.
Okay.
Sure.
Then his cutie pie said,
"I've been paying attention.
While working,
I noticed someone older
doing something strange".
Oh?
(Older?)
Someone older?
I was about to wash
your clothes from the other day.
Then I turned around
and saw An Er
digging through them.
(Aunt Pai told Ding
about An Er acting strangely)
Was she
threatening you or what?
No.
I just
needed something,
and she helped me get it.
What did you need?
I wanted to know
why Uncle Er kept sneaking...
Why dig through the clothes?
What was he looking for?
(Why was An Er searching
An Xiaoding's clothes?)
Let's see what this is.
Recipient, An Er.
(Rebuilt envelope: An Er)
It's a package.
Urgent delivery.
Must arrive by the 24th.
Important documents?
What's inside...
It's too shredded.
(File destroyed. Cannot restore)
The shredder...
Our card!
Instant Restore Card!
Right.
(Skill Card: free on first login)
(Then redeemed with Golden Keys)
(Skill Cards are one-use)
(Use wisely)
(See "Prologue: Logging In" for details)
(Restore Card: restores one clue)
I'll use the Restore Card.
Okay.
Then
I'll use
the Restore Card.
(Restore Card)
Player used a Restore Card
to restore one clue.
It actually worked.
(Shredded file restored)
It's back.
It worked.
It really worked.
DNA test report.
What?
A DNA test?
(The shredded file was a DNA test report)
Come on.
Here we go.
(DNA test report)
Dear Mr. An Er,
based on your samples,
DNA analysis confirms
the following.
An Yi and An Xiaoding
(are not biological father and son.)
(Shocking reveal)
He's not my father?
What?
No.
Mom!
Mom.
Who's my father?
Jin Xiangyu.
Unbelievable!
Who was it?
Who's his father?
Now you know
what my gift meant.
I get it.
As for the gift,
you two
can figure it out.
A broken butterfly.
Broken family?
So, who's your dad?
(Still rich in Henan)
No wonder.
Isn't he your dad?
(For real?)
(Good grief)
Uncle Ke.
Not me.
No.
No, not me.
Could you be...
That's possible.
Maybe Uncle Ke
is your dad.
(Explain yourself)
(No)
I asked
who your dad is.
I never said
it was me.
(Uncle Ke from Shanxi)
(Cold sweat)
An Er kept digging through your clothes.
So that's why Uncle Er
kept sneaking around.
He was digging through my clothes
for hair.
He wanted your DNA.
To beat me...
To take power,
An Er wanted to prove you...
To prove I had a scandal.
Exactly.
(An Er used Jin Xiangyu's
scandal for power)
Jin Xiangyu, explain yourself.
Show some respect
when talking to your elders,
even if I'm morally flawed.
Even if you're morally flawed?
You're a suspect now.
What right
do you have
to act high and mighty here?
Look how far you've fallen.
Honestly,
after I married An Yi,
there was no other man.
But before that...
(I'm not even an An)
Mom.
I had one drunken mistake.
With who?
Mom.
I don't know who he was.
(So, who is my dad?)
What?
How could you?
You don't even know his father?
You...
I was drunk.
(Drunk, and I got hurt)
Then who tore it up?
I did.
One day,
I went over
and saw it
by the door.
After I saw the letter...
Kid...
Then I...
(Uncle Ke feels bad for you)
I knew
I wasn't my mom's...
Wait, no.
I wasn't my dad's
real son.
That's bad.
I won't have money
to buy haute couture anymore.
(An Xiaoding always flaunts fashion)
(DNA Test Report)
I have a question.
You said
(Found a loophole)
you knew about this letter, right?
When I got to the door, I saw this letter.
You saw it?
So you knew it.
You've always been protecting me.
But someone knows your secret.
(This is the key point)
Yes. I was afraid
Uncle Er would find out.
(An Er still doesn't know?)
So, you and your mom
wanted to kill An Er?
No.
I just tore this up.
This letter
was right outside his door.
He hadn't had time to take it yet.
You tore this up?
Because of one tiny action of yours,
we used a Restore Card.
You already knew the contents.
Why didn't you say it?
Just like that, my Restore Card is gone!
(You owe me one)
Don't worry. He still has a Copy Card.
Give me your Copy Card.
Alright then.
The motive for murder between you two
has been established.
My son can actually prove
that he's innocent.
Why?
(How so?)
Because he already destroyed this.
There was no need for him
to kill An Er anymore.
The stuff had already been sent
to the hospital.
At most, it's just
getting a report done.
Yeah.
Come on, we're in a new era!
(It's 2016!)
Although you said
you didn't let An Er get this letter,
so he didn't know
you weren't An Yi's biological son,
you already knew An Er
was investigating.
Your motive is completely valid.
Ding, I can't help you anymore.
Just confess.
(Clues about Aunty Pai's
Cleaning Cart Scene)
(An Xiaoding and Aunty Pai
used each other)
(Motive for murder: Prevent An Er
from revealing his identity)
(An Xiaoding and An Yi
are not father and son)
Let's look at this black clip.
Quickly clear me of suspicion.
Your suspicion
can't be cleared anymore.
(Feeling wronged)
Come.
A tablet!
It's a tablet!
"My ideal type"
Full spelling?
(The tablet needs a password to unlock)
(My ideal type)
An Xiaoding.
Is this mine?
Yes. This belongs to Aunty Pai.
Then it should be An Xiaoding.
Have a try.
An
(First attempt: anxiaoding)
Xiao
Ding.
Wrong.
She...
Not you?
(Not you?)
Her ideal type isn't An Xiaoding?
Bring over that cleaning bag.
My treasure.
Treasure?
(Missed clue recovered)
Let's see what's inside.
My treasure.
My treasure...
Who is this?
(Glass necklace)
While working,
her neck and hands were bare.
They won't be bare anymore soon.
Wasn't this necklace from you?
She said her neck was bare,
and you said it wouldn't be for long.
I didn't give it to her.
You didn't?
If you didn't, then who did?
Pai...
Let me see.
A huge piece...
Glass.
Who would know
how to make this glass?
No, wait.
Our family makes glasses,
and you're in charge
of the production line.
Yeah.
I'm in charge of the technical work.
Then that means...
He.
Me?
What?
How dare he!
That's very possible.
You brat,
you're holding the necklace so naturally.
I think you picked it out.
Because he's also one of the men
fighting for the inheritance.
Exactly.
You failed to see the true face
of your partner.
I failed to see the true face
of my partner!
Impossible.
It can't be him.
He's innocent and kind.
(Love has taken over her brain)
Don't worry, darling.
I can explain everything.
I believe you.
You brat.
You...
You were the harshest one.
How could you frame me?
Well...
(I don't like He anymore)
He was desperately trying
to pin the suspicion
(Saw it clearly)
on you.
He had his reasons too.
(Ding, don't cry)
Even if I gave her this,
even if there's
a secret...
Even if I had a secret with Aunty Pai,
what makes you say I killed An Er?
What does that have to do with him?
Wen,
look at this man's true colors.
You and I aren't related by blood at all.
Yeah. We don't even
share the same dad anymore.
(Poor little thing)
Open it.
He.
Ji.
Jia.
Hu.
Huan.
Okay.
Unlocked.
(Hubby King He)
(So shocked)
(The relationship takes a dramatic turn)
You...
You jerk!
He Jiahuan.
There are several things.
First, WeChat.
Let's take a look at the messages.
Hubby King He?
(Hubby King He)
Hmm?
What?
Hubby?
Don't look.
Sit down.
Wait a second.
Impossible.
(She's firm one second ago)
It can't be him.
He's innocent and kind.
I believe you.
(The cruel truth is now revealed)
Hubby King He?
I believe you.
Hey!
Ning!
(She's shattered)
Hey!
Geez!
Jerk!
I think you should explain
why she calls you King He.
"Hubby King" is one phrase.
Hubby King?
What does that mean?
(Also confused)
What?
It means the king among husbands.
(The top husband, Hubby King)
Alright.
The timeline moves forward
to March of this year.
March?
15 March 2016 was Consumer Rights Day.
(Chat records)
March 15th, 3 p.m.
What?
Hmm...
Aunty Pai was cleaning the windows.
The windows...
She's cleaning the windows.
Reflected in the window
was He Jiahuan.
It means they were living together.
Already living...
What an immoral man.
He said,
"Little dummy, I caught you, didn't I?
Don't let her see this."
I believe you.
Wait a second.
I'm so curious.
(Definitely taking a bite
of this juicy drama)
She said,
"Sir,
I'm sorry.
But what can I do?
As a capable maid,
I can carry rice sacks
and gas tanks,
but I can't bear missing you."
You fired a hard shot
straight into my heart.
"How's the matter with Uncle Er going?"
"Still investigating."
"There's been new progress."
"Okay."
"I'm putting her to sleep.
Once she's asleep,
I'll come find you."
"What if she finds out
about our affairs?"
"Don't worry.
I can totally handle her."
He Jiahuan...
Wen!
What kind of person are you?
He takes turn
to comfort the two of them.
You were lying beside me
while sending her those messages...
"My treasure", huh?
It's someone else all along.
He, explain yourself.
Darling...
Don't touch me!
You're dirty!
I can explain everything.
Go ahead then.
Firstly, I know nothing
about this pendant.
I swear.
You didn't give it to her?
Could there be another man?
Then it can only be you.
(Not many men left in this family)
Secondly,
I'll explain those conversations.
Actually, none of this
came from genuine feelings.
Everything I did
was so my darling and I
could have a better life.
Do you believe that?
Do you believe that, Xiaowen?
Would anyone believe that?
Ever since I came
to An Glass Group,
I've always worked
in a core technical position.
That's true.
But,
the group
is about to hold an election.
A new chairman will be selected.
So,
for the sake of our future,
I can't let my wife
end up under someone else's control.
I have to win
that position.
So that's how it is.
I'm so touched.
She believed him already?
But,
something
made me furious.
What happened?
An Er used some tricks
and put me
in a dangerous legal situation.
He got leverage over you?
Exactly.
He got hold of my weakness,
but that weakness was created by him.
(What weakness of He Jiahuan
did An Er create?)
So I went to Aunty Pai.
And then?
I used my
good looks.
(You better explain this properly)
Did you put her to sleep?
Understood.
I only put her to sleep.
(Speechless)
It's just about talking.
(Talk therapy)
Alright.
Talk therapy?
(Trying hard not to laugh)
I also asked Aunty Pai to help me
collect dirt on An Er.
(You had needs, and she could help?)
During this process,
I had to maintain my relationship
with Aunty Pai.
But why did she only mention me
and not...
What?
And not He?
Because you
were just a pawn.
He's
her ideal type.
(Ideal type)
(Pawn)
So I was just a pawn?
(Can't take it anymore)
You got used.
(Got used)
Still too naive.
(Way too naive)
She conned some benefits
out of you.
(Conned some benefits)
(Pity)
It's okay.
I needed something too.
You needed something too, huh?
Mutually beneficial, I guess.
(Comforting himself)
(Current doubts:
Who's An Xiaoding's father?)
(Who gave Aunty Pai the necklace?)
(What leverage did Uncle Er have
on He Jiahuan?)
Alright.
We're going to search everyone's rooms.
Let's see what secrets
you've been hiding.
First, let's go
to He and Wen's room.
You two share a room, right?
I'm going to find
evidence against this man.
So in the end, are we trying to find out
who my father is?
It could be me.
It could be your Uncle Er.
Or it could be the butler.
Very possibly the butler.
That would also explain
how the butler switched
the baby afterward.
That's entirely possible.
(The more they guess,
the more dramatic it gets)
Let's go.
(Rest & Recharge. Resets battle fatigue,
restores energy)
(To make it far, treat Rest & Recharge
as passive skills.)
Let's go.
(Third floor)
Welcome to our room.
(New scene unlocked.
He Jiahuan & An Xiaowen's room)
The Detective Weekly.
He Jiahuan & An Xiaowen.
The An Glass Factory welcomes its
"technical son-in-law".
You two got together
as an arranged business marriage.
(No no no)
No, we're genuinely in love.
(Deeply in love)
It's requited love.
That's what you each think.
No.
Don't try to tear apart our relationship.
(Still a relationship to speak of?)
What's this food?
Tangerine peel candy, I think.
Tangerine peel candy?
(Keyword registered)
I feel like I've seen this scene before.
Someone leaning on someone saying...
Want some?
(I can't partake in this one)
Check the phone first.
Right.
It's He's...
Let's search first.
He, come here.
Still that model photo, right?
Yes.
Lock screen.
Nice.
(An Songqiu,
the face of the glass factory)
A quick search.
Pixel beads.
An Wen and baby?
(A family of three)
Hey, what's this thing?
What is this?
(Stamina points)
(Randomly appear.
Collect to earn stamina points)
(Use: redeem stamina points
for food supplies)
Wait.
Hurry up.
I want to eat.
I'm your big brother.
Let your little brother have it.
I'm your little brother.
Alright, over here.
(An Xiaoning +100 stamina points)
Can I find something like
the ultimate clue?
(Also known as: key evidence)
(Dedicated to finding the ultimate clue)
Can this photo be opened?
Could there be something in here?
(Searched everything)
(But found nothing)
Something's in the cabinet.
(The same cabinet)
There's a laptop!
(Laptop)
(Truly a worthy detective)
Whose laptop is this?
That's my laptop.
Your laptop?
(Eagle-eye search)
(How did I miss that?)
(Empty)
There.
Underneath.
Where?
There should be something under here.
(Crawling search)
My notebook.
(All the roads that brought me here)
Why is there
so much tissue paper in the bin?
Oh, he has rhinitis.
Rhinitis.
(That makes perfect sense)
Let's check the phone first.
Since this is directly tied to
He, who's currently our top suspect.
Let's see what's suspicious about him.
(Checking the phone)
Year 2016.
March 22nd.
"Stood up by Mr. He"
Victims Alliance.
My darling,
fly slowly.
Why are you singing to him?
Don't miss any important information.
Had a great time drinking tonight.
Let's party again next time.
What's going on, bro?
Such a beautiful voice.
I've never heard anything like it.
(Jealous)
Mr. He is long gone from being
that cold CEO
who couldn't stand the hassle of women.
Now he's the guy
who bails on his bros
just to fly to Italy
to carry his wife's bags.
The devoted Hubby King.
Love's prisoner.
"Laundry Powder's" baby.
(Good to Coax)
This...
This is them
in Italy.
♪In this romantic summer♪
♪I want to walk in the rain with you♪
(They're so into it)
But he claimed he was wrongly accused.
He sent an emoji.
(Lu)
(Feelin' wronged)
You all know
I married her because
I had my own agenda.
(I'm about to lose it)
Who was that saying they were...
(Requited love)
"We both admitted it"?
(Oh my, oh my)
(A mother-son bonding moment)
He Jiahuan!
(Stay calm)
Calm down.
(Eye of the storm)
You...
Calm down.
There was another reason for this too.
Son,
the show's starting.
A drama for the ages.
(Better than prime-time TV)
(Uncle Ke also loves prime-time dramas)
The "requited love" part wasn't wrong.
But coming into this family,
I did have a purpose.
Because ever since I was young,
I've had a dream
and an idol.
My idol was
the founder of the glass factory.
An Songqiu?
(He Jiahuan idolizes An Songqiu)
My grandfather.
That's right
The domestic glass he created
was the gold standard I looked up to.
My whole life I've been
dreaming of carrying
that legacy forward.
So in my mind,
even at the start of the marriage,
it was mutual.
I chase my career.
My dream.
My idol.
(Career, Dream, Idol)
(Just not me)
"It's requited love."
You were chasing the glass.
She was chasing you.
That's brutal.
But later,
as I spent time with her,
I realized,
her love
for me was overwhelming.
(Can a heart that's been hurt
still love?)
So
I felt I owed her when it came to love.
And I started doing everything
I could to treat her well.
And now it's become something truly
mutual.
(Love that came after marriage)
Let's look at the laptop.
What about it? It's my laptop.
(Password required)
You can't open it.
(Password hint: the happiest day ever)
You're right.
It's my diary. Why?
The 17th of every month
has been circled by you.
Explain yourself.
What's the deal with the 17th?
You actually noticed that.
Don't you know about Tongcheng Travel's
17 Travel Festival?
So every month
on the 17th,
go on the Tongcheng Travel app,
and there are travel surprises waiting.
Book hotels, flights, train tickets,
vacations, group tours.
All great prices.
Every trip we take
is booked through
Tongcheng Travel.
And on the 17th,
you can also unlock extra travel perks.
So
the 17th feels like
our monthly anniversary.
I get it now.
In that case,
could the password actually be 1717?
You got it right.
That's it.
1717 means "together together".
Travel together.
Save together.
Be happy together.
Exactly.
Tongcheng Travel's unbeatable prices
speak for themselves.
Travel together and save big.
Who are you traveling "together" with?
With you.
I'm completely loyal.
You're so insecure, man.
Such a possessive streak.
Exactly.
You're covered in your own "stains",
and you still have the nerve.
To demand that from someone else.
(Okay, enough roasting)
Year 2016,
March 22nd.
(An Xiaowen)
These are videos I saved
of watching
Autumn in My Heart.
I can't handle it.
She's crying.
(Why has An Xiaowen
been crying so much?)
If only this were
me and my He.
Then...
that would be perfect.
"If only this were"
(Searching for clues on the side)
"me and my He."
I'm telling you,
if you can't find anything,
that just makes you look
even more suspicious.
(Detective Push)
(Nervous)
There really is something!
Well hidden too.
What?
Quite a few pieces.
(A stack of torn paper)
Tui City Biotech Genetic Testing.
Bio...
You're not...
You're not
your mother's child!
Hold on.
Piece it together.
Come on.
Here.
(Kinship DNA Report)
Dear Mr. An Er,
based on the samples you provided,
following DNA analysis,
the results confirm
An Xiaowen
and the chairman of Wang Tech,
Mr. Wang's compatibility is
at 99.99 percent!
Confirming a biological
father-daughter relationship.
Wang Tech's young heir, He Jiahuan.
An Xiaowen and
(Father: Chairman of Wang Tech)
the chairman of Wang Tech.
Compatibility
at 99.99 percent.
(Father: Chairman of Wang Tech)
You two...
share a father.
(Note: Chinese law explicitly prohibits
marriage between direct blood relatives)
(and collateral relatives
within three generations,)
(as siblings who marry face extremely
high health risks for offspring)
(and it violates public morality.)
You two...
You two have
the same father
and mother!
Same mother...
(Easily startled)
What's going on?
You two are siblings!
Thunderstorm!
Thunderstorm.
The evidence is irrefutable.
You and her are
siblings.
(Refusing to face it)
And now it's become something truly
mutual.
And you even fell in love with her!
(A love that was never meant to be)
Who tore this up?
Found under your pillow.
Who tore it?
Yes, I tore it.
You knew?
I was afraid this scandal would get out
and destroy both families' valuations.
(Personally destroyed the evidence)
An Er was the one
who sent it for testing.
Right.
(Dear Mr. An Er:)
Only An Er knew that she
was not An Yi's
biological daughter.
She's Mr. Wang's daughter,
which means she has no right to inherit.
So,
you wanted to kill...
(An Xiaowen's motive)
(To avoid tanking both companies)
Don't talk to me about inheritances.
You are my sister?
My brother.
(A soap opera moment)
(Clues about An Xiaowen)
(Motive:
To avoid tanking both companies)
(An Xiaowen isn't An Yi's daughter.
Might be He Jiahuan's sister)
So logically speaking,
the motives for those three
are pretty clear now.
(An Xiaoding's motive:
To avoid losing his inheritance)
(An Xiaowen's motive:
To avoid tanking both companies)
(He Jiahuan's motive:
An Er has some dirt on him)
And him.
He just said
that An Er has some dirt on him.
(What kind of dirt
does An Er have on him?)
Your dirt...
Spill it.
What's the dirt on you?
(Still staying silent)
Let's go search the other rooms.
Let's see if we can
dig up this piece of dirt.
Grab a box.
Just a box to hold
the evidence.
Got it.
What a dedicated detective.
(He Wen's room)
Welcome.
Welcome to my room.
Hope you guys don't make
too much of a mess.
Is Master inside?
Nope.
Alright.
(New scene unlocked)
Let's do
(An Yi and Jin Xiangyu's room)
some digging around
and see what's in this room.
(Starting the search)
There's this.
A golf club.
(Jin Xiangyu's phone)
There's a phone here.
(Checking the phone carefully)
This phone shows...
a chat with a DNA testing center
on March 18th.
Mr. An Er
ordered a rush DNA test.
He insisted it must be
received by the 24th.
I'll pay ten times the price.
Send me the digital version
of the test results.
Ms. Jin, that's against the rules.
I am a person of principle.
A hundred times.
(Please check the DNA report)
So you knew on March 19th.
(Mom! You knew!)
(Jin Xiangyu knew
that her son wasn't An Yi's)
You knew way before An Er did.
And you knew before your son destroyed
the evidence.
So it turns out you knew
everything all along.
It turns out...
you didn't want anything.
You just wanted An Er dead.
I found out on March 17th.
(Taking center stage)
(Jin Xiangyu's hidden secret)
I went back to my room that day
and realized that things
had been moved around and put back.
So I asked Aunty Pai
what on earth happened.
She told me
that An Er was acting
all sketchy in my room.
So, I started keeping a close eye on him.
I noticed An Er had collected
some of my son's and Master's hair
to send in for a DNA test.
I wanted to intercept that report
because I thought
(Jin Xiangyu's hidden secret)
my son was definitely Master's.
But the report told me...
(DNA Test Report)
(Not biologically related.)
(Who's Xiaoding's real dad?)
So when you married into the family,
you were already pregnant
and didn't know?
I had no idea.
My period has always been irregular.
Alright, as things stand right now,
I think you have
the strongest motive to kill.
On top of losing the inheritance,
your secret would have been exposed too.
(Jin Xiangyu's motive:
Inheritance + covering up a scandal)
This.
What's this?
It can't be that.
(Back to searching on all fours)
There's a body.
What?
Just kidding.
(Black plastic bag)
Just this.
(Feel my gaze)
This is
a bag
of murder weapons.
If I see anything in here
related to laser pointers or mirrors,
I'm locking in the killer.
But Aunty Pai
can also get into our room.
Xiaoding, well said.
You've got a point there.
My good boy.
(The defensive son)
You called her
your sweetheart yesterday,
and today you're calling her a killer.
He called her...
(She's married)
Let's not get bogged down by that.
We already...
What's this?
I'm locking in the killer.
This is...
the young-at-heart kind of thing.
(Stealing every gaze)
(With the bright light)
(Every step leads the trend)
How stylish.
You have a pair of light-up shoes?
A red-soled sneaker.
(Whose shoe is this?)
Let me tell you
exactly what kind of story this is.
Does everyone remember what I said?
You even stole his shoe?
(A thief steals everything)
You've all heard
the story of Cinderella, right?
This belongs to my Cinderfella.
(Cinderfella's exclusive flashy shoe)
Your Cinderfella?
Whoever can fit into it
is my guy.
(Devoted tech mogul)
(Talented family heir)
(Authoritative leader
of the detective circle)
(Who is her old flame?)
(Who is my real father?)
(Cinderfella, try on the shoe!)
Alright.
It's definitely not me.
(Taking it off confidently)
Is it yours?
(Perfect match)
It fits perfectly.
(Like it was custom-made)
You're her Cinderfella.
(Is An Ke the Cinderfella?)
(Are you my real dad?)
Call him Dad.
Wait, isn't he my uncle?
Hold on.
(Wait a minute)
Call him Dad.
Young man.
(Enjoying the drama)
(Sighing with relief)
I knew it was you that night.
No, wait a minute.
(Backing away)
I highly suspect you've got something
(Don't deny it)
going on.
I suspect you too.
What does this have to do with me?
(You won't admit it?)
You two are six-foot-three too.
Come on.
(If it's not him, it could be you)
Everyone give it a try.
Come on.
Hold on.
(I'm just a bystander)
This has nothing to do with me.
No.
(It's definitely not me)
Anyone could be the one.
It's just the three of us left.
(Convinced)
(He Jiahuan takes the lead to try it on)
(Fits just as well)
I can wear it too.
(Are you my real dad too?)
(Happy on his own)
But it pinches my toes.
(Really, definitely not an excuse)
Here's the thing.
You wear a size 11, right?
Yes.
What about you?
I'm an 11.
I'm a size 11 too.
So all three of us can wear them.
Because we all just happen
to wear a size 11.
(Then...)
Xiaoding,
call him
Eldest Dad,
(Taking them all)
Second Dad,
Third Dad.
He's my brother.
There's no DNA test for me.
Yeah, what does this have to do with me?
(Show some evidence)
Anyway, we just have this shoe.
(Who's the real size 11 Cinderfella?)
(Ke's defense: This isn't mine)
First of all,
I'm too old.
I don't wear shoes this trendy.
What about back then?
23 years ago.
The kid was born 23 years ago.
Am I that embarrassing to you?
No.
(Reason one)
(Overruled)
Okay, there are letters on it.
(Hard evidence is here)
There's a...
There are letters on it.
There are letters.
Letters?
What's this?
K-E.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
(K-E, Ke)
Ke.
K-E.
Ke?
(Only person related to K-E)
Call him Dad.
Stop playing dumb.
Ke...
Ke Daole.
(Ke Daole makes a temporary comeback)
This is Ke Daole,
aka Dollar Ke, who exposes fakers.
Ke.
It's you, right?
Wait.
♪Miss you. You didn't reject me♪
That night...
♪Heart. I ended up hurting you♪
Ke...
(Repeatedly checking)
Tell the truth.
I don't know anything about this.
You just don't...
(He still denies it)
You still don't want to admit it?
You refuse to admit
what happened between us?
Wait.
Don't call him...
Don't call him Dad, son.
Don't.
We don't accept him.
Yeah.
We don't.
We don't accept it?
We're not accepting him.
(Deeply wounded)
This matter
(Defender of justice)
is probably real.
You really are Ding's biological father.
(Ding's biological father,
suspected to be An Ke)
He's a detective.
A detective can be his dad too.
(Detectives can reproduce too!)
Why can't he have a detective dad?
(Dad's got my back!)
So...
Alright.
So we're confirming this now?
But how can you be sure it's me?
There are tons of people in this world
with "Ke" in their names.
Exactly, maybe it's just coincidence.
Forget it.
Let's just move on
and find the next clue.
Quick, let's stop talking about this.
This one.
Nothing left.
Nothing.
(Emotionally unavailable)
So in your heart,
you still don't believe this is true?
I know you're trying to help me.
Stop talking already.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
I just remembered something.
I only remembered it now.
When I was younger,
there was indeed a period
where I lived wildly and recklessly.
I want to ask you something.
The perfume you use,
is it cedarwood
and moss?
Such detail.
He changes fragrances every day.
I'm the one using it.
It's you?
Then,
what kind of father are you to me now?
No, no.
(Add more dramatic effect)
"A Group-Buy Dad."
(His first dad and second dad
are both his dads)
But actually,
I already had my own family.
I got married in 2015,
and in 2016,
I already had a child.
So you can't admit it.
I understand.
Am I really that shameful?
No.
Wait.
It's not like you're that desperate
to become someone's son either, right?
No.
Do you really have to claim a dad?
You can just not acknowledge him.
You're the most tragic one here today.
Passed from one dad to another,
and the new dad doesn't even want you.
(Clues from Jin An's Room)
(Jin Xiangyu's motive for murder)
(To stop An Er from exposing her scandal
and affecting her inheritance rights)
(An Ke suspected
to be An Xiaoding's biological father)
Let's go to An Er's room.
The victim's room.
=Crime Scene Investigation Begins=
Murderer, get away.
Get away, murderer.
Wait, I want to walk
with my ex-boyfriend first.
(He doesn't acknowledge you.)
You forgot everything?
No.
I...
I understand.
Let's go.
(He doesn't acknowledge you.)
At least we have Autumn in My Heart.
And what are you supposed to be?
Autumn in My Heart.
An Er's room.
(New Area Unlocked: An Er's Room)
Whose phone is this?
(An Er's Phone)
This is An Er's phone.
Let's take a look.
March 16th, 2016, 10 PM.
On the 24th,
the next chairman will be announced.
He Jiahuan, An Xiaowen,
Jin Xiangyu, An Xiaoding,
these people could become obstacles.
I need dirt on all of them.
The more explosive, the better.
March 17th, 2016,
8 p.m.
I hacked
into your home surveillance system.
Honestly, the footage is wild.
See for yourself.
Come.
Listen to me.
As for the heir issue,
don't even consider Jin Xiangyu anymore.
The moment I saw her taste in men,
I knew she was no good.
Her ex-boyfriend is An Er's subordinate.
An Er's subordinate?
Yeah, my ex-boyfriend worked under An Er.
Shi Wu'ai.
(Jin Xiangyu's ex-boyfriend: Shi Wu'ai)
According to An Er,
(An Er's subordinate)
that man was also involved
in the poisoned-glass incident
back in '92.
(Poisoned glass?)
Then he got involved with Wu,
did all sorts of disgraceful things,
and even had a child together.
Me?
Yeah, him.
I already showed mercy
by merely kicking that child
out of the An family.
Kicked out of the An family?
Then why am I still in the An family?
He didn't kick you out.
(Something's off!)
"I already showed mercy..."
As for Jin Xiangyu,
she's nothing more
than a money-making tool to me.
What I want is her brain
and her ability.
(Sympathy)
(Concern, Pity)
(Not a shred of love?)
If she knew what was good for her,
she'd understand
that being allowed to stay
in the An family until now
is already the last bit
of dignity I'm giving her.
Alright, that's it for now.
I'll send the rest to your email later.
He kicked out the child
you and Wu,
which is me, had together.
(But I'm still here.)
So is it possible
that he's not actually the child
of the two of us?
Then whose child am I?
Where is my real father?
(Whose child am I, really?)
(This completely broke Mom's brain.)
Were you ever kicked out?
No.
I've always been here.
You grew up here, right?
Since childhood.
Then there's one possibility.
Your biological son
may have actually been sent away.
And another child was swapped in.
Exactly.
Okay, this is getting complicated.
How did this suddenly happen?
Can I ask
who your ex-boyfriend is again?
What's his name?
Shi Wu'ai.
My relationship with that ex
was really strange.
We dated for a long time,
then one day he suddenly disappeared.
That's why I went drinking.
And then you ended up...
(That's right, it's just that magical.)
(Absolutely explosive.)
(But Uncle Er's bed finally gave out.)
Wait.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Careful!
Are you alright?
I'm okay.
How did the bed collapse?
We sat it to death.
Is there some kind
of mechanism underneath?
No.
It literally just...
Collapsed from sitting on it.
It simply couldn't handle
the weight of three grown men.
Just straight-up collapsed.
Right.
"I'll send the rest
to your email later."
Email?
Go check if there's email access.
See if there's email.
Then there should be a computer.
Probably something computer-related.
Nothing here.
Drawers.
Check the drawers.
Drawer.
There's a laptop here.
Back then, that woman Ning got pregnant.
That woman Ning?
(My woman?)
You had a woman back then?
Keep reading.
That woman Ning got pregnant.
She was only one
of Er's subordinates.
But Er said
she was also involved
in the 1992 poisoned-glass incident.
(Ning's woman was involved
in the poisoned-glass case?)
I never expected she secretly
got pregnant with Ning's child.
(I had a child too?!)
Ning never knew about it.
I paid someone to silence her
and had the child brought to me.
Coincidentally, Jin Xiangyu
also gave birth to that scoundrel.
(He called me a scoundrel!)
Didn't she cuckold me?
Then I'll make her raise my grandson.
You're his grandson.
(An Xiaoning and An Xiaoding
are father and son?)
(The spoiled younger brother)
A shattered butterfly.
(Turns out they're biologically related)
Who are you calling Dad?!
Exactly.
Who's your dad then?
(It started as a joke)
Wait, it actually means that?
No, that's not what I meant.
(A joke becomes reality)
How did this turn into a family drama?
(Absolutely insane.)
But haven't I been calling you brother?
Now call him "Brother-Dad."
He calls you little brother,
and you call him Dad.
(Everyone uses their own title.)
Time to recognize a new father.
(Brief father-son bond: ended.)
Whose dad is whose dad anymore?
Back in 1992,
I met a woman
named Qian Nvyou.
Then I really fell for her.
We got together,
even preparing to get married.
Then one day she told me,
"I'm going
to give you a surprise."
And her surprise was disappearing.
(An Xiaoning's ex-girlfriend
suddenly vanished.)
She ran away.
From then on,
I shut myself off emotionally.
I didn't date for over ten years.
Actually, decades.
That "surprise" was me.
(The surprise itself.)
She was actually planning
to surprise him with the child,
but never expected the child
to get taken away.
Right.
Then last year I met another girl
named Xi Hu.
Xi Hu?
Laundry detergent?
And after dating her for a year,
we had a child too.
Young Master,
your wife has returned
to the country with your child.
She came back?
Now this proves one thing.
You...
I am your son.
(Completely accepting his identity.)
Exactly.
(Hug)
Come here, son.
Call him Dad already.
(Struggling little feet)
(Accepting fate)
Fa...
Son.
I never thought after all these years,
I'd finally find you.
(A father pouring out his heart)
I never knew I had a son either.
I feel so happy right now.
Where's my mom?
From now on, I'm your grandma.
It's okay.
I know this may be hard to accept.
Sit down first.
If you can't adjust yet,
(still escalating the madness)
you can also call me "mommy."
Call her "Mom" in the morning,
and at night, call her...
(Sounded like sleep-talking)
I received a text.
I found it.
It's insanely explosive.
About He,
the biological child
of "Old Wang Next Door".
He Jiahuan
(Detective Agency Investigation)
actually died at the age of one.
Died at one year old?
(Then who am I?)
You're not him either.
You're the child who was abandoned.
(Child)
(Terrified child)
Later, they found an abandoned baby.
After investigation,
that child turned out to be
the son of Jin Xiangyu and An Ke.
I won't say anymore.
My son…
(Uncle's getting emotional)
I won't say anymore.
My son.
Uncle An Ke.
(A momentary title confusion.)
(Blood ties can't stay hidden forever)
Uncle An Ke.
I seriously won't say anymore.
My son.
Dad! Mom!
(Eyes opened wide today, huh?)
I finally found you.
(What other insanity is left?)
Wait, if I'm not biologically related...
Then the two of us
can be together again.
Daughter-in-law.
(We're not divorcing anymore!)
You two are siblings.
(Forbidden love can be exciting)
And you still fell for him?
(But healthy relationships matter too)
Dad.
Come, let's sit here
and watch their drama unfold.
(Front-row rock concert seats)
This is great! My grandson
wasn't born from inbreeding.
And you found your own son too.
These people are outsiders.
All outsiders.
(What does that even mean?)
None of you qualify for the inheritance.
Right.
You don't qualify either.
I'm fine just enjoying life.
Exactly.
(So enlightened.)
I mainly care because
I'm a legitimate member
of the An family now.
Exactly.
(Pureblood An family member.)
Who even are you people?
No, I'm an An family member too.
Right, Uncle Er is dead now,
so the inheritance falls to me, right?
(Hands on hips.)
Our An family fortune
is going to my little sister.
(Hands on hips.)
You're a generation younger than me.
I'm not obsessed with money.
You're my brother.
Wait, you're also my uncle, right?
Exactly.
We're uncle and nephew now.
(Awkward smile)
Okay.
No, hold on.
(Will someone control these detectives?)
You two detectives
don't even have inheritance rights.
(Breaking composure)
Exactly.
(Let's sort this out first)
They are direct descendants.
They're the next generation down.
We're the grandchildren.
The grandchildren generation.
Your generation rank is the lowest.
I'm the same generation as you.
My rank is the lowest?
Yep, the lowest.
I'm her son.
She's your grandmother.
(You during Lunar New Year visits:)
So do I call him Uncle?
Yeah, that's right.
I have to call you Uncle.
Why's your seniority so low?
Even if my rank is low,
I'm still your dad.
(How dare you!)
Show some respect.
It's okay. In the end,
everything's still mine anyway.
(I'll outlive all of you.)
(How filial)
Alright.
(Ke's son, Ning's younger brother)
Then I have inheritance rights too.
You do!
Then how about this?
The four of us team up
and secure the inheritance together.
Exactly.
We'll live a good life together.
Wait a second.
The four of us are on the same side.
So...
No, listen.
The four of us are together.
Only those two are outsiders.
You two are the outsiders now.
(Father-son. Uncle-nephew. Father-son)
Honey, c'mon.
We are...
(Married couple)
Oh, stop it.
Honey.
We still have little Anwen too.
That's true.
That's really true.
(Father-son. Uncle-nephew)
How did this somehow turn
(Father-son. Couple. Mother-son)
into one giant family?
Exactly.
We were family all along.
We really were one big family.
No wonder I liked this kid so much.
The more I look at him,
the more affectionate I feel.
How did you
(Feeling sorry for my son)
change sides that fast?
You two lived together
for twenty-three years.
How could you...
Honestly, there was always a bit
of emotional distance between us.
(Are you even human?)
We were actually far apart.
(Shattered)
Okay, and now suddenly...
Your son
buys you designer fashion every day.
(BarBer)
Everything you're wearing,
who bought it for you?
I bought it all myself.
It's okay. Your new son
can buy things for you now too.
My son.
This eldest son really is lovable.
(Look at that expression.)
No wonder he's so tall.
Who did you inherit
that giant height from?
(Yi & Jin: married (second wife);
Yi & Er: brothers)
(Er & Ke: brothers;
Jin & Ding: mother-son)
(Yi & Ning/Wen:
father-son/daughter (first wife))
(Ning & Wen: siblings;
Wen & He: married)
(Yi & Er & Ke: brothers;
Ke & Jin: past affair)
(Ning & Ding: father-son;
Yi & Ning: father-son (first wife))
(Ning & He: cousins;
He: son of Ke & Jin)
(Wen & He: married)
New messages are coming in.
Here.
Mr. An,
(Truth Detective Agency)
just like you predicted,
someone's looking
into the 1992 An Glass Factory
toxic glass incident.
That person has already entered
the An family.
(Someone's digging
into that toxic glass case?)
So that means...
Someone's watching us right now.
There's something up there.
It's an iPad.
Unlock it.
iPad.
Magazine shoot group chat.
For coordination.
We're in the chat.
Go on.
On March 21,
An Er started the group chat.
The set design for the shoot
is finalized.
He Jiahuan and Jin Xiangyu,
handle the stage setup.
Follow my design.
(Responsible for stage setup.)
Got it.
March 24, 9:30 a.m.
Today, right?
Half an hour earlier.
Hello, Mr. An.
The stage setup is complete.
Mr. He and Ms. Jin
have checked everything.
No one has been here since.
You can come to the set now.
An Xiaoding and An Xiaowen
didn't check the set?
An Er asked.
The staff confirmed it.
How are they not taking this seriously?
What if something goes wrong?
Forget it. I'll check it myself.
That's how he walked to his death.
(No prior entry to the set.)
So that points to...
Us.
Jin Xiangyu and He Jiahuan.
Yes.
(Suspicion increases on Jin and He.)
You two were in charge
of the stage...
Setup.
Yeah, setup.
So what could they have done?
First,
(#What Jin and He could do)
get familiar with the set.
Second,
make the wooden structure movable.
Yeah.
And hide a crossbow inside the pot.
Then I'm cleared.
That requires technical skill.
Who's the tech expert here?
(What kind of mom are you?)
Alright, next.
The shoot plan for the 24th
is finalized.
I've picked my position.
You can choose yours.
So on the 23rd,
we chose our positions.
An Xiaoding picked spot 4.
An Xiaowen picked spot 5.
He Jiahuan wanted to stand
next to his wife,
so he took spot 6.
Jin Xiangyu picked spot 1.
An Xiaoning picked spot 3.
An Ke picked spot 2.
(1. Jin; 2. Ke; 3. Ning;
4. Ding; 5. Wen; 6. He; An Er)
(Rotating lens installed
between spots 4 and 5.)
You two just kept replying "okay."
Xiaowen and Xiaoding
never responded.
We didn't have time
(No prior entry for Wen and Ding.)
to install
the mechanism
because we never went there.
So you two
were just the executors.
Here's the thing.
One of us installed
(Jin or He installed it?)
the mechanism,
and one of them
(Ding or Wen triggered it?)
triggered it.
Yes.
There's a conspiracy.
A conspiracy.
(How did the conspiracy happen?)
(Anyone home?)
Yes!
Who is it?
(An Er's autopsy report has arrived.)
(I left at the door.)
Where's the autopsy report?
The autopsy report.
(An Er's autopsy report)
Come on.
The deceased, An Er,
had a needle embedded in his chest.
The needle was coated
with a highly toxic poison.
This is likely
a poisoned needle.
(A poisoned needle, just as expected.)
A poisoned needle?
Yes.
This poison is colorless and odorless.
Death occurs immediately
after poisoning.
Further examination revealed
that the victim, An Er,
had suffered an electric shock.
(The victim, An Er, had suffered
an electric shock.)
(Had suffered an electric shock.)
Electric shock.
(The victim, An Er,
had suffered an electric shock.)
The cause of death
was likely this needle.
The victim, An Er,
had suffered an electric shock.
(Autopsy Report)
Unable to determine cause of death.
Further analysis required.
(A new clue has surfaced
in the case!)
This suggests two possible
methods of murder.
(A second murder method has appeared!)
What does this electric shock mean?
But...
So after being electrocuted,
he just stayed sitting there?
Impossible.
(What do the signs
of electrocution indicate?)
(Two signs of death.
What do they truly mean?)
(An Er, had suffered an electric shock.)
It must be one or the other.
(An Er, had a short needle
wound in the chest.)
Unable to determine cause of death.
Further analysis required.
There are two...
Two separate groups.
But they were not aligned
in their execution.
Yet both acted at the same time.
Both wanted him dead.
(An Xiaoding speculates:
two groups acted simultaneously.)
That is also possible.
Yes, exactly.
It feels like everyone
wanted to kill him.
All had intent, but acted independently.
There is no way he died
from electrocution, right?
It is possible.
But how exactly was he electrocuted?
(How was the electrocution carried out?)
Wait a moment.
No...
Is it...
because his hands were gripping
this the entire time?
(Tightly gripping both armrests.)
Is it that when this
mechanism was activated,
the chair became electrified?
(Speculation: current was transmitted
through the armrests.)
Let us move this chair
and see whether it can be moved.
(Leave it to me.)
This might be rather heavy, Ning.
Is this chair fixed to the floor?
It is not.
No.
(Carefully inspecting the chair.)
(Be careful not to get electrocuted.)
Careful.
And the back?
Wait a second.
Wires are linked to the back.
(The chair is connected
to the stage by wires.)
There are wires.
This is an electric chair.
Wires run behind it
Just as expected.
Someone planned
to electrocute him
the moment he sat down.
Then where did the electricity
come from?
Tear it.
Go ahead.
Come on.
Do it.
(How was the wiring
arranged by the killer?)
Move the body first.
It's here.
(Exposed wiring.)
This area.
(Power is cut off. Don't attempt this.)
With scissors or a similar tool.
Does anyone have scissors?
The toolbox.
It is open now.
(Power is cut off. Don't attempt this.)
Trace the wire.
This one?
What?
Who was standing here?
Was it the two of us again?
The two of us again?
Who stood in this position?
I was standing here.
And you.
(Hidden electrical seam,
movable mirror panel.)
One of you
could have rotated this.
The two of us again?
(How old are you?
Why is it always you two?)
(Complaining about fate.)
You two again.
The two of us.
This is completely unfair.
Both the electrocution setup
and needle mechanism
were controlled by you.
All the mechanisms are with us.
(Suspicion is at its peak.)
Why do we appear so intent on murder?
(But Ding said:)
Someone wanted to frame me.
They planted it on my side.
(This son's mental state is concerning.)
This would not frame anyone else.
It is definitely
Ding.
When he dances,
he is electrifying.
Full of energy.
Ding runs on passion.
Look here.
There are copper wires here.
(Copper wires.)
How would this carry electricity?
Well...
Two poles.
Ding is right.
This is only a one-way wire.
Electricity flows through here.
To electrocute someone to death,
there must be a power
source connected to it.
Exactly.
So where did the electricity come from?
(Where was the current supplied from?)
Yes, where was it powered from?
We need to find
where the voltage input is.
(Search for the power source.)
Wait, can this be removed?
I want to know.
Is this removable?
Pull upward.
Try it.
It can be removed.
No...
Power input port.
Let us lift everything and check.
See if there is anything unusual.
Try every section.
The wires are exposed.
When this rotates to this point,
the hidden copper plate is pushed out.
Once it touches the external
wire connector,
when it rotates here,
it makes contact with this end.
Only Ding and Wen could kick
the stage panel
during the performance.
(Hidden electrified stage molding.)
But these wires
had to be installed
in advance.
Neither Wen nor Ding had ever come here
before March 24th, the day
of the murder.
Mr. He and Ms. Jin,
(Ding and Wen had no opportunity
to pre-wire anything.)
had inspected the site.
No one came afterward.
So He and I arranged it.
How was it electrified?
One of you
must have done it.
They constructed the stage.
(The stage was constructed
by He and Jin.)
(Ding and Wen triggered electrocution.)
We are responsible for turning it.
(Triggering the mechanism on site.)
It does not have to be me and He.
(Accomplice?)
It could have been you and Ding.
Or you and He, while I worked with Ding.
Understand?
But about the third-floor
circuit breaker...
The distribution box
on the third floor
of the An family villa
was equipped with leakage
protection device
to prevent electrocution accidents.
A circuit breaker.
(A leakage protection device
was installed on the third floor?)
When the human body comes
into contact with electricity,
if the voltage becomes abnormal,
the relay automatically trips.
It shuts off.
Yes.
The entire system loses power.
The breaker trips.
Exactly.
Breaker trip.
So someone must have gone upstairs
and disabled the protection device.
(Someone manipulated the third-floor
protection device as well?)
This confirms the involvement
of a third party.
There was a third participant
involved in the electrocution.
(Three people were required
to complete the electrocution murder?!)
What?
The electrocution required
someone to control it.
The electrical box should
be on the third floor.
Let's take a look.
Come on, let's check the electrical box.
(Can the distribution box
prove all three were involved?)
Move the cabinet aside.
Come on.
(The distribution box.)
The electrical box
is here.
Come.
Come quickly.
There is a note here. Wait.
When the leakage protector is on,
the power cuts off
automatically during electrocution.
But the power never shut off today.
Right?
When the leakage protector
is turned off,
the power will not cut
off during electrocution.
It's turned off now.
(The leakage protector
was switched off.)
Someone deliberately
turned this off.
Exactly.
(Electrical Safety Inspection Log)
It was switched on once at 8:30.
(Electrical Safety Inspection Log.
Inspector: Security Guard.)
Switched on at 9:00.
Again at 9:30.
Again at 10:00.
If someone wanted to turn it off,
they had to go upstairs after 10:00.
The laser pointer was also
placed after 10:00.
(Needle murder investigation phase.)
Before filming began,
the entire villa had been inspected.
No suspicious items were found.
Filming now begins.
(Laser pointer: placed after 10:00.)
So the laser pointer only appeared
after filming had started.
So how many people actually
came to the third floor?
(What exactly happened
on the third floor after 10:00?)
My guess
is that the person who placed
the laser pointer
and the person
who tampered with the electrical
box were the same.
Yes.
And that person manipulated two
separate groups into killing him.
(The laser pointer and electrical box
were operated by the same person?)
What?
Why do you think that?
Because they kept mentioning
an outsider entering the villa.
And someone was investigating
the 1992 An Glass Factory
poisoned glass incident.
That person infiltrated the An family.
So the outsider in our household
is extremely important.
(Outsiders: Mr. Wu and Aunty Pai.)
The butler. Aunty Pai.
Aunty Pai is merely infatuated.
That person has figured it out.
Everyone here wanted An Er dead.
So that individual decided
to encourage both groups to act.
(Key question: Did An Er die
from poisoned needle or electrocution?)
Let's talk downstairs.
(Who exactly is the third person?)
Come over here
and help me sort this out.
Look at the way
I hold the steering wheel.
(Handsome, right?)
(I'll count to three.)
Hurry up. I will count to three.
Let's organize it.
We have now identified
two separate groups,
correct?
Two groups of three people.
(Two murder teams: poison needle
and electrocution.)
The ones using the poisoned
needle and another using electrocution.
He and I built
the stage.
(Responsible for stage construction:
He Jiahuan and Jin Xiangyu.)
The two tasks we needed to complete
were arranging the wiring in advance.
Pre-installed wiring.
(Stage builders: 1. Bury the wires.)
Then, modifying the mirror
to make it movable.
(2. Convert the mirror
into a movable mechanism.)
It is possible
that each of us handled one task.
During the live setup on stage,
the two of you definitely
(Stage mechanism activated:
An Xiaoding and An Xiaowen.)
rotated it,
while another straightened
the wire.
(Murder method: poison needle.
'He/Jin' prepared the mechanism.)
So two combinations can kill
(Third person controlled the laser.
'Ding/Wen' rotated the mirror.)
with poison needles
(Murder method: electrocution.
'He/Jin' prepared the mechanism.)
and two
(Third person disabled the RCD.
'Ding/Wen' activated electrified setup.)
(Victim was electrocuted.)
with electricity.
(Speculated accomplice combinations:
four possibilities.)
(He Jiahuan / An Xiaoding / An Xiaowen.)
(Jin Xiangyu / An Xiaoding
/ An Xiaowen.)
There is another possibility.
One group.
A single group.
Why would it be a single group?
The person preparing the mechanisms
was one person, right?
Right.
(An Xiaoding's theory: Killer 1 set up
poison and electrical wiring.)
The person activating both mechanisms
(Killer 2. Rotates the mirror
and kicks the wiring.)
was one person?
Correct.
And the installer was the same person?
(Killer 3. Controls the laser pointer
and electrical box.)
Yes. Three people.
I think the suspicion
would become too obvious otherwise.
Right.
Risk was shared among them.
Exactly.
One chosen from the two of us.
One chosen from the other.
These two groups may not
have known about each other.
That is certainly possible.
Perhaps they never knew
what the full plan actually was.
(He Jiahuan speculates: the accomplices
were unaware of the full plan.)
Which means we merely completed
our own assigned tasks.
Exactly. And then?
Only the third person may
have understood the full plan.
Rest of us were merely
pieces on a chessboard.
We only completed our own step.
And we never realized
we were part of a murder.
That person may
have been the mastermind.
He manipulated all four of us,
yet none of us directly killed anyone.
(What role did the third
person truly play?)
I believe
this third person initiated everything.
(Jin Xiangyu speculates: third person
was mastermind.)
Because of the poisoned glass incident,
that person wanted An Er dead.
And they were extremely familiar
with this family.
They knew that each of us
had motives
for murder.
Who understands us best?
Isn't it the butler?
(Everyone agrees:)
Mr. Wu.
I think it is the butler.
(#Mr. Wu. The person who knows
the An family best! The mastermind?!)
(The instigator? The organizer?
Laser pointer × electrical box.)
He is definitely highly suspicious.
(In that case...)
Let's arrest him and get a confession.
No.
(Back to proper reasoning.)
No, that is not the logic here.
Let us review
everyone's motive again.
(Reviewing the motives for murder.)
My motive involved my mother.
(#Reviewing the motives.)
I suddenly discovered
that I was not An Yi's biological son.
Correct.
(An Xiaoding: feared his mother
losing inheritance rights.)
I feared my mother
would lose the right
to compete for inheritance.
My motive
was that An Er discovered
my son was not biologically
related to me and An Yi.
(Jin Xiangyu: An Xiaoding isn't
blood-related, affecting inheritance.)
He intended to destroy
my inheritance battle.
I do not want the world to know
that I'm not
An family daughter.
(An Xiaowen: not part of the An family.)
And I also do not want
others discovering
(Fearing exposure of her sibling
relationship with He Jiahuan.)
that my husband and I are siblings.
My motive for murder was because
he framed me.
(He Jiahuan:
An Er held leverage against him.)
I wanted evidence against him,
something I could
hold over him.
(Framed?)
(What exactly happened
between He Jiahuan and An Er?)
His motive is actually the weakest.
If I had to name a motive,
it would simply be that I also
wanted the inheritance.
(He Jiahuan's motive:)
The inheritance battle.
(Fighting for inheritance rights.)
All right.
After changing into casual clothes,
we will continue the investigation.
All right.
(What is the truth
behind the dual murder methods?)
(Next episode preview:
danger at every turn.)
All four of you are guilty.
(All of you are guilty!!)
We are suspended in midair.
Seriously?
We really are.
This is incredible.
So frightening.
(The truth remains shrouded in mystery.)
Detective Empire.
Amateur Assassin Forum.
(A mysterious assassin
website discovered?)
Reward for method.
Yes.
Six accounts.
(Six assassins emerge?)
All different.
Did you log
into the Assassin Forum?
I logged into that website before.
So you developed
the intent to kill An Er.
I wanted him dead.
I hated him.
You worked together
to kill him.
I have no idea what you
are talking about.
There is no one behind me.
Your suspicion
has been locked in.
(Accomplices with conflicting
intentions secretly join forces.)
(The killers were three
accomplices working together!)
Three-person conspiracy.
Villains find it easy
to work together.
Good people only end up
suspecting each other.
(Everyone sinks deeper into suspicion.)
I feel extremely uneasy.
If that is how you think,
there is nothing I can do.
I believe we need to turn one
of them against the others.
Then victory is guaranteed.
So one of them must
be responsible for the electrocution.
How could I
be the 'Thunder God'?
Everything Ding said is a lie.
Stop pretending.
You and I may actually
be on the same side.
I cannot allow you to get to her first.
I think I know
who my accomplice is.
And I know what you did as well.
You are my teammate.
I would never deceive you.
(Can they successfully
uncover the true killer?)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪