(Loading)
(Dungeon Pass)
(Truth Inn)
(The Truth)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(All persons, backgrounds,
and descriptions are fictional.)
(Settings and actions are setups.)
(All photos and videos)
(are authorized.)
(Safety measures were taken
during shooting. Don't try this at home.)
(Parental supervision required
for underage viewers.)
(Enter game.)
(Previous episode)
Back then,
Tui, Li, and Kuang kingdoms
ruled the world.
(Qi)
(Blade Gala)
begins
now!
Wait.
This is getting called off.
Why?
Last night,
the young master died in the hall.
He was killed with the Qide Sword.
You said I died?
He's a ghost now.
(Is Ning Waver alive or dead?)
Lapdog!
You took the enemy as your father
and betrayed your sect.
They are the Vicious Duo.
You crook!
It's a locked-room murder.
(Locked-room murder)
That's right.
A mysterious man
showed up in Ghost Market
with Qide Sword.
It is hour of Xu.
The Ghost Market opens.
The light's green.
It's on.
Let's go.
(Vocalizing)
Come on.
(Songsong Biscuit)
(I...)
(I soar into the sky.)
(To greet...)
(My empty heart)
I got chills.
Is there something there?
What's that smoke for?
No way.
Stop it.
A boat's coming.
It really is.
Is it a boat?
Yes.
We're done for.
We're finished.
Wait. Someone's rowing it.
What's on it?
Please don't be creepy.
It's here.
It's scary.
I'm so scared.
What's on it?
A corpse.
It's that...
The ghost soldier.
(Scared)
Two boats.
Three people on each.
(Super calm)
You three on one.
We'll take the other.
Sure.
Careful.
You're just going on it?
(Super brave)
We are
going
to Ghost Market.
Look behind you.
Behind you.
(Argh!)
I'm sorry. I pinched you.
Nope.
Give you some light.
Isn't this creepy?
You now look.
Nope.
It looks good.
This looks better.
Look at the light.
A perfect Rembrandt lighting.
It's nice.
I love the side lighting
where half the face is lit.
Side lighting.
Yeah.
Makes your face look smaller.
Sir.
Young man,
such a handsome gentleman.
Wearing red like that,
you're bound to attract female ghosts.
About to become a groom.
A ghost groom, that is.
Red clothes.
I won't.
We're here.
Give it to me.
We've finally arrived at Ghost Market.
What's this?
Someone's over there.
What is this?
What's this?
(Super sensitive now)
What happened?
The light went out.
(All lanterns extinguished)
Yeah.
Ghost soldiers passing through.
(Fully immersed)
Let's step aside.
We should move aside.
Step back.
Yeah. We should.
They probably want to get on it.
Please have a seat.
(Guide played by Fu Jiahua)
The ceremony is complete.
Time to go!
Don't say that!
Where are you taking us?
Dude.
Stop it.
It's fine.
We're here.
Okay.
Alright, everyone.
From here, we'll continue on foot.
Okay.
It's on.
The lights are back.
It's starting.
You can't?
I can't watch.
(This sequence is a fictional setting
created for the story)
Please wait a moment.
Ghost Market is now open!
So lively.
Everyone, before entering the market,
please read the notice.
(Ghost Market)
If you seek hidden secrets,
you must first obtain
a Ghost Market pass.
Visit different stalls
to collect Ghost Stamps.
Gather four stamps
and head to the fortune-telling stall
under the Black Tower
for four pieces of intel.
(Collect stamps to earn clues)
No stamp, no answer.
Let's check out the stalls first.
See what they're all about.
Okay.
Here!
Check us out!
Carry good luck with you,
So lively.
and every trip goes your way!
Scholars and gentlemen,
come take a look.
(Meng Lingtai as Triple Lucky puppet)
Lucky charm set.
(Shi Zhongyuan as Triple Lucky vendor)
Guaranteed to bring you luck!
(Zhou Jinglin as Triple Lucky puppet)
Lucky!
(Huang Jiayi as riddle vendor)
Riddles to tease your mind!
(Zeng Yiqiong as animal hide vendor)
The best hides
keeps out wind and evil spirits!
(Yang Xinxin as umbrella vendor)
Fine umbrellas.
(Dai Daochao as smelting vendor)
Weapon forged here!
(Li Qi as weapon vendor)
Come take a look, folks!
We have all kinds of weapons.
What do they sell?
They sell fabric.
Let's skip it then.
Ladies and gentlemen, come take a look.
Don't miss out.
What's this?
A riddle stall.
Let's check the riddles out.
Care to solve some riddles?
What do we win?
Solve two riddles
(Curious)
to get one stamp.
Solve three to get...
(Stamps?)
(Riddle stall)
What's this?
(Jin wants to see)
We're checking the riddles.
Riddle time?
Let's try it.
This is Ning's forte.
You're the king of puns.
It's destiny.
None of your business.
Who's the Pun King?
(Certified Pun King)
Come on.
Let's guess.
This is...
(Tiger and horse)
Carry a sword. Tiger. Horse.
Sword horse.
Warrior maiden?
Warrior.
(Horse and sword)
Warrior maiden.
(Getting excited)
Sword horse.
(Taking a closer look)
This is a leopard.
(Leopard)
Leopard.
Leopard. Horse.
(Horse. Leopard)
(Tiger, horse, leopard...)
(Throwing words together)
Right away...
(Right away...)
Get rich
right away.
(Get rich right away)
(A new Pun Queen)
Got one right.
Get rich right away.
(So that's it)
Keep it up!
What's pork belly in a pot?
(Meat. Pork)
How many pieces?
(Everything comes back to pork)
Six.
Belly.
Lots of varieties.
Many...
(Meat. Pot)
(Pork belly in the pot)
(Pork belly in the pot. A pot of meat)
Twice-cooked pork!
(Twice-cooked pork)
Yes.
That's the right answer.
(I'm a genius)
Twice-cooked pork.
(Amazing)
(Even better than I am)
Look at the question.
Why are you looking at me?
(Classic teacher line)
Dude, you...
(Sibling bickering as usual)
(Deep in thought)
(Pig. River.)
(Pig. Looking)
(River-looking pig)
(Pig looking at the river)
It should be four words.
Stay (pig) river. River stay (pig)
Pig.
(Pig shot)
(Can't escape form pig puns)
(Pig, river, look)
River stay (pig). Stay (pig) river.
Main river.
Who rules the tide?
Who rules the world?
Pig.
Look.
Across...
Look at what?
Longing with all your heart.
Longing...
Shore.
Turn back before it's too late.
Nope. None of those.
Last one.
(Come on, everyone)
Does it have to be four characters?
No.
Together.
Pig and calendar.
How many pigs are there?
Is it just one?
One.
One pig... one pillar...
A pillar holding up the sky.
What pig?
@¥%¥pig, right?
@%#¥pig.
(Trying to get away with it)
%¥#%¥pig.
Why isn't it right?
#%#¥pig.
(Wrong)
A pig that didn't cross the river.
Piggy hero.
(Just kidding)
River-crossing pig.
(Pig, river, block)
Pig didn't cross the river.
River-crossing pig.
River...
River pig.
Guinea pig.
(Guinea (river-blocked) pig)
(As expected of Ning)
I knew we could count on you.
Guinea pig.
That's right.
(Got three right, gets the seal)
You answered three riddles.
We are mortal enemies with pigs.
(We'll get it next time for sure)
I'll give you a stamp now.
Sure.
Let's go.
Let's go there.
I have Invisibility Card.
What does it do again?
I can hide myself.
I can take all their stuff.
What's this?
(Medicine)
Medicine.
There's nothing here.
Don't miss out. Check us out!
(Fragrance wafts for miles)
Legendary stuffed bread.
(Each bite worthy of praise)
A single bite touches the soul.
Hello.
Smells amazing.
Did you make this?
Yes.
(Dong Jiaqi Tiffany as big eater vendor)
I brought this from Chang'an.
The famous one-bite stuffed bread.
If all of you can finish it in one bite,
you'll earn a stamp.
(Right up my alley)
That's too easy. Bring it on.
Look at this little foodie.
(Little foodie)
Little foodie
(Still growing)
is still growing)
(Just you watch)
Okay.
Sit.
Let's sit here.
I think it's going to be delicious.
Ghost Market has everything.
(Ready to unleash the abyssal appetite)
Okay.
It should be really good.
(Hungry and waiting)
Very delicious.
Not gonna lie.
It's pretty big.
It's a big bite.
(Watch me swallow it whole)
(Can't beat my appetite)
Is it good?
I'll try it too.
(Easy-peasy)
Is it good?
So simple.
(All in one bite)
(We got this)
(Mouth too small)
(Mouth can't cover the bread)
(A mouth full of food
leaves no room for mockery)
(Only one bread left
before they get the stamp)
(It's alright)
(Won't give up)
(Everyone succeeded)
This is awesome.
We're eating their food,
and they're giving us money.
(It's fun, we love it, come back often)
What kind of logic is this?
Give me a napkin.
You ate it in one bite too?
It's delicious.
(Obtained two stamps)
Would you two like more stamps?
Of course.
Yes.
Okay.
Restore the Money-Saving Manual
in 30 seconds
to get one stamp.
Okay. We'll try.
Sure.
Find the corners first.
The bridge's here.
Here.
Done.
Isn't this Tongcheng Travel?
You know about this Money-Saving Manual?
Of course.
Tongcheng Travel app
makes booking stays very affordable.
We ought to travel the world
with Tongcheng Travel.
Yes. Not only is it cheap,
but you can also
get cash backs for bookings.
Save even more
with Tongcheng Travel.
Alright. I'll stamp your pass.
Thank you.
You may continue your journey.
Okay.
Thank you.
At crucial moments, you can always
count on Tongcheng Travel.
Of course. Let's go.
Thank you.
It was delicious.
Come on.
Do a reading.
You ought to go a reading.
Come on.
Do a reading.
(Yang Zhibo as fortune-telling vendor)
Esteemed guests,
I can tell you have many questions.
That's right.
One stamp grants you one question.
Okay.
You can ask anything.
Tonight,
Who is the killer?
will it rain?
(A little humor)
Alright.
Tonight.
(Fortune teller accepted your request)
Tonight...
Wait. No!
(Argh!)
Think before you ask.
(I'll forgive you all)
Okay. We'll think about it.
Then let's ask him
who it is.
(Ask him who brought Qide Sword)
Will he know?
I don't think we should ask that.
He won't tell us.
Okay.
Let's ask why didn't Ning Waver die.
Okay?
Yeah. Sure.
Okay.
One question.
Sure.
Why didn't...
You crossed it out
before I even asked you.
Why didn't Ning Waver die?
Have you forgotten
the legend
of the ghost soldier's resurrection?
Scammed me out of my money!
(Change it into a question)
So that's it?
Yeah.
Yes.
Then he'll say you came back
because of the ghost soldiers.
I think we need another angle.
Another angle.
Where did
Yan Reason go?
What if he says,
"Don't you know"?
"Things have been really weird lately".
Then we're done for again.
Then let's just beat him up, okay?
(Solving it by hand)
Okay, come on.
If he says that,
we'll beat him up.
Okay.
(The muscle is ready)
Where did Yan Reason go?
(Try talking nonsense again)
(I'm behaving now. Please spare me)
How about this?
Do you have anything
related to her?
You can describe it.
A pair of black embroidered shoes.
(Yan)
They have beads and jade on them.
And a pattern.
There's a special pattern on the insole.
The mark
of the Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
Right. The Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
Ask him where else
that mark can be found.
(Where else is the Eagle King's mark?)
Where else is the Eagle King's mark?
The Thousand-Faced Eagle King
lives on top of this Black Tower.
(Ghost Market. Black Tower)
But
there are two guards at the entrance.
They're really tough.
Be careful.
Okay. How do we get in?
That will require
your wisdom and courage.
(One useless line for everyone)
I swear, I almost smacked you.
Seriously, what is wrong with you?
Where can we find the mystery man?
On top of the Ghost Tower.
Does the mystery man
have any specific look?
A black cloak.
He carries the Qide Sword.
The real Qide Sword.
I just remembered something.
What?
Didn't I say I was selling Qide Swords?
And how did I get
those Qide Swords?
I didn't actually forge them.
One day,
I was walking down the road,
and I found them.
Suddenly, I saw someone ahead.
He had a wine gourd.
He was a mystery man
who reeked of alcohol.
A wine gourd?
(A wine gourd again)
Didn't you make
a wine gourd for your master?
Yes. I made one for my master.
So his master...
(The one who sold He Ha the fake swords)
And my master also
(is Ding Pillar's master, Uncle Meng)
wears that black cloak.
Right.
And his hat...
I don't even know what he looks like.
Okay.
So it could be the same person.
Maybe he's the mystery man.
He's the one who gave me
fifty Qide Swords.
Fifty?
(Qide Sword wholesaler)
Fifty Qide Swords.
He told me to sell them.
Were those swords real?
They had to be fake.
Fake.
I bought them cheap.
- Let's go in first.
- Let's go.
I'll go ask first.
Let's just go.
What will happen if we go first?
Okay.
This is the Black Tower!
No outsiders allowed!
Their eyes are so high up.
Can't we crawl in along the ground?
We're the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King's grandsons.
The Thousand-Faced Eagle King's
grandsons.
(Used to instantly
lowering their seniority)
Who said that?
You... Who wants to be his grandson?
(Don't drag us into this)
If you wanna be his grandson, go ahead.
We've got Skill Cards, right, guys?
Invisibility Card.
Who has the Invisibility Card?
I have it.
(Ning Waver has the Invisibility Card)
I have the Transport Card.
Great. Then summon a train
and run them over.
Then we can get in.
(The idea guy is here)
Summon a plane.
Get a plane. We'll fly up there.
No. Just use a cannon.
Transport.
We'll ride the cannon later.
(Who's the cannonball?)
I have the Disguise Card.
That's easy, then.
With the Disguise Card,
I'll just turn into them.
Exactly.
I can't walk on stilts, Ning.
No. Turn into
the Thousand-Faced Eagle King!
I can't.
Because the Disguise Card
only works if you already know
what they look like.
Then let's use the Invisibility Card.
The Invisibility Card.
Can we all turn invisible?
Yes.
Let's go invisible for three minutes.
No problem. Okay.
Come on.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Use
the Invisibility Card!
(Invisibility Card: Hides you
from dungeon natives for 3 minutes)
Invisible cloak!
Okay. Let's go!
I can't see you guys!
Let's go!
Let me try.
Go. I'm good.
Go.
Why'd everyone disappear?
(Setting off)
Whose foot is this?
Lower.
There are no feet.
Whose arm is this?
Whose leg?
There are no feet.
That's so weird.
(Easy pass)
Why are there so many legs?
(Can't get through?)
Go.
Get down!
Crouch.
Where's that leg from?
Crouch down, Ning.
Why is it gone?
It's gone.
Maybe we were seeing things.
(Front-row spectators)
Go!
(Sneaking along)
Hold on.
Your butts are in my face.
That's really rude.
Whose leg?
Gone again.
Your butt is way too big.
(Teammate roasting him)
Who bumped into me?
Wait.
Who hit us?
Whose leg?
Close the door.
- Why's the door open?
- Close the door!
Is it that windy today?
(Successfully entered the Black Tower)
See this symbol?
I see it.
Yeah, I see it.
Eagle King.
(What does Yan Reason have to do
with the Thousand-Faced Eagle King?)
Who's crying?
(Where's that child crying coming from?)
Here!
Stairs.
(Why is there a child crying
on the second floor?)
It's okay. You're all safe now.
The healer said
that mysterious person in the cloak
gave you the antidote in time.
So the poisoning wasn't too bad.
You just need rest to recover.
What does he mean, rest to recover?
It should be
those kids with rotting wounds.
The mysterious person
gave them medicine.
(The mysterious person saved the kids)
So he's a good guy?
(Is the mysterious person good?)
(Second-floor guard post)
Did we save all the kids in the cells?
Except for the ones
who were already dead,
we got them all out.
But Yan was taken by them.
Yan?
(Yan Reason was taken)
What? That Tui guy is awful!
Exactly.
Back then, the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King made up
the ghost soldier legend
and built the Ghost Market
to scare off outsiders.
It was to protect
those important people,
and to give refugees like us,
poor folks like us,
a place to hide from the storm.
But that Tui guy
used the ghost soldier story
to hurt children.
Used the ghost soldier story
So the Thousand-Faced Eagle King
is a good guy?
(Thousand-Faced Eagle King: created the
ghost soldier legend and Ghost Market)
(To protect important people
and help refugees)
The Thousand-Faced Eagle King
was the one
who started this ghost soldier legend.
But his plan
was used by Lord Tui
to use this
to hurt children.
Right.
(Lord Tui used the "ghost soldier
legend" to persecute children)
Our Yan something...
Yan Reason.
Yan Reason was taken by them.
Now they're saying...
Right.
She was taken while saving the children.
But who took her?
Think about it. Lord Tui
is already dead.
So who could've taken
Yan Reason?
(Who took Yan Reason
while she was saving the children?)
The Thousand-Faced Eagle King.
They said he's a good guy.
What if he wanted to save her?
Didn't they say she was hurt? Missing?
She was bleeding. How could he save her?
(Ning's guess: Yan is already dead)
Wait. I think someone's downstairs.
Let's check.
Put this on.
Cover up.
Quick.
Someone's coming down.
No one's here?
That was probably the mechanism chair.
Must be new intel again.
Mechanism chair?
New intel again?
This is the mechanism chair.
(Mechanism chair)
Two pieces of intel.
Intel one.
Let's read one first.
(Intel one)
The cloaked person holding
the real Qide Sword has been secretly
making fake swords to confuse everyone.
(Someone has been secretly making
fake swords to confuse everyone)
We found out
he could enter and leave the Black Tower
(Intel one)
because he was very close
to Master Gui
who often treated the children there.
Intel two is
a photo of He Ha.
(Intel two)
It's called Mastermind.
He says,
"That scammer selling Qide Swords
has entered the city".
"Should we kick him out"?
Then the reply says, "It's fine".
"No idiot would fall for his tricks".
"Ignore him".
So one thing is confirmed.
The person who sold you the fake sword
is the mystery man.
(Guess: the person who sold He Ha
the fake sword is the mystery man)
The guy who sold you the fake sword
must have the real one, right?
And your key clue was that...
He wore a black cloak.
His hood covered his face,
and he had a jade pendant
with "Xia" on it.
I couldn't see his face.
Every night, he came to teach me.
At dawn, he left.
Okay. Then it's possible that
his teacher and the person
(Ding Pillar's teacher)
who sold you the fake sword
(The person who sold He the fake sword)
are the same person.
(Same person)
But
why would he sell fake Qide Swords?
To protect the real sword.
Right. To confuse everyone.
And he's really close to that master.
(He was close to Master Gui)
He used the medicine to save the kids.
There was a healer stall.
Did it sell medicine?
Yes, but no one was there.
There's nothing here.
Can we find Master Gui there
and ask him about
the Thousand-Faced Eagle King?
Exactly. Let's go.
So what if we walk out
like we own the place?
They won't let us in.
They can't stop us from leaving, right?
Makes sense.
Move aside, guys.
Three, two, one.
(Walking out like bosses)
Hold on. Who let you in?
Go!
Move it!
Where did all these people come from?
Getting in is hard.
Getting out is easy.
Get out!
Go!
Okay.
Hurry!
Who let you in?
- Okay.
- Hurry!
=The Truth (Season 4)=
Okay. Let's go find Master Gui.
(Loading)
(Medicine)
(Master Gui, played by Lin Tan)
There really is someone here.
Come on, guys.
Someone's here.
Hello.
Master.
Come. Have a seat.
Come on, Ning.
Master.
Come. I'll check your pulse first.
Another pulse check?
Go ahead.
(We're already here)
This is a woman's pulse.
So you can't see, right?
I have a slight eye condition.
(Master Gui has an eye condition)
Not bad.
Judging by your pulse,
this is classic career brain
with a foodie soul.
(Diagnosed with career brain
+ foodie soul)
Your pulse has a clever spark
of everyday life.
Three parts street smarts,
seven parts brilliance.
I believe
standing before me
must be a steel-boned beauty.
Steel-boned?
(Bang bang or not bang bang)
A steel beauty.
You're good at compliments.
My turn.
Here.
Come on. Praise me.
(Waiting for praise)
Sir,
you should pay more attention
to your heart lately.
For real?
Based on my reading,
in July,
you'll meet a woman
who makes your heart race.
One look at her,
and you'll feel like you're burning up.
(He got all that from a pulse?)
Burning up that much?
Isn't that a little too hot?
Too accurate.
(Stay tuned for Overdo)
One moment, she says she loves you.
The next, she says she hates you.
Then she pretends she doesn't love you.
Then she loves you like crazy.
In short, sir,
your heart is in for a wild ride.
Master,
so
how do I survive this?
It's not something to survive.
Just let it happen.
(Just let him burn)
No cure.
You're destined to burn!
That was a great pulse reading.
I love watching He fall in love.
Master, I'm sick too.
I always think people like me.
What should I do?
Okay.
Let me take a good look.
This is clearly a happy pulse.
Not again.
Here we go again.
Not that kind of happy.
The happiness I mean
is joy.
In other words,
(Beaming with joy)
you're really good
at lifting the mood around you.
It's joy as in charming.
Nice.
Okay. Come on, Master.
You...
(Check me too)
Seriously.
Master Gui.
Very creepy.
Wait.
What?
Why can't I feel your pulse?
(Why does Ning Waver have no pulse?)
What?
Could you be a dead man?
That's strange.
How can a dead man walk
and talk like he's alive?
We can even see him.
Right.
Life and death are major illnesses.
This man has a serious condition.
Look at my little clinic.
It's so simple.
You should find another way.
I can't treat this.
Then I want to ask.
What's this about you
saving children?
Children?
Yes.
A mysterious person
holding the Qide Sword
often used your connection
to enter that tower
and treat the children.
Who is that person?
You're talking about
a very mysterious person, right?
Yes.
Very mysterious.
A mysterious person.
That mysterious person
has been coming here a lot
lately for medicine.
(The mysterious person has been
getting medicine here lately)
But a gentleman's friendship
is light as water.
I don't know his name.
Also,
I have some trouble with my eyes.
So I never saw what
he really looked like.
(Master Gui doesn't know who he is)
I just remember
he often wore
a cloak.
A few weeks ago, the last time
he came here for medicine,
he was badly poisoned.
The poison had reached his bones.
So I checked his pulse.
I found that his time was almost up.
He didn't have much longer.
So I asked him,
with poison this severe,
(The mystery man was poisoned and dying)
how did you get poisoned?
He said
it was because of those children.
To save them, he tested the medicine
on himself.
(The mysterious person risked himself
to save the children)
Those children ate the rotten soup
and were poisoned.
He couldn't find the cure,
so he had no choice
but to use himself as a test subject.
He tried each medicine one by one.
Then I asked him,
why go that far?
He said those children
are Tui Kingdom's future.
As long as he could heal them,
even giving up his own life
would be worth it.
He even joked with me.
He said the medicine
was so hard to swallow.
If only it tasted
as good as his usual
god-tier stuffed bread,
he'd still gladly do it.
(The highest chivalry is sacrificing
oneself for what is right)
Right.
He also left
this wooden box with me.
I never opened it.
I don't know what's inside either.
Everyone,
I think
you're good people.
He's a good person too.
So this box
is now in your care.
Okay.
It's Da Men Junzi.
(It's Da Men Junzi)
A wine flask.
Meng.
Master Meng.
This belongs to my master.
(Meng, wine flask)
My master, Uncle Meng.
His wine flask broke,
so I made him a new one
and engraved the character Meng on it.
My master.
(Uncle Meng is the mysterious person)
This is my tonic, right?
You've taken this medicine?
After I fell off the cliff,
Junzi Ruyu
would always bring me special tonics
to help me recover.
Special tonic
restores inner strength.
Specifically cures the effects
of Eleven-Spice Tendon Powder.
Not long after taking it,
my inner strength returned.
(Ke Stubborn's antidote was given
by the mysterious person.)
Whose clothes are these?
These are mine.
Your clothes?
That day, I followed the man in black,
then
I almost got discovered.
Then...
Someone rescued you.
He grabbed my collar and pulled me away.
(The mysterious person saved Yang Glory)
So
a piece of the clothing was torn off.
There's a receipt here.
(Tui City Money House Receipt)
All debts are settled.
The principal and interest
owed by Jin Thrifty
have been fully repaid.
From this day onward,
we will no longer trouble her.
This is hereby certified.
Tui City Money House.
Yes, I borrowed money
from this money house.
Why is the receipt in this box?
It means this person
is connected to all of us.
He has secretly been helping everyone.
He repaid your debt.
So this so-called Uncle Meng,
the mysterious person,
has helped all four of you before,
right?
Yes.
(The mysterious person, Uncle Meng,
taught Ding Pillar martial arts)
(The mysterious person
repaid Jin Thrifty's debt)
(The mysterious person gave
Ke Stubborn the antidote)
(The mysterious person
rescued Yang Glory in a crisis)
(Why did the mysterious
person secretly help everyone?)
Right, everyone.
I just remembered.
He left
a package with me.
What is this?
What is this rod?
Bamboo?
Distance.
(Distance)
Four Symbols Manual.
There are four hidden martial arts
skills in the martial world.
They require strong inner power to use.
But if all four skills
are used together,
the user will be immobilized
for fifteen breaths.
What does that mean?
You will be frozen in place
for fifteen breaths.
(Black pink)
You will stop for fifteen breaths.
The four skills are extremely powerful.
Only specific moves can counter them.
However, the four counter
moves restrain each other.
If all four are used at the same time,
the user will suffer backlash.
One of the four secret skills
is Hedong Roar.
Countered only
by Cosmic Absorbing Skill.
The second secret skill
is Dark Rope Skill.
Countered only by Toad Skill.
The third secret skill
is Itch Finger.
Countered only
by Enjoying the Claim the Gain.
The fourth secret skill
is Sandstrike.
Countered only by Groundquake Skill.
The order of the four counter moves
will result in different
backlash symptoms.
(Blindness)
(Frantic Dancing)
(Spinning Around)
(Lost All Inner Power)
(Paralyzed)
(Handstand)
(Different counterattack orders
result in different backlash effects)
(Cosmic Absorbing Mark)
(Frog Palm Mark)
(Butt Mark)
(Shattered by Ground Shake)
Could it be
the marks on the mountain manor?
Probably.
Maybe.
Your father used three moves,
and you also used three moves.
These three moves left traces behind.
Shouldn't there be three people?
There are three people.
One culprit, a father and son.
(Lord Tui, Ning Waver & mysterious guy)
Yes.
The one holding the Qide Sword
was the culprit.
The Qide Sword.
The mysterious person
exchanged moves with it.
And this was left behind
by the culprit, right?
(Ding Pillar's theory: The Four Symbols
Manual was the culprit's)
Then where was he
while the fight happened?
(Where was Ning Waver at that time?)
He was already...
Lying there.
He was lying there.
Then the mysterious person
and Lord Tui fought there.
That's right.
(Ding Pillar's theory: Culprit fought
Lord Tui, Ning Waver was out.)
I think it happened like this.
The mysterious guy brought
the Qide Sword to kill his father.
His father used
the Cosmic Absorbing Skill
to pull his son over
and use him as a shield.
(The sacrifice)
Unexpectedly, the sword
pierced through both of them.
(Jin Thrifty's theory: Lord Tui
used Ning Waver to block the sword.)
(Both were pierced
by the culprit's sword)
The Toad Skill definitely exists, right?
Yes.
They all exist.
He just doesn't know the order.
That's right.
(Who fought whom?)
(Crime scene clues?)
Let's head back.
I'll use the Transport Card
to take us back, okay?
Okay.
Using Transport Card.
(Transport Card: Obtain a vehicle.)
(Transport Card)
Could it be the Portal Door?
Is this real?
Is this our vehicle?
What is this?
The Portal Door.
Let's go.
We're really here.
We're back.
We got back instantly.
Everything is clear now.
This...
this is the last position of the move.
Yes.
(The final skill before death)
The pull ended here.
I think we can
use the victim's position
to reconstruct what happened.
(He Ha's theory:
Use the final move before death)
(Recreate the fight sequence)
Okay.
What are the steps
for the Cosmic Absorbing Skill?
(Walk four steps east)
Four steps east.
Where is east?
This room faces east.
(The hall's entrance faces east)
So the Cosmic Absorbing Skill
moves east.
(North, East, West, South)
We go behind the east direction.
Move backwards.
(Four steps east)
Four steps.
One step.
Two steps.
Three steps.
Four steps.
Okay, this position.
Okay.
This is the Toad Skill.
(Toad Skill marks)
Let's take a look at the Toad Skill.
Starting with the Toad Skill,
it leaves a palm print.
Then it jumps over five
and a half steps,
and continues in a toad posture.
The toad marks appear
both in front and behind.
Yes.
So it was here.
(Toad marks 1 & 2)
It jumped from here.
Let's find the combination.
The final two skills
were Toad Skill
and Cosmic Absorbing Skill.
It's Claim the Gain Skill,
then Groundquake Skill,
then Toad Skill,
and Cosmic Absorbing Skill.
(The final two moves)
(The combinations of Cosmic
Absorbing Skill and Toad Skill)
(Verification)
The first one is here.
(If it is Claim the Gain, Groundquake,)
Then it's Claim the Gain.
(Toad Skill, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
These two round balls are
butt marks.
Butt marks.
(The counter move: Claim and Gain Skill)
That's right.
This is Groundquake.
Channel inner power
and walk three steps to activate it.
Within one inch,
everything shatters.
Then,
channel power and walk less than
four and a half steps.
So from here,
move back four and a half steps.
This should be it, right?
Yes.
He walks three steps first.
After the Groundquake hits here,
then four steps,
after the strike...
After the strike,
Toad Skill lands here,
pushes him over,
then Cosmic Absorbing Skill
pulls him back here.
Yeah.
Then the last two end up embracing.
Exactly.
Measure
three steps from here.
Come on.
One, three...
It can't reach.
Four.
Three.
This is four.
That takes four steps.
Four and a half.
(4.5 steps)
(3 steps)
(Steps don't match)
(This order doesn't work)
One, two.
That's three steps.
Exactly three.
From here to there is
four and a half steps.
That's right.
(3 steps, 4.5 steps)
(What's the correct move order?)
The final move is
definitely Cosmic Absorbing Skill,
right?
Yeah.
So let's work backward.
Cosmic Absorbing Skill is the last move.
That leaves
three,
four,
five.
(Final move: Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
(Rule out: Claim the Gain, Groundquake,
Toad Skill, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
(Claim the Gain, Toad Skill,
Groundquake, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
(Toad Skill, Claim the Gain,
(Test: Claim the Gain, Toad Skill,
Groundquake, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
What if we pair Cosmic Absorbing Skill
with Groundquake?
(If: Claim, Toad, Ground, Absorb)
Can Groundquake reach?
(If: Toad, Claim, Ground, Cosmic)
Cosmic Absorbing works with Groundquake.
It does.
Let's reconstruct it.
From the beginning.
Start with Claim the Gain.
Claim the Gain first,
right?
(Test: Claim the Gain, Toad Skill,
Groundquake, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
Come on.
(Walk 3 steps)
Stomp and leave the mark.
Then channel power and walk three steps.
Three steps. One, two, three.
(3 steps)
Reach this spot.
Toad Skill.
Okay.
Yeah, after Claim the Gain comes
the Toad Skill.
Then it jumps here.
(Over 5 steps)
That has to be right.
Then comes Groundquake.
Walk 3 steps first.
Three steps won't reach.
It won't reach.
One.
Two.
Three.
(More than 3 steps)
That's about three and a half.
So where do the 3 steps fit?
(Rule out: Claim, Toad, Ground, Absorb)
(Rule out: Toad, Claim, Ground, Absorb)
(3 steps, Over 5 steps, Over 3 steps)
But there's no 3-step point nearby.
Except this one.
Yes, this is exactly 3 steps.
From here to here is 3 steps.
Claim the Gain can't reach there.
It can't reach here either.
It can only reach here.
(Claim the Gain can only
connect to one Toad Skill mark)
Did we miss something?
Are we missing anything?
Channel inner power and walk 3 steps.
Everything within one inch
shatters.
Then walk less than 4.5 steps.
Groundquake is 3 steps, then 4.5, right?
That's right.
Let's work from this.
We'll use this as the fixed point.
Okay.
(Groundquake)
I shattered it here.
Before that,
I walked three steps.
Yeah.
Right?
So which point
gets me here in three steps?
Only this one.
(He Ha's theory: Groundquake and Toad)
Only this point is three steps away.
Alright.
So if this is
Groundquake's starting point,
three steps bring me here.
One quake.
Then where would
another 4.5 steps take me?
There.
Here.
Let's assume that's the point.
Okay.
That is
4.5 steps.
I end up here.
How many steps does the butt mark take?
The fart bounce move
is three steps.
Here.
(He He's theory:
Groundquake + Claim the Gain)
From here to here.
Here.
I can use Cosmic
Absorbing Skill directly.
(Cosmic Absorbing Skill:
Move east 4 steps)
Toad Skill jumps over directly.
Jumps here.
The quake hits this.
So Toad Skill is first.
That's right.
Got it?
Toad Skill.
Jump here.
Walk here and quake.
Walk four steps here.
Do the fart move.
Then walk
three steps.
Then strike.
Yes.
Then move here.
(Moves used in the fight)
(Toad Skill, Groundquake, Claim
the Gain, Cosmic Absorbing Skill)
(Dark Rope Skill: Attack)
(Toad Skill: Counter)
(Sandstrike: Attack)
(Groundquake: Counter)
(Itch Finger: Attack)
(Claim the Gain: Counter)
(Hedong Roar: Attack)
(Cosmic Absorbing Skill: Counter)
Then Toad Skill goes first, right?
Then you're frozen.
Frozen for ten breaths.
(Frozen for ten breaths)
Wait.
There's a line at the start
of the manual.
We missed it earlier.
It says
there are four secret martial arts.
They need strong inner power.
But
if all four moves are used in a row,
the attacker
will definitely
be frozen for fifteen breaths.
For example,
I'm using it here.
We're facing each other.
Right.
You stand here.
Your foot is here.
(Victim. Attacker)
The last move goes like this.
Catch it.
Suck it in.
Then...
We both freeze.
(Both freeze)
But he wakes up faster than you.
He wakes up faster than me.
(Attacker frozen for fifteen breaths)
You get fifteen breaths.
I get fifteen breaths.
So what does that mean?
The master of Chivalry Manor
died last night
at Chivalry Manor.
He's dead.
And
on his wound,
there was a silver mark.
What does that mean?
A silver mark?
On the left side of his chest.
Where the heart is.
Silver.
Do you have a wound
on your right shoulder?
Yes.
I got it.
His wound proves they both
froze.
The killer
walked here
and stabbed through.
Look at the wounds. Am I right?
(Bloodstain 1. Bloodstain 2)
Yeah. One in front and one behind.
You mean one sword stabbed
through both of them?
Of course.
(Yang's proud theory)
(When Ning and Tui froze together)
We were like this.
(Stabbed through by the killer)
Then a third person
stabbed through both of us.
Yeah.
I'm the killer.
Right.
You two are frozen.
At that moment, the killer...
We're both frozen.
The killer doesn't even
need martial arts.
No martial arts needed.
He stabs through me.
Then you fall.
I
lie here.
When he comes in, he sees me lying here.
Right.
Right?
So Ning Waver was fighting Lord Tui.
That's what I think.
(The one fighting Lord Tui
was Ning Waver)
But wasn't Ning Waver
knocked out?
I chased him with Tui's men.
But our lightness skills
weren't that good.
We couldn't catch up.
When we saw them again,
Ning Waver had already
been knocked out.
The man in black carried Ning Waver
into Chivalry Manor.
Before they entered,
we actually saw Lord Tui.
Qide Sword!
Don't hurt my son!
Then he went in alone.
Ning Waver was faking it.
Right!
He was actually working with the killer
to set a trap.
(Baiting the target?)
This was your plan with the killer.
(The killer and Ning Waver
set this up together?)
It's possible.
No. I think that's it.
Someone...
One of you four
teamed up with Ning Waver and said,
"Let's kill Lord Tui".
Yes.
Then Ning said,
"Okay".
But this person
actually wanted to kill both me
and Lord Tui.
He used me by playing along.
(Theory: The killer used Ning Waver
to kill two people at once)
Then he stabbed through both of us.
Then I lay here
and died.
No.
The killer didn't mean to kill you.
It was just out of desperation.
Maybe at that moment,
he had to kill you too.
(Ning Waver was killed by mistake)
Let's say it's me.
I get this manual.
What have I always called you?
Ning the Lapdog.
I've always hated you.
Why would I ever ask you,
"Do you wanna catch him"?
How could we possibly work together?
I must've hated you all along.
Then one day, I suddenly find out...
What?
You're helping me?
So you're actually a good guy.
I found out you're a good guy, right?
You'd say, "Yes, I am".
I got this manual by accident.
Then I say, "Here. Take it".
Go help me kill him.
Let's work together.
(Theory one: The killer used Ning Waver)
(Theory two: The killer
and Ning Waver were accomplices)
(Was Ning Waver used by the killer
or was he an accomplice?)
(Tui City Money House, Truth Inn)
The next time I saw them,
Ning Waver had already been knocked out.
The man in black
was carrying Ning Waver
(Chivalry Manor)
and went into Chivalry Manor.
Something just hit me.
Go on.
When I saw
Ning being carried
on the man's shoulder,
Ning was lying face down.
So when he carried him,
I never saw Ning's face.
(It was impossible to tell)
(Whether the man was carrying Ning)
It's unclear.
And there's another thing.
The second time I saw him,
I clearly heard
the 11PM night watch call.
That's hour of Zi, right?
Right.
(Timeline check)
The 11PM watch call doesn't add up.
(Before 11PM, He saw them fighting)
At the 11PM call,
(Saw him carrying Ning, not his face)
I was in my shop.
Me too.
At the same time, I saw my waiter,
my cook,
and my customer.
(11PM, all four suspects
were in the shop)
Then that's really strange.
(How was the killer
in two places at once?)
I didn't catch up.
(Tui City Money House)
The next time I saw them,
(Blind spot on the route)
the man in black was carrying Ning.
I was in my shop.
I was there too.
No.
I heard the 11PM watch call
right when I saw him carrying someone.
Right.
We were all there.
But
before 11PM,
(Timeline check)
there was a gap.
(Before 11PM, He saw them fighting)
Maybe five or ten minutes.
(11PM, saw him carry Ning, not his face)
I didn't see him.
(11PM, all four suspects in the shop)
I didn't see either of them.
(Before and at 11PM, no one saw
the man or Ning Waver)
So you saw them fight first.
Then for ten minutes,
they vanished.
(No witness for those ten minutes)
They vanished.
So what does that mean?
Hold on.
What?
No, hold on.
This morning, we kept saying
that thing was used for lightness skill.
Right.
Why
are they here?
Why are there
a cuju ball and bamboo slips
in the hall?
So when he carried him,
I never saw Ning's face.
Before 11PM,
there was a gap.
Maybe five minutes. Maybe ten.
I didn't see him.
I didn't see either of them.
Because this is the head.
Is this that body?
(Theory: They used similar-shaped items
to fake Ning Waver being carried)
So this is...
This is the dummy.
You're saying these bamboo slips
were used as a dummy, right?
A dummy, yes.
I get it now.
At that time,
Ning put on the man in black's cloak.
Then he carried
a dummy made with the bamboo slips
and cuju ball.
(That's the idea)
So he was working with the killer
from the inside.
Exactly.
He let the killer stay here...
To create
an alibi.
That's exactly what I meant.
Maybe they switched outfits.
Or maybe what he was carrying
wasn't even a person.
(Theory: They faked a dummy
to create an alibi for the killer)
Right. That's the first one.
Second,
he lured his father in.
His father was the target.
So,
it was
to kill him.
Godfather.
(Never call a thief Father)
Godfather. Right.
Here's the problem.
How did the killer leave this room?
That's the biggest issue.
Right.
There are only two ways.
One is using lightness skill
to get out here.
The other is through the secret room's
back door or something.
(Speculation: two escape routes)
Then,
let's check the yard
and see what else is here,
okay?
I think there must be
some clues or something.
Wait.
What's this?
It's a laundry basket.
This is...
This outfit
I saw
Ning Waver
wearing that night.
(Ning Waver's clothes)
Check the path outside.
Wait.
(There's a bird's nest
outside the window)
That proves one thing.
No one went through this window.
The swallow's nest is still there.
Does it push out
or pull in?
It only pushes out.
Pushes out.
Then if you push it out, that'd fall.
Right.
There'd be nothing left up there.
So no one went through it.
(The killer didn't escape from here)
No one went through.
Right.
Then he left through the secret room.
Right?
And he knew about the secret room.
So he turned the vase.
He even knew about the vase.
(The killer escaped
through the secret room)
Let's check the clothes first.
Look closely.
There's blood on it.
It went all the way through.
It did.
(The clothes were pierced)
Wait.
Was this piece pierced too?
(Also pierced)
They all were.
And on the black inner robe,
there's that silver mark.
That proves it really is mine.
There's a receipt.
(Receipt)
He bought two black inner robes.
This proves
his theory was right.
At first, the killer himself
passed the corner.
(Ning switched the dummy there)
He had another dummy ready,
carried on his back.
Ning Waver did that part.
(Theory confirmed: Ning faked the dummy)
He and the killer
(To create an alibi for the killer)
were already working together.
Okay. If that's the case...
I closed it.
Wait.
Did you close it from outside?
I just turned it here.
Counterclockwise closes it.
Clockwise opens it.
Clockwise
opens it.
Can it only be closed from inside?
Only from...
Only from inside.
Only from here.
(The secret room switch is inside)
Hold on.
Can you close it?
No.
(The secret room door
can't be closed from outside)
(Checking again)
Counterclockwise.
Okay.
This changes everything.
Right.
Then who closed it for him?
(How did the killer
escape the secret room?)
So now the question is this.
Like we said earlier,
we can now
be sure he didn't go that way,
right?
Right.
(No sign of escape through the window)
He couldn't leave this way either.
(The switch only works from inside)
(Both escape routes are blocked)
Now we have a new problem.
How did the killer leave this room?
The swallow's nest is still there.
It can only be closed from inside.
The killer never came in.
(The killer never came in?)
Then how did he kill him?
How could he kill him without coming in?
(He Ha's theory)
Ning came in carrying the dummy.
He threw it down.
His father came in.
They exchanged a bunch of moves.
They were locked in a standoff.
Then one of you four
stabbed him from behind.
Right here.
You can kill without entering?
So he had to kill Ning.
Yeah.
Here.
Here!
(Silver sword mark)
There really is a sword mark here.
It really is a sword mark.
Nice!
That's it.
(Trust the detective)
That makes total sense.
That also explains why they died here.
Exactly.
So the killer
even told him
the moves.
Where to ambush, the whole plan,
it was all set.
Because he'd rehearsed it.
This move goes here,
then here, then here.
In the end, both of them
had to be at the door.
Then he ran over.
No need to open the door.
No need to go in.
He killed them here.
Then he pulled out the sword and left.
Right. Pulled it out and left.
Because when I saw them,
they were already lying here.
That means he didn't need to come in.
So it wasn't a locked room.
And it had nothing to do
with the window.
Right.
Okay.
So now we've confirmed
the murder method and the sequence.
I think it's clear now.
What we need to discuss next
is the 11PM night watch.
What were each of us doing then?
Right.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
(Was Ning Waver tricked and killed,
or was there more to it?)
(Interrogation seat)
This is the interrogation spot, right?
Come on.
(A fake-out)
What do you mean?
Sit.
(You suspect)
Why interrogate me? I'm innocent.
There should be
a lamp shining like this.
Right.
(Focused questioning, 10-minute limit)
(Goal: Players start a hearing)
(Question a chosen suspect
or NPC for 10 minutes)
(Push the investigation forward)
Little killer.
I'm really not the killer.
I wish I were.
Little killer.
Show me real proof.
We're not doing pressure tests today.
Sit properly.
I'm so nervous.
Little killer.
(Pressure)
Not me.
I think the killer
knew Ning Waver.
(Yang Glory's theory: The killer
was close to Ning Waver)
No.
We all knew him.
I didn't know them.
I'm a pretty clean girl.
Why are you so quick to defend yourself?
(Is it that obvious?)
Okay. We just brought this box
back from over there.
The writing on this box...
Why did he
wipe it off?
Right.
(Da Men Junzi)
This has to be a clue.
So I was just thinking.
Second Brother is called Junzi.
What?
Junzi Ruyu.
Could it be
(Ning Que)
that Ning wasn't called Ning Que before?
No, Ning...
(What did I just hear?)
Ning Que Wu Lan.
(A past life story)
I'm Ning Que Wu Lan.
(Can't hold it in)
Ning Waver.
(He Ha's theory: Ning is the mysterious
person and the owner of the box)
For example, Ning might've been
called Junzi before too.
(Junzi Ru Ning)
(Junzi Waver)
It's possible.
So we can ask
this rumored Junzi Ruyu.
Come on, sit.
Please sit.
Here's your throne.
Over on your side,
is there some Jun generation
or something?
What Jun generation?
Is...
Is this box yours?
(Does the box have something
to do with Junzi Ruyu?)
(Shi Da Men Junzi Ruyu)
What box?
Sit first.
("Ding" tense)
Do you have anything on you?
What's wrong?
How about this?
Search him.
Let's search him first.
Got anything? Take it out yourself.
He does.
He definitely does.
Take it out.
Where is it? Hurry.
What's on his chest?
Hold on.
Don't be so rough.
This isn't rough enough.
My chest.
I have a heart here.
There's a heart mark.
What's this?
There really is one.
My lord.
This again.
(Missed another chance to show off)
What does that mean?
You went over my head.
With your accomplice too.
What?
I missed you in Ginkgo Valley.
(I missed you in Ginkgo Valley)
Ginkgo Valley is...
You already found one, right?
One isn't enough.
What else do you want?
Let me do it myself.
He's got more!
(Nothing escapes my sharp eyes)
I knew it.
Look.
Let me see.
Here, my lord.
(They don't respect me at all)
No one's listening to him.
They were beside me.
You went over my head.
(An even worse offense)
My lord!
(Detective, please forgive me)
The killer's intent is clear.
That little killer is up to no good.
(Detective, I won't do it again)
My lord, I'm innocent!
There's a letter here.
Master,
I'm a useless disciple.
I even have to sneak over
to drink with you.
I know you miss me.
I'll come see you tomorrow.
(I'll come see you tomorrow)
Back then, you tricked me
into taking the Qide Sword
and leaving Tui City.
I trained for a month.
When I came back, you were dead.
My junior was gone.
Our sect was destroyed.
I had just hidden the sword
when Lord Tui dragged me
to Chivalry Manor.
I thought I might as well fight.
My last home was gone anyway.
If I killed a few, I'd come out ahead.
But your face popped
into my head right away.
And you started nagging again.
A hero stands first for the world.
A hero speaks for the people.
My master always taught me.
A hero stands first for the world.
A hero speaks for the people.
My master.
My disciple,
your
path as a hero is yours to find.
(What is the letter writer's
relationship with Ding Pillar?)
Master, you're seriously annoying.
I was already ready to die.
And you were still talking
about some heroic path.
But in that moment,
I really found it.
Dying is easy.
But I need to live and do more.
So I knelt.
I knelt before everyone at the manor.
And called him my godfather.
After Master died,
I went back to Tui City to find you all.
I saw Lord Tui take you
to Chivalry Manor.
I watched from outside the wall.
I wanted to find a chance to save you.
But then,
you called him Father.
You made Lord Tui your godfather.
But I need to live and do more.
So I knelt.
(Sorting out Ning Waver's identity)
I knelt before everyone at the manor.
(The truth: He knelt to save his sect)
And called him godfather.
His own story.
I think...
(Ning's final letter)
From then on,
that crook pushed me around.
My fellow disciples hated me.
Lapdog!
- Heroes spat on me.
- Ning the Lapdog!
The people cursed me.
You sneaky punk!
It's fine.
- Let others judge me.
- You're such an ingrate!
I know right from wrong.
(Shuai X. Sha Ning. Sha Who. Bao Jiu)
You're an ingrate!
My path is to light a lamp
in the darkest place.
So Tui City's night won't last so long.
I'm willing to live on my knees.
Later, I realized
you really can do a lot while kneeling.
I could make tons of fake swords.
And have people sell them.
That crook still hasn't found
a single clue about the Qide Sword.
When he ordered me to kill
righteous martial artists,
I could secretly send them
out of the city.
Then take a token back as proof.
I could harden my heart
and cut ties with my junior.
Then find that bottle of
(Tonic: restores inner power)
Eleven-Spice Tendon Powder he used up.
(Sorting out Ning Waver's identity)
And develop an antidote.
Then secretly send it to my junior.
(The truth: He gave Ke the antidote
and cut ties on purpose to protect him)
After I ate this,
my inner strength came back pretty soon.
Then I could help the kind-hearted
innkeeper pay off her debt.
Debt cleared.
(Tui City Money House receipt)
Jin Thrifty's principal and interest
have all been paid off.
From now on,
we won't bother her again.
This receipt serves as proof.
Tui City Money House.
Then I could openly harass her
and hope she'd leave
Tui City to stay safe.
(Paid Jin's debt and forced her out)
Anyone I want gone
doesn't get to stay.
Are you leaving on your own,
or should we roll you out in a coffin?
I could also save the little cook
who risked herself to save others
and was almost caught.
This was from that day
when I followed the man in black.
Then,
I was almost found out.
He grabbed me by the collar
and pulled me away.
He saved me.
(Truth: Secretly saved her)
I could take on another identity
and teach a hot-blooded,
righteous young man
(Disguised as Meng, taught Ding)
to train.
My master suddenly showed up a year ago.
He taught me martial arts.
He always appeared at night.
So I respectfully called him Uncle Meng.
He taught you?
So he was my teacher.
Once he became skilled enough,
I could destroy this useless identity.
Later, I realized
some things couldn't be done
even if I begged.
I ate everything the kids ate.
(Hit Ding to check his martial arts)
I tried every poison.
(Truth: Risked his life testing cures)
I tried the medicines.
Those kids ate the rotten soup
and were badly poisoned.
He couldn't cure it himself.
So he could only use himself
as a test subject.
He tested the medicines one by one.
The last time he came
to me for medicine,
he was already deeply poisoned.
His days were numbered.
He was the kind of person
who didn't have long left.
You were the poison tester.
I still couldn't find a way
to save the children.
I knew I still had unfinished
business in this world.
But I really had no time left.
The night was too long.
It was time to use my broken body
to light the way.
I found a secret manual.
With it, I had a way to kill those scum.
I was worried I needed a helper.
Then a helper appeared.
Who?
(Truth: Ning did the whole act alone)
(Confirm Ning Waver and another
suspect committed the crime together)
The Truth Online alert.
This case has two killers.
Please find Ning Waver's accomplice.
Vote for the killer duo
you think is right.
There are two killers?
So the two killers are Ning Waver
and someone else working with him
to kill the Tui Gang, right?
I'm the obvious killer.
Okay.
(Who is Ning Waver's accomplice?)
Why was this letter on you?
Last night,
I went to visit my master's grave.
I noticed the soil
was fresh.
Someone had been there.
Someone had dug it up.
(Master's grave had been dug up?)
Someone dug up Master's grave.
No, I mean the soil was loose.
(Your wording is seriously misleading)
So I checked
why the soil had been touched.
So this letter
was from Ning Waver.
He meant to write it to my master.
He buried it under the soil.
Then I dug it out.
So Master didn't get it. I did.
So,
why did you call me a traitor today?
I was protecting you.
Because when I found out you
were undercover,
I didn't know who they really were.
(So heartwarming)
What's this, then?
This is
my
love token
with Yan Reason.
We went on a date in Ginkgo Valley
under that ginkgo tree.
We adopted a tree there.
It's the witness to our love.
Okay.
So last night,
before she came to Chivalry Manor,
I gave her an amulet.
At the same time, I always keep
this love token on me.
Okay.
You carry it with you.
This box is from the amulet I gave you.
The amulet you gave me?
Before I left,
I gave you an amulet.
This is the box that held it.
But what's inside the box now?
I don't know.
When you gave this to him,
was this crossed-out part already there?
I don't know who crossed it out.
(On the box Junzi Ruyu gave Ning Waver)
(The words were intact,
with no scratches)
Why cross it out?
(Dying is easy, but I want
to live and do more)
(Da Men Junzi)
I get it.
Ning
wanted to hide his identity.
So he wanted everyone to think
this was Junzi's box.
That's why he crossed out "gave".
Simple as that.
If he only crossed out "gave, "
we'd guess that word was "gave".
(Theory: Ning hid his identity)
So he crossed out "Ruyu" and the rest.
(Crossed out the words on the box)
Exactly.
Okay.
Now tell us your timeline
from last night.
You said you were
with Lady Yan
on a date. What time was it?
At midnight.
(Junzi Ruyu's timeline)
Midnight, 11PM.
(Midnight: 11PM)
(Date with Yan Reason)
When the watchman struck.
That's when we were all there.
We were all there then.
I don't think
he'd team up with Ning Waver.
He's still suspicious.
And his 11PM alibi
as far as we know,
doesn't count.
Who? I'm suspicious?
Yeah. Why else are you sitting there?
It's fine. What happened after 11PM?
I honestly don't remember
how long we stayed.
Where's the Ginkgo Valley?
Near Tui City.
Not around here. It's outside.
Yes.
(Ginkgo Valley is on the outskirts)
At midnight, Yan Reason
and I were together the whole time.
So he probably wouldn't have had time.
(Junzi Ruyu didn't
have enough time to do it)
The reason
I asked
about his timeline
is because he looked very suspicious.
Because he found this letter.
So he knew
I'm a good guy.
No, Ning.
If he found this letter,
the letter already says
you teamed up with the killer, right?
Right.
So if he found this letter,
he definitely isn't the killer.
Right?
So he's completely cleared.
Right. The ending's written right there.
He's totally cleared.
Yes.
Okay.
(Junzi Ruyu is cleared)
I'm a good guy.
"Good guys" don't belong there. Get out!
Okay, you can go.
I think this letter is very important.
You all owe me an apology.
Come on.
(Standing tall from now on)
I'll sit here.
Come apologize one by one.
(This detective is in for a treat today)
Don't forget,
you all pointed at my face
and cursed me all day.
Lapdog!
Shameless scoundrel!
Cunning crook!
Vicious Duo!
Ingrate!
Ning, you know apologies don't help.
(If sorry worked, why need detectives?)
Right.
But I like fake stuff like that.
Come on. First one.
(Settling every score)
Jin Thrifty, step up.
If I could face him directly,
I'd definitely tell this great man...
(All ears)
Ning,
I misjudged you.
(Kneeling with full respect)
I'll do a lying-fish pose for you.
Alright.
Okay, I accept your apology.
Who's next?
Young hero.
So who's shameless now?
I am.
(Own your mistakes)
Who's the lapdog?
I am!
I'm the laodog.
Master!
(Why the sudden plot twist?)
So I'm your master.
So I'm the crook.
What about you?
I called you an ingrate.
Looking at it now,
I'm the ingrate.
(My name is finally cleared)
Actually, I always believed
ever since all this happened to him,
I've always felt
there's kindness in my heart.
I kept
kept a little bit of
that kindness.
I believe
the brother who saved me
from that cliff back then
wouldn't do this.
He definitely wouldn't.
No.
I just thought of something.
On that doll of yours,
(Big Ingrate)
weren't there two layers?
(Little Ingrate)
One was Little Ingrate and Big Ingrate.
Right.
Why did you stick them
on top of each other?
After you stabbed him,
did you feel like you
were such an ingrate?
(He Ha's Theory:)
(Ke Stubborn felt guilty
after killing Ning Waver)
(So he added two sticker layers)
That's such a stretch.
How is that a stretch?
I really don't think it is.
When I made that doll,
all this hadn't even happened yet.
That sticker was put on again.
Who told you that?
Because there
are two layers stuck together.
Then how do you know
when it was stuck on?
I'm just guessing.
What makes you guess that?
Because it makes sense to me.
You're framing me!
Because there's one logic here.
You're setting me up!
Among the four of you,
someone already knew he was a good guy.
After stabbing him,
didn't you feel guilty?
(He Ha's Theory:
The accomplice killed Ning Waver)
(And would do something
to ease the guilt)
Then let me follow your logic.
After I stabbed him to death,
I came back
and thought, "What if no one finds out"?
Then what?
So I'll put this thing
on there super subtly?
Am I stupid?
It's an emotional thing.
There's no logic to it.
Emotions don't follow logic.
I'm heartbroken.
I'm devastated.
I stabbed the person I loved most.
I stabbed someone who helped me so much!
Then I went back and saw the doll.
I used to call him an ingrate.
At that moment, I felt so guilty.
So I put a Little Ingrate sticker on it.
Here's the thing. Listen.
To me, He is extremely smart.
His points are usually very sharp.
But that one was really a bit wild.
(Your Honor)
You tell me. Wasn't it?
You're still here?
I really was listening carefully.
That one really was a bit wild.
(Was it wild?)
When I heard him read that letter,
I listened to his deep voice
as he read about
everything he went through alone.
Honestly, I felt a lot.
Standing there, I almost...
Choked up.
I did.
I was really moved.
And I really want
to sincerely say
to my senior brother
who saved me back then,
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Your turn, Little Cook.
Me too.
I was blinded for a moment.
(I was shallow)
I didn't realize how righteous you were.
On behalf of the people
in the city, thank you.
And I'm sorry
for yelling at you today.
Yes.
And thank you for saving me.
Fine. I accept your apologies.
So if any of you still has a conscience,
whoever the killer is today,
stand up right now.
(Please confess)
That'll at least show some conscience.
Seriously.
I feel like if the killer
still won't confess
after all this buildup,
that's just "dog".
He's still sitting there.
Look. We all stood up,
but he's still...
(Sitting steady)
If it turns out
to be me,
then you all got it wrong.
Then that whole
thing just now,
(Give me the whole set)
you'll have to apologize to me too!
(New bonus scenes)
(every Sunday at noon)
Let's go over each suspect again.
(Doing his detective duty)
What were they doing after 11PM?
The killer must've
wanted to
create an alibi.
Right.
So the things they did after 11PM
must be at least a little
different from
what they normally do.
(Suspect theory 1: Timeline)
First off,
I'm cleared.
(How so?)
Because every night at 11PM,
I'm always
at the counter doing accounts.
(Jin Thrifty's timeline)
But that night,
(11 PM: Doing accounts at the inn)
each of you showed up
in a way that really surprised me.
Why?
You guys don't usually come by.
Because while I was doing accounts,
Ke came to buy something. Wine, right?
Right.
(Suspects' movements, 11 PM)
Right. But he was fine.
(Jin Thrifty: doing accounts at the inn)
He's a customer.
(Ke Stubborn: came to buy wine)
But that night, I found it weird.
Why did the cook suddenly
come out of the kitchen too?
Right.
And she left right at 11PM.
(Yang Glory: leaving the inn)
Right.
She came out.
I thought it was strange.
Then,
Ding Pillar showed up too.
I was like,
why is everyone here tonight?
Why did he come out?
I was stealing ginseng wine.
(Ding Pillar: came to steal wine)
So if they wanted to use
an alibi,
they probably used me
to back that alibi up.
(The only fixed movement timeline)
Can we say she's the least suspicious?
Yes.
(Suspicion by timeline:)
(Ke Stubborn, Ding Pillar,
Yang Glory > Jin Thrifty)
First, this person
(Suspect theory 1: Timeline)
had to show up
before 11PM.
To make everyone remember them.
To create an alibi.
Of course.
At 11PM,
since we had the Blade Gala coming,
I started simmering
the ingredients early.
Then I went into the kitchen.
Before I went in,
I saw you pouring wine for him.
Then he was...
I wasn't there yet.
I came out after you left.
Right. You weren't there yet.
Then I went into the kitchen.
After I went in,
when I came back out,
you rushed over and bumped into me.
I think
you bumped into me
so I'd see I.
You wanted my attention.
(Yang Glory's theory)
Then the 11 PM bell rang right then.
(Ding deliberately made a witness)
So I remembered him clearly.
Then at that time,
you were suspicious too.
(Same kind of deliberate behavior)
You asked me to get wine for you.
Maybe you wanted me...
Right.
If I'm right,
I was
(Suspects' movements, 11 PM)
(Jin Thrifty was doing accounts)
the first one there, right?
(Ke Stubborn arrived)
When I was buying wine,
I suddenly ran into...
Me.
The cook.
Right.
(Yang Glory was about to leave)
When the cook came in second,
she even said hi to me.
(Yang Glory also acted deliberately)
After she served me the wine,
before the cook arrived,
the 11 PM bell had already rung.
She left right on the dot at 11PM.
I was the one coming in.
(Ding Pillar just entered)
That exact timing, to me,
already says something.
If the killer
came to the tavern
to create an alibi,
and they knew
something intense
was happening over there,
they'd have to rush back.
They had to hit that window
when both people were frozen, right?
So they couldn't
stay at the tavern for that long.
Long.
That's why I think
it had to be a quick in and out.
Or whoever timed it
closest to 11PM,
(Ke Stubborn's theory)
I think that person
(The killer had to nail 11 for an alibi)
looks more suspicious.
Based on the timeline,
and the logic
that the killer had to rush
to the next crime scene to strike,
then to me,
it's definitely...
Yang Glory.
(Suspicion by timeline:)
(Yang Glory > Ke Stubborn,
Ding Pillar > Jin Thrifty)
Exactly. That's the point.
Besides that,
we also need to talk about
how long your master stayed with you,
or how much he helped you.
What Ding means is
it's about emotional bond.
The strength of that bond.
How deep is your bond
with this master
in the four of your hearts?
(Reasoning 2: The killer's
emotional bond with Ning Waver)
(Based on bonds)
They're all close to him.
One pair are fellow disciples,
right?
Right.
(Strong emotional bond)
Fellow disciples from the same sect.
The other is master and disciple.
(Master and disciple, close bond)
But he got close to you too.
We only met once.
I couldn't see your face.
So I had no idea
about your other identity.
(Only met once, weak emotional bond)
Wait, that doesn't add up.
Exactly.
Because I didn't know his face either.
I only knew he wore a cloak and that...
(Ding Pillar had never seen
Ning Waver's real face before)
No, I mean...
Were you their senior disciple
or master before?
No.
He...
He is my master,
but I don't know who he is.
Here's the thing with Ding.
He doesn't know you're his master,
but when he saw Ning Waver,
maybe there was this one moment
when you made a move,
and he remembered.
My master used to do that.
Then he'd realize you're his master.
I think if we're talking about
where the motive circles overlap,
then who'd be most likely to find out
Ning Waver is a good guy?
It has to be someone close to him.
They'd notice some small detail
and realize he's their master
or senior disciple.
I know you're a good guy.
(High motive suspicion)
It's likely one of you two.
That logic is really...
Really right.
That logic is solid.
Right?
I'd definitely investigate.
So both of them
have a strong reason to investigate
who you really are.
Curiosity.
(Reasoning 3: Who is more curious
about Ning Waver?)
(Who is more curious about Ning Waver?)
She has no curiosity about you.
You're just a bad guy. Pure evil.
(Curiosity level: Ke and Ding > Yang)
Right. I don't care.
Jin makes a good point.
That's another angle.
Basically,
who would be more eager
to know his real identity?
Who'd be in such a rush
to expose who he really is?
Who'd be most likely to find out
that he's actually a good guy?
The motive to investigate. Right.
I'm just giving an example.
Her impression of him is just that
he's heartless
and pretty brutal.
He...
To him, this guy saved his life.
Yes.
(Lifesaver + fellow disciple)
Such a good person.
He'd wonder
why he changed.
Right.
Maybe there's more to it.
So he'd investigate.
He has a reason to investigate you.
Got it.
(Curiosity level toward Ning Waver:)
(Ke Stubborn > Ding Pillar > Yang Glory)
I've totally locked in the killers.
Then vote. Come on.
But morally speaking,
shouldn't you vote for me?
We should.
For justice and the law.
I somehow went from detective to killer.
What you did was heroic.
We're looking for heroes now.
Two great heroes.
Got it.
Vote.
I'm telling you.
If you vote wrong today,
seriously...
Who are you voting for? Tell me first.
I can't tell you.
Why not?
Who are you voting for?
No copying answers.
No copying.
Come on. I can vote first.
(Can they lock in the killers?)
(Killer lock-in time)
The two killers I'm locking in today
are
Ning and Ding.
(Ke: Slot 1, Ning. Slot 2, Ding)
First, Ning is obvious.
He has to be the mastermind.
The reason I'm voting Ding
is because, from my perspective,
I do think he was really anxious
(Meeting hall)
to make that whole
in-and-out route happen.
I think that's also
a key part of him trying
to create an alibi.
So my final vote
goes to these two.
(Voting window)
Today, I'm voting for...
(He Ha: Slot 1, Ning Waver. Slot 2, ?)
My vote is...
(Jin Thrifty: Slot 1,
Ning Waver. Slot 2, ?)
Because they're master and disciple.
I think they're closer to each other
(Voting window)
and understand each other better.
(Yang Glory: Slot 1, Ning. Slot 2, Ding)
I'm voting for Ding and Ning.
My final vote goes to...
(Ding Pillar: Slot 1, Ning Waver.
Slot 2, Ke Stubborn)
Because Ke came back first.
He had to come back first
to set up an alibi,
then leave again.
That's why I voted for him.
Also because of his emotional bond.
(Ke Stubborn)
Because I
planned the whole thing today.
I gave this vote to myself.
And...
(Ning Waver: Slot 1,
Ning Waver. Slot 2, ?)
(Voting ends. Case archived)
No need to reason when traveling.
Tongcheng saves you money.
Next up,
Tongcheng Travel's truth reveal.
It's you.
In today's case,
the suspects are
Ning Waver,
Jin Thrifty,
Ding Pillar,
Ke Stubborn,
Yang Glory,
and Junzi Ruyu.
After all the reasoning,
there are two vote patterns.
Two vote patterns?
We're done.
Are you two old flames or something?
You're the bad guy.
(Could Jin Thrifty be the other killer?)
The first vote pattern is...
We're done.
(Vote pattern one: Slot 1, Ning Waver)
(Slot 2, Ding Pillar)
You voted that?
We're so cooked. It's over.
The second vote pattern is...
(Vote pattern two: Slot 1, Ning Waver)
(Slot 2, Ke Stubborn)
You definitely voted that.
I definitely voted that.
It had to be you.
Me too.
(Why did he vote for Ke Stubborn?)
(Could the other killer
not be Ke Stubborn?)
(Doesn't he want himself to win?)
(Did I vote wrong?)
It's fine.
(Ning Waver knows the other killer)
You're faking amnesia.
No.
I really lost my memory.
It's you.
(It can't really be you, right?)
Which vote pattern got the most votes?
Ke, please let it be you.
Ke, please let it be you, you villain!
Still acting?
You're still acting, Ding?
Still acting.
The one with the most votes is
Ning Waver
and Ding Pillar.
Nice.
It's not you?
We got it.
(Did I vote wrong?)
Are they really the true killer duo?
(Do you think the killer could be me?)
What?
You two...
(Look in my eyes)
We're done.
I hereby announce this case's
culprit call...
Failed.
Passed.
(Already traumatized)
Or was it right?
(Stop acting. It's you)
No.
No, we failed.
We failed.
Failed.
What do you mean?
I knew we failed.
Go on.
The real killer is
Ning Waver.
Nice.
(Huh?)
(Could the other killer be Jin Thrifty?)
The real killer is
Ning Waver.
(Hahaha)
For real?
The real killer's stunned.
Ke Stubborn.
(The killer is Ke Stubborn)
Nice!
Then I got it right.
I got it right too.
(The only two players who voted right)
Never lost.
This win feels so good!
(See The Truth Season 2 Episode 5
for details)
This win feels great, Ning!
So good!
(See The Truth Season 2 Episode 5
for details)
Second team-up.
When we team up, we never lose.
Exactly.
(Killer duo: N team-ups, 0 losses)
(Killers escaped)
(Ning Waver. Ke Stubborn)
(Should've known better)
(#Voting Round)
Ding and Ning.
(Jin Thrifty: Slot 1, Ning Waver.
Slot 2, Ding Pillar)
(He Ha: Slot 1, Ning Waver)
Ning and Ke.
(Slot 2, Ke Stubborn)
I picked Ke because
he'd have stronger
personal reasons to realize
Ning really was
the person who once saved him.
And he's a good guy.
He'd want to know more.
Also,
I felt that if he was the killer,
after stabbing Ning, he'd feel guilty.
Like he was an ingrate.
Another possibility is
Little Ingrate, Big Ingrate.
That nickname feels
like they're pretty close.
Hope I didn't pick wrong.
I gave this vote to myself
and Ding.
(Ning Waver: Slot 1, Ning. Slot 2, Ding)
Because everyone might suspect him.
(Case report)
So for my own win,
sorry, Ding.
I have to frame you.
(Voting results)
(Vote type 1: Ning Waver, Ding Pillar)
(Ning Waver, Ke Stubborn,
Jin Thrifty, Yang Glory)
(Vote type 2: Ning Waver, Ke Stubborn)
(He Ha, Ding Pillar)
Congrats. You two get
this case's Golden Key.
The Golden Key will be given out
in the game lobby after Case 7.
Nice!
(Golden Key secured)
(At every Thursday noon,
Dungeon Archiving)
It was obviously him!
Can the two of us share
one brain?
Half each.
Then it's all thanks to you.
And you.
Thanks to Jin.
Thanks to Chaoyue.
Was it because she said
I suddenly bumped into her?
Yes.
Who'd you vote for?
I voted for him.
You?
Him.
(Missed the Golden Key)
Don't jump!
Actually, when we were leaving,
he suddenly patted me.
Then he looked at my clothes.
When we were leaving?
Leaving where? From where?
Before we went to the Ghost Market.
Good thing you took it off.
(So random)
What the heck?
I didn't get it at the time.
But after I saw that receipt...
(Receipt)
(Bought two black robes)
I got it.
(To hide the silver mark left
by Qide Sword's stab)
(He needed two identical robes
to change into)
Weren't you watching him?
I didn't watch him closely.
I was watching him the whole time.
I don't know why.
(The charm of deduction)
I really did lose my memory, guys.
I know.
All I can say is...
(I admit defeat)
(Humble)
No, you let me win.
You let me win.
You've been something else this season.
I'm telling you.
Right now, I just wanna ask.
How many Golden Keys
does Liu Yuning have?
Yeah.
Right now, I think...
Looks like he's first now.
(Player Liu Yuning: Gold Keys x4)
I could've...
(Player TNT Ding Chengxin: Gold Keys x3)
Honestly, I wanted to help
the good guys win today.
Then why didn't you?
(My Golden Keys)
Need a comeback, honestly.
I don't even wanna scold
you anymore. Seriously.
From my point of view,
I had to choose one of three.
How could I choose?
(This is too hard)
Listen to the key evidence.
It's really interesting.
I know where this was.
We were so close.
What?
The key evidence we missed in this case.
There were silver marks
and bloodstains inside the sword case.
(Ke Stubborn's sword case
had silver marks and bloodstains)
Sword case?
I kept playing with it.
It proves he put the real Qide Sword
inside his own sword case.
(The sheath had silver marks
and bloodstains)
(My head hurts)
Didn't see that coming, huh?
But I remember.
I remember someone asked about it.
Him.
I was there.
I went there to play with it.
He told me to stop.
I played with every sword there.
I just wanted to see
if he had that thing.
Right.
Stop messing with my swords.
I wanted to see
if the Qide Sword was inside.
There isn't the Qide Sword.
You were this close!
(Another billion-point emotional hit)
This close.
It slipped right past us.
Babe.
(Babe)
(Don't cry)
Nothing we can do.
A narrow loss.
(A narrow loss)
Let's sum up
the suspicious points, guys.
First.
How did I come back to life?
Exactly.
Why didn't you have a pulse?
(Why did Ning Waver come back to life?)
Did you all forget
the legend of the ghost soldiers
coming back to life?
No.
The fortune-teller said it.
He said your revival
might be connected
to the ghost soldier legend.
(Ning's revival may be connected
to the ghost soldier legend)
Right. Ghost soldiers revive.
That's possible.
Right.
So you're a real ghost soldier.
Stop it.
Is this some Lam Ching-ying thing?
(Emergency brake)
That got way too spooky.
Wasn't that fake?
Where did this legend even come from?
And how did those people lose back then?
Wait. Wasn't it
the Thousand-Faced Eagle King?
Didn't the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King start that rumor?
We still don't know who the
Thousand-Faced Eagle King is.
Right.
(Who could the Thousand-Faced
Eagle King be?)
Lord Tui said,
"This medicine was given
to me by that benefactor".
He got a secret medicine
from the benefactor.
It can make rotten ingredients
look fresh.
(Luckily, I got a secret medicine
from my benefactor)
(Who is the benefactor behind Lord Tui?)
(What medicine did they make?)
When you said all that, I kept thinking,
Golden Key. You got the Golden Key.
Right.
That was Lord Tui's Golden Key.
His benefactor gave it to him.
(That's a pretty fitting metaphor)
And then there's
your good friend,
Yan Reason.
We don't know where she is now.
(Where is Yan Reason now?)
You did win.
Your analysis was spot-on.
Everyone!
Jin,
you scared me to death.
Heroes,
Lord Tui's death has already
reached the imperial court.
Chancellor Tui is on his way here.
That serious?
After he arrives,
he'll take over all affairs in Tui City.
Chancellor Tui?
He's done for.
Whoever comes is dead.
Things are unstable now.
You heroes should lay low for a while.
Try not to move around too much.
Oh, right.
Someone told me
to hand this over
to whoever sits here.
That should be you, right?
Why would you say it's him?
He's the murderer.
(Not my place to judge the trial)
Farewell.
Alright.
How shameless.
Hold on.
Hold on again?
I killed a bad guy, friends!
Come on, didn't he deserve it?
And I paid off your debt, girl!
(Peacemaker Detective is online)
She's been blinded by Golden Keys.
(Survival instinct maxed out)
I saved your life.
You...
I mean, I...
I cured your poison.
(Aren't we on the same side?)
We killed him together.
Yes, I helped you.
But that's a separate matter.
You should thank me.
(Thank you, Ning)
(Big ingrate)
(Little ingrate)
Disciple,
a teacher for a day is a...
Father for life.
(Father)
Got it?
(Big Father)
(Today's emotional damage: billions)
And the kids in this city
should thank me too.
Right.
Exactly.
I don't remember it now,
but I'm happy to take the credit.
Why?
Because it says here,
thank you.
It's from the rescued kids of Tui City.
I tested poison for them.
Again and again.
Let's see what's in here.
I'll do it.
One piece.
(Brave Ding is growing up)
Stuffed bread!
(The hungry boy is online)
Cheers with buns.
Tomorrow, we'll solve
even more mysteries.
(Cheers with buns)
Okay.
Let's go.
Cheers.
Cheers!
(Detective eats first)
(With Chancellor Tui's arrival,
how will things unfold?)
(After this whole journey,
what do you feel and think?)
All these years,
Ning Waver was called
trash,
a lapdog,
but he never once
defended himself.
In the darkest corner,
he did the brightest thing.
The night has gone on too long.
It's time to use what's left
of me to light the way.
True courage
can mean being misunderstood
by the whole world
and still keeping the kindness
in your heart.
I hated Ning for so long.
In the end, I found out
he paid my debt
and kept me safe all along.
When rumors spread long enough,
people start calling them truth.
But time will prove
that those who stay true
don't need anyone's answer.
They are the answer.
I have to say this to that good man.
Ning,
I was wrong about you.
I always wanted to be a hero.
Then I found out Uncle Meng,
who taught me kung fu, was Ning.
Master!
A hero isn't the top fighter
on a ranking.
It's someone who teaches you kung fu
quietly in the night
and leaves without a word.
Fame fades.
But chivalry grows in people's hearts.
I
hated him deeply,
but I respected him too.
After I learned he was undercover,
I realized he'd carried too much alone.
So on his final road,
I'll walk with him.
True righteousness
isn't being worshiped from above.
It's kneeling in the mud
and still being willing
to light a lamp for this city.
When I cursed him with a straw doll,
I didn't know
he was the one risking his life
to test medicine for the kids.
These kids are Tui Kingdom's future.
If my life
can keep them alive,
it's worth it.
Don't be so quick to hate someone.
The truth may be late,
but it'll show up.
On behalf of the people
in the city, thank you.
The victim in this case,
Lord Tui, wanted
(All the donations are mine)
to build his reputation as a great hero.
(These poor children are worth nothing)
Under the cover of charity,
(Why waste precious food on them?)
he hurt the poor children of Tui City.
True chivalry
shouldn't be charity from a high horse.
And it should never use
or feed on people's despair.
(A hero leads for the world.
A hero speaks for the people)
(Next episode)
Five days ago,
we solved the case and earned credit.
Yes.
So the one who took over Tui City,
Chancellor Tui,
invited us today
to a feast at Zuixian Inn.
(Deadly feast. Who survives?)
Chancellor Tui is here!
Let's get down to business.
Among you,
someone
survived
from five years ago until now!
Don't you deserve to die?
How did he die?
Guards!
His lips are black.
His face is rotting too.
I've locked onto the killer.
Ning Waver.
The best lightness skill master
in the world.
Look at that nasty face of yours!
(Memories return.
An old case is reopened)
Let me tell you all a secret.
I
remember now.
Longdong's bones
were left unclaimed.
Among the four of you,
one is from Li Kingdom!
When he was very young,
he was sent
to Tui Kingdom
as a spy.
That lowlife
is
you!
You'd better explain.
The people are innocent!
You're not one of the people.
You're a spy!
I hated him so, so much.
I tried to kill you twice.
I'm going to kill him.
You've lost your mind!
To me, that person was
on Chancellor Kuang's side.
(Ghost soldiers attack.
Summoning Longdong)
With Longdong's spear and Qide's sword,
the ghost soldiers have taken Tui City.
He wants
to unite the three kingdoms.
He wants to take over.
He wants to be the only ruler.
He used Tui and Li to wipe out Kuang.
His goal was to throw
both sides into chaos.
We're all his pawns.
Two birds with one stone.
When two sides fight,
the third one wins.
So you're the one with big ambitions?
Not bad.
A huge army of ghost soldiers
is about to attack.
Only the Longdong Army can stop them.
Isn't the Longdong Army
down to its last troops?
But we all drank
the Longdong Army's medicine.
Right.
That's it!
Stop war before innocent blood is shed.
We raise our staffs only
to protect the light.
(Dungeon Archive)
We're the two killers in this case.
(SVIP, every Thursday at noon)
Ning Waver.
(VIP, next day at noon)
Ke Stubborn.
To save the children of Tui City
and stop the villain
from hurting more people,
(Sect leader. Damen's tomb)
and avenge our master,
we worked together
and killed Lord Tui.
- Master, Ning.
- Master, Ke.
Different paths, same ending.
Master and disciples, same ending.
(Truth Clubhouse)
How about this?
(A sudden idea)
Each of us uses our own...
(SVIP, every Friday at noon)
Like,
(VIP, next day at noon)
I'm Ning Waver.
I...
I'm Ke Stubborn.
(This is too fun)
Jin Thrifty.
I'm Ding Pillar. I look lightly.
Mine's easy.
Heh heh ha hey!
(Girl, you sit at the bow)
(Immediately sings along)
I'll sit at the bow.
(Truth Supply Station.
Food perks delivered)
(SVIP, Sunday noon. VIP, next day noon)
What about drinks?
(Jin's service is online)
Come on. What do you want to drink?
(Cravings activated)
Jin, can you fill it up a bit more?
Eat more food.
(Self-service)
Take care of yourself.
I pressed three.
He's the best at finding food.
If you have money, you can eat.
If you don't,
just ask someone rich to buy you food.
Isn't that easy?
(Zero-frame opener)
Please.
I want to eat.
(Dungeon unlocking)
Who's that in the top left?
(SVIP, every Thursday at noon.)
Their figure is so good.
(VIP, next day at noon)
I just want to make one thing clear.
We're close.
The few of us are good friends.
But we've never been this close.
That's number one.
I really have sacrificed
my body for art.
Is this me?
I've had this look?
Now this one has become,
I think, the hardest one so far.
I see a washboard.
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Viewing Calendar)
The Truth Season 4 on WeTV.
(Case 01: Voting Now)
Tap "Play Together" below the player.
(01: My Family Is a Total Mess)
Join the online hunt.
(New case every Wednesday at noon)
Become a detective.
(Results every Thursday at 6 PM)
Solve it with the detectives.
(Enter the Lock-In Challenge)
Win Golden Keys.
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪