(Dungeon Pass)
(Loading)
(The Truth)
=The Truth (Season 4)=
(Previous episode)
Dungeon Three "Ghost Stories of Tui City",
scene rendering failed.
(Your friend He sent you a location)
Where are we being teleported to?
(Teleport to this location? Yes)
Select teleport.
Where is this?
(Ghost Stories of Tui City Control Room)
This is the game's control room, right?
This is the control room.
But an evil hacker somehow
turned your adorable traits
into nasty bugs
and attacked the system backend.
(Bug fix log)
Namely:
fear of the dark, glutton, playful,
loves dancing, and dramatic.
Now you've become
Tui City's five bugs.
Go to the five bug zones in the backend
and fix the bugs.
Let Door of Truth be bug-free again.
Tui City's five bugs,
(Taking down Tui City's five bugs)
definitely not bad.
Let's go!
(Taking down Tui City's five bugs)
Let me go!
What's going on?
I can't move.
Help me!
(Where did everyone get teleported to?)
Welcome to the first bug space.
(Darkfear bug)
The system detected
that someone among you
is terrified of the dark,
so it generated this Darkfear bug.
Who? It's so hard to guess.
I mean honestly,
it's so hard.
Who's afraid of the dark?
(Could it be someone else?)
Me.
Okay?
(Saving his dignity)
Yeah.
It's definitely me.
I'll protect you from now on.
Yeah.
(Roles reversed)
This sleeping bag really suits you.
(#naturevibes #OOTD #campingstyle)
Looks better than what I'm wearing.
You should just wear this
when you're filming on set.
It's very stylish.
(Compliment club president)
Yeah, super stylish.
Wear this next time
you walk the red carpet.
All Star Night.
(Booking the outfit six months in advance)
Yeah.
It feels like the peak of our lives
is just All Star Night.
Every time...
Is that already the highest honor?
The highest honor is All Star Night.
(No need to say more)
It's the highest honor.
What's this?
This is called
the Wriggler in the Dark.
Do you know what "guyong" means?
[*Wriggle]
(Confused Wuxi local)
Moving around like a worm.
In our Northeast dialect,
we call it "guyong".
Like, stop wriggling around over there.
Just like that.
This is called "guyong".
(Learned something new)
Okay.
You need to complete
the Wriggler in the Dark challenge
(Darkfear bug fix mechanism)
to fix the Darkfear bug.
Every player has their name
tagged on the back
of their sleeping bag.
Players need to find
their own sleeping bag
and slide into it.
You saw it?
I'll see it if you stand up.
Why should I stand up?
Wriggle.
Do you know what wriggling mean?
Is the word "wriggle"
that hard to explain?
(How do I explain "wriggling" to you?)
After sliding into the sleeping bag,
you must start from the starting line
(Finish line, Starting line)
and wriggle forward.
After hitting the turnaround line,
wriggle back to the starting line.
The first player to return
will get a chance to draw a Skill Card.
Lights will turn on and off randomly
during the challenge.
You can only move
when the lights are off,
and you must freeze
when the lights are on.
Who's going to control the lights?
I'll be the referee.
Alright, Player He
is now upgraded to referee.
He'll be in charge
of switching the lights
(Referee Trial Card used)
and calling out fouls.
(Power in hand)
Look at him acting all smug.
The referee is actually
looking handsome today.
(Flattery mode activated)
Only today?
He's always handsome.
(No wonder you're my bro)
Handsome every single day.
Honestly, yeah.
He's just extra
handsome today.
(Take notes)
Extra handsome today. That's right.
Alright, the referee
is heading out first.
Alright.
(Ready to take full control)
(Tosses)
(Restless)
You keep fouling.
How am I fouling?
What did I do?
Did the rules say anything about this?
I already touched it.
This guy is fouling.
(Exploring)
(Attacked from both sides)
What are you struggling for?
Don't you think you should be
the first one to get flipped over?
Why?
Kid is the easiest to bully.
Kid?
(Passing the blame)
The kid is over here.
True.
Wait.
Can we play like,
civilized?
Let's keep it peaceful.
(Turns into a peace dove)
If you think someone is in your bag,
just swap with them directly.
I think Ning is in mine.
Then let's flip him over.
(Setting me up)
Bullying the kid?
What?
Flip the eldest over.
The lights are on.
(Referee keeping things fair)
Right.
(Back to reality)
Okay.
(Saved my life)
(Striking a pose)
(Striking a weak pose)
Whatever the referee says goes.
Okay.
Here's what I'll do.
(Referee)
The lights are under my control.
When the lights are on, you can't move.
Everyone gets three chances.
("Generous",
three fouls allowed per person)
Alright, we'll start
when I turn off the lights.
Hey kids,
let's flip the eldest over.
I haven't been the eldest for years.
Help!
Three, two,
one.
(Night vision mode)
Let's go!
Holy crap!
(A change of target?)
So scary.
Let me feel around.
Let me feel it.
Hold on.
What are you feeling?
I'm feeling for the name tag.
Wait!
(Zhang Linghe's POV, Pitch black)
(Checking out the battle)
(Hitting the deck)
What kind of pose is that?
(Like a newborn baby in a swaddle)
(Adopting a kid again)
Who's my dad today?
I'm your dad today.
(What a show)
(Night vision mode)
This feels like mine.
(Purely based on touch)
(Making progress?)
I found it.
(Unzipping)
(Attempting to escape)
What are you doing?
(Can't figure it out)
You're supposed to wriggle inside here.
(Making room for you)
What are you doing?
I'm feeling your name tag.
(Night vision mode)
Hold on.
(Entering a 1v1 battle)
Okay.
(Lying down to create distance)
(Restricting movement)
(Front row seats to UFC)
Hold on.
(Breaking out to fight back)
Okay.
Hold on.
Whose is this?
(Using leg strength)
Turn on the lights.
Please.
Don't.
(It's getting intense?)
Please!
Turn them on!
(Turn on the lights)
This is Jin.
(Jin Jing's sleeping bag)
Yes!
Awesome, guys.
(Next target locked)
(Things just got interesting)
(Night vision mode)
(A new conflict begins)
How do we get him out?
Get him out of there.
(Rough start)
(They're strong)
(Fierce battle)
Whose do you have?
Take it off first.
You first.
(Attempting an alliance)
Take it off, and I'll show you.
No.
(Ding)
You can't move.
No moving.
(Referee)
That's one warning.
Don't move.
(Yellow card)
That's one warning.
(Night vision mode)
Hold on, Jin.
Help me find mine,
(Initiating a negotiation)
and I'll give you this one.
Take it off yourself.
Don't make this ugly.
No, help me find mine,
and I'll give this to you.
Mine might actually be yours.
(Sticking to physical force)
Get out.
I'll give you this!
Let's just swap.
Then you...
(We choose diplomacy)
Three, two, one, swap.
This is definitely not mine.
It's mine.
No, this is definitely not mine.
That one is mine.
This is mine.
I don't buy it.
I'm not giving it to you.
(Negotiation failed)
Help me find mine.
(Eavesdropping)
Lift your butt.
Help me find mine.
(The other side is just as chaotic)
Take it off yourself. Hurry up.
Take it off yourself.
Take it off!
Ning!
I'll give you this.
You guys...
(There are only 4 sleeping bags)
Hurry up.
(Referee's zone compromised)
I'll give it to you.
Take it off yourself. Hurry up.
Take it off.
This isn't looking good.
(Very chaotic)
Don't!
(Referee steps in to regulate)
(Saved)
(Referee, Two yellow cards)
Attacking me also counts as a warning.
I didn't. I...
(Too exhausted to argue)
Catch your breath.
(Sneaking a peek while it's bright)
You're moving.
You're still moving.
(Got it)
Take it off yourself.
(Silent threat)
This looks tragic.
What if you're wearing mine?
Can't we just swap?
How about this? Let's swap,
and then you wear mine,
and I'll tell you
what's on your back.
No way. Then you'd just win.
(Get a grip)
There are only four sleeping bags.
Jin, I think yours is mine.
Hold on.
Whose does Ding have?
Ding has yours.
(Ke's bag, Jin's bag,
Ding's bag, Ning's bag)
Is it?
Okay.
(Night vision mode, Start the fight)
Hand it over to me!
(I won't hold back)
Hand it over!
(Bye Zhou Keyu's sleeping bag)
Hold on.
Take it off.
This is mine.
Hold on.
Don't move.
Give it to me first.
Please.
Go easy on me.
(Begging Ning)
No way.
Go easy on me.
(Going full brute force)
Hold on a second.
(Snatched his own sleeping bag)
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
(What just happened?)
(Zhang Linghe's POV)
Get in. Let me get in.
Let me get in.
(Successfully checked in)
Are you sure that's yours?
(Just grabbing whatever's available)
This is Ding's.
(One step ahead)
There is a wriggler.
I'll strip that off you.
Just wait.
(Please be gentle)
Don't. We're all civilized people.
(I'll have my revenge)
No, we're going full brawl now.
Why are you "naked"?
Wait.
Why don't I have one?
(Night vision mode)
Hold on.
No more waiting.
(Tickling)
(Still as ticklish as ever,
From "The Truth (Season 3)" Episode 10)
(Ended up with nothing)
Three, two, one.
(Night vision mode)
Do you have a spare one for me?
(Returned to its rightful owner)
(Distribution in progress)
(Taking the lead)
You're rolling.
Don't roll. You have to wriggle.
Come back.
How do you turn this light on?
(Sill afraid of the dark)
Press the middle button.
(Helpful referee)
(Chasing hard)
(Collision)
What's up with those two?
Chase after them.
Whose is this?
(Still stuck in the starter zone)
(Staring at his name)
It's yours.
Don't even look.
Come back.
(Reached the turnaround point)
Gosh.
(Sudden stop)
Who's grabbing me?
Roll her back!
(Major advantage)
(Chasers behind, Roadblocks ahead)
Roll her back!
(Pushing forward)
Quick!
Yeah.
Catch your breath.
Honestly, since I can't win this round,
none of you are going to win either.
(Unbothered and cheerful)
None of you are going to win.
I'm not wearing
this sleeping bag anymore.
(No more nice guy persona)
I'm just going to camp right here.
Let's see who can pass me.
Don't.
Carry Jin back.
Wouldn't that just let you win?
Don't do this.
(Begging for mercy)
Can't let him win.
We can't let him win.
It'll be scary if he wins.
Alright.
(Defecting already?)
It's fine if I win.
Alright.
(End of discussion)
(Night vision mode)
(Striking immediately)
Oh no.
(Seize the opportunity)
(Secured first place effortlessly)
Yes, I won.
(The battle for dignity continues)
"Robbery"!
(Attacked from both sides)
Help me!
(Your hero has arrived)
Take it off.
Help me!
Help me.
(Unable to move)
I was wondering why I couldn't pull him.
(Not in the same weight class)
Turns out...
How about this?
No one survives.
(Let's go down together)
He was still moving
when the lights were on.
(Referee)
Referee.
I've fouled.
I've fouled. I admit it.
(Not even trying to hide it anymore)
I have three chances to foul.
(Look at him bullying the kid)
Referee.
(Referee)
You can still foul twice.
(Yellow card)
You've passed?
Yeah.
She already won.
Can we count points?
(Refusing to give up)
Sure.
I have five points now.
Get down.
(The battle continues)
(Night vision mode)
(Still pulling hard)
I'll just...
I give up.
Fine, I won't move.
I'm stopping.
Please.
You're not moving either.
(Trying to sneak away?)
You...
You still want to move?
Nobody move.
No one survives.
Get back here.
He's leaving. Go stop him!
Don't pull me.
No one survives.
Don't pull my pants off.
Even Ning...
Okay.
Bye-bye.
Nobody wear pants.
(Things are spiraling out of control)
(There's still a chance)
What are you doing?
Don't do this.
(Sending you far away
from the finish line)
Can someone please handle Zhou Keyu?
(Urgent intervention needed)
You three are at a total standstill.
You three,
(Assistant referee helping out)
put on your sleeping bags now.
Back to the starting line.
Yeah.
Fair competition, okay?
I was almost there.
(An illusion of winning)
Let's just make this a speed race.
We'll race to see
who wriggles faster, right?
(Race starts)
Hold on.
Come back.
The lights aren't off yet.
Go back to the starting line.
(Referee)
Go back first.
I was so close to making it.
I'm not listening.
On the road of growing up,
(Part-time therapist)
you're bound to run into some wolves.
There's nothing you can do.
(Is this what growing pains feel like?)
Alright, lie down.
Everyone get into position.
Bro.
We were born in the same year.
(Peers don't make life
hard for each other)
Why do you have to be so ruthless, bro?
Oh, now you know how to say that?
You've played both the good guy
and the bad guy all by yourself.
Get in.
(Valet parking in progress)
Alright.
Your legs.
Keep it fair for everyone.
Keep it fair.
Here?
Yeah.
Okay, let's go.
(Same starting line)
The lights will be on.
Let's do a speed race.
(Referee)
I'll do a three, two, one, and then go.
kay.
Three, two, one, go!
(Fierce competition)
(Wriggling in place)
Wait.
Ning.
(Nothing can save you now)
(Semi-defeated state)
(Halfway through the race)
(Here they come, run!)
Your head has to pass the line.
(Fighting hard for a spot)
(2nd place: Ding,
3rd place: Ke, 4th place: Ning)
It's great to be young.
I'm completely out of juice.
(I'm still your big brother)
What's wrong, babe?
I just didn't want
to accidentally kick you.
Are you elder, or am I?
(You really want to be my brother?)
I let you have this round.
You let him have it?
You let me have it?
(If only your skills were as solid)
We have a winner.
First place goes to Jin.
(Rankings, Scores, Total, Jin Jing +5, 05)
Second place is Ding.
(TNT Ding Chengxin +4, 04)
Third place is Ke.
(Zhou Keyu +3, 03)
Fourth place is Ning.
(Liu Yuning +2, 02)
Let's do one more round.
Alright.
I think this time, we
shouldn't fight over the sleeping bags.
Let's just go straight into a race.
(Direct)
How about that?
That works.
And for this race,
there's one thing we're banning.
No rolling over.
You can only wiggle forward.
Like this?
Yeah, only wiggling.
Alright.
Come on.
Let me check your gear. Get in.
Get in.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
(Master Zhang's valet parking
in progress)
Three, two, one.
Alright.
Hey wriggler, what kind of pose is that?
I'm wriggling like this.
The starting position must be
lying down.
Whatever the referee says goes.
Just listen.
Three, two, one.
Lie down.
Alright.
We should take a picture.
(Souvenir photo)
Three, two, one.
(Night vision mode)
(Wriggling on the back,
Wriggling on the front)
(Front-wriggler taking the lead)
How are you so fast?
(Nearing the finish line)
How is he wriggling like that?
(Requesting a tutorial)
What are you doing?
(Just getting started)
(Guaranteed last place)
It's over.
This round I'll...
(Night vision mode)
I'm not going anymore, honestly.
Nobody is getting back here.
(Activating roadblock mode)
(Clearing obstacles with one sweep)
Hold on.
Referees, jump isn't allowed, right?
(Do whatever you guys want)
This guy...
(Completely useless)
Hold on.
Made it!
Alright.
(1st place: Jin)
(2nd place: Ding)
(What's going on
with the two in the back?)
(Giving a push)
(Ning-style wriggling)
(Providing a chance to catch a breath)
(Let's go, bro)
(Night vision mode)
(Rolling)
Wait, no.
Someone's rolling.
Zhou Keyu, roll back here.
(Can't even use a little trick)
(Trying hard)
What am I supposed to do now?
Just give up.
I'm not giving up.
We've got to have the Olympic spirit.
(Putting the Olympic spirit
into practice)
(3rd place: Ning)
Three wrigglers have made it across.
As for the last one,
let's keep the lights on
and watch you come over.
Alright.
Wriggle in front of us.
Wriggle.
Hurry up.
No rolling allowed.
I am wriggling.
(Someone here doesn't know
how to wriggle)
(Working that butt hard)
You haven't mastered the technique.
Come on, Ding. Show him how it's done.
Give him a quick lesson.
How did you do it? You...
Let's see it.
Don't all your wriggles look like this?
(Wriggling masterclass)
(Absorbing useless knowledge)
Isn't this wriggling?
Like a caterpillar.
(Theory and practice aren't aligning)
Hold on.
Why aren't I moving?
You guys are both dancers.
You can't be less coordinated
than everyone else.
(In the name of dance)
(Just squirming in place
without moving forward)
This feels so awkward.
Such a smart kid,
yet he doesn't get
such a simple concept.
I'm so done.
Can you turn off the lights?
(Trying to save some dignity)
(Night vision mode)
Alright.
Almost there.
(Rolling and wriggling all at once)
How can you not know how to wriggle?
I just can't do it.
(Pass it on: #ZhouKeyuCantWriggle)
Maybe I'm too tall.
(Go take a shower if it's that itchy)
Are you feeling itchy?
This is painful.
Alright, let's announce the results.
(Rankings, Scores, Total)
First.
(Jin Jing +5, +5, 10)
Second.
(TNT Ding Chengxin +4, +4, 08)
Third.
(Liu Yuning +2, +3, 05)
Fourth.
(Zhou Keyu +3, +2, 05)
Alright, combining the scores
from both rounds?
First place...
I got ten points.
Congratulations to our players.
You've successfully fixed the first bug.
(Bug fix log: Darkfear)
(Loading dungeon three)
(Fear level continuing to rise)
(Brightness data syncing)
(Light source signal extracted)
(Fear level dropping)
(Module 01 fixed)
(Fix progress: 20%)
Player Jin Jing is the MVP
of this bug fix.
She earns one chance
to draw a Skill Card.
(Card box)
The Skill Cards come in N, R, and SSR.
(Rewind, Massage, Freeze)
Different tiers.
(Restore, Singing, Dancing, Compliment)
Good luck.
Compliment...
What is it?
What card is that?
Compliment Card.
(Compliment Card)
Everyone has to gather around you,
clap for 30 seconds,
and shower you with praise.
Come on, let's do it right now.
Come on, three, two, one.
(Compliment group ready for business)
Your hair looks so good today.
So pretty.
Your wriggling was
incredible.
She hasn't even used it yet.
(No forced sales)
She hasn't used it yet.
I'm going to faint.
I worked my butt off just for this?
No.
You won the praises
of this entire group.
Don't you think that's awesome?
To be honest, it's been so long.
I'm kind of used to it by now.
(Immune to compliments)
Compliments.
Used to being praised.
Alright, come on.
(Skill Card acquired,
Jin Jing: Compliment Card)
Let's go onto the next level.
Next level.
Three, two, one.
Welcome, everyone,
to the second bug space.
The system has detected
that someone among the players
is very dramatic.
Dramatic?
It's all your fault.
I'm telling you.
It's totally your fault.
Who's
dramatic?
Dramatic.
(Drama theater +1)
It fell off again.
Dropping items today?
We are now about to fix the second bug.
Look How Dramatic I Am.
You need to complete
"Look How Dramatic I Am"
(Drama bug fix mechanic)
to resolve the Drama bug.
Players need to draw lots
to split into three teams
and take turns taking on the challenge.
During the challenge,
two people must put on
noise-canceling headphones.
One person views the prompt
and describes what's on it,
while the other person
guesses the prompt.
Whichever team can guess the most words
within eight minutes
will be the winning team.
The winning team will receive
a reward for fixing the bug.
How are the five of us
splitting into teams?
Draw lots.
Okay.
Let's do it.
You go first.
Number one.
Number two. Who's number two?
I'm number two.
Aren't we guaranteed to win then?
(Confident)
Too strong.
We're too strong.
I'm number one.
Number one.
Me and Ning.
Look at you getting carried too.
I'm number three.
(Solo)
What does number three mean?
I'm a one-man team?
Since Player Ke drew a single number,
the other four players now need
to vote to choose one person
to partner up with him.
This player will get to participate
in two rounds of the fix game,
and their best round
will be used to determine
their final ranking.
Come on, rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper,
scissors.
(Scissors, Paper)
Won it in one shot.
(Mind blown)
(Team 3)
Come on,
first group starts.
You put it on first, Ning.
I'll guess first.
You guess first? Fine, I'll act it out.
Liu Yuning.
(Muted mode)
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me talking?
He looks so cute
in that military green jacket
with them on.
You went to Dandong?
You went there with Ning?
Eating strawberries?
He really can't hear anything.
(Totally confused)
(Referee steps in)
Three, two, one,
start.
(Secret)
Wait.
How many words?
One? Two?
Four words? Alright.
Gun.
Don't move.
(Scanning for keyword "gun")
Maintaining a youthful appearance.
Can be launched with a crossbow.
It can only be used once.
Second word.
(Secret)
Gun shot.
Four words.
The gun hits the pig's butt.
The gun hits
the pig's butt.
(The gun hits the pig's butt)
(Topic: The gun hits the pig's butt)
(The others are stunned too)
Nice.
The gun hits the pig's butt.
What?
(Secret)
Two words?
Two words.
First word.
Throw.
(Secret)
Spills...
(Correct)
(Spills water)
Don't disturb my work!
(Spilled Cup)
Spilled Cup.
(Topic: Spilled Cup)
Nice.
How did he even guess that?
(Secret)
(Liu Yuning's POV, Secret)
Two words.
(Liu Yuning's POV)
"Laundry Powder".
Honey.
Xi Hu.
(Topic: Xi Hu)
(Secret)
Four words.
(Liu Yuning's POV)
(Lip reading)
Turning up the pressure.
(Topic: Turning up the pressure)
(How is he this good?)
(Secret)
Six words.
Six?
Yes.
(Liu Yuning's POV)
(Perfect mouth score)
An Glass Factory.
(Topic: An Glass Factory)
Too fast.
(Topic: I am your son)
Five words.
I am your son.
(Taking a sneaky advantage)
(Don't miss either deal)
(He had no idea)
(Topic: Super cool)
Three words.
Super cool.
(Topic: Super cool)
You're super popular.
Cool.
Super cool.
Time's up.
So that's how
this game works?
You might think it's easy,
but I'm
the Game King.
(Game King)
I can't hear anything at all.
Yeah, you really can't hear.
This topic feels related to us.
Yeah.
It should be easier.
But Ning is smart
and great at guessing.
And his lips are very noticeable,
you know what I mean?
Honey.
(Tactic: exaggerated mouth movements)
An Glass Factory
Turning up the pressure.
I am your son.
(Thick lips: advantage)
(Liu Yuning and Zhang Linghe: 7 correct)
Okay.
Perfect.
I'll guess this time.
I'm pretty good at guessing.
Should I act it out?
Yeah, you act it out.
Can you hear me?
(Crystal clear)
The music hasn't even started yet.
The music just started playing.
Go away.
Move back.
Go stand over there.
Over there.
That's the mark.
You're an actor. Don't you recognize
the T mark?
Wait.
It's kind of intimidating
when you two tall guys come over.
(Overpowered by presence)
Three, two, one.
I'm pretty good at guessing.
Alright.
(I raise pigs to kill you)
(Topic: (I raise pigs to kill you)
Five words.
First word.
(Staring intently)
I...
I raise pigs to kill you.
I want to kill you.
(Messing around)
Correct?
I.
(Raise)
(Want)
(Pig)
(To)
Kill you.
(Focused stare)
I want to kill you.
I'm pretty good at guessing.
(Obviously the same strategy)
(Jin Jing's POV)
Big.
(Raise)
(Want)
(Grab)
(Baa)
(Pi)
(Giao)
(What are you Giao-ing about?)
(Topic: I raise pigs to kill you)
Pig.
I will strike you down.
Is it that hard?
(Can't even guess that?)
(Helpful audience member)
Just do it like this.
Itchy.
I'm itchy.
I raise pigs to kill you.
Oh, I raise pigs to kill you!
I'm pretty good at guessing.
(Voice worn out)
(Topic: Prince Kneeler)
Four words.
First word.
Kneel.
Foot.
Leg.
Chu.
Kneeler.
Prince.
(Kneeling so much your wrist hurts)
(Here we go again, making up words)
Prince Kneeler.
Kneeling in total shock.
(Bug found)
You're not allowed to write it.
(Got it?)
Prince.
(Finally)
(Husband-watching stone)
The husband-watching stone.
Prince.
(Prince)
This.
Prince Kneeler.
Kneeling in total shock.
(Completely exhausted)
We're doomed.
Me.
I.
Ding.
Bro.
(Ding)
(Bro)
Me.
Ding.
(It's me.)
Prince Kneeler.
Wait,
can we switch her in?
Sure.
(Red card from the team)
Fine,
put it on.
Put it on.
(Topic: Dandong dance king)
Ning.
Dandong.
(Dandong spokesperson)
(Topic: Dandong dance king)
Strong.
Strawberry.
Dandong.
He.
Liu Yuning.
His hometown.
He.
Where is he from?
Liu Yuning.
(That's Liu Yuning)
Looks like
you should send him some strawberries.
Dandong.
His brother.
Dan. It's here.
(You get it. You know it.)
Liu Yuning's belly button.
(Isn't that the belly button?)
Liu Yuning.
Dandong dance king.
He dances.
Liu Yuning can dance?
What do you mean?
(I'm the Dandong dance king)
Okay, switch back.
How come it's still
the same when we switch people?
Strawberry.
Spilled Cup.
(Is it that hard?)
I'll start with banana, okay?
Banana.
(Stop)
You're talking too fast.
I can't hear anything.
The volume is way too loud.
I really can't hear.
(Can't escape his own song)
Don't talk.
(Look at me)
(Moving closer)
Say it again.
Slow down a bit.
Wait.
Step back.
A bit more.
Stand there.
What happened to his belly button?
(My belly button is fine)
It has nothing to do with it.
That's wrong.
Okay.
(Belly button)
Forget it.
Start.
(Topic: Dandong dance king)
Last two words.
The third and fourth words.
Third and fourth? Alright.
Yeah.
Third and fourth.
Strawberry.
(What are you talking about?)
That makes no sense.
What does strawberry
have to do with this?
No.
The third
and fourth words are "strawberry".
What is this?
(Self-confused)
The third and fourth words.
(Dance king demonstrates personally)
Dance.
Dancing.
Third word. Dance.
Third word.
Dance.
King.
Yes.
Dance king.
Yuning dance king.
Okay, first word.
Dan.
Wait, it's him again?
Is it him or not?
(Who is it exactly?)
Egg. Chicken.
(Cluck cluck cluck)
Egg.
Egg dance?
Dandong dance king.
Stop laughing.
Six words.
(Challenge: You only care
that I speak harshly)
The last five words.
I.
(Challenge: You only care
that I speak harshly)
You.
Speak.
Harshly.
You keep talking nonstop.
(Completely confused)
I speak...
The fifth word.
Fifth.
I am a woman.
He is...
He is a man.
You are a woman. He is a man.
Yes. Man.
He is a man.
Just that one word.
Yelling at me will not help.
(Punching cotton)
I cannot hear you.
The fifth word.
Man.
(Man)
(Woman)
The three of them, plus you.
I don't think they can do it.
(Man)
Man.
Boy.
What?
Harsh.
Man.
(Truly difficult)
Okay.
Man.
All right.
That's enough.
Okay, step back.
(Harsh Jin)
(Harsh Ding)
The fifth word.
Harsh.
The sixth word.
Hear.
The first word. Only.
Only.
Correct.
Only care...
Only care that I speak harshly.
Speak harshly.
You only care that I speak harshly.
That is it.
How did this happen?
This is hilarious.
How many?
(Jin Jing and Ding Chengxin's
team answered 4 correctly)
Just look.
When we were playing,
did you think it looked easy?
(Their eyes are completely clear now)
After you two switched back,
it doesn't seem much different.
Jin,
this is far too difficult.
How can it be this hard?
The two of you keep
missing each other's point.
Exactly.
Even Dance King
of Dandong couldn't guess it.
I kept saying strawberry.
That means strawberry.
I was clearly telling you it, right?
I really need to reflect on this.
Ning made this game look far too easy.
Turns out you two are simply too clever.
(Only now realizing it)
I may have underestimated you.
I see that now.
(Game King returns)
Come on.
(Pokemon)
(Challenge: Pokemon)
Four words.
What do you call God's mount?
Pokemon.
Ride a horse.
Ride.
One, two...
What?
(God never crossed Dan's mind)
(Strict)
Riding a tiger.
Okay. Just describe...
(Give up on this approach)
Just describe the words instead.
Pokemon.
Is there...
(Is the problem with us?)
Anything wrong?
We are doing fine.
(Confidential)
You speak.
(I still refuse to believe it)
(Challenge: Confidential)
Three words.
Shoes.
Take off your shoes.
There is sand in the shoe.
(Confidential)
Put on your shoes.
I.
(Confidential)
My shoes.
Size 44.
Cinderella.
Three words.
(That fast?)
(Is the problem really me?)
This is so difficult.
(Challenge: I don't know.
My dance moves are graceful)
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine.
Ten words.
Should we skip this one, Ning?
(I am the Game King)
Let's do this one.
The first three words.
Three words.
(Challenge: I don't know.
My dance moves are graceful.)
I don't know.
My dance moves are graceful.
Social dance.
I don't know how to dance.
I.
My
dance moves.
I don't know.
Don't you know
that my dance moves are graceful?
(Impressive)
Look at you showing off.
(Please ask your brother.
Let your younger brother have it.)
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven.
Ten words.
Still ten words.
(Bring it on)
You.
Me.
Please.
Brother.
(Perfect interpretation)
I asked my brother.
(I'm right here)
Please ask your brother.
I asked my brother.
No.
You.
Please ask your brother.
I am asking my brother.
And then?
Please ask your brother.
All right.
You.
Please ask.
Stop repeating that line.
But that part is correct.
Please ask your brother.
I am asking my brother.
And then?
I asked my brother.
I am asking my brother.
I kept asking my brother.
Ask my brother, and then?
You.
Beg.
Beg your brother.
(They are talking
past each other)
You.
Beg.
Give it
to your younger brother.
What does he have to do with him?
I am the older brother.
(He is the younger brother)
How am I the younger brother?
(Completely bewildered)
Beg your brother.
(That part is right)
You.
Give it.
(Getting flustered)
Beg your brother to get on.
Beg your brother.
(Only making things worse)
Wait.
Yes.
Beg him to do what?
Watching the two of them
feels like watching you two.
Beg your brother.
(One sentence offended four people)
You, let...
Let.
What is that supposed to mean?
King of Dance from Dandong.
(King of Dance from Dandong demonstrates
his elegant moves)
Let.
(Challenge: Please ask your brother.
Let your younger brother have it.)
Brother, please get in the car.
Certainly.
Brother, please get in.
You.
Let.
(Get in)
(The car)
(Where exactly are you trying to go?)
Beg your brother
to go live.
(Even a shopping livestream has a cart)
You.
Give it to your
younger brother.
What?
Give it to your younger brother.
You get...
Brother, where are you going?
Where are you going?
(I am begging you)
(Game King's greatest defeat)
Beg your brother to go where?
(Challenge: Please ask your brother.
Let your younger brother have it)
Give it
to your younger brother.
Let your younger brother have it.
Not quite.
No, keep going.
Please ask your brother
to let your younger brother have it.
No.
I asked my brother
to let him have it.
Who asks does not matter.
Ask your brother
to let him have it.
No.
Wait.
Squats.
He has figured out "let".
He understands "let".
He has this part now.
The sixth word.
Sixth word.
The sixth word?
Yes, what is it?
Let.
(Let)
That is the seventh.
Let.
You.
Let what?
Give it.
Let you.
(Who?)
To whom?
Give it.
(Give)
Let.
Give it to him.
Give it.
(All-purpose gesture)
Strawberry.
Egg.
Give it.
(Give the egg, give the strawberry)
All right. It is fine.
Okay.
(Giving up)
Next one.
(Challenge: Confidential)
Six words.
The first word.
(Challenge: Confidential)
(Up, down, left, right)
Up, down, left, right.
(East)
(Game King, wake up)
Up, down, left, right, east.
All right.
Up, down, left, right.
Up, down, left, right, east.
What?
(What are you all laughing at?)
Okay. You.
Me.
You.
Describe yourself.
Six words describing you.
"Only me". Six words.
Yes.
(Take a guess)
What is it, Ning?
Act it out.
"Only me". Six words.
(From Zhou Keyu's perspective, what?)
(From Zhou Keyu's perspective)
Wu Yanzu.
Right.
What did he call you?
He called me...
the only Zu in East City.
(Challenge: The only Zu in East City)
(Challenge: A venomous woman)
Four words.
The first word.
(Challenge: A venomous woman)
Snake.
Second word.
Scorpion!
Snake and scorpion.
Femme fatale.
(High-EQ answer)
(Calm sideline judge)
Vicious what?
Make it more normal.
Not beauty.
More normal.
Vicious...
Woman.
(Prompt: The bed collapsed)
Three words.
You.
Me.
(Prompt: The bed collapsed)
(Perfect reenactment)
That acting was too good.
You can't miss that.
I'd be sad if I did.
Me...
Go to the bathroom?
(Not even hyped yet,
and he's dragging it again)
You, him, me.
The three of us.
(Get it now?)
Fell in a pit?
What is that?
Bed!
Bed.
Awesome?
Collapsed.
Too awesome?
What?
Right?
No.
You, me, him slept too hard.
Fell asleep.
Bed!
The bed collapsed.
Is time up?
Time's up.
This one's too hard.
Here, watch.
Beg your big bro.
Let your little bro have it.
That doesn't
make sense.
I beg you.
(Source: @Zhou Keyu)
(Liu Yuning and Zhou Keyu's
team got 6 answers right)
Congrats to the five players
for fixing the drama bug.
(bug fix log: Drama)
(Conflict index still rising)
(Emotion data syncing)
(Abnormal clip extracted)
(Drama value dropping)
(Module 02 repair complete)
(Loading copy three)
(Repair progress: 40%)
Congrats, players Liu Yuning
and Zhang Linghe.
You won first place
in Look How Dramatic I Am.
You get one Skill Card
for Door of Truth.
How about one each?
Can I give one away?
Of course not.
I'm begging you. Let me have it.
Give me one...
What card?
Give me one little blue card.
(What is it?)
I saw his.
Mine's insane.
I don't believe you.
Seriously?
Mine is
(Compliment Card)
the Compliment Card.
This...
The most compliments I've ever gotten
were on The Truth.
This isn't bad.
Mine's pretty good.
What's yours?
Singing Card.
(Singing Card)
Choose someone to sing a song for you.
Do you know
this card was made for you?
It's meant to let us...
In my hands.
(This songbird can request any song)
(Skill Card: Liu, Compliment Card.
Zhang, Singing Card)
Players, please head
to the next bug space.
Come on. Three, two, one. Go!
(Ghost Stories of Tui City backstage)
Come on. Sit.
Sit.
Sit down, everyone.
Players, welcome
to the third bug space.
The system has detected
that someone here plays too much.
(Plays too much)
Plays too much?
(He's clearly hinting)
Who stays up till dawn every night?
It's gotta be...
It's obviously that guy.
Ning.
What do you mean?
Ning sleeps the latest.
I'm into wellness now.
Then what was 5AM the other day?
I soak my feet every night.
Till 5AM?
Soaking my feet till 5AM.
They're all wrinkled by now.
So the system created the Play bug.
You need to complete
(Play bug repair protocol)
to fix the Play bug.
One player closes their eyes.
The other four players look at the task.
Then the player opens their eyes.
With guidance from the others,
they must complete the task.
The other four can't talk.
They can only use
such sounds to signal
if the player is right.
Within ten minutes,
complete seven tasks,
and the bug is fixed.
You'll also draw cards three times.
Okay.
Come on.
Then let's go left to right.
You close your eyes first.
I go first?
He goes first.
Sure.
Come on.
(Remove the egg white, keep the yolk,
and feed it to Ke)
Honestly, this is way too hard.
This is too hard.
(How hard?)
Okay, open your eyes.
Open them.
Okay.
(Remove the egg white, keep the yolk,
and feed it to Ke)
Go!
(Mm, wrong, wrong, wrong)
(Mm, smart! That's it)
(Mm, that's right)
(Waiting to be fed)
(Focused and careful)
(Can't watch anymore)
You're really wasting time, Ding.
Eat the shell too.
(Please eat)
(Egg)
(Crack it open)
(Crack it)
(Down)
So smart.
(No egg white)
(Egg white)
(Egg yolk)
(Yellow)
(Nice)
How long did that take?
(Time used: 1 min 20 sec)
That fast?
So good.
(First win)
I'll eat it myself.
No waste.
Next.
Okay, next.
Come on.
Okay, look at the task.
(Do a cool reverse parking move
in front of Jin)
Hard.
You really have to think
outside the box.
(Think wider)
Think wider.
Okay, I'm putting it down.
Okay.
(Task: Do a cool reverse
parking move in front of Jin)
(Take it off)
(Task: Do a cool reverse
parking move in front of Jin)
(Don't come closer)
(Don't go)
(Twist)
(Move forward)
(Go back)
(Hands in pockets)
(Squat down)
(Task: Do one cool reverse
parking move in front of Jin)
(Back up)
(Look at me)
(Brainwaves synced)
(Me)
(You)
(Mm)
(Ah)
(No one will get this for ten years)
(I get it)
I'm so tired.
(Reversing. Please be careful)
(Task: Do one cool reverse
parking move in front of Jin)
(Finally. Success is so close)
He, our hints were spot-on.
He.
(Time used: 2 min 10 sec)
Reverse parking?
Yeah.
We could only hint it
with engine sounds.
That was way too hard.
Okay. Come on.
I'm the Game King.
Alright.
(Game King)
The one who always saves the day.
(Cool and calm)
(Wink at He once with the left eye,
once with the right, and once with both)
So hard.
This one can be quick, though.
But how will he get it?
I'm just thinking how to tell him.
This is my natural reflex.
(Talking nonsense with a straight face)
I'm usually like this.
Can't help it. I'm just like this.
Yeah.
Okay, Ning.
Natural reflex, Ning.
Natural reflex?
What kind of phrase is that?
Come on.
(Wink at He once with the left eye,
once with the right, and once with both)
Natural reflex?
(Wink at He once with the left eye,
once with the right, and once with both)
(His eyes turned on hazard lights)
(Foot-powered upgrade)
Then it's...
(Look at me)
(Left)
(Right)
(Together)
(Get it?)
(Left)
(Right)
(Together)
(Time used: 40 sec)
Is...
(Game King has the shortest time so far)
Is there any task
Ning can't finish?
The one who always saves the day.
He never lets you down.
Alright.
Liu Yuning gets full approval.
(Game King)
Come on.
(Do a front leg raise, a side leg raise,
and a back leg raise)
This is way too hard.
(Hard)
Too hard.
Oh no. Hearing that made her stressed.
Yeah.
Come on.
(Do a front leg raise, a side leg raise,
and a back leg raise)
(Legs)
(Taking off shoes)
What are you doing?
(Front leg raise, side leg raise,
back leg raise)
(Front. Side. Back)
(Just one step away)
Kung Fu Girl, sit down already. Come on.
(Kung Fu Girl)
(Time used: 58 sec)
Fifty-eight seconds.
Okay, next.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
I'll definitely mess it up.
(Leave it to me. You should worry)
Come on.
(Pick Ning up bridal-style
and spin three times)
This one...
(A physical task)
Right?
(This takes strength)
(Task: Pick Ning up bridal-style
and spin three times)
Okay.
(Heads straight for Ning)
(Acting it out with his face)
(Lifts him easily)
(First bridal carry ever)
(Spinning)
(Not enough. Not enough)
Nice.
Strong.
So strong.
Seriously impressive.
(Reliable Ke. Time: 35s)
Congrats, everyone.
You've completed five tasks.
Your total time is now five minutes
and forty-three seconds.
You have four minutes
and seventeen seconds left.
Get two more tasks right,
and you'll fix the bug.
Okay.
(Took the longest)
(Volunteers to answer
and redeem himself)
Come on.
(Tie a bow on Ke with a rope)
This...
Ready?
Okay. Let's go.
Three, two, one. Start.
(Task: Tie a bow on Ke with a rope)
(Mm)
(Hinting)
(Cough, cough, cough)
(Innocent eyes)
(Making it obvious)
(Ticklish mode activated)
(Mm. Look at me)
(Mm)
(Got it)
I know now.
Okay, quick. Here. Stop.
Okay.
How's that?
(Time: 57s)
That works.
This one's kinda hard.
Very hard.
Too hard.
One more, right?
Okay, come on.
(Final challenge)
That hint was amazing, guys.
Amazing.
Let's go.
(Pout and dance "Little Swans".
Everyone's stunned)
Are you
for real?
Don't mess with us, man.
(Mentally broken)
We can.
We can. Let's go.
(Game King steadies the team)
(We can)
(Let's go)
Let's go.
Okay, go.
(Task: Pout and dance "Little Swans")
(Ke, listen)
(Pouting)
(Squats)
(High knees)
(Back kicks)
(Athlete Ke)
(Classic Little Swans move)
One more time.
Three, two, one. Go.
That works.
Okay, success.
This is way too hard.
What a bunch of...
(Time: 1min 19s)
Exactly one minute and nineteen seconds.
We did it, folks.
Congrats to our five players.
You've successfully fixed the Play bug.
(Bug Fix Log: Play)
(Fun index still rising)
(Behavior data syncing)
(Attention focus located)
(Playfulness dropping)
(Module 03 repair complete)
(Case 3 loading)
(Repair progress: 60%)
This round, the players have earned
three chances to draw Skill Cards.
If I see that Compliment Card again...
Okay, Ding. You draw one.
You haven't drawn yet, right?
Then you draw another one.
I've done it already.
The three of us all drew.
You draw another one.
Fine.
Whatever.
Look!
Mine's not bad.
(Rewind Card)
Mine's a Skill Card too.
Rewind Card.
(Massage Card)
This one's okay.
You can pick someone to massage you
for three minutes.
(Skill Card results)
(Jin Jing: Compliment Card, Rewind Card)
(Ding Chengxin: Massage Card.
Zhou Keyu: Rewind Card)
Next time I get that Singing Card,
I'll use it on him.
Make him sing to that ghost.
The Massage Card works too.
Make the ghost massage him.
(One second ago)
(The next second)
I'll use the Rewind Card.
Like after the ghost scares you,
I'll make it scare you again.
You know?
(Can't even smile)
Like, after he says that, I'll...
We can keep scaring him.
Say he's on a solo mission.
He walks into a room.
He finally gets out.
Then, Rewind Card.
Go back in.
The second he steps out,
I use the card.
Make him go in three times straight.
(Wronged)
No.
We wouldn't.
Of course not.
(Real bros)
No way.
Ding misses when he first came,
when the four of us still treated him
with some manners, kindness, and care.
Now we've already...
Now we just don't care at all.
Alright.
It's fine.
I'll accept it.
Players, please head
to the next bug space.
Okay.
Come on.
Here we go again. So fast.
(Bug fix to be continued)
(Next episode preview)
You need to finish Push-Jump
to fix the Jumping bug.
I'm totally fine with it.
Cute push!
Should we raise it a little?
This game
represents our IQ
and body coordination.
Cute push!
Then I'll...
Sultry push.
(Sultry push)
Ning's about to get stuck in that pose.
The system detected that one
of you is really greedy.
Who's that greedy?
Why are you so sure?
When you bite a lemon,
the juice bursts out into the air.
It sprayed on your face.
You're in such a rush to clear yourself.
You're playing that with me?
You're the greedy ghost.
Then he's your accomplice.
We've already confirmed each other.
No one else can be Five.
Besides him, only One,
Three, and Four are left.
It's you.
Your plan's kinda unclear to me.
That's still the bug logic
I just mentioned.
Come on, guys.
After fixing the bug today,
let's all have dinner together.
I'm really looking forward
to Ding's solo mission.
Don't. Please don't.
But I think if Ding does a solo mission,
he'll tough it out and finish it.
Ding would never quit or anything.
Who should get
the killer role next round?
You haven't had it.
Now the directors
will rewrite the script overnight.
You're always guessing
what the directors are doing.
Which five bugs got fixed?
Greedy, scared of the dark,
jumping, playful, and dramatic.
Oh no. We didn't fix horror.
What?
(Door of Truth: Chapter Two beta.
Thanks, cloud players!)
♪Come now, players all,
let the game of reason start♪
♪Unlock each hidden trial,
let courage spark the dark♪
♪Night falls slow, shadows grow,
the sleuth is lost inside the maze♪
♪Figures pass, lanterns sparse,
dark currents drift without a trace♪
♪Wind picks up, footsteps rush,
cold laughter swallowed by the dark♪
♪Truth concealed, the night
stands still, and nothing leaves a mark♪
♪An unsigned letter, coded words,
the solvers gather one by one♪
♪A broken game, illusion reigns,
who's hiding what they've done?♪
♪Hushed voices, nerves on edge,
wrapped in smoke and mirrors still♪
♪The next second, deeper riddles,
or the answer to the kill♪
♪Every piece of truth
has finally come to light♪
♪Unlock the mystery, turn the question,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Side by side, no holding back,
follow every clue to find the truth♪
♪The story blurs like flowers in fog,
let's begin tonight♪
♪Search for the vanished cipher,
trace the proof, and face the sleuth♪