[Episode 05: Is the rain seen from a hotel different from the rain seen from a motel?]
Kim Dali!
Kim Dali, are you in there?
It's me.
I knew it. I knew this would happen.
Something didn't feel right.
Why are you here in the middle of the night if I dropped you off at the hotel?
About that...
What? You can't pay for the hotel?
You said you sold your house.
About that...
It's because I have work left to do.
The exhibition is just around the corner. I need to work on the plans,
and there's a lot to prepare to convene a donor group meeting.
Do that work at the hotel.
Sorry?
If you work here all night, will you pay the electricity and water bill?
Electricity bill?
Even if the art museum is under your name,
won't the electricity and water bills be under the operating expenses of the art museum?
Why do you have to spend the operating expenses of the art museum to do what you couldn't do during business hours?
This is what personal use is. Personal use.
Personal use?
Why can't you tell the difference?
Hurry up and get your luggage. I will take you back to the hotel now.
No, Mr. Jin. I really have work to do today.
Those who are not good at studying always stay up all night and cram.
People who can't work are trying to work overtime.
You have to lead by example, starting from the director. Unnecessarily working overtime.
What's going on? She didn't even turn on the lights?
She's not scared of anything.
[Episode 5]
Mr. Jin.
You just need to take this, right?
About that ...
Were you going to stay here?
To save money on the hotel bill?
No. I have money.
What are you doing? Let's go.
How did you know I was at the art museum?
Do you have somewhere to go other than the art museum?
You don't have friends to drink with. It didn't seem like you have any relatives who stop by.
Put in your phone number.
My phone number?
I realized I was too complacent.
Somehow, the creditor still doesn't know the debtor's phone number.
Why aren't you entering it in?
Can you press the call button on the bottom?
Don't erase it
and save it. If I call you answer right away.
It's not because there's another meaning behind this.
You're saying that it's because you're afraid I'll run away.
As you said, I have no friends
and no relatives to take me in,
so where would I go? You don't have to worry.
When my father was alive, I thought I had a lot of friends
and relatives that I had too many to count,
but now it's become so simple.
That's how the world is.
People stick around when they can benefit from you.
If they make a mistake they might lose their benefits.
Did you think they would stick around?
Don't be too disappointed.
So, on a day like today,
you just get a good night's sleep in an expensive room and don't think about anything.
You already owe billions of won,
so if you pay for a hotel, it won't make a difference to your debt.
♫ Even if he's wrong ♫
Wow, where are you going to find another creditor like me?
Accepting your drinking habits, paying for your drinks,
driving you to get a good night's sleep in a luxury hotel,
and lastly, providing you with a complimentary drink.
Here.
It's made from a raisin tree or whatever.
Anyway, it was the most expensive one in the store,
so don't leave a drop of it and drink it all.
♫ Its mine ♫
♫ Time will be on your side ♫
♫ You need to come around to yourself ♫
♫ One day it'll be ♫
You can go now.
I will feel relieved when I see you go in.
What if you come out again like earlier?
- Goodbye.
- All right. Goo–
I said I'll pay for the hotel.
♫ Is it a deeply dug hole ♫
Tomorrow is the employee's payday,
what should I tell them?
♫ The words you said to me will be traces of the past ♫
A refund?
I beg you.
♫ So that you won't be able to see how I feel ♫
♫ But always see the same face in front of you ♫
♫ The heart that no one knows is hidden behind it ♫
♫ Will you think of me again ♫
♫ At night? ♫
[Heights Motel]
Excuse me...
I want to stay for one night.
It's 50,000 won.
You can go to room 205.
Honey. Honey. What room are we in?
203.
Are you sleeping?
No, not yet.
[Mr. Jin]
Hello?
If you're not sleeping, take a look out your window for a moment.
The window?
You don't know that it's raining right now, do you?
Watch the rainy night view before you go to sleep.
You should get your money's worth.
Are you watching the rain?
Yes.
Isn't it amazing?
That hotel is famous for its night view.
I mean, not that I've slept there before.
We had a year-end party with the franchisers there before.
That's how I know.
Why would I spend money to sleep at a hotel when I have my house? It's so expensive.
I mean, I could if I had moved out and didn't have somewhere to go.
What I'm saying is...
sleep well.
And don't think too much.
Sleep well too, Mr. Jin.
All right.
Goodbye.
Idiot.
♫ My days are sad, but I have a dream ♫
♫ Can't you ♫
♫ Love me? ♫
No. Please. Please don't take that money.
No, no. Please, no.
No, no. Please, please.
[Sung Dong Police Station]
Cheongsong Art Museum is being sued?
Yeah. It seems they're behind on some settlement payments.
I heard loan sharks or gangsters went there and
caused a huge mess. You haven't heard?
How did Cheongsong get like this?
Why are you telling me this now?
- Move it.
- What's wrong with him?
I only just heard this!
[Dali]
- Hello?
- Is this Detective Joo Won Tak?
- This is him.
- Do you perhaps know Kim Dali?
Who?
So it was someone who works at the motel,
and you remember his face?
Dali, you...
I'm Dali's guardian. I heard it was the motel employee's doing?
It wasn't a regular employee but a temporary part-timer.
Gosh.
Luckily, she remembers his face,
and they're currently investigating the crime scene,
so I'm sure they'll find him soon.
She's lucky it's only this bad.
First, go home and rest,
- then come out together–
- Lucky? She's covered in bruises!
Hold on, let go.
Does someone have to die for it to be a big deal?
- I mean...
- You're unbelievable.
Aren't you cracking down on these illegal motels lately?
What the hell were you doing on patrol that a robbery happened while you're cracking down on these motels?
Are you doing your jobs properly?
And how is the crime scene still under investigation?
Let go!
- Are you okay? I'm sorry...
- Why are you taking it out on us?
It hurts.
She's hurting!
I'm sorry for troubling you when you're busy.
I had to pay the bill to be discharged, but my whole purse was stolen.
You called me because of the hospital bill?
You wouldn't have called otherwise?
What?
Mr. Kim and you, both.
Why do you keep making me out to be an ungrateful jerk?
When I had nowhere to go,
you were the first ones to take me in.
And you were the ones who patiently believed in me without giving up.
So for me,
when I'm feeling angry, happy, or hopeless, I don't think I'm alone.
I think of you and Mr. Kim first.
But how come you don't do the same? Why?
How could you not tell me anything even when you're about to live in a motel?
- Get in.
- Okay.
I'm sure you know since you've come over,
I can't say it's better than a motel,
but it's safer at the very least, for now.
For now?
What?
Can't I stay a little longer? "For now" is too cold.
How about "for a while?"
- Just get in.
- Okay.
Just wait until you get caught. I'll kill you.
- Good morning.
- Good morning? You just came from a lunch meeting.
Is it important what time it is? It's still a good morning for me.
Why?
Because I just came to work.
Okay.
Why is the entry fee for an elementary school music camp so expensive?
World-renowned pianists are giving private lessons.
So that much is cheap.
I believe you need a professor's letter of recommendation to get in. Not everyone can get it.
That's right. How do you know that, Gong Joo?
I went to an art camp there when I was young.
As expected, it's different being from a rich family.
You must be having a hard time living paycheck to paycheck.
I heard your wife had to quit her job to look after your child.
If we want to raise the next Cho Seong Jin, then we have to endure it.
(T/N: South Korean pianist)
Speaking of which, there won't be any issues with our paycheck today, right?
There shouldn't be. I don't know about anything else, but it's our paychecks.
No way.
I really like the fact that
the art museum staff here
have a strong sense of economy.
Whether the art museum closes or not because it's ruined,
whether the director sells her house to prevent that or not,
none of that matters. Right?
As long as you get your paycheck, that's all that matters.
That's commendable.
It's selfish,
shameless,
and very humane.
It's beautiful. It's artistic!
Don't you think so, Mr. Han?
I didn't mean that.
But are we really closing our art museum?
Why are you asking me that?
You should ask the director!
Where's Kim Dali right now?
Earlier...
Well...
You don't know?
Didn't Kim Dali come into work today?
I called her earlier because of the meeting, but she didn't answer.
- Is that all?
- Pardon?
If she didn't answer, you should be calling until she does.
What are you doing? Call her again.
Yes, Sir.
The phone is turned off.
It's said the phone is turned off.
Try again.
Forget it. I will do it.
Over there...
That looks like the director.
Who's that guy?
Could it be her boyfriend?
What?
I'm a little late because I had an external schedule.
I was going to ask for your opinion on the exhibition, but since it's not urgent, let's talk about it at the next meeting.
You may go back to work.
Are you going out again?
No.
Do you have something urgent to go to?
Why do you ask?
If you do, cancel it.
My agenda is really urgent.
Sit down. Let's have a meeting.
Excuse me, Mr. Jin.
You said you would do whatever I wanted if you can't pay me back within a week. Are you going to pay me back?
Go ahead.
"A rescue plan for stabilizing the business operations of the Cheongsong Art Museum"?
What are you doing?
Sorry?
Aren't you taking your sunglasses off?
Well, it's—
- I think that's a good idea.
- What?
We do need a rescue plan. Especially one for stabilizing the business operations of the Cheongsang Art Museum.
I don't think an important agenda like this should be taken lightly and skimmed over.
I will take it and review it carefully.
Underlining without missing a single letter.
- I mean, you can just do that here–
- That's all for today's meeting.
But... this is a bit odd.
No working overtime. No charging your cell phones.
You are only allowed to use two sheets of toilet paper?
There's this too. Turn off the lights in the exhibition rooms when there are no guests.
What kind of rescue plan for stabilizing the business operation is this?
Are you serious?
You're right. You can't stabilize a business just by saving a little bit of money like this.
I agree with you.
We should at least fire half of the staff.
And turn the rest of the employees into temporary workers!
In order to share the burden, we'll reduce the salaries!
That's the only way to feel the burden.
Don't you think so, Mr. Han?
I think that's too much burden.
We're already running with the minimum amount of staff. How can we fire more?
We need to be squeezing dry mops right now!
It's not squeezing dry mops.
It's squeezing dry towels!
(T/N: It means there are ways to improve cost-cutting)
I'm sorry.
Mops or towels, it's the same thing!
That's enough, Mr. Jin.
Shouldn't the staff know what situation the art museum is in right now?
- You running around everywhere by yourself, that–
- I said I would review it.
I'll go over it carefully and come up with a proposal by tomorrow.
That's fine, right?
Whatever you want.
Mop?
I'll make sure to use the toilet paper sparingly.
I forget to tell you this, but–
How can you come in without knocking?
I'm sorry.
I didn't see anything.
What's this about?
Well...
Since I will start working in earnest, I thought I would need an access card.
If I'm going to go back and forth between the gamjatang restaurants and the art museum, I'll likely have to come in early,
or come in after everyone gets off of work.
I'll let Ms. Gong Joo know.
- Two cards. One for me and one for secretary Yeo.
- All right.
If you don't have anything else, then goodbye.
Did something happen?
No.
Your phone was turned off.
It's broken, so I'm having it fixed.
It was working fine last night.
I dropped it this morning.
Aren't you uncomfortable in those?
It's due to a personal matter. If you're done with your work, then–
What personal matter?
When someone does not explain something and says it's personal,
doesn't that mean that the person does not want to disclose a particular situation or maybe is not in a condition to disclose it?
It's a sty.
I want to get to work now.
Are you looking for a new place? You can't keep staying at the hotel.
So I looked into it.
I found a place.
- When?
- This morning.
- Where?
- My friend's house.
- What friend?
- Do I need to tell you?
- You said you had no friends.
- I do.
A woman?
A man?
What man?
- Was it the guy who dropped you off earlier? That jer–
- Mr. Jin.
I mean, as a creditor—
Is it your right to know my workplace, number, and temporary residence? Isn't that an invasion of my privacy?
An invasion of privacy?
The world is a dangerous and horrible place, so I am just—
trying to protect my asset.
Do you think I want to invade your privacy?
If something happens to you, then what about my money?
Will you take responsibility?
Is he trustworthy?
I have to work.
Is he trustworthy? You can tell me that much.
Do you have personal reasons for not sharing that as well?
Yes, he is trustworthy.
Trustworthy, my foot.
There's no man worth trusting in this world. What a naive woman.
- What did she say?
- My gosh!
What do you mean?
Didn't you go in there to ask her who that man from earlier was?
You went in so desperately, like a guy who found out the girl he likes has a new boyfriend.
Who? Me?
Like who?
Is it not true?
I am Jin Moo Hak.
Me? Like that woman, who's drowning in billions of debt of all people?
Did you hit your head?
- Forget it then.
- What?
Why were you so easily persuaded?
I wanted to check just in case.
Just in case of what?
You know, you two are...
So, we're what?
I... you know... um...
Do I have to say it in words for you to understand?
Yes, tell me in words because I can't understand.
So... I... uh...
So...
What? What did you say?
Say it louder. I can't hear you!
Chak Hee, I have plans so I was wondering
if you can deliver the art piece on your own?
We just met, but we seem to just understand each other.
We must be a match made in heaven.
Where should we meet next time?
Excuse me, Chak Hee. Chak Hee.
Is it someone you know?
Chak Hee?
- Do you really think we get along well?
- What?
I couldn't even understand half of what you were saying.
I understand that you're trying to show off by using difficult words that you picked up after studying so hard.
But isn't it etiquette you at least brush your teeth before a first date?
Why does your mouth smell like a bathroom?
Damn it my mouth... Hey...
Chak Hee?
The lady in the Seongbuk neighborhood isn't very particular,
so all you have to do is position the artwork. The driver will do the rest.
Chak Hee?
All right. He's leaving at 3:00 p.m., so I just have to be here before then. Right?
Chak Hee, this...
[Gallery Mond]
I'm on my way, so come out.
What now? I'm busy. Eat on your own.
It's regarding Cheongsong Art Museum.
Cheongsong Art Museum?
What about Cheongsong Art Museum?
Is there some kind of problem? What's the problem?
What's your relationship with Cheongsong Art Museum?
You were the gangster at Cheongson Art Museum from that time, right?
What do you mean, "gangster"? We got involved due to a business problem. It's nothing important.
Your business is not my concern, but why were you at a hotel with Kim Dali?
- You know Kim Dali?
- Is there anyone who works in arts that doesn't know her?
Oh, she's that famous?
I'm asking why you were at a hotel with that girl.
What do you mean? I just dropped her off because she was drunk.
- How did you know that, though?
- I was at the hotel at the same time.
Then why didn't you say hi?
You really don't have any relationship with that woman?
Whatever relationship we have or not, why is that your concern?
I'm busy. Did you call me here to ask me that?
You know that I'm very sharp when it comes to dating, right?
- Oh really?
- I can tell who likes who and who's dating each other.
I'm really good at seeing when someone likes someone.
That's why I give a lot of dating advice, too.
If you have that kind of talent you should work at a marriage bureau.
Why are you working at a gallery where you are getting bullied?
I'll take an iced Americano.
When I saw you at the hotel, I was reminded of the saying "A monk can't wash his own head".
(T/N: She meant the Korean saying "A monk can't shave his own head" meaning, you can't help yourself out)
I see. I'm always curious about this though...
Why can't a monk wash his own head?
What? What's wrong with being curious?
The monk needs hair to be able to wash it. How can monks wash their hair if they're bald?
Oh... That's why...
That's not what's important. Are you stupid? Do you not understand what I'm saying?
I, Ahn Chak Hee, am confessing that I have feelings for you, Jin Moo Hak, a guy who sees nothing else but money!
You have no sense, you are ignorant, you bully people, and don't even know any idioms,
but I still like you, you idiot!
All right, Chak Hee. Sit down.
I'll persuade my dad somehow.
I'll make sure you don't get hurt.
So, don't let me see you at a hotel with another woman ever again.
I have to go to work.
What's with her all of a sudden? My mind is complicated as it is.
What? You want me to grant you another loan and you'll put up the artworks as collateral?
Dali, do you have money saved up in our bank or something?
Unlike real estate mortgage, which increases over time,
artwork will only pile up dust and sell for nothing.
It's also a pain to take care of,
and it costs money too!
Why is this girl not getting the message?
Hello, sir, this is Dali. You remember me, right?
It's been a while. The reason I called is...
Sir...
[Kim Ki Woon]
[Kwon Gyeong Heon]
Hello, this is Kim Dali. Kim Dali. I'm not sure if you remember me.
But the reason I called is to ask a favor...
Are you going somewhere?
Oh no, I... I'm sorry. Are you all right?
I'm okay. I was caught up in my thoughts.
Here.
Thank you.
What?
That one's having issues, too?
Yeah, I think it's too old.
It's been worrying because the office and storage seemed to have been broken into.
The CCTV is giving us trouble too.
I did some repairs, but I think we'll need to replace it with a new one.
Okay, let's replace it.
I have something to tell you.
Please come to my office. Mr. Hwang, you too.
Me too?
What? You're pushing back our pay?
That won't work. How am I supposed to pay my credit card bill this month?
I have loan interest for my apartment to pay along with my kid's tuition and living expenses.
I have to send my kid to camp this month, too.
Why are you all so quiet? Am I the only one that's desperate?
Am I the only one living month-to-month?
Say something, Curator Song.
You have your mom's hospital bills and caregiver to pay, too. Don't you have more bills than me?
I'm sorry. It's because of my negligence.
I'll do whatever it takes to prepare your pay as quickly as possible.
Do you really not have any money?
- I'm sorry?
- I'm just having a hard time understanding.
- Gong Joo.
- The clothes on your back, your sunglasses, shoes, and bag.
Are worth more than enough to pay for three months' salary for all of us. You know that, right?
Three months?
You're covered in designer clothes,
yet you don't have enough to pay our measly salaries.
You're telling us to believe that right now?
That's really outrageous.
I think there's a misunderstanding. I wouldn't lie to you.
These clothes and this bag are several years old.
I wouldn't buy these while not paying your salaries.
Those shoes are from this season.
With only three pairs in the country.
These shoes... so...
For you, the money is less than the price of a pair of shoes,
but for ordinary people like us, it's what lets us feed, clothe, and care for our families for an entire month.
And whatever little is leftover we put into savings.
That money is our lifeline.
How despicable.
Gong Joo.
Seriously.
Take a look all the way behind Cheongsong Art Museum.
It's a Restricted Development Zone, but there's been a lot of deals in this area starting five to six years ago.
Here, here, and here.
Do you know whose land it is?
It's under a borrowed name, but it actually belongs to Assemblyman Ahn Sang Tae.
Ahn Sang Tae?
You know, the family of the girl Moo Hak went on a blind date with.
The girl that turned Moo Hak down for being too ignorant.
- Moo Hak said he rejected her.
- What?
Anyway, this man has been a council member at the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, and Transport Committee for seven years.
Why would he buy all this land in the Restricted Development Zone?
So, what? Are they removing the restriction?
Bingo!
Really? They're really removing the restriction?
You can't tell anyone yet.
You know what'll happen if word gets out. It'll be a mess.
You really can't even tell Moo Hak.
I'm saying that we shouldn't try to just take over the Art Museum and sell the land right now.
We should start a construction division in our company,
and jump into this project, Father!
But even if they really remove the restriction... will there be room for us to join?
They probably planned everything out amongst themselves already.
We can make room... if there isn't any room.
What?
I'll go and make room for us.
You just get the money ready, Father.
Let's keep it between us for the time being.
You can't bury the truth.
Did he say he'll get it ready?
I told you to wait in the room. Why did you come here?
I was preparing to rip that old geezer's hair out if he said no.
He better not leave you out in the cold again this time, or else...!
How could he? Not after knowing what I have up my sleeves.
What is it that you have that's making you so confident?
It's...
Forget it... It's so big that it's dangerous.
I'll tell you later, Mom.
What is it? What is it!
Go ask Professor Kim to write up a talisman.
One that will work wonders.
Okay? Okay!
Talisman? Okay!
She used to work overtime a lot before,
but because I told her off once, she went home right on time.
Where the hell did she go... I can't even get in contact with her.
Let go!
Hey, are you sure you looked for it properly?
Where could it be if not at his house or the art museum?
Where else would the old man have left it?
If you don't believe me, search for it yourself.
- This little..
- I'm going to quit my job.
Why would I stay when Mr. Kim's no longer here and I'm not even getting paid.
You didn't get paid?
So stop harassing me and find the documents or bunch of stamps by yourself!
Who says you can quit?
Don't be cocky. Shut up and stay put until I fire you.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Me?
I'm the one who knows what kind of person you are,
and knows all about what you've been doing.
You must think that you had become a real curator because you worked at an art museum.
Should I expose to the world everything you've been up to since coming to Cheongsong?
Those are all things you made me do.
Well...
Would people believe the word of an orphan bar girl?
Or would they believe me, the Cheongsong family's eldest son?
You must've experienced this all your life.
Are you stupid? Why can't you take your experiences and learn from them?
Excuse me.
What's going on?
Are you okay?
It has nothing to do with you so go on your way.
She's my employee, why would it have nothing to do with me?
Right? You work at our art museum?
"Our" art museum?
This is driving me crazy!
You little beggar!
"Beggar"? Does he know how much this suit is?
Are you all right? I can escort you if you're scared.
I'm okay.
Where the hell did he put it, then? The old fart!
[Reporter Song of Jae-Il Newspaper]
Reporter Song!
The bed will arrive this week. It might be uncomfortable but just wait a little longer.
I'm not uncomfortable at all. Don't worry.
You look extremely uncomfortable. How long are you going to keep those on?
But if I sleep here, where will you sleep?
I can sleep in the living room, my car, or anywhere.
In the car?
I'm always working late or on a stakeout.
I just come here to change. I mostly sleep in the night duty room at the station, so don't worry.
Then I'll sleep in the living room.
Hey!
I pay the rent so I should get the room with the TV. Have you no conscience?
You don't think the landlord will say something?
Who is he to say anything? It's my home until the lease ends.
He seemed a little fussy last time.
Fussy? I think he's a little weird.
He seems young too, but he won't stop talking about the electricity and water bills.
Anyway, he's not normal.
What?
He just reminds me of someone I know.
- You know someone like that too?
- Yes.
What is this?
I was going to give it to you later for making me worry about you.
We caught the culprit.
What?
We're lucky we were able to identify him so quickly.
Otherwise, we wouldn't have caught him in time before he used up all the money.
See? This is the class of Korea's police force.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Dali?
What's wrong?
It's because I am happy.
It's such a relief. Right, Won Tak?
I could not show how I felt throughout the day.
I had a really hard time today.
My employees cannot pay for their credit cards or send their children to prep schools because of me.
No matter where I called, because I am so pathetic and useless,
no one would come to help.
But...
I am glad it turned out like this.
I am really relieved.
Isn't it a bit boring?
I think it's time to change them.
Yes, Sir.
Don't just change the ones in the executive offices, change the ones in the lobby, cafeteria, etc.
The employees should also be able to see them.
I will let Gallery Mond know that.
I told you they're boring.
Sorry?
If we want to change the ambiance, we have to change who we buy from.
I think Cheongseong will be a good fit.
[Century]
What is this?
Why is this here?
Didn't you send it to Dali?
It looks like she moved.
She moved?
Then did she move out all of her stuff? Where did she go?
About that...
You don't know?
[Dali]
Her phone was switched off all day long.
The number you called is unavailable. You will be sent to voicemail.
How the hell did you let this happen?
I am sorry.
She went to work like always, so I don't think anything happened to her.
Also, about the man at the department store that you asked me to look into,
I think he is the creditor who recently visited the art museum and caused chaos.
So you are saying that even gangsters are after her now?
And you say that nothing is wrong with her?
I don't know!
Dali moving or even immigrating, how is that related to you?
You better let it go while I am still being nice.
How dare you pretend to worry about her?
Son of a bitch.
The downfall of Cheongsong Art Museum?!
[Jae-il News | Social news: The downfall of Cheongsong Art Museum?]
"Cheongsong Art Museum which has served as a symbol of Korea's private art museums
and a bridgehead for the advancement of culture and arts in Korea,
was on the brink of closure
less than a month after director Kim Nak Chun's sudden death.
It is said that the long-accumulated financial deterioration
caused an incident in which loan sharks occupied the exhibition hall and rioted,
and eventually reached a situation where they could not even pay their employees' salaries.
The problem is the inability of the succeeding director in tiding over the crisis.
The new director, Ms. Kim Dali, who is the only daughter of Kim Nak Chun
could not grasp the severity of the situation and
...pocketed the gallery's assets behind the back of the employees,
and is shopping at couture shops.
According to a concerned source, she was taken to the emergency room
after being robbed while entering a motel
- with a man that she is in a romantic relationship with."
- What?!
Robbed?
"It makes us wonder about the future of Korea's art culture and arts if we can leave
this private gallery growing on our taxes
to this incompetent and unreliable successor, as of now."
[Jae-il News | Social news: The downfall of Cheongsong Art Museum?]
Hello?
Am I speaking to Ms. Kim Dali?
Yes, this is she.
I am from the Nambu police station.
I'm calling you regarding the motel robbery incident.
Please come down to the police station today and file the report.
Sorry? But I heard that the culprit was caught yesterday.
The case hasn't even been filed. How can we catch the perp already?
Who told you this?
Were you going to stay here?
To save money on the hotel bill?
I forgot to tell you this, but–
How can you come in without knocking?!
I'm sorry!
When someone does not explain something and says it's personal,
doesn't that mean that the person does not want to disclose a particular situation or maybe is not in a condition to disclose it?
♫ To my poor soul ♫
Mr. Jin, didn't I tell you to knock before you come in!
Is it true, that news article?
What are you talking about?
♫ I don't want to ♫
♫ Surprise your soft heart ♫
What are you doing?
♫ But I think I love you ♫
If this is not about work, I would rather not talk about it.
You sold your house.
You sold your necklace or whatever at a really high price. You had money!
I even took you to the hotel, so why—
Stop it.
I know it, too.
How stupid and pathetic I am.
I didn't even think to hide the precious bundle of cash at that time.
I am realizing what kind of bottom I have hit, every day, quite miserably.
You really don't need to add to it.
It's not important, it's just money!
You should have just let it go.
That's nothing. That money isn't important!
Don't you have to live, first?
Do you know how dangerous that situation was? You could have died!
You're smart, why don't you know that?
Do you know how badly your father's heart would break if he were able to see this?!
What do you mean by "it's not important, it's just money"?
Why did this all happen in the first place?
It's because of money, isn't it?
Aren't you here because of the money?
Aren't you the want who laid down in the exhibition room, causing a riot, and followed me to the hotel scared that I would run away in the night without paying you?!
Also coming here the first thing in the morning and pretending to care about me,
isn't this all for money?
Am I wrong?
Tell me if I am wrong?
♫ Like calm music, it keeps lingering ♫
♫ I kept wanting to listen to your shy voice ♫
♫ Do you know anxious I feel? ♫
♫ As if today is the last day, ♫
♫ I will come to you day by day ♫
♫ It's strange how we met ♫
♫ How did we fall in love at first sight? ♫
[Dali and the Cocky Prince]
~ Preview ~
I wonder if she's eaten today?
Isn't there something like that? All of a sudden?
[I like you, Dali.]
What should I do for you?
Isn't something weird?
The collaborator's attitude did a 180 degree turn.
Just who was it...
Is this how you manage works of art?
Didn't you say this was priceless work of art?!
♫ Because my heart is set only on you ♫