(For a higher leap, )
(Woo Sang Hyeok is here!)
(Today's theme is people born in the Year of the Snake.)
(Jeon So Mi, Son Hyun Joo, Kim Woo Bin, So Ji Sub)
(Handsome Theme)
(Meet celebrities born in the Year of the Snake.)
(Do we have to search for them?)
(They must invite stars born in the Year of the Snake.)
(Is this possible?)
(Of course.)
(It's definitely possible.)
(From Kim Woo Bin born in 1989...)
(to Rhymer born in 1977)
(Can we go see you?)
(Team Handsome invites people easily.)
(It'd be great to meet Dae Hwi as well.)
(From the same agency)
(They get a chance to win two squares at once.)
(Rhymer born in 1977)
(Lee Dae Hwi born in 2001)
(I was born in early 2001.)
(Wasn't I born in the Year of the Dragon?)
What?
(Things don't go the way they expected.)
(I've lived my whole life as the Snake.)
(In the midst of controversy about being fake Snake)
(Someone born in the Year of the Snake appears.)
(My greetings in the Year of the Snake)
(This is Jun Hyo Seong.)
(She's really born in the Year of the Snake.)
(She has blind faith in tarot reading.)
(Thanks to Fanatic Hyo Seong, )
(Team Guys ties the score.)
(Team Handsome's weapon that remains)
(Kim Woo Bin born in 1989)
(Yi Kyung and Woo Bin are friends.)
You told me earlier...
(Woo Bin lied to be on Tae Hyun's side.)
(Could you bet on yourself?)
(With Kim Woo Bin, )
(their Handsome Race resumes.)
It'd be amazing if you could answer it.
If Woo Bin answers it...
- We should answer it together.
- Right.
- Here's the quiz.
- Please.
Until the 1980s,
this was possible with restrictions.
As the size of the Korean economy increased,
and the standard of living improved,
restrictions were removed...
starting from January 1, 1989.
What could this be?
- In 1989?
- Yes.
All restrictions were removed?
Yes.
- You don't know, do you?
- Not at all.
(I have no idea.)
Could it be curfew?
In 1989?
(No more curfew?)
Wasn't there a curfew until then?
I was in elementary school then.
When you were in middle school...
- Were you in high school?
- Curfew...
- Were you in college in 1989?
- in 1989?
- Were you in college?
- I was in middle school.
I was probably...
- in seventh grade.
- Was there any curfew?
I don't think there was a curfew.
Could it be no restrictions on hairstyle?
(Will you keep cornering me like that?)
It can't be about hairstyle.
When I was in middle school,
I was required to cut my hair short.
It can't be removing restrictions on hairstyle.
- I also had to get a buzz cut.
- Right.
When I was in middle school,
- there were hairstyle restrictions.
- Right.
That can't be the answer.
- I have an idea.
- What?
Removing all restrictions on traveling abroad.
Removing restrictions on traveling abroad in 1989?
Wasn't it done earlier?
That's possible.
How about this one?
The use of imported goods.
Weren't there restrictions on buying imported cars or home appliances?
Since then, were all restrictions removed?
On buying goods from abroad?
Isn't that the answer?
Without multiple choices...
Instead of your suggestion,
isn't removing restrictions from traveling abroad better?
- It's because...
- Unless it was a business trip...
Traveling abroad was limited...
to business purposes.
- Right.
- We had to get permission.
- I think it's correct.
- Here's why.
The Seoul Summer Games were in 1988.
Since the 1988 Seoul Summer Games,
- Korea started to develop.
- That's true.
It seems like after the Seoul Summer Games,
all restrictions were removed...
I think it's traveling abroad.
- Right? Traveling abroad is right.
- Traveling abroad?
Don't you think so?
We should trust his snake energy.
- Okay.
- Let's do it.
What Rhymer said was wrong, and he was born in 1977.
He was totally wrong.
(Rhymer born in 1977 said the wrong answer.)
I have a good feeling about it.
Let's go with traveling abroad.
- Here's the answer.
- I'd like to get one right.
Okay.
- Answer.
- The answer is traveling abroad.
(Traveling abroad)
- Please.
- All restrictions were removed...
since January 1, 1989.
Traveling abroad?
No way.
Traveling abroad.
That's correct.
(This is exciting.)
- Amazing.
- That's amazing.
This is really amazing.
Listen.
Let me explain why this is amazing.
We have a reattempt card, but we answered it correctly...
for the first time without using it.
Traveling abroad had restrictions until the early 1980s.
After that, anyone could travel abroad.
The year 1989 seems much later than I thought.
That's fascinating.
In the past, there was curfew.
- Right.
- This is incredible.
- I can't believe it.
- This is amazing.
- Woo Bin, this is amazing.
- Seriously.
- It was a hard question.
- You did it as fast as possible.
Find someone born in 1953.
Once we get that, we win.
(With the correct answer with a man born in 1989)
(They're short on one square before completing the bingo.)
- It's kimchi stew.
- That sounds good.
We can eat kimchi stew.
- That's substantial.
- Do they decide your menu?
Let's give him a fortune cookie.
Please pick a fortune cookie.
Try it.
Do I just pick one?
Yes, pick one.
And break it.
(Checking his fortune with a fortune cookie)
- Something should be inside.
- Shall I break it?
- You can eat it.
- It's edible.
"Your luck increases by being with someone who helps you."
"The one who helps you is wearing yellow."
"Always look around carefully."
(Yellow?)
(Where is yellow?)
(I'd like to be someone who helps him.)
I'm not wearing yellow.
Are you wearing yellow?
(Oh, right!)
Hey, that's not true.
Hold on.
We brought something yellow.
Did you bring that?
- We brought something yellow.
- This is accurate.
- Hey.
- We brought something yellow.
We brought something yellow.
- All of them are yellow.
- All of them.
- We brought egg tarts.
- All egg tarts are yellow.
All of them are yellow.
This is great.
- This is good.
- We're here to help.
- Gosh.
- We bought some help.
Exactly. This is unbelievable.
- Yes.
Woo Bin is the best.
(1989, Male)
(It's time for Woo Bin to go to work.)
- Can I take a photo with you?
- Sure.
- I want to tell Sang Uk...
- Goodness.
(He can't miss a selfie with Woo Bin.)
Thank you.
- Take one with Sang Hyeok.
- Can you take our photo?
I'll take it for you.
(Tossing it naturally)
Sure.
You're too close. Why is it so close?
One, two, three. Okay.
Let's go.
- Is it zoomed in?
- Yes.
Yes.
- See you, Woo Bin.
- Bye.
- Goodbye. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(While Team Handsome won their second square)
(Team Guys)
(Thanks to Hyo Seong, they won a precious square.)
There's no solution.
(They don't have anyone to meet anymore.)
(The other team won two squares.)
We have no chance of winning today.
We should play as much as possible.
- I'll search through my contacts...
- Yi Kyung.
I got a message from Cha Jun Hwan.
He was born in 2001.
Do you know him or his friend?
- I messaged him earlier.
- Gosh.
I am...
- Both of you are national athletes.
- I know him through my friends.
He definitely has dohwasal.
He messaged me back right away.
Can you explain the situation to him?
Or ask for his number. Calling would be the best.
Okay, I'll respond right away.
It'd be amazing if we could meet Cha Jun Hwan.
If we get someone...
born in 2001 and 2013, we'd complete the bingo.
If we find someone born in 2001,
the other team will be in a hurry.
(The tables may turn.)
It's the New Year. We should have some dumpling soup with rice cake.
Let's move.
Geumnam Market.
- Hello.
Sir, can we get three orders of dumpling soup with rice cake?
- Welcome.
- Here's the menu.
You want to order more?
- Sure.
- The side dishes...
You both eat a lot.
Did we leave our board?
(Seung Ho starts to analyze the menu.)
Just concentrate on him for the year 2001.
I'll find someone born in 2013.
He responded as soon as I messaged him,
but I responded so late.
(Feeling bad)
I was busy doing something else.
We had no choice.
Pyeonyuk sounds delicious.
Pyeonyuk...
(Naturally bringing up pyeonyuk)
Two orders of pyeonuk and...
How about one bibim naengmyeon?
Then three...
We already ordered three dumpling soup with rice cake.
We're 3, but you want 6 orders?
Three people... What?
One person gets dumpling soup with rice cake with pyeonuk.
That's enough food for one person.
- But he wants to order two...
- Dumpling soup with rice cake...
and pyeonuk are for one person.
Aren't we going to search those born in the Year of the Snake?
- Year of the Snake...
- Go ahead and order.
We'll just order quickly.
- A regular size.
- One regular bibim naengmyeon?
Thank you.
Shall we search now?
(I'll search for those born in the Year of the Snake.)
A figure skater on the national team...
Male born in 1989.
There is no way out.
It can't be helped.
We have no chance.
(Now, they're faced with the bingo crisis.)
A celebrity born in 2013...
(Food to comfort them arrives.)
- What's this?
- Wrap it.
Okay.
(Here is light pyeonuk.)
(Chewy)
It's homemade kimchi.
(Salivating)
(Shall we try the pyeonuk?)
(However, Yi Kyung isn't interested.)
Which celebrities were born in 2013?
I'm thinking of calling their agency.
Is that what you were thinking about?
I can't find celebrities born in 2013. Who are they?
Let's search for those born in the Year of the Snake.
(They postpone their eating.)
- Gosh, it's served already.
- Thank you.
I like how fast it is.
(Bibim naengmyeon)
It has the vibe of a market.
(Mixing without hesitating)
It smells really good.
(The appetizing smell of savory sesame oil)
It looks very chewy.
(It truly looks appetizing.)
Yi Kyung, please eat.
(He doesn't move.)
Have a bite.
No, you guys go ahead.
- Thank you.
- I'll keep searching.
(Starting with pyeonuk)
We need to narrow it down.
Where should we go?
(Wrapping it neatly with kimchi and taking a bite)
(Humming)
(Seung Ho also takes a bite of the pyeonuk.)
By the way, it's delicious.
How can kimchi be...
(In awe with the homemade kimchi)
this excellent?
(He's still searching.)
(Glancing)
(They're starting to be tactless.)
Do you know any...
(His true feeling explodes.)
(Try bibim naengmyeon.)
(Okay)
(Taking a bite of bibim naengmyeon carefully)
(While the two younger members devour bibim naengmyeon quietly, )
(he's strictly searching those born in the Year of the Snake.)
- Hello, Yi Kyung.
- Sir, we're shooting right now.
- Yes?
- In the entertainment industry,
do you know anyone...
who was born in 2013?
Can you call their agency?
An actor born in 2013? How old is he this year?
Would he be 12?
- In 6th grade.
- He's 13.
- Or 12...
(Sighing)
He'd be around that age.
I'll look it up and call you back.
- Okay.
- Bye.
I even called the CEO of an agency.
They only need to find someone born in 1953.
After realizing that, I gave up for a while.
I'll get back on my feet after eating this.
If we lose again, then the three of us will lose...
for two consecutive weeks.
(Losing 2 consecutive weeks with the same team)
(Feeling guilty)
Still, we were happy.
(Staying mentally strong)
You guys are...
more optimistic than I thought.
(We will destroy them after eating.)
- Your dumpling soup with rice cake.
- Thank you.
- That was served so fast.
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
- It's faster than microwaving it.
(Dumpling soup with rice cake you must have for the New Year)
(Hot)
You need to try this.
- Okay.
- Try a piece of pyeonuk.
What kind of place is this?
- Yi Kyung, it's amazing.
- Thank you.
I like eating, too.
It's because...
It's delicious, but...
(He's searching again.)
Short track speed skater, Lee Yu Bin.
She was born in 2001.
(Lee Yu Bin, a short track speed skater born in 2001)
Really?
If I can't get a hold of him, I'll call her right away.
Do you know her?
She's on YouTube with Yoon Gy all the time.
Really?
I searched for her before, but she didn't come up.
(She didn't come up before.)
(He eats some dumpling soup with rice cake first.)
How can kimchi be this excellent?
(He's searching again.)
For the actor born in 2013, I got his mother's number.
Isn't it bingo once we find...
- someone born in 2001?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- It's possible.
Mister.
Yes?
- Isn't it delicious? Yes.
- Is it delicious?
Mister.
(The dumpling soup with rice cake is delicious here.)
(Yi Kyung calls her right away.)
Hello?
Hello, you must be Jae Min's mother.
- This is Actor Lee Yi Kyung.
- Yes.
Hello.
Let me briefly explain the situation.
- Could we talk for a minute?
- Yes.
We're visiting celebrities born in the Year of the Snake.
We wish them Happy New Year and give them presents.
I see.
Was Jae Min born in the Year of the Snake?
That's right.
- He was born in 2013.
- Yes.
Would it be possible to meet him today?
- One moment, please.
- Sure.
She sounds very calm.
It's Lee Yi Kyung on the phone.
Why aren't you eating your dumplings?
I didn't have a chance to eat it.
- Do you want some?
- No.
Seeing you not eating...
- Here you go.
- Seeing you not eating...
Have one more.
Then I'll eat it.
(Gosh, then I'll eat it.)
Have one more.
Goodness.
(Mother Bird Yi Kyung takes care of the younger ones.)
(Huge)
(Eating without hesitating)
(He adds kimchi to it and stuffs himself.)
(Humming)
All right. It's possible.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Yes.
Okay, we'll come around 4pm.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Okay.
(Today's schedule: Lunch at 2pm, Meeting with the actor at 4pm)
We can go there right after eating.
I can finally eat. Goodness.
- Bibim naengmyeon...
- Without knowing where to go,
I don't know how you could eat so much.
(I respect you for eating without caring.)
Can you eat without knowing where to go next?
- That was delicious.
- We can't do anything when hungry.
(They pretend not to hear him.)
Don't give up on Cha Jun Hwan.
- He's supposed to contact you.
- For now,
- I got her number.
- Cha Jun Hwan's number?
- No, Lee Yu Bin's.
- Then call her now.
- What do I say?
- What do you say?
- What time should we meet her?
- Don't you know what we're doing?
What time should we meet her?
Around 6pm would be good.
Ask her where she lives. I mean...
(He calls her rapidly before he gets scolded more.)
Say that you're Oh Sang Uk.
Tell her politely...
that you have a lot of dohwasal.
(Laughing)
Good job.
- Hello?
- Hello.
This is Fencer Oh Sang Uk.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- Yes?
- We're shooting a variety show.
You were born in the Year of the Snake.
Yes.
Why is he stating the obvious?
(Laughing)
Do you like presents?
Of course I do.
When is your training today?
I don't have any training in the afternoon,
but I still have to work out.
What time do you finish?
It's up to me to decide.
Hello, this is Actor Lee Yi Kyung.
Hello.
Thank you for listening to him ramble.
- Sure.
- By the way,
could we meet you at 6pm?
Yes, that works.
Does that work for you?
Yes, it works.
Gosh, thank you so much.
We'll see you there around 6pm. If there's any change,
we'll let you know in advance.
- Okay, see you soon.
- Thank you.
You should lead the conversation like this.
Talking out of the blue...
That's how athletes talk.
"Can you do it or not?"
(Getting straight to the point)
Isn't it your first time calling her?
- I'm glad.
- You know what's funny?
Let's go to karaoke or coin karaoke.
- Finish those 30 minutes.
- That sounds good.
After meeting Jae Min,
we'll meet Yu Bin right away.
That's it for today.
- We got it planned out.
- The game is set.
How could we find anyone born in 2013? That's ridiculous.
(They still have a chance to complete the bingo.)
(Team Handsome)
(Home-style Korean food restaurant)
- Over here.
- Shall we sit like this?
Order something.
Don't we just need kimchi stew?
No, we need protein.
I'm fine, but Sang Hyeok...
We need some salted mackerel.
Order whatever you want. We don't mind.
There are pork cutlet and steamed eggs.
Pork cutlet doesn't go well with kimchi stew.
- How about rolled omelet?
- That sounds good.
- That's good with kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew, rolled omelet,
- and mackerel. Those three?
- That sounds good.
- Order them.
- You don't like bulgogi?
Goodness.
Just in case.
We have good teamwork today.
Thanks to someone old,
he knows about restrictions on traveling abroad.
Thanks to someone young,
Google Woo finds everything.
What's "Google Woo?"
(What's "Google Woo?")
(Did you ask what Google Woo is?)
(Whenever the members have questions)
(Searching)
(He got the list in an instant.)
(Google Woo, tell me how to get there.)
It came up.
- Is it in Apgujeong?
- Yes.
(Google Woo found the route.)
What's this? Is it chocolate?
I think that's apple cinnamon.
How do you know? How did you find out?
- I saw the photo.
- Google Woo is amazing.
(Google Woo is ready to search anytime.)
You call someone who's good at searching "Google."
Since he's Woo Sang Hyeok, he's Google Woo.
We have to explain to him because he's old.
(An old person)
He's old.
Jun Hyun Moo called me back right now.
(Hyun Moo?)
(They try calling him.)
- Hello, Dong Hyun.
- Hello, Hyun Moo.
- Gosh.
- Happy New Year.
Happy New Year to you too. I need to box.
You should come to box.
You only asked without ever coming.
(Please come starting this year.)
I apologize for sending you a text message...
suddenly and early in the morning.
It's okay. Why are you being so polite?
It's because we're on TV.
Hyun Moo, this is Tae Hyun.
- Gosh, Tae Hyun.
- Goodness.
From the way you were speaking, I knew you were being filmed.
(From the way you were speaking, I knew you were being filmed.)
Today, we have to find celebrities born in the Year of the Snake.
We get their fortunes read.
- I'd like that.
- By the way,
we didn't think you'd be available due to a shoot.
We contacted Rhymer...
and finished what we had to do.
- We already met...
- Yes?
A male born in 1977.
The time I was born must be different.
I mean...
We'll have your fortune read.
Could you send...
your information to Dong Hyun?
- Then I should call my mom.
- Okay.
Do you have Tae Jin Ah's phone number?
I probably have his old phone number.
Could you send that to Dong Hyun?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Hyun Moo. It's okay.
- I'm sorry for missing your call.
You must come to the gym. It's New Year 2025.
The way you're talking makes me want to vomit.
This is how I usually talk.
- All right.
- Okay, Hyun Moo.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
(Kimchi stew is served at the right time.)
You'll get one each, so please wait.
It looks amazing.
(The taste you never get tired of every time you eat it)
(Comfort food for Koreans, spicy kimchi stew)
(And what complements kimchi stew)
(Pan-fry the egg mixture until it turns golden.)
(Soft and moist rolled omelet)
(Protein for Sang Hyeok picked by Dong Hyun)
(Grilled mackerel that's light and whets the appetite)
- Enjoy your meal.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(Goodness)
It goes well with rice.
(It goes well with rice.)
It's a tasty restaurant.
In that case...
(Sang Hyeok takes a big bite of his meal ordered by Dong Hyun.)
- Can we order more mackerel?
- I'll give you more.
I'm okay, but Sang Hyeok...
I'm okay.
You always do that.
You're going to eat it anyway.
I'm okay, but athletes need protein.
Right.
(Eating eggs to supplement on protein)
(They nourish themselves in their own ways.)
For now...
It's delicious.
Did Hyun Moo send you the number?
(How about Tae Jin Ah's phone number?)
Didn't he say...
that he knows Tae Jin Ah's number?
(Once they meet Tae Jin Ah, they can complete the bingo.)
(Chuckling)
"I don't have his number."
(I'm sorry.)
(Feeling bitter)
Didn't you say that you can contact everyone through their friends?
(His dream of leaving work on time disappears.)
- Let's go. We don't have time.
- Okay.
Do you want one more egg tart?
You want to eat more?
- Isn't there any in the car?
- There is.
- No, there isn't.
- We finished it.
We did?
- Of course.
- Egg tarts...
(The members are searching again...)
(for those born in the Year of the Snake.)
It's 3pm right now.
What time will we get there?
(Tae Hyun gets a phone call.)
- Hello, Tae Hyun.
- CEO Rhymer.
Hello.
We'll get there in about 20 minutes.
- Okay.
- We're on our way.
Okay.
Things are going so smoothly.
(Why are they seeing Rhymer again?)
(Today morning)
(Rhymer invited Dae Hwi born in 2001.)
(Dae Hwi claims to have lived as the Snake.)
(It turns out...)
(that he was born in the Year of the Dragon.)
(They got information on someone else born in 2001.)
(We'll reserve him.)
Here we go.
(That's why they're going back to CEO Rhymer's office.)
Who has that card?
"By taking photos of any of the members with the characters,"
"complete the phrase."
"Year of the Snake" and "Happy New Year."
- We need to find these, too.
- Yes.
(We will find them.)
(Wide-eyed)
There is "Happy New Year."
- Where? Take a photo.
- Over there.
- It's over there.
- That's amazing.
It's over there.
- It's over there.
- Where?
New Year Greetings.
Gosh, you're amazing.
(Google Woo's strange searching ability)
That's amazing.
(I can't believe things are going so smoothly.)
Did you take a photo?
Sang Hyeok is amazing.
We got it.
Okay.
It's right here.
(How did he spot that?)
Unbelievable.
(This card will become powerless soon.)
That's impressive.
Now,
we only need "Year of the Snake" and "Handsome Guys."
(Wishing happy new year card's current status)
(With)
(Happy New Year)
(Soon, they arrive at a familiar place.)
We're here.
- Let's go.
(When Team Handsome arrives to meet someone born in 2001)
(Team Guys)
They definitely won't stay still.
They don't have to clear any missions today.
They have to take selfies.
If I were them...
(If I were them...)
I'd have gone to an Internet cafe.
- And?
- I'd have printed it.
The written phrase.
(Print the written phrase)
That's probably not allowed.
I'd have insisted.
There are no such rules.
(Insistent)
That only works for you.
It is...
one of your strengths.
Still, that's rude.
As an entertainer...
- We're on the signboard.
- Right.
I saw it on my way here.
On Handsome Guys...
My dream was having my photo up there.
- There's a signboard.
- What?
(Really?)
(I should save this.)
- I took a photo of it.
- You did?
I should send it to our group chat room.
Don't send it yet.
They're good with directions, and they know where it is.
Even I would recognize it.
How could you think of sending it to our group chat room?
You're rude too.
You were being rude to our team.
(They pass the Han River with two rude members.)
(Soon, they arrive at the next location.)
(Karaoke)
We just need to fill the time.
(30-minute karaoke time card)
Let's get off work on time today.
("Leave Work on Time" by Lee Yi Kyung)
Please.
Our team can't lose again.
Please, let our team...
(I want to leave work)
(I hate working overtime)
(I really want to leave work on time)
(We can't lose 2 weeks in a row.)
(I agree.)
Let's leave work on time today.
I like this song.
It's offensive to hear it when you're losing.
Let's leave work on time today.
("I Am Firefly" by LUNCH)
Sang Uk is a good singer.
(He's good at singing.)
(It pangs the listener's heart.)
(The husky voice of a fencer on the national team)
("Confession" by Deli Spice)
I love it.
- However - I love your voice.
- I'm sorry - Seung Ho!
Deep in my heart
- This is great.
- Someone else
He has a great voice.
His tone is wonderful.
He's also a gangster.
(He's also a gangster.)
He was a gangster when he was acting.
(Great tone, acting, and facial expressions)
His tone is wonderful.
(Shin Seung Ho, 29 years old)
Even if we lose, let's enjoy ourselves.
(Even if we lose, let's enjoy ourselves.)
How many minutes do we have?
We have time to sing one more.
This isn't easy. When taking a nap for 30 minutes,
- Right.
- you don't have to move.
Do you know this song?
It has high notes.
- DK?
- Gosh.
(He set up the microphone stand.)
- Here he is.
- Thank you.
(He turns into a singer.)
This will increase his dohwasal.
Dohwasal.
(His dohwasal is on.)
("H.E.Art" by DK)
(Feeling pleased and proud of him)
All right.
- Let's go, Sang Uk.
- Yes.
(The emotional and high chorus is the highlight.)
Thirty minutes are up.
(Singing)
It just ended.
- It's been exactly 30 minutes.
- Gosh.
- We have to go and meet him.
- Let's go.
- We have to go.
(Team Handsome)
Three weeks ago,
he got over ten million views.
- Ten million views?
- Only...
we didn't know.
He must be very famous.
(Reading about the one born in 2001 before meeting him)
These guys are incredible.
(Appearing while expressing disgust)
What's wrong?
Goodness.
- Again...
- Seriously.
We're changing places in the office...
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
Thank you, and I'm sorry.
Here's our main guest.
I brought the one born in the Year of the Snake.
He's our savior...
and our treasure.
It's EUNHO born in 2001.
- Yes.
- Hello.
(The year of 2001)
(Handsome Snake 4)
(EUNHO, Rhymer's treasure)
Please say hello to the camera.
Yes, EUNHO.
Hello, I'm the main vocalist of YOUNITE.
I'm EUNHO. Nice to meet you.
He's the main vocalist?
(His dancing is both powerful and soft.)
(Outstanding singing skills as the main vocalist)
(Charming in every way)
(The leader of YOUNITE)
He's the main vocalist?
- Right.
- The main vocalist?
- Isn't he the leader?
- He is the leader,
main vocalist, and the eldest.
He's the eldest with his amazing looks.
(Feeling shy)
You're quite young.
Have you gotten your fortune read?
Yes, recently in the dormitory with my mobile phone.
You've never gotten your fortune read by a fortune-teller?
No, I haven't.
Today, we're traveling...
- with one.
- Really?
A real fortune-teller.
He's incredible.
- Would you like to try?
- Sure.
(Would you like to try?)
I brought someone who was actually born...
- in the Year of the Snake.
- He's real this time.
He's the real Snake.
He's the real Snake born in 2001.
- I'm real.
- He's the real Snake born in 2001.
I'm the real Snake.
If you tell me your birthday,
I'll read your fortune.
I was born...
on March 25, 2001.
In March? That's for sure.
I read your fortune.
Your fortune made me think of this.
If I have a child of my own in the future,
I hope that he'd have the same fortune.
(Listening intently)
There are three things.
First, you're ambitious.
- Right.
- You aren't lazy.
You have...
clear goals in mind.
Yes, that's true.
Second, you have many talents.
- Thank you.
- I'm serious.
Usually, talents are called...
dohwa.
In your case, your dohwa is...
attracting fans.
You know how to make people side with you.
I didn't know such things existed in fortune-telling.
(Listening carefully)
Third, many people help you in life.
- I see.
- Many people help you.
(Am I one of them?)
Is CEO Rhymer one of them who will help him?
What's the compatibility between me and him?
- Our compatibility...
- They have to be compatible.
If not, he should change the agency.
I mean,
you seem compatible.
Here's why.
He harbors a lot of fire,
- and fire is what you need.
- Right.
In that sense, you are compatible.
He can be of help to you.
However, in your boss' case...
In Rhymer's case, you...
Well, it's good.
- What's wrong?
- It's a good relationship...
since EUNHO will make money for him.
(He's the pot of honey and Employee of the Year.)
- Good money?
- Right.
They'll create a much-needed flow.
You've only be telling us the good things.
Is there anything we should be wary about?
This year?
I think...
the year 2024 wasn't that good for EUNHO.
Is that so?
- I think so.
- In 2024...
A lot happened in 2024.
- It was a tough year for him.
- Right.
If 2024 was a tough year, 2025 will be a year...
for you to do a lot of things...
that'll help you overcome it.
I see an upward trajectory in your path in 2026.
Can't he get there sooner?
- You sound urgent.
- Right.
Taking too long to reach a certain level...
- won't be good for me.
- Right.
For EUNHO, it'll be May, June, July.
Can't he find luck in March?
- March?
- Be patient, Rhymer.
It'll happen in May.
March isn't a bad month for him, but...
- What about late March?
- Well...
(He's trying to decide when to release the album.)
- Hold on.
- Now,
you're a true believer of fortune telling.
You're asking him when to release the album.
- Please give him some good energy.
- Sure.
EUNHO, let's squeeze his hand.
- We'll take his hand.
- Unbelievable.
He said he didn't believe in fortune telling.
Now, they're true believers.
Please give us good energy.
(Late March will be good for us, right?)
Nice.
(Don't blindly believe.)
I feel like energy is being sucked out of me.
Here's your quiz.
(Time for Quiz)
I hope EUNHO...
- can answer this correctly.
- Exactly.
He's someone we consider as special.
(Will he help Team Handsome until the very end?)
The year 2001...
was the golden age of Korean movies with the number of tickets sold...
for Korean movies exceeding that for foreign movies.
- The year 2001?
- Yes.
The movie "My Sassy Girl..."
hit the theaters in 2001.
That was a great movie.
- Do you know the movie?
- Yes, I saw it.
What a relief.
How did you see it when you were born in 2001?
It's a masterpiece.
Thanks.
So did "Kick the Moon."
I saw them both.
- "Friend." - Yes, "Friend."
"My Wife Is a Gangster."
Line up the movies...
in the order of how well they did at the box office.
You'll know.
You were in one.
I only know how well my movie did.
You must've compared the scores.
Did "My Sassy Girl" sell over ten million tickets?
It didn't. I bet "Friend" did the best.
I remember "Friend" selling over seven million tickets.
"My Sassy Girl" sold about five million tickets.
- "Friend" definitely did better.
- Close to eight million.
It sold over seven million tickets.
What about "My Wife Is a Gangster?"
I remember...
that movie being the biggest hit at the time.
I don't trust him at all.
You saw how good I was earlier on.
(He said Jang Yun Jung entered the Campus Music Festival.)
(Incorrect)
(She must've entered the Riverside Song Festival.)
(He's quick to change his words.)
- I won't trust him.
- You saw me earlier.
(Distrust)
This is what I personally think.
First place, second place.
(1st place: "Friend," 2nd place: "Kick the Moon")
Third place, and fourth place.
For some reason, that's what I think.
"Kick the Moon..."
(Tae Hyun's guess)
This is tough.
Let's get the energy of the snake.
- Yes, EUNHO.
- What do you think?
Did you see all the movies?
The only movies I know...
- are "My Sassy Girl" and "Friend." - Right.
This is what I think.
First, second,
- third, and fourth.
- How?
- His answer is similar to mine.
- Really?
Here's what I think.
They're all famous,
but the movies that are still talked about are...
"My Sassy Girl" was a huge hit...
and "Friend" as well.
That's why there could be a complete twist...
with "My Wife Is a Gangster" in first place.
- He...
- No?
(Quiz roadblock, be quiet.)
I'd trust you if I had just met you.
But what happened yesterday...
(They were vaccinated the day before.)
I doubt that's it.
Which movie won awards at the year-end award ceremony?
"Friend," of course.
- Then that's in first place.
- "Friend" dominated.
What about your movie?
We were both rookies,
so we took home Best Rookie Actor and Actress.
Even though we get it wrong, it'd be nice for Tae Hyun to put...
- "My Sassy Girl" in second place.
- Right.
- I...
- Tae Hyun.
I think "Kick the Moon" was tough to beat.
Sure. Decide on that, then.
Did "Kick the Moon" also win a lot of awards that year?
It was talked about a lot...
even for years to come.
- Do you want to trust me?
- We should.
We'll decide on that.
- Okay.
- Okay, good.
Please name the movies in order.
- "Friend." - "Friend."
- "Kick the Moon." - In second place.
"My Sassy Girl" and then "My Wife Is a Gangster."
The order you gave me...
(Was it the correct answer?)
is incorrect.
("Friend," "Kick the Moon,")
("My Sassy Girl," "My Wife Is a Gangster")
That was too tough to answer.
It was tougher than a short-answer question.
How can one guess the correct order?
(Acting weird from the shock of getting it wrong)
- What's the correct answer then?
- We could get it right...
We could get it right if you told us what came last.
Should we spend ours together?
- We should.
- Of course.
When will we get this chance again?
Let this be the last time we team up.
Hold on. But I want to be on your team again.
Let's be teammates again.
No. There will be no other chance.
Let's get this over with.
Come on. We need to cash this in.
We can't afford to get this wrong.
(Reattempt card: You may try again after receiving a clue.)
Here's your clue. I'll tell you what you got right.
- Really?
- Here you go.
It'll still be tough.
You were right about "Friend..."
- being in first place.
- Okay.
"My Wife Is a Gangster..."
is in fourth place.
We only have to swap those two.
EUNHO and I were right!
Why did you look down on your own movie like that?
Unbelievable.
I guess it's my fault.
EUNHO was right.
(I didn't think too much about my own movie.)
- EUNHO, you say it.
- Sure.
- EUNHO will say it.
- You'll get another chance...
to answer it.
(What a bummer.)
- He got it right.
- EUNHO was right.
Name the four movies in the correct order...
according to how well it did at the box office.
"Friend" is in first place. "My Sassy Girl" is in second.
"Kick the Moon" is in third place...
and "My Wife Is a Gangster" is in fourth place.
That is correct.
- EUNHO was right all along.
- EUNHO was right.
If only we had gotten it right without using the reattempt card.
Something happens to me every time I'm at Brand New Music.
- I can't believe I couldn't get it.
- Goodness.
If we had listened to him...
EUNHO, you're a man...
- Thanks.
- of luck this year.
Anyway, good job, everyone.
- Good job.
- Thanks. EUNHO, thank you.
It was my pleasure.
All right.
- Let's go!
Go, EUNHO.
(1989: Female, 1977: Male, 1989: Male)
(Year 2001)
(Team Guys)
(On their way to meet someone born in 2013)
(Cuckoo)
Year 2001.
- Year 2001?
(Startled)
- Year 2001.
(They needed that square in order to complete a line.)
Who was born in 2001?
It's about occupying more squares now.
I should give her a call.
(He immediately calls Lee Yu Bin.)
- Hello?
Yu Bin, I'm so sorry.
- It's all right.
- We can't occupy the square...
on the bingo board...
once our opponent takes it.
It's all right.
- Just a second.
- Sure.
Yu Bin, hi.
I wasn't able to greet you earlier.
I'm actor Shin Seung Ho.
Hello.
Right. I'm so sorry about this.
It's all right.
Hang in there.
I'll be rooting for you.
Gosh, thanks. I think we already lost,
but we'll keep up the spirit to honor your words.
Happy New Year.
Beware of any injuries and stay strong.
I'll be rooting for you.
- Thanks for that.
- Thank you.
I promise to treat you to something delicious.
Sure thing.
I feel guilty for doing this.
(It wasn't enough, but they deliver their apology.)
The game isn't over yet. We're here to see Hong Jae Min...
and his mother.
They're here.
- Really?
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hello, ma'am.
How about a fist bump?
- Hi.
- He's adorable.
- Let's greet the mother.
- Hello.
- Hello, ma'am.
Thank you for sparing your time for us.
- I'm Oh Sang Uk.
- It's good to see you.
Didn't you think we were scammers?
I recognized the friendly voice immediately.
- My voice?
- Yes.
Anyway, we apologize for asking you here...
- out of the blue.
- First...
- Jae Min, will you sit here?
- Okay.
(He shyly takes a seat.)
Hello.
I'm a child actor,
Hong Jae Min, and I'm 12 years old.
Nice to meet you, Jae Min.
(Adorable)
You're curious about what's going on, aren't you?
- Yes.
- Well.
- You know bingo, right?
- Yes.
- This is you, Jae Min.
- Jae Min.
- Were you born in 2013?
- Yes.
In the Year of...
- In the Year of the Snake.
- That's right.
That's why we've come to see you.
I see.
(2013, The Year of the Black Snake)
(Handsome Snake 5: Cuteness overload, Hong Jae Min)
Can you tell us about the shows you have worked on?
"Under the Queen's Umbrella."
- "Under the Queen's Umbrella?" - The one with Kim Hye Soo.
An epic series, "KoreaKhitan War."
The one with Choi Soo Jong...
- and Kim Dong Jun.
- Yes.
A daily drama, "Meant to Be."
- You shot that too?
- Yes.
Hello, Brother.
(With a cute appearance that captivated online aunties...)
(and great acting skills, )
(Jae Min has starred in many big dramas.)
You've done a lot.
- He did more big ones than us.
- That's right.
- He was in masterpieces.
- Right.
(The two actors cringe.)
(Smiling)
Jae Min, do you know...
who we are?
Can you say who we are one by one?
(Well...)
Don't be nervous. It's okay not to know us.
- Lee Yi Kyung.
And...
I think I saw you in "Alchemy of Souls."
- You're right.
- "Alchemy of Souls?"
You're right.
- And...
- What about him?
(Hesitating)
(Thinking)
- What does he do?
- What do I do?
What do you think his job is?
I think he's an actor.
How did you know?
(Mischievous uncle)
I thought so because you were with other actors.
I'm an actor.
(I'm playing the role of a handsome actor in Handsome Guys.)
The guy over here...
- is Oh Sang Uk.
- Okay.
Of the sports,
do you know fencing where they fight with the swords...
- like D'Artagnan?
- Yes.
He is the number one in fencing in the world.
(Surprised)
I'm an athlete, a fencer.
(Amazed)
- You're surprised to see a fencer.
- Yes.
He's number one on the planet.
Momentarily. It's only for a moment.
Momentarily.
I think you're nervous.
- You're sweating.
- Is he sweating?
Goodness.
- Do you want a glass of water?
- Yes.
Okay. I know it's nervous.
You can take the jacket off.
- Give it to me.
- Okay.
- Good.
(Wiping)
They are the actors...
- with more experience.
- Yes.
Is there anything you want to ask them?
- There is.
- Is there?
What?
- You can ask us anything.
- Okay.
I get nervous when I'm shooting.
I want to know how you relax yourselves.
(How do you relax yourselves?)
I've never had this question before.
When I was about your age,
I started playing soccer as a soccer player.
I was nervous back then, and I'm nervous when I act today.
This is the method I use.
When I get nervous,
I think it's a matter of course that I get nervous.
The nervousness I'm feeling...
Is it too hard to understand?
That was awful, wasn't it?
No.
It sounded awful to me too.
(Joining in)
I need to answer so you can understand.
It's hard.
- As for me, - Yes.
I don't really get nervous.
- But in a nervous situation, - Yes.
I appreciate it.
(I see.)
I think his answer was more awful than mine.
(Embarrassed for some reason)
They were all good answers.
(Sorry. The uncles must have been nervous.)
Jae Min already...
has a good attitude.
Exactly.
Is there anything that worries you recently?
It doesn't have to be about acting.
(Thinking)
I want to lose weight.
(Eating a cookie)
(Halting)
Why? Did someone say something?
- No, that's not it.
- I see.
To continue acting in the future,
I want to do it after losing weight.
At your age, you shouldn't...
be stressed about weight.
- He shouldn't.
- You won't get tall.
With a lack of nutrition, you won't get tall.
Look at him. He's still eating.
He is...
How tall were you? Was it 190-something?
- It's 192.
- He's 192cm tall.
(He's tall!)
You have to eat a lot now to be tall.
Like Yi Kyung said, now,
you have to listen to your mom and eat everything you want.
- You look adorable right now.
- Okay.
When I was in a higher grade in elementary school,
(While the experienced actors consult him, )
I was really fat.
(he takes a bite.)
(Another bite)
(Sang Uk shows how to be tall himself.)
I think it'll be all right.
Well...
Stop eating.
(Me?)
- No.
- You can eat, Jae Min.
I was talking about this.
I was talking to Sang Uk. You can keep eating, Jae Min.
They are all yours.
(Chewing)
You can take your time. I'll read the question slowly.
I was...
We're at a good spot.
(Team Handsome)
I know that area through and through.
(They're heading to Dong Hyun's gym to meet the next Snake.)
It's garosu-gil.
(Touching)
- Su Jin.
- Yes?
- Are you home?
- Yes.
When do you go to study?
- Before 6:30pm.
- I see.
Can you...
check if there's a calendar for the year 2025?
A 2025 calendar?
(Why is he asking for a calendar all of a sudden?)
We have one.
On that calendar,
does it say, "The Year of The Blue Snake?"
"The Year of The Blue Snake?"
If so, what do I do?
If so, I'll go and pick it up.
Hold on.
- It's okay if it doesn't say it.
- I found it!
- What?
- The Year of the Blue Snake.
It's in Chinese characters.
- It's in Chinese characters?
- Yes.
- In Chinese characters.
It might not be okay. It should be in Korean.
Okay. It might not work if it's in Chinese characters.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Sorry.
(Unfortunately, he has to end the call.)
That's... No.
Tae Hyun, I'm sure...
Will they say something about it? Right. It was written there.
It wasn't in Chinese characters.
You're right.
I hate when they complain when I'm done with it.
You've arrived at your destination.
(They arrive in front of Dong Hyun's gym.)
Real estate agencies usually have many calendars.
- Do they?
- Yes.
Should I go and ask?
- I know a guy there.
- The agents...
(Team Handsome goes the real estate agency by the gym.)
- Hello.
- Yes.
Do you have a calendar for the year 2025?
The 2025 calendar.
- That's it. It's over. Come.
- Why?
- You got it?
- Tae Hyun.
- Does it say, "Year?" - "Year."
- It says the Year of 2022.
- Year.
It's over.
- It's done.
- Thank you.
We got "Year."
(They're about to enter the gym.)
(Scanning)
Is it on the second floor?
Blue.
- Tae Hyun.
- Yes?
- I'll take another photo.
- Okay.
"Blue."
(He gets the "Blue" of the Year of the Blue Snake.)
We're getting it one by one.
(They enter Dong Hyun's gym while collecting letter by letter.)
Look at the shoes.
(Filled with the traces of the UFC-ranking Dong Hyun)
(It's Dong Hyun's gym on garosu-gil.)
- This is my gym.
- Okay.
It's where the fighters work out.
(Pushing down)
Wasn't it on the basement level?
We have tough training in the morning here.
We have a shower room, a resting area, and everything.
It's nice here.
It's a place they can enjoy freely.
As for us, we do...
(He sits on the workout equipment.)
this in the morning.
For example,
we ride this for a minute,
then we go off and do the other one.
Do it.
(The demo starts.)
(As he pedals faster, )
(the sound gets louder.)
And that is...
(Now that I showed them how to do it...)
- Me?
- Try it now.
Where is the wind coming from?
Do it faster.
Step it much harder so that it'll make noise.
- Harder. What's with the wind?
- Goodness.
Aim to reach 100rpm.
(He pedals hard until his hair flies.)
- Harder.
The sound is so weak.
Harder.
It's hard.
- You have to make that big noise.
- Manually.
(Sang Hyeok is the second one to try it.)
(Though he looks awkward, )
Good.
(it makes an incredible noise from start.)
Back and forth.
(The rpm keeps increasing.)
Good. Keep going.
Let's get the gold medal. Let's go.
Harder. A little more.
Let's go. Two.
You burnt 22kcal.
(Trainer Kim is satisfied.)
- Amazing.
- Are you okay?
- Was it hard?
- No.
- It wouldn't be hard for him.
What is that? Look.
- Is that for this?
- For pull-ups.
Amazing.
(I should demonstrate it for them.)
(Easy)
Gosh. This is like...
a playground for you.
It's my favorite playground.
(He does pull-ups in perfect posture.)
Gosh. I love it.
I'm feeling great all of a sudden.
I didn't work out today.
I love it.
You can do it after taking a short break.
Gosh. You can reach it?
(Showing an amazing height)
Be careful with your ring.
(Pull-ups 101)
You do many pull-ups.
I can tell by his posture.
- He does a lot of them.
- He's good.
I always have six packs.
(Amazed)
It's real muscle from training.
I can tell you do lots of pull-ups.
(A national athlete excels at everything.)
Actually, when Sang Hyeok is playing the game,
he has a certain look and pose before he runs.
He does this while smiling.
Why do you do this?
- Like this.
- He does this.
(Shaking)
(With a roaring cheer, )
(he does the well-known move.)
- Like this.
- My shoulder can't turn.
- Okay.
- It can't turn...
counterclockwise.
- You're holding it down?
- Right.
When I step and turn counterclockwise,
- Like this.
- then I'll fly away.
You mean you end up turning too much.
Because of our body structure,
with the torque after we run,
- our shoulders...
- Aren't you panting so hard?
If my shoulder turns...
You're out of breath.
- Aren't you panting so hard?
- If my shoulder turns...
- You end up like this.
- Yes.
When I do this,
my body remembers which way to go.
I can go higher vertically that way.
Exactly. You always do this before you run.
- Like this.
- Right.
- With a smile.
- Yes. There's something to it.
Now, you talked with us today.
- We solve a quiz here.
- Do you like quizzes?
- Do you want to do it together?
- Yes.
Okay. Good.
We'll solve a quiz with Jae Min today.
Give us the quiz.
In 2013, kimchi-making was selected as UNESCO's...
Masterpieces of the Oral and Intangible Heritage of Humanity.
It was the first time...
that Korean food culture to be selected for it.
The reason they chose kimchi-making, instead of kimchi,
because they viewed the significance of this highly.
What is this significance?
(The reason they chose kimchi-making, instead of kimchi, )
(because they take this significance highly. What is this?)
Kimchi-making is...
(Thinking hard)
Have you made kimchi before?
- I saw people making kimchi.
- You did.
(Unfamiliar)
I think...
(Uncle Seung Ho starts guessing first.)
Usually, we exchange labor of kimchi-making.
- I thought of it too.
- It's the concept of collaboration.
Or the process of aging it?
Fermentation?
That's more of...
Some kimchi...
doesn't require fermentation.
(Glancing)
Since we've been doing it for a long time,
it includes our national spirit, doesn't it?
He said the most plausible sentence among us.
(Demonstrating intelligence)
What are the criteria for becoming the UNESCO's Masterpieces...
of the Oral and Intangible Heritage of Humanity?
It must be something...
that shocks the world.
It's a dish we have at home...
and it's something we make together and share it.
Would they find that interesting?
That was what I was thinking.
In the foreigners' eyes,
(The other difference of kimchi-making is...)
Korean affection might be interesting.
(Korean affection?)
Korean affection? That makes sense.
It's about that relationship.
(Based on that relationship)
Family and collaboration.
I think it's about sharing too.
They all sound right to me.
- Right?
- It's hard.
I think we're on the same track.
In that case, kimchi-making is...
about everyone getting together to make kimchi.
They provide labor for one another.
And they share the kimchi.
They exchange and share love.
Did you hear that?
That was our answer.
- We're listening.
- He said it.
They found it amazing and valued highly of that act of kimchi-making.
That is why they chose it.
The very long answer you had...
(Nervous)
is correct.
Jae Min.
- Good job.
- Nicely done.
We got it, thanks to you.
Let's hold hands together.
The game will end soon.
(Chanting)
That's it.
Jae Min, will you put the seal here?
Jae Min has good energy.
(Jae Min puts on the sticker with his good energy.)
Two, three.
- Hong Jae Min.
- Good luck.
Do you know what a fortune cookie is?
- Yes.
- Good.
- Please pick one yourself.
- It's random.
You have to be careful because there might be an awful one.
Come on.
(Careful)
He picked carefully.
(Excited)
There's the paper.
"This year,"
"you can achieve everything..."
"in whatever challenge you put yourself up to."
"Don't hesitate. Just go for it."
You picked a good one among everything.
(Excited)
He was shy when he spoke to us.
But you have a really good vocal even though you're young.
Is there something you want to say?
In 2025, I hope all the viewers and actors...
will have nothing but happy moments.
I'll pray for it.
- Thank you.
- Gosh. Thank you.
Jae Min, good job.
- Well done. Seriously.
- Good job.
- Okay.
- We'll talk a bit here.
Okay.
- Jae Min, don't forget your jacket.
- Right.
- Yes.
- You'll get cold...
when the sweat cools down.
(Right. My jacket.)
- Bye.
- Thank you.
Okay. Thank you, Jae Min.
Okay. Good luck.
- Happy New Year.
- Good job.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- Happy New Year.
(Team Handsome)
Sang Hyeok, do you use something like this too?
- Me?
- This is something...
(Cuckoo)
Year 2013.
- Year 2013?
How did they find them?
Who was born in 2013?
They must have met with a child actor.
Year 2013?
(Puzzled)
It'll be a problem if we don't get it with Ho Il.
We're tied. We never know.
We can't let our guard down.
I've never let my guard down. We just got the question wrong.
(Sulky)
It isn't easy.
(At that moment...)
Hey.
(He's here.)
For goodness' sake.
- Hello.
- Gosh. Hi.
You've come to my humble place. Hello.
- Hello.
- Happy New Year.
- Gosh. Hello.
(He burst onto the music industry in the 1990s.)
(With a mega-hit of the 3rd album...)
("Very Old Couples" in 1992,)
(he established himself as the idol of the Generation X.)
(In 1993, with "Love of a New Generation,")
(he swept the end-of-year awards.)
(Three albums became million-sellers consecutively.)
(Jang Ho Il, the guitarist of 015B, the icon of the Generation X)
Hey. I have Ho Il's number.
- Hello?
- Ho Il.
(They reached Ho Il, who was born in 1965.)
If you're available today,
- we can meet up.
- Right.
I have an appointment, so until 3pm to 4pm,
- I can't go anywhere.
- Is that so?
It'd be easier for me to go there.
Really?
I'll text you the location.
Okay. For now, it's all right.
Hello.
I'm Jang Ho Il of 015B.
- Yes.
- He's our hope.
In the morning,
I didn't know I'd be here in the afternoon.
- Exactly.
- Where were you before this?
I was getting ready to go out for an appointment.
I suddenly got a call from him,
telling me to come in a hurry. So, here I am now,
- but I don't know what's going on.
- Right.
I think I called you like this...
- a few years ago.
- A couple of years ago.
A couple of years ago,
Tae Hyun was shooting for a drama.
He called me all out of the blue...
and asked me to be in the drama...
as a special guest.
I said I'd do it happily.
But the first thing he said was...
"But you'll die as soon as you appear."
(Shall we watch the scene together?)
In the first episode...
(Ho Il made an appearance in a drama...)
(as a guitarist of a popular band.)
(But in just 5 minutes after he made an appearance, )
(he faces a tragic end.)
- It was a sudden appearance...
- It was about two years ago.
And a sudden death.
- I got a sudden call again today.
- Right. Again today.
Then he told me to come to a gym.
"Is he going to treat me harshly again?"
- "Am I going to die again?" - I see.
(I won't hurt you.)
Recently, I shot a drama again.
Which one?
It's even hard for the actors...
- to find a job these days.
- I know.
- It's all thanks to...
- Did the acting back then...
- help you get it?
- Of course.
- It sparked everything.
- I'm glad to hear that.
Which role did you play this time?
I'm one of the presidents of a company.
- I see.
- It suits you well.
Hence, the hairstyle.
- He suits the role well.
- This time,
do you die quickly again?
No, it's a proper role this time.
- So, it's until the end.
- I'll be in it until the end.
- Actually...
- It's all thanks to Tae Hyun.
- Thank you.
- No, thank you.
I heard a new song recently.
We... You might not believe it,
- but we release a song every month.
- You're right.
- Like Yoon Jong Shin.
- Yes.
(While collaborating with young musicians...)
(such as O.WHEN and Band Nah, )
(Band 015B has been releasing a song every month since 2018.)
Do you have a particular goal for this year?
- I always have a simple wish.
- Yes.
I hope I can keep doing...
the music I love continuously and well...
- without any problem.
- That's right.
I hope to perform too.
Let's see if you won't have any problems this year.
- Okay.
- A fortune-teller will join us.
Let's hear from him right away.
- My heart is fluttering.
- It's so...
(Time for Fortune Reading)
- He's Jang Ho Il.
- Hello.
- It's nice to meet you.
- Have you heard of 015B?
When I went to the karaoke in elementary school,
the list of popular songs...
- always had 015B.
- That's right.
We're confident...
because we have a song that transcends generations,
- "Goodbye Now." - That's right.
("Goodbye Now" by 015B)
(It's the national song of farewell that's still played at graduations.)
It's a song even kindergarteners know.
"Goodbye Now" is like that.
- So we can confidently ask, - That's right.
"You know that song, right?"
It's such a great song. The band was the best...
back in our time.
May I do the fortune read for you?
- Yes, please.
- Okay.
When is your birthday?
It's September 10, 1965.
I'll do the reading with your birthday.
- I was born at noon.
- Noon.
- Ho Il, - Okay.
You were born as fire. You have the strong wood element.
People with the strong wood element...
have young looks. They live young...
- compared to their age.
- It's true.
He does live young.
You're actually a scholarly type.
He has always been good at studying.
He went to a prestigious university.
Which university did you go to?
I went to S University.
- Seoul National University?
- Yes.
- Didn't you know?
- I didn't know.
(Ho Il was a good student.)
I know someone famous who has a similar fate as yours.
He works in the creative field.
He works in an advertising company.
I worked in an advertising company.
What?
I made music as 015B and worked in an advertising company at 1st.
(Ho Il made music and worked in a company at first.)
That's incredible.
I worked there for about three years.
The company gave me an early promotion.
They made me an assistant manager in two years.
I was a promising employee.
(He was a promising employee at an advertising company.)
But I began getting more work at the company...
while gaining more attention as 015B.
I was at the crossroads, so I thought hard about...
what I needed to do in life.
I turned in my resignation letter and chose a career in music.
You chose well.
I was anxious back then,
- but things worked out well.
- Seriously.
That's so fascinating.
(They heard about his life before 015B by chance.)
That's incredible.
So that's one aspect of your life.
In your later years... Especially next year, your fortune will change.
(Wasn't he very different just a moment ago?)
The artistic world...
you have will deepen.
You'll continue to do what others don't do.
But it'll become a genre of its own.
A genre of its own.
- Do you have something in mind?
- No.
I don't know what it is.
Your characters tell me that you'll continue to do...
creative work in your later years.
You'll be even more successful in your later years.
(Ho Il's musical life has a bright future.)
- Thank you.
- My goodness.
I'm so glad that I came here today.
I'm so happy.
(Happy)
I think I found my fate.
Thank you.
The fortune-teller is the best.
My goodness.
- For years...
- Hey, Seung Ho.
Tae Hyun.
What is it?
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
(There's no way he'll tell them so easily.)
We called to use a verifying the truth card.
So you have that card.
I forgot about the new card.
Send me a screenshot of your bank balance.
That's good. I'm curious as well.
There isn't anything interesting about my bank balance.
Here's what we want to ask.
We had agreed to meet up with someone who was born in 2001.
That person was waiting.
You should've moved faster.
(Being annoying)
- I'm sorry, but...
- He's so aggravating.
All right.
In any case, we want to know which square you're working on next.
Then we'll exclude that square when we look for someone.
Is that your question for the verifying the truth card?
Yes, it is.
Then we'll put him on the phone.
They met someone.
(Nodding)
Hello.
(Whose voice is it?)
- Hello.
I'm a member of 015B,
Jang Ho Il.
(I see.)
Ho Il, I love your songs.
It's nice to talk to you.
Did Tae Hyun recruit you?
Yes, I came out suddenly upon receiving his call.
I was in Gyeonggi Province,
but I came all the way to Seoul.
Are you in Gangnam, Seoul?
(He asks about the current location.)
- Ho Il, stop right there.
- Okay.
You should tell us where you're at.
What? Aren't you asking too many questions?
Then send us a screenshot of your bank balance.
- We'll ignore what you said.
- My goodness.
We're in Gangnam.
- I see that they didn't move today.
- They met everyone in Gangnam.
We could meet everyone in Gangnam.
We got lucky.
Did the information help?
The remaining squares are 1941...
and 1953.
Please introduce us to Uhm Young Soo.
Uhm Young Soo?
(We don't know Uhm Young Soo very well.)
There are also Tae Jin Ah and...
That's right. That's a good option.
Kim Hye Ja. Please give us their phone numbers.
I'm hanging up now.
- Okay.
- Eat something tasty.
- All right.
(Sighing)
A member of 015B.
It's something Tae Hyun can do.
Even if we do our absolute best and get a square, it'll be 4 to 3.
I want to go to one more place, but our options are...
Our options are limited.
- Let's wrap it up nicely.
- Is it time for a quiz?
Ho Il, it'll be the best if you can answer the question.
What kind of a quiz do you usually get?
- The quiz is a bit hard.
- is it hard?
We got this question earlier.
Until the 1980s...
- There were limitations.
Limitations?
- When the economy improved, - When it improved...
a ban on something was lifted in 1989.
Then people could enjoy it freely.
It marked the liberalization of the nation.
- Overseas travel?
- That's it!
Overseas travel?
- I see.
Overseas travel.
- I answered correctly.
- I see.
- You guys are from that era.
- That's right.
You might get a question like that.
That happened in our time.
- The ban got lifted.
- That's right.
The lyrics of 015B's song reflected that.
In the middle of "Essay and Vehicle..."
Is it in that song?
("Essay and Vehicle" is a song from 015B's 3rd album...)
(which described the changed lives in the 1990s.)
(Overseas travel)
(Whether or not you've done it is considered important)
Rich people traveled overseas early on...
- and bragged about it.
- They bragged about it.
"Have you traveled abroad? Haven't you done it yet?"
I could answer a quiz like that.
It's related to the era.
- Is it related to the era?
- Yes.
We got such questions.
(Time for Quiz)
In 1965, a drawing about the various aspects...
of people's lives in the 2000s was printed...
- in a newspaper.
- I know what it is.
Some parts of the drawing were accurate predictions...
while other parts weren't.
What goes in the "Blank..."
of the drawing?
My goodness.
I think I've seen this drawing.
Me too.
"Various aspects of the daily life. In 35 years,"
"how much will our lives change?"
Thirty-five years later...
- The 2000s.
They made this prediction in 1965.
(How did people predict the future in 1965?)
A small TV.
It was actually made.
- There are no moving roads.
- They exist at airports.
- There are escalators too.
- You mean the moving walkways.
The moving walkways.
- "Study at home." - We do study at home.
- Electric cars.
- There are electric cars.
"I can do the cleaning." There are robot vacuums.
- Robot vacuums.
- We have everything.
People thought that these imaginations were absurd.
But most of them came true.
(Among them)
(A question from 1965)
- Is it going to the moon?
- Yes.
It's going to the moon.
"Space travel?"
People say that space travel will be possible.
Elon Musk wants to go to Mars.
(Is it about a trip to a planet like Mars?)
Maybe it's about Chuseok or Jeongwol Daeboreum.
"Ride this to see the full moon!"
Chuseok.
He's going to the moon.
The destination has been decided.
- That's right.
- But...
I don't think it's "Overseas travel."
If it's "Space travel..."
"Ride this for space travel" would be too obvious.
Right? It'd be too obvious.
He's going to the moon.
It's really funny.
- Hold on.
- It's...
- I think it's a trip.
- Okay.
I just thought of something.
- He looks like a student.
- Okay.
Maybe it's "Ride this for a school trip!"
"A school trip" is a good guess.
- It's too long to be "A picnic." - It's too long.
"Ride this for a picnic."
(Considering the size of the blank, "A picnic" is too short.)
Four characters are this long, right?
Four characters.
- The size is the same.
- There are four characters.
You measured the length with precision.
- I think there are 4 characters.
It's "A school trip." I think Ho Il will be a hero.
It'll be embarrassing if my answer is incorrect.
"Ride this for a school trip!"
(Answer: Ride this for a school trip!)
"A school trip."
(Desperate)
(Please)
- "Ride this for a school trip!" - "Ride this for a school trip!"
(Team Guys)
(The food they acquired)
(Burger)
(Team Guys is moving to eat burgers.)
(One thought comes to mind.)
They got the quiz wrong.
- What?
- They got the quiz wrong...
for the 1965 square.
(It has been a while, but they haven't heard the alarm.)
We haven't heard the alarm.
That means we can go for the 1965 square.
That's right. I think we should find someone in Sangam-dong.
(They arrive at a drive-thru with hopeful thoughts.)
We arrived at a drive-thru.
Shubi dubap
(They order quickly.)
One large set and...
Thank you. All right.
I think they failed the quiz for the 1965 square.
Did they fail the quiz?
Otherwise...
We can't go for the 1953 square.
(Cuckoo)
Year 1965.
(Laughing)
Now,
- we can just enjoy the burger.
- Yes.
(We can just enjoy the burger.)
I suddenly lost...
my appetite for a burger.
I say that, but I'll enjoy the food.
(He's enjoying the food already.)
It's still tasty.
(It's still tasty.)
Enjoy the food.
(Eating)
My voracious juniors.
It's tasty.
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
We're quite cheerful.
(We're quite cheerful.)
(Seung Ho takes a bite as well.)
(While having a tearful eating show, )
(they return to the base.)
It'll be embarrassing if my answer is incorrect.
"Ride this for a school trip!"
It's correct.
(Answer: Ride this for a school trip!)
(Ho Il, you're the best.)
That's right.
I think I've seen it before.
You know, he didn't disappoint.
(Ride this for a school trip!)
I got lucky and answered correctly.
He's a hero.
I have no regrets today.
- You'll be successful this year.
- Thank you.
I'll work hard so that my music becomes a genre of its own.
- Let's go, 015B!
This is incredible.
It's bulgogi. How will we eat this?
Seriously.
We haven't even eaten instant tteokbokki before you came.
- We need to eat both dishes.
- I see.
(They got instant tteokbokki for the 2001 square.)
Dong Hyun, let's go and wait.
Afterward...
Let's go there.
We don't want to make Ho Il wait.
(They decided to eat after meeting up with Ho Il!)
(Failure to eat the food after getting the quiz right...)
(will make them lose the squares they acquired...)
(and the score will go back to 2 to 2!)
(Current time, 6:30pm)
Hey,
- we should hurry up.
- Yes.
- Let's hurry up.
- This isn't easy.
We need to hurry up.
(Team Handsome hurriedly heads over to the assembly location.)
We just need to get "Handsome Guys," right?
- Yes. "Handsome Guys." - Now...
Let's put in our order at the tteokbokki place...
and eat as soon as we enter.
Then I can run over and order bulgogi.
What's the time of arrival?
It was 7:10pm.
I think it got pushed to 7:20pm.
(If the time of arrival is 7:20pm...)
(The race ends at 8pm.)
(They need to finish the task for a wishing happy new year card, )
(eat instant tteokbokki, and eat bulgogi in 40 minutes.)
Let's put in an order on our way there...
- and eat hurriedly.
- Someone should eat.
Other members should get the characters for "Handsome Guys."
We just need to take photos for "Handsome Guys."
It'll be okay as soon as we get "Some."
- Is there a way we can find it?
- "Some?"
Google Woo.
"Some."
The beauty store has a cosmetics brand called Some Blossom.
- Google Woo is the best.
- Some Blossom.
- Yes.
Google Woo.
- Google Woo is incredible.
- He's incredible.
- There must be many products.
- Shall we go?
(With overflowing confidence, Sang Hyeok leaves the car.)
(Current time, 7:20pm)
(Will they be able to complete the mission?)
That team...
has various tasks to finish.
If they missed any one of them...
or did them strangely...
Then they need a scolding.
In that case, I think 1 or 2 members...
- should join the individual match.
- That's right.
- They should play with us.
Let's call and ask.
(They call Team Handsome right away.)
- Hello.
- Where are you?
- Us?
- Yes.
We have some remaining homework.
Do you mean the selfie?
- Really?
- Yes.
You need to hurry up and complete it.
We need to hurry up and find it, so please hang up.
We're very busy.
Are you finding it in Sangam?
No, we're... Hello?
Hello?
Dong Hyun.
His acting doesn't improve.
When I asked him if he was in Sangam,
he went, "Hello?"
- I think he's nearby.
- He must be nearby.
- Then...
(Base Camp, Sangam-dong)
They didn't have Some Blossom.
Which characters remain?
- "Hand" and "Some." - I will look for them.
We need them.
Which way is the tteokbokki place?
- We need to hurry up.
- Shall we go?
The "With" we have is small,
so it'll be nice to find a bigger one.
Okay.
(Team Handsome hurriedly looks for a tteokbokki place.)
They're looking for something.
(The chasers appear.)
They didn't see us.
(Whispering)
(Team Guys closes in on them.)
Why...
You haven't have found many characters.
Seriously.
Why did you guys follow us here?
- Are you guys going somewhere?
- What?
Where are you guys going?
The menu is instant tteokbokki. Do you want to eat it?
- Instant tteokbokki?
- Yes.
It does sound delicious.
- Do you want to eat?
- We just ate a burger.
We don't have much time. We need to hurry up.
(They have 30 minutes before the game ends.)
(Team Guys accompanies them to the instant tteokbokki place.)
They're quite busy.
It looks like...
they're solving a puzzle.
Okay.
Which dishes did you get?
Instant tteokbokki.
You guys got bulgogi too.
Anything.
- Was there "Anything?" - Was there "Anything?"
What did you eat?
- Egg tarts.
It was Tae Hyun's idea, right?
That was the only thing we ate until 2pm or 3pm.
Dong Hyun...
would've gone to eat beef if it weren't for Tae Hyun.
That's right.
- Did we put in an order?
- Excuse me.
You can take the ingredients you want.
- You need to eat for the square.
- That's right.
We almost failed.
You guys came here to distract us, right?
No. We didn't know either.
We almost failed.
(25 minutes remain.)
What's this?
(While the younger members make tteokbokki)
That was funny.
(Tae Hyun continues to organize something.)
(Let's see.)
(Team Guys members gang up on him like hyenas.)
(Are you ready? Shall we go?)
(It's time to check.)
Happy New Year...
It's long indeed.
With Handsome Guys...
on...
the Year of the Snake.
We did it.
(Happy New Year with Handsome Guys on the Year of the Snake.)
The Year of the Snake. We did it.
(They completed it.)
It's too...
We did it.
We were bound to find it.
(They completed the mission for a wishing happy new year card.)
Were you guys done when I messaged you?
- When you messaged us?
- We weren't done then.
- No?
- We finished it here.
It was a lie.
He replied in three seconds.
That means he lied without hesitation.
Don't you know that athletes are agile?
Of course.
They're true friends.
(Instant tteokbokki is done.)
(He blows on a sausage and puts it in his mouth.)
(Tae Hyun, the picky eater, gets a dumpling.)
(Dong Hyun eats tteokbokki quickly.)
We ate tteokbokki.
Thank you.
(The final score is 3 to 2.)
(Team Handsome won.)
- I want to ask you this.
- Okay.
We heard the cuckoo sound 4 times, so why do you only have 3 squares?
We had to eat 4 dishes for 4 squares,
but we didn't have enough time.
Didn't you eat one dish?
It doesn't matter. We won with a score of 3 to 2.
- You guys only had two squares.
- But...
we came here since you guys had four squares.
- We had time for one more person.
- It was 6:30pm.
Had the score been 3 to 2, we would've gone for another square.
But since the score was 4 to 2, we gave up.
It wasn't our intention to do this.
If things are going to be this way, we'll push off food until later.
Sang Uk and I can eat 4 to 5 meals in a single seating.
Seriously.
Okay. Shoot your shot then. What should we do?
One of the three members should join the individual match!
(One of the three members should join the individual match!)
- Seriously.
- We don't want anything else.
- We gave up on the last attempt.
- One of the three members.
We got here at 6:30pm.
You should do that much.
So that's the conclusion.
(Laughing)
One of the three members should join the individual match.
- Tae Hyun, - Will it be okay?
I can sense the flow of the match.
If one of us joins the match,
- that person will go hiking.
- He will go hiking.
- You know that, right?
- Yes.
- It's like that. It's strange.
- We shouldn't agree to it.
Is there someone you guys want in particular?
I won't join.
Why would you make that decision?
I'll never join.
(We want you to join.)
- I'll never join.
- If you guys refuse to join...
the match,
I won't have more to say.
But here's what upsets me.
This will become a bigger issue later on.
"Let's get 4 squares 1st and eat 4 meals afterward."
- We'll think that.
- That's right.
What's five?
What?
(You fool!)
- Tae Hyun.
- My goodness.
- Dong Hyun is a fool.
- Tae Hyun.
- What? What's this?
- For goodness' sake.
- Tae Hyun.
- You need to understand the signal.
(I need an explanation.)
(Sang Hyeok understands it before Dong Hyun does.)
I see.
He's a fool.
(You guys are something else!)
- Seriously.
- You guys are something else!
(I didn't expect them to scheme behind my back.)
- Gosh.
- Seriously.
Why didn't you understand?
The three of us should play rock-paper-scissors?
- I didn't know.
- Dong Hyun...
"What is five?"
You should've told me about it in advance.
(Laughing)
We should carry on with it though.
We should.
Then we should do this. Actually,
we were going to answer the third question...
- and get some tteokbokki.
- Right.
Tae Hyun called Jang Ho Il.
- He already called him.
- Right.
Tae Hyun asked to meet up with him.
I think you can be the one that can take responsibility for that.
Gosh.
- He should be the one to go?
- Right.
(He betrayed him right away.)
Up until he came here,
he said that he was going to be with me to the end.
He's amazing.
You're on fire today, so you won't get caught.
You've been in a lot of competitions.
You know if things will turn out well.
- Will he get caught today?
- He won't.
(He won't get caught.)
Will I get caught if I go?
Look at me. Will I get caught if I go?
- You will.
- Right?
Weren't you okay about it though?
About hiking in the morning.
I have a training session tomorrow.
There's a certain feeling about it.
I'll trust you.
You said that I wouldn't get caught if I went.
- Be certain.
- You won't get caught.
- Really?
- You really won't get caught.
Okay. I'm down for it.
- You're amazing, Tae Hyun.
- I think I won't get caught.
You're amazing.
I will get caught 100 percent if I go.
- It should've been Dong Hyun.
- Good luck, Tae Hyun.
It all comes down to this.
I'll be clear about this.
When I get caught here,
- I'll take one of them with me.
- Okay.
(He suddenly announces to take someone with him.)
- They will be loyal.
- Right.
- You said he wouldn't get caught.
- What?
I will take someone with me if I get caught.
- You won't get caught.
Here is the first question for exemption.
Up until 1953,
this was brought only through importation in Korea.
This was finally produced for the first time in Korea in 1953.
After that, the amount of this that was brought in...
during the holidays...
was known to represent the social status of a family.
That was how popular it was.
What could this be?
- Me.
Cooking oil.
Cooking oil? Incorrect.
So it was something...
- that was only imported.
- If it's 1953,
you should know about it.
Of course. He was in elementary school.
Tae Hyun...
- What are you saying?
- You know this!
- Me.
- But...
- Never mind.
- Bananas.
- Incorrect.
- Me. Chocolate.
That's incorrect.
- Flour.
- Incorrect.
No?
What could it be?
- Me.
- Seung Ho.
- Beer.
- Incorrect.
- That sounded like a good guess.
- His answers sound plausible.
If you hear the answer, you will be confused.
- Do you know the answer?
- Yes.
Google Woo searched it up right away.
(Dong Hyun checked the answer through Google Woo.)
This is really common now.
- What?
- Ramyeon.
- Incorrect.
- I thought of ramyeon too.
Me.
- Get it right.
- Apples.
That is incorrect.
- Melons?
- That is incorrect.
We'll be mentioning the dragon fruit at this rate.
This is hard.
- What could be really common now?
- It's really common.
Shall we start getting hints then?
It starts with S.
(It starts with S.)
- You got something different?
- It's something else.
- It's different?
- What's wrong with him?
- It's different.
- It must be something else.
Me. Salt.
- What?
- Salt.
That is incorrect.
Me. Sugar.
Sugar is correct.
Okay!
- It was sugar?
- Gosh.
That makes sense...
if you think of those times.
You're really good at avoiding the penalties.
Right.
You and I were the only ones that didn't get caught.
I have to get myself out of this too.
Please make sure to make Tae Hyun get caught.
- I'll do my best.
- Sang Uk.
- Yes?
- Let's get Tae Hyun.
- Let's make it happen.
Let's go.
- This question is about 1941.
- About 1941?
- Gosh.
In 1941,
Japan started a policy of subjecting to Japan...
and tried to annihilate our country's identity.
As a part of that policy, the name of an educational institution...
has been changed to mean "Japanese Loyal Subject."
What is the changed name?
National school.
Correct.
(Yi Kyung is correct.)
(Ta-da!)
You got it right away?
(You got it right away?)
(Team Guys gets a question right.)
(Tae Hyun is on the edge of the cliff now.)
Hold on. Things are becoming strange now.
Wait for me.
(We'll be going together.)
- Wait for me.
- Tae Hyun!
You guys said I wouldn't get caught!
Sang Uk has to win.
- Get yourself together, Sang Uk.
- Let's make it happen.
- Please, Sang Uk!
- It's the last question.
- Go for it.
- All right.
- I can get the answer.
In 1976,
this was developed in Korea for the first time in the world.
It was salted?
- "Developed." - "Developed."
Oh, right. I misheard it.
"Salted?"
Like salted shrimp.
- "Salted?" - Gosh.
Right.
Okay. I'll read the question again.
In 1976,
this was developed in Korea for the first time in the world.
This was assessed to have been developed...
by the culture of Koreans who have to get...
anything done really quickly.
Really quickly?
These days, this food product is really popular abroad.
What could this be?
- Me. Ramyeon.
- Ramyeon?
That is incorrect.
(I thought that was the answer.)
Me. Instant rice.
That is incorrect.
Me. Canned tuna.
Incorrect.
In 1976?
Me. Instant coffee?
Correct.
(Instant coffee)
(Sighing)
(Team Handsome and Team Guys share different emotions.)
Really?
Yes!
(We believed in you, Tae Hyun.)
This feels even better.
Go away!
He came back alive from the underworld.
- He got it right away.
- Gosh.
I couldn't think of anything.
(Sang Uk will be serving for two weeks straight.)
- We trusted in you.
- Right.
You were right about me not getting caught.
Right.
- That was amazing.
- Gosh. I'm crying.
We needed a miracle to happen.
(The person that feels the unhappiest)
That was amazing.
The instant coffee is popular. That's right.
(The next day before dawn breaks)
(Sunrise location: Mount Nam, the center of Seoul)
Gosh, it's cold.
(Sang Uk appears for the activity for two weeks straight.)
The weather is great.
Do I go up all the way?
All the way up to the top?
I'm just doing what I have been doing everyday.
I'm just doing my morning workout.
The sun can't be up.
I have to see the sunrise from the top.
I can walk quickly, right?
(Unlike his upper body that looks relaxed, )
(he takes quick steps.)
(His lower body moves aggressively.)
It's cold.
(When compared with a regular person, )
(the athlete hikes up a lot quicker.)
It's nice and refreshing.
(He walks through the fresh morning air.)
I feel great.
(Sang Uk hikes up at his own pace.)
You're all doing okay, right?
(We're not doing okay.)
Goodbye, everyone!
This is nothing.
I should actually be running up.
The sun is rising.
The sun can't be up yet.
I can see it.
I made it!
The view is amazing.
I can see all of Seoul.
I should have a drink here.
(Rummaging)
I'm here because of this.
(The instant coffee that secured his loss appears.)
The first thing that was done in the athletic club...
was to make some coffee for the coach.
I'm doing this after 14 years.
(How does the instant coffee that secured his loss taste?)
Gosh, it's nice.
I saw the head!
I should make a wish.
(The sun comes up over the ridge of the mountain.)
My first New Year's wish...
is to get good results as an athlete.
My second wish is for our show to get good viewer ratings...
and become a big hit.
My next wish...
(The last desperate wish)
is for Tae Hyun to get caught.
If I think about it, Seung Ho should get caught too.
The instant coffee developed in 1976.
(We hope you will win next time.)
I will never forget that.
(The sixth region, Gyeonggi Province)
(Handsome Heritage)
(Gyeonggi Province's creators)
(The arrival of Yurimping that took over...)
("The Trauma Code: Heroes On Call")
Hello. It's great to see you.
(Scene-stealer, Yoon Kyung Ho)
("The Trauma Code: Heroes On Call," Man that you keep thinking about)
(He did his research based on the show.)
(The arrival of a quiz master?)
(Team Handsome paces forward under the lead of Kyung Ho.)
(However...)
(This man's clumsiness...)
(slowly gets revealed.)
(I don't know anymore.)
(Another point to focus on)
(Sang Uk has changed.)
(He'll finally show his talent...)
(as a game changer.)
(Please listen to what I have to say.)
(Traveling around Gyeonggi Province)
(The six men struggle...)
(to make contents.)
(They complete unexpected missions...)
(and experience various contents.)
(A trip to the world of creators)
- Handsome Guys - Okay.
(See you next week on Handsome Guys.)
("Our Way" by 015B featuring Jeong Da Yeong)
Dramaday.me