(Handsome Guys)
(Gunsan, North Jeolla Province, 7:30am)
(At minus 8°C, one day when it's still fiercely cold)
Tae Hyun.
(The members came to work without fail.)
Tae Hyun came with a moustache.
Goodness.
Your skin has gotten much better.
I changed my face.
You look much better.
What happened to Tae Hyun?
To substitute Tae Hyun,
I joined the show as a member today.
He joined us...
not as a guest, but as a regular member.
Welcome.
(Jang Hyuk playing Cha Tae Hyun only for today)
It's good to see you.
(A huge welcome)
- Are you free tomorrow? - No, I'm not.
- You aren't free? - You aren't?
- Really? - Yes.
Jang Hyuk might get the penalty today.
- Right. - If he does,
Cha Tae Hyun will get...
- the penalty instead. - Right.
- Really? - Wait a minute.
- He's smiling all of a sudden. - Is that so?
Tae Hyun would feel troubled. Jang Hyuk helped him, but...
He wouldn't be aware of it.
- Is he not aware of it? - Is he?
- He isn't aware of it. - Right.
Hyuk, have you been acquainted with any of our members?
I've only been acquainted with Dong Hyun.
- And me? - It's my first time meeting you.
What? We've met before.
Where did we meet?
(Where did we meet?)
Your face...
Did you meet him in your dreams?
I don't know about now,
- but you used to live there. - Yes.
My parents also live there,
so I bumped into you twice when I visited them.
I said hello when we were recycling trash.
Really?
The gym in front of Cheongdam Station.
I said hello to you four times.
- This is embarrassing. - I said hello to you four times.
(Unbelievable)
- Do you remember him now? - Yes.
Now that he mentioned the gym...
You don't remember me.
Why am I always the only one who remembers?
He probably thought that you were his fan.
No one remembers meeting you.
It's a social phenomenon.
It's just a social phenomenon, so please understand.
(A social phenomenon?)
- But... - When you're past mid-40s,
it can't be helped.
- A social phenomenon? - I'm serious.
Then do we have a separate guest?
Yes, let's meet the guest.
(Who's here?)
- Park John. - Hello.
I'm so happy.
- Hello. - Park John.
Nice to meet you.
(A sentimental ballad singer who makes our hearts flutter)
(- His singing is way too good. - His low voice is so sexy.)
(His sweet voice transformed into a heavy metal style.)
(Now married, John to the Park)
It's cold today.
Do you know each other well?
We were on a show recently.
We hung out.
He wrote a song for me.
Sang Uk sent me a message.
- Yes. - What?
I'm his huge fan.
- I really like him. - Did you send him a message?
Yes, I really did.
(Dear John Park, I enjoy listening to your song "Places.")
(In 2021, Sang Uk displayed his dohwasal.)
(They became close ever since.)
- How about Hyuk? - It's our first time...
I feel honoured to meet you.
Maybe I don't remember meeting you.
No.
- It's our first time meeting. - Is that right?
Yes, it's our first time.
He feels embarrassed.
(Then I'm relieved.)
Sang Uk has gotten the penalty three times in a row.
- Right? - Yes.
- Three times in a row. - I've been losing in a row.
I shouldn't be on his team.
No, the two of you...
I have a lot of hatred built up.
I'm very spiteful.
When you team up with Sang Uk...
Not all three members get the penalty.
He ends up getting it.
(Sang Uk ends up getting it.)
He's the perfect member to have like a scapegoat.
Then I'll choose.
(It's time to decide the teams.)
I'll choose.
(Who will be on Team Handsome with John Park?)
(Sang Uk and...)
It will be us three.
- We'll be on the same team. - No.
You didn't pick me because you thought you'd lose?
I'm doomed.
He probably picked me because he thinks he'll lose.
With two of them I'm close to...
I'm with someone who prefers to speak English...
and someone who always gets the penalty.
(Close friends)
- I like this. - I'm confident.
I'm happy with my team.
Of course you're happy.
Whenever Yi Kyung and Sang Uk were on the same team,
I often saw them decide who would get the penalty.
(He's right.)
I've seen you...
- compete so many times. - Right.
We always did a quiz until the end.
Right. That's why.
All right.
I like my team.
Shall we pick the cards first?
Yes.
(Then we'll pick them.)
Wait a minute.
- We don't know. It's random. - We don't know.
I should take the last card.
(Why is he running? The cards are random anyway.)
(Everyone checks his card.)
Gosh, this is insane.
(Clapping)
(Happy)
Oh, my.
- What do we do? - I'm sorry.
(Worried)
We're in trouble.
(They seem a little doomed.)
What's wrong with this one?
We've never gotten such a combination before.
(Mixed reactions in the same situation)
We have both hope and despair.
We got one reattempt card.
Here's another one.
We have two reattempt cards.
We also have a card to identify the other team's location.
(Jealous)
- I have a 30-minute nap card. - Nap card?
It's okay. We can sleep.
I have a question. What's Pump It Up at the arcade card?
- What is it? - It's Pump It Up.
Isn't that a music game?
"Once you succeed Pump It Up during 30 minutes,"
"you can move right away."
(Rhythm game card)
Isn't it hard to find an arcade with Pump It Up?
These days, people play with their hands.
(Being playful)
I got the same one.
It's wishing happy birthday card.
You have to use all the cards before the game is over.
- Reattempt card? - I never had this combination.
- We're in trouble. - We'll definitely win.
What is today's theme?
Today's Handsome Heritage is...
a bakery tour in North Jeolla Province.
- A bakery tour? - A bakery tour?
Visiting famous or hidden bakeries is called...
a bakery tour.
("To Gen MZ's Bakery Tour Sacred Place")
(Gen MZ Makes Half of People on Bakery Tour)
(That's why they came to visit North Jeolla Province.)
(With local ingredients harvested from fertile fields)
(Where famous bread is made)
By visiting bakeries in North Jeolla Province, we'll taste their bread...
and ask questions.
We will create...
our own Handsome Guys' bakery tour map.
(Gunsan, Jeonju, Gimje, Imsil, Buan, and Jeongeup)
(Shall we go on a bakery tour on Handsome Guys?)
(Full of anticipation)
- I like bread. - Do you?
- I like bread. - He does too.
- This is good. - Any questions related to bread.
- Do you know about bread? - I could be good at it.
You have time until 7pm tonight.
- Until 7pm. - The deadline is at 7pm.
For the losing team,
there will be an activity in North Jeolla Province.
It's going to work at a bakery at dawn.
(Using muscles early in the morning)
(A persistent fight with dough)
(They must endure the heat from the oven.)
(Tomorrow's penalty requires strength, technique, and patience.)
Right.
- You will make bread with care. - Okay.
Tell me about the penalty in detail.
I have to call Tae Hyun and explain to him.
Please give me the details.
Hyuk is the only one exempted...
from the penalty.
In that case,
don't answer the question after we lose.
(Laughing)
(You can count on me.)
We have a new chance card.
- Which one? - What is it?
I have a Cha Tae Hyun card.
- It's called Cha Tae Hyun card. - Cha Tae Hyun card.
You don't get the penalty even if you lose.
Even if you lose, you never get the penalty?
(When you lose, the penalty goes to Cha Tae Hyun.)
I wouldn't exchange it with three reattempt cards.
No way.
We have something better than the reattempt cards.
(The ultimate card appears.)
Among these nine squares,
just like last week,
there's one Handsome Guys square.
(He spots the familiar Handsome Guys square.)
What do we do with this?
With this square at stake,
you'll do a quiz right away.
- Of course. - We must win this one. It's huge.
It's really big.
- We have to win this one. - Yes, it's huge.
They have two reattempt cards.
If they win this too,
we might as well lose.
We must win this to stay hopeful.
(Which team will take the first victory?)
- In December of 1948, - I wouldn't know.
In The Independence Newspaper,
an article was published under the title,
"MG Who Eat Doughnuts for Lunch."
What's "MG?"
It talked about the increase of women...
who eat expensive doughnuts for lunch.
What does "MG" stand for?
Is it an acronym?
(An article in the Independence in December 1948)
(MG Who Eat Doughnuts for Lunch)
(They read the article with their team.)
Is this it?
- No, this is poong... - Let's see.
- MG? - MG?
(MG?)
- What's MG? - Yes, it's an acronym.
What's an example for a recent acronym?
(An acronym?)
What are some recent acronyms?
- Team Guys. - Will you go first?
Once you say your answer,
the turn goes to the other team.
- Really? - MG?
- MG. - MG.
(He withdraws for now.)
- Look. - Are the words Korean?
"Women in the wealthy class."
- This is missing. - In my opinion, it's in English.
Could it be mesdames?
Team Handsome.
- Will you take your turn? - Yes.
- Mesdames. - Mesdames?
Mesdames is incorrect.
- Wait. - Shall we go?
Why did they say mesdames? Isn't it an acronym?
So that's wrong.
I said it because it starts with M.
What's wrong with you?
How could it be mesdames when it's an acronym for MG?
- Team Guys. - Team Guys?
(All of a sudden?)
Modern girl.
Modern girls.
(Answer: Modern girls)
Modern girl?
(What will be the answer?)
- Modern girl. - I bet it's right.
Correct.
Unbelievable.
(Jang Hyuk answered the quiz in one go.)
(Surprised)
(Amazing)
This is nothing.
It's no big deal.
(Pompous)
I've read the newspaper for 20 years.
I read editorials.
(Impressed)
- We didn't get it. - No.
We didn't get the answer.
This was when...
the concept of modern girls was popular.
An example is women drinking coffee.
Your answer is so precise that I don't need to explain.
(His answer and explanation are perfect.)
I might not look like it,
but I'm a brainiac.
(I'm a brainiac.)
(Our eldest member is amazing.)
- Handsome Guys. - Guys.
(Handsome Guys)
Sang Uk, you have to win this time.
We have two reattempt cards. We have a good chance of winning.
They have to eat anyway,
so we can pick any location.
How about this?
Like Tae Hyun's strategy,
shall we go to all the places nearby?
One by one?
Then shall we go to Gunsan?
(To Gunsan?)
Yes, we can go to Gunsan first.
Then we can go to either Iksan or Gimje.
- What do you think, Park? - I like it.
- What's your idea? - I'll follow your lead.
- Here we go. - Let's go.
(Team Handsome heads to a bakery in Gunsan.)
(Team Guys)
(Their first restaurant near Gunsan Station)
Let's go. We must eat quickly.
We don't have much time.
- Hello. - Hello.
(What food do they have to eat after their first win?)
(Opening segment: Braised monkfish)
(A mix of chewy texture and spicy marinade)
(A delicacy to try even early in the morning)
Is the medium size enough for three?
- Yes. - We'll order that.
(To eat quickly and leave, they order right away.)
To block our row,
they would either go to Ilksan,
which is nearby.
Or they might go after Imsil.
(Team Handsome probably went to Imsil.)
Once you win Imsil,
you get so many advantages.
That's true.
I think...
the other team will try to complete a bingo.
They have two reattempt cards.
Then what should we do based on that?
We can go to as many places as possible.
Even if we fail, we can go to another nearby city.
That's what our strategy should be.
I don't know if I'm right.
I think...
we should be a little daring.
- Let's be honest. - Okay.
None of us will get the penalty.
(Smiling big)
My friend will handle the penalty, so don't worry about that.
(Cha Tae Hyun will get the penalty anyway.)
- Let's be drastic. - Can I really trust you?
- Think of it as travelling. - Yes.
Think of it as travelling in Gunsan.
I'll do my best.
(Glancing)
(The mixed braised monkfish arrives.)
This is medium size, and it's this big?
(Surprised)
(The amount is generous.)
Gosh.
(Exclaiming)
I've never seen a cuttlefish before.
(Cutting into bite sizes)
Look at the cuttlefish.
It's full of protein.
Enjoy your food.
- You too. - Enjoy.
(It's time to eat.)
(The eldest one takes a bite of red monkfish first.)
(The second eldest takes a big bite.)
It's a tasty restaurant. It's hot.
It's so delicious.
(One bite)
(Two bites)
(Three bites)
(3 bites of monkfish with 1 spoon of rice)
(While Dong Hyun is eating a lot of protein)
This is so delicious.
- Yes. - I was actually full.
(The youngest falls in love with the monkfish charms.)
Instead of leaving, I want to take my time and eat.
(I want to take my time and eat.)
I don't know much,
but fretting about winning doesn't make you win.
Right, it's always the case.
This is something I've watched over 100 times.
I watched it over 100 times.
"Rocky."
- I saw all the series. - "Rocky?"
For "Rocky,"
Sylvester Stallone wrote the original script.
He wanted to direct it but couldn't.
After retiring,
he still wanted to compete.
"Rocky" isn't just about sportsmanship.
What's important isn't winning.
Enduring the match...
In the process of preparing for a match,
there's a story about his life.
On top of that, he's a gangster.
Shall we have some soju and talk?
The vibe is perfect for some soju.
Usually, when we eat,
Tae Hyun tells us to hurry up.
"We have no time to eat."
He told us to eat fast.
It's nice that you're leading the team today.
- We get to talk about life. - I love it.
Take your time and eat.
(Their meal continues in a relaxed atmosphere.)
Gosh.
Do you know the address?
Here it is.
- Suseong-dong, Gunsan. - Suseong-dong.
Suseong-dong.
It's 2km away? Where is it?
In Gunsan.
- Let me see. - It's only 2km away?
It's around the corner.
- We're in Gunsan right now. - I know.
Did they not go there?
They must have gone there.
- There's no reason not to go there. - Right.
(It only takes 10 minutes. They set off in a hurry.)
It's closer than what you see on the map.
If we find them at the bakery in Gunsan,
let's just get bread.
- Why don't we get bread? - That's possible.
We can tease them too.
- That's perfect. - Either way,
we have to buy a cake.
If they're there, let's buy bread while teasing them.
(Lightheartedly)
We'll say that we came for some bread.
(They arrive at the destination.)
We're here.
(Will Team Handsome be in Gunsan?)
(10m until the destination)
(Will they get the quiz...)
(or will they get to buy bread?)
- I don't think they came here. - They didn't.
(Destination)
(The bakery looks empty.)
They didn't come here.
- They didn't. - Where did they go?
Please go to the parking lot on the left.
They could have gone to Iksan.
They're going after a bingo.
- Go ahead and try. - This is for the better.
We'll come to block you.
Getting a bingo isn't easy.
We'll just block them.
We can put them to sleep.
(Team Handsome)
Park's idea is amazing.
Going to Iksan first is...
a good idea.
(As Dong Hyun expected, they're heading to Iksan.)
(A moment ago)
(He was looking at the board carefully.)
Since they're over here,
their options are...
these two.
This place is far away.
(Based on possible bingos for Team Guys)
We'd better win Iksan first.
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
Iksan is very important.
(Blocking the other team's bingo)
They started off by winning one square,
but we must win today's race no matter what.
We must win.
Since we have two reattempt cards,
we'll win two.
It's impossible not to win with these cards.
During the race...
You know what?
When you fail once,
you get a mental breakdown.
I'm serious. We have to move to the next location.
It feels like...
losing all your money in your bank account.
Seriously.
- It's that bad. - Like it's futile?
You feel like you lost everything.
(For now, he finds it funny.)
You might be laughing now,
but I'll see your eyes widen very soon.
(To win their first square)
We arrived at our first spot, Iksan.
- Good. - Okay.
(The first bakery during the bakery tour in North Jeolla Province)
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
What was it?
- Corn toast bread. - Corn toast bread.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Handsome Bakery Tour 1, Single Corn Path)
Gosh, the smell.
- Hello. - It smells sweet.
I love the smell.
The smell of a bakery.
(Inside the trendy-looking bakery)
(There's toast bread you can't buy unless you come in the morning.)
- Isn't that corn toast bread? - Where?
At the very end.
- Toast bread? - It must be over there.
(Exclaiming)
Corn toast bread.
The colour looks bright.
(The toast bread doesn't look special on the outside.)
There's also corn toast bread with glutinous rice.
- Shall we try some? - Shall we?
That sounds good.
(He also takes toast bread with glutinous rice.)
You have to eat bread all day long.
It won't be all day long...
because...
Once we eat at three places, it will be over.
- Okay. - And we'll win the bingo?
- Great. - That's a good attitude.
(Won't we get a bingo after eating bread three times?)
So we can eat a lot here.
(It's okay to eat a lot.)
Corn.
Hello.
The smell is amazing.
It smells really good.
Is there anything that we must try?
I recommend you to try three types of toast bread.
- Three types? - All of them?
- And... - Is there more?
I recommend anything made with corn.
It's corn chestnut toast bread.
There's corn chestnut toast bread.
It must be freshly made. It's warm.
Hey, this is warm.
Then let's eat it.
It looks delicious.
(It's time to taste.)
Here are the top three at a bakery famous for corn toast bread.
Which one shall we start with?
- How about the basic one? - It looks attractive.
The basic one?
She gave me the pair of scissors.
(This one is for Park.)
(Thank you.)
It's to die for.
(This one is for me.)
There you go.
(The big one is for Sang Uk.)
Isn't that a brick?
Isn't it for you?
As expected,
Sang Uk's piece is much thicker.
- Of course. He should eat a lot. - Thank you.
What's with the texture?
(Surprised the 1st time by the bread's texture)
It's like sponge.
(The yellow inside stretches out as it tears.)
Shall I try the classic type?
(Yi Kyung takes the first bite.)
The inside is so soft.
You'll be very surprised.
(Surprised the 2nd time by the soft texture)
(Foodie Sang Uk takes a bite like Yi Kyung.)
(His forehead reacts right away and expresses the truth.)
(John Park also takes a bite.)
It's good.
(The taste makes you move up and down.)
- The taste is subtle... - Yes.
Instead of being strong.
Usually, corn toast bread is...
- toast bread with corn kernels. - Is that so?
I think that there's corn inside the dough.
The bread has a strong flavour of corn.
(There's a strong flavour of corn in the bread)
The glutinous rice bread is incredible. Look inside.
- What's that? - Isn't it sweet potato?
Isn't it glutinous rice inside?
Is it like corn jam?
(The second is corn toast bread with glutinous rice.)
(What are the transparent chunks?)
- Is it jam? - No.
It's glutinous rice made into rice cakes. The texture is...
It's so chewy that it sticks inside the mouth.
(The chewy texture is interesting.)
(They're so curious that they can't resist it.)
You know what I mean?
(The glutinous rice toast bread makes him nod automatically.)
It's like glutinous rice doughnut with bread inside.
It's neither bread nor rice.
Right. It's rice cake-like bread.
You chew on glutinous rice.
- Do you like chestnuts? - I do.
It has about five chestnuts.
(Lastly, it's corn chestnut toast bread.)
(Full of sweet and crumbly chestnuts)
(They all take a bite at the same time.)
It's very...
sweet in a nice way.
It's chestnut itself.
(It's chestnut itself.)
It must be the bakery owner.
- Are you the bakery owner? - Yes.
- I see. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- The bread is delicious. - Hello.
You're much younger than I thought.
I'm the baker's eldest son.
Are you the successor?
I'm working hard to learn in order to succeed the bakery.
(He's still learning to succeed the bakery.)
- Is Iksan not famous for corn? - Right.
Then how did you start making bread with corn?
My father did a lot of research.
He likes the savoury taste.
Toast bread that's light and savoury is popular.
That's why we use corn as the main base.
We add corn to the dough and mix them together.
I see.
They actually add corn.
It's a starter.
- We call it mother dough. - Right.
Mother dough isn't normally used for toast bread, is it?
Right, it's hardly used.
(Impressed)
It's to make the dough chewy.
Based on my father's secret,
- Is it his secret recipe? - we created...
three more bread recipes.
Regular toast bread is soft...
and easy to tear.
But this one is sticky.
I agree.
- It's because of the mother dough. - Exactly.
That's the biggest difference.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
He said that the baker did a lot of research,
- and I can tell. - Totally.
I never had toast bread like this.
- It's made with love. - Right.
You know a lot about bread.
We have a good chance today.
We just need to visit two more places.
You sounded very smart.
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
(Time for Quiz)
Since Park is with us, I'm not worried.
- It seemed like he knew a lot. - Right.
- Here's the quiz. - Okay.
- Let's get it without hints. - Of course.
The number of kernels on a cob is...
equivalent of this.
What is it?
Could it be the number of teeth?
They're not the same at all.
- You mean, puffed corn snack? - No matter what...
Isn't it right?
When you measure one row...
(No one has 100 teeth.)
- Is it similar or the same? - It's exactly the same.
He said that it's the same,
- not just similar. - That's what he said.
If it's the same,
- they must be the same family. - Definitely.
Something in the corn family with grains.
What's similar to corn?
Is corn...
a type of grain?
Grain.
(Grain?)
Then barley.
Barley doesn't have many kernels.
(The number of kernels)
I can only think of barley when it comes to grains.
- There's definitely... - Only barley has kernels...
that splatter.
When he gets stuck on something, that's all he talks about.
(Laughing)
When he gets stuck on something...
Barley.
Wait.
Did you think of something?
Isn't it popcorn?
- Popcorn? - In one bag of popcorn,
there's an ear of corn.
That sounds plausible.
Won't it be possible?
Doesn't it depend on the seller?
He said that they're exactly the same.
- The same. - Think about it.
Each ear of corn has a different number of kernels.
They're all different.
- The number can't be consistent. - You're right.
- Darn it. - Every ear of corn has...
a different number of kernels.
How can corn have the same number of kernels as another grain?
It must be something that's made with corn.
- You're a genius. - John.
The answer must be a bag of popcorn.
Seriously.
It's a little vague.
As Sang Uk said,
one bag of popcorn depends...
- You meant the microwavable kind. - on the brand.
Yes, that's what I meant.
- It's unclear. - It's unclear.
- The answer is unclear. - It's unclear.
How about this?
During the corn's growing process,
there could be seeds.
Here's what I thought.
Corn has roots.
On the roots,
- is it called hair? - Fine hair?
- Corn silk? - There are a lot...
- Corn silk? - Yes, corn silk.
Not the kernels...
So it has the same number as the kernels?
Corn silk makes sense.
Corn silk?
Maybe a kernel grows from each strand of corn silk.
Don't they get separated when corn silk is pulled off?
What are you talking about?
Like the root of the hair?
Exactly.
We don't know because corn silk is removed.
Corn has a lot of corn silk.
- Corn silk. - Corn silk.
- Corn silk. - Corn silk?
- It's the only answer. - Okay.
Go, John Park.
The answer is corn silk.
(Answer: Corn silk)
Correct.
- That's crazy. - Yes, man.
We got it. This is insane.
This is insane.
- We got it. - Goodness.
Didn't I tell you that we're getting off work early?
The male flower on a corn plant is on top of the stem.
The female flower blooms on the side of the stem.
When pollen from the male flower falls on the female stigma,
which is corn silk, pollination takes place.
That's where corn kernels form.
Kernels form as many as the number of corn silk strands.
That's why the number of kernels and corn silk strands are the same.
It's similar to the hair example.
What I said sounded strange.
Here's what we have to eat.
(Food that Team Handsome will eat)
- Kimchi? - Kimchi?
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
(Iksan: Kimchi)
(Simple!)
We can buy it at the convenience store.
- It will be salty. - Let's hurry and eat it.
We can buy it at a convenience store and eat it on our way.
Sir, do you have any kimchi?
(Sir, do you have any kimchi?)
Kimchi at a bakery?
(That's ridiculous.)
- Corn. - Corn.
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
That's great.
- We're off to a good start. - We're off to a good start.
We need to decide where we're going.
Let's go to Imsil...
and head to Buan.
(They plan out their route.)
The other team won't sit back.
(Thinking)
Let's do this.
I got it.
Instead of taking our chance,
we'll go to Gimje.
If the others win Imsil,
we can block them.
Then we can go to Gunsan.
We will have these two rows...
as a checkmate.
- Gimje is a good idea. - We can check their location.
- We can check their location. - Okay.
This is great.
We'll get some kimchi to go...
- and head to Gimje. - Let's go.
Let's go.
(With John Park's great performance, they head to Gimje.)
(Team Guys)
It's really big.
What's the most famous here?
(It looks like an ordinary bakery in the neighbourhood.)
(Master of Baking)
(List of patent registration)
(Bakery Master's House)
(It's full of extraordinary texts.)
We'll load on a lot of carbs today.
(What type of bread will they find here?)
- Gosh. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
This is perfect.
- These are... - Jang Hyuk.
Hello, we're here.
(My goodness)
Ma'am,
what's famous here?
Our rice flour bread.
Here it is.
Is this it?
- Is this famous? - Yes.
It's also healthy.
(Castella)
(When you take a bite, )
(the castella melts in the mouth.)
(Handsome Bakery Tour 2, sponge cake made with rice)
- Is it made with rice? - Yes.
It sells a lot.
How many do you sell per day?
We sell over 200 every day.
- Two hundred of this size? - Yes.
(Impressed)
- By the way, - Yes?
Rice flour is written here too.
Right.
(Rice cream cheese bread)
(Rice)
(There are other types of bread made with rice.)
- Are these made with rice? - That's correct.
Is all of your bread made with rice?
About 70 percent of our products are made with rice flour.
(Their specialty is rice bread.)
I saw some unusual bread.
What's jjamppong bread?
Jjamppong bread?
It says that it's a popular product.
- Is there jjamppong inside? - Yes.
Are there jjamppong ingredients...
- inside? - Yes.
It contains squid, Manila clams, mussels, and shrimp.
That's why it smells like it.
Gosh, it's soft.
(Cuckoo)
- Iksan. - I knew it.
- Iksan. - I knew they'd go to Iksan.
(Crazy Gamer mode is on.)
They'll go this way.
Here's what's amazing. They won Iksan.
For them, these two places were open.
Now that we'll win Gunsan...
(We need to win Gunsan to block them.)
- At this rate, - Right.
- we must win Gunsan no matter what. - Okay.
We can put them to sleep.
We have to go to an arcade and wish someone happy birthday.
If we search this apartment building,
we'll find someone whose birthday is coming soon.
Is anyone's birthday this week, by any chance?
- This week. - This week.
One who has birthday this week.
The baker's wife.
(Yes, the baker's wife.)
- Where is she? - Where is she?
- The baker's wife. - Where is she?
- Wait. - She's here.
We got it.
(Amazing)
It always works out.
- When is your birthday? - February 6.
(Surprised)
- Wait. - Your birthday is on February 6?
Yes.
It worked out.
- Things are working out. - Today...
- That's great. - My niece's birthday is the same.
- Goodness. - We have the same birthday.
We have two people.
Your niece has the same birthday?
- That's amazing. - In that case...
We're very lucky today.
- What's your name? - Jang Hyo Jin.
- Hyo Jin? - Yes.
A cake that you want.
- Do you have any favourite cake? - The strawberry cake.
- Strawberry? - Okay.
We came to Gunsan...
- for a reason. - Would you like a big one?
How many candles?
Fifty candles.
Fifty?
- Gosh. - Make it...
- forty-five candles instead. - Forty-five?
(Clapping)
- Shall we get number candles? - Shall we?
I'll bring number candles.
(Sir?)
We can use number candles if she wants to.
How about...
a heart-shaped candle and make it cute?
- One heart-shaped candle? - Yes, that's better.
One's age is...
He already told us her age.
Make it pretty.
(They acted fast to protect peace in the family.)
Your niece should join us.
Start.
(Happy birthday to you)
(Dear Baker's wife and Hyo Jin)
Happy birthday.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - Thank you so much.
This is amazing.
We're grateful to be able to wish you happy birthday.
- This was the best gift ever. - You're too kind.
The cake... Right.
We usually give you the cake...
- after wishing happy birthday. - Really?
Yes, of course we leave it with you.
But it feels weird to leave the cake with the bakery owner...
- especially when it's one of hers. - Still.
Still, we'll leave it to wish you a happy birthday.
- The niece can have it. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - The pleasure was ours.
- Thank you. - Right.
It's my first time getting a cake on my birthday.
Should we give them some?
They got you the cake for your birthday,
so you should have it.
Even though I bake cakes,
I never got her one on her birthday.
What an honour.
I'm touched.
Things are going smoothly.
(They were able to successfully wrap up an event.)
I can't believe it was her birthday.
No way.
(Time to taste the rice castella)
This must be so famous to sell 200 a day.
- Tell me about it. - A rice one is a first for me.
- Same here. - Here you go.
- I can smell the rice. - Really?
- At the very end. - Really?
(This castella that gives off a nutty rice scent)
(Nutty rice harvested in North Jeolla Province)
(A heap of it is ground.)
(Lots of eggs!)
(Whisked to add air into the batter)
(Fluffiness created from our own rice)
This must be enjoyed with milk.
I can have three packets of these if I have milk.
I mean it.
I'll load up on carbs today.
Say no more.
(Immediately sipping his milk)
You know,
- this seems fluffier. - Right.
It's not that...
this is tastier because it was made with rice.
It tastes the same as the fluffy castellas...
I've had before.
But I'm amazed...
that it was made with rice.
(A bite of the castella)
And then...
(Followed by a sip of milk)
When you soak the castella in your mouth with milk...
(A foolproof combo that has you gulping it down)
That's how I eat one.
The next one will be dunked in the milk.
Have you tried eating it soaked with milk...
- as a kid? - A lot actually.
If you get greedy and dunk it too deep,
- half of it will fall off. - Right.
Dip it gently.
Like that.
There's already less milk.
- The top fell off. - The top fell off.
You know how delicious this top part is.
Of course. I'm gulping all of it down at once.
It's coming apart.
(Now properly loading up on carbs)
I'm so happy.
I should have one more.
(One more pack of carbs)
The milk beat me once,
so I'm dipping it in the other way.
(He dips it in the other way to secure the top!)
All right.
This is crazy.
(They're done loading up on carbs.)
This is the highlight.
The highlight.
(This is the real deal.)
(Yummy)
(Now, he's finally done loading up on carbs.)
This is incredible.
I'd love to buy a few.
I'd give this to my children daily if this were in my neighbourhood.
(The soft sweet flavours would be a hit even with the kids.)
This might not...
- be appropriate to say to you. - Yes?
But I'm so happy right now I don't care who wins.
- I'm in bliss as well. - Same here.
(Joy was given to them in the form of sugar.)
Out of 13 episodes, you can enjoy one in that sense.
Right?
Korean variety shows should now take a different approach.
In what way?
- Let us relax... - Right.
And learn things in a serious way.
Of course we should seek laughter,
but we should find meaning and talk things out.
Since we're in Gunsan,
we should feel what this place has to offer.
Something like that.
By the way, when do we get our question?
Once we're done eating.
- Once we're done eating? - We'll soon be given the question.
You're more competitive than you let on.
You say we should relax, but you're competitive.
(You still have the jjamppong bun.)
(Goodness)
Check this out.
Hyuk, there's jjamppong in here.
Gosh, check out the filling.
There's a lot of filling in this.
How did he even think to put jjamppong in here?
This looks incredible.
- Try it. - Sure.
Try this.
Have the bigger piece.
I'll have this.
(Yummy)
No way. This works.
It's like the pizza buns we have...
but it also tastes like jjamppong.
- It's like a pizza croquette. - Yes, a croquette.
- A croquette. - It's exactly like a croquette.
- There's even a squid here. - I'm full.
I'm so full.
(He polishes it off.)
All right.
We've been lucky today so far.
- We're off to a great start. - Right.
- All right. - We can do this. Just relax.
- Take Hyuk's advice. - Relax.
Can't the owner try and guess it too?
If you know the answer,
feel free to say it out loud.
- Because... - We...
(Giggling)
- Here's the quiz. - Please give me one I know.
I want there to be one where I know the answer instantaneously.
Gunsan is famous for its rice.
Rice is a typical gluten-free grain...
that can be a substitute for flour.
- Which of the following... - It's a multiple-choice.
Has gluten in it?
A, potato.
B, buckwheat.
C, barley.
D, almond.
It suddenly got tougher.
Why is almond among the choices?
Why?
(For some reason, it's highly suspicious.)
Why is almond among the choices?
I don't think we have to consider almond.
- On purpose? - It seems like bait.
You're right. We can exclude it.
Can we exclude it?
There's a lot in flour but none in rice.
Then buckwheat.
It's in wheat, so buckwheat will have it too.
(Because there's wheat in buckwheat)
What has gluten?
I just saw the producer's expression.
(Me?)
- This is a mind game. - I know.
- I see people's expressions. - Those who do martial arts...
are experts at mind games.
Why did they choose this as a question?
- Exactly. - Also,
why did they bring us to a bakery?
What of the following has to do with bread?
- Right. - We should consider that.
What do you think the answer is?
Without thinking too hard, I say it's barley.
Barley? Why?
(Why do you think it's barley?)
Barley, barley, barley.
- What? - No reason.
No reason?
(I just think it's barley.)
- We don't have any chance cards. - The rice-barley game.
Rice and barley?
Because of the rice-barley game?
There's no reason behind it. It's a wild guess.
You can't just say it's barley.
If we get this wrong, we'll be at...
a huge disadvantage.
There's gluten in wheat.
I don't know.
- It's in wheat. - This book.
(His lack of trust makes him want to read.)
We're allowed to read, right?
- What book is that? - It was here to begin with.
A textbook for the patissier test.
- Is it in there? - Check it out, guys.
I'll find something else that could help us.
As if the answer would be in here.
(King of Reading)
It could be in here.
You never know.
(Something could be in here.)
(It has suddenly become a library.)
My gosh.
- Gliadin. - Hold on.
It could show up in this book.
"Gliadin and glutenin in flour..."
"bind together to form gluten."
"Various types of bread can be made by choosing a different flour..."
"such as medium flour, weak flour, wholemeal, rye, and others."
- That's all it says. - Right.
- That's all it says. - I have no idea.
The word glutenin is in here.
Either way, I chose my answer...
based on no exact reason.
I made an educated guess...
which is why I don't find this situation...
to be serious.
You need to take this a bit seriously.
If we get this wrong, we'll be at a huge disadvantage.
My gut is telling me it's barley.
Your gut feeling has been on point today.
- Exactly. - I want to go with your answer,
but it's too out of the blue.
The rice-barley game?
I'd love to take your side.
- If you had said... - Hyuk...
you had heard it from somewhere, I'd go with it.
If only you had lied...
- about knowing it from somewhere. - Right.
We would've gone with it.
It was too out of the blue...
which is why we can't.
I'm clueless.
I personally think it's potato.
- Potato? - What about you?
Every multiple-choice question...
has a choice that messes with your head.
See buckwheat, for example.
We see that in a lot of dishes.
I think that was put in there...
to throw us off.
It's actually gluten-free.
Let's cross out buckwheat.
Almond is...
Many times, the least suspicious one was the answer.
- We shouldn't think so much. - Potato?
(2. Buckwheat)
This is what we should do.
Let's count almond out.
If we get it wrong because it was almond,
I'll leave, saying, "Gosh. That was unfair."
- You'll leave. - As for buckwheat...
There's no way buckwheat is the answer.
That's all I can give you. Now, you two can decide.
I don't think barley has gluten.
Potato?
I'm talking in a vague way.
- The ansure is potato. - "Ansure."
The ansure is potato.
- Or... - Okay?
- Should we go for potato? - Yes.
- Potato. - It's 55 versus 45.
- Even if we get it wrong, - It's a 50 percent chance.
- let's accept the loss... - Yes.
- and move on. - Okay.
- What now? - Let's say it together.
- It's 59 versus 41. It's the same. - Okay.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Potato. - Potato.
That's your answer.
The ansure is potato.
Say "Answer," not "Ansure."
- That's our answer. - Your answer is potato.
Answer.
Potato.
That was so confusing.
(Ominous)
Please.
(A. Potato)
- Incorrect. - What was the answer?
- What was the answer? - Wait. Time out.
Just don't tell me that it was barley.
- What's the answer? - The answer is...
(Please.)
Number three, barley.
I told you!
I said it was barley.
(The rice-barley game logic was correct.)
- I told you so. - I know.
I have a good hunch today.
See? I told you that it was barley.
My hunch kept telling me that it was barely.
There was a reason why we had barley...
during the barley hump, the period of spring poverty.
- Gosh. You're good. - Yes.
But if you had explained...
the reasoning behind it a little...
Just like now, you should have said, "When we were young,"
"there was the barley hump, so I think it's the answer."
But instead, you were like, "The rice-barley game."
Gosh. Potato is gluten-free.
Let it go.
- Okay. We got it. - Okay.
- Let's go to Gimje. - Let's hurry.
- We'll get going. - To Gimje.
- We'll head to Gimje. - Where are you going again?
- To Gimje. - We'll go to the closest one.
- The closest one. - Yes. We'll go to Gimje. Let's go.
Today, we'll move along without thinking so much.
- That's what we'll do. Yes. - We'll get going.
Do you want to go to the arcade?
- Should we go to the arcade? - We have to go to the arcade too.
- Let's go to the arcade. - We have to go there.
(Searching quickly)
Haetae Arcade.
There's one nearby.
Should we walk...
- since our car is already parked? - Yes.
We'll get going.
(Iksan: Corn Toast Bread)
Gosh. That was close.
(Team Guys failed to occupy Gunsan.)
(Gunsan)
(They'll try to finish the remaining mission in Gunsan.)
(In the meantime, Team Handsome is...)
(Iksan)
Gosh. We'll get going.
(Iksan: Kimchi)
Someone can eat this.
Can you hand me the paper with the address on it?
- Kimje's C Hotteok. - C Hotteok.
We solved the quiz without using the hint.
- That was amazing. - I'm relieved.
The remaining two quizzes will be a piece of cake now.
- We can use the reattempt cards. - Exactly.
We'll arrive in just 30 minutes.
Gosh. I love it. It's a short drive.
John, I didn't know...
you were so enthusiastic about and good at variety shows.
No. I'm not that good.
Your daughter has changed you.
(Smiling)
(After getting married in 2022)
(he has become a happy father to a daughter.)
I'm jealous.
(I'm jealous.)
I thought I'd be married by now.
Did you have that feeling?
When you met your wife,
did you think, "I think I'm going to marry her."
Yes.
- I had that feeling at some point. - That exact feeling?
It was my first time to have such a feeling.
I didn't think...
- that I was going to get married. - I see.
I have a question about one thing.
Did you have a feeling that your life would be stable...
when you married her?
- Yes. - Was that it?
Of course, I love her...
as a woman too.
But at the same time,
she is someone who's stable.
She grew up in a loving home.
Her family is very harmonious.
Those aspects of her...
made me...
open my eyes about getting married.
That's awesome.
Your wife...
has a younger sister, right?
She has an older sister and a younger brother.
- A total of three. - An older sister.
Is her sister single?
She's married and lives in the US.
She's far away.
She's in America.
Just in case.
If we can be a family, it'd be...
(If we can be a family, it'd be...)
I think of you
(Meantime, in the back of the car)
(Opening the kimchi package quietly)
(Starting the mission)
It looks good.
(Taking a bite)
(Crunchy)
Kimchi can't go wrong.
- It's good. - Of course.
(Passing kimchi to the front seats)
Chopsticks.
- Please hand me the garlic bread. - Really?
(He gets the garlic bread they got as a gift from Iksan.)
It's freshly out of the oven.
(Eating the garlic bread first)
(And eating Kimchi after that)
Garlic...
is sweet.
I told you that you're my only love
It's sweet and salty.
You know how it is, right, everyone? It's the garlic.
Who are you talking to?
- You guys. - "Right, everyone?"
Everyone as in you guys.
I thought that camera was for your individual content.
It goes well with each other, Sang Uk.
Next, we'll have hotteok.
Hotteok.
Hotteok sounds good.
I love hotteok.
- Do you like hotteok? - I'm in trouble. Yes.
I always buy them whenever I see one on the streets.
You like it that much?
Especially in winter,
I have to have hotteok and fish-shaped buns.
I love the fishcake broth.
(Gosh. We just have to have it.)
I can spend 30 minutes easily while having them.
(Heading to get hotteok already appearing before them)
The fishcake broth is amazing...
- on a freezing day. - Right.
Wait. We have to study for it.
Hotteok.
What does "ho" mean in hotteok?
- "Ho?" - Do you know the answer?
- No. - Okay. Let me see.
Right. I wonder what it means.
Isn't it because you blow on it, like "Ho-ho?"
- I think I heard of that before. - But...
Then why is the steamed bun called a steamed bun?
Because they steam the bun.
- Why is hotteok... - We blow on the steamed bun too.
Called hotteok?
- Is it the AI chatbot? - Yes.
(It responds right away.)
Hotteok means rice cake from China.
- "Rice cake from China?" - "Ho" means...
It refers to foreign stuff in China in the past.
What are the other words with the letter "Ho?"
Foreign "Ho."
(The words with "Ho," which means foreign?)
Homyeon, which is glass noodles.
Hobyung, which is Jurchen warriors.
Those are some of them.
That's enough.
(That's enough.)
It won't be given as the quiz.
I think it'll be something about hotteok.
(In a moment, they'll face a shocking question.)
I wish we could have that drink.
Gosh, but we can't.
(They're on their way to an arcade nearby for a mission.)
Gosh. We can't have it.
I'll finish the mission at once.
I played Pump It Up a lot...
- when I was a college student. - I can't do it at all.
I played it a lot.
I've even beat the "Turkish March."
(Singing)
(Shadow-dancing out of the blue on a street)
(His foot skills excite them for the result.)
I played it a lot.
I remember the songs from it.
I'll finish it in five minutes.
- Please finish it in one go. - Okay.
They have it.
Show it to us.
Okay. Let's go, Dong Hyun.
(Seung Ho's in charge of the coins.)
- I'll finish it right away. - Okay.
It's hot.
We have to play the normal level.
- I can do it with the panels. - You can use the panels.
(The mission is a success...)
(if you get over Grade S on the normal level.)
- Choose a song you know. - What?
(He tries to choose a song with confidence.)
(Going through the songs one by one)
Is there an old song?
(Moving his foot with familiarity)
("Turkish March")
This one.
(What? This one.)
(It's the "Turkish March" he mentioned about on the way.)
("Turkish March" by BanYa)
I'll play the hard mode.
(He chose the hard mode boldly.)
I've played it many times before.
They have it here.
I'll complete the mission.
(Chanting)
(A wild performance is expected.)
Gosh. I remember this.
It's a hard one.
(Dong Hyun's "Turkish March" finally starts now.)
Let's go.
Wait.
(What?)
(The arrows are coming up ruthlessly.)
(Despite his confidence, his steps are tangled up.)
(Sighing)
What? It's hard.
(As the arrows go wild, )
(the train of misses goes wild too.)
I was in great shape when I was young.
I guess I was fit back then.
(His steps are lost.)
(The misses keep piling up.)
(The old me)
My legs hurt.
(I miss you.)
Gosh.
(He fails epically in 1 go.)
I was in great shape when I was 20 years old.
How can one finish it?
You should have chosen the song well.
(I'm the king of the rhythm games, Kim Dong Hyun.)
(My pride doesn't allow me to go out like this.)
I'll play at the normal level.
I guess I was fit back then.
(The former king of the rhythm games tries it for the 2nd time...)
(with his startled legs.)
(Stepping)
It's easy.
(The combo starts to pile up.)
(The hard mode versus the normal mode)
(He looks much more stable.)
It's so easy.
(Surprised)
(He has already reached 50 combos.)
It's so easy.
(I knew you could do it.)
(Dong Hyun focuses on his steps until the end.)
- It's done. - He's good.
It's done. The normal level is so easy.
(Will he make it this time?)
Let's go.
- Okay. - Okay.
(He even succeeds with a Grade S Plus.)
Yes. I got an S Plus.
- Hey. - Let's go.
Where is Seung Ho?
(He's on a claw machine because he trusts Dong Hyun.)
(Elaborate)
(He's on a mission of his own though no one asked him to.)
(In fact, he succeeds it.)
Did you get a plushie?
- I got a cute one from "Minions." - Try it.
You got one already.
- Good. - Let's go.
Let's go.
Even though I've built up my strength as an athlete,
I can't beat my youth.
My legs couldn't keep up.
After occupying Gimje,
we'll think of which way to go between the left and the right.
We've already used all the chance cards.
We've completed all missions.
But the important thing is that we didn't get any stamps.
That is the most important one.
- We've only been to one place. - Right.
We can increase them slowly.
Everything I do this,
it always feels futile when we get the question wrong.
We only get one chance.
It's so hard, isn't it?
(Will they be able to play the remaining games well...)
(without a reattempt card?)
(Team Handsome)
Gosh. This must be the busy downtown of Gimje.
- I think it's in front of us. - This is it.
We're here.
(Gimje: Hotteok)
- Thanks for driving. - It's nothing.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let's go and have some hotteok.
- Okay. - Good.
- Let's go. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
You look like you're from here.
Thank you. We heard that your hotteok was famous.
Gosh. Thank you.
Can we get three hotteok?
It's 5 dollars for 4 hotteok.
- We'll get 4, then. - Please give us 4.
- We'll have four. - Okay.
- Sang Uk will have two, right? - That's right.
Do the rock-paper-scissors, so the winner can get one more.
- He has already won. - No need.
- Look how big he is. - You should come inside.
- Thank you. - Yes.
Gosh. They look good.
- Are they taking a photo? - Yes.
- Look. - You're getting filmed.
(A regular was inside.)
- Are you here for the hotteok too? - What?
- Are you here to get some hotteok? - Yes.
How long have you come here to get hotteok?
- Here? - Yes.
Tell them that you're from this town.
It's our town's famous hotteok.
Hurry and make them.
Okay.
(He's cute.)
- Do you want the fish cake broth? - It looks good.
- I'd love to. - You too, Sang Uk?
- Yes. - You can take one.
- Thank you. - Today...
You have to put some green onions in.
(He's equipped with good sense to put some green onions in it.)
Gosh. Like I said,
you can't skip the fish cake broth.
This is the best in winter.
(You can't skip the fish cake broth on a cold day.)
It's the best to have when it's cold.
You'll be on TV.
(I love it so much.)
Do you have this hotteok frequently?
It's a bit far.
When I come to the downtown, I have it.
Gosh. It wouldn't be further than where we've come from.
We've come from Seoul.
- From Seoul? - Yes.
(We've come all the way from Seoul.)
- I've come from my town. - Is it...
- Is it far from here? - It's far.
How far is it from here?
It takes about 15 minutes.
(What? 15 minutes?)
That means it's right by here.
(It's far anyway.)
Is there something you always get here?
- What? - What is the menu you always get?
It's hotteok. What else would it be?
- And fish cake. - Hotteok.
How is this place's hotteok different from others?
It's different because it's tasty.
- We have to try it first. - Yes.
- Try it. - We should try it.
- Try many. - Okay.
- Have a safe trip home. - Okay. Enjoy.
- Thank you. - Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
He was here at the right moment.
(In the meantime, tasty hotteok is getting cooked.)
It's written here when it started.
Have you been running this place since 1994?
- I was born in 1996. - It's been almost 30 years.
- It's been 31 years. - I started in front of the J Bank.
Do you know Towner?
A small truck.
- Pardon? - Cha Eun Woo?
- Towner. - Towner.
- Towner. - It's a truck.
- It's an old one. - Right.
Right. The towner truck in the past.
It's been discontinued.
- Right. - Yes.
I ran my business in it for a few years.
Then you moved to a shop.
I've come to this place.
(Started in a small truck, she's moved to a restaurant.)
You must have made a lot of money...
back then to move here.
I made so much money.
(Cracking up)
You started your business in a truck.
- Wait. - Get the tongs...
- and take them. - I'll hold it.
- Thank you. - We'll take it.
- Do we get a set of tongs each? - Yes.
(They'll try the super tasty hotteok.)
(I say, "Ho")
(You say, "Tteok")
(Hotteok)
(Hotteok in my hand)
(Hotteok is sweet)
(Dripping with honey, sweetness overload)
(Crunchy and chewy)
(Hotteok beloved by Team Handsome)
(Give me hotteok)
(Handsome Bakery Tour 3: Hotteok of a lifetime)
(Crunchy outside, filled with honey inside)
(Shall we try Gimje's hotteok?)
We'll grab tongs.
Okay. Thank you.
- I'm happy. - Gosh. Grab it with the tongs.
Thanks for the food.
Let's grab one and try it.
- Hotteok. - When you eat it,
- fold it in half. - Should we fold it?
- Yes. Like that. - We fold it in half.
(They fold it in half as the owner suggested.)
- Cheers. - It smells amazing already.
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you. - Yes. Please enjoy.
Hold on. I can't eat it because it'll be hot.
Thank you.
(The older brothers take a bite even though it's hot.)
(Happy)
Thank you.
(Crunchy)
(They keep getting amazed with happiness.)
(Sang Uk goes for the sugar in the center first.)
(Eye-opening)
It's so good.
- This is... - When I think of it... Yes.
First of all, it's not oily.
She grilled it so well. It's crunchy.
It's not greasy.
When we have hotteok, do you know that?
It has that flour taste.
- This one doesn't have that. - Right.
- You're right? - Right?
When we eat hotteok, it always has that flour taste.
But this one doesn't have it.
(Instead of the flour taste, it's filled with sweetness.)
Also, the dough is thin.
- You're right. - That's the technique.
Is this the technique?
Yes.
Rather than honey, I can taste brown sugar...
and nuts from time to time.
- Yes. Do you smell the cinnamon? - Yes.
I like how subtle the cinnamon is.
It's subtle.
- If it was strong, I'd not like it. - That's right.
I could understand how you came to this place...
after starting from a truck.
If it's been 31 years selling hotteok...
What?
Have you been selling it since you were ten years old?
- I was young. - Come on.
Were you ten when you started selling it?
Gosh.
I've devoted my youth to it.
You got me. If it's been 30 years...
How could you do it when you were ten?
- It's hotteok filled with tears. - Gosh.
(How could you have done it since you were 10?)
The thin part is so good.
- I fold it in half, - The part with honey.
But it's still this thin.
- It's crazy. - It's crunchy outside. It's...
This part is so tasty.
I've been to many places, including the marketplace in Busan,
because I'm a big fan of hotteok.
(John Park is a hotteok lover.)
- It's hotteok of my life. - Really?
I admit it. It's the best, ma'am.
- Thank you. - Of the hotteok I had...
How do you get the ingredients?
As for the ingredients,
I get the Horizon Rice that was cultivated here in Gimje.
I use its glutinous rice powder.
(The key ingredient is glutinous rice powder.)
- It's the rice powder. - With that,
I mix it with flour for the dough.
I see.
- I see. - On our way here,
we said Gimje was famous for its rice.
- The Horizon Rice. - I see.
They also host the Gimje Horizon Festival.
- Really? - Yes.
Gosh. Don't you know about the famous Gimje Horizon Festival?
Sorry. We didn't know about it.
Do you cultivate the rice yourself?
Yes, I do.
- Really? - I do rice farming.
I also sell tteokbokki here.
- I use glutinous rice for hotteok. - It must be rice tteok.
I use the non-glutinous rice for tteokbokki.
We'll get one serving of tteokbokki.
(Out of the blue?)
Wait. We have to try it now.
- You grow rice yourself... - Yes.
- to make tteokbokki. - I do everything.
We'll get one of it.
(Just do it.)
- You don't have it? - Can you eat it, though?
Yes, we can.
(They casually add tteokbokki to their order.)
- Thank you. - It's made with the Horizon Rice.
- Yes. We'll enjoy it. - Thank you.
- Gosh. - It smells amazing.
I serve 5 pieces of tteok for 1 serving.
But I forgot to put one.
- Why? - You might be full.
- I can finish it. - She's thinking of us.
- Thank you. - She's thinking of us.
We appreciate it.
- We have to eat more later. - Yes?
(Surprised)
Hey.
One bite will already shock you.
Gosh. It tastes like home-made tteokbokki.
You can't find tteokbokki like that in Seoul, so enjoy it.
It felt like marshmallow in my mouth.
- It's the tteok made of rice. - What was that?
The texture in your mouth...
It's made of rice.
It's chewy.
The texture is incredible.
(Sang Uk is also highly satisfied.)
The food is tasty,
and the owner has incredible energy.
She has love.
- Your energy... - Thank you.
- draws people in. - That's right.
Gosh, you have a good eye.
Seriously.
(She's cute until the end.)
She's full of energy.
In Gimje,
we really enjoyed hotteok...
- by the energetic owner. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Shall we move on to the quiz? - Shall we?
(Time for Quiz)
Here comes the quiz.
"Ho" from hotteok...
(We know this!)
(John looked it up on their way here.)
means "Barbarian."
So hotteok means "Rice cake from China."
- We know that. - Yes.
We talked about it in the car.
(We studied it on our way here!)
Among the following,
which word doesn't contain "Ho,"
the character for "Barbarian?"
This is it.
You saw a few examples earlier, right?
Only a few.
It's a multiple-choice question.
Number one,
hodu or walnut.
Number two, homi or hand hoe.
- Number three, - Hand hoe?
Hobak or pumpkin.
Number four, hojumeoni or pocket.
The one that doesn't contain the character.
We need to take out walnut.
I think it means "A barbarian's head."
("Ho" for "Barbarian" and "Du" for "Head")
- "A barbarian's head?" - "Du" for "Head."
You know, "Du" is...
- Seriously, walnut... - It looks like a brain.
Looks like a brain when you open it.
A brain.
Thus,
I think it contains the character. I think pumpkin also contains it.
- I'm certain. - Your name sounds similar.
Yes.
- Hobak or pumpkin. - It isn't pumpkin.
- Pumpkin... - Only John Park...
can be a Park.
- Your name sounds similar. - There can't be pumpkin.
It isn't pumpkin.
It must be either pocket or hand hoe.
- To be honest, I have information. - What is it?
I read an article about how...
homi or hand hoe was exported overseas.
Had the word contained that character,
a different word would've been used at this point.
(Wouldn't the name have been changed?)
Maybe.
(Doesn't "Ho" from homi or hand hoe mean "Barbarian?")
Back in the day, Korean clothes didn't have pockets.
Seeing the foreigners' clothes might've changed that.
Old Korean clothes didn't have pockets.
- It's plausible. - Is that so?
- It's plausible. - As far as I know, yes.
I think it's hand hoe.
- Hand hoe. - Yes.
I suddenly think it's walnut.
(He suddenly chooses walnut.)
Things go like this.
Listen.
- You said that it wasn't walnut. - John.
- You said that first. - I just remembered something.
Walnut immediately sounds like a wrong answer, right?
It must be a trap.
Do you see why Sang Uk got the penalty three weeks in a row?
(My head hurts.)
Think about it.
Hey.
(Did Yi Kyung notice something?)
- I made deductions. - Okay.
- Hotteok. - Yes.
If we take out "Ho," one word remains.
- "Tteok" can stand on its own. - Yes.
- "Bak" can stand on its own. - Yes.
- "Jumeoni" can stand on its own. - Yes, it can.
So it's either walnut or hand hoe.
- It's a good strategy. - Right?
- "Ho" should be an addition... - That's right.
- to an existing word. - That's right.
That's right. "Ho" was added...
to a pre-existing word to denote a similar item...
- that was from China. - That's right.
- Pocket, pumpkin, and hotteok - That's right.
- So what are "Mi" and "Du?" - I don't know.
(Don't you know that?)
Can "Du" mean...
something like "Nut?"
Nuts.
- No. - We don't use "Du."
- You don't use "Du." - No.
- Nuts. - How about "Mi?"
Hand hoe is for digging.
"Mi" could mean "Flavour."
Two options remain.
- It's 1 of the 2. - It's 1 of the 2.
These are the options the two you picked.
- That's right. - One each.
- I think it's walnut. - Play rock-paper-scissors.
I think it's walnut.
- Play rock-paper-scissors. - Judging by the past...
I'll be upset if I lose in rock-paper-scissors.
Pick hand hoe then.
- If it's wrong... - I'll go with your choice next.
- Okay. - Hand hoe.
- Shall we trust him? - Which one?
- He read an article. - I...
- He read an article. - It's your intuition, right?
- It's my intuition. - It's...
the animalistic intuition of the world's number one fencer.
It's your intuition versus my knowledge that's based on...
- something I've seen. - It's my intuition.
You should pick one then.
Since it's 1 to 1, you should take a pick.
Why are you putting that burden on me?
No.
We'll follow your decision.
Which one do you think makes...
more sense?
I think...
(What's John's verdict?)
Yi Kyung promoted his answer much more diligently,
so I think we should go with that.
- Hand hoe. - He'll regret it...
if he picks walnut and it turns out to be incorrect.
- So let's go with hand hoe. - Let's use a hint if we must.
- Okay. - Let's shout it out together.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let us answer. One, two, three.
- Hand hoe. - Hand hoe.
(Hand hoe)
Correct.
Hey, you punk!
You punk!
- Lee Yi Kyung! - You punk!
- Well done. - I trusted you.
- Of course. - I trusted you.
(Yi Kyung, I trusted you.)
Walnut means "A barbarian's head," right?
"Du" comes from "Do," a character that means "Peach."
(Barbarian peach)
- So it used to be "Hodo." - Like peach.
"Hodo" became "Hodu."
It probably got its name...
because it looked like a peach.
Homi or hand hoe is pure Korean.
- Pure Korean. - See?
You're a punk like a walnut!
For goodness' sake.
Would you like a walnut?
You can see why I'm like this, right?
- Still, we did it. - We didn't use a hint.
- We had a good result. - Here.
- Gimje. - Gimje.
Hand hoe.
Walnut.
(Gimje: Hotteok)
We got hotteok in Gimje. What's the food item?
We can eat it here! Fishcake!
It's one thing we didn't eat.
(Gimje: Fishcake)
(The best snack with soup, fishcake)
It used to cost 20 cents in front of my place.
It was a long time ago.
I used to take taekwondo classes.
(A big bite)
Didn't the other team finish?
- No. - Not yet.
- Where did they go to? - Ma'am,
does squid go into fishcake?
When fortunate people eat fishcake, they taste squid as well.
(So it depends.)
It depends.
That's right.
Sometimes, fishcake is tasty. Sometimes, it isn't.
I can't believe fishcake is sold here.
- Fishcake is tasty too. - Seriously.
(They clear the mission by eating fishcake.)
Where should we go to? Gunsan?
(Team Handsome can go to the next location right away.)
- Firstly... - Gunsan.
Since we got these squares...
Let's take Gunsan. It's close from here.
Twenty-five minutes.
- Okay. - We have a reattempt card.
If we get the Gunsan square,
we just need to complete 1 of the 2 for a bingo.
- Also, - The moment it rings...
we have two unused reattempt cards.
- That's right. - Yes.
Can we trust Sang Uk's words now?
Let's see.
- Things are going as we planned. - We'll go to Gunsan.
- Let's get off work fast. - Thank you for the food.
- Thank you. - All right. Good luck.
- Okay. Have a good day. - Bye.
- Bless you. - I hope you become more successful.
It's perfect.
Good.
I can't believe our luck.
We need to go to Gunsan.
(Gimje residents recognize Team Handsome.)
(Thank you, Gimje.)
(Sang Uk bows as well.)
(They leave Gimje and drive to Gunsan.)
(Team Guys)
(Gunsan, Gimje)
(They just enter Gimje.)
(Cuckoo)
Already?
- Gimje! - Gimje?
Where should we go to then?
(Nothing is going well for Team Guys today.)
What happened?
I think we should stop.
(They stop the car for a moment.)
If they took the Gimje square...
- I think they did it to block us. - Right?
Then we have no reason to go to Imsil.
- It won't be the best choice. - That's what I think.
So why don't we go to Jeonju?
What do you think?
If we go down after visiting Jeonju,
we might only visit two places.
But if we go down right away,
we'll be able to visit three places even if we don't get the quiz right.
Hyuk, you have a good hunch. Please decide.
(It's between going to Jeonju or Buan and Jeongeup.)
I think it'll be better to go to Buan.
If we block Buan A or B...
- They took these squares. - That's right.
So we can go there and stop them from completing a bingo.
Or we can go to Buan A and B and Jeongeup.
We'll get two squares at the very least.
That's right.
They might go to Gunsan thinking, "Why didn't they go there?"
They might go to Gunsan.
- Shall we go to Buan B? - B.
Let's see how it goes and go left or right from there.
- That's right. - Either side.
- Bakery. - Bakery.
- Let's hit the road. - okay.
(Team Guys heads to Buan to attempt turning the tables.)
(Team Handsome)
(Team Handsome is heading to Gunsan as Team Guys wants.)
Today, it's like...
What is the other team doing?
We didn't hear a cuckoo in a long while.
(Why didn't we hear a cuckoo in a long while?)
It has been a while.
Seriously. It's either they failed to get the quiz right...
or they're in Imsil.
- That's the only explanation. - Yes.
Perhaps they went far to take the center square.
You know that I haven't won once, right?
Today is the day.
- Today is the day. - I lost every single time.
(Gosh, Sang Uk!)
I can win now, right?
- Us? - Me.
- We'll win if you don't insist. - We...
If I don't insist?
- It's because of my name. - We'll win if you don't do that.
Let's graduate.
(Will he graduate the title of the man with zero wins?)
I've done the penalty three times. It's enough.
I hope the other team withdraws...
for the first time in history.
(I hope the other team withdraws. for the first time in history.)
Imagine them having 1 square when we have 4 squares.
Modern Girl was the last one.
"We withdraw."
- Modern Girl was the last one. - Modern Girl was the last one.
(Will the game end as Team Handsome's victory?)
(Gunsan)
We began at the Gunsan Station...
and came back to Gunsan.
You usually feel bad in such cases, right?
I feel like we're returning home in glory.
(They get close to the destination under the clear sky.)
The clouds move so fast in the clear sky.
(The clouds move so fast in the clear sky.)
They're like us.
(They're like us.)
The clouds are moving so fast.
The tempo is fast.
- Are we here? - Yes.
We're here.
(Gunsan)
Let's go.
For some reason...
Why do I feel so relaxed?
I haven't felt this relaxed during my time on the show.
- Really? - John, you came at the right time.
I just feel like I'm touring bakeries.
It's so much fun.
(Gunsan: castella)
What kind of bread exists here?
They sell rice castella.
Rice castella?
(Will Team Handsome be able to take over Gunsan?)
How is a bakery so big?
Hello.
(Will Team Handsome be able to take over Gunsan?)
We should get rice castella, right?
Is that it?
It says, "Bakery tour."
- "Rice flour bakery tour." - I see.
- This is it. - This is it.
- Rice flour. - Rice castella.
This is it.
What was your daughter's name? So Yun?
- Seo Hyun. - Seo Hyun.
This one is for Seo Hyun.
Thank you.
- We'll get these ones. - I'll ring you up.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - There are freshly made ones.
I'll switch yours to these ones.
- They're freshly made. - They look tasty.
What a timing.
They look tasty.
(Touching)
- It's warm. - Back in the day...
They're freshly made.
It's really tasty with strawberry milk.
Go ahead and eat.
It's for your daughter, Seo Hyun.
Thank you, Yi Kyung.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
They just came out.
I should ask.
Ma'am.
Was Kim Dong Hyun here?
- Yes, he was. - What?
- Was he here? - Was he here? When?
It has been two hours, right?
It has been two hours.
- He was here. - They went to Gunsan first.
His face was dark when he left, right?
(His face was dark when he left, right?)
- Of course. - He was disappointed, right?
The alarm didn't sound.
Did he say where he was going?
He didn't say where he was going.
He just went that way.
That way? I see.
- So he was here. - Yes.
Okay. Thank you.
They visited Gunsan and Imsil,
- but failed to win a square. - That's right.
(Laughing)
We figured it out.
They came two hours ago.
Let's look at the board.
Let's make simple predictions.
The other team had monkfish and failed the quiz.
That was when they heard the alarm for Iksan.
- They were in Gunsan. - Yes.
Since we took Iksan, they headed to Gimje.
Then they heard the alarm for Gimje.
We took Gimje too.
So they probably went to Imsil or Buan.
They probably went, "This won't do."
(Their deductions are nearly precise.)
- It's so nice. Seriously. - I feel relaxed.
- This is incredible. - We're set.
Let's eat the freshly-baked ones.
(Shall we eat castella in a relaxed way?)
Since it's freshly made, it goes in when you press it.
It's soft.
It smells amazing.
It smells different.
The smell is to die for.
- It's tasty. - I feel like I'm eating a cloud.
- You're right. - That's what it feels like.
- You're right. - It's like eating a cloud.
- A cotton candy. - Yes.
I should've eaten it with a latte.
I saw at the entrance...
that he got recognized as a master in Gunsan.
He received another plaque from a Korean association.
(Patisserie and boulangerie master hand: Hong Dong Soo)
This is a master baker's place.
(A master baker made this bread.)
(At a corner of the bakery...)
(are various award certificates.)
(Who is the master baker who made the rice castella?)
- Did you enjoy it? - It was so tasty.
- It was so tasty. - Thank you.
Master.
- Hello. - Hello.
How...
did you start making bread using rice flour?
In the beginning,
I grew up in the countryside and had an interest in the Korean crops.
I had a lot of love for the Korean crops.
I thought it'd be nice to make bread using the Korean crops.
That was when I met four rice.
Flour rice.
How is flour rice different from regular rice?
Flour rice is the name of the variety.
(Flour rice)
(It has the taste and nutrients of regular rice.)
(But it has been improved for easier processing.)
So it isn't...
- It isn't blended rice. - No.
It's an improved variety.
That's why it's different.
So it's the best rice variety...
- for making bread. - That's right.
After the flour rice came out,
I began making gluten-free products.
- You don't make wheat flour at all. - No.
Is this 100-percent rice flour?
- That's right. - One hundred percent?
I met flour rice by chance.
I signed contracts with the farmers.
Then I milled and powdered the rice.
I used to do that.
That was when I began making bread with rice.
(He studied breadmaking using the Korean rice.)
The first successful product was castella.
(Rice castella became...)
(the most famous.)
(Most of other products are made with flour rice!)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Okay. Enjoy the bread.
(While they check out bread with love for the Korean crops)
We have 4.5km left to go.
Without thinking about anything else,
we should go to Buan B and answer the quiz correctly.
Then we should take food to go.
(Take the mission food to go.)
Then we should put them to sleep and go to Buan A.
- If we do that, we won't lose. - Okay.
That only works if we get all the quizzes right.
(But they must get all the quizzes right.)
If we get the quiz wrong for the steamed bun square,
we'll have no ways to stop them from making a bingo.
- That's right. - We'll need to wait.
We won't be able to do anything.
(They'll cross their arms and watch.)
The lack of reattempt cards makes us dispirited.
I see that the reattempt cards are very powerful.
They're so powerful.
What are we eating here?
We're going to Buan B, so it's steamed bun.
- Steamed bun. - Steamed bun.
Hearing the name...
suddenly makes me crave for steamed buns.
(His mouth waters.)
The red bean paste should feel hot in the mouth.
It should be hot enough to burn.
Eating a hot red bean steamed bun...
with milk is the best.
(He loves milk.)
You drink so much milk.
It goes well with milk.
The combination is perfect.
Castella and steamed bun are the same.
Which question will we get for steamed bun?
I'll study up on steamed bun.
What's the difference between steamed bun and hoppang?
(What is it?)
What is it?
I don't know. I just thought of the question.
(Gosh, Dong Hyun)
Hoppang...
It could be a question.
(It's a good prediction.)
Steamed bun has red bean paste inside.
How did the filling come to be?
Who began adding the red bean paste?
(Handsome Bakery Tour 4)
(A steamed bun place next to a salt farm)
(It's next to Gomso Salt Farm which is the pride of Buan.)
(Buan's steamed bun place)
(Buan: Steamed bun)
(On holidays, it's full of customers from all over the nation.)
(It's a popular destination for the bakery tour.)
(They arrive when the snow begins to fall.)
Thank you.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Welcome.
Gosh, the atmosphere is incredible.
- This place is fun. - The atmosphere is incredible.
- We're doing a bakery tour. - Okay.
Many people visit this place for a bakery tour, right?
Yes. Many people visit. We're grateful for it.
(CEO, Lee Jong Ho)
Which product is famous?
Our steamed bun is famous.
If you make a round, you'll see the kinds.
(The display is full of bread.)
- Steamed bun is famous. - Steamed bun.
- All of these are steamed buns. - All of these are steamed buns.
(They aren't the typical steamed buns...)
They aren't the steamed buns I had in mind.
(you see every day.)
(There are 10 kinds of steamed buns.)
Milk cream steamed bun.
I'll eat this one.
It's heavy.
You're right. It's heavier than I expected.
There's a lot inside.
- It's heavy. - You know how it is.
It'll be full of white cream when you open it.
Salted steamed bun.
It's two per person.
Our products run out very fast.
Customers can't buy them if they come in the evening.
That makes me buy two.
- One warm steamed bun. - One warm steamed bun.
- Two, please. - Two warm steamed buns.
(They finish ordering steamed buns.)
Many places sell steamed buns.
- Most steamed buns are tasty. - Yes.
What's different about your father's recipe?
My father...
began making steamed buns in 1999.
We've made steamed buns using the crops from Buan...
for 20 years.
(It began as a steamed bun place in the neighbourhood.)
(It grew in size.)
(The current place came to be after 26 years.)
Most steamed buns only has red bean paste inside.
- As you can see, - Yes.
We have a variety.
- They're original recipes. - Yes.
I'm sorry, but who's Seul Ji from the store name?
It's my older sister.
So Mr. Jong Ho, your older sister...
No. We're the same age.
- Really? - Yes.
You guys are the same age.
(Embarrassed)
Right. I just look a bit old.
- He looks pretty old too. - No. I look old too.
You two should both be friends.
(The men born in 1995 can really relate to each other.)
- You were born in 1995? - Yes. I was born in 1995.
I see.
We'll try them.
Awesome.
I'm really curious.
First,
I'll cut these two up.
- Right. - Let's give them a try.
Go ahead and try them.
(Representative dish, salted steamed bun)
Give it a try.
- I'll take this one. - Here.
(How does it taste?)
It's neat.
Gosh.
(Seung Ho takes a bite too.)
I love salted buns.
This is totally my style.
This is something you can't stop eating.
- In the past... - It does feel like a steamed bun.
The alcohol bun.
- Right. - The alcohol bun.
- At Namhansanseong, - Right.
There were trucks that sold alcohol buns.
It's the alcohol bun,
- but it's salted. - Right.
It has a salty taste...
and the grease is left on your hand...
just like the usual salted bun.
It's good.
(This is how the addicting salted steamed buns are made.)
(The steamed bun dough is taken out into balls.)
(They are rolled out into shape...)
(and spread out with the rolling pin.)
(The butter made with Gomso salt is placed inside...)
(and it's rolled up.)
(The dough for the salted steamed bun is ready.)
(They are steamed in the steamer for 30 minutes.)
(The salted steamed bun gets cooked.)
(The cooked salted steamed bun gets coated with melted butter...)
(and it is ready to eat.)
It's good.
(The final boss of an addicting taste)
You might end up eating ten of these once you start.
Do you want to try something else...
- or have the same one again? - Let's try something else.
Let's try something else. Let's go with this one.
Gosh, it's good.
(Milk cream steamed bun)
I'm curious to see how it looks when it's cut in half.
- It's full of cream. - Gosh.
You can already tell it will taste good.
(Passing it to Seung Ho)
Thank you.
(The youngest one takes a bite first.)
When it's split into half at the start...
(Amazed)
(The barley guy takes a bite too.)
Gosh.
(Nodding)
This just has to be good.
(Dong Hyun takes a bite too.)
(Amazed)
It's so good.
It's just good.
(Thrilled)
It's fluffy like foam,
but the cream isn't greasy. It must be handmade.
I've never tried anything like this.
(Landing on his lips even with a slight touch)
It washes away my concerns.
This is so good.
The cream is amazing.
(The magical cream that makes you feel better)
- This is the red bean steamed bun. - Right.
The red bean steamed bun.
This is how it's served?
(Warm red bean steamed bun)
This is amazing.
I'll give it a try.
- We can each have one. - Gosh, it's hot!
Steamed buns have to be hot to be good.
The buns here are pretty heavy.
It's heavy...
because there's so much red bean paste inside.
The dough is thin...
and you can see the red bean paste inside.
(The barley guy that wanted the steamed bun...)
(carefully takes a bite.)
This is it.
(Greatly satisfied)
(He takes a bite of the hot steamed bun he was excited for.)
They must've crushed the red beans for the paste.
- Right. - Right.
You can feel the beans.
(You can feel the beans in the bun filled with paste.)
Gosh, it's hot.
- Gosh, it's hot! - This is the original steamed bun.
You know how Dong Hyun looks like...
- characters of old cartoons, right? - Me?
He's like the character from "Black Rubber Shoes."
Gosh, it's good.
(Laughing)
It's good.
(He takes another bite while enduring the heat.)
The other buns are good,
but this one brings back memories.
- Right. - This is what it's like.
I wasn't going to have it.
(A line of evaluation for the red bean steamed bun)
We ate all of them.
(Classic is permanent.)
My body is starting to sweat now.
It's definitely about the steamed bun or red bean paste.
It's definitely about the steamed bun or red beans.
Red beans.
(Red beans)
Were they eaten during Dano?
- Dongzhi. - Oh, right.
Sorry.
(Embarrassed)
- I'm sorry. - No. That can happen.
Right. It's a social phenomenon.
- It's a social phenomenon. - It can happen.
It's because I know a lot of things.
(Buan B, steamed bun)
(Quiz time)
Here's the quiz.
In the "The Collected Works of Lee Deok Moo..."
written by Lee Deok Moo, a Silhak scholar...
of the latter period of the Joseon Dynasty,
the recipe of this bread is recorded like this.
"A small box of fine flour and 1200g of white sugar..."
"is made into a dough with eight eggs."
"It's put into a copper pot..."
"and cooked until it is yellow with a charcoal fire."
What kind of bread is this?
What is it?
(Does he know this?)
- The castella! - The castella?
- The castella. - The castella!
- You're right. - The castella!
(Are they getting the answer at once so easily like this?)
- You're right. - This is why I know this.
People will think this to themselves.
"How was castella around back then?"
- They were around! - They were around!
They were pronounced differently.
"Gastella?" "Gasutella?"
The word was written with Chinese characters.
At the latter period of the Joseon Dynasty,
all kinds of Western products have already been brought in.
Right.
It was the time when Western products from places like...
the Netherlands and the US have all come in.
For at least once,
I wanted a question to be asked that could be answered right away.
So you're 100-percent certain.
I'm 137-percent certain.
I'm 20,000-percent certain.
- All right. - Okay.
Okay.
The answer is "castella."
- "Castella." - Yes.
Don't even look at them.
- You said you were certain. - Forget it.
Let's just eat. Get ready for the next one.
- "Castella." - You never know.
I might collapse if it's incorrect.
Correct!
I told you it was correct.
- It was castella. - Finally!
(Touched)
That was amazing.
(Feeling emotional)
Dong Hyun talked about this...
- all day long. - Right.
For at least once,
I wanted a question that I could answer right away.
Right. One must study.
Back then, it was called "gasujeora."
- Right. "Gasujeora!" - You were close.
It was "gasujeora."
- "Gasujeora!" - "Gasujeora!"
"Gasujeora!"
(Buan B, steamed bun)
This place feels great.
- Right. It has a great energy. - Thank you for letting us leave...
with a great feeling.
It should feel greasy, but it doesn't taste that way at all.
(The Bakery Tour Race continues.)
(Current score tied at 2 to 2.)
(They don't have the reattempt card, )
(but Team Guys is on fire.)
(In the end, )
(they take the lead.)
(A win even without the reattempt card?)
(We can't stay back like this.)
(Sang Uk goes for the answer.)
(No. Go back.)
(You jerk! Get away, you demon!)
(This happened because of the demon of incorrect answers, Sang Uk?)
(I have no clue.)
(Even John who had everyone's trust starts wavering.)
(They even use up their reattempt cards.)
(We need to make a big move to take the win!)
(The last hope)
(Imsil, cheesecake)
(The one who takes the center will take the win?)
(Set the flag at Imsil to take the win.)
(At the end of this crazy and unpredictable race, )
(which team will end with a smile?)
(I'm desperate to win.)
(Which team will take the win?)
("LIKE A DREAM" by John Park)