(The second exploration, South Jeolla Province)
(A special guest invited to South Jeolla Province)
(Choo Sung Hoon)
(I'm fine among middle-aged men.)
(The race starts.)
(Today's Handsome Heritage: Traditional liquor)
Today, having meals is mandatory.
(The center always has an advantage in bingo.)
(Both teams sprint to Gangjin.)
(Please put the other team to sleep.)
(By using the nap card, )
(Team Guys got ahead.)
(With their strong spirit, they won Gangjin.)
(Meanwhile, Team Handsome arrived in Jangheung.)
(By using their reattempt card, )
(Team Handsome chased after Team Guys.)
(Team Handsome's next destination was Yeongam.)
(Current score: 1 to 1)
(Team Guys arrived at Yeongam first.)
(They face a crisis after failing to win.)
(Team Handsome cleared the happy birthday mission.)
(They also used their last reattempt card.)
(They turned the tables by winning Yeongam.)
(Commanding)
(Will Team Handsome remain high-spirited until the end?)
(Team Guys)
Goodness.
We should have won Yeongam instead.
(After failing in Yeongam, they head to Haenam.)
If we did, the game would be over.
Since the other team went to Yeongam,
- we are...
- We must block them.
The odds are stacked against us.
We lost two reattempt cards.
We also have to go to karaoke.
If we win today, it will be a major reversal.
- Right.
- Yes.
- We're at a disadvantage now.
- We're losing.
- Let's forget about the past.
- Okay.
Just think about our accomplishments.
- We'll go to Haenam and win.
- Yes.
- Let's see.
This time, it's makgeolli.
Let's go again.
(Handsome Heritage 4: Makgeolli with deep roots)
(Exclaiming)
They won the Grand Award in 2024.
(You can tell their reputation and quality on the banner.)
Hello.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Nice to meet you. Hello.
What kind of place is it that you won the Grand Award?
Please come in.
Gosh, you traveled far.
It was worth the trip. What a nice place.
(Food is welcoming Team Guys.)
(Welcome, it's makgeolli this time.)
This is Samsan-myeon, Haenam in South Jeolla Province.
- Samsan-myeon?
- Samsan-myeon.
In Haenam,
the most famous mountain is called Mount Duryun.
(Mount Duryun, the most famous mountain in Haenam)
Underneath Mount Duryun...
is 1,000-year-old Daeheungsa Temple,
which is listed as UNESCO World Heritage Site.
The place is visited the most...
by tourists in Haenam.
That's where our brewery is located.
I cannot tell you the exact year,
but according to the elder local residents,
this brewery started...
in the 20s or 30s.
It means that it's been almost 100 years.
As for my family, my grandfather...
started operating this brewery in 1950.
- Was that your grandfather?
- Yes.
Then my parents took charge of the brewery.
After working in the city, I left work...
to run this brewery.
You're running it with your nephew who is the fourth generation.
Yes.
If the children of the family are interested in working here,
it must mean that the business is going well.
- Right.
- Exactly.
Behind you,
- there's a drawing.
- That drawing.
It was drawn in 2019 by an artist...
who was a big fan of our makgeolli.
My parents ran the brewery when it looked like that.
You can feel affection in the drawing.
In order to continue running...
the brewery for four generations,
the facility was too old.
That's why we modernized...
- You modernized it?
- and renovated the facility.
- In the same place?
- Yes, exactly the same.
I see.
You should taste some first...
- Sure.
- before I introduce our makgeolli.
We'll serve you.
Goodness.
- Is this first?
- Yes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- I feel nervous.
- That's good.
Thank you.
(What's the alcohol content?)
- It's six percent.
- Six percent?
Yes, it's six percent.
This makgeolli's alcohol content is six percent.
For the production of our makgeolli,
we have never changed...
my parents' recipe.
- So this is the original.
- In this region,
this is the farmers' favorite in Haenam.
- It's loved by many people.
- They drink it for snacks.
Compared to regular makgeolli, you'll notice that...
it has an unusual flavor.
- Right.
- Is it ginseng flavor?
I tasted some ginseng.
- Many people taste...
- Wild ginseng.
Ginseng or wild ginseng...
- in the makgeolli.
- Right.
Actually, it's not ginseng, but dong quai.
- I see.
- Dong quai?
(Dong quai?)
There's a story behind why we added dong quai.
My parents used to deliver makgeolli...
in containers on their bikes.
Their customers kept making this request.
"Please make regional makgeolli..."
"with a distinguishing taste."
- They wanted it customized.
- Right.
My parents added various ingredients to experiment.
Among them, dong quai gave...
a subtle flavor.
It also neutralized...
the sweet flavor in makgeolli that could be unpleasant.
That's why for the makgeolli with six percent alcohol,
we follow my parents' recipe even now.
- It's quite unique.
- Yes.
There's something different about it.
After making this makgeolli for years,
I thought of making alcohol that fits the trend.
- Right.
- By using glutinous rice...
and non-glutinous rice grown in this region,
we increased the concentration without artificial sweeteners.
With rich flavors from the ingredients,
we made makgeolli with nine percent alcohol content.
- What's this?
- The concentration...
It's clearly different.
It's much thicker.
You're right.
(How does the makgeolli taste with 9 percent alcohol content?)
- Hey.
- Yes?
It's definitely different.
What does it taste like?
- I'm sorry, but...
- It's very different.
I apologize to your parents, but this is better.
(I'm sorry, but I like this more.)
The family recipe is good, but...
People these days might prefer this.
You can see from the glasses that it's thicker.
Wait, the taste is...
It's simply delicious.
- To be honest...
- I bet it sells well.
(Now that they did some tasting...)
It's time for our quiz.
- Thank you.
Let's get it right. Seriously.
Let's do it this time.
(Cuckoo)
Yeongam.
- Okay, we got it.
- They won Yeongam?
- Didn't I tell you before?
- Yes.
What time is it exactly?
(Yeongam, Gangjin, Jangheung)
Between 2:30pm and 3pm...
We'll finish...
answering the quiz by 2:40pm.
If they win Yeongam,
we'll hear the cuckoo sound before we answer the quiz.
We can feel positive about this...
because they took longer than we expected.
We need to win this. Otherwise, we're doomed.
- Then it's over for us.
- If we get it wrong,
- The game is over.
- we'll surrender.
Surrender?
(He declares to surrender if they fail.)
- We have to surrender.
- Right.
(There's nowhere to back down.)
- Here's your quiz.
- Please.
(It's time to answer the quiz.)
What goes inside the makgeolli...
with six percent alcohol that you just tasted?
- Dong quai.
Correct, dong quai is added.
In the past, women packed dong quai...
for their husbands on their way to join the war.
Please describe the meaning of dong quai's Chinese characters.
(Sighing)
- Are you kidding me?
- Let's give it a try.
We just need to know the Chinese characters for dong quai.
It was given to husbands on their way to war.
It probably meant, "Come back home alive."
"Come back home alive."
What's wrong? Have you given up?
I'm thinking.
Wait, could you say the question again?
In the past, women packed dong quai...
for their husbands on their way to join the war.
- They gave them dong quai.
- It's where it comes from.
Come back home alive.
Quai must mean "return."
What could "dong" mean?
Come back safely.
What are some Chinese characters for "dong?"
(The meaning of "dong")
Darling?
(The meaning of "dong" is darling?)
(Darling?)
Darling, you're cute.
(Laughing)
I'm sorry.
Does it come from "no doubt?"
Of course, you have to come back?
Say words that start with "dong."
- Carrots.
- No doubt.
Phrases like "no doubt."
- That's what I thought.
- No doubt.
- Right away?
- Right away.
Return right away?
Is it "darling, come home?"
- Darling, you're cute.
- I mean...
(There he goes again.)
Darling, you're cute.
He can't let go of "cute."
He's obsessed with "cute."
Let's think of it this way.
Maybe it's related to safety.
- I'll be the wife.
- Going to the war.
- You will be...
- This is dong quai.
(Husband Yi Kyung on his way to war and Wife Seung Ho who sees him off)
I'm leaving.
Honey.
I can't think of anything but "darling, you're cute."
I can't think of anything else.
I'll stay out of it.
I'll just think alone.
I can't think of anything but "darling, you're cute."
To your husband on his way to war, "darling, you're cute?"
- You're so cute.
- Like a toy?
This is a tragic situation.
I might not come back from the war.
It could be our last time.
"Please take care."
- "Just come back alive." - Right, that's what it means.
- That's what I would say.
- Me too.
- I'll trust Tae Hyun this time.
- Okay.
Last time, Seung Ho answered. Tae Hyun should answer this time.
I'll answer the next one.
(Suddenly, the quiz is assigned.)
I'll just... Here I go.
Come back without a doubt.
- If I'm wrong...
- Dong quai...
given to their husbands on their way to war.
Does dong quai mean "come back without a doubt" in Chinese?
(A feeling of anxiety sweeps over them.)
If it's wrong...
(They must guess correctly this time.)
I don't think that it's correct.
(What will happen to Team Guys?)
Correct.
(Correct!)
(Tae Hyun's answer brought back hope.)
What does "dong" mean?
Dong quai means "returning naturally."
- That's what it means.
- "Naturally?"
- Is that what "dong" means?
- Return without a doubt.
Does it mean "naturally?"
For their husbands...
to return home without a doubt from the war,
they gave them dong quai.
- I mean...
- It also meant...
something that gave you energy...
when you're exhausted.
- Darling, you're cute.
(Haenam B, Makgeolli)
Now that we're full, let's go to a sauna.
(Exclaiming)
That sounds perfect.
- It's a routine for athletes.
- Routine.
Speaking of which, there's a public bath right in front of us.
(Lucky Team Handsome)
It's unbelievable.
- Here's a public bath.
- Here it is.
It's written "sauna."
(Cuckoo)
Haenam B.
(Haenam B, Makgeolli)
Haenam B? That's where they went.
They went there to block us.
They'll probably head to Suncheon next.
It means that they used their GPS.
- Right.
- They used it.
Should we head to Naju right away?
I think we should.
- Then let's go.
- Shall we?
We came all the way here.
We should have heard "Naju."
What would be better than blocking Suncheon?
While they eat, should we block Suncheon?
Or should we complete ours quickly?
If we block Suncheon,
the number of wins will matter, and we would still win.
That's true.
Let's go there.
- Should we go to Suncheon?
- Let's go to Suncheon.
- They probably took off already.
- It'll take an hour.
- No.
They must still be eating.
- Right.
- Tae Hyun would refuse to eat.
Still, we'll arrive around the same time.
We'll head to Suncheon.
(In a hurry, they set off to Suncheon.)
We wanted to avoid Suncheon, but we end up going there.
(From Yeongam to Suncheon)
(It'll take 1 hour and 10 minutes.)
(They hurry in order to win Suncheon first.)
(On their way, they volunteer to take a nap.)
(Team Guys)
Nothing is in moderation here.
They prepared us a feast.
(Haenam, wild vegetables set menu)
(A table full of food)
There's so much good food.
Isn't this yellow croaker?
It looks so plump.
Kimchi and salted seafood.
(Delicious seasoned vegetables with seafood)
(Shall we eat with makgeolli flavored with dong quai?)
- Darling, you're cute.
- Either way...
- It tastes good.
They were notified.
We will depart at 4pm.
- At 4pm?
- Yes.
This fish looks amazing.
What's this anyway?
Isn't this yellow croaker?
It looks delicious.
(Taking a bite of the plump fish)
(It's good.)
Look at the deodeok.
Deodeok with makgeolli...
- That's all you need.
- Darling, you're cute.
The skate looks cute too.
(Seung Ho devours skate first.)
It could cause big trouble.
This is amazing.
(Between two members with a big appetite)
Is there a store that makes this japchae?
(Tae Hyun with a small appetite)
They must serve everything with ginseng.
(He eats...)
(and eats.)
On our way back...
(Tae Hyun's chopsticks move endlessly.)
I'm sure that they'll eat together.
This is amazing.
I'm eating.
(Humming)
It's delicious.
- What did you eat?
- Oysters.
Oysters?
It's my first time hearing him hum after eating.
(Look at this.)
You're eating with such gusto.
(Delicious food pairing that increases the appetite)
This is healthy.
Why aren't they calling us?
Shouldn't we tell them that we'll finish in Suncheon?
Yi Kyung is calling me.
(Interested)
(Focused)
- He's calling you?
- Hello?
- Tae Hyun.
- Hey.
You used the GPS at the right time.
How do you know that?
It's obvious.
You don't know.
You could have gone to Jindo or Naju,
but you went straight to Haenam.
You probably realized that we went to Yeongam from the GPS.
Instead of going to the bakery in Yeongam,
didn't you go somewhere else?
Yes.
The owner told us.
How did you find out?
He told us that you stopped by.
Do you have his phone number?
(What?)
Dong Hyun, let me tell you one thing.
We didn't use the GPS. We saw you.
You saw us?
Yes, we saw you in Yeongam.
Really?
We'll go to Suncheon and finish the game.
Just stay warm in the sauna.
Let's see who gets there faster.
We're approaching Naju right now.
All right.
- Bye.
- Talk to you later.
(He hangs up quickly after a war of nerves.)
They're heading to Suncheon after all.
They want to see who gets there faster.
(Their plan worked.)
He simply told us.
(Information about the opponents is easy to find out.)
Today,
we'll go with Seung Ho's strategy.
We won't complete the bingo today.
Until 8pm tonight,
we'll keep winning the squares.
We're serious.
(Inside the van on their way to Haenam B)
(Seung Ho noticed something on the karaoke card.)
It says here on the karaoke card.
Instead of completing the bingo,
if we decide to keep winning the squares,
we won't have to use this card.
(It must be used before completing the bingo.)
(Seung Ho interpreted the card logically.)
Why you... Seung Ho finished adapting to the show.
Please keep it a secret.
Directors, please keep this promise.
You can't call them.
Seriously.
Where are we going next?
Let's go to Haenam A.
(Haenam A, makgeolli)
We'll be in big trouble if they arrive before us.
- In Suncheon?
- Yes.
We'll probably get there first.
- We'll get there first.
- Right.
(Naganeupseong Folk Village in Suncheon)
(Next to Naganeupseong fortress walls that are well preserved)
(There's a brewery that makes a traditional taste.)
(Takju)
I think we got here first.
It looks very traditional here.
It looks beautiful.
It looks traditional.
(What kind of traditional liquor will they find in Suncheon?)
It looks amazing.
This is someone's house.
Right.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- I'm Oh Sang Uk.
Nice to meet you.
Please have a seat before the introduction.
We're three big men.
The wooden bench is small...
for men with big builds.
When it comes to Korean alcohol,
most people only know about makgeolli, dongdongju, and soju.
Actually, makgeolli is one of various types of takju.
We repeat the process of making...
in order to increase the taste and the alcohol content.
As a result, there are many types of takju.
(Various types of takju can be made.)
At my brewery, we repeat the process three times.
It's called Samyangju.
"Sam" means three, "yang" means to make, and "ju" is alcohol.
In other words, it was made by fermenting it three times.
- So it has a high alcohol content.
- I see.
It's about 15 percent.
- That's as much as wine.
- Wine?
When alcohol is fermented several times,
you can taste various flavors of fruit or flowers.
- You'll find out soon.
- Okay.
Takju should be shaken before drinking.
That's right.
When you shake makgeolli,
- most people...
- Doesn't it explode?
He didn't get scared.
Please be careful.
He could react to your movement.
- I would react out of habit.
- Out of habit.
Please be careful.
If not, you might get hurt.
Even if you shake this,
- it won't overflow at all.
- You're right.
(Takju doesn't overflow.)
- Is it makgeolli without gas?
- There's no gas in it.
- All the makgeolli...
- Why is that?
That we tasted today was carbonated.
Sometimes, carbon dioxide that's formed is...
- kept in the bottle.
- Right?
Do you get rid of the carbon dioxide?
Carbon dioxide disappears naturally when it's fermented for a long time.
It disappears into the air.
- Would you like to try some?
- Yes.
- I'll serve Sung Hoon first.
- Thank you.
I can tell that he likes makgeolli.
He's a big fan.
- Thank you.
- He's someone with depth.
Thank you.
Here you go.
(All of them are served thick-looking takju.)
Thank you.
(Sung Hoon smells it first.)
- Thank you.
- It smells like makgeolli.
Thank you for the drink.
Please try it.
It's quite strong.
Yes, it has a high alcohol content.
- This tastes good.
- It tastes sweet to me.
- I like when it's sweet.
- There's a strong aftertaste.
It's made only with rice, traditional nuruk,
- and underground bedrock water.
- I see.
The sweet taste comes...
from the natural sweetness of rice.
We went around all day today to taste makgeolli.
I didn't know that it could be this good.
- Makgeolli tastes so good.
- It's delicious.
It's good enough to sell abroad.
I agree. Can we try other alcohol?
This is cheongju.
It's alcohol that's transparent.
I'll serve the one whose glass is empty.
Thank you.
(Sung Hoon savors the drink slowly.)
(How does cheongju taste?)
Gosh.
It tastes good.
This tastes really good.
This tastes much better.
Many people would drink this because they like the flavor.
You know what it tastes like?
Orange or yuzu.
- Or tangerine.
- You have a keen sense of taste.
It's like wine flavored with tangerine.
Of all that we tasted today,
- this is my favorite.
- Really?
It was fermented by nuruk.
There are different types of yeast inside the nuruk.
As they interact,
they create delicious flavors that are different every time.
It's a natural product.
I see.
(Thanks to nature)
After Korea gained independence,
making alcohol without a license was prohibited.
We weren't allowed to make alcohol at home.
Do you know why?
It was called the Grain Management Act.
As people didn't have enough rice to eat,
we weren't allowed to waste rice on making alcohol.
(Exclaiming)
- We couldn't answer that.
- We should've come here first.
- I know.
(Regretful)
- Was that your quiz?
- Yes.
You told us so naturally.
We should've come here first. You're right.
Instead of eating, they made alcohol with rice.
(They regret on the timing.)
You offered us good alcohol.
- It was a great experience.
- Thank you.
Please support Korean alcohol.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
(Team Guys)
The wind is strong, and I'm full.
- I can't believe that we're here.
- This place...
(Haenam A, makgeolli)
- We came to the famous brewery.
- Unbelievable.
(Next to the wide field in Haenam)
(A simple brewery is located.)
(They're leading the enhancement of Korean traditional liquor.)
(Brewery with a beautiful garden, 1927)
(What kind of story will they hear at this place?)
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
I recognize you.
- Hello.
- He's also dressed.
Welcome.
I know the brand because it's so famous.
- It's impossible to visit here.
- Right.
Now that you're here today,
please enjoy 100 years of history.
- And taste our products.
- That's nice.
We'll enjoy 100 years of history.
A hundred years of history.
(We will enjoy 100 years of history.)
It looks different up close.
(Impressed)
Look at this tree.
All the trees look old.
Look at this tree. It looks amazing.
(When you follow Team Guys and go inside the brewery, )
(you find yourself in a beautiful garden.)
(Various trees each with history of its own)
(Meow)
This is a crape myrtle.
- You can tell that it's very old.
- Right.
The tree isn't dead, right?
Right, it's about 800 years old.
This is unbelievable.
(A crape myrtle that's about 800 years old)
Do the flowers bloom in the spring?
Flowers bloom when we plant rice seedlings.
Flowers stay alive for 100 days until rice gets harvested.
- That's where the name comes from?
- Yes.
(Crape myrtle, flowers bloom around July.)
This tree is also...
Every tree at this place is like treasure.
(Every tree at this place is like treasure.)
Goodness, the cats look adorable.
Kittens.
(Cats run around freely in the brewery.)
Did these cats come from...
They were born here.
Were they born here?
I feed them.
I take care of them and take them to the doctor.
(Amazing)
What's that?
This is...
a brewery where we make alcohol.
- To pay respect to the deity...
- Deity?
(There's a mysterious bell on one side of the garden.)
I ring the bell every morning and night before praying.
(He prays and rings the bell for the alcohol to taste good.)
When you ring the bell three times,
the deity will give you health and luck.
Please help Handsome Guys be successful.
(Please help Handsome Guys be successful.)
Please make Team Handsome fail.
(Laughing)
Please help us get off work first.
(He doesn't forget to wish for getting off work.)
My wishes will come true.
(Will they?)
(Team Guys spots something.)
Take a look at how we make hard rice.
I've never seen anyone make hard rice.
(White steam rises from a huge container.)
(Hard rice is getting cooked.)
It smells like rice.
So this is how it's done.
- Did the steam make it expand?
- Yes.
How does this work?
- It's being cooked with steam.
- Steam?
Is it how it's made?
Hard rice shouldn't be overly cooked.
- It should be nice and firm.
- Right.
(Fascinating)
How much rice is inside?
I would say...
about 400kg.
(No way.)
- It's cooking 400kg of rice.
- Yes.
(With organic glutinous rice that's milled once in two days)
(Nice and firm hard rice is cooked.)
- You should taste some.
- Yes.
You came a long way.
We have three different types.
It has 9, 12, and 18 percent alcohol.
- They have 18 percent.
- You have 18 percent?
That's right.
I'll serve the one in the middle.
- Thank you.
- He's the eldest among us.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
(Thank you.)
This is...
makgeolli with guts.
(Makgeolli with guts)
- This makes me happy.
- Thank you.
- I'll drink some with you.
- Sure.
- You should serve him a drink.
- I'll serve you.
Its alcohol content is nine percent,
- but it's very thick.
- It's really thick.
- Thank you for inviting us.
- Thank you.
(Smiling)
(Nodding)
It's incredible.
This is...
I've had this often.
(Smiling big)
It's good.
I might be imagining it,
- but drinking it at its brewery...
- Right.
- It has 12 percent.
- Will you open it right away?
Yes.
He's nice and speedy.
- You'll open it now?
- Goodness.
He seems to understand...
our situation very well.
It's called supposition.
(The feeling of incorrect answer still lingers.)
I'd like to ask before getting too drunk.
How did you start this brewery?
- I'd like to hear your story.
- It's nothing special.
I came to visit here 20 years ago.
I loved the makgeolli so much that I often got it delivered.
That's how I got to know the owner.
He didn't have a successor,
so he asked me to do it.
It's been 20 years since I moved here.
- Were you a frequent customer?
- Yes.
You must have loved makgeolli a lot.
It was possible because he was a frequent customer.
Life happens according to your relationships.
You must love drinking.
You're truly a frequent customer.
That's why.
- Let's drink some.
- Hey.
What are you looking at?
- Were you sleeping?
- No.
The brewery owner is...
(We should taste the one with 12 percent.)
The packaging...
- of this bottle is golden.
- It's the bottle cap.
It's the limited edition.
Thank you.
(They also try makgeolli with 18 percent alcohol.)
It tastes better and better.
- Right.
- My goodness.
Why doesn't it taste stronger?
When you drink this...
It's only for tasting.
Do you have an appointment after this?
We haven't finished this one.
This isn't bad. Don't stop him.
Yes, but it has 65 percent alcohol.
- We are...
- He's being understanding.
He's being very generous.
Gosh, what's that?
- It's a golden shot glass.
- Where did it come from?
(Laughing)
Where did that come from?
Have a drink.
In a golden glass?
(Try the hard liquor in a golden shot glass.)
This tastes good because it's made with love.
Doesn't the 65 percent taste smooth?
I might not finish it.
(The thick concentration makes him dizzy.)
It tastes really good.
It tastes good and strong.
Gosh.
This is fascinating. My throat feels okay,
- but my chest...
- It burns inside.
I don't feel cold anymore.
Right.
(The vibe gets friendly instantly.)
(Moving about)
Keep it hidden from him.
(He hid the golden shot glass.)
If that disappears...
(Something falls into it.)
It fell so beautifully.
Could you get a close shot of this?
A leaf fell into it right now.
Doesn't it look pretty?
People who like to drink would know.
(Well, it looks okay.)
People call your makgeolli...
the best makgeolli of all.
Is there a reason why you do this?
Do you have a goal?
Alcohol isn't necessarily healthy,
but life is a series of stresses.
Instead of living under stress for five years without drinking,
I'd rather live ten years while drinking good alcohol.
I believe that it's a contribution to the country.
(Living happily for a long time while drinking good alcohol)
- Making good alcohol is your goal?
- Right.
(His goal is to make good alcohol.)
I'd like to make alcohol that makes us healthy.
This wasn't just about makgeolli.
We got a glimpse of the brewery owner's...
- sense of romance and life.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Thank you very much for inviting us.
- I'll take the glasses back.
- The glasses?
Goodness.
- Thank you.
That was amazing.
- Now...
- While being joyful,
shall we answer the quiz?
- Okay.
- Let's focus.
Let's try...
to freshen up from our last mistake.
- Please.
- Here's your quiz.
- Okay.
In "Kojiki" that records Japanese ancient history...
Oh, my goodness.
A man named Susuheori from Baekjae came over...
and transferred...
a new method of making alcohol with this.
Since then, he was respected as a deity of alcohol by the Japanese.
What could this be?
(He transferred a new method of making alcohol with this.)
Hold on.
- What is it?
- Didn't you read it a moment ago?
(What do you mean?)
You're right.
We read it before ringing the bell.
I didn't read it myself,
so I'm asking you now.
I was in the back...
I was looking at the falling leaves in the back.
(Seung Ho in the past, why did you do that?)
"Why didn't I read it?"
(30 minutes ago)
(The brewing master in Baekjae called Susubori)
(The older members were reading the passage.)
(Enjoying the foliage and relaxing)
- Wait.
- Why didn't I read that?
Was it a candid camera?
Wait, newly harvested rice, glutinous rice...
If his name is Susubori, isn't it barley?
(Simple)
That's just his name.
In the question, his name was Susuheori.
- It was written "Susubori." - Susubori.
I don't think his name is important.
It's asking what it was made with, so it must be an ingredient.
What we learned so far for Korean traditional liquor...
Newly harvested rice.
- Glutinous rice.
Wasn't the alcohol made with barley?
- Isn't it barley?
- When I read that,
did I say the word "glutinous rice?"
I definitely read that out loud.
(Frustrated)
I read that...
out loud like this.
I didn't expect...
(Tae Hyun read it diligently.)
We won't win like this.
Why don't we narrow down the answer?
Newly harvested rice, glutinous rice, and barley. That's all.
- Is there more?
- Nuruk.
Nuruk?
Why does "wheat" pop up in my head?
Like an arrow into my brain, "wheat" came up on my mind,
but I don't know why.
I just remember his name, Susubori.
I probably read it a moment ago.
I might remember it.
If we fail this quiz...
What was it?
Or we can get it wrong and head to Jindo now.
Shall we?
That sounds more realistic.
- Let's pick a good one.
- Yi Kyung.
- Each of you, say one answer.
Say one answer each.
If I get it wrong again, I have no right to say anything,
- but I think that it's nuruk.
- Nuruk?
What about you, Tae Hyun?
(Nuruk?)
I'm so sorry, but I don't remember reading nuruk.
- I don't think that it's nuruk.
- Newly harvested rice?
I can't read that.
- How did I skip just that word?
- We can't read that.
It's too far,
but I read it a moment ago.
I even read it out loud.
- We read it together.
- But...
It's either newly harvested rice or non-glutinous rice?
Newly harvested rice?
I don't think that I read non-glutinous rice.
Don't you think that it was newly harvested rice?
What do you think it is?
It's either glutinous rice or nuruk.
Are you convinced about nuruk?
All the makgeolli we tasted had nuruk.
It feels like I read it somewhere else.
Makgeolli is made with nuruk.
Isn't nuruk what remains?
Listen, Yi Kyung.
There's a lot of transparent alcohol in Japan.
- But...
- What's wrong with you?
You still can't see it.
There's a lot of transparent alcohol in Japan.
But...
(What is he doing?)
You still can't see it.
Not being able to see it makes me crazy.
- Goodness.
- I can't see anything!
You're acting like you're drunk.
- No.
- What is this?
Yi Kyung, think about it this way.
In Japan, whether it's glutinous rice or newly harvested rice,
they must have had alcohol made with rice...
before Susuheori arrived in Japan.
Do you really think that they didn't have such alcohol?
I bet that they did.
Why?
I think your answer is right.
- In Korea...
- He probably discovered nuruk.
I trust you.
Don't you think nuruk was a starter?
When you add it, it explodes.
(Exhaling deeply)
My answer is nuruk. We have to hurry and go.
Then I'm out.
I don't think that it's right.
Either way, we have to hurry.
- Leave me out of it.
- We have no choice.
- Answer whatever you want.
- No.
- I can't do this.
- You answer it.
I can't answer it. I can't do it anymore.
If I answer wrong again...
(Scared)
- Tae Hyun.
- Then I'll say it.
- I know the answer.
- Wait.
- We need to go now.
- Come back, Yi Kyung.
We need to leave.
Just go with nuruk.
- Say it.
- I have no idea.
Just say it.
- Is that your answer?
- Yes.
- I have no idea.
- Please say your answer.
- Okay.
- The answer is nuruk.
(Answer: Nuruk)
What Susuheori spread in Japan.
(No, no)
Is it nuruk?
(I can't watch this.)
(Nervous)
(Answer: Nuruk)
That's correct.
(Screaming)
(What?)
(Shouting)
I told you. Nuruk...
(Nuruk men run out right away.)
Hey.
- Where is it?
- Nuruk.
"The brewing master taught how to make alcohol with nuruk."
It's nuruk.
Seung Ho.
How did you know? Did you read it?
No.
- I didn't read it.
- I hugged him like this last week.
I really didn't read it.
I hugged Seung Ho just like this last week.
(According to "Kojiki")
Seung Ho, that was amazing.
- This is...
- Tae Hyun.
How did you know? Did you feel something?
(It's considered an important incident in Japan.)
Did you feel it?
There was always nuruk in every alcohol that we learned today.
There was always nuruk.
- Today is Seung Ho's day.
- Nuruk.
Both of them insisted on it.
- We got it.
- This is amazing.
- Nuruk.
(Haenam A, makgeolli)
Something important awaits us.
- For us?
- Yes.
(Cuckoo)
- What?
- Gosh.
Haenam A.
They won both Haenam.
- They went to this one.
- This is what they got.
They're trying to win more than us.
We traveled far for nothing.
We came here because we expected them here.
Gosh.
They knew that we'd come here...
and went somewhere else.
Team Guys are really quick.
On top of that, they got it right.
Something seems strange.
They're up to something.
Here's your quiz in Suncheon.
Among famous tourist spots in Suncheon,
there's a place called Suncheon Bay National Garden.
- Suncheon Bay National Garden?
- I don't know what it is.
(Confident)
- In Suncheon?
- It's a big garden.
When the garden was created,
the first thing they planted was a pine tree.
That tree is about 15m long, and it weighs about 5t.
When they were transferring the pine tree,
the helicopter wasn't able to lift the tree at all.
While everyone was worried,
the head manager who planted this tree suggested...
pouring this to the tree before lifting it.
Only then, the tree could be lifted.
What could this be?
He poured something on it?
Makgeolli?
Dong Hyun, no way.
Sung Hoon, please say something.
- It's very hard.
- Please.
The question is really hard.
Could it be oil?
- Oil? Why oil?
- It can't be, right?
When the roots absorb the oil,
- It can be lifted easily?
- pulling it out is easier.
Why not pesticides instead?
To melt all the roots.
The tree should slip out of the ground.
We learned about alcohol throughout the day.
What does alcohol have anything to do with this?
We should've gone to the sauna instead.
- Goodness.
- You're right.
Going to the sauna and eating skate...
- would have been perfect.
- We lost anyway.
Sung Hoon, please answer it at least once.
You have years of experience.
- Sung Hoon.
- Sesame oil?
- No, that's not right.
That's not it. Please, Sung Hoon.
Could it be arrowroot juice?
- Arrowroot juice?
- I have no idea.
Wouldn't it be better to say a type of alcohol?
Makgeolli.
- Right, makgeolli or...
- Could it be makgeolli?
The answer can't be makgeolli...
when we had some. That's too easy.
But alcohol...
has energy.
- I think that it's oil.
- Oil?
(Supporter of oil)
- Tears?
(Supporter of tears)
Maybe he cried.
(Laughing)
- After crying...
- Dong Hyun.
Go away.
When he cried, the tree came out.
(Gosh, where are you going?)
- On top of it.
- By saying it was good.
Since the old days, there was that power...
- to liquor.
- Exactly.
- I agree.
- I'm sure of it.
When there was an event of some sort,
- liquor had to be poured.
- Exactly.
A lot of the time,
the answer is the opposite of what I think.
- The opposite?
- I think it's liquor.
Darn.
You think it's liquor?
- Really?
- I mostly guess the opposite.
- Darn.
- And I think it's liquor.
It can't be liquor, then.
It could be the right answer.
I'm sure it's liquor.
We have time to go to one more place.
We should at least aim for a tie.
If we get this wrong, we'll go and eat.
We'll guess liquor and leave if we get it wrong.
- Sure.
- Sung Hoon, go ahead.
The answer is...
I learned a lot from liquor today...
which I appreciate.
The answer is liquor.
You guessed liquor.
Please let us get one right.
- Please let us get one right.
- Please.
What kind of liquor?
- What did I tell you?
- We guessed correctly.
- It's liquor.
- We were right.
Sung Hoon, it has to be makgeolli.
Remember what we're here for.
- Makgeolli.
- Makgeolli, right?
- Right.
- Makgeolli.
- We must guess makgeolli.
- It has to be makgeolli.
- Makgeolli.
- Makgeolli?
- Makgeolli, the liquor.
- It has to be right.
- Yes, makgeolli.
(Answer: Makgeolli)
- We got it right.
- We got one right!
That's a first.
- My gosh.
- Oil, did you say?
Why would anyone pour oil?
(Yes!)
- My gosh.
- You're the best.
- You at least got one right.
- Exactly.
I admit you did good.
No way.
- Yes!
Makgeolli.
(Suncheon: Takju, Cockle set menu)
(Suncheon: Cockle set menu)
(Team Handsome arrive at the adjacent restaurant.)
Cockle set menu.
(Waiting for the food)
We need to eat and hurry along.
What could be tastier?
- Our dinner?
- The skate combo is good.
Yes, the skate combo is better.
- Let's go to Naju.
- We're off to Naju.
- We have only until 8pm.
- Right.
- It's 6pm.
- That's when we have...
to be in the parking lot.
That's right.
We have 20 minutes to eat.
Right. Let's eat and hurry along.
(Goodness)
(The cockle set menu is served in no time.)
This is incredible.
(Seasoned cockle)
(Raw cockle)
No way.
- Is this spicy cockle salad?
- Yes.
Everything's so pretty. How pretty is this?
(Cockle set menu in Suncheon)
- This is a lot.
- They serve a feast.
(The feast didn't disappoint.)
This is a first for me.
- What's this for?
- You open the cockle with it.
How does one use this?
(He just takes it to his mouth.)
- Have one each.
- The cockle...
First, grab it by the top and bottom.
Then, slide this in.
- In the other direction?
- It's in the other direction.
Okay.
- Squeeze to open.
- Goodness.
(How to shuck a cockle: 3. Open shell from behind.)
I'll enjoy it.
(Clip!)
(See?)
(Easy, isn't it?)
It's good.
(Now that they obtained the skill)
Should we have some makgeolli?
Sure.
- Sounds good.
- Here you go.
- Goodness.
- Thanks.
(A refreshing glass of makgeolli)
Gosh, that's good.
- That's clean.
- That tastes great.
(How is the spicy cockle salad?)
Like this.
(A heap of the spicy cockle salad is added to steamed white rice.)
Add like so.
I can't believe all these cockles.
That's crazy.
(Humming in approval)
This calls for rice.
(The flavors are crazy.)
(It doesn't need an explanation.)
- Isn't it good?
- It's to die for.
I wasn't that hungry.
- This increases my appetite.
- Don't I know it.
Shouldn't we get going? Are we good on time?
We need to check the clock.
(In they go.)
Who invented this?
- Isn't this protein?
- Music to my ears.
How is it this good?
We need to leave within ten minutes.
(What?)
- We have eight minutes left.
- Really?
We'll be done in no time.
It's a bummer that we don't have enough time.
Let's eat what we can.
(Trust ourselves.)
I've got the hang of this and can shuck it in seconds.
(Snap)
There you go.
(4 minutes left, 6:16pm)
This is as good as medicine.
(They devour the food like it's a competition.)
This is nice.
We must go.
- My temperature is rising again.
- What?
It has gotten hot.
- I want one more bite.
- It's hot.
We need to go. I mean it.
I'm going to the restroom to wash my hands.
- Get ready.
- Let's go.
(The two get up despite wanting to stay.)
- What a bummer.
- I'm going to the restroom too.
Sure.
This is good.
(The baby brother can't stop eating again.)
Goodness.
I'm done.
Let's go.
We need to go. We're out of time.
(Current time: 6:20pm)
Guessing nuruk as the answer? That was the bomb.
Nuruk? I would've never guessed it.
(Cuckoo)
- They got one right.
- Suncheon.
- Okay.
- They went to Suncheon.
We guessed they'd go to Suncheon.
They went to Suncheon.
After dinner, we'll be in the end game.
(Haenam: Raw Spanish mackerel)
(Enjoy shiny raw Spanish mackerel.)
- Eat up, guys. We'll then move.
- Sure.
Look at how plump the raw Spanish mackerel is.
(Thick)
Do you wrap the raw fish in that?
Have it with the dried laver.
- With this?
- Here you go.
(That's new.)
(Here's how you eat it.)
(Dried laver)
(Raw Spanish mackerel)
(Seasoned green onions)
(Kimchi)
(Rice)
(Stack them carefully.)
Look at how thick they are.
(Make a wrap and enjoy!)
I'll enjoy.
- You like vinegar gochujang.
- Yes.
(Seasoned green onions)
What's this?
(Eating)
(Wait, these flavors...)
The raw Spanish mackerel.
It melts in your mouth as is.
I know. It's quite nutty as well.
This is what raw Spanish mackerel is like.
Look at how thick it is.
(They love it.)
Tae Hyun, look at you eat.
This is delicious.
You eat in a way that makes the food look tasty.
(Laughing)
The final battle will take place at the next location.
- Let's go to Jindo.
- Let's go.
We're off to Jindo.
To Jindo.
(They head out to go to Jindo.)
(The current race so far)
(Team Guys, Gangjin, Soju)
(Team Guys are geniuses when it comes to the quiz.)
We did it.
(Another correct answer!)
(Team Guys, Haenam (B), Makgeolli)
(Team Guys, Haenam (A), Makgeolli)
(The team of actors let their brains guide them.)
(Meanwhile)
(Incorrect!)
(They immediately used their reattempt card.)
(Team Handsome, Jangheung, Dongdongju)
(Team Handsome, Yeongam, Yakju)
(Team Handsome, Reattempt card)
(They managed to stay in the game thanks to their lucky cards.)
(Team Handsome, Suncheon, Takju)
(Team Handsome is on a roll!)
(Current score 3:3)
(They must answer the next one correctly to win.)
(7:30pm, Jindo, South Jeolla Province)
(Jindo, Hongju)
We ended up coming to Jindo.
The hongju of Jindo.
- Hello.
- The wait was long.
- Hi.
- We're here in Jindo.
- Hello.
We're in Jindo.
I'm the CEO of the brewery that makes Jindo's hongju.
Hong in hongju means "red" which is why everything is in red.
Right. Hongju of Jindo is made with rice...
and an herb called red gromwell which is red.
- It's made with an herb.
- That's right.
- That's why it's red.
- Exactly.
(Jindo's hongju is known for its scarlet color.)
(Red gromwell: An herb with red roots that grows in Korea)
(Infusing red gromwell in soju)
(Our traditional liquor of a long history with unique aroma)
You're not coloring the liquor in any way.
It's red because of the color of the roots.
- That's right.
- I see.
Rice and barley, a ratio of 7 to 3.
- Nuruk is used once again.
- Right.
How did Jindo come to brew hongju?
Since Goryeo Dynasty, Jindo was a place for exile...
due to it being an island.
(Being an isolate island, Jindo was a place for exile.)
Those who were exiled...
were usually scholars.
(Many intellectuals who were exiled in Joseon)
They knew how to make liquor...
which is how it came to this.
(In "Sejong Chronicles," it was called a red soju.)
(In "Seongjong Chronicles," it is recorded...)
(that 10 bottles of red soju were gifted to a Chinese envoy.)
(Back then and even now, )
(many breweries in Jindo are making hongju.)
(There's a new way of sipping this traditional liquor.)
Would you like to try it?
- The liquor itself is too strong.
- I see.
So I'll make you a cocktail with some soda.
(Soda is poured into a clear glass first.)
This is 60-percent ABV.
It's called The Sunset.
- The Sunset!
- The Sunset?
That's a pretty name. The Sunset.
- Gosh. The color is...
- Goodness.
- It divides into layers.
- It's splendid.
(Staring)
It's so pretty.
The Sunset.
(Yi Kyung tastes it first.)
- It's amazing. Look.
- Gosh.
- It smells like the 60 percent.
- Look.
Really? Does it still smell like it?
It tastes good.
- That's true.
- Tae Hyun, it tastes nice.
Does it taste nice?
It doesn't taste strong.
It's so interesting. It smells strong, but it's not.
It smells strong, but it doesn't taste strong.
Now, it's mixed to suit its name.
(Electrifying)
You had the strong liquor first.
You had the undiluted part.
(He hurries to try the one that's more diluted.)
That one's pretty good too.
It's the same.
(The tasting is tough for Tae Hyun.)
Ma'am, today,
we've been tasting liquors since 9am.
Honestly, I think this one is the strongest.
(Honestly, I think this one is the strongest.)
- It's the strongest.
- This one's ABV is 60 percent.
- It's stronger, right?
- Yes. It's different from others.
Compared to the others, ours is...
- Is there a milder hongju?
- This is 40 percent.
We should have tried that one first.
We chugged the 60-percent one first.
Ma'am, at this place,
do you go downward?
We usually went upward.
For a second, I thought,
"They must be all 60 percent ABV."
"We can probably light one of them."
We can light this one.
(Don't worry!)
- Ma'am.
- Thank you.
We appreciate your poetic description.
Thank you for coming here.
(Hongju, Time for Quiz)
It's a tight game.
Gosh. We've come all the way to Jindo from Haenam.
Okay. The quiz for Jindo.
There's a story about a white Jindo dog...
that ran over 300km for 7 months...
and came home after it was sold...
to a family in Daejeon in 1993.
Have you heard of the story?
I think I've heard of it.
- It was the dog...
- I saw it on TV or something.
(This quiz is on video.)
(Today's video quiz)
(Running 300km to find its owner, A story of a Jindo dog)
It's a true story about a Jindo dog...
that leaves to find its owner after it was sold.
It's an ad.
The longing it can't get rid of in its lifetime.
How touching is it to see...
how it serves only one person in its life?
Once an owner, you'll forever be the owner.
Is this the dog?
Is it over?
Yes.
Here is the question.
You just watched an ad.
What product is the ad selling?
That ad...
(He can't go on.)
Let's write down whatever comes to our minds.
The ad was aired in 1996.
How old were you in 1996?
Maybe a few months old.
I was born in November, 1995.
Were you born in 1996?
I wasn't even one year old yet.
Gosh. Tae Hyun, you're our only hope. I...
I was an elementary school student, but...
- This is so...
- I...
That song.
Yes. It sounds familiar.
(To the one born in 1989, the melody sounds so familiar.)
As soon as I heard it...
Many telecom companies used such a tune.
In 1996,
they did have cellphones,
- but they were...
- They weren't Anycall?
Anycall...
I shot the ad for it.
That came out...
- much later than 2000.
- That came out later?
(Smiling)
(Tae Hyun was quite bright back then.)
(It's been a while, but this was from 2002!)
It's either an internet ad of the time or...
They had a portal site called Chollian.
I know.
- It could be internet-related.
- It could be a telecom company.
Yes. It's either internet service or...
Back then...
(I have no idea.)
- I think...
- Can we hear it again?
Of course. We can play it as much as you want.
(They need to hear it again.)
That song became really popular.
It's a true story about a Jindo dog...
that leaves to find its owner after it was sold.
We have to be immersed in the ad.
See? It finds its owner.
It's a true story about finding its owner.
Help me infer it.
You can't get rid of it.
How touching is it to see...
how it serves only one person in its life?
How touching it is?
(Woof)
Once an owner, you'll forever be the owner.
That's the key.
(They grasp the ad through the feelings.)
(Thinking anguishedly)
There used to be a computer called Jindo Dog Computer.
If it's a computer...
Does a story of a Jindo dog coming back to me...
- makes sense?
- There was Jindo Dog Computer.
There was Jindo Dog Computer or something.
No?
You've lived longer than me.
Even so, does it make sense?
I think a car makes the most sense.
We usually drive one car brand without changing it.
That's true when choosing cars.
- But...
- I...
When he said Jindo Computer,
why do I feel like I've heard it somewhere?
- There were many computer brands.
- I think...
Why have I heard of it?
- Where did I hear it?
- Is that a real one?
Maybe I was gaslit by you, or...
Maybe they did have a computer called Jindo Computer.
I have good memories. Where is that memory from?
(For a guy born in 1976, the memory of the time is blurry.)
Okay. We'll hear it again twice.
(He hears the question again out of frustration.)
Okay.
(Will the memory that left the house come back?)
(Team Guys' fate depends on it.)
(Current time: 19:40, Team Handsome)
For goodness' sake.
Does it make sense the alarm didn't go off until now?
They were so good, but did they get it wrong in Jindo?
- Last week, - Yes.
We got the question long before,
- but we hid until you came.
- Yes.
Are they hiding somewhere right now?
In Naju.
(Are they hiding in Naju after winning the game?)
- Last the last time?
- Yes.
- We're here.
- We're here for now.
Let's check the cars.
(Team Handsome arrives in Naju while feeling anxious.)
- It feels fishy.
- It's fishy.
They are busy.
There are many cars too.
But we did our best today, didn't we?
- Come on.
- No?
I won't be fooled twice.
- This doesn't feel right.
- Come on.
- They must be hiding somewhere.
- Hello.
(They go into the mart in a resigned manner.)
I'm honored.
- Gosh. There are so many cameras.
- Hello.
There are so many.
- Come on.
- Nice to meet you.
(Suspicious)
Did someone come before us?
Yes, they did.
- What? Did they?
- They came.
- Did someone come before us?
- Pardon?
Honorable guests paid a visit,
so we had an event here.
- An event?
- Yes.
- With who?
- It was a big event.
We shot "Unexpected Business 2" here.
- "Unexpected Business." - They shot it for ten days.
- A while ago.
- Yes.
(Actually, this place is...)
They have a barcode reader and everything.
(the place Tae Hyun worked as a boss for ten days...)
(for "Unexpected Business.")
This is not a supermarket.
Are we...
This is too much.
We do everything ourselves like this.
(So, Tae Hyun was here!)
- It's been three years.
- I see.
- What about today?
No one came today.
- No?
- You're the first to come.
- Tae Hyun wasn't here yet?
- No.
Really?
You came here first.
It's awesome.
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Which traditional liquor will they experience here?)
We've been brewing makgeolli in Noan, Naju for two generations.
I'm Jeong Nae Jin.
I see. Nice to meet you.
All of the owners...
- say they "brew" it.
- Yes.
They don't say that they make it.
They say they brew makgeolli.
- Gosh. That's cool.
- So,
you brew makgeolli...
and supply the makgeolli you brewed to this mart?
Yes. We brew it ourselves and supply it too.
(He supplies the liquor he made to local places.)
(Handsome Heritage 8: Our liquor by our side)
It'd be nice if you introduced the liquor to us.
This product...
- is called dongdongju.
- Right.
I assume...
- you've had makgeolli many times.
- Yes.
Dongdongju got its name...
- because the rice grains...
- I see.
Float on most of it.
When I pour it, you'll see...
- They do have rice grains.
- Yes.
- Gosh. Really?
- There are many rice like sikhye.
(The rice floats as soon as he pours it.)
I've never had makgeolli with rice grains in it.
Let's try it.
(It's a dongdongju-tasting time.)
It smells like the ones sold in the markets.
It's good.
The rice grains melt.
I've never had makgeolli with rice in it.
It tastes so comfortable.
- It's relaxing.
- It's so soft.
The rice doesn't stick in your mouth.
- The Japanese would like this.
- Really?
- Are you going to sell it?
- Exactly.
"Exactly."
- We've learned a lot today.
- Yes.
Of everything we had, this is really interesting.
Each liquor is different.
It's nicely carbonated too.
- Slightly.
- It's good.
- It's tasty.
- I'm curious about this one too.
Will you introduce it to us?
It takes about 100 days to make this.
What comes to your mind when you think of "Naju?"
- Naju?
- Gomtang, the beef-bone soup.
- Pears.
- Yes.
Right. We used pears from Naju.
It amplifies the scent of pears.
- They have pears in it?
- Generally, - Thank you.
- you can enjoy its scent better...
- We can enjoy its scent...
when you chill it like white wine.
It looks like white wine.
- Gosh. This is nice.
- It doesn't smell strong.
- It's not that strong.
- Is ABV 15 percent?
- Yes.
- Is it 15 percent?
- I can't tell by the smell.
- The smell... Right.
It's because your nose is broken after getting beaten up many times.
(Here he goes again.)
- I can't tell by the smell.
- The smell.. Right.
- It tastes just like pears.
- Yes.
Seriously.
It's so good.
It's as sweet as dessert wine.
Seriously.
- Sir.
- Yes.
Do you sell these two products...
- in your mart too?
- That's right.
How do people like it?
Do the locals here like it?
They love it.
They buy several bottles, saying it tastes so good.
They enjoy it a lot.
- Really?
- Yes.
(Where is makgeolli?)
(Our traditional liquor is beloved in our everyday life.)
(Thanks to many people's efforts, )
(it's being protected and developed even today.)
(Team Guys in the meantime)
Should we say it's for a computer? Do you think it's a computer?
There's nothing else.
(They're still discussing whether it's for a computer or not.)
- It's for a car, right?
- Then...
Listen. J, I, N, D, O.
Why do I feel like I saw that somewhere?
J, I, N, D, O.
Jindo.
You've seen Jindo before?
Yes. Where and why did I see it?
There wasn't a car model named Jindo.
It must be correct if you say so.
- Let's do it.
- We have the answer.
- Computer?
- Should we go for it?
- Okay.
Seung Ho wants to go for it.
- Let's follow him today.
- Yes. Seung Ho...
- saw it somewhere.
- He's okay with it.
- We got it.
- One, two, three.
- A computer.
You said a computer for the answer.
Let's check the answer through a video.
(They check the answer in a desperate manner.)
How touching is it to see...
how it serves only one person in its life?
- Once an owner, - I think we were wrong.
You'll forever be the owner.
- A lifetime warranty.
- There you go.
(A lifetime warranty)
- Gosh. We're right.
- Sejin.
There you go.
- We're right.
- Sejin.
- That's right.
Why? What does it have to do with the Jindo dog?
What does a Jindo dog have to do with Sejin?
Sejin Computer Land...
did have a computer named Jindo back then.
(It does exist.)
You're amazing.
How did you know about Jindo Computer?
Look what I wrote. Do you want to see them?
Is there such a thing as Jindo Computer?
Jindo Dog Computer.
Jindo. The year 1996. I kept writing it.
Jindo dog!
(Jindo: Hongju, North Jeolla Province set menu)
Gosh. That was crazy.
Now.
We'll give you the quiz.
The last one will be easy.
- Jindo!
- What?
Jinho?
Jindo?
- Jindo?
(Current time: 8:15pm)
Did they get it right in Jindo?
So, they did go to Jindo. Gosh.
- Why does the alarm go off so late?
- Why does it go off now?
(That makes it 3 versus 4.)
- They just got it.
- Really?
Darn it.
(The pressure builds up.)
We have to get it right, then.
We have to occupy this site.
We have to occupy it to...
(If they get it wrong, they'll lose.)
But we did a good job.
- We made the best choices we could.
- Right.
You're right.
- Okay.
- Please.
Here's the last question of the day.
- I bet it'll be a hard one.
(Time for Quiz)
This is an old name...
for dongdongju that you just had.
It used to be called buuiju.
- Buuiju?
- Okay.
(It sounds unfamiliar.)
The fermented rice grains after the fermentation process...
are floating...
like these fell into the water. That was where the name came from.
Okay.
(The old name for dongdongju is buuiju.)
What are these...
that fall into the water?
- Buuiju...
- Yes.
Means these floating on water?
- That's what "buui" means?
- Yes.
- I'll show you the Chinese letter.
- Okay.
Buuiju is...
Do we have to know the Chinese characters?
The Chinese characters for buuiju are...
- Is that "ui?" - Is the first letter "bu?"
(They have no idea even if they see it.)
This is "ui" of buuiju.
It's such a difficult letter.
It's a difficult one, indeed.
But do you remember it?
(I might remember it while writing it.)
First, it's something related to insects.
There are different Chinese characters.
I think that one is for ants.
It's an ant.
Ant?
(Does he really know it?)
That is a Chinese letter for an ant.
(He is certain.)
Sung Hoon, if it's correct, that'll be crazy.
(Desperate)
- What?
- Wait.
Aren't they really the ants that fell into the water?
Do the ants in water look like that? It's possible.
- That makes sense.
- Right.
- Look.
- The color is different, but...
when the ants fall into the water, they look like that.
There are white ants too.
- Yes.
- Guys. This...
Maggots?
(Or can they be maggots?)
- Aren't maggots bigger?
- They are ants.
(I think the answer is ants.)
- It's the ants.
- The ants in the water.
- Sung Hoon, you are correct.
- In the water...
How is it correct?
- It has to be the answer.
- Really?
When you held it, I thought they were ants.
Really? They don't look like ants.
Sung Hoon, if we get this wrong, we have to work tomorrow.
They look forward to that.
- Right.
- Yes.
Sung Hoon, our fate depends on you.
Okay. I'm here as a guest.
So, I should get it right in the end.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Gosh. Please.
The answer is ants.
- Please.
- Ants.
If it's correct, you're a legend.
- It'll be legendary.
- Seriously.
- You did it all.
- If you get it right...
If you are right... Please.
Dongdongju is also called buuiju.
So...
(Will it be correct?)
They look like ants in the water.
(Answer: Ants)
Correct.
(Cheering)
(The game ends as a tie.)
See? We did it!
(This is the spirit of the athletes.)
- Don't do it.
- Sung Hoon.
- Sung Hoon. What?
They were the ants.
(Brother Choo did it.)
Sung Hoon.
- Gosh.
- Bring it on.
Of our six members, he'd be the only one who knows this.
It's crazy that he got it.
How can he think of the ants while looking at this?
Does "ui" mean ants, then?
- Yes. Ui for the ants.
- There's no way.
- Is that the Chinese character?
- Yes.
It's ui for ants?
How did you know this letter?
- Why do you know it?
- I don't know.
I have no idea.
- It's crazy.
- It was the last one.
We got it right at 8:25pm.
We made it. We're safe now.
- It's our lucky day.
- Exactly.
In that case, it's a tie now.
- It's a tie.
- We occupied Naju.
- Gosh. It's crazy.
- Gosh.
It's a tie.
- That makes it a tie.
- It's a tie.
What happens now?
Is there a one last fight?
You want to fight for it?
He wants to fight. Let's win it by force.
- Yes.
- Let's fight for the win.
- It'll be quick.
- Yes.
- Yes. We'll only use one hand.
- Exactly.
We won with Sung Hoon's energy.
- That's right.
- Right.
Getting the ants right was a big one.
The other team would never guess it right.
If they say the ants for the dongdongju question,
do you want to say that we lost?
- We can do that.
- I'm totally up for it.
- They won't know it.
- We can show the Chinese letter.
That is a hard letter.
- That's a good idea.
- Right?
- That's fun.
- They'd never guess it right.
I like that idea.
(Team Guys arrives in Naju.)
Hey. I love that we're here.
Hey. This is the G Mart!
(He's happy to see it!)
(Tae Hyun recognizes the mart.)
My goodness.
It's where "Unexpected Business" was shot.
- Gosh.
- It's been a while.
(He's happy to see him.)
- I can't believe it.
- It's been three years, I think.
(Reuniting with the boss of the mart...)
(after a long time of three years.)
They shot "Unexpected Business" here.
- I can't believe it.
- How have you been?
Goodness.
- Gosh. I'll be darned.
- I know. How long has it been?
Everyone he met is here.
The show aired three years ago.
A lot has changed, though.
- Did you eat a lot?
- I ate a lot.
We really did eat a lot.
- That's good.
- Well done.
Why are you so good with the quiz?
You didn't have any hints.
- In the end, - They are so hard.
- Seung Ho nailed it.
- Did you really get them right?
Did you say Seung Ho nailed it?
- Yes.
- I think he's drunk.
- I...
- They're surprised to hear it.
Since last December...
Why didn't you play the bingo?
- Today... You go on and tell them.
- Yes.
We got the quiz wrong in Yeongam-gun, right?
When we lost Yeongam-gun, it became hard for us to win.
Really?
The 30-minute karaoke time card.
That was the new card that came up today.
The card looked like this,
so I covered the top.
Like this.
It said,
"You must use it before completing the bingo."
So we had no intention to complete the bingo.
He said, "Let's not complete the bingo."
They didn't go for the bingo.
- They went for the number.
- We didn't go for the bingo.
- Then they didn't have to use it.
- We went for the number.
Despite everything,
- we didn't want to lose.
- Weren't you flustered...
- because we went someplace strange?
- Yes, we were.
As for us, Sung Hoon made...
most of the decisions today.
I said this.
- He kept going...
- "Let's eat something tasty."
- Seriously.
- So you couldn't foresee our moves.
- Sung Hoon.
- That wasn't a strategy.
- We didn't have a strategy.
- Had we fallen...
into Sung Hoon's trap belatedly,
the tables would've been turned on us.
We didn't use our brains.
Do you know which question we got in Jindo?
- What?
- We had to identify a commercial...
with a Jindo dog.
I think I know what it is.
- What is it?
- Sejin Computer.
How do you know that?
- See?
- This is unbelievable.
(It's a big twist.)
People who used computers a lot definitely know the commercial.
When I was young, Sejin Computer had a commercial with a Jindo dog.
I must've watched it.
- The Jindo dog commercial.
- I...
Gosh, there was a question I could answer.
That's right. There was.
So here's the thing.
- You know...
- The score is a tie.
So... You can explain.
As for the last question...
- "Why don't we do this?" - We answered it by chance.
- So...
- You answered it by chance.
We asked the production how they'd choose the winner.
They didn't have an idea. So we said,
"We got the answer by chance. Will they be able to get it?"
I jokingly said,
"They won't be able to get the correct answer."
"If they do get it, we'll say that we lost."
- What are you talking about?
- Our quiz.
- No one understood.
Can't you explain it properly?
- By Dong Hyun's words...
- No one understood.
- By Dong Hyun's words,
we have a chance...
I'll wrap it up.
The makgeolli brewery you'll visit tomorrow to work is too cramped.
Thus, only one person will go.
(Only 1 person will receive the penalty.)
- It's too cramped.
- So we had originally planned...
to have an individual match.
It was supposed to be Anyone But Me.
- I like that idea.
- Seriously.
Okay.
Let's put our bags here.
- That was the original plan.
- Listen.
But Team Handsome has a suggestion.
A team match?
If the three members of Team Guys answer the question correctly,
Team Handsome will lose.
Then one of them will receive the penalty.
- Okay. If we fail...
- If you fail...
- One of us will go.
- One of you guys will go.
- Only one person will go.
Isn't an individual match better?
Listen. You answered four questions correctly.
So you have a big chance of getting this question right.
It isn't too hard.
- We got it right.
- The fact you said that...
We won't fall for that trap.
It's a 50-50 chance.
- That much is certain.
- Why would we take that risk?
While we're curious,
we won't fall for Dong Hyun's trap.
- We don't want to do that.
- Gosh, live a little.
Seung Ho, didn't you do well today?
I got it right.
(Laughing)
Are you running away?
I got it right too.
- Come on.
- His behavior makes me certain.
Are you scared?
- "Are you scared?" - We're scared.
For goodness' sake.
- We're scared.
- Really?
Instead of making the offer in a polite way,
he went, "Are you scared?"
- Our day of effort was wasted.
- Excuse me.
Please accept the offer just once.
(Gentle)
I think it'll be a funny situation.
- No.
- Please accept it just once.
You need to think about the viewers.
(A piece of advice)
Don't think only about yourself.
- Let it be an individual match.
- An individual match.
- All right.
If it's an individual match,
- I can't write well.
- Sung Hoon has a disadvantage.
- That's right. Sung Hoon is...
- That's a bit of a problem.
Will it make the individual match funny?
- An individual match.
- It can't be helped.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Let's go. An individual match.
An individual match. Okay.
Only one person will remain.
Here's the first question. Today,
you guys visited eight places.
- You only missed a place in Yeosu.
- It's the Yeosu question.
- The Yeosu question.
- I'll give the Yeosu question.
I knew that we'd have that question.
(At a beautiful island in Yeosu, Nangdo, )
(there's a brewery that has been in operation for 4 generations...)
(for 114 years.)
(Nangdo, an island where water is scarce, has seven springs.)
(One of them is called Milk Spring.)
(It got its name from making the mothers get more breastmilk.)
(Makgeolli that's made with this spring water...)
(has been passed down for 4 generations.)
(It's a great liquor that's made in a strictly traditional way!)
When you go to Yeosu,
there is a small island that's beautiful in a picturesque way...
and its famous makgeolli.
The name of this island is Nangdo.
- Nangdo?
- Nangdo.
Nangdo.
The island got its name, Nangdo,
because the shape resembled a certain animal.
What's this animal?
- "Nang" refers to this animal.
- Yes.
Does it come from a Chinese character?
- "Nang" is the matter.
- I don't know that one.
(He figures it out in 1 second.)
He got it from the Chinese character.
He shouldn't have gotten the Chinese character.
(A big twist)
- I told you so.
- The Chinese character...
It's game over.
- I told you so.
- This is... Hold on.
This is meaningless.
This isn't right.
Thank you for your hard work.
That was why I wanted to take up on the offer.
Do you want to answer last?
- But...
- Let us each take a turn.
(It's fun to watch.)
What do you want to do?
Instead of answering this question,
- do you want to accept our offer?
- Let us each take a turn.
No. Listen.
- I can answer this question.
- That's right.
But instead of answering this question...
- There was a question we answered.
- Yes.
If the three of you answer it correctly,
we'll stay here.
How about that?
He's looking after the two juniors.
- I'm looking after them.
- That's right.
Sung Hoon.
- How about that?
- Even if Sung Hoon gets it right...
- and leaves, - Okay.
- five members remain.
- Yes.
Still, the probability is 1-5th.
- That's right.
- You think you can beat Dong Hyun.
- You're certain.
- You put him...
- below you.
- Make a choice.
- Is that it?
- Let me put it precisely. Hold on.
I can beat those two.
Listen.
- All right.
- Listen.
I have knowledge too.
- I know that.
- I got Sejin Computer right.
Just you watch.
- Now...
- Today, Seung Ho will remain.
- Be careful.
- Okay. We got it.
So what will it be?
- We won't accept the offer.
- No?
- Let's have an individual match.
- An individual match.
You can answer correctly and go home.
Sung Hoon, you got it right.
That's good. I'm glad.
Sung Hoon, go.
- I...
- You need to get it right.
He hasn't turned in his answer.
I haven't turned in my answer.
- What?
- I need to look it up in Korean.
You can't do that!
(Stop right there.)
That was what I wanted to say.
If Sung Hoon doesn't know...
- He doesn't know Korean.
- He doesn't know.
If he doesn't know it in Korean, he can't get the answer right.
Come here.
Hold on. Time out.
I can look up what it is in Korean! Why?
- Time out.
- I can look it up!
Then I should be able to look up the Chinese character.
I should be able to do that. That's nonsense.
He just knows the Chinese character.
- How is this possible?
- It's...
It's such a big twist.
Sung Hoon is so funny.
Time out.
(I know the animal!)
Did you try to make them accept the offer...
- without knowing the answer?
- No, I know the answer.
- Okay. It's game over.
- Sung Hoon.
Sung Hoon, hurry up and answer. Say it in Korean.
- Sung Hoon...
- Wolf.
- Wolf?
Wolf? Say it in Korean.
Say it in Korean.
Say it in Korean?
This is sudden. I made an offer in order to look after you.
- This is sudden.
- Sung Hoon,
you'd know the answer in Korean.
They say that all men are this animal.
- So parents with daughters say, - That's right.
- "All men are 'Blank.'" - Jindo dog.
Jindo dog, my foot.
He is scary.
Hey.
(Defending himself)
You're the worst.
- Wolf.
- Yes.
- Correct.
- That's right.
It was very easy.
- The Chinese character...
- It was given to us.
Would you have known after a round?
- No.
- I wouldn't have known.
Sung Hoon, you can't go home yet.
- Why are you sitting there?
- I want to sit here.
(I won't sit with them.)
This is a good seat.
Their offer must've come with a catch.
- Now, five people remain.
- Okay.
- Here comes the second question.
- Four questions remain.
When you have a get-together, people raise their glasses...
and give a toast before drinking.
- Okay.
- You know many such toasts, right?
- D.D.S.
- D.D.S.?
This question is totally unrelated.
Where did D.D.S. come from?
"Don't be disheartened,"
- "don't complain," - This is insane.
"and spread your chest." D.D.S. is the short form.
This is insane.
In that case,
- what does a toast, "119" mean?
- Did you say "119?"
- One, one...
- One, one, nine?
One, one, nine.
(A toast, "119")
(Dazed)
I'll give it a go.
(He decides to give it a go.)
One bottle per day until 9pm.
(One bottle per day until 9pm)
"One bottle per day until 9pm?" Hold on.
We could steal the answer.
- We could steal the answer.
- Incorrect.
- That's right.
- It's something along the line.
- Did I get one component right?
- Yes.
That's right. The three of us have a chance.
Let me answer.
A Gen Zer will get it right.
One cart per day until 9pm.
One cart?
- Incorrect.
(This Gen Zer's standards are something else.)
I think I've given away too much.
- Let me answer.
- "Let's go home before 9pm."
- It's "Before 9pm." - Let me answer.
Let me answer.
- So that part was correct.
- Seung Ho was the fastest.
One bottle per person...
before 9pm.
- Incorrect.
- Didn't he say that?
No, it's my turn. Let me answer.
One bottle in the 1st round until 9pm.
(The 2nd try)
You got another component right.
Come on!
- I keep getting a component right.
- Seriously.
It's a toast about changing the drinking culture...
in a healthy way.
- Dong Hyun.
Let's drink 1 type of liquor in the 1st round and go home at 9pm.
Correct.
(Dong Hyun succeeded in stealing the answer.)
(I practically spoonfed the answer.)
(Making a big fuss)
One type of liquor.
This is driving me crazy. I'm so upset.
(I can't believe I lost to him!)
Sung Hoon, I did it.
We were certain that he wouldn't be able to answer.
Seung Ho, what did you say earlier?
(Seung Ho, what did you say earlier?)
You have my approval.
(You have my approval.)
Dong Hyun is the best when it comes to stealing answers.
- Seriously.
- Sung Hoon, we're set.
We won.
- It's nice, right?
- I'm jealous.
Give us the next question. Four members remain.
- How is it so hard?
In our daily lives,
many four-character idioms that are related to liquor are used.
What's the four-character idiom that's used...
for someone who comes to a drinking party belatedly?
Isn't it something like "Hurae three shots?"
Is there a four-character idiom for someone who came late?
- Yes.
- It's so hard.
This four-character idiom actually exists.
I think I know the 1st 3 syllables.
- Really?
- Can't you tell the rest...
- if you know the 1st 3 syllables?
- Don't you know it?
It's confusing.
It's my 1st time seeing someone who only knows 3...
out of the four syllables.
He doesn't know.
(Teasing)
- I'll try it.
- Please go ahead.
- Let me answer.
- Okay.
Hu...
(Hu)
- rae...
- Rae.
No way.
- Are you going to say that?
- Hurae...
- Is that it?
I thought of the same thing.
Is that really right?
- Maybe not.
- Is that it?
Huraejasik.
- Let me answer.
- Incorrect.
Let me answer.
Hurae three shots.
Incorrect.
Hurae...
- Is it really "Hurae?" - Is it really "Hurae?"
Sambae.
- It's right.
- Seriously.
Sang Uk is correct.
(Huraesambae is correct.)
(Guys, I got it right!)
What was it?
(Confused)
- What was it?
- What did he say?
- See? This was why I wanted it...
- to be a team competition.
- It was right.
What did he say?
(All the athletes escaped!)
- Are you serious?
- What did you say?
Huraesambae.
- What?
- Huraesambae.
- It was the one I knew.
Yes.
- Huraesambae.
- Is it huraesambae?
It's in the dictionary.
- Is it in the dictionary?
- Yes.
(The idiom does exist in Korean dictionary.)
I can't believe that this happened.
- My brain froze.
- I know. My head went blank.
It's shocking that three of us remain.
You should've accepted it.
You should've accepted our offer.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
It can't be helped.
Since things have come to this, give us that question.
Things have come to this.
- Give them that question.
- Things have come to this.
- That's a good idea.
- All right.
- Do you want the question?
- Yes.
You're looking at dongdongju.
Another name for dongdongju is buuiju.
It's already complicated.
(This is fun.)
The three of us would've remained anyway.
It's because rice grains float like "Blank" that fell into the water.
What's "Blank?"
What do they look like?
What are you?
- What do they look like?
- Nails?
- Check out the Chinese character.
- Is there a Chinese character?
- There's a Chinese character.
What? Why is it so hard?
- Is there such a Chinese character?
- Who knows?
(What?)
I don't know it.
(Tae Hyun is unfamiliar with the Chinese character.)
Is that...
My goodness.
It's an insect.
(A hint)
- At this point...
- Should we be able to answer?
Let me answer. Caterpillar.
Caterpillar is incorrect.
Let me answer. Larva.
Larva is incorrect.
Let me answer. Silkworm.
Incorrect.
Let me answer. Grasshopper.
- Let me answer. Bush cricket.
- Bush cricket.
Incorrect.
- They'll get it now.
- I guess it's something like that.
- Mantis?
Let me answer. Longheaded grasshopper.
- Incorrect.
- I won't answer anymore.
(I won't be Fabre.)
He tried so hard.
Cricket.
- Someone said it earlier.
- You guys are so close.
Say what comes to your mind. Not many options remain.
Fly.
Let me answer. Mosquito.
Let me answer.
- Ant.
- Correct.
(Ant is correct.)
(I did it.)
(Insect Boy burned his passion.)
I see.
He got ant.
Didn't I say "Ant" before?
- Congratulations.
- Come here.
See? Seung Ho did all the work.
- I couldn't think of it at first.
- You did well.
- I'm sorry.
- It's like that.
This is the last question. One of you will get the penalty.
- Okay.
- The brainy ones remain.
Chong In Ji is the man who wrote "Yongbieocheonga,"
the first Hangul poem in the history of Korean literature.
Okay.
- He was known to enjoy drinking.
- I see. He enjoyed it.
But every time he drank, he caused trouble...
- because he had drunken habits.
- Gosh.
Is it about the trouble he caused?
When King Sejo threw a banquet...
for the subjects who were over 60, he did something to the king.
What did he do?
This is driving me crazy.
- To the king? A casual tone.
- Yes.
He used a casual tone with the king.
Correct.
(Yes!)
Are you serious?
(Is it over?)
- That was...
- That was unbelievable.
Wasn't that a conversation?
Tae Hyun.
You answered correctly because you were drunk.
- Being drunk helped.
- That's right.
Since they were conversing, I wondered when I'd answer.
They went back and forth.
(I don't know about that.)
A casual tone.
Let's go.
Do you use a casual tone when you're drunk?
I use it often.
(Yi Kyung will get the penalty.)
That's incredible.
- Dong Hyun.
- What?
I feel so victimized to carry out the penalty.
- Dong Hyun.
- What?
Thank you for working hard until the late hour.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- My goodness.
Go to Seoul.
(What will he do the next day as the penalty?)
(Early morning next day, Brewery)
(People are working diligently...)
(to make dongdongju.)
In the heat of 40C,
they turn over the grains continuously.
There are many steps that must be done manually.
(It's the hardcore brewery that was on "Extreme Job.")
The process is as physically demanding...
as that of a construction site.
Sometimes, I tell it that I love it...
like a madman.
(Who will make the beloved dongdongju with him?)
(At 8am, Yi Kyung arrives at work to carry out the penalty.)
My goodness.
- Hello.
- You'll need to work hard today.
- Okay.
I'm here to do that.
Shall we get started?
(Kneading and Steaming Station)
(The first step of dongdongju-making)
As if we were making baekseolgi,
we're steaming rice for makgeolli.
You're steaming rice for makgeolli.
This is rice.
- This is regular rice.
- Yes.
- We soak it in water.
- It's soaked in water.
We turn the soaked rice...
- into powder.
- You ground it.
- Yes.
- I see.
- Do you mix the two?
- Yes.
Today, you'll mix the two as they get steamed.
The steaming process.
(Rice, moisture, )
(and rice powder)
(When the rice is processed like baekseolgi, )
(the liquor becomes full-bodied and gets the sweetness of rice.)
(It becomes the buuiju they tasted yesterday.)
Turn it over and break it like this.
I'll shovel it toward you.
- Like this?
- Yes.
(There's so much steam that they can't see ahead.)
(Yi Kyung)
Scrape the bottom.
- Okay. The bottom.
- Yes.
(It requires a lot of strength since the mixture is sticky.)
(That way, )
(the three of them turn it over for a while.)
(My goodness)
(The hard turning process comes to an end.)
Now, it's over.
Let's add more.
You pour it again.
We need to steam all of this.
- All of that?
- Yes.
- It'll fill up the container.
How many kilograms of rice is this?
- We're steaming 320kg of rice.
- Did you say 320kg?
(What he did so far was nothing.)
(He can only exclaim.)
You might not be able to film me due to steam.
(My heart is cloudy like this steam.)
("Fog" by Jung Hoon Hee, labor by Lee Yi Kyung)
Shall we get started?
It comes up like this.
There's so much heat.
Go to Seoul.
(All alone)
(I walk)
(On this foggy street)
You do this every day.
Yes, we do this every day.
Congratulations.
(In the past, you showed me kindness)
I'll work hard tomorrow.
We did it!
I can't go because I feel so upset.
Dong Hyun!
I got it right too!
(Your shadow)
(Thinking about them is meaningless)
I think it will be so upsetting to let that team win.
(The past memories)
(But my heart)
(Still longs for you)
Thank you.
- You will do it again.
- Okay.
(Where has that person gone?)
Should I do it? Just this part.
(He is back!)
(The incarnation of revenge has returned with spite.)
(I will make all of you get punished.)
(Where will they go...)
(for the return match?)
(Island of fantasies, Jeju)
(Looking for Jeju's special structures)
(Revenge is left behind.)
(Sightseeing mode is on.)
(A race where anything can be done)
(Do what you want to do.)
(What do you want me to do?)
(We have no time to waste!)
(Team Guys is focused on the race.)
(With smart planning, )
(their win rate is built up nicely.)
(Things are working for us today.)
(We won.)
(The race hits a twist all of a sudden.)
(Which team will take the win?)
Dramaday.me