What's the name of our show?
- I don't know.
- I don't know either.
What kind of show is it?
I wasn't informed at all.
I just know that Ho Jin is the director.
I know that it's a new TV show.
(A new variety show on tvN to entertain you on Sunday evening)
(We will introduce it now.)
(One morning at the end of October in Busan)
We're in Busan at 7am.
(Cha Tae Hyun)
What are we doing?
(Kim Dong Hyun)
Calling us to Busan at 7am is...
very old-fashioned.
- Is it?
- People don't do this anymore.
Hello.
Someone young is here.
Right. Nice to meet you.
- Someone young.
- I'm your fan.
- He's very tall.
- Right?
I'm Oh Sang Uk on the national fencing team.
- Seriously.
- Goodness.
(2024 Paris Summer Games)
(Gold medalist, twice in a row in fencing)
(Handsome swordsman in fencing, Oh Sang Uk)
- He's really tall.
- Right.
Dong Hyun, compared to him...
I'm also tall.
People usually tell me that I'm tall.
- That's amazing.
- He's really taller.
You have a strong physique.
You're very tall. You must weigh...
Another tall person arrived.
- Hello.
- He's tall too.
- Hi.
What kind of show is this?
- Is it...
- It must be a sports show.
- Is it aiming...
- He's really tall.
For the Summer Games in four years?
- I know.
- What's going on here?
This is unbelievable. This is Seung Ho.
Hello.
(How cute)
I'm Actor Shin Seung Ho.
(He became known for playing Sergeant Hwang Jang Soo in "D.P.")
(He played Go Won in "Alchemy of Souls" with unexpected charms.)
(Handsome macho in movies, Shin Seung Ho)
You'll be singing on this show.
- Sing?
- You'll dance and sing.
(He's a new recruit on variety shows.)
Anyway, you won't be acting here.
- Right.
- Everything except acting.
That's true.
Goodness.
- Hey.
- He's an entertainer.
The first entertainer arrived.
- Finally.
- He's old but pretends to be young.
Hello.
- The first entertainer arrived.
- I told you about him.
Are you on your offseason?
(Chubby)
He should keep fencing.
- The entertainer.
- Goodness.
There are no fencing competitions these days,
right?
I just finished a big competition,
so I thought of taking a break this year.
He looks chubbier...
than I expected.
It's just his baby fat.
- He looks good.
- Sang Uk is our youngest.
- That's true.
- So it's his baby fat.
The youngest is the tallest.
(Sucking in his cheeks)
Come here, Sang Uk.
Did I gain that much weight?
By the way,
what is our show called?
- I don't know.
- I don't know either.
I'll ask my questions later.
- Do you know, Sang Uk?
- I'm not sure.
No one knows about it.
We decided the name of our show...
the day before yesterday.
The day before yesterday? What is it?
(What's the name of our show?)
The name will be...
Handsome Guys.
(We're Handsome Guys.)
- "Handsome Guys?" - Wait.
(Handsome Guys?)
- "Handsome Guys?" - Wait, Dong Hyun.
- Let's leave.
- Hey.
- Still, you're an actor.
- I'm in the wrong place.
- Handsome Guys.
But you're an actor.
You can stay.
I'm really sorry.
Dong Hyun isn't part of it, right?
Dong Hyun, come here for now.
Tae Hyun has gotten old now.
- Both of us...
- Right.
Most people don't say that I'm handsome.
"Handsome Guys?"
Stay a little longer.
Is it really true?
Is it "Handsome Guys?"
Seung Ho asked me,
"Is it really true?"
(He didn't want to believe it.)
"Is it really 'Handsome Guys?'"
Has the name been decided as "Handsome Guys?"
My goodness.
The four of you can talk about being on the show.
If someone asks me, "Which show are you on now?"
"I'm on Handsome Guys."
"You? What's your role on the show?"
With five of you who are very handsome to us,
we'll start the show for the first time.
We also invited a guest.
Our guest has to be handsome.
Please come out.
- He looks handsome from afar.
- Right.
- Even from afar.
- That's a relief.
We're just guys.
- We are simply guys.
- Is that what we are?
We have a handsome guest every week.
That makes sense.
He's considered a handsome guy.
Jin.
(Today's first guest to fulfill the handsome role)
Goodness.
(BTS, the best global artist)
(A handsome member recognized by the world)
My face is...
(Worldwide handsome BTS)
- Have you been well?
- Of course.
- I've been well.
- Hello.
Hello.
- He's here.
- Hello.
Hello.
- Goodness.
- Hello.
- We've met before.
- He's handsome.
- How did you know?
- I recognized him right away.
- Hello. How did you know?
Do you know the title of our show?
What is it?
(Tell him.)
Our show is called Handsome Guys.
(Laughing)
He's very flustered.
He's the first guest on our show.
(The first guest on Handsome Guys, Jin)
- He's the best.
- By the way...
This is amazing.
He can't be excluded.
He's the only one to match the show title.
Jin, for next week,
- try not to schedule anything.
- Try to adjust it.
I haven't scheduled...
anything yet for next week for this show.
That's good.
- Leave it free.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay, now that we know the name of our show,
- what kind of show is it?
- Seriously.
On Handsome Guys,
with beautiful men who represent Korea...
(Smirking)
It's a show that will search...
beautiful places, beautiful cultural heritages,
and people we're curious about in Korea.
(Beautiful)
("It's more beautiful...")
("when you look at it in detail.")
(From "Grass Flower" by Na Tae Joo)
(Treasures on our land)
(In detail)
(Our tradition and people)
(Closely)
(The more you look, the handsomer they get)
(In search of our heritage)
(Why don't you join us in the evening on weekends?)
(2024 Korea's handsome exploration of heritage)
(The first exploration)
(The national heritage of South Gyeongsang Province)
I was wondering why there's only one in Busan.
- It's South Gyeongsang Province.
I don't recognize any of it. Do you know any?
- I know...
- Tongdosa Temple.
Of Gwak Jae U.
- Really?
- Do you know him?
I have a certification...
in Korean history.
- Really?
- Seriously?
That's amazing. You have a certification?
- I passed grade five recently.
- Why?
I was on a show about Korean history, and I wanted to study more.
I got the certification for my own good.
- I wanted to study more.
- Really?
Yes, so I know things...
like Stone Seated Buddha.
(Stone Seated Buddha of Gwallyongsa Temple)
Can you briefly explain what it is?
I need to check on that.
- They'll cancel your certification.
- No.
- Was he in a righteous army?
- Don't say things like that.
He was in a righteous army.
- He was in a righteous army.
- Righteous army?
- He was slightly...
- I know about him too.
I learned about him in high school.
- Unbelievable.
- Can you tell us what you know?
I've heard of Yongmunsa Temple.
I think I've been there.
- Upo Wetland.
- What's that?
Isn't it a wetland?
(Upo Wetland)
- Where crocodiles live?
- Crocodiles?
- A place with crocodiles.
(The youngest Sang Uk's childish beauty)
Sang Uk isn't ordinary either.
What's all this? Will we be going there today?
Do we have to go there?
Will you be visiting all of these nine places?
Will we?
What's going on?
You'll pick places by playing bingo.
Is that why it's a 3-by-3 square?
Yes, do you know how to play bingo?
- Yes.
- One complete line means bingo.
The first one to complete a line wins.
The center must be occupied first.
- Right.
- It's always the case in bingo.
Tae Hyun, you're smart.
- We play this a lot.
- His experience can't be ignored.
He's resourceful.
- He's Zhuge Liang on the show.
- He's resourceful.
- Of course.
- He's different.
You'll be split into a team of three.
(They will play bingo in 2 teams of 3.)
It's a competition.
Each team will visit the place of their choice.
After looking at the national heritage,
you'll be given a quiz.
(A quiz related to the location will be given.)
If you guess the right answer,
you'll occupy one square on the scorecard.
(If you answer correctly, you occupy the square of the location.)
The first team to complete one line...
will win.
- What happens if we win?
- If we win...
- Will we get off work?
- If you win, you'll get off work.
(The winning team will get off work.)
The losing team can't get off work?
What if you lose?
The losing team will stay one more day.
(You'll stay one more day instead of getting off work.)
What?
You'll leave early in the morning to catch monkfish.
- Monkfish?
- Yes.
- Do you mean fishing?
Is it a monkfish of this size?
Monkfish as in braised monkfish?
(A beautiful ingredient in South Gyeongsang Province)
How will we catch it? By fishing?
Are we going to be working?
A fisherman promised to help out.
(Also known as "Extreme Job")
Let's go.
(Like the winter monkfish meat, )
(a chewy and thrilling penalty awaits them.)
Most people go out before dawn...
around 3 or 4am.
(The thought of going to work before dawn makes them dizzy.)
This is...
- Seung Ho, please say something.
- Right.
I'm thinking about which location to visit.
- He's a brainiac.
- I knew it.
Geographically speaking, there are two places in Changnyeong.
Upo Wetland and Yongmunsa Temple.
- Did he catch that?
- He figured it out in an instant.
- He's right.
- None of us...
- He already started.
Knew about that.
It's advantageous to go to Changnyeong.
You know what?
What about this?
(What about this?)
Forty minutes of hiking?
There's a round trip of hiking for 40 minutes.
I missed that one.
He missed it?
- Seung Ho.
- Yes?
You should read more carefully.
You struggle to get there,
but if your answer is wrong, you'll have to go somewhere else?
If your answer is wrong,
you won't occupy that square. You must go somewhere else.
The square will be empty,
and the other team may occupy it.
You struggle to get there, and the other team answers correctly.
- You can't occupy that square?
- However,
if a team goes there and answers correctly,
- Will it show?
- you'll see that it's occupied.
- I see.
- Okay.
(Just like this)
Gosh, that startled me.
Yangsan.
Then the other team occupied it.
When we hear "Yangsan," Yangsan is occupied?
If we're on our way there and hear that, we should turn around.
- Of course.
- Okay.
You have until 8pm tonight.
If neither team gets a bingo until then,
the team that occupies more squares will win.
So one team is sure to win.
The game will be over.
- You've been waiting to hear this.
- Teams.
Here are your teams.
I'd like to hear from the younger members,
Seung Ho and Sang Uk.
Is there someone you want to team up with?
- Seung Ho.
- Just in case?
I don't know clearly...
with whom I want to work.
I know whom I don't want to work with.
- Who?
- Dong Hyun.
- What?
(Dong Hyun)
- Why me?
- Actually,
- I have my certification.
- before the shoot,
we got together and introduced ourselves.
Most of the things...
he said sounded like a lie.
(Most of them were lies.)
Goodness.
We found out that they were lies.
It's not what you think.
I remember correctly, but I got confused with my words.
When I met you last time, I learned that you used to play soccer.
So I called you a goalkeeper,
but you were a center-back.
- I've never seen the goalkeeper.
- Wrong information.
- I say wrong things by mistake, - Wrong information.
- but what I know is clear.
- So you know.
I have a smart brain.
- I can't wait to find out my team.
- Let's go.
(While their feelings are revealed)
First of all,
- Lee Yi Kyung, - Yes?
- Jin, - That's a relief.
And Oh Sang Uk will be on the same team.
(First team, Yi Kyung, Jin, and Sang Uk)
Then Seung Ho and Dong Hyun are on the same team.
He got unlucky.
He shouldn't have said that.
- I'm sorry.
- Goodness.
- They met on bad terms.
- I'm sorry.
- What I meant was...
- It's okay.
- They got teamed up after that.
- They met on bad terms.
I said wrong things by mistake.
- Don't hurt his feelings.
- I won't.
Yi Kyung, Jin, and Sang Uk will be...
Team Handsome.
Tae Hyun, Dong Hyun, and Seung Ho will be...
- Guys?
- Team Guys.
(Tae Hyun, Dong Hyun, and Seung Ho on Team Guys)
This is how we get split.
So that is why.
Seung Ho joined Team Guys.
He's one of the guys.
I'll feel more at ease.
- He's on our side.
- He's on Team Guys.
- This is funny.
- He's on our side.
Will we get together again at the end?
- We can't.
- No.
- We should go back to Seoul.
- Then I won't see...
the three of them anymore?
That's true.
Is this...
our last time seeing each other?
For now,
check your schedule next week.
Yes, check your schedule next week.
- My schedule next week?
- You should probably come back.
Say goodbye to the three of us before leaving.
- I'll think about it.
- Okay.
We must win for his fans' sake.
He has to come back.
You might need help during the competition.
We have these cards for you.
Come and pick one each.
We prepared a total of six.
- One per person?
- Now?
Yes.
(Jin picks a chance card first.)
Should I read it out loud?
Go back to your place and read it.
- This isn't bad.
- What is it?
- Really?
- I think I picked a good one.
A nap of 30 minutes.
I can choose when to put the other team to sleep for 30 minutes.
- That's amazing.
- Nice.
- That's too...
- It's really nice.
If you think that the other team is heading to...
- the same place, you can stop them.
- When we're moving together.
That one is intense.
(That one is intense.)
- Go ahead, Seung Ho.
- Okay.
Our youngest.
He looks scary.
Is something the matter?
Stop making a face.
(The member who's resolute for no reason)
I picked an amazing one.
- What is it?
- Seriously.
- This is very good.
What is it?
A chance to try again.
When your answer is incorrect,
you can get an additional hint and try again.
They definitely have a chance.
An additional hint?
With an additional hint, they're likely to get it.
Hide this right here.
Someone might...
You guys can take a nap.
Okay.
I will take care of it.
(How about Sang Uk's card?)
Is this for real?
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Seriously...
- What is it?
- A free car wash.
- What?
- What is that?
- That's the best.
- I must use this...
before completing the bingo.
Do you mean this vehicle?
Do we have to use it?
(A car wash is necessary before the game is over.)
Where will he get a car wash?
I used up all my luck...
in Paris.
- This is terrible.
- No, it's okay.
No, it's okay.
We can get it done quickly.
(Jin encourages the younger one.)
- Hey.
- Is it good?
We got very lucky.
- Why?
A card to track the other team's location.
You can find out the other team's current location.
(It's getting worse and worse.)
- We must win no matter what today.
- Please.
(Embarrassed)
Use that card when we're getting a car wash.
If they do,
they'll see that we're at the car wash.
(Location)
You don't know when they'll use it.
This is really terrible.
He said "terrible."
(He said "terrible.")
- Shall we do it together?
- Let's do it.
(Only two chance cards remain.)
Do you want to switch or not?
- Do you want to switch or not?
- Let's switch.
- His team has been getting lucky.
- Right.
- We switched.
It feels strange.
What is it? Let me see.
We got one too.
- I'm glad that they didn't get it.
- I agree.
- What is it?
- What do you have?
(Did their fate get switched?)
- Unbelievable.
- There must be two bad ones.
(Darn it.)
- I got lucky after switching.
- I'm glad you did.
Wishing happy birthday.
Buy a cake for someone whose birthday is today.
- That sounds terrible.
- That's the worst.
Someone whose birthday is this week. Wait.
How will I find someone whose birthday is this week?
We'll have to ask the passersby.
That one is unbelievable.
Right, it's horrible.
(Did he cause trouble again?)
By the way...
I apologize.
It's okay.
- At first...
- Your intuition was right.
- Yes.
- Everything was going so well.
Now that we're split into teams,
we have to read the room carefully.
Should we go to the location in the center?
Or somewhere in Busan because we're already here?
Yes, you're right.
- Where are you going first?
- Which place is the best?
We should definitely go to Yangsan.
If we get Yangsan, we'll win.
- Is that our strategy?
- Yes.
- Then let's get there before them.
- Okay.
To Yangsan?
The one at the center looks the best.
We must go to Yangsan no matter what.
(A war of nerves over Yangsan, the center of the scoreboard)
- We should decide together.
- Right.
- We should decide?
- Let's decide the first location.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
How about a relay of rock-paper-scissors?
- Let's do that.
- A relay sounds good.
People might complain if one from each team plays.
A relay of three players.
- Dong Hyun should go first.
- Okay.
Why me?
- You're bound to lose.
- Right.
- I'll show you my energy.
- Okay.
- Sure.
Sang Uk will go.
Are you giving up on him already?
I feel unlucky today.
Can't you see through him with your fencing skills?
I'll take a look.
(I can read Dong Hyun's mind.)
The two of them picked unlucky cards today.
(Unlucky brothers start the relay.)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Yes!
I knew it. Okay.
- Good job.
- The relay continues.
- Next player.
- It's okay. We knew he'd lose.
All right.
(Letting him pass)
- The relay continues.
- Next player.
It's okay. We knew he'd lose.
- All right.
- It was expected.
All right, rock-paper-scissors.
Okay!
(He wins 2 consecutive times.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Okay!
He's different because he's a fencer.
- Seung Ho.
- We'll get the center square.
Please.
Don't worry. I have my method.
He has a method.
Seung Ho has a method.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Nice!
Nice! Nice fencing.
- What's gotten into him?
- Nice.
Rock-paper-scissors.
(And...)
Let them have it.
We have our plan B.
- We don't have any plan B.
- Plan B?
- That was good.
- We have no plan B.
The score is neat.
Three to zero is nice and neat.
(The neat freak is quite shameless.)
You expected me to lose, but...
(You expected me to lose, but...)
- Where are you headed?
- You expected me to lose.
Sang Uk, you should decide.
He's the winner and the hero.
Sang Uk, pick a location as our hero.
We'll go to Yangsan.
- The center one first?
- Yes.
The center one?
Where are you headed? You should tell us too.
- We must go to Busan first.
- Okay.
- Busan?
- Definitely.
We decided on the first location.
- Okay.
- Let's be honest.
Let's keep our promise...
- since it's our first day.
- We should keep our word.
If I see you in front of the Eastern Palaces...
on the first day,
that means war.
(That will mean war.)
- Both of us...
- We're going to Busan.
- We won't go there.
We're going to Yangsan first.
The fight starts now.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Is this the scoreboard?
(The race is in full swing.)
Good luck today.
I enjoyed shooting with you today.
I hope to see you again at another shoot.
He's so mean.
- It's been...
- Right away?
- Our paths may cross again.
- Right?
How long have you been driving?
- I started in high school.
- Are you experienced...
- What?
- Since high school.
I got my license when I was 19.
The age limit was 18, so I got it when I was 19.
- Did you start driving right away?
- Yes.
Whatever you guys want. I'm willing to drive.
If you're good at driving...
I'm good at driving,
- but tell me what you'd like.
- I'm also good.
Then it's up to you.
- What do you prefer?
- Here's a thing.
We're taking one vehicle,
and I know what's on your mind.
We'll be going to many places,
- so we can take turns driving.
- We have to take turns.
Where's our first location in Yangsan?
We should look it up on GPS.
Yangsan, Habuk-myeon,
- Habuk-myeon.
- Tongdosa-ro.
- It's 108.
- It will take...
- One hour.
- One hour?
- It's 58km.
We'd better get going.
Let's go.
My shoulder hurts.
We need to be smart about this.
(In the end, Dong Hyun decides to drive and they'll take turns.)
(Tongdosa Temple in Yangsan, the Eastern Palaces in Busan)
If we occupy Busan,
we'll have to go to Changnyeong no matter what.
If we occupy Changnyeong as expected,
we will win.
Right, but if we fail to occupy Yongseondae,
we'll need to occupy Upo Wetland.
Then we have to go to Namhae.
You know what I mean?
We have to occupy that no matter what.
It takes four hours to get to Namhae.
We should have won the rock-paper-scissors.
(Team Handsome sets off first.)
They're leaving.
They're leaving right away.
(Should I follow them?)
Should I follow them?
Go to Busan first.
- Let's go to the Eastern Palaces.
- How do we get there?
Let's go to the Eastern Palaces first.
The Eastern Palaces don't come up on GPS.
(In a hurry)
Why did Changgyeonggung Palace come up?
It's right in the front.
It's 22 Gudong in Seo-gu.
Where is D?
He's a bad driver, so we're setting off late.
Like this?
(He's bad with gadgets.)
Here we go. We must hurry.
- Let's go.
- We don't need to hurry.
Tae Hyun, I know the neighborhood very well.
It's over there where there's a skyscraper.
I see.
(Heading to the Eastern Palaces in Busan)
The Eastern Palaces, palace.
Tell me more. I can try...
The Eastern Palaces is a painting of palaces.
(A painting of palaces?)
"It's a painting of Changdeokgung Palace..."
"and Changgyeonggung Palace..."
"from the bird-eye's view."
I get it now.
Changdeokgung Palace is next to Gyeongbokgung Palace.
They look the same.
Sejo of Joseon might have lived there.
The Eastern Palaces.
I lived in this neighborhood in Busan over ten years.
I never saw the Eastern Palaces.
You don't get a chance to see this.
Right, but I could have heard about it.
I never heard of it.
You arrived at the destination.
It's on a school campus.
- Inside here?
- Yes.
Seokdang Museum?
(University's Bumin Campus)
It must be around here.
- What?
- They're here.
See?
(There's a vehicle that arrived first.)
Tell me the address in Busan.
- We should see how close it is.
- It should take 30 minutes.
It takes 15 minutes. It's around the corner.
- Let's go there first.
- Really?
Yes.
(Really?)
Let's go.
- It's foolish not to go to Busan.
- Right.
From Busan...
They will feel dejected when they see our car over there.
(He's easy to influence.)
(Waste of time)
I knew it.
Should we go directly to Yangsan?
Let's go.
- Is that right?
- Will it be okay?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
- going to Yangsan now.
- Definitely.
- We should definitely go.
We won't get the right answer now.
We wanted to go to Yangsan anyway.
(Yangsan, Busan)
This is incredible.
Yangsan. Changnyeong.
(In that case...)
So you don't plan to go...
to Tongyeong or Namhae, right?
- These are second on the list.
- Right.
- For now...
- That's a difficult word.
Tongyeong.
We must do this no matter what.
We failed to occupy the Eastern Palaces.
We have to go to Yangsan,
Changnyeong, and Haman.
We should go to Changnyeong first.
Then they'll have to go to Namhae.
- Great, it means that we won.
- Go to Changnyeong first.
If we occupy Yangsan and Changnyeong,
Yi Kyung's team that got Busan...
has no choice but to go to Namhae.
What do you call it when you fall for your own trick?
He shot himself in the foot?
I think that's right.
That's it.
(A moment ago in Busan)
Is this Dong-A University Museum?
It's inside the museum.
It's on the university campus.
The building is on the university campus.
(There's a national treasure with an unfamiliar name.)
We definitely got here first.
(A treasure house that we didn't know)
- Hello.
Welcome.
I'm the director of Seokdang Museum.
I'm Professor Kim Ki Soo.
Nice to meet you.
This museum is on a university campus.
Yes, established in 1959,
it's the first museum in Busan.
- The first museum in Busan?
- Yes.
There was no public museum back then.
During the Korean War,
the building was used as a government office building.
- A government office building?
- Yes.
The pseudonym of the founder is Seokdang.
- Is it his pseudonym?
- Yes.
During the period of chaos,
many Korean relics were taken out of Korea.
The founder collected the relics that were taken out.
- These precious relics...
- That's important.
Were donated to the school.
We have two national treasures...
and about 200 designated cultural properties.
In the entire country,
it's rare to find a university museum with so many relics.
Right.
It's so big for a university museum.
The quality is high.
We have a total of six exhibition rooms like this.
- Six of these?
- Yes.
Is there an entrance fee?
- No.
- On top of that, it's free?
That's right.
- The maintenance cost must be high.
- Including the public?
It's free?
Really?
It's amazing that it's free.
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
When I heard that you were visiting today,
we brought out two relics that had been hidden in storage.
Why did you bring out these two?
I'll explain now.
This is a painting by Kim Yun Gyeom.
During the Joseon Dynasty, he painted...
beautiful sceneries in Yeongnam area while sightseeing.
(Album of Landscapes of the Yeongnam Area)
In the painting, do you recognize this place?
- It's...
- It's Haeundae.
It's a famous place in Busan...
- called Taejongdae.
- "Taejongdae?"
Your answer was close.
("Taejongdae" in Album of Landscapes of the Yeongnam Area)
(A refreshing view where you can almost hear the waves)
This one is a painting...
- of Taejongdae.
- It looks the same.
- Yes.
- Only the trees disappeared.
Right? These are the rocks.
- This?
- Like this,
the lines are short and straight.
This is called Jinkyung landscape painting.
I see.
(Jinkyung landscape painting was popular...)
(during the late Joseon Dynasty.)
This way...
(One more painting of the surrounding view)
- This is...
- What's this?
It's called Chochungdo.
Wasn't it painted...
- Exactly.
- by Sin Saimdang?
We talked about it before.
I have quite a bit of knowledge.
(Embroidered Chochungdo Folding Screen)
(From 1700s)
(An elegant garden on the folding screen)
This is a painting by Sin Saimdang...
called Chochungdo.
- Is it a painting?
- This is...
the folding screen version of the painting.
(Sin Saimdang painted Chochungdo, )
(which is a still life painting of plants and insects.)
(Among copies of the folding screens made by generations to come, )
(this one is known to be the most beautiful.)
Did she paint it?
- It looks embroidered.
- Right?
Colored threads were embroidered on black silk.
It's embroidered?
- Isn't it embroidered?
- Yes.
As you can see,
there are eggplants and plants like chrysanthemum.
There are also butterflies,
plants, and insects.
As these were the theme,
it's called Chochungdo.
- I see.
- I don't know much about art,
- but it looks incredible.
- Right?
Do I look like a nobleman standing here?
(When did you get there?)
He looks like a scholar.
Someone young who's about to take his state exam.
Someone who studies a lot?
There's a secret in here.
Do you have a 50,000-won bill?
- I do.
- Okay.
You have a lot of money, Yi Kyung.
Do you see the drawing in the front?
- There are eggplants.
- There's a drawing.
- If you look carefully...
- Where is it?
Do you see the eggplants at the bottom?
Doesn't it come up to the top?
- This is it.
- The one in the back?
Yes, the one in the back. It's faint.
(The folding screen is hidden.)
Is this the same one?
When the 50,000-won bill was first made,
the Korea Minting and Security Printing Corporation...
came by to take a photo of this.
They took a photo of it, and had it engraved...
- along with Sin Saimdang.
- That's right.
Because it was Sin Saimdang's painting,
this was added in the background.
What do you think? They came by to take a photo of it.
The two you saw earlier are just treasures...
while this is a national treasure.
It's one of the most important pieces of artwork we have.
(A national treasure and a handsome heritage on the bingo board)
(National treasure: The Eastern Palaces)
(Painting by an unknown artist from the 1800s)
(It is 584cm wide and 275cm long with 16 fold screens.)
Above anything else, it's grand.
- The Eastern Palaces?
- It's called the Eastern Palaces.
In Seoul, there's Gyeongbokgung Palace.
This was given its name because it is a drawing...
of the two palaces to the east of it.
That's why it's called the Eastern Palaces.
- The right of Gyeongbokgung Palace.
- The palaces to the east.
The palaces to the east.
We have Changdeokgung Palace and Changgyeonggung Palace.
Changdeokgung Palace and Changgyeonggung Palace.
- This area here is Daehak-ro.
- That's right.
We've all seen them while passing by.
I've never seen them before.
I probably visited them during my younger years.
(You don't have to visit the palace to know how big it is.)
If you look at it closely, you'll see...
the names of the quarters and houses.
Right.
- Yes. In Chinese characters.
- Right.
- Above the tiles.
- I see them.
Behind them, you'll see other quarters...
that were essential to life at the palace.
It's safe to say that...
it's the most realistic drawing...
- we have from that time.
- It's fascinating.
I'm curious about the artist.
Of course.
Here's why it's a national treasure.
Only two of these have been discovered.
One is at the museum in Korea University...
while we have the other one.
It's assumed that only three were drawn...
under the supervision of the king, the crown prince,
and the department that oversaw the project.
Having this drawing at the time is the equivalent...
of knowing military secrets.
Of course.
- Maps were used for everything.
- Exactly.
Like intelligence units.
Since this was a drawing of palaces,
- Absolutely.
- you can imagine...
The enemies could use this...
- to carry out assassinations.
- Exactly.
- You're right.
- That's why we assume...
that only three people...
were allowed this drawing.
I get it now.
In the present day, this is used as a reference...
when restoring traditional buildings...
that were destroyed due to fire.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
(We appreciate the detailed explanation.)
(Busan: The Eastern Palaces)
(Time for Quiz)
Let's now listen to the question.
I'm completely lost.
Appreciating it is one thing,
but you still need to give a correct answer.
- Yes, that's most important.
- Of course.
- I can answer anything you ask.
- That's nice to hear.
Here's your question.
Is it a multiple choice or not?
All I can remember are...
Changdeokgung Palace and Changgyeonggung Palace.
- Same here.
- This...
is a short-answer question that is like a multiple choice question.
What does that mean?
Is it like ordering 1 portion that is like 2?
Having 1 portion that is like 2.
A small-sized plate that is like a middle-sized plate.
- Here's your question.
- Sure.
(At least they have good chemistry.)
With the Eastern Palaces, there isn't any information...
regarding the making of the drawing...
which is why we have no way of knowing...
who drew it and why and also when it was specifically drawn.
However, there are things...
that can be assumed by it.
Which season of the year is the drawing set in?
(Let us see.)
We could probably guess...
- by examining it.
- The season?
(Which season is it set in?)
The season?
- It can't be winter.
- From what I can tell...
- The fall?
- I see yellow.
Wouldn't that be the reason why these were colored that way?
(Is this fall foliage?)
Is that a ginkgo tree?
- Then...
- Maybe it's...
- Hold on. What's this?
- The tree?
(Is this an open-book exam?)
It was drawn from January to before the end of August.
- That means it's spring.
- Spring or summer.
Is it set in the heart of spring?
(Drawn from January of 1828 to before the end of August of 1830)
It was drawn from January to before the end of August.
Then it must be spring or summer.
It can't be fall or winter.
Our answer can be "between January and August."
They asked for a season.
Must we name the exact season?
Of course.
- The season?
- I'll check over there.
- We should study the trees.
- Exactly.
Hey, it's spring.
- Why?
- I see cherry blossoms.
- Where?
- Right here.
They're cherry blossoms!
(Flowers have blossomed on unknown trees in the yard.)
(That's huge!)
Nicely done.
- Right.
- They're cherry blossoms.
We can insist that these are cherry blossoms.
(The flowers are in full bloom, so are they right?)
(Jin has become the brain of Team Handsome.)
Jin spotted something huge.
This was drawn when it was pretty outside.
There are flowers that look like cherry blossoms...
which usually bloom in spring.
It can't be winter judging by the leaves on trees.
- It can't be winter.
- It's not winter.
There are flowers of that color that bloom in the fall,
but since it was drawn between January and August,
- we'll go with spring.
- You scored big time.
We're confident with our answer.
- Are you confident?
- Absolutely.
(Their confidence is at 100 percent.)
I'll tell you the answer.
The season that the Eastern Palaces is set in is...
(Which season is the Eastern Palaces set in?)
(Answer: Spring)
I'll tell you the answer.
The season that the Eastern Palaces is set in is...
(Which season is the Eastern Palaces set in?)
(Answer: Spring)
- It's spring.
- Yes!
(Startled)
No way.
(Jumping around)
My gosh.
- He said it like we got it wrong.
- Yes, exactly.
- That startled me.
- We're in a museum, so hush.
The season which the Eastern Palaces is set in is early spring.
- Of course.
- Early spring.
If they had chosen summer or the fall,
the trees would've been too thick...
for the quarters and palaces to be seen properly.
- You're right.
- If they had chosen the winter,
the drawing would've been too bleak...
leaving it aesthetically unpleasing.
- That's also right.
- Aesthetics are everything.
The drawing was set to early spring...
where new life appears in yellow.
It's a problem being handsome...
when I'm also smart.
You must be a regular on this show.
He's still trying to nab me.
You are correct.
(Busan: The Eastern Palaces, National treasure)
(Team Handsome marks their first space.)
Good job. Please look at the back of the card.
- The back?
- There must be something on it.
(A location card is given to them if they get the right answer.)
(On the back of the card)
(Busan: Raw fish table d'hote)
(Their meals are as important as the game they'll play.)
(By getting the answer right, )
(they will get to eat a staple dish of that region.)
(If they leave that region, they won't be able to eat it.)
(Are we allowed to ask for food?)
(Yes, but you can't take any by force.)
- Raw fish table d'hote in Busan?
- Hold on.
(Thickly sliced raw fish)
(How can you be in Busan and not eat this?)
I had pork and rice soup for breakfast.
- Did you?
- Really?
(He feels slightly betrayed.)
Didn't you eat breakfast?
- I left at the crack of dawn.
- Of course not.
I haven't eaten since last night.
We can be offered something more delicious in Changnyeong.
Hold on a second. This is a full-course meal.
(He can't give up on the raw fish full-course meal.)
Allow me to voice my opinion.
Let's say that the others went to Yangsan.
But without having their meal,
they could go straight to Changnyeong.
Should that happen, the plan we had...
could be rendered useless.
- That's why...
- Do you know what's sweet?
If we get both in Changnyeong...
(By scoring both in Changnyeong, they'll block the other team.)
Them having the center space won't mean a thing.
This will be their only play.
- You're right.
- That's true.
- We should go to Changnyeong.
- That's so smart of you.
No way. We can just go to Changnyeong.
What if we don't score there?
Then the other team will be at a huge advantage.
We'll use what we have.
- The reattempt card.
- That's right.
Let's assume we answer one of them correctly.
We'll use the reattempt card on the other one.
Think of this as well.
Should we do this on our way?
Or should we travel further and then backtrack?
No, look. We'll go here first and circle like so.
Should we go to Upo Wetland first?
We have...
- to travel downward anyway.
- Should we do that?
This is on the inside.
- Okay, then...
- We'll go to Upo Wetland.
Yes, we'll go to Upo Wetland.
(From Busan to Changnyeong)
- Then we'll...
- This is a battle of wits.
We'll go to Upo Wetland.
- Upo Wetland.
- Upo Wetland?
- Okay.
- We're off to Upo Wetland.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Upo Wetland.
(Team Guys)
- I have a good feeling.
- Yes.
- It feels good to go to Yangsan.
- Right.
(Yangsang: Tongdosa Temple's Geumgang Ordination Platform)
The center is the key...
- in a bingo game.
- Right?
Why did they make such a choice after winning rock-paper-scissors?
How stupid! We gave them a chance.
- It's good for us.
- It's good for us, Tae Hyun.
Therefore, we have to occupy Yangsan.
We don't hear the sound of "Busan" yet,
- so they didn't get it right.
- Yes. You're right.
(Did they fail to get the quiz in Busan?)
I don't think they're an easy competition, though.
Tae Hyun, the close location is still far.
- Yangsan wasn't a close location.
- But...
- Then, Namhae and Tongyeong are...
- That's right.
That's frustrating to think.
No one's thinking about going to Namhae.
Namhae and Tongyeong are...
(Cuckoo)
Busan!
- "Busan?" Okay.
- They occupied Busan.
They'll put us to sleep now.
They will.
Their plan was to arrive there before us.
We should have hurried.
It's a 30-minute nap.
We don't have much time, then.
Will they be 30 minutes ahead of us?
Well, they can't go that fast.
We were stuck in the morning traffic.
- They got Busan.
- Yes.
- But they're not making us sleep.
- Right.
That means they're sending us to Yangsan,
saying, "You can go to Yangsan."
I think they're heading to Yongseondae in Changnyeong now.
- That's possible.
- Yes.
I'm sure they'll climb the mountain in Changnyeong.
(They'll choose Yongseondae without a doubt.)
Otherwise, they have to go to Namhae.
That's right.
- In 1, 2, 3, Upo Wetland.
- Upo Wetland.
(That's wrong.)
They won't go there.
- They'll go hiking first.
- That's true.
(While they are guessing wrong in a logical way...)
(Team Handsome)
Who'll drive? Rock-paper-scissors?
- I'm okay to drive.
- Really?
- Goodness.
- Gosh.
Excluding Sang Uk, you and I are groaning.
(The youngest one is fine.)
Look. Let's see how long it takes.
I think it'll take an hour and a half.
Upo Wetland.
(The distance to Upo Wetland: 1 hour 50 minutes away)
An hour and 50 minutes? Gosh. It's far, indeed.
- We have to eat when we get there.
- An hour and 50 minutes?
Yes. Let's eat when we get there.
(They have to get the quiz right to fill up their empty stomachs.)
Raw fish sounded really good.
We could have had it,
but if the other team leaves without eating,
we might...
go home tomorrow.
That can happen.
Should I call Dong Hyun?
Yes. We think they're on their way to Yangsan.
Right.
Kim Dong Hyun.
(Calling Dong Hyun)
Yes?
Hello?
- It's Jin on the phone.
- Hey, Dong Hyun.
Hello.
We heard the news.
What news?
We heard the alarm.
- Busan.
- We heard you occupied Busan.
We just stopped by it on our way to Yangsan.
We just stopped by.
I knew you'd play cheap from the beginning.
It was because...
How could we miss it when it's ten minutes away?
- It was on our way.
- Come on.
Sure. We didn't believe you.
- And we were right.
- Are you ready to take a nap?
What?
Are you ready to take a nap?
(Right now?)
Right now, we are...
- We're okay so far.
- Really?
If you're sleepy, should we use it now?
- We're good now.
- Now, it's...
- We're almost done eating.
- I see.
- We'll get sleepy after the meal.
- We...
Let's be humane,
and let us sleep after we got at least one quiz right.
(The veteran actor takes a submissive attitude.)
You sound tired right now.
We're not sleepy at all.
We just placed an order for lunch.
We just ordered it.
Stop talking about the meal when it's not there.
Come on. Let us finish our meal.
Dong Hyun keeps talking gibberish.
But I'll tell you exactly what's going on.
Let us take a quiz in Changnyeong.
- We'll let you have Yangsan.
- Okay.
You stole Busan from us. Don't you feel sorry for us?
- We'll let you have Busan.
- Dong Hyun.
When you speak, it's so obvious you're lying.
(Dong Hyun, we can tell that you're lying.)
- We can tell when you speak.
- What?
Tell what?
I'll keep quiet from now on.
- Seung Ho, you speak.
- Right.
Actually,
I didn't say a word on purpose.
Dong Hyun...
doesn't know where we're going.
(That somehow sounds reasonable.)
- He's just...
- I'm just...
He's just driving...
because there's a road ahead of him.
Whatever.
Just get ready to sleep.
- What?
- What? No.
Come on, Yi Kyung.
- Wait a second.
- Then, tell us one thing.
Good night.
Wait, Yi Kyung. Okay. Hold on.
Then...
If you tell us where you're going, we won't make you sleep.
- Okay. That sounds good.
- What?
Changnyeong!
Yangsan!
(Lying and faking)
- Yangnyeong!
- They're going two ways.
It's Yangsan.
- Yangsan, a perfect place to sleep.
- We...
We don't lie.
We're being honest.
- Good night.
- What?
(He hangs up.)
- They're going to Yangsan, right?
- Yes.
- They want to win the center first.
- They're lying...
about Changnyeong.
Gosh. Let us go there.
- Let us ring the bell once.
- Tae Hyun.
We're already here.
(We're almost there.)
(Parking lot)
We are here.
Thanks for driving.
(A temple located in Mount Yeongchuk with a great mountain range)
(Tongdosa Temple in Yangsan)
(What will the national heritage here look like?)
(Tongdosa Temple, Geumgang Ordination Platform)
(Handsome heritage 2: The temple with real Buddha)
It's so nice here.
It looks amazing here.
Isn't Tongdosa Temple really famous?
Right?
- It's really big.
- Yes.
It's so pretty.
There's a monk.
(A monk welcomes Team Guys.)
- Hello.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm the chief of propagation in Tongdosa Temple.
I'm Monk Su Jin.
- "Monk Su Jin." - Hello.
- My daughter is Su Jin too.
- Right.
As for Tongdosa Temple,
it's the largest temple in Korea. So...
- Is it the largest?
- Yes, it is.
- I see.
- That's amazing.
There are three great temples in Korea.
They are called the Three Jewels Temples.
- Three...
- "The Three Jewels Temples?"
Three Jewels?
(Three Jewels)
There are the three great jewels in Buddhism.
Buddha, Dharma,
and monks. Those are the Three Jewels.
The temple symbolizing the Buddha's teaching...
is the one with the Tripitaka Koreana,
which is Haeinsa Temple.
(Dharma Jewel Temple, Haeinsa Temple)
Nineteen monks acted as the advisors for the king.
The temple they were from...
was Songgwangsa Temple, so it's the temple of the monks.
(Sangha temple, Songgwangsa Temple)
As for Tongdosa Temple, we represent the most important,
the Buddha.
(The Buddha!)
(The real Buddha's sarira is preserved in Tongdosa Temple.)
The Buddha sits in Tongdosa Temple.
He watches us himself.
It's Jewel Temple representing the Buddha.
It's the temple of the Buddha.
(Buddha Jewel Temple, Tongdosa Temple)
(Amazed)
We'll go inside...
and see how it looks.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Because Tongdosa Temple is big and famous,
it's the head family of Buddhism.
It's the big temple in the country.
Those are what...
those signs were saying.
Head family of Buddhism and the great temple of the country.
I'll memorize that it's the head family of Buddhism.
Why are you memorizing that?
- Great temple of the country.
- You memorize that.
It's the great temple of the country.
- It's the head family.
- The largest Tongdosa Temple.
In front of us...
is the gate called Cheonwangmun.
The Cheonwangmun acts as a security office.
It prevents the evil people from coming in.
Look to the left.
It's the deity that guards the south.
They guard the four directions, including the north.
You memorize those two.
(Laughing)
- It can be on the quiz.
- Can it?
Gwangmok-cheonwang.
The west is Gwangmok-cheonwang.
The north is "Da."
(They keep memorizing without a reason.)
Come on.
- Jeungjang-cheonwang.
- The north is "Da."
All they care about is the quiz.
The head family of Buddhism.
The east is "Ji."
Jiguk-cheonwang.
The north is Damun-cheonwang.
The north is "Da," and the east is "Ji."
Jeung, Gwang, Da, Ji.
I'll listen to him from here.
We have to study it,
so we should listen to him closer.
What? This is...
You can have them.
They said it was okay to have the free food.
Tae Hyun.
- It's okay to eat the free food.
- Free food is okay, right?
- Free foods are okay to take.
- We can get the free food.
- We have to cheer up.
- That's right.
Let's take a few.
- Can I take a few?
- Yes.
- About three?
- Sure.
- Hurry up.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Sir, can we have these?
- Yes. You can have those.
- Thank you.
(Putting in his mouth)
(Now that they stole some sugary treat...)
They said it was okay to get the free food, and there it was.
Now, we'll go to the Geumgang Ordination Platform...
- where the Buddha is.
- Geumgang Ordination Platform.
- Geumgang Ordination Platform?
- That's right.
(When you go deep into Tongdosa Temple, )
(you encounter a building that is the heart of the temple.)
(National Treasure, Daeungjeon)
- This is the Daeungjeon.
- The Daeungjeon.
There's Daeungjeon in every temple.
That's right.
In fact, at the Daeungjeon in Tongdosa Temple,
the stonework on the bottom is from the Silla Dynasty.
But the wooden building on top of it got burnt down...
during the Japanese invasions of Korea.
It was rebuilt during King Injo's rule.
Since then, it has remained like this.
That stone is...
- hundreds of years old.
- Right.
It's old because it was there since the Silla Dynasty.
It's more than 1,300 years old.
- It's pretty.
- It's amazing.
(And...)
And you see a stone structure in front of you.
(Another national treasure behind the Daeungjeon)
That's the Geumgang Ordination Platform.
(National treasure, Geumgang Ordination Platform)
(The Geumgang Ordination Platform in Tongdosa Temple)
(Selected as the national treasure in 1997 with the Daeungjeon)
(Repaired many times through the Goryeo and the Joseon Dynasty)
(It has the traditional structure of Korean ordination platform.)
To be exact, the tower in the middle is called stupa.
(The stupa that looks like a bell)
The platform that bears the stupa...
is called the Geumgang Ordination Platform.
The whole thing is called Geumgang Ordination Platform?
That's right.
- So...
- That platform.
Ordination is to follow the precept.
The precept?
You have to follow the precept to become a monk.
(The ritual to become a monk is ordination.)
It's called the ordination platform because you become monks here.
(Geumgang Ordination Platform, the platform to get ordination)
Geumgang means diamonds.
With the hope that precept won't break like diamonds,
it's called the Geumgang Ordination Platform.
(It's named so that the precept stays strong like diamonds.)
- It's the whole thing?
- Yes.
That's the Geumgang Ordination Platform.
(The significance of the Geumgang Ordination Platform)
They say the Buddha's sarira is in the stupa.
The stupa in Tongdosa Temple...
has an actual sarira in it.
So, it's called true body sarira.
It's sarira from a true body.
- True...
- True body sarira.
- True body sarira. The real body.
- Yes.
It means true body.
Jajang Yulsa went to China himself.
(When Jajang Yulsa was praying in the Tang Dynasty, )
(Manjusri gave him 100 true body sarira and a robe...)
(of the Buddha.)
He sealed the sarira from India here.
(The sarira of the Buddha was brought and separated...)
(in three bell-shaped stupas in Hwangnyongsa Temple's pagoda, )
(Daehwasa Temple's pagoda, )
(and Tongdosa Temple's ordination platform.)
(Thanks to the Geumgang Ordination Platform, )
(the Tongdosa Temple's Daeungjeon has something different.)
Actually, all Daeungjeon and Buddhist buildings...
have a statue of the Buddha in the middle.
(Generally, )
(the statue of the Buddha is located in Daeungjeon.)
When you look closely,
there's no statue of the Buddha in our Daeungjeon.
No, there isn't one.
(You don't see the statue of Buddha at Tongdosa Temple's Daeungjeon.)
(Why didn't they put the statue?)
Here's the reason.
It's because we believe the real Buddha himself...
sits in the middle of the Geumgang Ordination Platform.
There's no need to put a statue modeled after him...
when the real self is sitting there.
That's why there's no statue in there.
There's only a window where people can see through.
- That's how it was built.
- That's right.
(The Daeungjeon is structured so that you can see the Buddha.)
(It's a significant and religious space for the Buddhists.)
(Even the non believers can see the historical importance...)
(of the Daeungjeon and the Geumgang Ordination Platform.)
Sir, you said the tower there...
- was called a stupa.
- Yes.
Is it a stupa or stuppa?
Stupa.
It's a stupa with one P.
(He got it completely.)
It seems we can't go in there?
You can go in only on special occasions.
(We'll go close to it and look since we can't get inside.)
Gosh. That's how it looks.
It's not stairs. It's a platform.
It's a platform.
(You can feel how magnificent it is up close.)
I thought it was stairs, but it was not.
- It's a platform.
- Right.
(They felt the holiness of the Geumgang Ordination Platform...)
(though it was only for a short moment.)
Thank you, Monk Su Jin.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Goodbye.
Thank you.
By the way, when's your birthday?
My birthday? It's July 4.
- I see. Thank you.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- That was...
Is there a monk whose birthday is this week?
- I don't know about that.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Thank you.
(Team Guys finishes touring Tongdosa Temple.)
(Team Handsome, West Busan)
(Are they getting off at a resting area all of a sudden?)
We can only buy drinks, right?
- You can only buy liquid drinks.
- It's right here.
- Liquids.
Can I buy two since you're buying?
Yes. Drink as much as you want.
Gosh. Jin is buying.
- Get all you want.
- Do I get to see the black card?
I should mark this on my calendar.
"The day Jin bought me an iced tea."
- I'll get the iced tea.
- Grande.
(You're buying, right?)
Thank you.
Jin is buying.
Everyone, Jin is buying.
What's so important?
Gosh. His wallet is Gucci.
(He buys them drinks with a luxurious heart.)
They don't have it.
(Waiting for the drinks)
Hello. He is Jin of BTS.
I see.
- Do you know me?
- Don't you know Jin of BTS?
He's acting. He knows him, of course.
You know who he is, right?
(Confused)
He's Kim Dong Hyun.
(Kim Dong Hyun, the UFC fighter)
(Swordsman Kim Dong Hyun is good with punches too.)
Let me know if you want to dislocate your bones.
(Free manual therapy)
I guess he doesn't watch TV.
(Comforting him)
- He doesn't watch TV.
- That's right.
- Here they are.
- Thank you.
- The sweet potato one.
- Iced tea.
Our staff, are you okay without a drink?
I can buy you a drink if you want.
- Really?
- No way.
We can order it...
- if you're okay with the time.
- We're fine.
Then we have to wait 20 minutes...
- for the drinks to come out.
- Let's go.
(We almost thought World-Wide Handsome bought us a drink.)
We have to keep moving.
I can feel the sugar going in.
My chin just throbbed.
(They do have a long way to go.)
(Team Guys)
There is so much to memorize.
We have no idea what the quiz will be about.
- It's so hard.
- There's so much to memorize.
It's so hard.
(They found Monk Su Jin.)
Monk Su Jin, was it Daebangbangjeon?
What were the names...
of the four deities?
The names of them?
- What?
- They are...
- Jeungjang.
- Jeungjang-cheonwang.
They're cramming for the quiz.
- Dabo-cheonwang?
- Didn't they say Dabo?
- Pyunggyeong-cheonwang?
- Damun-cheonwang.
- Damun-cheonwang?
- Jiguk-cheonwang.
- Jeungjang-cheonwang.
What was the last one?
Memorize them.
We're in trouble. He won't tell us the last one.
I think this is the quiz.
- I don't know.
- Can we study more?
- Yes, you can.
- Go ahead.
Come on. Let's go. Where?
- I'll check the deities.
- Will you?
I'll check the deities.
Damun-cheonwang.
Jiguk-cheonwang.
- Gwangmok-cheonwang.
- Damun.
This is how I memorize things.
- I just memorize the first letter.
- The north is Da. The east is Ji.
- Jeung, Gwang, Da, Ji.
- Dong Hyun.
Why don't we do this?
The south is Jeung. The west is Gwang.
That's how I memorized those.
I can't go beyond four letters.
I'll memorize Jeung, Gwang, Da, Ji.
- I memorized these.
- Yes. Jeung, Gwang, Da, Ji.
- The north is Da.
- Jeung, Jang...
- The east is Ji.
- Jeung, Gwang...
- The south is Jeung.
- Jeung, Gwang, Da, Ji.
- Gwangmok-cheonwang.
- Ji.
- Jiguk-cheonwang.
- Jeungjang-cheonwang.
- Okay. I'll give you the quiz.
- The quiz.
(Nervous)
- Please.
- At Tongdosa Temple,
each building has the eaves.
- What?
- When you see the eaves,
there are pots underneath them.
- The pots underneath the eaves.
- Okay.
If you haven't seen them, you can go and see...
- the eaves near you.
- Have you seen the pots?
- Monk Su Jin!
- Okay, for now.
He didn't mention the pots.
If you can go and check the eaves right behind you...
Where are the pots?
What's in them?
- Before...
- Something like that?
Wait. That one over there?
The brown one between the pillars.
- Which one?
- The brown one over here.
I was going to ask him about it, but I didn't.
Monk Su Jin didn't teach us about it.
He didn't say anything about it.
- I'm certain of it.
- You have to quiz us...
- on what he said.
- This is really...
- We really haven't heard of it.
- We just saw it for the first time.
We've never heard of the pot before.
Rewind the audio and check.
- I...
- Monk Su Jin.
You didn't talk about the pot, did you?
- I was going to ask him about it.
- This is crazy.
Monk Su Jin got too nervous,
and he forgot about it.
There was nothing about the pots.
- Please listen to the whole quiz.
- Okay.
(Please calm down and listen to the quiz.)
- Here's the quiz.
- Okay.
The quiz starts now?
The pot you just saw...
is placed under each eave...
to wish for a good year and prevent fire.
Okay.
They put this in the pots...
as "The seawater prevents fire."
What is this?
They put the seawater in?
- But this is...
- It's not saltwater, is it?
They say it's seawater.
I'll read the quiz again.
- "The seawater prevents fire." - They put...
this in the pots...
- as "The seawater prevents fire." - That's what it means.
- Yes. What is this?
- You don't put out fire with it.
Tae Hyun, they have the same thing in Gyeongbokgung Palace.
They hold some water in front of it.
- Water?
- Like this much.
- That's the ancient extinguisher.
- I see.
It was easy to catch fire because it was a wooden building.
Did they put seawater in it?
No, just water.
It means "The seawater prevents fire."
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yes.
Is this something we've learned?
- Exactly.
- I know.
- I kept memorizing...
- This is really important.
- It's because...
- You're right.
- Come on!
- Jiguk... What was it?
Jeungjang-cheonwang. I memorized all of them.
Jeungjang-cheonwang is the deity of the south.
At the west is Gwangmok-cheonwang.
At the north is Damun-cheonwang.
At the east is Jiguk-cheonwang.
- Jiguk-cheonwang and such.
- But if you ask us about a pot...
(He actually memorized all the deities' names.)
- Seriously.
- We didn't learn about it.
What's in that pot?
(The quiz is different from their expectations.)
The thing is,
you can answer this question by listening carefully.
Hold on. In that case...
- They thought...
- Seawater.
The seawater prevented fire. So what did they put in the pot?
I guess it's water like you said.
- Water.
- Saltwater?
- Saltwater.
- It can't be seawater.
"The seawater prevents fire."
Is it seawater?
- Did they put salt in it?
- Any type of water puts out fire.
- But what's inside the pot?
- Saltwater?
(Carefree)
- That's what we need to guess.
- Tae Hyun, you're incredible.
- Is it saltwater?
- It's salt.
- What?
- Salt.
- Is it salt or saltwater?
It's salt.
Water dries out.
- Water dries out.
- It's salt. Salt prevents fire.
- Really?
- "The seawater prevents fire."
- So they put salt in it.
- In the pot,
they put salt to prevent fire.
- Who are you talking to?
- Salt.
- Is it saltwater?
- Who are you talking to?
- It isn't like that.
- Is it salt?
- What?
- Do you think it's salt?
- I think it's salt.
- It must be salt.
We can get it wrong since we have a reattempt card.
Okay. Let's go.
- Tae Hyun, I'm certain.
- Okay.
I'm the game changer.
- It's salt.
- Okay.
It has to be salt.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Salt.
- What's the answer?
One, two, three.
- Salt.
Salt.
Please.
It has to be right.
It's correct.
(Correct)
This is incredible.
(Happy)
- We did it.
- Hey.
Tae Hyun.
Tae Hyun, we got Yangsan.
- Yangsan. The most important one.
- We didn't even use a hint.
We didn't use a hint.
(Yangsan: Tongdosa Temple's Geumgang Ordination Platform)
Things are going well.
- Nice.
Let me give a brief explanation.
Salt prevents decomposition.
People use salt symbolically...
to ward off evil energy.
On the Dano Day which is May fifth on the Lunar Calendar,
Tongdosa Temple holds a ritual for the Dragon King.
They empty the salt pots...
that were under the eaves of each building...
and fill them with new salt.
(The pots get set up with new salt.)
(The energy of water gets added too.)
(The salt that protected Tongdosa Temple for a year...)
(is given to the followers on the Dano Day.)
- They change the salt.
- It's salt.
I had never seen those pots before.
(They feel the joy of answering a question correctly.)
I have seen them before.
Do we get a meal?
Since you answered correctly,
- you'll get a meal.
- Okay.
- What is it?
- The Yangsan card.
This is incredible.
- On the back is...
- My goodness.
- a dish you can eat here.
This is incredible.
(What's the Yangsan menu that got good reactions?)
(Yangsan: Water parsley pork belly)
(At Yangsan, the city of the water parsley festival, )
(they'll enjoy the combination...)
(of the fragrant water parsley and savory pork belly.)
(The dish is both aromatic and tasty.)
(Water parsley pork belly)
- We don't have to eat it?
- No.
(They can decide whether or not they want a meal.)
Tae Hyun, aren't we going to eat?
- Shouldn't we hurry up?
- It looks so tasty.
- This is a problem.
- Tae Hyun.
- Tae Hyun, it looks so tasty.
- Hunger isn't an important issue.
- Tae Hyun.
- Think about...
- the race.
- I mean...
Tae Hyun, did you have breakfast?
- No, I didn't.
- Then let's have a meal.
- Suppress your hunger, you punk.
- Tae Hyun, they must be eating too.
That was why they didn't put us to sleep.
Hey, none of them would be tempted to have a meal.
Tae Hyun, pork belly can be eaten in Seoul.
But water parsley pork belly can only be eaten here.
It's true.
- It looks so tasty.
- They're the same.
- For goodness' sake.
- We need food for energy.
- We can't think otherwise.
- Unbelievable.
Tae Hyun, the brain uses the most amount of energy.
It uses 22 percent.
The brain uses 22 percent of the basal metabolism.
Twenty-two percent is a lot.
- Right? 22 percent.
- Let's talk on our way.
(Let's talk on our way.)
- The drawing looks so appetizing.
- I know.
Water parsley pork belly.
(Will Team Guys choose water parsley pork belly?)
(Meanwhile, Team Handsome)
(Cuckoo)
- Yangsan?
- Yangsan.
- It's as we expected.
- Yes.
As you can see, we got this square.
- Namhae is so far away.
- I know.
Let's try these two locations.
If we use a reattempt card, we'll be able to get one right.
Once we get one of the squares,
we'll be able to decide which direction to take.
All right. If we answer at once, we won't need a reattempt card.
That's right. Then we won't need to use it.
Then we won't need to be wary.
(They finish the briefing in a relaxed way.)
We're doing well...
thanks to Captain Jin's command.
- It's different.
- It sure is different.
It's easy.
(They have 30 minutes until they reach Upo Wetland.)
(Team Guys)
- Now, we got this square.
- Yes.
(They don't know that Team Handsome is headed to Upo Wetland.)
They're bound to go to Changnyeong.
They have to go to Changnyeong.
Shall we go to Changnyeong then?
Shall we?
Let's say they go...
to Yongseondae, Changnyeong.
If we get Jinju first,
they won't be able to complete the bingo.
They won't reach Jinju from Changnyeong...
while we eat, right?
I wonder where in Changnyeong they're at right now.
If you really want to eat,
we can hold out and have a meal in Jinju.
Once we go there, you'll tell us to hold out again.
- No.
- You'll do that.
- I won't do that.
- That way,
- we'll need to wait forever.
- No.
No. Let's eat in Jinju.
We have time to eat. Do you know why?
- This one involves hiking.
- It'll take a while.
It involves 40 minutes of hiking.
Wouldn't it be better to eat and travel comfortably?
- Eat in Jinju.
- Jinju?
Once we reach Jinju,
you'll go, "We don't have time. Let's eat at the next location."
Won't you do that?
But we need to think about this.
If they put us to sleep while we're eating,
- it'll be game over.
- I see.
Do you prefer going to Jinju then?
- You wanted to eat earlier.
- I'm torn.
You wanted to eat earlier.
- Hey, time is passing.
- We need to hurry up and decide.
(They've been having a meeting for 10 minutes.)
I hope they put us to sleep now.
Then we can lie down and think.
(Laughing)
It'll be perfect.
(Sighing)
- Hey, in that case...
- I'm so indecisive.
Tae Hyun, in that case...
- Hold on.
- Okay.
- I made up my mind.
- Here comes Solomon.
I want to give up on the meal and go to Jinju.
- Shall we go to Jinju?
- Okay.
I made that decision...
because I thought about the possible outcome.
The image of us catching monkfish flitted through my mind.
- We need to avoid that fate.
- Okay.
We should go to Jinju.
The GPS tells me that it takes an hour and a half to get there.
- Okay. Let's go, Tae Hyun.
- Okay.
- Aren't you hungry?
- Are you okay with driving?
- Shall we switch seats?
- Okay, I'll drive.
My goodness.
(The driver gets switched.)
They'll definitely know that we're going...
to Changnyeong.
- It'll take an hour and a half.
- An hour and a half?
- Yes.
- Okay.
(Team Guys heads to Jinju.)
We're entering the market.
I bet they sell water parsley pork belly here.
(Laughing)
(Dong Hyun is ridiculous.)
There's a pork belly restaurant.
Water parsley pork belly sounds so delicious.
(He's still hung up on the water parsley pork belly.)
- Water parsley.
- Gosh.
I see that Dong Hyun is a handful.
It's so tasty when it's grilled.
I see that you love to eat.
Of course, I love it.
Tae Hyun, we'll eat if we answer correctly in Jinju.
Okay. I promise that.
We have to eat then.
I promise that.
(They'll revolt if he doesn't make a promise.)
Where is the board? Let me see it.
Tae Hyun.
Let me make a cautious guess.
Let's say we get Jinju...
and they get Upo Wetland, Changnyeong.
Don't say that we need to go to Namhae right away, okay?
We have to eat, okay?
- Okay.
Jinju.
(Team Guys' mission: Eat in Jinju no matter what.)
(A bit later)
(Focused facial expression and busy hands)
(He's looking up something on YouTube.)
- Tae Hyun.
- Yes?
Just in case,
I looked up how monkfish was caught.
- Can you guess the first video?
- What is it?
"Extreme Job."
("Extreme Job")
Catching monkfish is considered an extreme job.
- My goodness.
- You set off early in the morning.
(The monkfish boat sets off early in the morning.)
It isn't fishing we have in mind.
You need to throw and pull up the net.
- It's like commercial fishing.
- Totally.
Tae Hyun, they can bite and cut off your hands.
I heard that they could cut your fingers.
We have to focus on winning.
- Unbelievable.
- We have to do that.
(Team Handsome)
That's the road to Changnyeong.
(Changnyeong)
It's my first time visiting Changnyeong.
Don't you think that we can buy anti-drowsiness gum?
I think it'll be okay.
It's not like we'll swallow it to fill our stomachs.
That's right.
All right.
(Sang Uk remains silent.)
They can hear us, but we act like we're talking to ourselves.
(Restless)
It'll be for the adults.
(He seems to be looking for something desperately.)
I'm hungry. Aren't you hungry?
Of course, I'm hungry.
I really want to use the restroom.
(The red alert for the restroom gets issued in the car!)
Hey, you should've told me sooner.
We should make a stop if we see a restroom.
There isn't a gas station nearby, is there?
There must be something like a restaurant.
(Is it the effect of iced tea?)
Hang in there. We'll find something.
(Consoling)
I can't believe there's a crane truck in front of us.
It'll be nice if it can let us pass.
(The crane truck drives slowly.)
I enjoy overcoming such hardships.
- Is that so?
- I'm an athlete.
It's no wonder you got the gold medal.
It makes sense.
I know. The gold medalist sure is different.
Overcoming hardships.
If there were no hardships,
I wouldn't have been so appreciative.
Do you want to pee in nature?
I can't do it in nature.
I can't do it in nature since I have a stomachache.
(I have a stomachache.)
- Is it number two?
- Yes.
- You should've said so.
- Is it number two?
- There's a village. Hold on.
- If it's number two...
- That changes things.
- Seriously.
My goodness.
- Why didn't you say so?
- Seriously.
Look at this. I'm driving hurriedly now.
- It's okay.
- I thought it was number one.
I enjoy hardships.
There's a community center.
Nice.
- Here.
- A community center.
The door is open.
(The door is open.)
- Okay.
- Try knocking.
- There.
- It's a restroom.
Hurry up and go to the restroom.
How nice.
- Check if there's toilet paper.
- Okay.
(Thanks to the older members, he enters the restroom relaxedly!)
We need to find toilet paper if there isn't any.
I think it's too small for you.
- There's toilet paper.
- It's so cramped.
It's a nice restroom.
- Because you're tall...
- It's too small.
Sang Uk, take your time.
(We're adjusting the screen to protect the medalist's dignity.)
(Team Guys)
(My goodness)
(The worrywart has another worry.)
I think they're going to Jinju.
- You think they're going to Jinju.
- Tae Hyun,
I'm someone who wrote a book on psychology.
Stop it already.
(Dong Hyun, stop talking big.)
I wrote "Kim Dong Hyun's Lesson on Mentality."
Tae Hyun, trust my hunch.
They're going to Jinju.
I think...
they'll go to Changnyeong.
In that case,
why don't we check their location?
Tae Hyun.
We already took Yangsan.
We just need to know...
whether they're going to Jinju or Changnyeong...
to block them.
- It'll be easy for us.
- Yes.
Then we'll know...
- if there'll be a switch.
- That's right.
Our current location is...
We're right before the crossroads...
- of Changnyeong and Jinju.
- Okay.
- We should check now.
- It's the perfect timing.
- We'll use the card...
to check the other team's current location.
We'll message you the location.
I'm curious.
(Curious)
Please.
(This is the location of Team Handsome.)
They're in Changnyeong.
- Upo Wetland.
- They're going to Upo Wetland.
Yes. We can see Upo in the map.
- Are they going to Upo?
- Yes.
Hold on.
(Jinju is incorrect!)
Are they willing to go to Namhae?
It's okay. We're going to Jinju.
We can go to Namhae afterward.
Because of that,
you're going to postpone eating.
We should eat something.
- Seriously.
- We need to reach Jinju quickly.
I have a feeling that he'll tell us not to eat...
since they can put us to sleep.
(Team Handsome)
We're nearly there.
- It's in 700m.
Just what will we do here?
(The road suddenly becomes unpaved.)
What's this?
Why is this road...
(Team Handsome drives along the bumpy road in the forest.)
What's this place?
(What kind of a place is Upo Wetland?)
(He spots something.)
Sanbakbeol?
It must be a popular travel destination...
since there's a sign.
Shouldn't we go left? Go left.
Go left.
(Which way should I go?)
The curator will get in the car...
and you'll listen to the explanation in the form of a safari tour.
In the car?
Will the curator get in the car?
- I'll welcome the curator.
- Okay.
- Hello.
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
- You must've waited long.
- Not really.
I had to use the restroom.
Ma'am, please fasten your seatbelt.
- Okay. Please go left.
- Shall we go left?
(It's the wetland that has the wonders of the ancient times.)
I'm in charge of Changnyeong's national heritage.
I'm Curator Kim Mi Jung.
It's nice to meet you. There must be...
a department that's dedicated to the national heritage.
The official name for Upo Wetland is...
the Changnyeong's Upo Wetland Natural Reserve.
- This is the place, right?
- Yes.
(Changnyeong's Upo Wetland Natural Reserve)
(Upo, Mokpo, Sajipo, Sanbakbeol, and Jjokibeol)
(The area is made of 3 wetlands that end with "Po...")
(and 2 wetlands that end with "Beol.")
There are many marshes here.
How big is the area?
It's about 2,600,000m in size.
It's estimated to be made...
when the Korean peninsula came to be 140 million years ago.
Since it has been around for a long time,
people often say...
that Upo Wetland has...
the wonders of the ancient times.
(Exclaiming)
The reeds look insanely beautiful.
- Seriously.
- It's a field of reeds.
(Opening the window)
It's nice.
(After a brief explanation, the scenery looks different.)
This place is open.
A trip to this place will be therapeutic.
People can come here and walk.
Look at the tree. It's so big.
It must be a protected tree. It looks old.
(It's the handsome heritage site they encountered today.)
In 1998, it was listed as a protected wetland...
by the Ramsar Convention.
There's better news. In 2024,
UNESCO listed Changnyeong-gun as a biosphere reserve.
Was it listed this year?
Yes. It means that the value of the location...
is well-known worldwide.
Many aquatic plants live in Upo Wetland.
About 60 percent of the aquatic plants in Korea...
live in Upo Wetland.
Sixty percent?
A freshwater turtle species of Korea, Reeves' turtle...
- also lives in Upo Wetland.
- Reeves' turtle.
About 180 migratory birds...
visit every winter. It's a habitat for migratory birds.
It's called the haven for migratory birds.
You can find birds that are Korea's national monuments...
such as tundra swans and bean geese.
Look at that man.
He's birdwatching with binoculars.
You're right. He's birdwatching.
- There are many dabbling ducks.
- Dabbling ducks.
So you'll see many visitors.
(They arrive at the destination, Mokpo Embankment.)
- Let's get off here.
- We're stopping here, right?
This place is so big.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
(Let's walk on the Mokpo Embankment and explore Upo Wetland.)
Does it cost money?
- No, you can use it.
- I see that it's free.
I'm curious. There are birds.
- They usually cost 50 cents.
- I know.
I can see well.
Can you see...
- Take a look.
- Can you see the ducks?
We're looking at the birds, right?
(Jin becomes curious and looks through the telescope.)
- Can you see the birds?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- They look pretty big.
(The giant youngest member goes last.)
- The image is so clear.
- Yes.
- There are so many birds.
- You're right.
- They're gathered in one place.
- The image is big.
You're right.
I can see them.
(They look once more using binoculars.)
How are they fast?
(Both the bird that hop...)
(and the bird that walks elegantly live here.)
- What?
- What's that?
What? What is it?
(There are birds everywhere they see.)
Is it a fight?
They're coming in a line.
They're making ripples.
What are those birds?
They look like ducks.
In Upo Wetland, you can see migratory birds.
Have you heard of a crested ibis?
Of course.
Wasn't there a song about it? Ibis, ibis
- You know the song.
- Yes.
The place where you can see the most number of crested ibises...
is Upo Wetland.
In 1979, crested ibises disappeared.
They went extinct in Korea.
In 2019, they were restored...
- and released in the wild.
- That's incredible.
- To this day, - How were they restored?
The birds are protected in the area.
Back in the day, new folders in the computer...
got names such as "Crested ibis."
- That's right.
- You remember, right?
- Yes.
- That's right.
They were named after birds.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Another name was "Grey heron."
That's right.
You can see all of those birds here.
We tell the visitors that Upo Wetland is...
the living museum of natural history.
So I hope many people will visit Upo Wetland...
and check out the ecosystem.
- Thank you for the nice tour.
- Thank you.
- Shall we have the quiz?
- Okay.
After seeing and learning something new,
- this is the main event.
- That's right.
There are various tales that are related to Upo Wetland.
- I'll tell you one of the tales.
- Okay.
Once upon a time,
at a valley called Aegol near the place...
lived a "blank" family.
One day, a big rainstorm hit...
and the baby of the family got washed away.
The father left to save the baby,
but never came back.
In a worried state, the mother set off to find them.
Then she came across a pine branch...
her husband rode next to a rock.
Until the cold winter came, she didn't leave the rock.
She waited tearfully.
In the end, her body froze...
and she became a black rock.
Afterward, the name of the rock became...
"Blank" Rock.
What goes in the blank?
Give us the choices.
There are...
- no choices.
- Come on.
- This is a hard one.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
- It might be a bit hard.
We need to make deductions.
Most rock names have two syllables.
- "Blank" Rock.
- Ulsan Rock.
"She became a black rock."
"Black."
(Black)
- "Ice." - "Black Ice?"
"Black Ice?"
- "Black Ice Rock?" - "Black Ice Rock."
It sounds like the name of a bingsu.
"Black Ice Rock." It doesn't sound promising.
(It was "blank" family.)
(Black Ice sounds totally off.)
It's the name of a black rock.
(They have no idea.)
"Blank" Family. "Blank" Rock.
Is the same word used for both of them?
Yes.
- We have to find that word.
- I see.
- It must be an animal.
- You think it's an animal?
It must be a family from stories from the past.
Is it the Migratory Bird Family?
The Frog Family. The Pig Family.
It won't be the Super Radical Gag Family.
(The sudden attack of the Super Radical Gag Family)
Why would it be the Super Radical Gag Family?
That was the only family I could think of.
"Blank" Family.
If that happens to be the actual answer...
It would be something like the Beaver Family or Turtle Family.
It would be a really simple word.
Bird Family Rock.
(Bird Family Rock)
This place is known for the birds.
If the baby didn't leave...
and was swept down by the flood,
won't it be an animal that lives in the water?
The Turtle Rock? The Turtle Family?
- Turtle?
- It sounds plausible.
More than it being a bird,
I think there's a higher possibility of it being a turtle.
Birds fly.
There's no reason for a bird to be swept away with a branch.
Won't it be something simple?
You'll be surprised by how simple it is.
Right.
- The Super Radical Gag Family?
- But...
(The Super Radical Gag Family?)
It's not that one, my friend!
That sounds like a simple answer to me.
If we know the number of characters...
- Let's try to go for the answer.
- Okay.
- I have no clue.
- So what did we decide on?
I'm not sure.
Bird Family could be a good shout.
- Go with it.
- All right.
- We'll go for the answer!
- Right.
This rock is called...
I feel bad about calling it out as it doesn't seem right.
Let's think about it one more time.
- Right.
- That's such a great idea!
That's such a great idea!
Let's think about it one more time.
(The rock that appears in a fable of Upo Wetland)
(What is the name of it?)
(Team Guys)
Tae Hyun.
Should I carefully make another prediction?
It has been a while since they arrived at Upo.
I don't think they got the answer.
That can't be true.
Upo was just five minutes away.
They got it wrong.
When are they going to come?
They won't beat us now.
Everything has been decided.
They can never beat us now with how things have panned out.
(They enter Jinju while being certain about their win.)
All right. We have around ten minutes left to Jinju.
Jinju feels like...
the city of victory for us.
- Why?
- I can feel it.
The birthday person is definitely here.
Stay in the car. I'll get it quickly.
(He moves quickly to get the cake.)
- Can I get this one?
- Right.
- I'll take that one.
- Okay.
- It's a gift for someone.
- Right.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Thank you.
Okay. Done.
It's our first day together, but we're a perfect team.
The bread smells nice.
You can smell bread?
I think I can smell it slightly.
- I can smell things like donuts.
- I can smell something savory.
It's from your clothes.
- I smell donuts.
- Right.
- I'm serious.
- No way.
You two must be really hungry.
I want to buy a cologne that smells like that.
- Gosh, I'm hungry.
- We're here.
Can we celebrate their birthday with them...
and have the cake with them?
(Can we have the cake too?)
Because we're hungry?
- We can charge up there.
- That's a great idea.
It can become a greater memory...
- when the cake is shared.
- Right.
- Nice one, Seung Ho.
- That's a great idea.
Right.
(After dreaming big about winning and the cake...)
Did they really not get it right?
- I'm 100 percent certain.
- Even until now?
It only makes sense that way.
- They went somewhere else.
- No way.
(What is the result of Team Handsome's quiz?)
(Team Handsome)
This is what I got.
- It's "Blank" family.
- It's an animal that lives...
by the water.
Frogs. Turtles.
I still believe that Bird Family is the biggest shout.
You should go with what you feel is right.
Go with what you want.
Super Radical Gag Family?
(He wants to feel better after saying completely wrong.)
- What are we doing?
- After all of that discussion.
This is driving me crazy.
What a shame. We came all the way here.
It's a shame that we have to...
- go somewhere else.
- Do you know what's bad about it?
He had to poop on our way here.
He went on the unpaved road,
saw a bird, and did this and that.
Now, he's talking about the Super Radical Gag Family.
(Embarrassed)
(Jin is lost in thought.)
If only I didn't go to the restroom.
No.
You have to take care of your business.
I just saw a frog hopping around over there.
(I just saw a frog hopping around over there.)
(Hopping)
Wasn't that a sign from above for the answer?
- You should go.
- I keep looking over there.
You should go.
(The right is handed over to him right away.)
- I can't go.
- This is what happens.
- But I don't think it's "Bird." - Really?
"Turtle."
Go with what you want.
- What are we even talking about?
- Jin!
You should go for it.
- You should go.
- Just go for it.
- My gosh!
- Gosh!
- What's wrong?
There was something pointy on my hand.
There it is. It was some kind of grasshopper.
- Really?
- It was a grasshopper.
That really got me awake.
- "Grasshopper Rock?" - "Grasshopper Family?"
It could've been saying, "It's me!"
It's hinting at us.
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Okay.
You'll go with "Bird" if you win.
He'll go with "Turtle" if he wins.
- I'll go with "Frog" if I win.
- Okay.
- Let's have no regrets.
- No regrets.
- Okay.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(Sang Uk and "Turtle" get eliminated.)
- I have to lose.
(I have to lose.)
Rock-paper-scissors.
(Seok Jin wins.)
Okay!
It's definitely "Turtle."
(Roaring)
Why did I have to win?
(Feeling so much pressure)
All right. Please say your answer.
All right. Frog Rock!
(Frog Rock)
Frog Rock.
All right. Frog Rock!
(Frog Rock)
Frog Rock.
Correct!
(Frog is correct!)
Gosh!
(Feeling extremely happy)
Really?
Yes. That is the correct answer.
- I told you!
- Gosh!
- Seriously?
- That was insane.
I said it was "Frog!"
What would've happened...
if I lost in rock-paper-scissors?
This makes no sense.
I'm feeling goosebumps all over.
- I'm feeling goosebumps.
- Seriously.
Here's the explanation.
(There's a huge rock in front of the valley.)
In the Gyeongsang Province, a rock is called "deom."
From the side,
the rock was formed like a frog's mouth.
That was why the elders called that rock the Frog Deom.
And that was how that story was passed down.
One, two, three.
- Frog!
- Okay.
- We did it.
(Upo Wetland)
- That was insane.
- The thrill was insane.
My heart is pounding right now.
- Gosh. That was great.
- Hear my heart.
- It's beating really fast.
- To be honest, - It's beating really fast.
Things would go wild if he doesn't join our show.
I can't believe this.
He has to carry on with this energy every week.
Don't you want to feel this thrill every week?
Get the sticker first!
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
That was insane.
Thanks to Seok Jin,
- we now have...
- We got it done.
- Check this out.
- "Frog."
We got Changnyeong and Busan down.
We're secure our bingo with just Namhae.
(They are in the best place with just Namhae left!)
This feels great.
- Awesome!
- That was great.
- Seriously.
- This feels really great!
That was really great.
- Did they really not get it right?
- I'm 100 percent certain.
- Really?
- Oh, right.
(Cuckoo)
- Right.
- Changnyeong, Upo Wetland.
- All right.
- They occupied Upo Wetland?
Where do you think they will go next?
They will definitely go to Namhae.
- Namhae?
- Of course.
(An ominous feeling surrounds them all of a sudden.)
Then we'll meet them there.
Right.
(Using all of his brain power)
We're in trouble then.
(Emergency situation for Team Guys)
If they go to Namhae from here...
How long does it take from Changnyeong to Namhae?
It takes 2 hours and 5 minutes.
We'll take 1 hour 15 minutes to get to Namhae from Jinju.
When we take the quiz in Jinju,
we have to take a 30-minute nap.
Won't it be dangerous for us?
We must move quickly no matter what.
We have no time.
- Are we here?
- It's over there.
We have no time.
We must hurry.
(To occupy Namhae first)
It's a race against time.
Right, we must be diligent.
We plan to arrive in Namhae in two hours.
We must move diligently.
Let me see how long it takes from here.
One hour and 17 minutes.
It takes a long time. Goodness.
What if we have to work?
How about we pass...
this one and go straight to Namhae?
We have to calculate time for our nap.
It's better that we skip here. What do we do?
That's the only way.
We have a better chance of winning that way.
(Will they give up Jinju?)
- What should we do?
- We must decide.
(What will Team Guys choose?)
(If we occupy Namhae in Namhae, )
(then it's game over.)
(They must win Namhae to finish the bingo.)
(To avoid the penalty work, )
(Namhae Battle starts.)
(A long way to Namhae)
(However, the biggest problem is)
(Extreme starving)
(Who would eat at the thought of working?)
(They must stay alert until the end.)
(The hidden treasure race hasn't ended.)
(It's overwhelming.)
(Their first game of bingo with many twists)
(Which team will be the first to complete a bingo?)
Dramaday.me