So pretty.
Yeah.
Let's take a few more.
This spot is great.
Let's take a family photo later.
Cheese.
No, thank you.
Zhi Mei,
did you prepare all these for me?
I remember telling you
that no matter how busy my parents were,
they would always take photos
they would take photos for me.
You actually remember that.
That proves I planned it well.
Zhimei,
from now on,
I'll be with you
throughout your life.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
That's it?
Great, really good.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm a photographer.
You two are so sweet.
Can I take a picture of you?
Sure.
Wu Xi.
I remember
your face clearly.
Zhimei.
Don't be bothered by those noises.
Just look at me
with your eyes and heart.
I will help you
clear away all those bad emotions
and memories.
The good news is that
the blood clot pressing on your optic nerve
has basically been absorbed.
The recovery of your vision
is just a matter of time.
Yes.
Mr. Wu,
the next part
will involve a deep psychological assessment of the patient.
which requires a private discussion.
Please wait outside.
You can go now.
Okay.
Here's the thing.
Based on your description,
you can't recognize the face of the person close to you,
and even firmly believe
that he has been replaced,
accompanied by cognitive biases
towards reality and the world.
These typical characteristics
are consistent with
the rare Capgras delusion after a severe injury.
Impossible.
This is ridiculous.
How is that possible?
I know.
It's hard to accept.
I've been the Ye family's doctor
since the former chairman started his business.
I have no reason
to lie to you.
What you need now
to trust the judgment of a professional
and
cooperate with the treatment.
Dr. Zhang,
how is she?
Let's give her the medication first
and observe the effects.
This is a nerve stabilizer
that can help her vision recover more steadily.
Thank you.
Zhi Mei,
be good,
Take the medicine.
Am I
really hallucinating?
Good girl.
Drink some water.
Okay, take a rest.
Lie down.
Take a nap.
I'll be right back.
Mr. Zhou,
I've sung the opera
you asked me to sing
as you asked.
As for
the expansion project,
it's almost done.
Thank you, Mr. Zhou.
Ye Zhimei
now holds such a large fortune.
She's like a lamb to the slaughter.
Not just you people,
even I...
Her name
is defiled coming out of your mouth.
If you can't control your mouth next time,
what you lose
will be more than just a little blood.
Understood.
Sir, Madam,
welcome home.
Why haven't I seen
these people before?
The previous ones weren't attentive enough.
These new ones
know better how to take care of you.
You.
Prepare the bathroom for me.
Yes, ma'am.
How's the water?
Ma'am, the water temperature is fine.
Ma'am, are you okay?
I'm fine. Leave me alone.
Yes, ma'am.
The only rule you have in this house
is to take care of the wife.
Everything
should prioritize the wife's safety and comfort.
You have to report everything
to the husband.
Now take out your phone and write it down.
First,
the wife and the husband should eat light.
Remember that.
What's wrong?
Sorry, sir.
I think I left my phone in the bathroom.
Zhi Mei.
Are you in there?
Zhi Mei!
Do you know the girl in the photo?
She's my friend. She's missing.
Zhi Mei!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just in a bad mood recently.
I wanna stay in the water
to think about things.
It's getting late.
Go to bed.