Thank you.
Our young lady is
the heir of Chenghai Group.
Her life has been
laid out since birth.
Your lives
are destined not to intersect.
Of course,
if you have any needs,
you can also make demands.
Fortunately, it's a low-concentration corrosive reagent.
The wound isn't too deep.
Change the dressing on time.
The attacker has been taken away by the police.
He's being interrogated.
I believe we'll get the results soon.
Thank you.
I always get hurt and make you worry.
Don't take such risks in the future.
But I'm happy.
Finally, I got a chance to save you.
As long as it's you,
no matter how many times I get hurt,
it's worth it.
Mr. Wu, you're in a wheelchair,
but you're so agile
to jump like that.
The timing was just perfect.
If it's a coincidence,
you seem to have more coincidences
than I do.
Too many coincidences
make people wonder.
Zhou Xubai,
come out with me.
Is Mr. Wu Xi attacked
related to Mr. Zhou Xubai
from Lanze Capital?
Mr. Ye,
sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry, Mr. Ye is not available for interviews now.
Mr. Ye is not available for interviews now.
Sorry.
Stop!
Mr. Ye, Mr. Ye.
Why are you here?
The media
are scrutinizing me and Chenghai Group.
Your presence
in this spotlight
will only bring more trouble.
So you've decided
to stand by his side again?
It's fine.
I can be the one
who remains unseen.
As long as you need me,
I'll always be there.
Just don't push me away again.
Zhou Xubai,
there's no chance
between us.
So you decided
to be with him?
What are you trying to do?
[How do you like]
[this big gift?]
[I've got something even bigger coming up.]
Meimei,
you've been zoning out for half an hour.
Jiayi, do you think I should
I should go back to Wu Xi?
He's sacrificed so much for me,
even nearly lost his life.
If I follow my heart,
wouldn't that be too selfish?
But you need to think clearly.
Is it love or guilt
that's driving your decision?
Mei,
feelings can't be weighed on a scale,
and they can't be compensated with self-sacrifice.
Close your eyes
and try to imagine a picture.
At a time that makes you feel
very safe and happy,
you are waiting for someone to appear.
Don't try too hard.
Let him appear in your mind naturally.
See who he is.
Xiaomei.
The case has made a major breakthrough.
The attacker has confessed
and identified the mastermind.
Zhou Xubai.
These are the call records
and transaction records provided by the attacker
to the police.
Make her feel threatened,
but be discreet.
Don't let her die.
Understood?
It's the first time I've received such a strange request.
Boss,
what do you want
to get by spending so much money?
I want her to think of me
the only one she can think of
when she's in panic.
You should be familiar with his voice.
I specifically asked a technician
to check it out.
This voice
is not AI synthesized.
I want to be the only one
she can think of
when she's in panic.
I want to be the only one
she can think of
when she is in panic.
Hello.
Can I
hear your voice?
Hello.
I remember it's here. Why can't I find it?
Zhi Mei.
What are you doing?
What are you looking for?
Do you remember this phone?
There are many memories of us in it.
Unfortunately, I don't remember the password.
Can you
help me open it?
It's your birthday.
How could I forget?
Really?
You still remember after such a long time.
The PR department said
that after the incident
was exposed,
the public opinion has become much more positive.
So I want to take
this opportunity
to arrange another exclusive interview.
Are you willing to do it with me?
Of course, I am.
As long as I can be with you,
I can do anything.