Where's your phone lover?
You haven't met after all this chatting?
None of your business.
You're the campus belle, the ideal of humanity,
the dream of countless young men.
And you're into voice chat?
And single-threaded at that.
The input-output ratio is too low.
We'll meet soon, okay?
Once I see him,
I'll finish this painting.
He's not meeting you
he must be ugly
and afraid to be seen.
Who are you calling ugly?
Him.
Don't touch my painting.
It's not dry yet.
Don't touch the pink one next to it.
Jiayi, that's the one next to it.
Jiayi.
I'm getting mad.
It took me a long time to finish it.
You can draw another one next time.
Does it hurt? I'll be gentler.
It's fine. It doesn't hurt when you do it.
Zhimei,
I was wrong about yesterday.
I was too anxious.
I just
missed the old days when we were together.
Tomorrow is your birthday.
Do you remember our promise
to spend every birthday together
no matter what?
I remember.
Do you know when she lies,
her fingers will squeeze tightly?
Thank you for remembering.
Mr. Ye,
are you here to hold me accountable?
I have a very profitable deal,
which you should be interested in.
Okay.
But I want to talk to you
alone.
This is the core data of Chenghai for five years,
and the profit forecast for the next three years.
Although the valuation is low at the moment,
the foundation is solid,
and the assets are of high quality.
Moreover,
Lanze is best at discovering value depressions.
Investing in Chenghai
aligns with your investment logic
and the basic interests of Lanze.
Your analysis is very good
and thorough.
But Zhimei,
why are you so sure
I won't take this opportunity
to negotiate other terms with you?
If you
want to try other ways,
I don't mind
using Wu Xi's minor injury certificate
to invite you to the police station for a cup of tea.
Although the injury is not serious,
it's enough to get Lanze's directors
into trouble.
Very good.
You've learned to bite.
The negotiation between Lanze and Chenghai
can be restarted.
But the data you have now
is just the tip of the iceberg.
Chenghai
is much deeper
and more complicated than you think.
Who are you?
This is a restricted area.
No outsiders are allowed.
During the internal audit,
during the audit.
Check it!
Stop!
We didn't receive any notice.
Where's the board's approval?
I'm the chairwoman of Chenghai Group,
Ye Zhimei.
The finance department is temporarily suspended.
All original vouchers,
electronic accounting records,
and bank statements
are to be sealed and taken away.
for auditing purposes.
Focus on
all transactions
and bridge financing
with subsidiaries over the past five years,
especially the overseas portion.
Also,
all participants, please do not leave the venue.
Yes.
Look here.
Did you sleep well?
I'm sorry, Mr. Zhou.
I've delayed the progress.
The preliminary investigation has clarified
the suspicious fund flow,
suspicious accounts,
and a few departments
and individuals that need special attention.
They're all marked.
This account's
fund flow is suspicious.
Smart.
According to the timeline,
it was shortly after your parents
your parents' death,
someone colluded to
drain Chenghai.
[Sir, a financial officer]
[is trying to escape]
[with documents from the parking lot.]
Looks like we've hooked a big fish.
Let's go.
I'm coming too.
Situation unclear.
Splitting up is more efficient.
You handle the surveillance.
I'll intercept.
Be careful.
OK.
Get down.
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
It's okay.
Zhi Mei, you care about me so much.
Don't think you can take advantage of my concern.
We don't have that kind of relationship anymore.