So what are you planning to do next?
I want to investigate Yan Jiu again.
I've run out of leads for now.
Maybe with Yan Jiu,
there are clues about my identity.
A big businessman.
Yan Jiu.
It's said the Japanese have been watching him for a while.
There's a Yan residence on Fuxing Road.
But it's definitely dangerous.
I have no other choice.
Take it easy.
How about this,
I'll go buy you some medicine first.
Wait until you've recovered.
Then you can think about what to do next.
It's not too late.
I'm leaving now.
Miss, take a look at these flutes.
Cigarettes for sale.
Feather dusters for sale.
Handmade flutes.
No, thank you.
Take a look.
Brother.
There they are.
Over there, chase them!
Chase!
Watch out.
Stop!
Don't run!
You, stop right there!
Stop!
Stop! Stop!
Run!
Keep running, Little Pepper.
Aren't you good at running?
Fat Jin.
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
You really have the nerve to come see me.
And you even try to stop me.
You're suspected of betraying the party.
I've already reported you to the station chief.
You'll be expelled from the party.
But,
if you beg me nicely now,
maybe I can put in a good word for you with the chief.
Say a few nice things for you.
Help you get out of trouble.
But if you still don't know what's good for you,
What are you doing?
Step back.
What?
No evidence?
You want to execute me on the spot?
Accuse me of betraying the party?
Fat Jin.
You'd better watch what you say.
If you have the guts today,
come back to the Shanghai station with me.
Explain everything clearly and openly.
If you don't have the guts,
then hurry up
and get out of here with your tail between your legs.
Fine, fine, fine.
Still so sharp-tongued.
What a pity.
Now, should I crush you flat or roll you into a ball?
It's entirely up to me.
Where is it?
Hand it over.
What are you talking about?
Still pretending to be clueless?
You secretly investigated the military warehouse.
And you even stole the safe's key.
Give it to me now.
I might let you go.
Take it out.
So what you've been thinking about all along
is that key.
That key seems pretty important.
If it's gone,
then inside the safe,
the untraceable firearms and gold
can't be taken out.
Enough with the nonsense.
Give it to me.
Back.
Alright, alright, back, back, back.
No.
Back.
Back, back, back.
It's this key, right, Fatty Jin?
Yes, yes, that's right.
Chili, don't get so worked up.
It's just a key.
Give it, give it to me.
I'll give it to you.
As long as you can catch it.
It's yours.
You two, go after them!
Hurry up!
Go.
What are you standing around for?
Get down there and fish it out!
They went that way.
Boss.
They should be nearby.
He's definitely connected to Master Jiu's death.
Catch him.
Finish him off.
Yes.
Boss, we've found them.
They're over there.
Let's go.
Go.
Boss.
They're inside.
Search.
Yes.
Teacher
It's windy outside
Let's go inside
Just thinking about going back to Shanghai
keeps me tossing and turning, unable to sleep
In the middle of the night
I always think of those years
and that wonton shop in front of the Shanghai office
In the blink of an eye
seven years have passed
Teacher, what are you worried about?
Chengchun
tell me
the plan set by Director Dai
what is it for?
To sabotage the peace conference
jointly held by the Japanese cabinet and the Wang puppet government
The peace conference
what is it for?
The fighting in Central China is intense
The Japanese army is advancing straight toward Chongqing
What they are plotting
is nothing more than to better
control the areas of our country that have already fallen
That's right
The Battle of Wuhan
cost the Japanese army two hundred thousand casualties
It really shook their foundation
It was an unprecedented pyrrhic victory for them
I believe, to some extent
it has already dealt a blow to Japan's ambition to annex China
So
they are trying to create
a false image of peace and prosperity
so they can make a comeback
We absolutely cannot give them this chance
But there's one thing
that's quite suspicious.
Ever since we received the tip-off,
more than twenty days have passed.
Our intelligence network
hasn't been able to detect any
confidential information related to the Peace Conference.
All we know is that the conference will be held in thirty days
somewhere in the northern district of Shanghai.
The exact location,
the schedule for the day,
the conference agenda,
and the documents to be signed—
we know nothing about any of it.
It is indeed suspicious.
As far as I know,
just the puppet government alone
plans to send over two hundred officials to attend.
With such a big event,
such a large-scale operation,
yet all along,
we only hear about it on the surface,
but never see its essence.
Before returning to Shanghai this time,
I arranged for Lu Xijian to be transferred to the Shanghai station
precisely to uncover
the secrets behind the Peace Conference.
I just didn't expect
that the two agents I personally placed
would both meet with accidents one after another.
It's like a fog is clouding our vision.
It seems that if we want to find out
what's really hidden behind the Peace Conference,
we'll have to take it one step at a time.
No matter what,
we must find a way to destroy it.
Yes.
Teacher
The weather is about to change.
A storm is brewing in the mountains.
The wind fills the building.
What is meant to come
will always come.
I'm back.
So many cops around.
It's not usually this strict.
These are unusual times.
If no one questioned me,
that would actually be strange.
The guys heard you were back.
Everyone was really excited.
They wanted to throw a welcome party for you.
But right now,
let's skip the party.
Of the old crew,
how many are left?
Not many.
After you retired,
we've been struggling too.
Some died,
some got hurt.
Those who stayed,
are just trying to make a living,
working for Wang Mutian,
getting by at the Shanghai station.
This time, I came
to help you get your place back.
Drive.
Old Dong
Boss, the usual, please.
Alright, have a seat first.
Old Lu
You know, right?
Something big happened in Shanghai recently.
What happened?
Master Jiu is dead.
Big Brother
He should be somewhere around here.
Master Jiu's death is definitely connected to him.
Catch him.
Take him out.
Take a look, everyone.
This is the latest news.
They say he had an accident out of town.
Yan Residence
They're holding a memorial right now.
Really?
He was perfectly fine,
how could he just die like that?
These days,
you never know.
Someone as kind as Master Jiu,
usually,
not only helped with disaster relief,
but also did favors for the gangs.
Who wouldn't show him some respect?
Besides, the poor people around here
have all received his help in one way or another.
That's right, that's true.
I just can't believe he died in an accident.
I heard he was in Shanghai not long ago,
and was even invited to Hongkou for tea.
Stop, stop.
It's not good to talk about things like this carelessly.
Who are you?
That's pretty strange.
Do you know each other?
No, we don't.
This person is pretty strange.
Have you found Shadow?
Not yet.
We're still investigating.
We still can't be sure yet.
What exactly happened to Shadow.
But according to the informant's report,
the Military Police and Unit 76
are at Ruijin Building and Tailong Trading
hunting down suspicious individuals.
The key point is,
this person successfully
escaped from Hirata Xizi's pursuit.
You suspect it's him?
The time and place match.
But we can't be sure.
Logically,
his mission was to find out from Yan Jiu
where the explosives went.
There was no need to show up at those two places.
Doing this is too risky.
Unless he
Unless what
These actions
are too reckless
They don't seem like something he would do at all
Teacher
Maybe there's a special reason
Normally
if he returned to Shanghai
he would contact the Yan family right away
The current plan
is already in chaos
We can't judge by common sense
I just hope
his identity won't be exposed
Turn left ahead
Let's go somewhere first
Where to
Since we can't get useful information from the inside
we can only rely on that lady
Go meet her
Yes
Miss Jiang
I'll take my leave now
Take care
Miss Jiang, please return
Miss Jiang
There's a guest outside who wants to see you
It's an old acquaintance of mine
Please invite the guest up quickly
No one else is allowed to disturb us
Alright
Previously, with you, Miss,
after our brief meeting in Shanghai,
though we've only corresponded by letter since,
your words still linger in my ears.
Every time I read them,
it feels as if I am meeting you in person.
Mr. Gu, I hope you have been well.
The national situation has been unpredictable lately.
I have managed to get by safely.
I wonder how you have been recently, Miss.
Feiman is doing well.
Thank you for your concern, Mr. Gu.
If I may ask,
what brings you here today?
What is the purpose of your visit?
I came to Pingchuan Academy to see Miss Feiman.
Besides enjoying the music,
there is another reason.
I am here to seek information.
I must admit, to my shame,
this time, it is for the latter reason.
During this stay in Shanghai,
I will be staying for a short while.
I hope to
maintain a long-term cooperation with you, Miss.
Of course.
I wonder, Mr. Gu,
what kind of information are you seeking?
The movements of Section 76 are quite secretive.
If you want to know someone's exact movements,
it's not easy.
What's more,
this kind of information is highly time-sensitive.
I'm afraid that even if you find out,
it will still be difficult.
Miss Feiman, you've misunderstood.
I don't intend to take any action.
I just want to know his whereabouts.
That's all.
I see.
I need some time.
Alright.
I'll send someone to contact you again.
Then I'll take my leave.
Pingchuan Academy is a mix of all kinds of people.
When you come and go,
you must be careful.
Thank you for the reminder.
Over here.
Spread it out, spread it out.
Alright, alright.
Right here.
Yes.
Here, here, here.
Move aside.
Come down.
Come down, come down.
Move out of the way.
What are you doing?
You guys, this...
Chief
Everything is going according to plan.
Everyone, put on servant uniforms.
No matter who comes to pay their respects,
let them in first.
Cigarettes
Newspapers for sale!
I want to investigate Yan Jiu again.
My current leads have run dry.
Maybe at Yan Jiu's place
there are clues about my identity.
Yan Residence
Alright
Please have a seat.
Miss Jiang
Your medicine
Thank you
By the way
Dr. Tan asked me to remind you
Be sure to decoct the turtle shell medicine first
Got it
Sir
The first group of guests here to pay their respects has arrived.
Everything outside has been arranged.
Everything is ready.
This time,
we must catch him.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Go.
It wasn't me.
You've got the wrong person.
Go!
From now on,
this will be your home.
Young man,
it's not your turn to pay respects yet.
There are still so many guests.
Once you've offered the tribute, leave quickly.
Honestly, you...
No matter how many times I tell you, you never listen.
Hurry up, go, go, go.
Go on.
Hurry up.
Go!
Who is it?
Uncle
Now that Central and Southern China have fallen,
Changsha is in grave danger.
Our nation is at a critical moment of survival.
The Japanese invaders are rampant.
The drums of war never cease.
The calamity of war
sweeps across China.
Even an ordinary man cannot shirk his responsibility.
In the past, I joined the army but failed to die for my country.
Now, I have spent all my family fortune
to purchase military supplies
to support the nation.
Please do not refuse.
When I saw Manchuria fall,
I realized how fragile life is.
I am willing to join the army and follow the Scorpion plan.
Cross the river and burn the boats,
never to turn back.
Scorpion.
Mission.
You must understand what a mission is.
Complete it.
Do your utmost.
Even if it costs your life.
Stop!
Hurry!
Go after them, quickly!
Stop!
Chase after them!
Out of the way!
Go to the intersection at Ding'an Road.
Find Director Cui.
Tell him to block the crowd for me.
Yes.
Thank you.
Director
I was hoping to catch something extra while doing this.
But I didn't expect the Japanese to mess it up themselves.
Now I can't explain this to Director Li.
What bad luck.
Instead of complaining,
you should keep your eyes open.
Anti-Japanese elements would never
walk openly on the main road.
Pair up in groups of two.
Watch every street and alley for me.
I don't play games hoping for extra catches.
I'm like the King of Hell's Five-Finger Mountain.
No one is getting away from me.
Yes, sir.
Director
Our intelligence department
makes a living by being observant.
Director Cui
The team leader said they didn't catch anyone
and they're heading your way.
Got it.
Brothers,
did you all hear that clearly?
Anyone Chen Gengsheng can't catch,
we must catch.
Yes, sir.
You, come with me.
Okay.
Where is the person?
Didn't see them.
Yes, sorry.
Stop!
Move aside.
Move aside, quickly.
Get out of the way.
Move aside, move aside.
Hurry.
Hurry, hurry.
Behind.
Faster, faster.
Driver, go faster.
Hurry, driver.
Stop, stop.
Keep the change.
Thank you.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
It really is you.
Who is she?
And who are you?
Do you know me?
Do you know who I am?
Tell me.
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
Put the gun down.
Tell me quickly.
You put the gun down.
Go away.
I'm helping you.
This is between us.
It has nothing to do with you.
Put the gun down.
Looks like today I
have really gained a lot.
Turn your head.
Or I'll shoot.
Liang Shuo.
What's going on?
Is this a ghost?
Didn't Director Liang die at Yulong Mountain?
Yeah, that's right.
Didn't he fall off a cliff?
Everyone shut up.
Put the gun down.
You scared me to death.
I thought you and Ma Yuan
both died at Yulong Mountain.
Liang Shuo
What are you doing?
What on earth is going on?
Go.
Tell the director.
Director Liang is still alive.
He's right here in Shanghai.
Yes.
Liang, my friend, Liang.
You're back already.
Why didn't you let me know you were safe?
Do you know during this time
your men and I
have been getting by?
Director Liang.
Boss.
I've been telling myself all along
that you'd be fine.
Didn't I tell you all
with Director Liang's abilities,
he'd be all right?
Yes.
Director Cui.
Aren't we here to catch the assassin?
Catch what assassin?
Are you blind?
Is Director Liang the assassin?
Yes.
Liang.
Brother.
What's wrong with you?
Liang.
I'm fine.
I'm back.
It's good that you're back.
When did you come back?
Why didn't you report back to headquarters?
What's going on with these two ladies?
You're Miss Jiang from Pingchuan Academy, right?
I really didn't expect that.
Your delicate hands, skilled in poetry and romance,
are also capable of handling a gun.
What is it?
Did this lady offend you?
This gun
is from Meihua Hall.
It was a gift from Mr. Mizuno.
I know.
You have some connection with Mr. Mizuno.
But brandishing a weapon in broad daylight
you owe me a reasonable explanation.
This is our personal matter.
It's not for you people from No. 76 to interfere.
A personal matter?
Brother,
what's going on?
Liang Shuo,
for another woman,
you'd even point a gun at me now?
If you have something to say, say it calmly.
Don't resort to violence.
Yeah.
You only see the new one smiling,
but never hear the old one crying.
From Nanjing to Chongqing,
from Chongqing to Shanghai,
how could you possibly remember
how much I've suffered?
All these years,
you've never given me an explanation.
I'm just not willing to let go.
You know me.
Some things,
if I don't hear them from you directly,
I won't give up.
Since things have come to this today,
and your colleagues are here as witnesses,
Liang Shuo,
make yourself clear.
Choose her,
or choose me.
Let's end it here.
Do you even know how to use this?
The safety isn't even off.
Don't use it to scare people again.
I must have been blind.
To have fallen for you in the first place.
Miss,
is this really the kind of man you like,
someone so fickle?
What,
are you going to hit me?
You little brat, are you looking for trouble?
What are you doing?
Are you tired of living?
I'm someone who values the past.
You should go.
Otherwise, don't blame me for forgetting our past.
Liar.
What is it?
Can't you hear what I'm saying?
Bro,
what's really going on?
You saw what happened.
Do you think I don't care about my reputation?
Fine.
We'll do as you say.
Let's talk about it when we get back.
But wait a second.
About the Yulong Mountain incident,
and about these two ladies,
you need to explain everything to me.