Mr. Liang
You are both wise and courageous
A truly rare talent
And time and again, through your actions
You have proven your loyalty to the new government
And to the Empire of Japan
The position of Deputy Director of the Special Investigation Department
Could belong to no one but you
As you Chinese would say
After Mr. Liang
The responsibility is heavy and the road is long
It is my honor
Regarding the recent Wang Qiaosu case
I have troubled you, Chief
As the
Director of the No. 76 Operations Division
I did not fulfill my duty
I ask for your punishment, Chief
This was due to Takagi's recklessness
It has nothing to do with you
Mr. Liang, please have a seat
Thank you, Chief
What’s done is done
We need to find out
What the Chongqing agents’ next objective is
That is what we should focus on now
I invited you here this time
Because I also want to hear
Your thoughts on
The current state of the struggle
So that in the future
We can work together more effectively
I, Liang Shuo, will speak without reservation
The code name for the Chongqing agents’ secret plan
Is "Snow Blindness"
In your opinion, Mr. Liang
Do these two words have any special meaning?
As far as I know,
snow blindness is a common eye condition
in the northern snowfields.
As for whether it has any special significance,
I would need to ask the chief for guidance.
My hometown is in Nagano, Japan.
Skiing is a popular pastime
among young people where I'm from.
I was no exception.
When I was young,
I didn't know
that you shouldn't stay in the snow for too long.
Ignoring my friends' warnings,
I went alone
to the top of the mountain,
planning to break the village's skiing record.
But what I didn't expect
was that just as I was feeling confident,
ready to ski straight down
from the summit,
an accident happened.
Snow blindness.
That's right.
I didn't realize
that staying in the snow for too long
had put a lot of strain
on my eyes.
In just an instant,
everything in front of me turned white.
I couldn't see anything.
And in that same instant,
I
fell from the top of the mountain.
I broke thirteen bones all over my body.
If my friends hadn't found me,
then right now,
I probably wouldn't be standing here.
I understand what you mean, Chief.
Snow blindness isn't a serious illness.
It's also easy to cure.
But if it happens at the wrong time,
it can be extremely deadly.
Mr. Liang, you really grasp things instantly.
I was thinking the same thing.
The anti-Japanese elements
are looking for the right opportunity.
Now it seems
that opportunity is likely the Peace Conference.
That's right.
Since the anti-Japanese elements plan to act at the Peace Conference,
instead of passively defending,
we should take the initiative.
Disrupt their plans.
I wonder, Chief,
what your plan is.
I've already submitted a request to the Army Department
and the Special Affairs Committee
for approval.
To move the date of the Peace Conference
up by two days,
and relocate it from the original northern Shanghai district.
This way, we can completely disrupt
the anti-Japanese elements' plans.
Mr. Liang,
what do you think?
I completely agree.
The more tense the situation,
the more likely the anti-Japanese elements
are to make mistakes.
As soon as their arrangements are disrupted,
that's the best time for us to close the net.
But I wonder, Chief,
what your deployment will be.
Wait until the time is right.
Mr. Liang will naturally find out.
We suspect
that the intelligence headquarters has already been infiltrated by anti-Japanese elements.
Therefore, together with
the Special Affairs Committee,
the purpose of establishing the Special Investigation Division is precisely this.
This way,
Mr. Liang's men will become
a surprise force during the Peace Conference.
What we want
is not just
the safety of the new government officials,
but also
the heads of the anti-Japanese elements.
I understand.
The plan has changed.
We must get the message out as soon as possible.
Chief,
what is your first impression of Mr. Liang?
He is a sharp hunter.
But he gives me an indescribable feeling.
Chief, do you suspect him?
As long as they're Chinese,
I won't trust any of them.
At the moment,
there really isn't anyone else besides him.
If he doesn't waste time and works efficiently,
and if we train him to get up to speed quickly,
he'll be a useful weapon.
Dying is easy.
Dying with value is what's hard.
Say something.
Go on, say something.
The Snow Blind mission is on the verge of collapse.
I need you to do whatever it takes,
to infiltrate the enemy.
From now on, the codename Scholar
will be a thing of the past.
If Shadow dies,
you will become Shadow.
If Shadow returns alive,
help Shadow.
Cover him.
That is your only mission.
You must be prepared to sacrifice yourself for him at any time.
Who are you?
Why are you giving me information about him?
Have the people we called from out of town arrived?
They've arrived.
This time,
there can be no more mistakes.
Yes.
Salute.
At ease.
Boss, are we going back to headquarters or...
I have something important to take care of.
Take me to Xiyuan Road.
Then you can leave.
Okay.
Ow, it hurts!
Why is it you?
It hurts.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
I've been looking for you.
Let go, it hurts.
Someone is chasing me.
Who is it?
It seems like when I just got back to Shanghai before.
The people who tried to kill me.
Let's go.
It looks like they're catching up.
I'll try to lure them away.
Hurry, after them!
Sit here, don't move.
Get out of the way!
That's him!
Chase him!
Stop!
Catch him!
Move aside!
He's over there, go after him!
Stop! Stop!
Chase him!
Stop!
What are you doing here?
They must be from a gang.
How did Liang Shuo get into trouble with them?
He mentioned it to me before.
He said a group of gang members have been after him.
Because of his identity as Number 76,
it's not necessarily true
that everyone chasing him is a bad person.
No wonder he didn't fight back.
I'll call the police first.
Then I'll inform Number 76.
You stay here.
No.
I can help.
Six bullets.
If your life is in danger, shoot without hesitation.
This gun isn't very powerful.
As long as you don't aim for vital spots,
it won't be fatal.
Alright.
Let's split up.
Be careful.
Everyone, don't panic.
Don't be afraid.
Please, sit down quickly.
Troupe leader, keep singing.
Is this the police station?
This is Pingchuan Academy.
I want to report a crime.
Someone committed an assault.
I suspect it's an anti-Japanese activist.
Who are you people?
Why are you targeting me?
Traitor!
You're the one who got Master Jiu killed.
Even if I die, I, Gu Zhentian, won't let you go.
Go!
Let him go.
I told you to let him go.
Stop.
I'll say it again.
Let go.
Liang Shuo.
Take me to Fei Man.
Otherwise,
it'll be too late.
Go.
Hurry.
Slow down.
Troupe leader, keep singing.
Everyone, please sit.
Keep listening to the music, keep listening.
Who called the authorities?
Step back, step back.
Officer.
Just now, a group of people were chasing someone with axes.
They went that way.
I saw it clearly.
A group of people with axes.
Chasing.
Yes.
It's all right now, it's all right.
Everyone, sit down and listen to the music.
Everyone, sit, sit.
Keep watching the show.
Liang Shuo.
The police are here.
They should be able to hold them off.
He's badly hurt.
Help me support him.
Hang in there.
Tell Old Tan
The time has changed
It's two days earlier
Thirty-one
Plan Thirty-One
There's no time left
What are you talking about?
Liang Shuo
Help him into the car
Come on
Slow down
Hurry up
Be careful
He has a very high fever
We need to go to the hospital right away
Where is the nearest hospital?
The Japanese Army hospital
Don't go to the hospital
He's so badly injured
We can't worry about that now
We have to go to the hospital
Hurry
They're up ahead
You go first
Leave the rest to me
Be careful
Liang Shuo
Lie still
You got beaten up this badly
And you're still being stubborn
I...
Director Cui
The search operation is already in full swing
Our whole department is here
Please give us your instructions, Director Cui
Thank you for your hard work, Director Liu
It's my duty
Brother
Where are you from?
Are you from an association or a gang?
Chongqing
You're not from Yan'an, are you?
Director
This is the leader of Da Feng Hall
Gu Zhentian
Da Feng Hall
Master Gu
I like men with your kind of spirit
Take him back
Treat him well
Yes
Take him away
Bring him back
Treat him well
Chief Liu
Anyone we catch from now on
Send them to me as well
Don't worry, Director
Director
Director Cui
What's wrong?
Something happened
It's Liang Shuo
He might be in trouble
He just went nearby to take care of something
Then he told me to go back first
But then...
I suspect this isn't just a simple disturbance
Someone wants to assassinate Director Liang
They're asking for death
Don't move.
He's the Director of Operations at the Special Agent Headquarters.
This is his ID.
His name is Liang Shuo.
You have to save him.
He's the Director of Operations at the Special Agent Headquarters.
His name is Liang Shuo.
You have to save him.
This is his ID.
Hurry up.
You're awake.
You...
How do you feel?
Come on, take it slow.
Hey, look at me.
Who am I?
Do you still remember?
Xie Nianci
You scared me to death.
I thought you had forgotten everything again.
Thank you.
If you hadn't shot to save me,
If you really want to thank me,
can you tell me the truth?
You and Jiang Feiman—
what exactly is your relationship?
What are you trying to say?
Do you still remember
that before you fell unconscious, you kept asking me
to take you to find Jiang Feiman?
I asked Jiang Feiman.
I know you two aren't lovers.
So what is your relationship, really?
While you were unconscious,
if it weren't for her,
we wouldn't have made it here.
To put it simply,
as for her,
she's very meticulous,
and she knows how to use a gun.
She's not an ordinary person.
Then who exactly is she?
And what's her relationship with you?
You're overthinking it.
What do you think she is?
I don't know.
But I want to hear it from you.
Who is she?
You're not answering me.
Why?
You don't trust me.
Are you afraid I'll tell Old Xie?
Nian Ci
You’ve saved me twice.
I trust you.
But
at a time like this,
I won’t risk anyone’s life as a joke.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I just feel
there’s nothing you need to hide from me.
Even if she’s with the underground,
I wouldn’t tell anyone.
Let me be honest with you.
As for Chongqing,
I lost faith in it a long time ago.
That includes Lao Xie.
Why?
I think he’s changed.
He’ll turn his back on anyone to complete his mission.
The matter at Pingjia Lane,
you’ve already taken care of it.
He also promised me
he’d get you out of Shanghai.
But he went back on his word.
And he’s full of lies.
I see that clearly now.
He never really wanted you to leave.
As expected.
And as of today,
I don’t plan to leave Shanghai either.
Why?
Even if I die here,
you still won’t leave?
I thought that if I forgot everything
I could start over
and live as an ordinary person
leave Shanghai
and do anything I wanted
But I don't think that way anymore
Do you know how many of our compatriots I saw
in No. 76
die under Japanese guns?
How many heroes I saw
sacrifice their lives?
In times of national crisis
where can we find refuge?
Rather than just surviving out there
I'd rather live a passionate life here
I will use my own way
to fight them to the end
But
I still worry about you.
You know that.
Old Xie is a very suspicious person.
If he ever starts suspecting you,
you'll be in trouble.
The patient in bed fifteen is in critical condition.
Come quickly.
Where is this place?
Why are there Japanese people here?
It's a Japanese Army hospital.
Your injuries were too severe.
I really had no other choice.
That's why I brought you here.
I used your pass.
That's bad.
There could be trouble.
What do you mean?
You risked your life to get me to the hospital.
That proves our relationship is not ordinary.
With Hirata Xizi's attention to detail,
she will definitely notice this clue.
You have to leave immediately.
It was my oversight.
I'll leave right now.
Then take care of yourself.
Remember,
if anyone asks,
just say we are
dating.
Okay.
Director Hirata
Do you know how Liang Shuo is doing now?
I'm very worried too.
However,
the Army Hospital has the best doctors in Shanghai.
About this incident,
how exactly did it happen?
Liang Shuo
wasn't he supposed to return to headquarters after the ceremony?
Wasn't he supposed to go back to headquarters?
I'm not sure either.
The driver said
he went there to take care of something.
He was inexplicably targeted.
These anti-Japanese activists nowadays
are really audacious.
They even dare to kill people in broad daylight.
Have you found any leads?
It's said
that it was anti-Japanese activists
seeking revenge for Yan Jiu.
We must investigate this thoroughly.
Liang Shuo is currently handling affairs for the Special Investigation Division.
Nothing can be allowed to go wrong.
I will also suggest to Director Li
that we protect Liang Shuo at all costs.
Director Hirata
If Director Liang knew
that you were concerned about his safety,
he would be extremely grateful.
Please.
How is Director Liang?
It's just a superficial wound.
Nothing serious.
We've assigned the most professional medical team to care for him.
He's also in a special ward with the best facilities.
Please rest assured.
By the way,
Who brought him here?
Please wait a moment.
It was a young woman.
She didn't sign her full name.
She only wrote "Director Liang's friend."
Friend?
Yes.
Director Cui.
Does Liang Shuo usually have any
close female friends?
That's his personal business.
I usually don't ask about it.
Is his friend still here?
Yes, she's still here.
Wait.
Miss,
haven't we met somewhere before?
It's you.
And you are?
Liang Shuo.
Why are you back?
Director Hirata.
Brother Cui.
Why are you two here?
Mr. Liang.
No need to be so formal. Get some rest.
Excuse me.
How did things end up like this?
Director Hirata and I heard something happened to you.
We were both very worried about you.
Originally,
we didn't even know which room you were in.
As luck would have it,
at the entrance,
we ran into Miss Xie.
Brother.
You two—
what's going on between you?
Sorry to have made you laugh at me.
Liang.
You're this badly injured,
yet you can still joke around.
If it were someone else,
they'd be half dead by now.
Chief Hirata should know
I've always been lucky.
Don't say things like that.
It's bad luck.
I heard Miss Xie brought you here.
A beauty saving a hero,
that's pretty romantic.
About you two,
when did it start?
You didn't even tell me.
That's too distant of you.
Hiding your beauty away.
Liang, you really know how to keep a secret.
In our line of work as agents,
we're always living on the edge.
Once we step out of headquarters,
there are too many people who want us dead.
No matter how well we keep things secret, it's useless.
Take this time, for example.
Everything was fine,
so how did we get exposed?
I feel like these assassins have been planning this for a long time.
Brother Cui, have you investigated these people?
Preliminary investigation shows
they are remnants of Yan Jiu's group.
The rest is still under investigation.
Don't worry.
I will get to the bottom of this.
If they dare to touch you,
I'll take their lives.
I should have thought of this earlier.
Ever since the news that I killed Yan Jiu
came back from Manchuria,
the people looking to cause me trouble
have only increased day by day.
Since you know this,
why were you so careless?
Why didn't you bring more men with you?
And also,
why did you go alone
to such a remote place?
Chief Hirata,
I wonder if it's convenient
for me to have a private word with Brother Liang.
Of course, that's fine.
Actually,
I also want to spend some time with Miss Xie.
Get to know her better.
Then I'll go have a chat with this young lady.
This Miss Xie,
I've seen her before.
Brother,
now that there are no outsiders,
you owe me an explanation.
No need to be nervous.
Miss Xie,
I'm just going to ask a few questions.
That's all.
Why?
It's just
a routine procedure.
You know what Mr. Liang does for a living.
Cooperating with our work
for you
won't do any harm.
Please have a seat.
What do you want me to say?
Men and women have desires and emotions.
That's only human nature, isn't it?
When Brother Cui and his wife first got together,
did they have to report it to their colleagues too?
You know,
times have changed.
The Japanese are watching too closely now.
Not to mention that Miss Xie and I haven't even established a relationship yet.
Even if we had,
we would still have to report it to the General Affairs Office.
I'm just looking out for you.
I'm just puzzled.
Your sister-in-law introduced you to so many
well-bred ladies and socialites back then.
You didn't like any of them.
Matters of the heart should happen naturally.
You can't force them.
As for Miss Xie,
what's her story?
I'm really curious.
What kind of girl
could possibly catch your eye?
Well-bred ladies are certainly nice,
but when two people are together,
what matters most is understanding each other.
The affection you and your wife share
is truly enviable.
In my opinion,
two people must have similar interests and hobbies
to be together.
How did you two meet?
Miss Xie,
how did you meet Liang Shuo?
It's a long story.
Why don't we wait until Miss Xie comes back
and then talk about it?
Brother,
to be honest,
it's not that I don't trust you.
Would I ever doubt you?
It's just that your current position
is too sensitive.
We always have to be careful of those
who deliberately try to get close to you.
I knew it.
Today, when Brother Cui asked questions,
it felt very official.
Really?
Alright.
Since this is official business,
I'll cooperate fully.
Brother Cui asked
how I met Miss Xie.
Near the train station.
At that time,
I was being questioned by a group of patrolmen.
At the train station,
Miss Xie ran into a bit of trouble.
I forgot to bring my identification.
Mr. Liang came over to help me.
A few patrolmen were pestering Miss Xie.
So I revealed my identity.
And scared them off a bit.
When did you
start playing the hero to save the damsel?
It was nothing, just a small favor.
If it were you, Brother Cui,
you would have helped too.
After we met,
after we met,
Mr. Liang kept asking me out.
Eventually, I agreed.
We had arranged to meet
on the morning of the 26th last month.
But he didn't show up.
Come in.
Let's talk inside.
How's the situation?
He's out of danger.
Miss Xie has temporarily sent him to
the Japanese Army Hospital.
The only concern now
is Hirata Xizi.
She might become suspicious of Miss Xie's identity.
We have to trust Liang Shuo.
He'll definitely find a way
to handle it.
By the way,
Liang Shuo has important information to pass on.
Tell Old Tan
the time has changed.
It's moved up by two days.
Three-One.
The Three-One Plan.
There's no time left.
No wonder
As soon as the award ceremony ended
he went straight to Pingchuan Academy
What he means
should be
the Japanese want to move it up by two days
and hold the peace conference
The location has also changed
This completely disrupts our previous plan
The 3-1 Plan
What exactly is it?
The peace conference
is far from as simple as it seems
Behind it
there must be an even bigger plot
We don't have much time left
At least
the first step of our mission is now complete
As long as Liang Shuo
can stay in his position at the Special Investigation Division
without any mistakes
he will definitely be able to get to the core of the conference
and we can seize the initiative
If we want Hirata Xizi not to notice anything
and avoid any mistakes
that's easier said than done
What does Miss Xie do?
She just graduated from a girls' school.
She’s currently working part-time at a clothing store.
So you haven’t known each other for long?
Not long.
We’ve only met a few times.
That was before you went to Yulongshan?
That’s when we met.
That’s right.
So today...
Today, he finally managed to ask me out again.
We agreed to have coffee together.
But then something like that happened again.
It scared me to death.
We were just meeting for coffee.
I didn’t expect
anti-Japanese activists would ruin our mood.
I didn’t expect Miss Xie
to have such a good memory.
If it’s someone or something I want to remember,
of course I can remember it.
You just graduated.
I just started at the clothing store.
I found a temporary job there.
Miss Xie, can you guarantee
that everything you’ve said
is true?
Of course.
Why would I lie to you?
Where are you living now, Miss Xie?
I’m renting a place at 16 Chunhua Road.
Thank you for your cooperation, Miss Xie.
If I was in any way impolite,
please forgive me.
May I leave now?
Please.
I hope I'm not interrupting your conversation.
Director Hirata, you're joking.
Brother Liang and I
were just chatting about everyday things.
Brother Cui,
Director Hirata,
Since you are both here,
I'd like to ask you both for a favor.
Please, just tell us what you need.
No need to be so polite.
Director Liang,
you're being too polite.
Just give the word,
and I'll do as you ask.
Then, Brother Cui,
could you bring me my coat?
Thank you.
I asked you out today,
but I didn't expect
that you would be frightened.
It all happened so suddenly
that what I wanted to say to you at the café
I didn't get the chance to say.
I didn't have time to say any of it.
But after what happened,
it has only strengthened my resolve.
That is,
I don't want to have any regrets.
Our time together has been short,
but it's been unforgettable.
Maybe what happened today
was a bit rushed,
but I have thought it through carefully.
Director Hirata,
and Brother Cui,
please be my witnesses.
What are you doing?
Facing the unknown risks ahead,
I am willing to be your strongest armor,
to protect you completely.
Yuxin,
are you willing to give me this chance?
This gift is too valuable.
I can't accept it.
Director Hirata and Brother Cui
have both witnessed this for me.
Are you not giving them any respect?
Of course not.
Then you must not like me.
That's definitely not it either.
Miss Xie,
what Brother Liang just said
was truly heartfelt and sincere.
With my brother's status
and his looks,
in all of Shanghai,
countless women long for him but can't have him.
Don't miss out on such a good match.
Mr. Liang
You usually act swiftly and decisively.
I didn't expect
that when it comes to relationships,
you'd be just as resolute.
In the past,
I was always focused on my work.
I never considered personal matters.
But now,
thanks to Director Hirata's support,
I've been promoted to Deputy Director.
I'm also taking this opportunity
to express my feelings to Miss Xie.
to let her know what's in my heart.
It's also a way to give myself closure.
Thank you, Director Hirata, for your understanding.
Of course I understand.
Family matters and national affairs
are equally important.
Without family, there is no country.
Miss Xie,
it seems very soon
I'll have to start calling you sister-in-law.
You two go ahead and talk.
I'll go get some hot water.