ELITE LEAGUE
I hope the game is fun and unique.
I'm so nervous.
I'm a wreck right now.
My heart is literally racing.
Check my pulse.
We said we were going to have fun,
so let's just enjoy ourselves.
That's right. Let's have fun.
They must be under a lot of pressure.
We just need to stay positive.
If we want to win, we need to stay strong.
Today's main match
is Find My Personality Type.
What?
Do I have to find someone by myself again?
In Find My Personality Type,
players will exchange information
to deduce the personality types
of the opposing teams' players.
What?
Players will be assigned
a personality type among the 16 types
by choosing a card randomly.
I see.
Each player will be assigned
a unique personality type,
and this will not be revealed
to the other teams.
UNDISCLOSED
The only way to find out
the other players' personality types
is to exchange information
by comparing cards.
If two players agree to compare cards,
they will place their cards
on the table in front of the host.
The screen will then show
the number of letters
their personality types have in common.
The game will consist of 3 rounds,
each lasting 10 minutes.
The duration of the game
will total 30 minutes.
Each team must deduce
the opposing teams' personality types
and submit their answers
within these three rounds.
Guessing the opponent's personality type
will grant your team one point.
At the end of the game,
the team with the highest number
of correct answers will survive.
The remaining two
will face the Deathmatch.
If a tie occurs,
the team that submits
their answers first will survive.
THE TEAM THAT SUBMITS FIRST SURVIVES
- We need to use logical reasoning.
- Right.
We all have a fair chance at winning.
I wonder what the benefit is.
The benefit for Team SNU,
the winner of Relay Match,
will now be revealed.
You may choose one player
and ask if they have
a certain personality type.
Your question will then be answered
with a yes or a no.
CHECK ONE PLAYER'S PERSONALITY TYPE
- That's huge.
- That's going to be helpful.
- That's big.
- They can earn a point with that.
We shouldn't use it at first.
Of course not.
We should use it
right before we submit our answers.
We can double-check
if we're not sure about someone.
Before we begin the game,
each player will pick a card
that has a personality type.
Each team's first player,
please come forward and pick a card.
I'm sorry.
I'm number one, so I chose the first card.
Don't let the others see.
Each team's second player...
Each team's third player...
Each team's fourth player,
please come forward and pick a card.
We chose the first four cards.
- We chose 1, 2, 3, and 4.
- That's 1, 2, 3, and 4.
- What did we pick?
- What's this?
Eleven, thirteen...
What did you pick?
- Okay. We're all set.
- What does yours say?
DO-HYUN: ENTJ, HYUN-MIN: ISFP
HYUN-SEOK: ESTJ, HYUN-BIN: ENFJ
JUNG-MIN: INTP, DONG-KYU: ISTP
JI-SOO: ESTP, SEUNG-MIN: ESFP
REMAINING CARDS: INTJ, ENTP, ESFJ, INFP
All players have been assigned
a unique personality type.
You will now be given
ten minutes to discuss your strategy.
...ten minutes to discuss your strategy.
Let's go.
Let's move!
Let's go inside.
We need to exclude
our personality types first.
Write everyone's names down.
We can eliminate it 1 by 1,
and we'll only use the board.
Writing down all the possibilities
under each player's name
and eliminating the personality types
with the information we have
is the most logical approach.
Are you writing it all down?
We need to hurry.
We can narrow it down from here.
We'll just erase the irrelevant ones.
We'll write all the possible types
for the eight players
and then erase the ones
that aren't applicable.
The possibilities are endless.
Let's compare one card
to narrow it down and go from there.
COMMON STRATEGY
1. EXCHANGE INFORMATION WITH OTHER TEAMS
2. ELIMINATE THE POSSIBILITIES
THROUGH DEDUCTIVE REASONING
- I got ENTJ.
- I got ISFP.
You got ISFP?
- I picked ESTJ.
- Mine says ENFJ.
Hyun-min and I don't have
any letters in common.
This is good for us.
Hyun-min and I had
completely different personality types.
TEAM SNU'S STRATEGY
ENTJ AND ISFJ: 1 MATCH
ISFJ AND ISFP: 3 MATCHES
ENTJ AND ENFP: 2 MATCHES
ENFP AND ISFP: 2 MATCHES
It'd be best not to reveal
IT'S UNNECESSARY TO REVEAL BOTH CARDS
both our cards.
I'm going to stay here
and keep a low profile.
STRATEGY IS TO CONCEAL DO-HYUN'S CARD
I'll be the wild card.
Who has the same two letters as me?
You and I have two letters in common.
HYUN-SEOK AND HYUN-BIN SHARE 2 LETTERS
Okay, we'll pair up.
If Hyun-bin and Hyun-seok
compared cards with the same person,
we'd be able to find out
one or two letters
of that person's personality type.
We need everything you can get.
- I'll do all I can.
- We need 16 comparisons.
I know.
If we compare as many cards as we can,
we'd be able to narrow it down.
TEAM SNU'S STRATEGY
MAKE AS MANY COMPARISONS TO GATHER INTEL
Then, we'll use the benefit
to confirm a player's personality type.
Once we have that information,
we can use deductive reasoning
to figure out the rest.
Your ten minutes is up.
You may now begin to exchange information.
Team KU won't cooperate later on,
so let's ask them first.
I have my concerns about Team Harvard.
They tend to be individualistic,
so they may not cooperate
if they think they have enough intel.
Let's ask Ray and David.
- I'll ask David.
- I'll ask Ray.
HYUN-SEOK AND HYUN-BIN
APPROACH TEAM HARVARD FIRST
I'll go first.
Ray and David,
would you like to compare cards?
Hold on. Give us a moment.
Why don't I compare with David
and Hyun-seok compare with Ray?
Please give us a moment.
TEAM HARVARD DENIES THE OFFER
Should we ask them?
- Do you want to compare cards?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- You two go ahead.
SNU'S HYUN-BIN AND KU'S JI-SOO
COMPARE CARDS
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin
and Team KU's Lee Ji-soo,
would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Please place your cards on the table.
Your cards have been compared.
1 MATCH
HYUN-BIN: ENFJ, JI-SOO: ESTP
In that case, she could be an ESTP.
That's one possibility.
HYUN-MIN'S PERSONALITY TYPE IS ELIMINATED
She could also be an INTP or an ISTJ.
JI-SOO: ESTP, INTP, ISTJ
KU'S JI-SOO AND SNU'S HYUN-BIN
1 MATCH
HYUN-BIN: ENFJ, ISFJ, INTJ, INFP
KU'S JUNG-MIN AND SNU'S HYUN-SEOK
COMPARE CARDS
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Please place your cards on the table.
Good luck. May the best man win.
1 MATCH
Your cards have been compared.
- They also have one in common.
- Again?
KU'S JUNG-MIN AND SNU'S HYUN-SEOK
1 MATCH
SEUNG-MIN'S PERSONALITY TYPE IS ELIMINATED
HYUN-SEOK: ISFP, ENFJ, ESTJ
SNU'S HYUN-SEOK AND KU'S JUNG-MIN
1 MATCH
HYUN-MIN'S PERSONALITY TYPE IS ELIMINATED
JUNG-MIN: ENFP, INTP, INFJ
TEAM SNU LOOKS FOR PLAYERS
THEY CAN COMPARE CARDS WITH
Excuse me.
You're considering it, right?
TEAM SNU TRIES TO COMPARE CARDS
- Do you plan on comparing cards?
- Yes.
Yes.
Do you want to compare cards now?
Are you up for it?
- Yes.
- All right.
5 MINUTES AGO
TEAM HARVARD DENIED TEAM SNU'S OFFER
- You don't want us to go first?
- That way...
If Team KU and Team SNU
compare their cards first...
We wanted to wait for them to go first
because it would give us more intel.
That was our initial game plan.
TEAM HARVARD WAITED TO SEE THE RESULTS
BETWEEN SNU'S HYUN-BIN AND KU'S JI-SOO
THEN THEY COMPARED
THEIR CARD WITH SNU'S HYUN-BIN
Please place your cards on the table.
3 MATCHES
Your cards have been compared.
- Three letters?
- He could be an ENFP.
So Hyun-bin must be 1 of these 4.
- He's 1 of these 4.
- That's right.
Since Hyun-bin and Ji-soo
have one letter in common,
we can narrow it down for Ji-soo.
LEVERAGE THE INFORMATION FROM OTHER TEAMS
- We need more data.
- Really?
- Should we?
- I'll go and compare cards.
Go for Ji-soo.
THEY TARGET KU'S JI-SOO,
WHO COMPARED WITH SNU'S HYUN-BIN
What do we do?
- Can I compare cards with Ji-soo?
- Should I? I'll just do it.
- Sure. We need their information.
- Are you sure?
- Thanks.
- Will you compare with us?
Sure. After I do it with Ji-soo.
KU'S JI-SOO AND HARVARD'S RAY
COMPARE CARDS
We're running out of time.
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Please place your cards on the table.
Your cards have been compared.
2 MATCHES
JI-SOO: ESTP, RAY: ISTJ
That's two letters.
HARVARD'S RAY AND KU'S JI-SOO
2 MATCHES
DAVID'S PERSONALITY TYPE IS ELIMINATED
JI-SOO: ISFP, INTP, ESTP, ESFJ, ENTJ
Can I talk to you
before you go back inside?
Sorry?
Can I compare cards with David?
- One second.
- Either David or Janice.
Hyun-bin wants to compare cards
with either David or Janice.
- No, we can't.
- No?
In that case,
can I compare cards with Ray?
Ray's busy right now. I'm sorry.
So all three of you can't do it?
- I'll check with my teammates.
- Okay.
- Should I do it?
- No.
I won't do it.
Your cards have been compared.
Sky was being really cautious.
She didn't want to take any chances.
She didn't want to reveal our cards.
Your cards have been compared.
- Who did Ray compare cards with?
- We have an issue.
No one from Team Harvard
would come out of their base camp.
We were screwed.
That's just so...
Don't you want to know what I am?
Look into my eyes.
Team SNU's Park Hyun-min
and Team KU's Lee Ji-soo
have agreed to compare cards.
2 MATCHES
JI-SOO: ESTP, HYUN-MIN: ISFP
Your cards have been compared.
This is so annoying.
Why won't Team Harvard compare cards?
- What's this?
- It's Ji-soo's type.
Damn it.
- What's wrong?
- All three work.
- They all have two matches.
- How is that possible?
- That can't be.
- Even with my comparison?
HYUN-BIN'S COMPARISON
NARROWED DOWN JI-SOO'S TYPE TO 3
JI-SOO: ESTP, INTP, ISTJ
SNU'S HYUN-MIN AND KU'S JI-SOO
2 MATCHES
HYUN-MIN'S COMPARISON
FAILED TO YIELD NEW INFORMATION
- You have two minutes left.
- What a shame.
We just ended up giving Team KU
a lot of information.
- Ji-soo and Hyun-min have 2 in common.
- Ray also has 2, right?
TEAM KU'S INFORMATION
JI-SOO: 1 MATCH WITH HYUN-BIN
JI-SOO: 2 MATCHES WITH HYUN-MIN AND RAY
JUNG-MIN: 1 MATCH WITH HYUN-SEOK
Should I go and ask Sky?
- Hold on.
- Go ahead.
It's the same.
- Where are you going?
- Stop. Don't open the door.
- Would Sky be--
- Let's do that in the next round.
- The next round?
- Yes.
We'll leave the INFP here.
If Hyun-bin is an INFP...
Do you realize how much we're losing out
by refusing to compare cards?
Tell us what you think we need.
- We've only made two comparisons so far.
- Let's try ESFP.
What was that?
You're all being unreasonable.
We need to compare our cards.
Sky and Janice didn't want
to give out too much information.
They wanted to think things through
and compare cards later or not at all.
But David and I disagreed.
We couldn't deduce anything
because we had no information.
So we wanted to compare cards
with the other teams
to get some answers.
- Who is it?
- Come in.
Jung-min, let's compare cards.
Should I?
Ji-soo and I will do the comparisons.
You can go ahead.
KU'S JUNG-MIN AND HARVARD'S DAVID
COMPARE CARDS
We will compare your cards.
Team Harvard's David
and Team KU's Kim Jung-min,
please place your cards on the table.
2 MATCHES
Your cards have been compared.
- Who just went?
- Jung-min and David.
- Is Team Harvard avoiding us?
Our strategy isn't...
- Our strategy isn't working.
- I know. It's not going as planned.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Our plan was to obtain
the information as quickly as possible.
Then we were going to brainstorm
the possible outcomes
and eliminate
the irrelevant personality types.
We were positive our strategy would work.
It is what it is, so don't panic.
That concludes the first round.
ROUND 1 RESULTS
HYUN-BIN, JI-SOO: 1
HYUN-SEOK, JUNG-MIN: 1
HYUN-BIN, SKY: 3
JI-SOO, RAY: 2
JI-SOO, HYUN-MIN: 2
JUNG-MIN, DAVID: 2
We will now begin the second round.
- You didn't compare with anyone, right?
- No.
Sky, can you please
compare your card with mine?
Is Sky up for a comparison?
Do you want to do it with me?
- With you?
- Yes.
- You haven't done it yet, right?
- No. Let's do it.
Sure.
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
HARVARD'S JANICE AND KU'S JI-SOO
COMPARE CARDS
Is Sky going to compare cards?
I think she's busy, but I can ask her.
1 MATCH
Your cards have been compared.
TEAM KU'S JI-SOO
1 MATCH WITH JANICE, 2 MATCHES WITH RAY
JI-SOO: INTP, ESTP, ENTJ
We need to adjust our strategy.
Let's target Team KU.
What about Dong-kyu and Seung-min?
Between the two of us,
whose card was revealed more?
I only did it once.
Then I'll ask Dong-kyu.
You should ask Seung-min.
Okay.
Seung-min, do you want to compare cards?
Do you want to compare cards, Dong-kyu?
What should I do?
It wouldn't hurt us.
We already shared a lot of information.
Let's just do it.
Compare your card with Hyun-bin's.
- Do it with Hyun-bin.
- Let's go.
Let's compare cards, Seung-min.
Come on out.
Seung-min won't be comparing his card.
Keeping one card concealed
seemed strategically sound.
So that's why I didn't reveal my card.
Are you serious?
Seung-min won't reveal his card.
He's going to hold out until the end.
Damn. This is driving me crazy.
We failed to come up
with a bulletproof strategy.
So I was really mad at myself.
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Please place your cards on the table.
- Is that the result?
- Your cards have been compared.
0 MATCHES
DONG-KYU: ISTP, HYUN-BIN: ENFJ
- Is that the result?
- Your cards have been compared.
Is it really?
This works for both of us.
Maybe we're meant to be.
We were both born...
BOTH HYUN-BIN AND DONG-KYU
WERE BORN IN 2000
- We were born in 2000.
- Did they plan this?
- Zero matches?
- They know now.
- Zero?
- But we also know.
This is huge.
Getting zero matches early on
can be quite significant
because this doesn't give
the third team much information.
But this gives the other two teams
a huge advantage.
Since we know for certain
one player's personality type,
we can narrow down the types
much more quickly with every comparison.
- Zero matches.
Shoot.
If we figure out what Ji-soo's type is...
TEAM HARVARD
TRIES TO USE DEDUCTIVE REASONING
If we know Hyun-bin's,
we'll know Dong-kyu's.
We need to compare cards with Ji-soo.
Sky! Ji-soo wanted
to compare cards with you.
JI-SOO AND HYUN-BIN
COMPARED CARDS IN ROUND 1
Ji-soo.
Would you like to compare cards with me?
Give me a second.
Hold on.
We have nothing to gain from Sky.
40 MINUTES AGO
There are 16 personality types,
and my team has four of them.
If you list the number of common letters
between each personality type,
you would get a number between 0 and 4.
0 MATCHES: 1 POSSIBILITY
You'd only get 1 case of 0 matches.
1 MATCH: 4 POSSIBILITIES
There'd be 4 cases of 1 match.
2 MATCHES: 6 POSSIBILITIES
Then there are 6 cases of 2 matches.
3 MATCHES: 4 POSSIBILITIES
Finally, 4 cases of 3 matches.
AVOIDING 2 MATCHES
WOULD HELP FIND THE SOLUTION QUICKLY
I knew using that chart
would help us determine
who we needed to compare with.
If we have one letter in common,
we can look for what we need
among these four.
Since there are 4 cases of 1 match,
we'd move to the row below.
It'd be 2, 2, 0, 2.
That means Seung-min
shouldn't compare his card.
- Right.
- We don't want two matches.
So we'll go one row down,
and that'll give us 1, 3, 3, 1.
It'd be better to go with that.
Do you get what I mean?
JUNG-MIN IS THE BETTER BET
- We'll compare cards 1 by 1.
- Okay.
TEAM KU'S STRATEGY
COMPARE CARDS WITH PLAYERS
BASED ON THE CHART
- If we want to do it with Sky--
- I should do it.
You're right.
SKY HAD 3 MATCHES WITH HYUN-BIN
We can narrow it down to two.
- Go for Team Harvard.
- Are you keeping notes?
JI-SOO WON'T BE ABLE TO NARROW IT DOWN
IT'D BE BETTER FOR SEUNG-MIN
TO COMPARE CARDS WITH SKY
Sky, do you want to do it with me?
No, I wanted to compare cards with Ji-soo.
- But...
- I haven't compared my card with anyone.
- All right then.
- I haven't done it yet.
Please place your cards on the table.
SEUNG-MIN AND SKY COMPARE CARDS
Your cards have been compared.
3 MATCHES
SEUNG-MIN: ESFP, SKY: ENFP
Let's compare cards, Seung-min.
- I need to talk to my team first.
- We have five minutes.
I'll be right here.
- Can I compare cards with Ray?
- I got two matches with him.
Are you up for it, Seung-min?
- Hold on. Give us ten seconds.
- I'll go ahead and do it.
JI-SOO HAD 2 MATCHES WITH RAY
IT'S FITTING FOR SEUNG-MIN
TO COMPARE CARDS WITH RAY
- Do it.
- Go ahead.
KU'S SEUNG-MIN AND HARVARD'S RAY
COMPARE CARDS
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
1 MATCH
Your cards have been compared.
Please retrieve your cards.
POSSIBLE CASES FOR RAY
RAY IS EITHER AN ENTJ OR AN ISTJ
Is anyone from Team Harvard up for it?
- I am.
- Okay.
No, wait.
Who should compare cards with him?
We shouldn't? All right.
Then who should do it?
- We're not going to do it.
- No one will?
- Your team won't compare cards with me?
- Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- There's no one?
I think so. Sorry.
This is a pain in the neck.
Janice told her team
not to compare cards with me.
She told all of them not to do it with me.
I'm getting pissed off.
- Who should we ask? We need information.
- We need to compare with Ji-soo.
We need to compare with Sky and Ji-soo.
Ji-soo made the most comparisons.
1ST: SNU'S HYUN-BIN
2ND: HARVARD'S RAY
3RD: SNU'S HYUN-MIN
4TH: HARVARD'S JANICE
If we know hers,
we can eliminate a whole bunch.
Can I compare cards with Ji-soo?
- Hold on.
- It's David.
- One second.
If you go, we're done for.
- Really?
- Yes.
So that's why he asked me.
Ji-soo, let's compare cards.
- With you?
- Don't you know a lot about my card?
- But we already know...
- We'll pass.
KU'S JUNG-MIN AND SNU'S HYUN-SEOK
1 MATCH
SEUNG-MIN'S PERSONALITY TYPE IS ELIMINATED
HYUN-SEOK: ISFJ, ENFJ, ESTJ
- Hyun-seok, why don't we compare cards?
- Me?
- Should I do it?
- Go ahead.
HYUN-SEOK AND DAVID
TRY TO COMPARE CARDS
- Hold on.
- David.
Do you want to compare cards with me?
If you say yes to him,
we'll let you compare with Hyun-seok.
Take it or leave it.
We'll only do it
if you compare with both of them.
You have one minute left.
- We need to hurry.
- What do you think?
- We'll throw in two people.
- They're making an offer.
If you want to do it with Hyun-seok,
you have to do it with me too.
TEAM SNU WANTS MORE INFORMATION
Hold on.
We don't have much time, so please hurry.
But think about it...
- We need it too!
- We have nothing.
We have nothing right now. Just hurry up.
You have 30 seconds left.
Would you like to compare cards?
Please place your cards on the table.
Your cards have been compared.
1 MATCH
DAVID: INFJ, HYUN-SEOK: ESTJ
You'll keep your word, right?
- Of course.
- No, stop.
I'll do it.
- But I said David.
- Stop.
- He wants David.
- You said it was two-on-two.
- No.
- We both wanted David.
- Both of you?
- That's right.
- I thought you meant two-on-two.
- I see.
- We could do that too.
- All right.
Let's do that.
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Team Harvard's Ray
and Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin
have agreed to compare cards.
Your cards have been compared.
1 MATCH
RAY: ISTJ, HYUN-BIN: ENFJ
Hyun-bin and Ray have one in common.
Can we please get more rounds?
- We already know Hyun-bin's type.
- Right.
- That means Ray...
- It's one match, right?
We figured out Ray's personality type.
RAY IS EITHER AN ENTJ OR AN ISTJ
HE HAS 1 MATCH WITH HYUN-BIN
TEAM KU CAN DEDUCE THAT RAY IS AN ISTJ
- Please retrieve your cards.
- Hurry up, David.
- We're running out of time.
- Hurry.
That concludes the second round.
ROUND 2 RESULTS
JI-SOO, JANICE: 1
DONG-KYU, HYUN-BIN: 0
SEUNG-MIN, SKY: 3
SEUNG-MIN, RAY: 1
HYUN-SEOK, DAVID: 1
HYUN-BIN, RAY: 1
TEAM KU'S FINDINGS
2 CONFIRMED ANSWERS
HYUN-BIN: ENFJ, RAY: ISTJ
TEAM SNU'S FINDINGS
1 CONFIRMED ANSWER
DONG-KYU: ISTP
TEAM HARVARD'S FINDINGS
NO CONFIRMED ANSWERS
We will now begin the third round
of Find My Personality Type.
Please place your cards on the table.
HARVARD'S DAVID AND SNU'S HYUN-BIN
COMPARE CARDS
3 MATCHES
DAVID: INFJ, HYUN-BIN: ENFJ
HARVARD'S RAY AND KU'S DONG-KYU
COMPARE CARDS
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Team Harvard's Ray
and Team KU's Lee Dong-kyu...
- Wait! What is Dong-kyu doing?
- Dong-kyu?
- What are you doing?
- Dong-kyu!
Take care of him.
3 MATCHES
Your cards have been compared.
- You didn't need to compare with Ray.
- You didn't.
We already know Ray's personality type.
- We do?
- Yes!
Why did you do that?
I just realized that we knew Ray's
when he compared with Team SNU.
Exactly.
I ended up giving Team Harvard
and Team SNU more information,
which was a big mistake on my part.
THEY CAN'T FIGURE OUT DONG-KYU'S CARD
It can be both.
What the heck?
Didn't Ji-soo give us more leads?
Ji-soo and Hyun-bin had
one match between them.
THEY NEED TO KNOW JI-SOO'S CARD
We have to find out if she's an I or an E.
David, compare your card with Ji-soo's.
Go ask Ji-soo.
Ji-soo, would you like
to compare cards with me?
Hey, do it with David.
David!
Hurry. We need to submit the answers.
If we know David's,
we'll know Hyun-seok's.
- Would you like to compare cards?
- Yes.
Team Harvard's David
and Team KU's Lee Ji-soo
have agreed to compare cards.
Your cards have been compared.
Please retrieve your cards.
He has zero matches with Ji-soo.
0 MATCHES
DAVID: INFJ, JI-SOO: ESTP
Then I don't need to do it
with Hyun-seok, right?
- Nice.
- That means David is an INFJ.
I have zero matches with Ji-soo.
- Then it's this.
- Right.
- But with Hyun-bin...
- She had one match.
- One match.
- We need answers now.
He's an ENFP.
Let's pin down Ji-soo's card.
- Ji-soo's card can tell us Janice's.
- Let's figure out her card then.
Let's go for Ji-soo.
TEAM SNU USES THEIR BENEFIT
TO CONFIRM IF JI-SOO IS AN ESTP
- Your handwriting needs to be clear.
- ESTP.
Hurry up.
We'd like to use our benefit.
Team SNU will use their benefit.
- Please hurry.
- Hurry!
TEAM SNU HAS CONFIRMED
JI-SOO'S PERSONALITY TYPE
We got it right.
- We got it.
- We have it now.
We're all set.
- She's an ESTP.
- Seung-min and Janice are comparing.
Team Harvard's Janice
and Team KU's Chae Seung-min
have agreed to compare cards.
2 MATCHES
JANICE: ISFJ, SEUNG-MIN: ESFP
Your cards have been compared.
You must submit
your answer sheet within the time limit.
- Hyun-bin is an ENFJ, right?
- Right.
- And Ray is an ISTJ.
- Ray.
- Did Do-hyun compare his card?
- No.
- We have no idea what he is.
- Moving on...
- What do we know about Sky?
- Sky had three matches with Seung-min.
- She also had three with Hyun-bin.
- So it's this...
- Three matches with Hyun-bin.
- And one match with Dong-kyu.
- One with Dong-kyu.
- And three with me.
That means INFJ is eliminated.
- We eliminated INFJ.
- Right.
TEAM HARVARD'S BASE CAMP
ANSWER SHEET FOR TEAM KU
ANSWER SHEET FOR TEAM SNU
- Should this be ESTJ?
- Who's the ESTJ?
- INTP.
- Hyun-seok.
- Hyun-seok is an INTP?
No. Jung-min is an INTP.
- I'll put him down as INTP.
- Jung-min is an INTP.
All right.
- We need to submit our answers.
- ESFP...
We went over Ji-soo and Ray's.
Ji-soo and Janice had one match.
Look at all those possibilities.
We need to go through this quickly.
- It's not this one.
- We need to erase that.
- It isn't ISTJ either.
- Erase that one too.
Dong-kyu is an ISTP, the opposite of ENFJ.
Ji-soo had two matches with Ray.
We went over Ji-soo and Ray's.
Ji-soo and Janice had one match.
Look at the ratio between P and J.
- Do all these people have Js?
- Yes.
It's J, J, and then P.
- You have 20 seconds.
- They're all Js.
- It's a little odd.
- Let's go with ENFP.
- You have 20 seconds.
- They're all Js.
- It's a little odd.
- Let's go with ENFP.
- Let's hand it in.
- Take it.
- How much time do we have left?
- We have 20 seconds.
We have 20 seconds.
- Hand it in first.
- Submit it.
1ST: TEAM KU
Team KU submitted their answers.
2ND: TEAM HARVARD
Team Harvard submitted their answers.
I wondered what more I could do
to contribute to my team.
Then I remembered that submitting
the answer sheet first would break a tie.
So I ran for my life.
3RD: TEAM SNU
Team SNU submitted their answers.
That concludes the third round
of Find My Personality Type.
The final results will now be revealed.
Team KU scored...
TEAM KU SCORED 5 POINTS
five points.
- Damn...
- Why are they starting from us?
- We submitted it first.
- Right.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Please...
Team Harvard scored...
TEAM HARVARD SCORED 5 POINTS
five points.
It's a tie.
We have to do the Deathmatch.
- We did it!
- We're safe.
We can't be certain.
- We submitted it first.
- We did.
- Team SNU scored...
- Please...
TEAM SNU SCORED 3 POINTS
three points.
We did it!
The teams with the highest scores are
- KU and Harvard.
- I'm glad we submitted it first.
However, as Team KU
submitted their answers first,
they are the winners.
TEAM KU PROCEEDS TO THE FINALS
We've won the main match a few times.
TEAM KU'S ANSWERS
WRONG:
DO-HYUN, HYUN-MIN, JANICE
CORRECT:
HYUN-BIN, HYUN-SEOK, DAVID, RAY, SKY
TEAM HARVARD'S ANSWERS
WRONG:
DO-HYUN, HYUN-MIN, SEUNG-MIN
CORRECT: HYUN-BIN,
HYUN-SEOK, JUNG-MIN, DONG-KYU, JI-SOO
TEAM SNU'S ANSWERS
CORRECT:
DONG-KYU, JI-SOO, RAY
CORRECT: JI-SOO
WRONG: DAVID
JI-SOO WAS THE EXACT OPPOSITE OF DAVID,
BUT TEAM SNU FAILED TO CATCH THAT
DURING ROUND 3
Harvard's David and KU's Lee Ji-soo
have agreed to compare cards.
DAVID AND JI-SOO
HAD THE OPPOSITE PERSONALITY TYPES
0 MATCHES
TEAM SNU MISSED THIS CRITICAL INFORMATION
The information was shared
while we were discussing things,
so we all missed it.
Team Harvard and Team SNU,
please prepare for the Deathmatch.
We weren't happy
that we placed second in the main match.
We need to move on
and not let negativity bring us down.
So my focus is on the Deathmatch,
and I'm determined to win.
It was humiliating.
I felt lost and helpless.
As the oldest member,
I should've kept them grounded.
I should've been
the leader my team needed.
But I felt really bad
because I don't think I pulled my weight.
What's done is done,
so we're going to move on.
If the Deathmatch
is what we have to do to win the show,
we'll do it and win.
DO-HYUN, HYUN-MIN, HYUN-SEOK, HYUN-BIN
- They must be so nervous right now.
- I know.
- I was really nervous yesterday.
- You can't let yourself be overwhelmed.
Today's Deathmatch is...
Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors.
What is that?
- Rotate?
How do you rotate it?
In Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors,
you will roll a dice that has
two rocks, two papers, and two scissors.
You will then rotate
the dice on the board to win.
Before the game begins,
the net of the dice will be shown
to the players for two minutes.
After that, it will not be displayed.
The players and the dice's net
will be different for each round.
When a match begins,
the dice will be placed
at the top of the board.
Players will roll a dice
that only has the numbers 3, 4, and 5.
Then they will rotate the dice
according to the number they rolled.
3 MOVES
You may move the dice
in any of the four directions.
However, you may not move it back
to its previous position.
This is going to require skill.
Once the dice has reached its destination,
the side that touches the board
will determine the results.
If you win, you will receive one point.
If you lose, you will receive zero points.
If you lose, you will lose one point.
You'll be given 20 seconds for each turn.
If you fail to move the dice
within 20 seconds,
you will lose a point.
The game will consist of five rounds.
Whoever wins
four points first wins the round.
The team that wins
three rounds first wins the game.
I've been wanting
to play against Team Harvard,
and I'm positive we'll win.
SNU is the best university in the world.
A chance to beat
Harvard students won't come by often,
so I really want to beat them.
They're extremely on edge.
We placed second,
and Team SNU came in last.
That's a prime example
that even Team SNU isn't perfect.
So I'm confident that we will win.
Just watch. We'll show you why Harvard
is the world's number one university.
We're in a better place
than Team SNU at the moment,
so I'm sure we'll win the Deathmatch.
Harvard is the best university
in the world,
and we'll show you what the best can do.
I can't believe we have front-row seats
to the Deathmatch between SNU and Harvard.
- I want Team Harvard to win.
- I see.
That's what...
That's what we want.
Facing Team SNU in the finals
might prove to be a challenge for us.
Before we begin,
we will decide who goes first.
The team that rolls
a higher number will get to go first.
Please roll the dice.
TEAM SNU, TEAM HARVARD
Good job.
We'll start the game
with Team SNU playing first.
Both teams,
please prepare for the Deathmatch.
Let's go inside.
Let's do this.
TEAM HARVARD'S STRATEGY
MOVING 3 SQUARES UP
If you move three squares up, it's this.
THE ONE BELOW THE SIDE FACING TOP
If you move right, it's the one above.
MOVING 3 SQUARES TO THE RIGHT
If we go this way, it'll be this.
THE ONE TO THE LEFT OF THE SIDE FACING TOP
MOVING 3 SQUARES IN 1 DIRECTION
WILL MAKE THE DICE LAND ON SIDES
THAT'S ADJACENT TO THE ONE FACING TOP
MOVING 4 SQUARES UP
MOVING 4 SQUARES TO THE RIGHT
MOVING 4 SQUARES IN 1 DIRECTION
WILL ROTATE THE DICE
BACK TO ITS ORIGINAL POSITION
THE DICE MAY BE THE SAME,
BUT THE POSITION AND DIRECTION
OF THE DICE WILL CHANGE THE DICE'S NET
We have to be able to picture
the dice in our heads,
so instead of overcomplicating things,
I decided to memorize the net of the dice.
This is insane.
Can anyone play this game
without panicking a little bit?
Once the dice rotates,
I'm sure I'll forget the net.
If you forget the net,
you'll blow the whole round.
I know.
I'm so glad we won the main match today.
- That's all I can say.
- We would lose if we played this game.
What are you drawing?
Is that the game board? Got it.
The starting point is over here.
DO-HYUN EXPLAINS HIS STRATEGY
Think of it this way.
All sides are marked with A, B, or C.
Rotating the dice three times to the right
is the same as going once to the left.
So this would be C'.
I assigned an alphabet to all six sides.
My plan was to find
and memorize the squares
that I know will have a certain outcome.
For example,
if we rotate the dice three times,
I'd move it up, right, and down.
That'd make the side facing the board
face the board again.
SQUARES WHERE 3 MOVES
WOULD MAKE A' FACE THE BOARD
Our plan was to memorize the squares
so that we could utilize it in the game.
SQUARES WHERE YOU CAN MAINTAIN
THE SIDE THAT FACES THE BOARD
Since you're the best,
you should play first.
I want to play first.
You can go first.
Your time is up.
We're going to win.
- We can do it.
- I know.
This is our chance
to beat Harvard students.
I know we have it in us.
I appreciate how hard
you all have worked so far.
On three.
- Victory is SNU's!
Let's shout louder than them.
But I don't want to.
I don't want to look like a copycat.
We'll win with grace.
"With grace"?
Both teams, please gather
at the Main Hall for the Deathmatch.
You'll experience
the might of Korean education.
Bring it on.
Let's spare the baby of the team
from the Deathmatch.
HYUN-MIN
SNU'S YOUNGEST MEMBER, ROUND 4 PLAYER
Let's finish it in three rounds.
Twenty seconds is a really long time.
If you relax, 20 seconds is enough time.
David will do great.
ROTATE! ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS
The best university in the world is...
- Harvard.
- SNU.
DEATHMATCH
TEAM HARVARD VS TEAM SNU
Players for round one,
please come forward.
- Good luck.
- You've got this.
TEAM HARVARD'S DAVID
VS TEAM SNU'S DO-HYUN
I think Team Harvard might win.
- Why?
- It's really hard to tell.
I don't think Team SNU
is exceptionally good at this.
Just remember
the net of the dice, Hyun-min.
ROTATE! ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS
START
Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors. Round one.
We will now reveal
the dice.
NET OF THE FIRST DICE
I noticed that Team SNU
had some sort of strategy,
but I couldn't figure out what it was.
For this game,
we adapted Fleming's Left-Hand Rule.
The thumb would stand for scissors,
the middle finger for rock,
and the index finger for paper.
There's a point where the signs
are positioned at this angle.
TEAM SNU'S STRATEGY
Once you find that point,
you just need to memorize
what's on the other side of each sign.
THIS MAKES IT EASY TO MEMORIZE THE NET
That's the trick. If the dice moves,
you can move your hand
to mimic the dice's movement.
That's why I kept moving my hand
while memorizing the net.
Hurry.
Make it.
Maybe I should do it.
TEAM KU MAKES A DICE
You have ten seconds.
Your time is up.
We'll start with Team SNU.
Please roll the dice.
DO-HYUN HAS 5 MOVES
I rolled a five.
You rolled a five.
You have ten seconds.
I'll move the dice
down, down, down, down, and left.
Down.
Left.
TEAM SNU'S DO-HYUN WINS 1 POINT
You win.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: 0
How did he do that?
I won.
You win one point.
Team Harvard's David.
TEAM HARVARD'S DAVID GOES NEXT
Please roll the dice.
DAVID HAS 5 MOVES
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
You have ten seconds.
You have five seconds.
Okay. I'll go right.
- Your time is up.
- Right...
DAVID LOSES 1 POINT FOR GOING OVER TIME
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: -1
Twenty seconds went by
faster than I expected.
So I was really flustered.
Team SNU's Kyung Do-hyun,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 3.
- You rolled a 3.
DO-HYUN HAS 3 MOVES
You have ten seconds left.
I'll move the dice right, down, and left.
Right.
Down.
Left.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: -1
Team Harvard's David,
please roll the dice.
DAVID HAS 3 MOVES
It's a 3.
You rolled a three.
You have ten seconds left.
Please move the dice up, right, and up.
Up.
Right.
DAVID LOSES 1 POINT
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: -2
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
- You have five seconds.
- I'll go right, up, left, left, and left.
Right, up, left, left,
and left.
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: -2
- You lose one point.
- He made a mistake.
I think he mistook that side as A'.
DO-HYUN GOT CONFUSED
He'll be fine.
This game is crazy difficult.
I know. This is the hardest game ever.
Team Harvard's David,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 4.
- You rolled a 4.
I'll go down, right, right, and right.
Right.
DAVID'S SCORE REMAINS UNCHANGED
It's a tie.
I realized memorization
wasn't working for me.
So I kept trying to come up
with a strategy so that I could win.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: -2
Team SNU's Kyung Do-hyun,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 4.
- You rolled a 4.
I'll go right, right, up, and up.
Right, right, up, and up.
DO-HYUN WINS 1 POINT
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: -2
My team's strategy was to use our hands,
but at one point, I lost my place.
I needed to reset the dice,
so I drove it into a corner.
I knew having it in the corner
would make it difficult
for David to score a point.
So my plan was to find my place
when the dice was being moved.
Team Harvard's David,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
I'll go left, left,
down, right, and right.
You lose one point.
Team SNU's Kyung Do-hyun,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 3.
- You rolled a 3.
I'll go left, down, and right.
Right.
TEAM SNU: 3, TEAM HARVARD: -3
You win one point.
DAVID HAS 3 MOVES
It's a 3.
You rolled a three.
I'll go down, left, and left.
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 3
TEAM HARVARD: -4
1 MORE POINT AND TEAM SNU WINS
Kyung Do-hyun, please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 4.
- You rolled a 4.
I'll go up, up, left, and left.
Up, up, left, and left.
You win.
TEAM SNU: 4
TEAM HARVARD: -4
You win.
You earn one point.
TEAM SNU'S DO-HYUN WINS ROUND 1
It's all right.
Don't worry about it.
It was hard, wasn't it?
It's okay.
I had the net memorized,
so I should've been able
to picture the dice moving,
but I couldn't do that.
Was it hard to picture it moving?
I did memorize the net of the dice.
But I had to consider the board
and picture how the dice would move.
I didn't have time to do both,
so I guessed the whole thing.
It's just not doable.
Great job.
It's super difficult.
I knew my teammates believed in me
because they asked me
to play the first round.
So having that kind of support
helped me win the game.
Do-hyun is amazing.
He's really good.
The winner of the first round
of Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors
is Team SNU's Kyung Do-hyun.
ROUND 1
TEAM SNU:1, TEAM HARVARD: 0
Good luck. You're going to win.
I can beat Hyun-seok.
We played a similar game this morning.
I solved it faster than him.
ACE SELECTION
6TH: JANICE, 7TH: HYUN-SEOK
During the Ace Selection,
Hyun-seok placed lower than I did,
so I was optimistic about winning.
When things got confusing,
I drove the dice into a corner.
Even if you lose track,
you can find your place again.
- It's--
- You can see it move.
Exactly.
The fact that we ended up
in the Deathmatch alone was upsetting.
I knew the odds were 50:50
no matter who our opponent was.
Players for round two,
please come forward.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
- You too.
Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors. Round two.
Team Harvard's Janice
will compete
against Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok.
TEAM HARVARD'S JANICE
VS TEAM SNU'S HYUN-SEOK
I'm confident that I can memorize it all.
My team has to win no matter what,
and I have to pull my weight.
We will now reveal the dice for round two.
NET OF THE SECOND DICE
Rock, paper, scissors...
Scissors, rock...
Scissors...
Scissors, rock, paper...
Rock...
This is paper...
I want Team Harvard
to win the second round.
Same here.
Is it green, green, and yellow this time?
- I already memorized it.
- Really?
You just need to memorize two pairs.
If it's not the two, it's the other one.
So 2 rocks and 2 scissors?
Team Harvard will start off
the second round.
Team Harvard's Janice,
please roll the dice.
Okay.
I rolled a three.
JANICE HAS 3 MOVES
You rolled a three.
Down...
You have ten seconds.
I'll go down, down, and down.
Down, down, and down.
It's a tie.
JANICE'S SCORE REMAINS UNCHANGED
You win zero points.
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
HYUN-SEOK HAS 4 MOVES
You rolled a four.
He could go right, right, up, and up.
Or down, down, left, and left.
That's right.
You remember the rule, right?
SQUARES THAT MAINTAIN
THE ORIGINAL POSITION AFTER 4 MOVES
THE SIDE FACING THE BOARD
HE CAN WIN IF HE LANDS
IN ONE OF THESE SQUARES
I'll go right, right, up, and up.
Right, right, up, and up.
You win one point.
HYUN-SEOK WINS 1 POINT
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: 0
He's doing well.
Team Harvard's Janice,
please roll the dice.
JANICE HAS 4 MOVES
You rolled a 4.
I'll go left, left, down, and left.
Left, left, down, and left.
JANICE LOSES 1 POINT
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: -1
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
You rolled a 5.
I'll go up, right, down, down, and down.
Down, down, and down.
HYUN-SEOK'S SCORE REMAINS UNCHANGED
It's a tie.
Thank goodness.
A tie is acceptable.
It's much harder than it looks.
You rolled a 3.
JANICE HAS 3 MOVES
I'll go right, down, and left.
Right, down, and left.
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: -2
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
HYUN-SEOK HAS 5 MOVES
I'll go right, up, left, up, and up.
Up.
You lose one point.
TEAM SNU: 0
TEAM HARVARD: -2
What? He got it wrong.
It's fine.
I panicked when I got it wrong.
Team Harvard's Janice,
please roll the dice.
You rolled a 5.
JANICE HAS 5 MOVES
I'll go down, down, down, left, and up.
Down, down, down, left, and up.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 0
TEAM HARVARD: -1
I might be able to win this.
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 3.
- You rolled a 3.
I'll go down, right, and up.
Down, right, and up.
HYUN-SEOK'S SCORE REMAINS UNCHANGED
It's a tie. You win zero points.
You win zero points.
- Don't look at us.
- Don't look.
It's confusing.
I panicked. It was harder than I expected.
You rolled a 4.
JANICE HAS 4 MOVES
Right, down, right, and right.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 0
TEAM HARVARD: 0
We may be able to win the second round.
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
HYUN-SEOK HAS 4 MOVES
You rolled a 4.
I'll go up, up, up, and up.
TEAM SNU: 0, TEAM HARVARD: 0
It's a tie. You win zero points.
- I'll go up, up, left, and left.
- You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: 0
It's a tie.
I'll go down, right, up, right, and right.
You win zero points.
TEAM SNU: 1, TEAM HARVARD: 1
You win one point.
I'll go right, up, left, left, and left.
TEAM SNU: 2, TEAM HARVARD: 1
You win one point.
It's a tie. You win zero points.
The urge to win keeps getting stronger.
I have to win, and I will.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: 1
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 4.
- You rolled a 4.
HYUN-SEOK HAS 4 MOVES
I'll go up, up, left, and left.
Up, up, left, and left.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 3
TEAM HARVARD: 1
Team Harvard's Janice,
please roll the dice.
You rolled a three.
JANICE HAS 3 MOVES
I'll go down, right, and up.
Down, right, and up.
You lose one point.
JANICE LOSES 1 POINT
I got it wrong.
Team SNU's Song Hyun-seok,
please roll the dice.
I rolled a three.
HYUN-SEOK HAS 3 MOVES
He should go back.
A FEW MOMENTS AGO
Left.
HYUN-SEOK WON 1 POINT
ON HIS PREVIOUS TURN
I'll go down, right, and up.
IF HE TRACES BACK JANICE'S ROUTE,
HE CAN WIN 1 POINT
He can do this.
I'll go down, left, and up.
Down, left, and up.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU'S HYUN-SEOK WINS ROUND 2
- Good job.
- You too.
I was so nervous.
- It's harder than it looks, right?
- Good job.
My heart is still racing.
I'll go down, down, down, left, and up.
Down, down, left, and up.
JANICE ROTATED THE DICE
SO THAT THE TOP SIDE WOULD FACE THE BOARD
I had a feeling I would win.
You've got this, right?
Hyun-bin's meditating.
Can I talk to you for a second, Hyun-bin?
Is he busy?
DO NOT DISTURB HIM
- Can he do it?
- He knows it better than you.
- Okay.
- I'm sure he'll win.
Players for round three,
please come forward.
Wish me luck.
- You've got this.
- That hurts.
- Good luck.
- You too.
TEAM HARVARD'S SKY
VS TEAM SNU'S HYUN-BIN
It'd be a shame
if Team Harvard loses in three rounds.
Tell me about it.
Ray won't even get to play.
Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Round three.
We will now reveal
the dice for round three.
NET OF THE THIRD DICE
Rotate! Rock, Paper, Scissors.
Round three.
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin
will compete against Team Harvard's Sky.
will start off the third round.
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin,
please roll the dice.
I rolled a four.
HYUN-BIN HAS 4 MOVES
I'll go down, down, right, and right.
Down, down, right, and right.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: 0
Team Harvard's Sky, please roll the dice.
SKY HAS 4 MOVES
You rolled a 4.
You have ten seconds.
Left, down, left, and up.
SKY'S SCORE REMAINS UNCHANGED
It's a tie. You win zero points.
TEAM SNU: 1
TEAM HARVARD: 0
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin,
please roll the dice.
I rolled a three.
HYUN-BIN HAS 3 MOVES
You rolled a 3.
Please let him remember...
I'll go down, right, and up.
Down, right, and up.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: 0
He's good.
I caught on to Team SNU's strategy
while watching them play.
There's a pattern you can follow
while focusing on the top side only.
If you understand this pattern,
you don't need to memorize the dice.
After learning their strategy,
I knew how I was going to play the game.
IF SKY LOSES, RAY CAN'T PLAY THE GAME
- I rolled a 4.
- You rolled a 4.
SKY HAS 4 MOVES
You have ten seconds.
You have five seconds.
- I'll go--
- Your time is up.
SKY TIMED OUT
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin,
please roll the dice.
TEAM SNU: 2
TEAM HARVARD: -1
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
HYUN-BIN HAS 5 MOVES
I'll go down, right, up, left, and left.
Down, right, up, left, and left.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 3
TEAM HARVARD: -1
How is he doing that?
I was rattled.
He's really good.
When it comes to one-on-one games,
I'm confident I can win
regardless of who the opponent is.
Team Harvard's Sky, please roll the dice.
SKY HAS 4 MOVES
You rolled a 4.
You have ten seconds.
Down, down, down, and right.
You win one point.
SKY WINS 1 POINT
TEAM SNU: 3
TEAM HARVARD: 0
I knew I could do better,
but 20 seconds was a bit too short.
Team SNU's Jung Hyun-bin,
please roll the dice.
- I rolled a 5.
- You rolled a 5.
HYUN-BIN HAS 5 MOVES
I'll go right, up, left, down, and down.
Right, up, left, down, and down.
...and down.
You win one point.
TEAM SNU: 4
TEAM HARVARD: 0
Good game.
TEAM SNU WINS THE DEATHMATCH,
ROTATE! ROCK, PAPER, SCISSORS
You were amazing.
Since Team KU was in a Deathmatch,
I was glad we got to experience it too.
I'm confident we'll win the finals
no matter what the game is.
What do we do?
You did great.
I was really confident in myself
up until the game started.
I thought memorizing this
would be a piece of cake.
We failed to think out of the box
and ended up wasting our time
during the strategy meeting.
The fourth team
to be eliminated from Elite League is
Team Harvard.
It never feels good to lose.
I made a lot of mistakes,
so that was a tough pill to swallow.
I feel bad because it feels like
we're sending them home.
Team Harvard, please exit the grounds.
In one of the interviews,
I said I wouldn't go home so easily.
I'm very competitive,
and I don't like it when my pride is hurt.
So I was really upset when we lost.
I know we could've done better.
It was sad being eliminated
after such a disappointing performance.
Based on what I knew
about the rigid education system here,
I assumed Korean students
would lack creativity.
...who can call a timeout.
But they turned out to be
very creative strategists.
Although they were my competitors,
I was really happy to meet
so many brilliant Koreans.
He's a genius.
This show introduced me
to a new group of friends.
It was a very fruitful
and worthwhile journey.
That was fun.
Brainpower survival challenge,
Elite League.
Let the finals begin.
We'll defeat Team SNU.
Victory is SNU's.
In the end, Korea University will win.
We won't lose to anyone.
All the numbers point to our victory.
We will beat Team KU
and win the show.
He's insane.
He's amazing.
Dong-kyu is really fast.
That's impressive.
No one can stop Dong-kyu.
- Hold on.
- You have to hold the fort.
No. Just move.
Hold on. Is that the right call?
You can do it.
- Team KU...
- They shouldn't be allowed...
Do we need to clap?
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim