ELITE LEAGUE
That concludes
the first round of Signal Investigation.
Team SNU, Team Yonsei,
Team KU, and Team Harvard
have apprehended the culprit.
SNU, YONSEI, KU, HARVARD SUCCEED
Team KAIST has failed
to apprehend the culprit.
ROUND 1
TEAM KAIST FAILS TO CATCH THE CULPRIT
We're screwed.
We lost this round,
but I knew there would be
other teams that would mess up.
So, if we use fewer cards,
we will still have a decent shot.
Before we begin the second round,
you will be given ten minutes
to confer with your teammates
and edit your 15 Signal Cards.
Your arresting officer
may also switch roles
with one of the investigators.
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
ROUND 1
KAIST: 0
SNU, HARVARD, YONSEI, KU: 1
All contestants,
please return to your base camps.
- What happened?
- I'm so sorry.
- No, hold on.
- What confused you?
What was confusing?
We almost had it.
- Was it down to these two?
- Yes, I even had it set aside.
We should've been able
to tell them apart by their hairstyles.
We need additional clues
for different hairstyles.
- This card drove me crazy.
- Great job.
JUST LIKE SO HYUN-JI,
KIM JUNG-MIN WAS TORN BETWEEN 2 SUSPECTS
I had to guess
because they shared the same traits.
Really?
- They're both wearing earrings.
- Team KAIST...
- Did they choose this?
- Team KAIST chose this.
We need to work on our hairstyle clues.
Let's add length to the description.
TEAM KU ADDS HAIRSTYLE DETAILS
It would've been easy
if we had known the hair length.
- Are you okay as the arresting officer?
- Yes.
- You'll do well.
- He's right.
- I'm sorry.
- It'll only get more difficult.
- It wasn't your fault.
- It wasn't.
I wanted to give her
a chance to make up for it.
I thought Hyun-ji would be the best
at scrutinizing the clues we gave her.
I trusted her.
First, let's add "short hair."
TEAM KAIST ALSO ADDS MORE DETAILS
Write "mid-length" next.
And "ponytail."
The next important thing is colors.
As for colors...
We devised a 3 by 3 matrix
to convey information on colors.
The card's placement would tell us
what color we were describing.
It covered all the colors of the rainbow
including black, white, and gray.
So I was confident
we'd apprehend the culprit this time.
I think we should add
a card that describes colors.
Why don't we use
the clock system here as well?
- What?
- The colors of the rainbow and black.
We can use the eight directions
to indicate different colors.
THE PLACEMENT INDICATES THE COLOR
Hey.
You did great.
I want to keep apprehending.
You did an amazing job.
- There was one thing that confused me.
- What was it?
I could only see one ear.
THE NUMBER OF EARS VISIBLE
ARE DIFFERENT FOR EACH SUSPECT
0 EAR, 1 EAR, 2 EARS
In that case...
Hold on.
Two ears and one ear.
- One ear.
- I see.
"EARS" MEANS 2 VISIBLE EARS
"EAR" MEANS 1 VISIBLE EAR
- The number of ears?
- Yes.
You can see 1 ear, 2 ears, or no ears.
I think we can add clues
by rotating cards 2, 3, and 4 around.
Let's take ears as an example.
Each direction would represent 0, 1, or 2.
A CARD'S DIRECTION INDICATES A TRAIT
This means black, and this means dyed.
- Bangs, no bangs.
- No bangs.
Having a trait is the default.
- If you turn it...
- Right.
Guys, when we rotate the cards,
it should be counterclockwise,
not clockwise.
We should go counterclockwise.
Always rotate the cards counterclockwise.
- Like this, right?
- That's right.
I just wanted to make sure
that we're aligned.
We're engineering students.
Give us a little credit.
30 MINUTES LATER
I find it hard to believe
that Team SNU is struggling this much
when it's only the second day.
I'm just so mad at ourselves.
Your time is up.
Investigators,
please gather at the Main Hall.
Arresting officers,
please remain at your base camps.
This is so sad.
We really have to focus
if we want to avoid the Deathmatch.
Hopefully, two more teams
will mess up, right?
We'll be fine as long as we use
1 evidence photo in the next 2 rounds.
You never know what will happen.
We can turn it around.
- Anything could happen.
- We shouldn't be overly confident.
We thought we wouldn't mess up.
I know. We shouldn't be arrogant.
It could lead to our downfall.
Representatives of each team,
please take a photo of the culprit.
That looks like Yu Jae-seok.
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
ROUND 2 CULPRIT
Does he look like he's happy?
Well, if we did--
He looks happy if you look at his eyes.
His lips curve upwards as well.
Is he happy?
He looks happy to me.
It does seem that way,
but it's not obvious.
So if it's vague...
Let's leave that out.
The color of the tie could be a huge clue.
We should put it down as brown.
What? You mean the tie?
It's plum.
Is it brown or plum?
We should leave this out then.
No, hear me out.
- It's still better to add a color clue.
- Let's pick one among these.
So this is where I'm torn right now.
Should this be flagged
as "others" or "tools"?
- It's not a tool.
- It's "others," then.
- Okay, we can go with that.
- You're not sure if we should include it?
No, I think it would confuse him.
I still think we need it.
So you think it's better
to let him know there's an object.
Exactly.
"Glasses, hat, beard." That's "OXX."
TEAM SNU IS READY
TO TAKE THE EVIDENCE PHOTO
- What's next?
- Next...
"Pants, short hair, jacket."
That's "OOO."
- He's wearing pants.
- It's "OOO."
He has short hair and is wearing a jacket.
- "Short-sleeves, object."
- Right.
"Short-sleeves, object."
We're ready.
We're done, right?
Hold on. What about bangs?
- Is the order no bangs, bangs?
- I think so.
Right?
He has bangs.
- I mean...
- This is right.
Does this mean "no bangs"?
- Why?
- No bangs, bangs.
Is it the other way around?
- Hold on.
- No bangs, bangs...
Isn't it bangs, no bangs?
What if we fail because of this?
We had an issue
with how we'd place the card.
Placing the card
horizontally or vertically
would determine
whether the culprit had bangs or not.
Damn it.
If we lose this round,
we'll be tied with Team KAIST.
I think having bangs was the default.
30 MINUTES AGO
Card 3 is for bangs.
Bangs, no bangs.
VERTICAL: NO BANGS
HORIZONTAL: BANGS
CARD 3 IS PLACED HORIZONTALLY
WHICH MEANS THE CULPRIT HAS BANGS
BUT THE CULPRIT DOESN'T HAVE BANGS
It was a dumb mistake,
so we were trying to find a way
to let Hyun-bin know
that we forgot our strategy.
I feel bad about messing this up.
I know. We have to own that.
Let's shoulder
the responsibility together.
Damn it.
TIME TO CREATE EVIDENCE PHOTOS IS UP
Your time is up.
Please deliver your envelopes
to your base camps.
SUSPECTS FOR ROUND 2
TEAM KU'S BASE CAMP
GLASSES
SUSPECTS WITHOUT GLASSES ARE RULED OUT
DAVID RULES OUT SUSPECTS WITHOUT GLASSES
TEAM YONSEI'S BASE CAMP
CHO HYUN-JUN IS SORTING OUT
THE INFORMATION PASSED ON TO HIM
TEAM SNU'S BASE CAMP
What the hell?
Why did they place it like that?
CARD 3: SHORT-SLEEVES, OBJECT
Why?
We agreed to place it
either vertically or horizontally,
but my teammates placed it
at an angle that was slanted.
It wasn't what we had agreed on,
so I wasn't sure what it meant.
What's that supposed to mean?
10 MINUTES AGO
How's this?
- Let's keep it as is.
- I have an idea.
Since we're confused,
we should let him know.
Let's set these slightly apart
and place "OXO" here at an odd angle.
- He'll know what that means.
- What?
We'll turn the card slightly
and place "OXO" next to it.
This should tell him we got confused.
Placing the card
at an angle we hadn't discussed
was our way of telling him
we were lost and forgot the rules.
I find it hard to believe
that Team SNU is struggling this much
when it's only the second day.
I'm just so mad at ourselves.
You have one minute.
TEAM KAIST'S BASE CAMP
TEAM KAIST'S SO HYUN-JI
HASN'T IDENTIFIED THE CULPRIT YET
It was incredibly difficult
to choose between the two,
so I wasn't sure
if I could find the culprit.
Do you think Hyun-ji will get it?
She must be under
a lot of pressure right now.
I'm sure she'll manage.
I hope Hyun-bin will get our message
and understand
what we were trying to convey.
I just want other teams to mess up.
You have 30 seconds.
Your time is up.
Arresting officers,
please put the photo of the culprit
in the envelope
and send it to the Main Hall.
Let's see.
- Please...
I'm too scared to look.
I just can't.
Investigators, please open the envelope.
Did he get it?
TEAM KU CATCHES THE CULPRIT
- Nice.
- It was so easy.
TEAM YONSEI CATCHES THE CULPRIT
TEAM HARVARD CATCHES THE CULPRIT
I bet she got it right.
She got it.
TEAM KAIST CATCHES THE CULPRIT
- Please...
- Just tear it here.
Please... I can't look.
I was scared we would lose this round.
I had faith in Hyun-bin.
He got a perfect score
on the CSAT for a reason.
He got it right.
- We got it, right?
- Everyone got it right.
TEAM SNU CATCHES THE CULPRIT
I seriously thought we were done for.
Let's ask him if he got our message.
Did everyone get it?
I think everyone got it.
You're right.
Oh, no.
That means the team that used
one evidence photo will win, right?
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
IF TEAMS HAVE THE SAME NUMBER OF ARRESTS,
THE TEAMS THAT USED
FEWER EVIDENCE PHOTOS WILL SURVIVE
TEAMS A, B, C: SURVIVE
TEAMS D, E: FACE ELIMINATION
All teams have apprehended the culprit.
Before we begin the third round,
you will be given ten minutes
to confer with your teammates
and edit your 15 Signal Cards.
Why did you place card three that way?
We got confused.
We forgot which direction
meant bangs and which meant no bangs.
- I see.
- So was it no bangs, bangs?
It was bangs, no bangs.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Was this round difficult?
- This round?
No, but this confused me.
We tried to let you know
that we were confused,
but we used "XX" to convey
that he doesn't have bangs.
It took me a while
because the placement threw me off.
So I excluded that information,
and managed to find the culprit.
TEAM SNU SORTS OUT DIRECTIONS
Let's keep it consistent.
If it's about bangs,
- the default would be bangs are present.
- Okay.
- So it's bangs, no bangs.
- Right.
- It's 0, 1, 2.
- That's right.
Male, female.
- Male, female?
Hey, that was so difficult.
Was it difficult?
It was really confusing.
The tie wasn't red. It was brown.
It wasn't just brown,
but more like dark brown.
It's almost black.
We'll have to use more specific clues.
What do we need to add?
- Let's fine-tune clues for colors.
- Okay.
- We could add "dark" and--
- "Light"?
We'll add "dark" and "light."
This is getting complicated.
I hope I don't get confused.
Judging from how it's been going,
the next round may be impossible to solve.
Would the direction
the person is facing help?
- Yes, that'd help us a lot.
- Facing front, right, and left.
Most suspects face the front,
but some are slightly turned.
I know.
So we'll tell you if they're facing front,
facing slightly to the right or left,
or standing at a 90-degree angle.
Let's use the card as a protractor.
Does slightly left mean
the left shoulder is further back?
From our point of view,
this is slightly left,
- and this is slightly right.
- Okay.
So slightly left means
the right shoulder is further back, right?
The left shoulder would come forward.
- Right.
- Check the shoulder that comes forward.
We'll add another one here.
- We want to add patterns.
- We'll be adding patterns.
We'll add patterns.
- I can't really focus when I'm waiting.
- Really?
The three of them had discussed
and fine-tuned a lot of clues,
so it was hard for me
to keep up with all the updates
within a short period of time.
You're not confident in your role?
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm not.
- One of us should do it.
- How about you?
- Me?
- Yes.
I know all our clues inside out,
- but you can do it if you want to.
- I don't want to.
- You should do it.
- I agree.
- Do you understand all our clues?
- I do. I know it inside out.
I'm sorry to bring this up,
but if everyone
gets it right in the third round,
they'll have used 3 evidence photos
when our count would be 4.
We went overboard in the first round.
We need the third round to be difficult.
- Totally.
- That's our best-case scenario.
I hope we get it right
and one team gets it wrong.
I really don't want to do the Deathmatch.
There's a possibility another team used
more than one evidence photo.
How many evidence photos
did the others use? Did they all use two?
- I think they used two at most.
- Damn it.
We've only used four so far.
We'll try to use one this time.
The next round will be harder,
so getting it right matters more.
I hope it's super difficult.
You can do it, Hyun-ji.
If it's difficult,
you'll be the only one to get it right.
I hope the last round
is extremely difficult.
Your time is up.
TEAM KAIST MAY FACE THE DEATHMATCH
FOR FAILING TO APPREHEND THE CULPRIT
TEAM HARVARD MAY FACE THE DEATHMATCH
FOR USING TOO MANY EVIDENCE PHOTOS
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
THE LAST ROUND WILL DETERMINE
WHO GOES TO THE DEATHMATCH
We can do this.
We just need to remember our clues.
What do I do? This?
I'm jealous they can joke around.
Representatives of each team,
please take a photo of the culprit.
Please.
The more difficult it is,
the more cards we'll use.
But in the third round,
the culprit didn't have
a lot of distinct traits.
This round will be difficult for Hyun-ji.
- Seriously?
- She's wearing heels.
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
ROUND 3 CULPRIT
WHO IS THE CULPRIT IN THIS LINEUP?
- She has long hair.
- We can use our direction clues.
Her right shoulder is forward,
so that's slightly right.
Does she have long or short hair?
- Is it short?
- She has short hair.
- No bangs.
- Is her hair long?
No, let's go with short hair.
- Isn't it long?
- No, it's mid-length.
- Is it?
- If her hair reaches her shoulders,
- we agreed it would be mid-length.
- Got it.
I'm worried that Hyun-bin
will think she has short hair.
- He won't.
- No way.
Short hair would reach just about here.
How about her pants?
These are definitely pants.
They are. Don't worry.
She's wearing long, wide slacks.
That's my go-to look.
Does she have long hair?
She does.
Where's the "holding object" card?
We shouldn't use
more than one evidence photo.
We really need to keep it at one.
We should've used
one evidence photo in the first round.
- I know. I'm kicking myself over it.
- Well, we didn't know.
I'm worried that the suspects
are going to look very similar.
Adding the number
of visible ears was a good idea.
We might win because of this clue.
If it takes Team KAIST this long,
they may be using
multiple evidence photos.
Let's make it as detailed as possible
even if it takes one more evidence photo.
Getting it right was our priority,
so we used two evidence photos.
Is there anything else we could add
with the cards we haven't used?
There are so many cards we didn't use.
We should tell her it's a rose.
The other suspects could be holding
some other object that's red.
Why don't we make the letter F
to let her know it's a flower.
20 MINUTES AGO
We can make letters with the cards.
We can make the letter R.
Should we go with rose?
- The letter R?
- Yes.
Like this.
It does look like it.
I think this will be enough
for her to get it right.
Please deliver your envelopes
to your base camps.
Damn.
Is this it?
DAVID IS FLUSTERED
THAT THERE'S ONLY 1 EVIDENCE PHOTO
I knew the other teams would try
to use as few evidence photos as possible,
so I suggested we use one evidence photo.
David is very logical
and doesn't overthink things,
so I was confident he'd get it.
1 VISIBLE EAR
TEAM KU'S BASE CAMP
I was flustered at first because the cards
were scattered all over the place.
What I saw in the evidence photo
didn't align with what we'd agreed upon,
so it threw me off.
20 MINUTES AGO
How does this sound?
We'll place the direction card below
and the object card above it.
Sounds great.
- So the cards mimic her posture?
- Right.
CARDS ARE PLACED
ON CORRESPONDING BODY PARTS
We didn't discuss this,
but I hope he gets it.
I really hope he figures it out.
Please look at how the cards are arranged.
I hope Jung-min gets it.
I'm counting on him.
I really am.
TEAM SNU'S' BASE CAMP
SHORT HAIR: X
THE CULPRIT DOESN'T HAVE SHORT HAIR
SUSPECTS WITH SHORT HAIR ARE RULED OUT
BLACK HAIR
SUSPECTS WITH DYED HAIR ARE RULED OUT
TEAM KAIST'S BASE CAMP
HAPPY, LONG PANTS, HEELS
RIGHT HAND
We added a clue that indicates
which hand they're holding the object.
The clue would tell me if they're using
the right hand, the left hand, or both.
So I was able to rule out
the suspects using the wrong hand.
SUSPECTS USING
THEIR LEFT HAND ARE RULED OUT
That concludes the third round.
Arresting officers,
please take the photo of the culprit
and gather at the Main Hall.
Well done.
You did great.
- You're finally out.
- I'm not sure if I got it.
- Was it confusing?
- You got it.
The suspects all looked identical.
Really?
Was this round easy?
See for yourself.
- I bet it was the hardest round.
- I think I got it, though.
Was it complicated?
Not at all. It was super clear.
If everyone gets it right,
we might end up in the Deathmatch.
- Why?
- We used five photos in total.
TOTAL NUMBER OF EVIDENCE PHOTOS
SNU: 3, KAIST: 5, HARVARD: 5
YONSEI: 4, KU: 3
We need one team to fail this round.
SNU, KU, or Yonsei needs to get it wrong.
Team SNU, please open your envelope.
SIGNAL INVESTIGATION
ROUND 3 CULPRIT
- Please.
- I'm too scared to look.
- I'll flip it over.
- Please.
Did we get it wrong?
- He got it right.
- He got it.
ROUND 3
TEAM SNU CATCHES THE CULPRIT
TEAM KU CATCHES THE CULPRIT
He got it.
Let's open it.
I hope I got it.
It's correct.
ROUND 3
TEAM KAIST CATCHES THE CULPRIT
You should've gotten
the first one right, dummy.
I'm sorry.
We used the most number of photos,
so that made me nervous.
ROUND 3
TEAM HARVARD CATCHES THE CULPRIT
TEAM KAIST WILL FACE THE DEATHMATCH
IF YONSEI SUCCEEDS,
HARVARD WILL FACE THE DEATHMATCH
It didn't feel great.
Try not to look so happy.
Team KAIST is miserable right now.
ROUND 3
TEAM YONSEI FAILS TO CATCH THE CULPRIT
What? They got it wrong.
They got it wrong.
Why do they all have long hair?
The clue said she had short hair.
Hold on.
You didn't look?
- We did.
- We did, but she had a mid-length bob.
At first, I was sure I got it right
because I chose the suspect
that I thought had short hair.
So I was convinced that I got it right.
It turns out that we all had
different definitions for short hair.
- This is what short hair looks like.
- I know,
but we only had this picture,
and it looked like she had short hair.
But this is what short hair looks like.
We categorized the hairstyles
into short and long hair.
But we should've thought it through
and added mid-length.
40 MINUTES AGO
Let's discuss hairstyles.
We should go with
bald, cropped, short, and long hair.
Is it short hair
if it reaches the shoulders?
- This should be short hair.
- Okay.
The final results will now be revealed.
Team SNU
made three arrests.
Team KU
Team Harvard
made three arrests.
Team Yonsei
made two arrests.
Team KAIST
The top three teams,
SNU, KU, and Harvard, have survived.
The two teams
that will face the Deathmatch
are Team Yonsei and Team KAIST.
TEAM YONSEI VS TEAM KAIST
- We need to prepare for the Deathmatch.
- I just...
We had a great system,
so it bummed me out that we got it wrong.
How can that be short hair?
I was confused and flustered at first.
After I calmed down a bit,
I thought about
how to prepare for the Deathmatch.
We have to prepare for the Deathmatch.
I'll win the Deathmatch for us.
You need to let it go
because it wasn't all your fault.
We're a team, so everyone is responsible.
I knew I could've done better,
so I felt bad for letting my team down.
I was overwhelmed with guilt and regrets.
It'll be amazing if we win.
Stop saying "if."
We have to win, and we will.
Let's just focus on how we'll win.
We can do it.
- We can do it.
- We can win.
Both teams,
please prepare for the Deathmatch.
DEATHMATCH
TEAM YONSEI VS TEAM KAIST
KI-HONG, NA-YOON, JU-HYUNG, HYUN-JUN
HYUN-JI, JUN-HYUK, SEO-YEON, SUNG-BUM
How did we end up here again?
I was quite exhausted at that point,
and it all felt like a bad dream.
We all felt cornered.
I think my team ended up
in the Deathmatch because of me,
so I was determined to give it my all.
I knew we had to do well,
but I had a feeling we'd win.
Team KAIST must be exhausted
doing this two days in a row.
It's about perseverance at this point.
It'll be hard
if they're as exhausted as I am today.
I knew it'd be a cutthroat match,
but I was confident we'd win.
We needed to be prepared
to win the Deathmatch.
We'll survive this Deathmatch
no matter what.
Today's Deathmatch
is Pixel Number.
"Pixel Number"?
- What's that?
- "Pixel Number"?
In Pixel Number,
you will be asked to find target numbers
by combining a set of cards.
The team that finds
the most target numbers wins the game.
TARGET NUMBER 6:
COMBINATION: 1, 8, 11
When the match begins,
you'll be presented with 15 Pixel Cards
TARGET NUMBERS: 3, 6, 9
and 3 target numbers.
- That sounds fun.
- It totally does.
The target number is the number
that appears when Pixel Cards are layered,
and you must use at least two Pixel Cards
to make a target number.
MINIMUM NUMBER OF PIXEL CARDS: 2
The contestant that rings the bell first
will be given a chance to answer,
and he or she must give the answer
within the ten-second time limit.
You will be awarded
one point for a correct answer.
Your opponent will get a chance to answer
if your answer is wrong
or your time is up.
Each round will come to an end
when all the target numbers are found.
ROUND OVER
This match will consist of five rounds.
For rounds 1 to 4,
you will be given 3 target numbers.
In round 5,
you will be given 2 target numbers
and one hidden number.
If you get the hidden number right,
your team will be awarded three points.
After the five rounds,
the team with the most points wins.
Please choose
the contestant for each round.
They're playing one on one?
- Choosing the order will be important.
- Totally.
Matchups can be critical, too.
We can't prepare for this.
We'll just have to pull our own weight.
Both teams,
please prepare for the Deathmatch.
Let's go.
You will be given
five minutes to discuss your strategy.
So it's a one-on-one match.
How should we do this?
We only have five minutes. Let's hurry.
- I'm not that confident.
- Me neither.
- We have to decide who'd do best here.
- Not me.
Honestly, I think I'll do fine.
- Really? You think so?
- Yes.
I'll go first.
All right. Cool.
- Go and set the tone for us.
- I will.
You'll see the same
pixelated numbers in elevators.
Whenever I took the elevator,
I would look at the numbers
and would work out which pixels
were present for different numbers.
There are 2 holes in the number 8, right?
There can't be a pixel there,
but there should be pixels in the middle.
I've thought about this quite a lot,
so I was confident
I'd do well in this challenge.
Ki-hong will play first,
practice during the next three,
and play again in the fifth round.
Numbers 2, 3, and 5 seem important.
Are you suggesting we tackle them first?
- Wouldn't 1 be easy?
- These 3 lines are used often.
It's used for 2 as well as 3.
My strategy was to identify the numbers
that filled the top, middle, and bottom.
PRIORITIZE THE 3 HORIZONTAL LINES
The numbers 2, 3, 5, 6, and 8
fill up all three rows.
So I wanted to prioritize checking
whether the given Pixel Cards
can be combined to create those numbers.
We can so win this.
We'll get three target numbers,
so find the pixels that are used the most.
Numbers 3, 4, 7, 8, and 9
need the column on the right.
TARGET NUMBERS: 3, 4, 7, 8, 9
Here's the rundown. 3, 4, 7, 8, and 9
all need the right column.
And 6 and 8 need the left column.
TARGET NUMBERS: 6, 8
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 5
That makes it easy.
Two and five are the only exceptions.
Six and eight need the left column,
and the rest need the right.
1, 3, 4, 7, 9: RIGHT COLUMN
6: LEFT COLUMN
8, 0: BOTH COLUMNS
2, 5: PARTIALLY FILLED
Look for numbers
that fill up the right column.
TEAM KAIST PRIORITIZES THE COLUMNS
Since all numbers use pixels
on both the right and left columns,
I thought it'd be easier
to have them filled first.
We went over this earlier,
so just memorize the patterns now.
There are so many overlaps.
Like I said earlier,
write it down in your notepads.
I drew all the numbers on the board
because I had to look at the cards
and come up with a combination
that would form the target number quickly.
I kept practicing
with the patterns on the board.
This will be really tricky.
What about the order?
The order will be important.
I'll go first since I'm the leader.
Not many can step up
the way he did under such pressure.
We needed to win the first round
to set the tone of the game.
We needed the momentum on our side.
Please gather at the Main Hall
for the Deathmatch.
Guys, let's go.
So it begins.
Don't be intimidated.
We had no choice but to win.
Losing was not an option for us.
I'm sure Team KAIST is exhausted
and under a lot of pressure right now.
We're going to win
because we're full of energy.
They must be so stressed right now.
I'd hate to be in their shoes.
PIXEL NUMBER
We will now begin
the first round of Pixel Number.
Players for the first round,
please step forward.
I wonder who's first.
I have to see who's up first.
Players for the first round,
please step forward.
TEAM YONSEI'S PLAYER FOR ROUND 1
KIM KI-HONG
I knew they would
choose their best player to play first,
so I expected Sung-bum to step up.
TEAM KAIST'S PLAYER FOR ROUND 1
HEO SUNG-BUM
I was confident I'd win.
- Is it Sung-bum?
- I knew it'd be him.
I guess the aces are going first.
- I think he's cool.
- Who?
- Sung-bum.
- Me too.
I'll show them how it's done.
Sung-bum is good, but so am I.
The question for round one
will now be revealed.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBERS: 1, 7, 9
They need to make 1, 7, and 9.
- That's tricky.
- I know, right?
He just rang the bell.
Heo Sung-bum from Team KAIST.
My target number is one.
The combination is 2, 9, and 14.
Your target number is 1,
and your combination is 2, 9, and 14.
Team KAIST's Heo Sung-bum.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 1
That is correct.
He got it right. Number one is easy.
I believed in him
and knew I could count on him.
TEAM KAIST: 1
TEAM YONSEI: 0
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBERS: 7, 9
We will now resume the game.
Heo Sung-bum from Team KAIST.
My target number is seven.
The combination is 4, 6, and 10.
Team KAIST's Heo Sung-bum.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 7
That is correct.
He's a genius.
Team KAIST got two numbers already.
He's good.
I admit I was anxious,
but I knew I had to keep my cool,
especially at a time like this.
We will now resume the game.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 9
We will now resume the game.
Kim Ki-hong from Team Yonsei.
I rang the bell
without thinking things through.
My target number is nine.
The combination is 3, 11, and 12.
Your target number is nine,
and your combination is 3, 11, and 12.
That is incorrect.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 9
That is incorrect.
I got it wrong.
I thought I lost this round
because I practically gave
the answer away.
Your opponent will have
ten seconds to give an answer.
I had it earlier.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 9
HEO SUNG-BUM FAILS TO ANSWER
Both of you may answer now.
Kim Ki-hong from Team Yonsei.
My target number is 9.
The combination is 3, 7, and 12.
TARGET NUMBER: 9
COMBINATION: 3, 7, 12
Your target number is nine,
and your combination is 3, 7, and 12.
ROUND 1
TARGET NUMBER: 9
That is correct.
That concludes the first round.
Team KAIST earned 2 points,
and Team Yonsei earned 1 point.
ROUND 1
TEAM KAIST: 2, TEAM YONSEI: 1
I wasn't happy with the results.
I was sure my teammates
were more capable than Team Yonsei.
If all of them earned 2 points each round,
we'd stand at 8 to 4.
So I thought we'd win with nine points.
We had the upper hand in this game.
Earning one point
against Sung-bum isn't bad at all.
I agree. He's good.
He stands out as an individual player.
It's simpler than we expected.
Tackle the easy ones first.
Numbers 1 and 7 were easy.
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 2
The second round will now begin.
Players for the second round,
please step forward.
- Who is up next?
- Who is up?
We're all thinking the same thing.
The lineup is pretty important.
Sung-bum, then...
As soon as I saw my opponent,
I knew I would win.
My opponent seemed like an easy target.
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 2
KAIST'S HYUN-JI VS YONSEI'S HYUN-JUN
The question for round two
will now be revealed.
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBERS: 4, 6, 9
This round seems more complicated.
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBERS: 4, 6, 9
He should go for four first, right?
All right.
Cho Hyun-jun from Team Yonsei.
He got it this fast?
My target number is nine.
He's going with nine?
The combination is 3, 7, and 11.
Your combination is 3, 7, and 11.
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBER: 9
That is correct.
I was screwed.
I knew I could win this round.
He's really good.
Team Yonsei got it already.
In six seconds.
I was worried that he was taking the lead.
I knew I had to be quick
in finding the numbers.
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBERS: 4, 6
So Hyun-ji from Team KAIST.
My target number is four.
The combination is 1, 10, and 12.
TARGET NUMBER: 4
COMBINATION: 1, 10, 12
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBER: 4
That is correct.
TEAM KAIST: 3
TEAM YONSEI: 2
I had my faith in her.
Cho Hyun-jun from Team Yonsei.
My target number is 6.
The combination is 2, 6, and 15.
Your combination is 2, 6, and 15.
TARGET NUMBER: 6
COMBINATION: 2, 6, 15
ROUND 2
TARGET NUMBER: 6
That is correct.
TEAM KAIST: 3
TEAM YONSEI: 3
I was relieved.
To be honest,
I knew I was going to win from the get-go.
I felt really bad
for messing this up for my team.
The score is now tied at 3 to 3.
ROUND 2
TEAM KAIST: 3, TEAM YONSEI: 3
- It's a close match.
- It's really close.
They're neck and neck.
They must be really alert right now.
They're laser-focused
on finding the numbers.
We will now begin
the third round of Pixel Number.
Players for the third round,
please step forward.
It didn't matter who my opponent was.
I just wanted to win.
I wanted to score
as many points as I could.
We should all get at least 1 point.
If we get 2 points, even better.
Na-yoon will do well.
I reminded myself
to keep my calm at all times.
The question for round three
will now be revealed.
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 5, 8
Two, five, and eight.
Eight seems the easiest, is it not?
I'd go for eight first.
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 5, 8
It was really nerve-racking.
My target number is eight.
The combination is 1, 2, and 7.
Your combination is 1, 2, and 7.
TARGET NUMBER: 8
COMBINATION: 1, 2, 7
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBER: 8
That is correct.
She was doing great,
so I was confident we'd win.
I reminded myself to focus.
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 5
Park Na-yoon from Team Yonsei.
My target number is two.
The combination is 3, 14, and 15.
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBER: 2
That is correct.
So they're tied at 4 to 4?
Whoever scores next will win this round.
TEAM KAIST: 4
TEAM YONSEI: 4
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 3
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBER: 5
I couldn't find it.
You both rang your bells
almost at the same time.
I knew the answer,
so I was anxious
she might get to answer first.
I was nervous she'd get to go first
because that meant she'd win this round.
Choi Seo-yeon from Team KAIST.
- My target number is five.
- Okay.
The combination is 4, 6, and 11.
TARGET NUMBER: 5
COMBINATION: 4, 6, 11
ROUND 3
TARGET NUMBER: 5
That is correct.
It was intense, so I was glad when I won.
I felt really bad
for putting pressure on my teammates.
ROUND 3
TEAM KAIST: 5, TEAM YONSEI: 4
There are two rounds left.
It's so close.
- I know. They have two more rounds.
- Even I'm nervous.
We will now begin
the fourth round of Pixel Number.
You have to get at least one.
Okay.
I couldn't help
but feel the pressure to do well.
Keep your cool, okay?
I don't think I can do it.
You can do it.
I know that for a fact.
Players for the fourth round,
please step forward.
We were winning,
so I was determined to keep it that way.
I was set on bringing my team to victory.
The question for round four
will now be revealed.
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 4
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 3, 5
- I don't see it.
- Me neither.
I expected the questions to get harder.
It didn't seem easy to tackle.
I have the combination for five.
You get 5 with 4, 8, and 13.
TARGET NUMBER: 5
COMBINATION: 4, 8, 13
Ju-hyung needed to do well,
and to be honest, I was worried.
Son Ju-hyung from Team Yonsei.
My target number is five.
The combination is 4, 8, and 13.
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 5
That is correct.
I was off to a great start.
TEAM KAIST: 5
TEAM YONSEI: 5
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBERS: 2, 3
Yang Jun-hyuk from Team KAIST.
- My target number is two.
- Okay.
The combination is 1, 7, and 10.
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 2
That is correct.
Is the score 6 to 5?
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 4
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 3
I can't figure out
the combination for three.
That's crazy.
Hurry up.
Please...
I just couldn't figure out
the last target number.
I didn't know what to do.
- Yang Jun-hyuk?
- My target number...
- My target number is three.
The combination is 3, 9, 11, and 15.
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 3
That is incorrect.
This can't be happening.
Damn it, the time.
Son Ju-hyung will be given
ten seconds to provide an answer.
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 3
- Son Ju-hyung.
- My target number is three.
The combination is 2, 6, 11, and 15.
Your combination is 2, 6, 11, and 15.
ROUND 4
TARGET NUMBER: 3
That is correct.
TEAM KAIST: 6
TEAM YONSEI: 6
That is correct.
We can use four cards?
- It's 6 to 6.
- It's so close.
This is so fun!
That concludes
the fourth round of Pixel Number.
ROUND 4
TEAM KAIST: 6, TEAM YONSEI: 6
We will now begin
the fifth round of Pixel Number.
You will be given one hidden number.
This hidden number is worth three points.
We have to get it.
Just focus on the hidden number.
Okay.
- The other two don't matter.
- That's right.
ROUND 4
TEAM KAIST: 6, TEAM YONSEI: 6
THE TEAM THAT FINDS
THE HIDDEN NUMBER WINS THE DEATHMATCH
Players for the fifth round,
please step forward.
WHO ARE THE LAST CONTESTANTS?
Do you want to go, or shall I?
AFTER ROUND 4
You should do it.
I'm not good at this.
I want you to play.
- We're not as fast as you.
- You're faster than us.
You're the only one who can do this.
I'll do it then.
Guys, must I play?
Either Seo-yeon or you should play.
But to be honest, you're better than me.
You're better than me.
I'm not sure.
Relax. You'll do fine.
I just needed to find the hidden number,
and I was confident I would.
When I saw Hyun-jun,
I knew it wouldn't be an easy match.
But I was set on finding
the last number and winning the match.
It's all about the energy.
You need nerves of steel.
I was sure I'd win.
I felt confident that I'd win this round.
If I'd made a two-point headway...
It's fine. Don't beat yourself up.
The question for round five
will now be revealed.
PIXEL NUMBER: ROUND 5
ROUND 5
TARGET NUMBERS: 0, 6, ?
I knew I just had to find
the hidden number to win this round.
My ears are quite sensitive,
so I covered them up to focus.
But the combinations wouldn't work.
Cho Hyun-jun from Team Yonsei.
The hidden number is eight.
The hidden number is 8.
The combination is 1, 4, and 9.
You named eight as the hidden number.
And your combination is 1, 4, and 9.
TARGET NUMBER: 8
COMBINATION: 1, 4, 9
That is correct.
How did he get that?
- Great job.
- Good game.
Team Yonsei scored nine points,
and Team KAIST scored six points.
Congratulations.
The victory goes to Team Yonsei.
TEAM YONSEI WINS THE DEATHMATCH
I had targeted the number eight
from the beginning.
The number eight
has the most number of pixels,
so I thought it was highly likely
to be the hidden number.
WHEN THE QUESTION FOR ROUND 5 WAS REVEALED
If eight wasn't included
in the target numbers,
the quickest solution would be
to find the combination for eight.
The hidden number is eight.
Frankly speaking,
I had no trouble finding the combination.
Do you have regrets?
What could we have done better?
I don't have any regrets.
It's just my first time
to fail at something.
I never imagined losing a game
that tested my intelligence.
The second team
to be eliminated from Elite League is
Team KAIST.
So this is it.
They're all very smart.
To be honest, I couldn't believe it.
We were competing against one another,
but it didn't feel great to see them go.
What?
It's still painful to watch
the second time around.
That breaks my heart.
I was embarrassed, and my ego was bruised.
It felt like it was all my fault.
I couldn't believe our journey had ended
and we were being sent home.
I never saw it coming.
It didn't feel like a survival show
until that point in time.
Team KAIST, please exit the grounds.
I know we lacked
in many aspects to represent KAIST,
but we did our best.
We could've done better,
so I'm quite bummed out.
And it's a shame
because we had more to show you.
Being with all these people
helped me realize
I still have a lot more to learn
and improve upon.
I wanted to show my fellow students
how capable KAIST students are,
so it's a shame I couldn't.
Our potential can't be measured
by this show alone.
We will keep moving forward
in our respective fields,
so I would really appreciate it
if you could cheer us on.
Are you sure we're being filmed?
- Great job, team.
- You all did great.
Brainpower survival challenge,
Elite League.
Today's main match is...
Please form alliances as you please.
- Let's go for Team Harvard.
- They're the best.
We have to find out
if the best option is SNU or Harvard.
Let's talk to Team Harvard.
Do you want to team up?
Are we left out again?
Why are you obsessed with Team Harvard?
We should consider
the worst-case scenario.
What's so amazing about Team Harvard?
We have to decide
which team to target today.
Team Harvard simply got lucky yesterday.
They didn't stand out at anything.
I honestly don't think
Team Yonsei's that good.
Who do we want to partner with?
We're not sure yet.
I think Team KU's going home.
We're in the worst position.
We have to win no matter what.
The pressure is too much.
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim