♫ Heaven is silent, all is quiet ♫
♫ Yourself in the mirror, can't see clearly in the fog ♫
♫ Floating across the galaxy, across the Netherworld,
injury and parting ♫
♫ Broken dreams are locked deep at the bottom of the sea ♫
♫ Fog and clouds disperse between heaven and earth ♫
♫ The rain washed the dust away, who is waiting for me ♫
♫ Our fated love can light up the starry sea of time ♫
♫ I come alone to look for you step by step ♫
♫ Getting into my blood through every breath ♫
♫ Love is reborn on its own ♫
♫ I fall towards you ♫
♫ Word for word, you're as bright as a flower ♫
♫ The grief is so vast ♫
♫ The fish leaped and broke out of the cold water ♫
♫ Imagine us enjoying the moonlight at the end of the world ♫
♫ A grain of sand growing out of everything ♫
♫ A teardrop falling into the sky... ♫
[The Blue Whisper II]
[Episode 20]
Maybe I deserve to survive.
If I hadn't been at rest for so long, you wouldn't have let down your guard.
You can't kill me easily.
Don't forget. I've got a secret weapon.
What's going on?
She cannot harm the North Abyss.
You shouldn't have that power.
The Bodhi fruit reforged my meridians. My tail is back.
Now my power is back.
Shunde, give up.
Don't you look down upon me.
A tail won't change a thing.
That's not as powerful as the evil thoughts of the entire world.
Wake up.
Come on, wake up. Wake up!
Clear your mind! We must stop the fight!
Chengyu!
Luo Luo! Luo Luo.
Kong Ming, I... I'm not a burden this time, am I?
You promised me to stay at home and wait for me.
Why did you run out?
I was going to save Yunhe.
But you're so stupid.
So I came to help you.
This time...
don't you... don't you say I'm useless.
I won't. I won't, Luo Luo.
I will never... I will never blame you. I could never...
Don't talk. Hang on.
Kong Ming.
I just realize that...
you're more important to me than the spirit stones.
Luo Luo.
Luo Luo!
Luo Luo, stay with me.
Don't fall asleep.
I can give you as many spirit stones as you want.
I'll give you whatever you ask for. Luo Luo.
Once we live through this battle, let's get married, shall we?
Marry me.
Luo Luo!
No.
Chengyu!
All right. This is all over now.
Wake up!
Come on! Brother!
Master Donglian.
Xiaoxing!
Thankfully. You are sober now!
Where's Master?
Did Shunde capture him, too?
Is Lin here?
Do you think the Golden Bell is all I have?
That bell is only for the ordinary puppets.
I cast it with my power. It's indestructible!
A perfect match for Lin Haoqing.
Senior!
Chang Yi, Heavenly King is in danger.
Go ahead. I'll take care of her.
Senior! Stop!
Be careful, Guardian Ji.
Don't be distracted. I'll handle him.
Senior, wake up!
Senior...
Yunhe, listen to me.
I'm trapped in this game.
It's beyond my control.
I don't deserve to love someone.
If I can use my power
in exchange for the freedom of the girl I love,
I will consider it my final wish.
Don't worry, Yunhe.
I'm by your side.
Don't worry, Yunhe. I'm by your side.
From now on, you can call me Brother Haoqing.
What will you pay to protect someone you love?
Everything.
What if they misunderstand you and hate you for betraying them?
I will pay the price if I can keep him safe.
You're A'Ji.
Ji as in memory.
Master!
Senior!
Chang Yi.
I can't believe you're killing me for those pests.
Ungrateful brat! We're family!
You don't deserve the throne!
All right.
Hard as you may try,
I won't let you win easily.
I still have my cultivation!
It will preserve my spirit.
I will turn into the wind and kill everyone I meet.
The entire world shall be buried with me.
I will chain you up, even if you turn into the wind.
I will stop you with my life!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Chang Yi.
I have to do this.
With the light of the Glazed Lantern,
I can draw the Heavenly and Earthly Fire which burns all evils.
As long as the lantern is lit, there is hope.
Long live justice.
Ji Yunhe, I'm right inside you.
If you seal me, you'll stay there with me, too.
Can you abandon the merman?
Yunhe, burning the demon with Heavenly and Earthly Fire. You'll sacrifice yourself again!
But Shunde hasn't given up.
We'll never see peace if she's alive.
You don't want her to intrude on the world, do you?
I'll go with you.
Chang Yi, when I jump into the lava,
Shunde will try to escape for sure.
By that time, I'll need a helper to seal the volcano
with the power of the Scepter of Merman Clan and stop her.
You must stop the eruption, too.
It has to be you.
You are asking me to seal you with my own hands.
I know it's hard.
But I trust you the most.
You yearn for freedom.
You cannot be imprisoned in this dark place.
I'll go for you.
I used to dream about freedom.
That's because I'm indifferent to everything.
After seeing you,
the North Abyss, and what we've gone through,
I've changed my mind.
They're all a part of me.
Chang Yi, this is my choice.
Don't worry.
I have faith in the lantern. It will protect me.
I will be fine.
Once the demon perishes,
I will find my way back.
We shall be honest with each other.
Whatever obstacle there will be,
we shall face it together.
Okay?
Okay.
I need your promise.
♫ Hey, if I weren't me and you weren't you ♫
♫ Hey, think more... think more ♫
♫ Hey, where are you going? ♫
♫ Any fool looking up can't keep the light ♫
♫ Hey, just follow the flow ♫
Take it.
And you'll know I'm always your Big-tailed Fish.
I will wait for you.
No matter how long it is,
a merman sticks to his spouse all his life.
I promise.
Whenever it is, wherever I am,
I will find my way back.
I will always end up by your side.
This time, don't be trapped in the North Abyss for me.
Take a tour.
See what the world is like.
See if there's any delicious food and beautiful sights.
Make some preparations.
Show me the best of the world once we reunite.
All right?
Okay.
I promise.
♫ I hope you're like the moonlight ♫
♫ Having no pain or wounds ♫
♫ With a pair of white wings, no more frost ♫
♫ No more hiding yourself ♫
♫ May you never fall into the net ♫
♫ Enjoying the sunrise and moonset♫
♫ Engraving time into the palm of your hand♫
♫ Let good dreams nourish you♫
♫ Say goodbye to the long dark night♫
♫ The flowers here are blooming once again ♫
♫ As bright as you are, in the blink of an eye, tens of thousands
of light years have passed ♫
♫ Have you ever seen this world as you thought it would be? ♫
- We're free!
- It's all over now!
Li Shu, this is the end.
Can you see this?
Are you sure you want to leave me behind?
Would that be costly?
Luo Luo.
Luo Luo! You're alive!
The wedding ceremony, would that be expensive?
How many...
how many spirit stones would it cost?
Whatever it takes.
Whatever it takes!
Out comes the sun.
Is this the end of the chaos?
I finally understand it.
The million soldiers Father left me
are not some mysterious troops waiting to be summoned somewhere.
It refers to every righteous guardian in the world.
Each one of you is a part of it.
- It's just...
- I didn't expect
that Yunhe would sacrifice herself.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
That's how she is.
No one can change her mind once she makes the decision.
Likewise, she will keep her promise.
How long will it take for the devil to perish?
It depends on how strong her mind is.
Maybe 100 years, 1,000 years. Maybe even tens of thousands of years.
I get it.
Heavenly King, please reopen the east sea and take care of Thousand Flower Valley.
As for North Abyss,
I believe Qing Yao will make it thrive again.
Are you... resigning from the position of master?
She deserves the title more than I do.
Home is where your heart is.
Looks like North Abyss isn't your home.
[300 years later]
Immortal Master.
- Immortal Master.
- Keep your voice down, Luo Luo.
Immortal Master is discussing with Heavenly King. They don't want any intruders.
But I'm not an intruder.
After you.
Luo Luo!
What are you doing here?
Your Majesty, glad to see you.
Please judge for us.
Ever since he became Immortal Master, I can hardly see him.
After our wedding day, it's been a long time since the last time we practiced.
That's not how a couple works.
This isn't the right time.
Well. Now that Ms. Luo is here, I should get going.
Hold on. I'm waiting for your gift.
Gift?
What gift?
Are you hungry?
All right, it's time to eat.
It's the baby.
Are you saying...
You'll be a father.
I'll be a father!
Luo Luo!
Great! I'm a father!
Is this the right time?
It is! Always!
Master.
Have you heard about Luo Jinsang's pregnancy?
Prepare a gift for me.
Once I finish the business here, I'll set off to congratulate them.
Yes, Master.
Master, as busy as Kong Ming is, he's got a baby.
Shouldn't you think about having a spouse?
We've received so many proposal letters.
You didn't even open one.
Come on.
Is love the only thing you pursue?
Look around.
Isn't it lovely that North Abyss is peaceful and lively?
It's been so long.
You're still bothered by Fairy Shunde.
I know that my sister committed a severe crime.
Still, she took care of me and raised me up.
Now, she's dispersed.
But I'm still thinking of her.
Master, am I being too weak?
Everyone has his or her life.
It's destiny.
No need to hold a grudge.
But you don't have to forget it.
Sometimes, reflection can light up our way ahead.
Master, you look delighted today.
Any good news?
I heard that Fei Lian and Lei Ze have come to life again.
It makes me happy.
Great. I'm heading to Thousand Flower Valley.
I should tell Commander Xue about it.
If only Prince Li Shu were still alive.
Li Shu is an heir of Lu Wu.
He has nine lives.
He escaped from death many times.
Maybe he'd make it again this time.
On my way here, I came across the Immortal of Marriage.
He told me...
What did he say?
Come on, tell me.
Forget about it.
It's a secret.
A surprise is better left unsaid for lovers.
Don't you think?
There you are again.
You must be hungry.
I've prepared you dried fish.
Where are you going?
You forgot your fish.
Naughty you.
There you are!
You seem overly active today.
Bright fur, smooth figure.
You take care of your spirit pet well.
Who is it?
I'm new here as a mortal disciple.
I lost my way and got here by accident.
You must be a disciple here, too.
I heard that among all the masters here,
Commander Xue is the most powerful one.
I have always admired her.
Do you know about her habits?
Would you like to tell me about them?
I'd like to cheer her up.
I shall pay you a formal reward if she could meet me.
♫ We bloomed like a flower ♫
Excuse me. Why are you crying?
I like the way you smile. Special.
♫ We once met like a song in the sounds of nature ♫
♫ What is left blank is my love confession ♫
Master, Commander Xue has met him.
The time I saw his profile, I knew this was destiny.
Assign him to Sanyue.
He is a mortal with little spiritual power.
But he's innocent and smart.
It's good for him.
Yes, Master. You barely escaped from the fall.
Still, you're badly wounded.
You need rest.
They can renew their bond.
Aren't you happy for them?
They can have a happy ending. I am happy for them.
But you've lost too much.
Your legs...
I'm concerned about you.
Nothing is perfect in this miserable world.
Thousand Flower Valley is intact.
So are you.
That's enough.
What about you?
Me?
I'm good.
Although I'm a cripple now, I'm free.
I can follow my heart.
More importantly, I can face myself.
You should be happy for me.
Yunhe and Chang Yi, any news about them?
Nothing from the volcano.
Chang Yi has been silent since he went to the human realm.
Do you want me to look for his trail?
Forget it. Let it be.
I trust in Yunhe.
She will keep her promise.
It's sunny outside. Let's take a walk.
Sure.
☙❧
Many thanks to our Channel Manager:
nicoletak
☙❧
Many thanks to our Chief Editor:
kakashiandme
☙❧
Many thanks to our Chief Segmenter:
bjohnsonwong
☙❧
Many thanks to our segmenters:
hana_860, nmelova, porkypine90_261, sabrinafair, baepsae29, bepina, phoebe171_915, kitty100, and shastalime.
☙❧
Many thanks to our Other Languages Moderators, Editors and Subbers.
Many thanks to our viewers for watching and loving this amazing drama ♥!
The sky lantern carries wishes.
Shall we try it?
Chang Yi, what's your wish?
I wish that your dream comes true.
What's yours?
That's not how it works! That's a loss.
All right. I'll make one for us.
I wish that in the next life, we can be free from the titles of Master or Guardian.
May we be an ordinary couple, living in a warm place.
We can enjoy cherry blossoms in spring,
starry nights in summer,
the full moon in autumn,
and the first snow in winter.
Stay together over the four seasons.
Exactly. The four seasons, all year round.
Stay by your side and never depart.
♫ My heart leaves a projection ♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ My leap reflects the mountaintop ♫
♫ From the sun, the moon to the dust ♫
♫ I just want to come and go with love ♫
Yunhe, you're like a flower blooming in my heart.
All the things we did, they are full of love.
We dreamed about freedom.
We fled holding hands.
We had misunderstandings.
No matter how, we will meet again.
You have my mark.
I lost you, many, many times.
And I waited for you, day after day.
I believe that one day, we will stay side by side.
Chang Yi, think about it. Our story is like a fairy tale.
In the fairy tale, it's a dreamy world, but it looks so real.
How I wish that all the blessings can act like the breeze,
casting away the mist, and bringing happiness to the world.
By the way, how is your tail?
Just like the day we first met.
It's just... you haven't seen it.
I always find it weird.
Why are you so pure and innocent?
But now, I've witnessed the sea. Everything seems small in the vast ocean.
Obstacles are like sprinkles, they're just temporary.
No need to worry about them.
In this wide world, we live by each other.
Yunhe, this time, we shall never depart.
Chang Yi, now that you've got your tail back,
shall we have a race to see who swims faster?
♫ For the rest of our life, I'll travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ to write an end that will last forever ♫
♫ We won't be afraid or separate ♫
♫ I'll be with you forever ♫
♫ You gave me freedom by loving you ♫
♫ I get the meaning of life when I'm falling ♫
♫ I don't care whether I live or die ♫
♫ Hey, if I weren't me and you weren't you ♫
♫ Hey, think more... think more ♫
♫ Hey, where are you going? ♫
♫ Any fool looking up can't keep the light ♫
♫ Hey, just follow the flow ♫
♫ I hope your wishes will come true and you go
to a bright place ♫
♫ Away from me, away from sadness ♫
♫ From now on, there will be no lies, forget the mundane world ♫
♫ Let regret not grow ♫
♫ From now on, you don't have to be scared of anything ♫
♫ Wanting and lacking nothing ♫
♫ Like fireflies pursuing waves ♫
♫ The uncatchable light ♫
♫ is left for one person to recall ♫
♫ The wind blows causing the flower petals to fall ♫
♫ Sand is washed away by the rain ♫
♫ I think you are someplace else, singing happily ♫
♫ Never again recalling anything about me ♫
♫ The flowers here are blooming once again ♫
♫ As bright as you are, in the blink of an eye, tens of thousands
of light years have passed ♫
♫ Have you ever seen this world as you thought it would be? ♫