♫ Heaven is silent, all is quiet ♫
♫ Yourself in the mirror, can't see clearly in the fog ♫
♫ Floating across the galaxy, across the Netherworld,
injury and parting ♫
♫ Broken dreams are locked deep at the bottom of the sea ♫
♫ Fog and clouds disperse between heaven and earth ♫
♫ The rain washed the dust away, who is waiting for me ♫
♫ Our fated love can light up the starry sea of time ♫
♫ I come alone to look for you step by step ♫
♫ Getting into my blood through every breath ♫
♫ Love is reborn on its own ♫
♫ I fall towards you ♫
♫ Word for word, you're as bright as a flower ♫
♫ The grief is so vast ♫
♫ The fish leaped and broke out of the cold water ♫
♫ Imagine us enjoying the moonlight at the end of the world ♫
♫ A grain of sand growing out of everything ♫
♫ A teardrop falling into the sky... ♫
[The Blue Whisper II]
[Episode 15]
From now on, I won't force you to do anything.
As long as you're happy, you can do anything.
I can't get paid for what I didn't do.
I didn't help much.
Is there any reason for you to be so nice to me all of a sudden?
The snow here is really beautiful.
What kind of reason is it?
This merman is unpredictable.
I can't stay with him for too long.
Are you sure that I can do anything?
Yes. No more restrictions, it's all up to you.
Then let me play a round in the North Abyss.
After I'm done, I'll let my master take me back.
Didn't you just say I could do anything, are you backtracking so quickly?
Are you so reluctant to stay here?
Then I'll say it straight.
I'm afraid you'll lock me up again.
It's a nice place and you're handsome,
but I haven't seen enough of this world,
so I don't want to be stuck here
looking at your face for the rest of my life.
Let's go back today.
Let's discuss this later.
Then I'll go back to Ape Wing Camp.
Anyway, my leg is better.
There is no need to stay in your place.
Okay.
Let's go.
The antidote has finally been made.
I have finally made it.
Master, the medicine is unpredictable.
Do you really want to test it yourself?
Whether it is medicine or poison,
I'm going to try it all out.
Master. Master!
Master, you've done it.
You've done it.
Has the Frost been detoxified?
Father, I finally detoxified the Frost.
I've finally…
Master, what's wrong?
How are you?
Master.
No need to wear yourself out.
The Frost has been detoxified,
why is it growing back?
Master, a fox named A'Ji appeared in the North Abyss,
and behaves like Yunhe.
Now she is staying with Chang Yi.
I don't know if she is related to Yunhe.
This is God's will.
General, we caught a dying fox.
General Qifeng?
What a surprise.
How did you end up like this?
Well, before I destroy the North Abyss,
let me take your life to sharpen my sword.
Don't kill me.
Report!
General, it's hard to find the Thunderfire Vein.
There's been no message from anyone sent.
What are you telling me if you haven't found it?
Do you want me to praise you?
Go and find it!
Yes, Sir!
I'm very unhappy now. You're unlucky.
Don't kill me. Stop!
I'm useful to you.
You're the trash that North Abyss has given up on, what use are you to me?
Aren't you looking for the Thunderfire Vein?
No one is more familiar with the terrain of the North Abyss than I am.
I can definitely help you find it.
You are really ruthless, even abandoning your kin.
I will destroy that merman.
I'll let Qing Yao know that I'm the right one.
Great.
It's a nice place
and you're handsome,
but I haven't seen enough of this world,
so I don't want to be stuck here
looking at your face for the rest of my life.
I heard that since you got back from Ice Lake,
you've been held up.
Your old friend has returned,
why are you still here drinking?
Sir, she wants to get out of here.
If you want to keep her,
it's certainly not a difficult task for you.
I don't want to trap her anymore.
I want to let her follow her heart.
So this time, she chose to be free
and let go of you.
We are no longer the former Spiritual Master and merman.
Now I bear not only my own love and hatred,
but also the lives of more people.
I don't want to trap her with this responsibility.
But I really can't accept that...
she is leaving here.
Everything in this world is not perfect.
If you don't know how to choose,
you just have to think about the war coming
and what kind of future you most want her to have in your heart.
War?
There is a letter from Xue Sanyue.
The truth behind Immortal Master
has been found by Heavenly King.
So A'Ji really is…
She is Yunhe. It's complicated. No need to say more.
Where is she now?
Why did the merman look so lonely
when he heard that I was leaving?
It's not all determined.
Didn't I make up my mind to leave?
Why do I feel so sad when I see his eyes?
Master?
I'm a little tired today.
If you don't want me to leave,
then I can leave a few days later.
Master.
Master! Master!
- Who let you come to the North Abyss?
- Hurt. It hurts.
Why didn't you listen to me?
Actually, I just saved someone on the way.
Unexpectedly, I was taken as an accomplice of Immortal Master Mansion's disciples
and was captured together to the North Abyss.
Did I do something wrong?
You're right.
You're the kindest kid.
Leave it to me to save people.
I'll take you away now.
Leaving so soon?
Actually, I'm staying quite well in the North Abyss.
Why don't we stay a little longer?
A'Ji, after a few days in the North Abyss, you are willing to disobey our master?
Master, I saw the merman in my dream.
What did he say to you?
He didn't say anything,
but sometimes he was cold.
Sometimes he was very strange and was very nice to me.
How did you feel about it?
I can't tell you how I feel.
When I see him, I will feel strange;
and sometimes, my heart will beat fast.
Master, is he really my enemy?
What did I tell you?
You told me not to look back.
And if you forget the past,
then don't think about it again.
Leave with me.
Master, when we came to the North Abyss this time,
the guards were already alerted.
I'm afraid Chang Yi won't let us go easily.
I won't let him stop us.
The power behind the Immortal Master
turns out to be the ancient fierce beast Zhu Yan.
Yes.
Now, Heavenly King is trapped in Infinite Mountain.
I'm afraid that Immortal Master will take action soon.
This war is inevitable.
Chang Yi, this time,
what will you do with A'Ji?
Your Master, someone at the border found Lin Haoqing's whereabouts.
He has sneaked into the North Abyss again.
- I think he's here for A'Ji.
- Where is he?
He knocked out the guards and took someone from Ape Wing Camp
to the back of the mountain.
When did the North Abyss start to vibrate underground?
The Thunderfire Vein has been revived.
Then the power of the mountains and rivers will drive the operation of the formation
until the last drop of lava is forced out.
This place will be surrounded by fire soon.
Merman, I'd like to see
how you're going to save North Abyss this time.
He will only die, and so will you.
With the merman and the entire North Abyss buried with you,
I think you can die with no regrets.
Let's go.
Except for the Spiritual Master that Immortal Fairy wants,
kill all the creatures of North Abyss by fire.
A trick to lure me away.
Chang Yi, we are at least old friends.
Please don't fight.
Immortal Master will tackle the North Abyss one day.
A'Ji, no...
If Ji Yunhe stays here, you can't guarantee her safety.
Besides, according to her nature, if something really happens to North Abyss,
do you think she would stay out of it?
Don't you feel that
the bottom seems to be getting hotter and hotter,
and there is a strange smell.
There is a change underground.
Chang Yi, it's the Thunderfire Vein.
After you left, Lingshuang Pavilion shook.
The earth quakes and the birds are scared.
It's the sign of the rekindling of the Thunderfire Vein.
Thunderfire Vein.
Hasn't it been dormant for millions of years?
How could it suddenly rekindle?
It's the Immortal Master.
He took action first.
What will happen next?
The earth will crack, avalanches will happen, and the rivers will boil.
Until lava erupts, the earth will burn, and everything will turn into ash.
Kong Ming, go back now.
Together with Qing Yao and Luo Jingsang, take the time to evacuate everyone.
Are you going to suppress the fire alone?
Chang Yi, are you crazy?
How can you fight against the power of the mountains and rivers?
The lava is coming from the ground.
I have to suppress the veins from the root.
Suppress the veins from the root.
Are you going to the cave of the veins?
No. The lava is on fire,
so the ground is worse than hell.
You'll turn into ash.
I have the Water Scepter of East Sea. I may be able to fight.
Kong Ming, you know what is important.
- Chang Yi.
- Go!
Just go!
The Spiritual Masters in the city need to be transferred now,
should we call Master and A'Ji back to help?
No need. Tell Lin Haoqing to take her out of here,
as far away as possible.
Soon, there may be a big war in North Abyss.
Let her never come back.
A'Ji, leaving this forest,
we'll be out of the North Abyss.
What's wrong, A'Ji?
Master, I don't know what's wrong with me.
I should listen to you.
But when I think of leaving here,
my heart hurts like it's being cut.
What happened between me and North Abyss, and the merman?
Master, is something wrong?
Master, Immortal Master ignited Thunderfire Vein.
- The lava is about to erupt.
- Lava is about to erupt?
Isn't North Abyss City just down the hill?
Ji Ning, Lu Jinyan, Fu Chao,
and there are so many other people.
So, will they all be burned into ash?
Your Master, Chang Yi said he will go into the cave to suppress the fire, and asked you to take A'Ji away.
What does the merman want to do?
He is trying to use his own power to fight against the catastrophe.
Even though he is good at controlling water, there is a limit.
He is ready to die.
A'Ji, what are you doing?
Master, are you going to do nothing to save him?
A'Ji, if you go back now,
the past will be in vain.
You asked me what your relationship with the merman was.
I'm telling you now.
You had a painful past.
You went through the worst time of your life.
It took a long time for you to regain your freedom.
A'Ji, leave the North Abyss with me,
then you can roam all over the world without any restraint.
Master, you said that
one day, I would find where I want to go,
and what I want to do.
Now I found it.
I don't want to see the North Abyss burned.
I don't want to see those fresh lives in the city disappear.
I… I also don't want to see the merman in trouble.
No matter what happened between us,
it doesn't matter at this moment.
I just want to go back to save people.
Master Lin.
I didn't expect that you would retreat to Thousand Flower Valley
for the sake of the beauty…
Old friend.
Why did he come to the North Abyss?
You are so cunning
that you hid her from the Immortal Fairy for so long.
Master, who is he?
Stop pretending. When I take you back to Immortal Master Mansion,
the whip of Immortal Fairy will remind you of everything.
Catch them!
A'Ji, go do what you want to do.
- Master.
- Go!
The Frost mark in your body has taken effect, and you are seeking death.
That's enough to fight with you.
Now that you know who A'Ji is,
you won't leave alive.
- Chang Yi!
- Young Lord!
Young Lord!
Lava is about to erupt. It's too dangerous here.
Since Master asked you to leave with the people, then don't go in there.
But Chang Yi is in there. I have to get him out.
The cave is like hell.
If you go in now, you won't be able to get out.
Do you want me to watch him die?
Young Lord, if you go in now, you'll only die with Master.
Don't you care about your kin and North Abyss?
That was Ji Yunhe.
She's back.
Are you stupid?
How can you do this alone?
Why are you back? Don't you know how dangerous it is here?
Leave!
No. This is not your North Abyss alone.
I have friends here, too.
And… And you can't die.
To sacrifice my life for the peace of the North Abyss,
it's worth it.
Leave!
♫ Heaven is silent, all is quiet ♫
♫ Yourself in the mirror, can't see clearly in the fog ♫
♫ Floating across the galaxy, across the Netherworld,
injury and parting ♫
Guardian of Thousand Flower Valley, Ji Yunhe.
- Ji Yunhe.
Yunhe.
♫ Broken dreams are locked deep at the bottom of the sea ♫
Big-tailed Fish,
I like you.
May the rest of my beloved's life be peaceful and happy.
The soul of a Spiritual Master is free forever.
- Your name is A'Ji.
- Master.
You have not told me the answer, and I have not forgiven you.
Big-tailed Fish.
I don't allow you to die.
Forget me and relieve yourself.
♫ Love is reborn on its own ♫
Go now, Yunhe!
♫ I fall towards you ♫
♫ Word for word, you're as bright as a flower ♫
♫ The grief is so vast ♫
♫ The fish leaped and broke out of the cold water ♫
♫ Imagine us enjoying the moonlight at the end of the world ♫
Big-tailed Fish, I'm coming.
♫ A grain of sand growing out of everything ♫
♫ A teardrop falling into the sky... ♫
♫ Four seasons of the rest of my life ♫
♫ For the rest of our life, I'll travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ to write an end that will last forever ♫
♫ We won't be afraid or separate, I'll be with you forever ♫
♫ We shall be together forever, we'll be together ♫
♫ You gave me freedom by loving you ♫
♫ I get the meaning of life when I'm falling ♫
♫ I don't care whether I live or die ♫
♫ I became fireworks and burn everything ♫
♫ I'm worthy of my life ♫
♫ For the rest of our life, I'll travel everywhere with you ♫
♫ to write an end that will last forever ♫
♫ We won't be afraid or separate ♫
♫ I'll be with you forever ♫
♫ We shall be together forever, we'll be together ♫
♫ You gave me freedom by loving you ♫
♫ I get the meaning of life when I'm falling ♫
♫ I don't care whether I live or die ♫
♫ I became fireworks and burn everything ♫
♫ I'm worthy of my life ♫
Yunhe.
I accidentally used too much power.
Don't talk.
Big-tailed Fish...
Don't frown.
It's so hard to reunite, I want to take a closer look at you.
When I was Ji Yunhe, I wanted to forget everything.
But when I became A'Ji, I forgot everything except you.
Big-tailed Fish, I can't bear to part with you.
Yunhe.
Yunhe! Yunhe!
This time, I will protect you.
It stopped. It stopped. It stopped.
- The fire has stopped.
- Look.
- The fire stopped.
We survived.
North Abyss is safe now.
North Abyss is all right.
Our home is saved.
North Abyss is saved!
Saved!
Master, the fire is out.
That merman put out the fire.
Master, you've used up too much of your spiritual energy to resist the Frost.
Your body is important.
Take me to see if A'Ji is safe.
- Chang Yi!
- Master!
Where's Chang Yi? Where's Chang Yi?
He went inside and didn't come out.
Master!
Master, come out! Don't scare me, Master!
Impossible.
Chang Yi is so powerful, he couldn't die so easily.
- Let me have a look.
- Luo Luo.
Danger!
Chang Yi.
Master.
Yunhe.
Master, they are safe.
I used to think that since it was a new life,
she should cut off the past and never look back.
But it turns out that some things are destined to be together.
She still went back.
What? The fire was subsided.
Where is Zhu Ling? Didn't he catch any Spiritual Masters?
We only know that the fire in North Abyss has been subsided.
But we can no longer contact General Zhu Ling.
I'm afraid…
I'm afraid he's already dead.
Rubbish.
You're all rubbish.
What can you do for me?
Ru Ling, time to take your medicine.
I heard that the fire in North Abyss was put out by that merman.
I know.
You promised to make me stronger.
Not a single Spiritual Master has been caught yet.
What should I do?
As long as you want, I'll help you catch them.
Put on your shoes and socks.
Don't let the cold hurt your body,
or it'll affect the medicine's effects.
Just a few last steps, then your face will be the same as before.
The same as before.
Then get some preserves for me.
The medicine is bitter.
Your spiritual power is pure.
If you can help me, can my power grow faster?
Master, what I want is not only the past.
Please help me.
You want so much.
But don't forget that you don't have that ability.
You should drink the medicine.
Until now, you still want to cure my face.
I dared to fight against you
and take away your spiritual power,
why don't you kill me?
You know it.
Because of this face, right?
You raised me, taught me,
and brought me all the way to this point.
I've betrayed you. Why don't you kill me?
Do you love this face so much?
What am I but this face?
Ru Ling.
I'd rather you kill me than spare me because of this face.
Why don't you kill me?
Don't do anything stupid.
Master, you can't give me what I want.
And you can't get what you want.
[Immortal Fairy Hall]
Don't make trouble for yourself.
Stop.
Even just for yourself.
Are you taking pity on me?
When is it your turn to pity me?
Who are you to persuade me now?
You know all the things that our master has done.
Senior, you were a part of it too.
Don't you think it's too late to regret now?
Yes.
We're both guilty and can't even pay for it with death.
I will bear the consequences of the evils I have done.
I just want to beg you,
don't push everyone and yourself into the abyss of doom.
The fairy I once knew was a good person.
Unfortunately, we both went further down the road of sin.
Now I hope that...
we still have the chance to atone for our sins.
Sin?
What is my sin?
I'm the noblest fairy.
Everything is with my blessings.
All of you should respect and thank me.
You wait.
When I am powerful enough,
whatever I do, Master will follow my wishes.
No, not only Master,
but everyone!
You've just used so much spiritual power, how dare you cast spells without a good rest?
Sir, Yunhe is…
Wait outside. I'll heal her.
One more word, I'll drug you and kick you out of here.
Sir, how is Yunhe?
Her heart veins were burned by the earth fire.
Although I stabilized her injury just now, it's difficult for her to wake up soon.
If I seclude and heal her with my water control spell,
maybe I can relieve her of heat poison.
Chang Yi, you've just over-exerted yourself in the cave,
now you're going to take great pains to heal her.
Do you want to seek death?
In the cave, I was ready to perish.
But she risked her life to come back to me,
which means that we are not over.
Since we're not over, why don't I try my best?
But during my seclusion,
the North Abyss needs you to take charge.
If you want, just go ahead.
I can take care of the North Abyss.
But remember, if you need help, you must tell me.
Don't fight alone.
I thought you would stop me again.
Can I stop you?
Besides, I and the North Abyss owe Ji Yunhe.
Don't worry. While you're in seclusion,
I'll do my best to help him.
Besides, here are some tonic medicines that may help A'Ji's recovery.
Thank you, Young Lord.
Young Lord, your attitude towards Ji Yunhe
seems to have changed greatly, too.
In the past, I did have various prejudices against her.
But this time Master was in trouble, at the moment of dying,
she didn't hesitate to save him at all.
I can't help but admire the chivalry.
Besides, Master loves her.
Such a couple should be blessed by all.
But I stopped at the door of the cave at the last moment,
unable to enter and fight the fire with Master.
Young Lord, you don't have to feel guilty.
You just prioritized the future of the North Abyss first
and did what you had to do.
Sometimes, it takes more courage to make such decisions.
If the Fox King were still alive, he would be very happy that you had finally grown up.
Thank you.
Your Master.
Someone wants to see you.
Just say it.
You're usually so talkative, why are you stammering today?
Who makes you like this?
I…
I know it.
Take him to the main hall.
Yes.
How is A'Ji?
Now she is Yunhe.
Her memories came back.
Kong Ming has stabilized her injury.
Next, I will heal her.
I didn't expect you'd agree to see me.
I thought after I took A'Ji— Yunhe away,
you would hate me to the bone.
After all, it was you who saved Yunhe.
And I also heard that Zhu Ling was going to invade the North Abyss to slaughter during the chaos,
but it was you who stopped him.
Not to help you, just being forced by the situation.
Grace is grace.
We in the North Abyss have always been clear about grudges and grievances,
so I will definitely repay you for this.
But you still won't let me take her away, right?
Don't worry. I'm just asking.
From the moment she chose to turn back and fight with you against the fire, I understood.
Even if she loses her memory, she is still Ji Yunhe deep in her heart.
I still can't keep her.
I received a message from Xue Sanyue.
One of the things is related to the Frost mark.
Do you want to know the truth?
The body of Zhu Yan is eternal black ice.
Every Frost mark comes from him.
If Zhu Yan does not die, the frost will not disappear.
So the Frost is born from the body of Zhu Yan,
no wonder it can't be cured by medicine.
♫ Hey, if I weren't me and you weren't you ♫
♫ Hey, think more... think more ♫
♫ Hey, where are you going? ♫
♫ Any fool looking up can't keep the light ♫
♫ Hey, just follow the flow ♫
♫ I hope your wishes will come true and you go
to a bright place ♫
♫ Away from me, away from sadness ♫
♫ From now on, there will be no lies, forget the mundane world ♫
♫ Let regret not grow ♫
♫ From now on, you don't have to be scared of anything ♫
♫ Wanting and lacking nothing ♫
♫ Like fireflies pursuing waves ♫
♫ The uncatchable light ♫
♫ is left for one person to recall ♫
♫ The wind blows causing the flower petals to fall ♫
♫ Sand is washed away by the rain ♫
♫ I think you are someplace else, singing happily ♫
♫ Never again recalling anything about me ♫
♫ The flowers here are blooming once again ♫
♫ As bright as you are, in the blink of an eye, tens of thousands
of light years have passed ♫
♫ Have you ever seen this world as you thought it would be? ♫