♫ A gentle smile on lips disturbed the time-line ♫
♫ A thousand years passed in moonlight ♫
♫ In the corridor at the end of the world ♫
♫ I seem to see us there out of the corner of my eyes ♫
♫ We bloomed like a flower ♫
♫ Meeting by the river of time ♫
♫ We were at the same play stage ♫
♫ A step for thousands of miles ♫
♫ A glance at numerous colors ♫
♫ What is left blank is my love confession ♫
[The Blue Whisper]
[Episode 07]
Luo Luo, I found the antidote.
We got the antidote.
Antidote?
What antidote?
Xiaoxing, here.
Take these antidotes.
When the thing is settled, find an opportunity to escape out of the valley.
When we meet then, I'll tell you all about it.
Leave now.
Luo Luo, take this antidote and wait for me outside.
What about you?
Chang Yi is still in Reflect Cave.
I promised him to leave together. I can't go back on my word.
Again…
I'll stay with you. I can help you.
Luo Luo, the antidote and spirit stones have all been given to you.
You have to find a safe place to hide, so that I can rest assured.
- But…
- Luo Luo, be a good girl.
Then you must come back safely.
If you break your word, I'll kill my way back to take you away.
Master Qing.
Xue Sanyue, what are you waiting for?
You have Li Shu's elixir, kill him.
You're dead.
Ning Ruochu, you dared to trick me into the formation.
Why didn't you have the guts to wait for me to come out alive?
How dare you imitate him?
It's impossible to break the Ten Directions Formation overnight.
How long did it take you
to find the ten array eyes in Thousand Flower Valley?
Sanyue.
You approached me for her, right?
You gave up your life to save her,
and also gave me up.
You made me look like a joke.
Go to your Master Qing.
Father.
Are you okay, Sanyue?
Hold on.
Ten Directions Formation is almost completed.
Sorry, Sanyue.
Master Qing, take her away.
There's no fun in this place anymore.
The Ten Directions Formation is almost completed.
You can't leave.
What can a broken formation do to me?
Chase!
Yes.
Oh no. Lin Canglan probably restarted the formation.
Doesn't this place happen to be one of the array eyes of the formation?
Could Big-tailed Fish be so stupid to wait for me inside?
Chang Yi.
Danger.
Run!
Hurry up!
The barrier is broken, why didn't you run away?
You told me to wait for you here.
You stupid fish.
Xue and Blue Feather Phoenix.
Where is Li Shu?
Is he…
Let's go.
Chang Yi.
Ji Yunhe.
Chang Yi. Chang Yi.
Get up.
Chang Yi, why did you block that blow for me?
I didn't want you to get hurt.
Why can't I use spiritual power?
He is so badly injured that it should be cured in time.
I need to find some water so that he can warm up and heal.
Does the wound hurt?
Yes.
But it's good that you're fine.
What does this mean?
It's a special spell I learned from Earth...
that can make the injured person feel better.
A gentle touch can heal me?
Yes. A gentle touch can heal.
But I'm not healed now.
You will be healed.
What a long spell.
Chang Yi, I can't use my spiritual power here.
And I don't have anything with me to help you heal.
I'll go to look around.
Even just finding some water
to give you some strength will be fine.
You stay here until I get back
and don't move. Okay?
Yunhe, it's so foggy here.
I'm afraid you won't be able to come back.
Let me go with you.
Here.
You hold on to this end.
When I find water,
I can follow this thread back.
You know what?
Connected by a red thread,
a thousand-mile marriage can be tied together,
and we can grow old together, hand in hand.
As long as we are tied together,
we will not get lost.
So whether I can come back,
whether I can live to be old,
it's up to you.
What a big pool.
Not to mention healing Chang Yi,
even bathing is enough.
Master, Spiritual Masters chased the phoenix with all their might,
but she still escaped.
Should we report it to Immortal Master Mansion?
If they know that the phoenix escaped,
they will certainly blame us for being incompetent.
At that time,
no one in the valley will be able to escape punishment.
Send more people to capture her.
No one is allowed to reveal the escape of the Blue Feather Phoenix.
We should stay calm,
our master must have a method to turn things around.
Now, Master is in seclusion
and Fairy is in charge.
If we can successfully tame the merman,
Fairy will be happy,
then this matter can be subsided.
All right, go back.
Yes.
Master, the merman in the cave is gone,
and so is Ji Yunhe.
Master, are you not feeling well?
Did you get hurt?
Qing Shu, send more people to search for them.
We must find them.
- Hurry.
- Yes.
It's almost the last step.
Why did this happen at such a time?
Yunhe, after soaking in the water, my wound doesn't hurt anymore.
A little more medicine will heal it.
So fast.
It's true that good-looking people are suitable for any clothes.
The old clothes that I found casually
are so suitable for you.
That's not right.
Didn't you just soak in water?
How come there's no water on you?
Why is there water?
We, mermen, love cleanliness and care about appearance.
After coming out of the water,
our clothes and hair are no longer wet.
Fastidious.
Do you want to soak in the water?
I can help you bathe.
No, no need.
I... I have to clean up the house.
Did you make all those?
I found them from that cabinet.
That's strange.
Blue Feather Phoenixwas imprisoned in the Ten Directions Formation,
This place is not horrible, but a paradise.
Could it be that when she was imprisoned here,
she created a new world for herself?
Blue Feather Phoenix?
- She is...
- When I was in the sea,
I seem to have heard of her.
She is quite powerful, right?
She had been imprisoned here for 1,000 years.
Then, will we meet her here?
No. She's escaped.
So it was all because of her just now?
Yes.
The whole Thousand Flower Valley is in chaos because of her.
She is quite powerful.
By the way, Yunhe, how are Li Shu and Xue Sanyue now?
Lin Haoqing said that their love was discovered,
so they would be punished.
We made an appointment to escape together,
but now Li Shu and Xue Sanyue...
Forget it. This silly fish has nothing to do with these things.
There's no need to bother him more.
They're fine now.
All has been settled.
You helped them out?
Then you're great, too.
This is for you.
Where did you get the flower?
Li Shu gave me flower seeds.
He said women would look good with flowers.
Li Shu and Xue Sanyue also fell in love with flowers,
but they ended like that.
This flower looks really ironic now.
This flower can neither be used as a spirit stone
nor can it be eaten.
You might as well give me some ganoderma,
I might be happier.
Okay, then I'll plant ganoderma lucidum for you.
Right now, the most important thing is to escape,
don't think about anything else.
You are here to recover from your injuries. I'll go out to explore the way.
Big-tailed Fish, if there is any attack in the future,
you don't have to block for me.
If you are in danger,
I may not risk my life to save you.
Is this the place where Xue Sanyue and Li Shu met privately?
Yes.
I'm afraid that they were already in love.
Li Shu tried to find the eyes of the formation,
which led to the escape of Blue Feather Phoenix.
This is my fault, I ask for your punishment.
It's a serious crime in the valley for a Spiritual Master
to fall in love with an Earth Immortal.
Why didn't you cut down the tree?
Qing Shu, you've been in charge of the laws for many years,
and you have never shown mercy.
Since when did you have compassion for those who break the rules?
It's my fault.
I'll ask someone to cut down this tree.
Forget it.
Keep this tree.
It's good to make it a warning
to let everyone remember that
there are some things that can be thought about,
but never done.
Get up.
I understand.
I know my duty.
Your Master, Ji Yunhe and the merman escaped together.
I'm worried that there is also affections between them.
If so, that might not be a bad thing.
Where there is desire, there is weakness. Isn't that so?
I am just worried that
what if Young Master has the same weakness?
Ji Yunhe, you and Chang Yi started with lies.
How is it any different from Li Shu?
If one day the lie is exposed,
Chang Yi will hate you as much as Xue Sanyue.
How should you face his affection?
Since there may not be results,
then there is no need to start.
Forget it.
Anyway, after leaving Thousand Flower Valley,
we have to go our separate ways.
He will return to the sea,
and I'll go to the North.
Since our roads ahead are different,
it's better to break his dependence on me early.
Making it clear can make a happy break.
I should no longer be gentle to him,
and no longer be soft-hearted to him.
Yunhe! Yunhe!
Yunhe!
What's wrong?
Why are you naked?
I was going to apply the medicine,
but it slipped from my hand and broke.
Do you know what medicine it is? Just rubbing it on.
Come here.
Sit down.
I can't just ignore you.
It's my fault. I shouldn't have taken care of you so well before.
Do you know what medicine it is?
Just rubbing it on.
Don't talk like me.
I have experienced many battles.
Of course, I know what a vulnerary herb smells like.
Yunhe, you're weird, too.
You say one thing, but you do another.
I mean I won't risk my life to save you.
There is no point in putting on some medicine.
Okay.
Put your clothes on.
It's getting late, so let's go to bed.
Wait!
We can't sleep together.
Why?
A man and a woman shouldn't be close to each other.
Since you are on land, you have to follow the rules of the land.
Didn't we sleep together before?
You have a smell now.
There is no smell.
Then you can sleep in the house,
I'll go out to sleep.
It's so cold outside.
I'll go out, and you sleep inside.
Forget it, let's both sleep here,
but only for one night.
Okay.
Come on.
Why do you sleep down there?
If you really don't like to sleep with me,
- I'd better go out.
- No, no.
Sleep. I'll sleep there. I'll sleep with you.
Just lie well to heal your wound.
Don't move.
Big-tailed Fish,
you'll get in trouble on land for being so stubborn.
Tomorrow, when Chang Yi's body is better,
I'll tell him we should go our separate ways.
Master, the valley has been searched.
There is still no whereabouts of Ji Yunhe and the merman.
When the Blue Feather Phoenix caused chaos,
didn't someone see Qu Xiaoxing and Ji Yunhe
leave the inner hall sequentially?
Has Qu Xiaoxing confessed the whereabouts of Ji Yunhe?
We've already interrogated him.
But Qu Xiaoxing has always been good friends with Ji Yunhe,
so he kept silent about her whereabouts.
There is no mouth that
can't be pried open in Reflect Cave.
Father!
Young Master.
Father, can you leave Qu Xiaoxing to me?
I will definitely ask about the whereabouts of Ji Yunhe and the merman.
After the battle with Blue Feather Phoenix,
your injury has not yet healed,
so you don't have to do that.
As Young Master, it is my duty to do so.
Okay. Since you are sure, then show me.
Yes.
Xiaoxing, Ji Yunhe took the merman away without a word.
In order to find her, the brothers in the valley
didn't even drink a drop of water for a day.
She acted so unruly.
Why are you covering for her?
Right. As long as you point a direction,
we wouldn't be going around like blind flies.
I have told you many times that
I don't know where she's gone,
no matter how many times you ask.
You are putting us in a difficult position.
Young Master.
- You can leave.
- Yes.
Thank you, Young Master.
Although I am friends with Yunhe,
I really don't know where she has gone.
Of course, you don't know.
She fell into the formation with the merman.
What?
According to her nature, she will try her best to come out.
At that time, I want you to help her before everyone else.
You mean that you want me to save Yunhe?
You don't want to?
But don't you hate Yunhe so much?
Now she is the sinner of Thousand Flower Valley.
Once Master finds out what you have done,
even if you are his son, he will definitely punish you heavily.
I know.
Then why?
Lin Haoqing, what the hell are you thinking?
It's none of your business.
Do what you have to do.
Big-tailed Fish,
don't be nice to me anymore.
I'm afraid I can't bear to part with you.
Yunhe, come out and have a look.
Yunhe!
Come out, Yunhe!
Come on, look!
You're not even healed, why do you catch fish?
We can't use our spiritual power here.
I think tonic food might help me recover.
This fish is very tasty.
They are all for you.
Chang Yi, you're nice to me.
But sometimes the better you treat people, the more burden you will make, do you know?
You're nice to me, too.
The foolish fish even can't tell between the real and the fake.
I don't feel any burden.
In fact, you can be nicer to me.
Can you stop talking?
Okay, I can shut up,
then tell me.
Is something bothering you?
Can you tell that?
When you talk, you dare not look into my eyes.
No hurry. I can wait.
I live longer than immortals on average.
If Shunde knows that you talk in this style,
she will certainly regret giving this order.
I don't know what you are hiding in your heart.
But if you don't say it,
it proves that it's not that time yet.
That's okay. Eat the fish.
If they are not enough, I'll get you more.
What happened?
Chang Yi, do you feel that after being in the water,
your wound heals faster?
The wound.
A gentleman uses his tongue, not his fists.
So just say it.
Yes.
Then, do you feel that spiritual power flowing into your body?
But we can't use spiritual power here.
Qing can build a house with spiritual power here
and there are fish in the water,
so there must be a place to circulate the spiritual power outside.
As long as we can find the source,
we can definitely get out of here.
Besides, Li Shu has broken this formation,
so it shouldn't be difficult for us to escape the broken formation.
I caught the fish from the water.
Could the source be in the water?
Hasn't the Blue Feather Phoenix broken through the formation?
Is she sealed up again?
Spiritual Master, I'll swallow you!
She can't leave the water.
She isn't Blue Feather Phoenix.
She is her spirit.
Spirit?
Probably because she has some obsessions and she can't let go of them.
These emotions have been suppressed in the formation for thousands of years, and can't be eased,
which then formed the spirit of the phoenix.
You Spiritual Masters are all heartless.
I'll swallow you one by one.
If you have the ability, then go for the Spiritual Master who sealed you.
Don't take it out on us.
I will, I'll avenge the Spiritual Master.
It's Ning Ruochu, who imprisoned me in the Ten Directions Formation.
Why imprison me here? Why imprison me here?
Why?
Let's go inside. Wait till she calms down a bit.
Master, Young Master gave medicine to Qu Xiaoxing and released him.
Haoqing is still too soft-hearted.
Compared with that person, he is still not ruthless enough.
Ground Haoqing.
Pass on the news that Young Master is seriously ill.
As for Qu Xiaoxing…
Should I clean him up?
No.
He is too close to Ji Yunhe.
If something happens to him, Haoqing will be criticized.
I know.
I'll find a reason for Young Master to release him.
Qu Xiaoxing is not clever,
he won't look into it himself.
Master. Master.
You…
Qing Shu, send more people.
No matter how, we must find Ji Yunhe and the merman, especially Ji Yunhe.
I spent a hundred years of effort on her.
This game has come to an end.
At this moment, no mistakes are allowed.
Yes.
Do you mean that the exit is under the pool?
Although I just touched the water lightly,
I could feel the spiritual power flowing in it.
Although the spiritual power is very weak, it does exist.
If I'm right, this pool should be connected to one of the holes of the formation.
In the past, the Ten Directions Formation was very powerful.
But since the Blue Feather Phoenix broke out of the formation, even if it closes again, it is only a broken formation.
As long as we can break this eye of the formation, then we will be able to break out of the formation.
It's just that this spirit is too hostile to Spiritual Masters.
I just touched it lightly, and she came out to fight back.
We have to find a way to deal with her.
Do you have an idea?
Chang Yi, you really want to get out of here too, don't you?
Now neither of us can use our spiritual power.
- This spirit is so powerful. We definitely can't defeat her, right?
- Yes.
Well, in that case, we must not blindly force our way out but go out with wisdom.
Do you agree?
Yes.
I have an idea.
Do you want to try it?
What is it?
The spirit said that she was cheated by a man and suffered from love.
The easiest way to cure the love injury is to start a new love.
You are so beautiful, how about seducing her?
No.
How can you push me to her?
I'm not pushing you to her.
I didn't ask you to do anything to her.
I just want you to say some good words to coax her,
to make her a little happier and open her heart knot.
Then we can get out of here.
No.
We mermen never lie and we never cheat.
But it's a good lie.
Not all people lie with cunning minds.
Some people can't tell the truth, while some people are forced to tell lies.
If one day you really meet such a person, can't you be flexible?
As my father said, there are no white lies at all.
It's all self-deception.
For us mermen, lies are unforgivable.
You mermen are really pure and kind.
It doesn't matter. Let me do it.
How will you do it?
You're not a man.
Since ancient times, no woman in the scripts can resist the temptation of scholars.
Help me tie my hair.
Who are you?
Just after such a short while, she can't recognize me.
It seems that this spirit is just a spirit, whose mind is not complete.
But that's good. I don't have to explain myself.
I'm just a scholar.
I saw you from a distance and was attracted by you.
What is a scholar?
Why are you here?
And why are you attracted to me?
A scholar is a person who studies.
I see you sitting here alone, looking as if you are sad.
Is there something that makes you sad?
I was cheated by a Spiritual Master.
His name is Ning Ruochu.
We used to love each other very much.
But he broke my heart.
Is the one you're talking about the Impermanence Sage Ning Ruochu?
Isn't he the one responsible for sealing you?
Did you really fall in love with each other?
I remember that when Li Shu was just born,
his father, Lynx King, accidentally went mad and injured many people.
So he was hunted down by Spiritual Masters.
Li Shu is actually in the Lynx King's bloodline.
No wonder his power is so great.
Because of this, the good reputation that Li Shu's grandfather had earned
by following the former emperor to fight against Zhu Yan was destroyed overnight.
I saved little Li Shu who was almost hurt by them.
But Spiritual Masters accused me of being a criminal and hunted me down.
They chased me to Le You Mountain.
- Go there.
- Okay.
[Spiritual master of Thousand Flower Valley, Ning Ruochu]
[Le You Mountain]
Thanks to his timely help, little Li Shu was safe and sound.
Also, because of that, I knew that he had no malicious intentions.
He knew he had misunderstood me, and took the initiative to apologize to me.
Master Ning!
Are you Ning Ruochu?
But his juniors were far less enlightened than he was.
They believed in the rumors that I was a murderous deviant.
Ruochu tried to persuade them for me
and took me away.
He protected me and little Li Shu,
but I didn't want to owe his favor.
Knowing that he loved wine,
I gave him the wine made of the essence of flowers and grains to make even with him.
But he seemed to be addicted to drinking,
and he insisted on being my drinking buddy despite the gossip.
Gossip is most hurtful.
Aren't you afraid?
If I can't do what I want to do with my heart,
then what's the point of living?
That's how we fell in love.
♫ Each pair of eyes belongs to a merman ♫
♫ A drop in the ocean ♫
♫ Time is dreamy and turns into scales ♫
♫ The Milky Way ripples ♫
♫ I'm flying in the Milky Way like wind ♫
♫ Passing through the sea of stars ♫
♫ Enter the forest of light ♫
♫ Leap over the stream in the sky ♫
♫ My shadow is like a smile curve ♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection ♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ My leap reflects the mountaintop ♫
♫ From the sun, the moon to the dust ♫
♫ I just want to come and go with love ♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection ♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ The will of Heaven is disclosed ♫
♫ The love remains silent ♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection ♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ The sky is slightly rolled up ♫
♫ The longings emerge from the sea ♫
♫ The heart of infinity turns into scales ♫