♫ Heaven is silent, all is quiet ♫
♫ Yourself in the mirror, can't see clearly in the fog ♫
♫ Floating across the galaxy, across the Netherworld,
injury and parting ♫
♫ Broken dreams are locked deep at the bottom of the sea ♫
♫ Fog and clouds disperse between heaven and earth ♫
♫ The rain washed the dust away, who is waiting for me ♫
♫ Our fated love can light up the starry sea of time ♫
♫ I come on my own for you, searching for you step by step ♫
♫ Getting into my blood through every breath ♫
♫ Love is reborn on its own ♫
♫ I fall towards you ♫
♫ Word for word, you're as bright as a flower ♫
♫ The grief is so vast ♫
♫ The fish leaped and broke out of the cold water ♫
♫ Imagine us enjoying the moonlight at the end of the world ♫
♫ A grain of sand growing out of everything ♫
♫ A teardrop falling into the sky... ♫
[The Blue Whisper II]
[Episode 06]
Master Fei Lian, what brings you here?
I'm concerned about the Ganoderma and your safety.
I'm here to check on you.
Thanks for that.
I heard that you'd left Thousand Flower Valley.
There were many things that were not available to me at the time.
Anyway, I don't regret it.
I'm wondering what your plan is.
What's your suggestion?
Heavenly King is pursuing the Great Cause.
It will be a tough journey.
We are in need of more help.
You're known for your superb swordsmanship.
Would you like to join us
and aid us for a fair and peaceful world?
Well. It looks like they're talking business.
It's now or never.
Just make a match between them. That's all.
But there's a great age gap!
Forget about it.
Do you have some herbs with you?
Prince, let go. It hurts.
How dare you!
Setting me up already?
Did you really think you could hide it from me?
I've never seen anyone as good at acting as you.
Prince, it's for your own good.
Think about it. The lynx on Chongwu Mountain, isn't she beautiful?
And there's the hot leopard.
Why do you have to stick to the jinx?
He has a point! You fooled us first!
You said that once that jinx was eliminated,
you'd go back to Chongwu Mountain and inherit the crown.
Now, that jinx has been deceived by you.
Why aren't you leaving with us?
Jinx?
Exactly! Prince said you were a jinx.
You're the obstacle in his cultivation.
He also said if he didn't wipe you out,
he would be condemned as a sinner through the ages.
What's more, once he settled the scores with you,
he could be free and blameless.
There are plenty of female cats waiting for him.
Sanyue. Sanyue. Let me explain.
That's the truth! No need to explain.
Is that...
Thunderbolt Talisman of Thousand Flower Valley?
From now on, keep 10 meters away from me.
Now you call me a jinx,
I shall show you what a real jinx will do.
Sanyue!
Would you like to tell me about them?
Just ignore them. They're insignificant.
But I can tell that he is in deep love with you.
But he's being disrespectful.
He deserves it.
- You two!
- Prince...
Get lost!
She enjoys sending me gifts
just like the old times.
Master, I ordered this soft armor for you.
Would you like to try it on?
Thank you.
I have gotten one already.
You may save it for another general.
The armor you got looks delicate.
I'm wondering who made it for you?
I would like to learn from her.
It's by a random person.
It's far worse than the one you made. No need.
All right.
Now that you've gotten one already,
I shall pack this one away.
I'll send it to you later when needed.
By the way, Master,
I'm here to brief you on the preparations of the war material supplies.
If there are any deficiencies, you can bring it up.
I'll arrange it.
Young Lord. Sit down, please.
I've managed to hold on for a day.
It's really exhausting.
I didn't expect that I'd be so weak now.
Thankfully, Chang Yi didn't find it out.
You have shown up at last.
Who on earth are you?
Why did you come into my dream last time?
You were in the way.
I come and go by the wind.
When the wind blows,
I sense it.
So, it was you!
What are your intentions?
I'm asking you for a favor.
Now that you're so powerful,
why do you need my favor?
Only you can meet me. Only you can help me.
What am I supposed to do?
Here, I'll show you everything.
- Senior Brother.
- Junior Brother.
Qing'er, let me introduce him to you.
This is my senior brother, Ning Qing.
It turns out, Ning Ruochu was a senior to Immortal Master.
What I saw...
What you saw is the past.
Back then, Ning Ruochu fell in love with Qing Ji,
which was opposed by the people in the world.
So they went to Leyou Mountain
and lived in seclusion.
Later, Ning Ruochu sent a message to Ning Qing.
That was the first time Ning Qing visited Leyou Mountain.
There, he met Qing Ji.
But from what I saw, they seemed friendly.
Why did they become enemies in the end?
Maybe their love was doomed from the start.
Later, their hideout was exposed.
Qing Ji harmed the spiritual master coming for her.
As the message spread out,
it got even worse.
Later, Ning Ruochu got a message from Ning Qing
and met him in Thousand Flower Valley.
This formation is the Ten Directions Formation.
Grandmaster Ning learned the formation from Immortal Master!
But Grandmaster perished outside Ten Directions Formation.
He didn't join Qing Ji in the formation.
Could it be...
Right.
Ning Qing killed Ning Ruochu.
Why would he do that?
They were brothers of the same sect!
That's all the supplies we have.
What do you think, Master?
I know I can trust you with the arrangement.
Master, where are you heading?
What's so urgent in the middle of the night?
Please check on her.
What's going on?
Her pulse is getting weak.
The backlash is hurting her heart.
Yunhe!
Yunhe.
Please save her. Save her life.
If you want her to live, leave her to me and walk out.
Do not disturb me.
You can leave!
You can only meet me in your dream at your weakest moment.
But falling into a dream for too long, you might perish.
I must send you back.
Why do you show me your memory?
Who are you?
You're the lady Immortal Master can't forget.
Master.
What brings you here?
I saw you leave in a hurry, looking worried.
I was concerned about you. I came here to check on you.
What's going on?
Not a big deal. Don't worry, Young Lord.
Tell Qing Ji that it was Ning Qing who killed Ning Ruochu.
Tell her that Ning Qing must be stopped.
Why are you doing this?
You can't hold any longer.
Let me take another look.
Towering aloof in this grand world,
enjoying the snow in the breeze.
That was Ning Qing as a kid.
- So...
- You must go now.
Be sure to stop Ning Qing.
- That is my...
- ...redemption.
She's awake!
Finally, she made it.
Yunhe.
You frightened me! Don't you do this again.
I only took a nap.
Why are you all here?
A nap?
You almost died in your dream!
The backlash is hurting your heart.
They'd think I drugged you.
I was too tired, that's all.
Calm down.
♫ Hey, if I weren't me and you weren't you ♫
Master!
♫ Hey, think more...  ♫
Why did he kiss her?
♫ Hey, where are you going? ♫
♫ Any fool looking up can't keep the light ♫
Chang Yi!
Are you crazy?
♫ Hey, just follow the flow ♫
♫ I hope your wishes will come true and you go
to a bright place ♫
♫ Away from me, away from sadness ♫
♫ From now on, there will be no lies, forget the mundane world ♫
♫ Let regret not grow ♫
♫ From now on, you don't have to be scared of anything ♫
♫ Wanting and lacking nothing ♫
♫ Like fireflies chasing the waves ♫
♫ The uncatchable light ♫
♫ is left for one person to recall ♫
Ma... Master...
Are you insane?
Lin Haoqing is about to attack the North Abyss.
How could you pass on so much spiritual power in your merman pearl?
How will you fight against the Spiritual Masters now?
You're asking for death!
Passing on power?
You're saving Yunhe.
It's meaningless.
You tried it before. It won't work.
Chang Yi, are you crazy?
Take your merman pearl back.
I gave it to you.
You have to take it.
You have no other options.
You don't cherish your life, all right.
But what if Immortal Master ambushes us?
What could we count on? The snow outside?
Fairy Shunde hasn't recovered.
He won't be here.
Fine. Fine.
You've made up your mind a long time ago.
Master of North Abyss, huh?
I'm not worthy of you, Master!
Do as you wish.
Calm down.
Luo Luo, please leave.
- Should I stay here and...
- Just leave.
I need to talk to him.
All right.
Don't be angry.
- What did Master do...
- Piss off!
Luo Suo, what happened in there?
Well.
Nothing. It's just...
Didn't you see the beam of light?
That was the merman pearl.
Chang Yi used it to save Yunhe.
Shut up! Shut up! Don't talk about it.
The pearl is inside Ji Yunhe now?
Don't you know about our situation?
Master is responsible.
How could you cheat him out of the pearl and waste his power?
What on earth are you thinking?
We didn't cheat him!
Chang Yi had given his pearl to Yunhe a long time ago.
It's his choice.
He only cares about Yunhe.
Chang Yi, I don't care about other things.
But this is not child's play.
Take the pearl back.
Child's play?
So, let it be child's play.
It's not your problem.
Why do you insist on returning it to me?
Are you thinking about bossing me around like Kong Ming?
North Abyss isn't for yourself.
We're all a part of it.
You have no right to teach me what to do.
You shouldn't turn back.
You shouldn't become like this.
Don't be obsessed with hatred.
What obsesses me was never hatred
from the very beginning.
What is it then?
What do you think?
Chang Yi, even though I'm about to die,
I'm in sole charge of my life.
You shouldn't have wasted your spiritual power.
I don't want you to suffer.
You've cut off your tail. Now, the pearl isn't with you.
How will you secure North Abyss?
The way I secure it doesn't require a merman pearl
nor my spiritual power.
Master, what on earth really happened?
Did you really give your merman pearl to Ji Yunhe?
Is she that important to you?
Young Lord, you should get some rest.
Yunhe. Good for you.
All right. I'm sorry that I frightened you.
Luo Luo, would you do me a favor?
What's that?
Please ask Qing Ji to come here.
Why are you looking for her?
Talk about the good old days.
Father, I should have known.
I kept lying to myself.
But now... I cannot stand it anymore.
Chang Yi keeps saying that he hates Ji Yunhe,
but he cherishes her the most.
She's the most important one to him.
I cannot hold him back.
What should I do?
Father.
Father? You can hear me, can't you?
Father, please wake up soon.
Right now, you might be the only one to stop him.
You look lively!
So the spiritual power in the pearl does work!
If the pearl can prolong one's life,
merfolks should have been wiped out to make medicine from their pearls.
What do you mean? Can't it help Yunhe?
Just like Kong Ming's medicine.
Injecting spiritual power into the pearl can only make her look good.
Her life cannot be saved if the time has come.
Does Chang Yi know this?
Even if he does, he won't take it back.
Big-tailed Fish is so disobedient.
How will he fight Lin Haoqing? Is he out of his mind?
In my opinion, he's been crazy for a long time.
It's good that way.
Look at me, even if I want to be crazy,
I cannot find the reason.
Madam, I heard that Immortal Master and Grandmaster Ning were apprentice brothers.
Were they close? Was there any division?
Apprentice brothers?
Why isn't it recorded in the books in Thousand Flower Valley?
I never heard about it before. How do you know?
I heard about it from Immortal Master back in Congji Jail.
I don't think there was any division.
The two of them and Ning Xiyu grew up together. They were like a family.
If Ning Xiyu were alive, Ning Qing wouldn't have been insane like he is now.
Who is Ning Xiyu?
Ruochu's master.
She was the only female master of Thousand Flower Valley.
Master of Flower Valley?
Didn't you know?
I see.
Now that you brought it up, there must be a reason.
What do you want?
What I saw in the dream is too suspicious.
Shall I tell her about it?
Senior, do you still hold a grudge
for Grandmaster's absence in Ten Directions Formation?
Yunhe, you shouldn't rub it in.
It's all right.
To be honest, I hated him and blamed him.
But it's getting vague now.
After many years, I can finally laugh at the grudge I held.
I was kept in the formation for a 1,000 years.
Why should I keep my heart locked up?
That's right.
Live freely in a wide world with wine and snow.
That's satisfying enough.
Why should we be bothered by the past?
Senior, I'd love to make a toast with tea instead of wine.
It took a long time for Qing Ji to move on.
I shouldn't bother her and ask her to fight with Immortal Master
for the sake of a foamy dream.
Fine.
The next time I met Ning Xiyu, I'll ask her for details.
Now that you don't need my help, why do you bring me here?
The terrain here is steep and complex.
Spiritual Masters will come through the forest to save up energy.
I'm thinking about setting up a formation here and luring them out.
What do you think?
Are you serious about asking me for advice? You're determined to go your own way.
Your pearl and your power were sent to Ji Yunhe generously.
How can you win this battle?
Shunde's intention is to drain our energy using Thousand Flower Valley's troops.
Then, she can reap the benefits. We can't let that happen.
Thousand Flower Valley's troops traveled all the way here.
It must be against their will. That way, there will be a crack.
Are you suggesting peace talks?
Immortal Master and Shunde are scourges to our realm.
Immortals have suffered from being suppressed for a long time, but they are powerless.
Right now, North Abyss is gaining strength. Thousand Flower Valley is the leader of all spiritual masters.
If we can make peace, maybe there will be more immortals on our side.
We can wipe out the demons.
However, Thousand Flower Valley is too proud to cooperate with us.
To persuade them, we must attack them and drain their energy.
Once they let their guard down, can we negotiate with them.
So, even though I have an obsession,
I have never forgotten about my identity.
Thankfully, you are clear-minded.
I thought love turned your head.
Still, I must warn you whether it's love or hate,
the obsession with a certain person is not beneficial for the great cause.
But I haven't made any trouble.
Don't quibble.
What about you? Don't you love Luo Jinsang?
Haven't you done anything following an impulse?
We're talking about you! What about her?
I just want to tell you
that I can separate my private interest from my obligation.
And I know what I'm doing.
Why? Are you telling me that you still don't know if I'm the one?
Stop talking about the Golden Lotus.
It's a good thing you know it.
It's a lousy world. We can never be too careful.
With an obligation, I dare not slack off.
I cannot do that.
Sanyue, I only said it to fool Da Huan and Xiao Huan. I didn't mean it.
Nor did I talk about some cats.
They made it up.
I'm afraid that's exactly what you're thinking.
Of course not! I improvised!
Stay away.
Give me some time.
For what?
So I can think about us.
Since the day we met, joy and peace seldom come to us.
Maybe you got it right. I am your jinx.
Maybe, we shouldn't be together.
It's best for you to keep a distance from me.
That's not up to you!
You're the best for me. The best thing of all!
Don't you dump me.
Li Shu, just leave me alone, all right?
I'll talk to you later.
Please, stop overthinking. Okay?
That's not the right way to picture our relationship. Don't make it worse.
Thanks for your hard work, Commander Xue.
Master Fei Lian.
Nectar Ganoderma will be ripen soon. Heavenly King is concerned about you.
He sent me here to see if you need help.
Thanks, and please transfer my gratitude to His Majesty.
Li Shu has been bothering you recently.
Shall I send him away from Daiyu Mountain?
Don't bother. I can work it out on my own.
No need for this. He's far away.
You kept talking about keeping a distance.
But I can tell from your eyesight that you still love him.
So? You're forgiven him about the jinx?
It's just a joke. We've witnessed life and death.
It doesn't bother me.
Even if I was mad, I'd forgive him soon after.
Then, why don't you remove the talisman?
You talk in a detached way and ask him to stay away.
Is it... you're worried that something will go wrong with picking Nectar Ganoderma?
You're protecting him.
Why don't you tell him about your intention?
He's done enough for me.
It seems that I always take it for granted.
But now, I realized it and I cherish our relationship.
At least, I'll try to keep him away from the danger.
Once I get the Nectar Ganoderma, I'll remove the talisman.
I'm touched by your sincere love.
It's just...
Please go ahead.
It's just Li Shu is persistent in staying by your side.
He doesn't care about the efforts you have made.
Sometimes, what you have in mind isn't what he wants.
Whether you're good to him isn't solely up to you.
His feelings matter. Don't you think so?
Do you think I did it the wrong way?
It's your relationship. I have no right to judge you.
You know it better than anyone else.
Report!
Young Lord. General. Just as Master expected,
Thousand Flower Valley's troops are marching through the woods, unguarded.
Their troops have entered the formation we set up.
We're all prepared. Thousand Flower Valley's troops have been attacked in the woods.
No wonder he's the master.
All right, it's our show.
Wait. What do you want?
The enemy is trapped.
They cannot escape from us.
If we attack them now, we can wipe them out once and for all.
Don't!
Master ordered us to defend here and cooperate with the others.
How could you disobey the order and walk away from the post?
Behind us is the natural defense.
To attack or to defend, it's up to us.
It's now or never.
You can't go against Master.
Are you sure that Chang Yi is always right?
Uncle hasn't woken up.
We must fight for our glory.
Come on. Time to attack.
- Yes, sir!
- Qifeng!
Chang Yi has been out for a long time.
Is Lin Haoqing being besieged already?
Yunhe! Yunhe.
Thousand Flower Valley's troops have been ambushed.
They are trapped in the woods near the border.
Great!
As long as they're willing to negotiate,
North Abyss will be safe.
Lin Haoqing!
How did you lead the troops?
You brought us into a trap!
Thankfully, Lin Canglan already passed away.
If he found out you got Thousand Flower Valley into this embarrassment,
he'd be furious!
You!
This time, I volunteered myself to Immortal Fairy to be the observer.
This is your luck.
Think about it.
I'm the only famous Spiritual Master in the entire world.
Exactly. The observer's reputation is far reaching.
You handed over your territory and gave out Lingshuang Pavilion.
Everyone knows about your behavior.
How dare you!
She's my attendant. I will discipline her.
I have my plan for commanding the operation.
Don't forget, Immortal Fairy nominated me to be the commander.
Even though you're the commander, so what?
Immortal Fairy can dismiss you from this post easily!
She sends me here as the observer only because she doesn't trust you.
Don't be smug.
You'd better know what you're doing.
Or I'll report to Immortal Fairy and let her punish you!
Report!
Master, we've explored the area.
There are formations everywhere. We cannot move.
Besides, the potential breaches here are heavily guarded.
We cannot make it.
See? What did I say?
If it wasn't for you, we wouldn't have ended up here.
You'd better listen to me and hand out the seal.
I can lead the troops and fight our way out.
I will not sacrifice my men for a mission impossible.
They all have a Frost mark inside.
They will die anyway.
Is there an enemy at the mountain pass in the north?
It feels strange.
No one attacks us but there.
A troop is attacking us from the north mountain pass.
Break out from there.
Lin Haoqing, are you deaf?
They are attacking from the north. You're asking for death.
Now we're trapped here.
North Abyss could have taken us over.
There must be something wrong.
It could be an internal discord.
Give out my order, break out from the north mountain pass.
We must strike them while they're celebrating.
Yes, Master.
Hold on!
That's too arbitrary.
What if something goes wrong? Can you take the blame?
I will take it!
Give out my order!
Yes, Master.
Chang Yi, you're back.
How is the fight?
I heard it from Ming that you stayed up all night. Waiting for the update?
Anyway, I have plenty of time to sleep.
Just let me hear about it.
I heard that Lin Haoqing has been trapped in the woods.
Who will you send to talk to them?
It cannot be you.
Just let me go.
I grew up with Lin Haoqing in Thousand Flower Valley.
We're friend and foe.
In a way, he's my last family left in this world.
I'm sure no one knows about him better than I do.
Family?
I didn't know you were that close to him.
Are you plotting for Lin Haoqing to take you away?
I...
Master!
Lin Haoqing distorted the formation and got out of the woods.
How is that possible?
Where's the breach?
North mountain pass, Qing Yao and Qi Feng were supposed to hold it.
Qi Feng again! Being greedy and aggressive.
He didn't listen to Qing Yao and launched the attack.
The enemy took the chance and fought back.
Although our troops have withdrawn to a safe place,
the enemy has the upper hand now.
Where's Qi Feng?
He's been caned 300 times.
That's too easy for him!
Anything else?
Lin Haoqing sent a messenger for negotiation on one condition.
What's that?
To meet Ji Yunhe.
Who's the messenger?
Siyu.
Siyu?
Right. I should have told you earlier.
Siyu didn't die.
Lin Haoqing hid her away.
I thought he was too harsh on Siyu.
No wonder, it was a show...
Anyway, it doesn't matter now.
The point is how will we settle the attack.
Chang Yi, please let her meet me.
We can't afford the delay.
Bring her to Cloud Quarters.
Yes, Master.
Lin Haoqing.
Now we've broken out.
Why don't you take the chance and attack Lingshuang Pavilion?
You're dawdling. What's on your mind?
Fairy asked me to be the observer.
Don't you dare fool me!
We cannot settle this battle in a short time.
- You should know it better than I do.
- You!
Besides, the priority isn't the North Abyss.
What matters to Immortal Fairy is capturing Ji Yunhe.
I've sent a messenger to Lingshuang Pavilion
and asked them to hand her out.
What's the condition?
What will you do if they hand her out?
Retreat?
I'm telling you. That's impossible.
Immortal Fairy wants Ji Yunhe's life.
And she wants to destroy the whole North Abyss.
There's no compromise.
Lin Haoqing, you know perfectly what Thousand Flower Valley is to Immortal Fairy now.
If you screw it up,
Immortal Fairy will abandon you at any time.
By that time, Thousand Flower Valley will be doomed.
Master. Guardian Ji.
Siyu, just tell us straight.
What does Lin Haoqing want?
You.
Master wants no trouble with the North Abyss.
Casualties aren't what he wants.
As long as you hand Guardian Ji out,
we can agree to your conditions.
Is that all?
Right.
Listen up and transfer my reply to Lin Haoqing word by word.
We've shown our kindness.
We wanted to cooperate with Thousand Flower Valley to wipe out the common enemy.
But you insist on standing on the wrong side and keep pushing our limit.
We will fight to the end.
Don't think about taking Ji Yunhe from me.
Nor will I hand out Kong Ming.
I will not give you anyone sheltered by North Abyss.
Yunhe, I've never seen him talk so seriously.
Even I want to refer to him as Master.
Big-tailed Fish,
you've changed a lot.
You've made your point clear. I'm leaving.
Hold on.
Leaving like this?
Luo Jinsang, it's not permitted to harm the messengers from your enemy.
Let her go.
I'll see you off.
Hold on.
She's a cunning snake.
I must follow her in case she harms us.
Let's go.
Chang Yi.
I know what you're going to say.
I don't want to hear it.
Well, what was I about to say?
You want to tell me that you are not someone who wants to be sheltered by North Abyss.
Ji Yunhe, I don't care about what others say.
But you, you have no other option but to take this shelter.
Big-tailed Fish, you have it wrong.
I want to tell you...
that I really like the way you talked to her.
You're tough enough to be North Abyss's master.
This time, I'm here to help you.
We've got a hard battle to fight.
♫ Hey, if I weren't me and you weren't you ♫
♫ Hey, think more... think more ♫
♫ Hey, where are you going? ♫
♫ Any fool looking up can't keep the light ♫
♫ Hey, just follow the flow ♫
♫ I hope your wishes will come true and you go
to a bright place ♫
♫ Away from me, away from sadness ♫
♫ From now on, there will be no lies, forget the mundane world ♫
♫ Let regret not grow ♫
♫ From now on, you don't have to be scared of anything ♫
♫ Wanting and lacking nothing ♫
♫ Like fireflies chasing the waves ♫
♫ The uncatchable light ♫
♫ is left for one person to recall ♫
♫ The wind blows causing the flower petals to fall ♫
♫ Sand is washed away by the rain ♫
♫ I think you are someplace else, singing happily ♫
♫ Never again recalling anything about me ♫
♫ The flowers here are blooming once again ♫
♫ As bright as you are, in the blink of an eye, tens of thousands
of light years have passed ♫
♫ Have you ever seen this world as you thought it would be? ♫