♫ A gentle smile on lips disturbed the time-line ♫
♫ A thousand years passed in moonlight ♫
♫ In the corridor at the end of the world ♫
♫ I seem to see us there out of the corner of my eyes ♫
♫ We bloomed like a flower ♫
♫ Meeting by the river of time ♫
♫ We were at the same play stage ♫
♫ A step for thousands of miles ♫
♫ A glance at numerous colors ♫
♫ What is left blank is my love confession ♫
[The Blue Whisper]
[Episode 08]
That's how we fell in love.
But the prejudice against me was still there.
Our relationship was not acceptable to the world.
To avoid disturbance,
Ruochu gave up his reputation, status,
and everything in the Thousand Flower Valley.
He went to live in the mountains with me.
Like a normal married couple,
we cooked meals and brewed tea.
Life was uneventful but full of happiness.
If you like,
I'm willing to tie your hair for the rest of your life.
But the good times did not last,
Spiritual Masters finally found where we lived.
- Ruochu and I... wounded a lot of spiritual masters.
- Let's go.
It all got out of hand.
Why did you stop me?
If you kill them, you'd really become what they call the devil.
Then shall I just sit back and wait for them to kill me?
Ruochu, in this world, you and I are on different paths.
We walked together up to now. It was a good time.
I don't want to put you in trouble.
Later, we heard that when the Ruochu's master traveled around,
he passed away.
Ruochu was filled with grief.
He secretly went back to Thousand Flower Valley to worship.
I waited for him outside Thousand Flower Valley.
I thought he would be reluctant to come because he was reluctant to part with Thousand Flower Valley.
In my heart, I prepared for the worst.
But he eventually came back.
He told me.
Qing'er, since the rules of the fairy world shackle you and me,
let's just forget them.
I know a place. It is empty and lifeless.
But we can be together forever.
Would you like to come with me?
Listen carefully, Ning Ruochu.
In Heaven or Earth, throughout the world,
I'll be wherever you are.
I have found an ancient formation called Ten Directions Formation.
In the name of sealing you, I'll ask for help.
I'll invite nine Spiritual Masters to make Ten Directions Formation together.
After sealing you, I'll make an excuse of traveling around to hide my tracks.
And I'll sneak in to find you.
Then, we'll live together in the formation.
No more worldly disturbance.
In the formation, I built a cabin.
The decorations were the same as before.
Then there went a day,
a month, a season.
I passed spring, summer,
autumn, and winter.
A thousand years had passed.
He never came.
A thousand years of captivity.
A thousand years of waiting.
He promised me.
Why didn't he come?
Why hadn't he come yet?
Let's go.
Come on.
Are you okay?
What are you thinking?
Things are a little different than I thought.
It turns out that the man Qing called a heartbreaker was Master Ning.
I just heard it.
But you know what?
The reason why Master Ning is called Impermanent Sage of Thousand Flower Valley, admired by the younger generation,
was because he sacrificed his life to put down the Blue Feather Rebellion and sealed her.
That's why in everyone's mind, he's the greatest hero in the Blue Feather Rebellion.
Qing's years of waiting were just a scam by Master Ning.
You mean Ning Ruochu betrayed Qing.
But books in Thousand Flower Valley
have never recorded Master Ning's relationship with Qing.
Probably from the beginning, Master Ning cheated Qing.
But now, Master Ning died long ago.
Who would know the thoughts in his mind?
If you were Qing, would you believe Master Ning again?
Sure enough.
When there's deception in a relationship,
trust can no longer exist.
I mean I think Ning Ruochu, he should...
- Ning Ruochu!
Your debt, just let your apprentices pay for you.
This is terrible. Even if she's an attached spirit,
Qing is still the Phoenix King.
Even if the attached spirit only has a tenth of her power,
we can't get around her to escape from here.
You can stay here. I'll go distract her.
Then you try to escape.
What are you going to do?
I'll go tell her the end of Ning Ruochu.
This is the truth she deserves to know.
Are you crazy? She's out of control now.
If you tell her Master Ning deserted her,
she will tear you apart.
I don't think Ning Ruochu betrayed Blue Feather Phoenix.
He failed to keep his promise. There must be some reason.
Lovers don't lie to each other.
Just like you and me.
Chang Yi, there are some things
that happen even if you think they won't.
We have too much desire and concern on shore.
There can be lies between lovers.
I know.
On the shore, what you say may be different from what you think.
Words don't count.
But thoughts cannot be hidden.
Right.
If Qing were not in Master Ning's heart,
he wouldn't keep that hairband in his hands.
In the mirage just now,
Master Ning was attacked by both Qing and Spiritual Masters.
He should be injured.
Maybe there was an accident when activating the Ten Directions Formation.
He knew his days were numbered.
And he was afraid that Qing would be sad and die with him.
That's why he chose to die out of the formation.
Chang Yi, you're not stupid.
You see it better than anyone.
I know now what she wants in her heart.
Just let me tell her.
Let me do it. It's too dangerous to approach her.
After all, I am the apprentice of Master Ning.
His debt should be paid by me.
However, I don't think I can use this identity to get close to her.
I have to change my identity.
Who are you going to be this time?
Who are you?
It's me, Ning Ruochu.
Qing'er...
May I come?
What took you so long to get here?
You said you'd be with me.
I have been waiting for you for a long time.
I'm sorry.
But I know you'd come.
It's been so long.
Where have you been?
I went to a place far away.
So I didn't keep my promise to accompany you.
But I went all the way thinking about you.
- Qing'er.
- Are you lying to me again?
You still wear it.
I went to a very cold place.
I was afraid I'd forget you.
So I tied it around my wrist.
I've never taken it off.
I wanted to find you more than anyone, Qing'er.
The attached spirit, or rather, Qing herself,
had always believed that
no matter how long it went, Ning Ruochu would surely come to her.
So in this Ten Directions Formation, whoever came in here, male or female,
as long as I called myself Ning Ruochu, she would recognize it.
She doesn't believe in whoever may come.
She believes in Ning Ruochu.
Loneliness for a thousand years. Hatred grows from it.
But these emotions can be solved by one sentence, actually.
However, I couldn't help her meet the real Master Ning.
♫ Each pair of eyes belongs to a merman♫
♫ A drop in the ocean ♫
♫ Time is dreamy and turns into scales♫
♫ The Milky Way ripples ♫
Your song can control the water.
♫ Passing through the sea of stars♫
♫ Enter the forest of light, leap over the stream in the sky♫
♫ My shadow is like a smile curve♫
Ruochu, you finally came to me.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
But in fact, I've always been here with you.
I know.
Now, I should probably go find you, too.
From then on, everything around Le You Mountain...
will only belong to you and me.
Big-tailed Fish, according to the five elements, water represents life.
Now the water is receding rapidly.
I think the life path is cut off.
Ten Directions Formation will soon turn into a death formation.
If we want to get out, we have to jump in.
After we leave, where are we going?
I thought I could carefully think about it.
But I didn't expect that there would be no time to consider.
Are you afraid that after we leave, we'll be separated like them?
The road ahead is uncertain. I don't know.
- Why don't we just use a magic spell to decide?
- Magic spell?
It's the easiest spell we learned from the mortal world.
By bending and extending our fingers, we compete with each other.
Let me teach you.
On the count of one, two, three. Pick any one from those gestures.
One.
Two.
Three.
I win.
What do you mean?
You win, I'll go with you.
I win, you come with me.
Anyway, we just don't separate.
♫ Heaven is silent, all is quiet ♫
♫ Yourself in the mirror ♫
I've always wished to escape Thousand Flower Valley.
For that, I can put up with a lot and give up a lot.
Because I thought I was pursuing freedom.
But now I understand.
That's not the meaning of freedom.
It's not the point of being alive, either.
I don't want to be like this attached spirit, indulging in the past.
No matter what the road ahead will lead to, let's go and see it together.
Okay?
Are you saying that no matter what happens,
we will always be together.
From now on, there's no lie at all.
Forever. Always. Together.
♫ I fall towards you ♫
♫ Word for word, you're as bright as a flower ♫
♫ The grief is so vast ♫
♫ The fish leaped and broke out of the cold water ♫
♫ Imagine us enjoying the moonlight at the end of the world ♫
♫ A grain of sand growing out of everything ♫
♫ A teardrop ♫
♫ falling into the sky ♫
You gave me your pearl.
It's a token and a promise to you.
Is that how you mermen give the pearl?
Or did you read some strange books?
Even if there are strange books, they were given by you.
I really misguided you.
Are you afraid?
As long as I'm with you, I'm not afraid of anything.
The song you sang when you were controlling water.
What's that?
Song of Mermen. Praise of freedom.
It's time to sing this song.
We are going to be free.
Qing'er.
You drink too much.
You are dead.
You're long gone.
Ning Ruochu, when I was under the Ten Directions Formation,
I'd been thinking of millions of endings with you and millions of paybacks.
That's how I managed to get through all this.
I didn't expect that...
you were dead.
You're malicious enough.
You simply died,
so that I could never kill you however I wished.
For a thousand years, what did I exist for?
For what?
What do I live for?
Tell me. What was the relationship between Li Shu and you?
Since I brought you back, you refused to eat, drink, or talk.
I thought you wanted to die.
Now it seems that you're not so lame.
What's your relationship with him?
Why was he willing to die for you?
He owed me his life before.
And now it's fair to return it.
It's none of your business.
It's fair for you two.
Then what was I to him?
Things between you two, why did you get me involved?
So you are trying to kill me.
Are you trying to get revenge for Li Shu
or trying to take my head back to Thousand Flower Valley to show loyalty?
Until now, do you think you can go back and be a Spiritual Master as usual?
Get revenge for Li Shu?
Who am I to him?
From the very beginning, everything was fake.
The meeting at Mountain Qiongling was fake.
Daily togetherness was fake.
The sweet talk was fake.
Even his identity was fake.
All of these were because of you.
You overestimated yourself.
Then kill me.
I know I can't kill you.
You're not the one lying to me.
If Li Shu were still here,
I would cut him to pieces.
However, he's dead...
without leaving an explanation.
He just died.
I didn't know him well.
I'll accept and take all the results.
But why did he take the last attack for me?
He was plotting against me until he died.
He used his life to block my retreat.
I can neither love him nor hate him.
But I don't need it.
I don't appreciate it.
And I'll never forgive him.
You're so noisy.
We've finally escaped. Big-tailed Fish.
Guardian Ji, have you had a good sleep?
Why am I here again?
Guardian Ji, when you got out of the formation, you picked a good spot.
You came out with the merman right from Master's backyard pond.
Since you were in a coma, Master asked me to bring you here first.
You didn't know that the pond was one of the ten key points of the Ten Directions Formation.
Why do you laugh, Guardian?
It's ridiculous and pathetic... I thought I saw a light.
But I didn't expect that it turns out to be just a flash of fire in the stone.
Chang...
Where's the merman?
The merman, after trying his best to protect you, was also captured.
He's currently being held in Reflect Cave.
What will you do to him?
Just worry about yourself.
In this Ten Directions Formation Rebellion, Xue Sanyue defected.
Li Shu was executed. None of them can be blamed.
Now, everyone is focusing on your escape and collusion with the merman.
Think how to defend yourself.
Master, as a Guardian, Ji Yunhe
was supposed to protect Thousand Flower Valley.
And she took advantage of Blue Feather Phoenix's rebellion,
trying to escape with the merman.
It's a terrible sin.
Master, please severely punish and discipline her.
Yunhe, how will you explain this?
Lin Canglan is foxy.
If I admit it, I'll lose my training qualification and never see Chang Yi again.
If I deny it, it means that Chang Yi committed the crime of escape
and would be subjected to capital punishment.
Master, I'm not guilty.
That day, I didn't join in the battle with Blue Feather Phoenix
because after Li Shu broke Ten Directions Formation,
I watched the golden light and headed for Reflect Cave.
I was afraid the merman might get away with it, so I went to check.
Accidentally, I fell into the formation.
That's just sophistry.
Of course, the battle with Blue Feather Phoenix concerns the reputation of Thousand Flower Valley. It was indeed important.
But if we let the merman escape and offend Fairy Shunde,
Thousand Flower Valley's reputation would also be at stake.
It seemed that even if I joined, it's impossible to capture the Blue Feather Phoenix.
But if we want to keep the merman, I'm enough to do that.
Guardian Ji is right.
I didn't expect that though Guardian Ji is young,
she would see the big picture clearer than we Elders.
She's the hope of the Thousand Flower Valley.
I think you're talking nonsense.
Let me ask you. If Guardian Ji didn't collude with the merman,
when we captured them, why did the merman try so hard to keep her safe?
Why shouldn't he protect me?
Mastering spirit is to master its mind and make its heart obedient.
Don't you know the temper of the merman?
I just changed it into a different way to make him obey me.
Is that a sin?
That makes sense.
As you say, the merman should be fully obedient to you.
Why can't he speak yet? It has been delayed for a long time.
If we fail to achieve Fairy Shunde's order, what shall we do?
That's my dereliction of duty. I accept the punishment.
Great.
You deserve twenty floggings with the Red Tail as a warning to others.
Vile person. I'm a vile person?
Nothing can be accomplished without rules.
I accept the punishment.
Don't flog her!
I didn't expect that the merman would start talking.
Guardian Ji was right.
Yes.
Chang Yi, how are you?
I'm okay.
Qu Xiaoxing, at this moment, why do you bring the merman here?
Master, the merman opened his mouth in Reflect Cave.
I dare not make arbitrary decisions, so I brought him here.
The truth on that day, it's more convenient to ask him in public.
If you want to avoid suffering, you have to tell the truth.
On that day in the Reflect Cave, what happened exactly?
How did you escape?
And why did you protect Ji Yunhe?
Ten Directions Formation was broken. I accidentally fall down.
She was the one who saved me. I appreciated her.
So, you have no reason to flog her.
Now that the merman has spoken,
do I still need to be punished with 20 Red Tailfloggings?
Congratulations to Master. Fairy Shunde's first wish has been achieved.
Guardian Ji is a hero.
The punishment is exempted.
Thanks, Master.
Congratulations to Master.
Xiaoxing, take the merman back. Take good care of him.
Let's go.
I didn't expect that he really listens to you.
Master, the merman has a stubborn temperament.
We need to treat him softly to get what we want.
Master, please allow that when I'm with the merman,
I can order others to leave or stop the punishment of the merman.
If you can achieve Fairy Shunde's wishes, I'll support you.
Thank you, Master.
Yunhe, come here.
Well done for your training. I'll reward you.
Bad Yunhe, you stood me up.
Luo Luo, why did you come back?
If I don't come back, who can take care of you?
I know what happened to Li Shu and Xue Sanyue. We really can't stay here any longer.
Even if I have to carry you, I'll take you out of the Thousand Flower Valley.
Luo Luo, I can't leave yet.
Chang Yi is still in Reflect Cave.
What about our Immortal Island?
Did you really decide to go to the East Sea with Chang Yi?
Did Lin Canglan torture you again?
Come on.
Take the antidote.
Why are you getting worse?
Master sent me to tell you.
Those are cooling pills.
Guardian, you should take them with care.
Doesn't it make the Frost mark worse?
You...
It seems Master knew I would go steal the pills.
And he secretly put fake drugs in the inner room.
If he knew all this,
why was he pretending patiently in front of me?
Why didn't he give me a quick end?
The blade is not finished yet.
So the whetstone can not be discarded.
Master knows clearly what you're doing.
He spared your life and maintained your position.
You should be grateful for Master's kindness.
What are you going to do?
Master asked me to remind you.
Though the merman is obedient to you,
don't forget, Guardian, who you should obey.
These days, just reflect on yourself here.
Yunhe.
Master, Ji Yunhe is stubborn.
She won't give up easily.
What should we do in the second round?
Please give the order.
How is Haoqing?
Young Master is wounded.
He has been grounded for days.
There's no movement.
All right, let's go and see him.
Okay.
Ji Yunhe and the merman have been captured.
Young Master, the merman has spoken.
The first round, you lost.
Father, I know I was wrong.
I'll try harder.
Father, please don't...
Don't what?
Don't punish her for taking your credit?
Haoqing, Ji Yunhe can use the soft way
to win the heart with love and make the merman obey.
You can also take advantage of it, right?
Young Master.
Master has planned carefully.
The second round of taming the merman
is for you to achieve.
I understand.
Father, this time I won't let you down.
Take the medicine.
Recover well and get the job done.
Yes.
I've set up a barrier on Le You Mountain.
Thousand Flower Valley forces cannot reach here.
This is where I used to practice.
From now on, you stay right here.
Don't come out to bother me.
I would rather die than accept your protection.
I only promised Li Shu to take you out of Thousand Flower Valley.
I don't care whether you're alive or dead.
I won't take care of you.
But don't forget that
your life was saved with his life.
Whether you want it or not,
think about it carefully.
One day, I'll kill you.
When you can get out, you can try.
He's dead...
without leaving an explanation.
He just died.
He blocked my retreat with his life.
I can neither love him nor hate him.
Right.
Why leave me alone?
Love or hate.
Either way is good.
Little Li Shu,
you sacrificed your life to save me from the Ten Directions Formation.
What's the point of it?
A thousand years have passed by.
Ning Ruochu has turned into ashes.
I was left alone.
Useless.
And you're also dead.
You are all liars.
Yunhe will be fine. Right?
How dare you ask about her?
Yunhe has always been loyal.
Master liked her so much.
If she wasn't obsessed with you,
how would she have the idea of escaping from the valley.
It would have been nice if she could escape,
but she was dragged down due to a thing like you.
I'm not a thing.
You are even worse than a thing.
I want to see her.
Yunhe's position in the valley is at stake now.
You need to stay here. Don't go anywhere else.
It's my fault, too.
I couldn't reach you in time.
But who would imagine that
the small pond in Master's backyard is the array eye.
Young Master.
From today, I'll take over the training of the merman.
But Master had promised Yunhe...
In the Thousand Flower Valley, I only listen to one spiritual master,
that is Ji Yunhe.
She is really capable.
Finally, you are willing to speak.
Young Master, what are you doing?
The second round of training a merman.
Cutting off the tali.
Unless I'm willing to,
even if I'm dead,
you can never cut off my tail.
♫ Each pair of eyes belongs to a merman♫
♫ A drop in the ocean ♫
♫ Time is dreamy and turns into scales♫
♫ The Milky Way ripples ♫
♫ I'm flying in the Milky Way like wind ♫
♫ Passing through the sea of stars♫
♫ Enter the forest of light♫
♫ Leap over the stream in the sky♫
♫ My shadow is like a smile curve♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ My leap reflects the mountaintop♫
♫From the sun, the moon to the dust ♫
♫ I just want to come and go with love♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection ♫
♫ The projection of a world ♫
♫ The will of Heaven is disclosed♫
♫ The love remains silent♫
♫ My heart leaves a projection♫
♫ The projection of a world♫
♫ The sky is slightly rolled up♫
♫ The longings emerge from the sea ♫
♫ The heart of infinity turns into scales♫