~ Revenge Note 1 ~
Kim Hyang Gi
Kim Hwan Hui
Cha Eun Woo
Park Solomon
Ji Geon Wu
~ Revenge Note 1 ~
Episode 5
Deok Hui.
Gosh.
Come on.
Are you pooping?
Why did she leave without telling me?
The truth about Eun Woo behind his angelic face
Share
Deok Hui, why did you just leave yesterday?
Do you want to come over later? I have something to tell you.
No, I'm busy today.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
I'm going to nap. Don't talk to me.
Deok Hui, I've got the ticket.
Really?
I failed at getting mine. Can you sell it to me?
Twice... No, I'll give you three times the amount.
No way. My fingers almost bled trying to get these.
Please, my friend. Let's talk about this.
Oh my gosh. The thing about Eun Woo must be real. There's a video this time.
"The truth about Eun Woo."
"A video of another victim?"
"Eun Woo habitually molested minors
even before his debut"?
I went out simply as a fan,
but he kept telling me to get in his car.
He took her to a studio apartment...
I can't believe this.
Isn't Cha Eun Woo the kindest-looking one?
He was totally wearing a mask.
Guys like him always turn out to be the worst.
He is totally a habitual criminal.
You don't know anything. Don't talk of him like that without a thought.
Is she a fan too?
This isn't good.
I need to at least tell Deok Hui about everything.
Eun Woo
The phone is turned off. You'll be connected to voice mail.
An additional fee will be charged after the beep.
What do we do?
What's going to happen to him?
I'm coming in.
Eun Woo's phone won't work for the time being.
He told me to tell you not to worry about him.
I think he knows what he's doing.
Let's wait and see.
Deok Hui, why did you leave without me?
Deok Hui, are you still busy?
Will you be the Revenge Goddess?
Enter target's name
If I knew who it was, I could at least try to do something.
I want to at least tell Deok Hui about everything.
Showtime K-Pop
Manager, may I have a moment?
Producer, have we checked on the smoke?
The cue sheet suddenly changed,
so their performance got canceled today. I'm sorry.
How could that happen?
The fans are already here, and the damage won't be small either.
The decision was made higher up.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Wait a minute. Producer.
Producer.
I wonder if we'll even be able to have our concert.
Hyeong, what is this?
You should at least give an explanation or take the blame.
Do something!
Hey, let's not do this.
It's under investigation. We decided to wait it out.
I'm just frustrated.
Ah Reum, do you have an umbrella?
No.
Do you want to share mine?
We're going opposite ways though.
It's all right. It doesn't matter.
Let's go.
What do you think?
You got here thanks to me.
I'll get going.
I'm back.
Yes.
Clean your room.
Is your room a pigpen or something?
Give me a break.
I don't even have time to clean these days.
Take this.
Why did you take this out? Put it back.
What?
- Why is this here?
- I gave that
to your friend to look at when she was here.
Orabeoni Gu Jun was so cute when he was little.
Gu Hui was quite adorable too.
She became uglier as she grew up.
What...
What is this?
Gu Hui, what is this?
What?
What is it this time?
- What?
- Why did you show this to her? Why?
- Hey!
- Why?
You're no help to my life, you jerk.
I was going to tell Deok Hui everything.
How can I face her now?
I couldn't think that far.
Oh my gosh.
Who is it? Did you order something?
- No, I didn't.
- You didn't? What is it?
Who is it?
Why isn't anybody here?
What is this?
Did you order this?
What is it? I didn't order anything.
Really? Maybe Gu Hui left it outside.
I think I saw a letter inside. Look at it.
To Deok Hui
Does she think this will make me feel better?
Astro.
Merry Christmas, Deok Hui! Have a wonderful Cristmas!
Deok Hui, good luck on your exam.
Study hard, Deok Hui!
Happy birthday, Deok Hui!
I got these signed cards in advance to give them to you
on special occasions.
He was my oppa's close friend since we were young.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you earlier.
Because of his situation, everyone kept quiet,
so I couldn't say anything either.
But as I got close to you day by day,
I felt like I was doing you wrong, and it was distressing.
I was going to tell you that day,
but you happened to see the photos first.
Meeting you
was the best thing
in my life since entering high school.
Deok Hui,
please, forgive me.
Hello.
Oh.
Deok Hui, what are you doing? Why aren't you going inside?
Well,
I don't feel quite ready yet.
Why do you need to get ready for eating chicken?
- It's—
- Let's go in.
- Come on.
- All right.
What's wrong with them?
Maybe they got in a fight.
I'm not completely over it yet, you crook.
Thanks for coming anyway. I'm so glad.
Eun Woo Set is always delicious.
Eat as much as you want. For you, it's free forever.
Really? You better keep that promise.
Deok Hui, thank you.
My gosh.
- What's up with them?
- You're the best.
Are you all right?
Come here.
It's seriously free for you forever.
Thanks.
First of all, we need to help Eun Woo.
Yes, please help me, Deok Hui.
Shut up.
I'm not helping you. I'm helping Oppa, you crook.
Whoever is trying to tear him apart,
will definitely pay for it.
Let us show them.
The power of Aroha!
Enter.
Comrades, let us unite.
Who is important? Eun Woo is important.
- Who is important?
- Eun Woo!
- All right!
Let's do this! Let's go!
Let's go!
- Gosh.
- What's going on?
Let me see.
IP address lookup
IP tracker.
That's it. Yes.
Zoom in right here.
We're looking for sources regarding Eun Woo's scandal.
Hello?
Ho Gu Hui, we found the IP address of the initial source.
- Okay.
- The funny thing is...
it's the Internet café right next to Eun Woo's agency building.
This person kept changing their ID and leaving malicious comments.
The first ID used is "dmsdnzlf".
In the Korean keyboard, it's spelled out as "Eun Woo kill."
We're tracing their personal information.
"Eun Woo kill"?
- Okay.
- Yes.
Good work, Deok Hui.
Will you be the Revenge Goddess?
Enter target's name
dmsdnzlf
We will proceed with the revenge
Maybe Deok Hui really is the Master.
Wait, no.
Deok Hui would have made a move first.
I don't know.
I don't know who it is,
but please help!
Shocking idol scandal. Suspected to be dating minor
You have been selected as a revenge target.
Your misfortune will continue until the revenge is complete.
We can just check the hallway surveillance cameras.
We can compare the dates too.
All right then. Team A can check the cameras outside the building,
and Team B can take the inside. Let's move.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Are you the manager?
Yes.
Hello. Could I ask you something?
Yes, what is it?
Oh, this was broken.
Does that mean nothing got recorded?
It doesn't seem to be functioning well because it's so old.
I'm sorry.
I guess we can't do anything about it. Thank you anyway.
He looks strangely familiar.
E-Sports Internet Café.
I'll continue to put updates online.
I'll see you all later.
- Good work.
- Good work, everyone.
- Goodbye.
Is this the right roof?
I think it is.
I'm pretty sure the video showed this area.
Look harder. We might get more clues.
Isn't this the girl in the video?
Did you find something?
Search, choose face.
The account is deactivated now,
but when I ran the program, it seems to be the same person.
Special feature, possibly by plastic surgery
After their Asia concert tour,
Astro has finally landed home.
Regarding the scandal of Astro member Cha Eun Woo,
Cha Eun Woo's fans have gathered the sources of malicious comments
and have submitted them to a lawyer
to clarify any suspicions.
It is still in question whether it is simply a spiteful rumor
or a true unveiling of the idol star
wearing the mask of an angel.
The issue is being highlighted with their domestic concert coming up...
Oppa,
I'm getting nervous.
What if we actually get caught?
Pack your things and go to the States. Stay with your eonni for now.
Don't contact me for the time being. I'll follow you there you soon.
Okay.
The noisier it gets, the larger the amount will become.
I'll contact you soon.
Be careful, okay?
It's late.
I'll go and eat the Eun Woo Set
and then I'll go to the meeting.
Gosh, that scared me.
We could've just grabbed something near the hagwon*,
(*private cram school)
but you insist on having chicken again.
You're obsessed with chicken these days.
Hey, I've always liked chicken.
That is definitely a lie.
- What's this?
- What?
Isn't this...
- Did you get the license plate?
- What?
It's HA 13...
- It's 2745.
- Yes, 2745.
International Terminal
Departures.
Look over there.
HA 13
7544...
No, it's 2745.
I know.
Hey.
13 HA 2745
Hey,
call the police first just in case.
Okay.
Hello?
I'm calling because I think my friend has been kidnapped.
Where are we? We are...
in front of the Internet café.
It's at Chorongmaeul-ro 3-gil.
Please hurry.
Ben E-Sports Internet Café
Be quiet.
I'll keep you for half a day and let you go, so just stay still.
I told you to be quiet.
Who are you to ruin everything?
My life was ruined because of that punk.
Why are you getting involved?
If it wasn't for that punk,
you wouldn't be stuck here in an Internet café like this.
- Let go of me!
- Stay still!
Are you okay?
This is just crazy.
Hurry.
Let me go! Let go of me, you punk!
Why are you doing this? What did I do?
- Step aside!
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
Let me go!
Let go of me!
This isn't fair!
I don't deserve this! This isn't fair!
- How do you feel?
- This is unfair!
We have no time for that.
This is unfair!
Do you want to say something?
Wait a second!
I was walking with Ji Hun when we found the doll.
So I picked it up
and saw a car driving away.
I saw Deok Hui inside.
The doll must be precious to you.
Yes, it's the doll
of an idol group that I like.
I dropped it
and I guess these guys saw it.
And so...
Well,
my boyfriend was originally a member of Astro,
but he was replaced with Eun Woo.
He trained for a few years and never even got to debut.
Woman arrested for falsely accusing pop Idol Cha Eun Woo.
We were going to
split the settlement money.
Fans of Astro have played a big part in solving this incident.
Through the surveillance footage submitted by an anonymous individual
and a hacking program, they have obtained conclusive evidence.
- What a relief.
- The offender was
a trainee disqualified from Astro due to Cha Eun Woo.
His grudge led him to consistently post malicious comments,
and he even made up a false scandal for a large sum of settlement money.
He has come forward with his confession.
- Yes?
- Gu Hui,
it's me, Deok Hui.
Deok Hui, are you all right?
Yes, I'm all right.
But, Gu Hui,
could you please get me a ticket to the concert?
I couldn't get it.
Okay, I will.
I'll try to get one for you.
Thanks so much.
I love you, my friend.
Okay.
Woman arrested for falsely accusing pop Idol Cha Eun Woo.
Since Deok Hui was kidnapped,
it probably isn't her.
Then is it Eun Woo?
No way. Eun Woo was the victim.
I don't know. I'm getting more confused.
Your revenge is complete.
STAFF
I love Astro
- Astro!
- I love him.
Astro!
- I love them.
- I'm so nervous.
Let's go. I'm nervous.
Since I've got our tickets, you need to double my allowance.
All right. Gosh.
I'm so nervous. Should I keep my glasses on or off?
- Take them off.
- Ms. Jeong Deok Hui?
Yes?
This way, please.
What's going on?
- No!
- No way!
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
- Wait here for just a moment.
- Sure.
They're in there.
What do we do?
My heart is about to explode.
Have fun at the concert.
- You can come in now.
- Ah, yes.
They're over there.
- Hello.
You don't really have to eat it now. It might get on your shirt.
You have to do the concert.
It's amazing, Nuna*.
(*"elder sister", said by a male)
What did he just say? Nuna*?
(Normally, a married woman her age would be called "ajumma")
I also enjoyed the soy sauce marinated crab you gave me yesterday.
- It's so good.
- Nuna?
Nuna, take a picture with us.
Okay.
I'll be back.
- See you.
- What do I do?
There's the camera.
One, two, three.
Three.
You look so handsome.
One, two, three.
- Let's take one more. I think I blinked.
- Okay.
I'm sorry. My mom's a little weird.
No, it's all right.
I'm the one who's thankful.
By the way, are you all right? I heard you almost got hurt.
I'm all right. I'm perfectly fine.
After the concert, let's have chicken together
at Gu Hui's restaurant, oppa.
Sure. Let's definitely do that.
Yum.
~ Revenge Note 1 ~
[Preview]
I like Ji Hun. Can you help me out?
Look at her so obviously hitting on him.
Forget it. Don't do it.
Don't bring Gu Hui into this.
Wait and see. I'll make your life miserable.
You two look great together.
What do you mean, we broke up? We were just having a fight.
So please stop being interested in me.