The Long Ballad
Episode 15
I worked so hard to win half a pound of silver
and you bought this?
Half a pound of silver is enough to buy this
You're lying
I could buy three bags of rice the day before yesterday
Did you buy the silver again?
No
Did you buy it again?
I didn't
It's the same as when you hid the gold and silver treasure
I didn't find it
Did you not take it out even if you were dead?
I really didn't
I only sold these
after I got the name of the Mi family
on the night of the auspicious day
Look at your mouth
Come
It hurts
My edges are לא
and take care of the
You even made your father cry!
Why are you so pale?
I'm fine.
By the way, Doctor Ji,
how is Yuan?
He's still in a coma.
But he's much better now.
That's good.
Why are you blushing?
What's wrong?
Do you like him?
I don't.
I'm just concerned about him.
By the way,
how is the test of
the Spirit Snake Reconciliation Method I taught you?
I asked everyone in the County Office
to come to the Seven Flames Pavilion that night
and told them
there was a poisonous snake in the pavilion.
If they lied,
they would be buried in the pavilion.
The poisonous snake would bite them to death.
In fact, there was no poisonous snake in the pavilion.
Exactly.
If someone is guilty of being a thief,
he will put a hand of the snake on the hand of Liu Huang
in advance to dispel the poisonous snake.
As long as the hand of this person
is put in the medicinal herb water,
it will turn slightly red.
So...
The hand of the liar
turns red in the medicinal water,
right?
Yes.
But I've tested everyone in the County Office.
No one lied.
You've tested them all?
Yes.
All...
I don't know.
There's one more person.
Who?
Father.
You're overbearing!
You really dare...!
There was a poisonous snake in this pavilion,
the tangling looked ordinary.
If the liar puts his hand in the pavilion,
he would be bitten by it
and the poisonous snake would bite him to death.
And you are shopping
for the snake.
I may go now.
Do you dare to try it?
Where are you going again?
I'm going to deliver the medicine.
I'll be back in a while.
No, Brother.
硬要应该不说话
I don't sound right, either.
Wendy,
you're having an affair
with a man.
It's all rather useless to try
and resist your love
instead of it.
Dini,
He must have come to Suizhou.
It turns out that you are here.
The show is about to start.
What...
What are you doing here?
I don't know him.
He wanted to kill the people.
I...
You bitch!
I... I don't know him.
Who are you?
Get out of my way!
Or I'll kill you too!
How is it?
Is your heart healed?
It's done.
Doctor Ji,
you're really a good doctor.
Stop talking nonsense.
How did you deal with him?
There's a cry in the yard.
Really?
Ya'er,
stop talking nonsense.
There must be a chance to escape.
I'm still alive.
I finally got rid of this evil spirit.
But my illness
is gone with my illness.
I don't need to pay the debt.
I don't need to be beaten.
I'm scared.
His house,
his land,
his money, his life,
they're all mine.
They're all mine.
If anything happens to Dongchuan,
will you
blame me for everything?
No, no.
I swear I won't.
Why do I feel like
he can still move?
I'll kill you.
It's okay.
When I put the lid on,
no one will notice.
The last question.
What?
What is more annoying than love?
What are you doing?
It's hate.
Hate
is a thousand times more annoying than love.
It's like I'm thinking about you.
You...
You... You are...
How are you,
Sun Fengxi?
Gu Chacheng.
On the day of the wedding,
you didn't save me.
You even pushed me down the cliff.
I still remember
you were standing on the cliff
and counting money.
You're laughing.
Why aren't you laughing?
But I think
you look
prettier
than you are now.
They forced me.
Then you deserve to die.
If others ask,
you'll say
I forced you to kill your own husband.
No.
I can prove it for you.
I can prove you wrong.
I can tell the world.
I can tell them
you didn't kill him.
I...
That's not what I want.
I can give you
whatever you want.
What I want
is a good reward.
A good reward.
You too?
Help me.
I'm begging you.
The wind blows,
the dragon flies,
the river flows.
The sea of clouds,
me and you,
can only look out.
The sun,
the rain,
how can it escape from the clouds?
The wind,
the rain,
how can it escape from the clouds?
Can you and I
still look out?
The rain,
how can it escape from the clouds?
The past life,
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for you.
The wind,
how can it escape from the clouds?
I'm here to deliver medicine.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to
cover the wind and block the rain.
You're so talkative.
Black-smiled cat.
Black-smiled cat?
Are you scared?
No.
I thought
you were so bold
that nothing could scare you.
Black-smiled cat,
is it cold?
The cloud,
you're so worried.
Can it escape from the clouds?
The wind,
how can it escape from the clouds?
smoke the紅袍
into a smoke.
It's like bread
and eyes
is gazing at me.
I love you so much
and wish you
to remember it as our dream.
Make your political decision
I will help you
Time to set off
You guys should hurry
Farewell
Un travel
不到
Electrical
Mer precaution
Throw all at the river
Thanks for watching!