The Long Ballad
Episode 15
I can't kill you because of my old feelings.
I told you to leave the capital and never come back.
But you came back to me.
You are so bold.
Mrs. Qiu.
These years,
I told you about the princess'
words and habits.
And I blocked the disaster for you.
I came to remind you
to keep your promise.
You said...
As long as...
Shut up.
I will keep you rich and beautiful.
I have prepared the carriage.
You will leave the capital tonight.
Mrs. Qiu is so anxious.
Is she guilty of being a thief?
You mean I...
A thief?
Mrs. Ji thought you were the one who
poisoned the embroidery.
And you wanted to kill the princess.
If I want to testify for her,
I don't know how much she will pay me.
Just tell me.
How much do you want?
If I want to leave the capital,
you should prepare a house
where I live.
If you want a house,
you should hire three or five servants
to clean up the house.
If you want servants,
you should have a lot of money.
In exchange, I will tell you
I am not patient enough.
I don't even have
half a box of kung fu.
What's wrong?
My dear.
The King's Mansion
Steamed gourd.
What's the matter?
You are awake?
I am awake.
I am tired.
Tell me a joke.
Have you eaten lotus root?
I fried it with oil.
It tastes good.
Do you know how it came?
No.
How?
Long time ago,
Nezha offended the dragon king
and committed suicide.
He made lotus root with real people
to make his body.
The King of Meat grilled it with the firewood
to make the meat soup.
He gave it to his father,
Zhou Wenwang.
Today,
the firewood and Nezha
are in the sky.
They are a team.
They become a couple.
I don't want to eat lotus root.
I have a story about lotus root.
Okay.
Let's talk about something serious.
What's your plan?
I will go to Suizhou.
Suizhou is in heavy rain and flood.
Where are you going?
My father was killed by the rebels.
He was killed in an emergency.
He was killed by a thousand people.
I will go to collect the body.
I can't find a witness.
His name is Wang Bowei.
I suspect he knows the truth.
I have been looking for him for years.
But I couldn't find him.
But recently,
I received a secret message.
He is in Suizhou?
He has been hidden for long.
He should be killed.
If you want to go to Suizhou,
you have to show yourself.
The disaster relief?
Suizhou has many county counties.
The flood is so severe.
People are in need of food and shelter.
The people's lives are in danger.
Please send someone to help.
Three years ago,
I sent Song Hongjian to help.
In less than half a month,
he committed suicide.
He only left a confession letter.
The flood in Suizhou is unimaginable.
Minister Jiang,
in your opinion,
who can take the responsibility?
Zhou Junlan is in the court now.
He is a loyal man.
I'm afraid his confession
is already his responsibility.
But...
The water is slow, the fish is slow.
The moon is slow, the moon is slow.
He is young and powerful.
He will make His Majesty worry.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm just thinking,
if you want to go to Suizhou,
I will go with you.
Why?
Suizhou had a minister die before.
I'm a little worried that you will go alone.
Thank you.
For what?
You are loyal and intelligent.
You don't mind my loss of power.
I'm sorry for your hasty action.
You always help me.
You are right.
You are too kind.
I did this
to stop you from being jealous.
I'm glad to hear that.
Junlan.
The past is not to be traced.
Why repeat it?
You just need to remember
that I helped you get what you wanted.
I didn't do it for you.
You did it for me.
I was wrong.
Xian.
Isn't this the gift you gave to Xianyang?
Yes.
He has returned.
Why?
Maybe he is afraid of my teacher
because of Ji Yunzhao.
Don't you care?
You said he had the late emperor's edict.
Maybe he can help us in the future.
Why are you laughing?
I can't laugh.
You killed the maid of Qingyang an hour ago.
I helped you.
You are not afraid of the east window.
You are not afraid of the ghost.
You can still laugh.
My good husband.
I know you well.
The assistant minister of the court
is not afraid of the disaster
because of a crow's life.
You are just afraid
Pei Yan will take your post.
His Majesty is afraid of my power.
But the disaster in Suizhou is urgent.
There is no one in the court.
He should only ask me to go.
But he killed Pei Yan.
You can't live a good life.
Tomorrow,
who can go to Suizhou with Pei Yan?
I can understand the future.
But the future I know is in the heaven.
The heaven?
Why?
Butterfly effect.
What do you mean?
A butterfly's wings are shaking.
It may cause a storm
a thousand miles away.
A slight change
will make everything
unimaginable.
Who changed?
Gu Zhao Zhao.
I am the butterfly.
It is the wind storm
I made.
Enough. Stop laughing.
You are commanding me.
I just...
Laugh.
Qian.
Laugh until I am satisfied.
You want me to teach you everything?
Do you want me to teach you to laugh?
Kneel down.
Cute.
Gimme.
Open your eyes.
You mentioned just now
you are a dog who has lost a family.
What about the contdinance by original master?
I'm afraid I can't help you
How about
we work together?
Work together?
What can you give me?
Pei Yan
as long as we work together
I will help you achieve your dream
and live a peaceful life
Interesting
I want to go to Suizhou
but there is no way
to be a good person
But Minister Jiang won't recommend Zhou Junlan
Because of this
His Majesty will suspect that he is colluding with the city
He won't deny it
Because of this, His Majesty will suspect that he is a traitor
He will only recommend those
who are the lowest in the court
But you are one of them
What's more
Minister Jiang's daughter Jiang Yue
owes me a favor
She recommended me
His Majesty may not use me
My Lord
His Majesty wants you to come to the palace tomorrow
As long as I can face the victory
I will have a chance
Who gives him a chance?
Call the secretary of the central office
Zhou Junlan
Xuan Yinghong, Pei Yan
to come
I am here
Greetings, Your Majesty
As long as I can face the victory
I will have a chance
Who gives him a chance?
Prince
What do you want?
I help you to be a
Why?
To ascend the sky
Who?
Arise
Father, it's him
He is my savior
Give him to him
Why?
You are angry
So cute
Why?
Always be the White Night
Good
Suizhou is a dragon lake
This trip will never go back
never go back
zet
with you
What are you laughing at?
Ji Yunzhao
What's wrong?
Why is he following us?
He's a skilled doctor
He can solve the problem at critical moments
How about this?
It's boring to work so hard
Pei Yan
Are you still laughing?
I'm not laughing
I'm just laughing
Are you still laughing?
He?
He's laughing?
Dr. Ji
Do you like lotus root?
Yes
Oh, I brought some
Here, Yunzhao
Eat it while it's hot
I'm not eating
I'll eat it then
By the way
What joke are you going to tell me?
It's said that long ago
Nezha offended Dragon King
and committed suicide
I don't want lotus root anymore
dealing
Master
Chamberlain learning
What to do
No matter how bad you're
My lord
Your tip is a bit misaligned
Places that you are not well 두려
Thank you
My lord
If there is anything to do
Just order Yuan to do it
I heard that from Her Highness the Queen.
Please.
Hurry up!
Open the door!
Open the door! Is anyone there?
Someone help!
Open the door! Help!
Save the fire!
Open the door!
Hurry up! Save the fire!
Some more people go help out there!
Hurry up! Help!
Help!
Go over there! Hurry up!
Yunzhao!
My Lord!
Yunzhao! You can't go in!
Move!
A police officer has died recently!
You're also here to help?
Let me go!
No, My Lord!
Yunzhao!
My Lord!