Music
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
What do you want to investigate?
I can investigate as I want.
But you must bring me along.
Why?
No reason.
Ji Xiao,
isn't there in the imperial palace...
Uncle!
I'll take the bug and throw it out.
Who's on the list?
Zhao Yan?
No.
Then who is it?
No one.
Yunzhao,
you know when you lie,
you always like to look into people's eyes.
Just like now.
You're wrong.
Only those who are anxious
dare not look into other people's eyes.
You are Ji Yunzhao.
You are so calm,
so you can act in a different way.
That's why I'm so sure
that you are hiding something from me.
I'll tell you when the time is right.
What is it?
Like when people died in Suizhou in front of me.
Maybe.
This is not fair.
You know everything about me,
but I don't know you well.
Yunzhao,
you can keep secrets from me,
you can lie to me.
I won't force you to get rid of all the past.
I just want to know,
do you have to get involved in this?
Then on the list,
there's my name.
Is it just a name?
No.
That's Yin Jian.
Ceng Shi.
You can't go.
Chang'an is the most critical place to get involved.
What about Zhao Yan?
He's also on the list.
You forgot what you promised Zhao Meng.
If Zhao Yan goes to the dead end one day,
you'll help him.
I'll help him.
You can't go.
You can't go to the dead end.
You'll help him.
It's also good to help him get through this.
Yunzhao,
I promise you,
I'll do my best.
But you have to promise me,
you won't get involved in this.
Sorry,
I can't do it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to find the boat.
I got it.
You can leave.
Yes.
Is it really like what Xian said?
He's really innocent.
Impossible.
Sir,
Ji Yunzhao from the Jishi Hall is here.
Come in.
Yes.
You don't come to the San Bao Hall.
What brings you here?
I'm here to talk to you about a deal.
Tea and wine are good for your health.
I'm glad to hear that.
Sir,
Ji Yunzhao is not allowed to enter.
I'm not allowed to enter.
I'm just doing my job.
Just doing your job?
He's a good man.
My mother can't listen to him.
Madam, you can't...
Madam.
Sister Qiu,
you're from a noble family.
How can I treat you like a sister?
I'm here to deliver soup.
Get out.
I came first.
Yue'er.
She just married you.
She's your daughter.
Why do you treat her like this?
Beauty makes soup.
You're so lucky.
You said you can't drink.
That's right.
I didn't ask you to drink soup.
You didn't ask Jiang Yue to marry you.
I didn't ask you to meet Ji Yunzhao in private.
You didn't miss it.
You're spying on me.
You're mine.
I told them to take good care of me.
What's wrong with that?
Tell me.
What did he come to you for?
He's a good friend of mine.
He's involved with the Gu family in the South and North case.
He wants to investigate with me.
The Gu family?
He clearly wants to tell you that he's Gu Zhao Zhao.
He doesn't even want a family.
You think he cares about the Gu family's life?
He just wants to take the opportunity to see you.
He's just trying to break my teeth.
He said he's not Gu Zhao Zhao.
He's just a little bit like Master Gu.
A little bit like him.
What does he say? What do you believe?
Why don't you take him into the family?
I believe you.
I obey you.
And now I tell you.
I have no collusion with him.
Do you believe it?
You don't believe it.
In your heart,
how I say, how I do, how I think is never important.
What's important is yourself.
You think I'll do whatever I want.
Why?
Because I know my future.
But don't you have a time to lose your mind?
That's because you didn't do well enough.
I didn't do well enough.
You've always been the one to decide.
Why don't you let me decide?
If Jin Yunzhao can really help me get rid of that person,
what's the harm in cooperating with him?
Drink.
I don't drink.
Fine.
You're not obedient.
I'll change it.
There are 51 people in total.
One of the examiners.
11 people of the investigation officer.
A total of 63 people.
Pei Yan wants to know if there's any collusion between them.
At least 63 families have to be investigated.
Then we'll just go to his house before him.
And investigate the accounts.
That's what I meant.
But I don't know where to start.
Gu family?
You don't have to worry about me.
Pei Yan doesn't know that I have a marriage with the Gu family.
As far as I know,
he should investigate the accounts one by one.
Xu Ying has already investigated 3 or 4 households.
Let's start from the 5th household.
How about it?
Okay.
Come on.
The old man is a wolf-catching demon.
But my family's accounts have been confiscated by the Xuanying Marquis.
We're just one step behind him.
We have to take two steps ahead.
Only then can we be one step faster.
What a coincidence.
The Xuanying Marquis also asked me to take the accounts.
So the Xuanying Marquis took the accounts...
I'm sorry.
We've already messed up the order.
Why would he take the first step?
Someone can help him.
He can be a good man.
You mean...
Your wife.
No need to make a fuss.
Let's go to the Gu family.
They might be waiting for us.
He's waiting for us?
Maybe he thinks that I took his accounts and he wants mine.
He's not good enough to be in the palm of my hand.
He's still so arrogant.
Let me see him.
Mr. Zhou.
You have the ambition to be a red fox.
But you're trapped in this place.
Don't you want to find another way out?
Find another way out?
Life is like a fire in the morning.
How long can you live?
Mr. Zhou.
Please think twice.
Let's go.
It seems that he's more interested than I thought.
Mrs. Ji.
What a coincidence.
There are many bars in the capital.
But I'm the one who chose to meet at my bar.
I don't know if it's a coincidence
or some stupid thing
that's deliberately attracting people's attention.
Qiao Xian.
Which stupid thing is the right thing to do?
As far as I know,
there are some people in the bar who are from the Gu family.
I'm afraid it's not appropriate to say that it's yours.
The Gu family has no queen.
I'm the only goddaughter that my aunt has.
The current one is from the Gu family.
It's still from the Gu family.
In the future,
it's not a good thing.
I've been to the Gu family.
You two
don't have to go there anymore.
Mr. Fang,
pack up your luggage.
Don't treat your guests well.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To the Gu family.
But...
Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
Mr. Zhou,
Mrs. Ji,
please go back.
The accounts of the Gu family
have been handed over to the Marquis of Xuanying.
I'm sorry.
The Marquis of Xuanying has to make a decision.
But as far as I know,
the Gu family has been in business for generations.
Mr. Gu is always cautious.
He always keeps a record.
Even the accounts
have to be kept.
How did you hear that?
It's just a rumor.
Did my son
tell Mr. Zhou?
Mr. Zhou
told you?
Why did you say that?
Mrs. Ji made a marriage contract with someone else.
How can she be separated from her husband?
The Marquis of Xuanying is your fiancee.
You should take good care of her.
How can you let her go?
She can't go with her husband.
And Mr. Zhou,
it's inevitable for a couple to meet.
You should be more tolerant.
Give it to them.
Don't worry, Mrs. Ji.
Just check the accounts.
I'm right.
It's a long story.
It's suspicious.
If they want to investigate,
just give it to them.
Right.
I was wrong.
There were many problems.
Please forgive me.
Mrs. Ji, please be serious.
Mr. Zhou, please wait a moment.
Mrs. Ji,
please come with me.
This is it.
I have one more thing to ask you.
Please.
You have done a good job.
Why do you still want to get the title?
Do you know what this is?
Feng Ling.
I have a daughter.
Her name is Zhao Zhao.
She was naughty and naughty when she was a child.
She was often punished by her mother.
She was afraid of pain.
She cried when she was hurt.
I cried so much that I couldn't drink tea
or check the accounts.
I had to think of a way to make her happy.
I couldn't check the accounts.
I had to think of a way
to get her all kinds of things back.
Later I found out
that she liked Feng Ling the most.
When she heard the sound of the bell,
she smiled.
She smiled and forgot to move.
She was in a daze.
She ran away.
I don't know where she ran to.
I wanted to find her.
But everyone said
that she ran away.
On the night of the wedding,
she ran away with a man.
She lost the dignity of the Gu family and the Zhou family.
Why bother to find her?
Zhou Shi Lang didn't want to find her.
He didn't let me go either.
How dare I not doubt her?
I am ashamed to face the grudge.
In this case,
Mr. Gu is just trying to prove himself because of Xu Nu.
If I am the one who is in charge of Tao Tian,
I can protect her.
I won't let her wander around
and have no home.
I will not let her go.
You are a good man.
You have been a doctor for many years.
Have you ever seen a woman
who looks like you
and is called Zhao Zhao?
I have seen her.
She...
She is good.
Many people have told me
that I look like her.
But I have never seen her.
I don't know if she is doing well.
It's also the same.
It's the same.
If one day we meet,
will you give me flowers?
I will give them to her.
Just say that
I look like her
when I am with her mother.
Okay.
I will remember it.
I will send this account book
to the Zhou family later.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
The End