(Don't Forget Me)
(Episode 5)
Master Anren, I thought you
could become the head of the Shen family.
That's why I persuaded others
to strongly support you in temporarily being
the chairman of the Haidu Chamber of Commerce.
But given the current situation,
we are in an embarrassing position.
Don't worry, Mr. Qian.
I'm the only one who can be the head of the Shen family.
But now, this...
Master Anren,
how can I accept this?
You just need to help me keep
those merchants in the chamber of commerce calm.
As long as I can become the chairman,
the promises I made to you before will still stand.
Come on.
-Cheers.
Master Anren, you've given me such a generous gift.
If I don't return the favor,
I'd lose face, right?
A few days ago, I won
an excellent western watch in the gambling house.
I wanted to keep it for myself,
but now I'm giving it to you.
Thank you, Mr. Qian.
This watch suits me perfectly.
You really know how to play the game.
When your father was the chairman,
many things were not allowed.
Now it's so difficult to do business.
Yes.
Some deals might not be above board,
but they're profitable.
Don't worry, Mr. Qian.
Now, as long as we can
get rid of Shen Zheng,
we'll be able to make a lot of money.
Come on.
Bottoms up.
Master, Governor Shen is here.
Governor Shen?
Why is he here?
Governor Shen is very busy.
Stop.
Why did he come at this moment?
Have you seen the Extinguishing Lampshade?
No.
Governor Shen, welcome.
Your presence brings honor to my humble abode.
I just took up my post in Haidu.
Mr. Qian, I've heard a lot
about your reputation in Haidu.
So I specially came today to pay my respects.
I'm flattered.
This is a gift for you.
Thank you.
But now it seems
you're quite busy today.
Not at all.
I usually love to dance.
So I invited a few friends here to have fun.
Right,
Master Anren came to discuss official business with me.
So I invited him to join us.
Brother, if I had known you'd come,
I would have come with you.
No need for that.
This is...
I am his...
Fiancée.
Brother, when did you get engaged?
Why didn't I know?
It's my business.
Do I need your permission?
Governor, since you are here,
let's dance together.
I'll go prepare some dishes.
Let's have dinner together tonight, okay?
Okay.
I'll go make preparations.
Please make yourself at home, Governor.
I sensed it was
in Mr. Qian's house.
How did it suddenly end up in Shen Anren's hands?
Looks like their relationship is not ordinary.
Let me go over there now.
I can't wait any longer.
Sister.
Sorry.
It's alright.
Governor Shen,
you are so handsome.
Shut up.
Sister,
are you really engaged to my brother?
You want to know?
Then you'll have to trade something for it.
Okay.
But it's not convenient to talk here.
Let's go somewhere else.
Okay.
Governor Shen.
You said you'd help me get the fragments.
But you're so close to another woman.
The place up ahead
is where Sister and I first met.
If she really is her, she'll definitely remember.
Sister.
You're unlucky.
I'm in a bad mood now.
Why hasn't she come back yet?
Governor.
Governor?
Just do as you just said.
Yes, sir.
By the way, what did you just say?
I...
Governor,
I think you're in a bad mood.
Is it because of Ms. Qin?
I saw everything at the banquet.
Governor, since you have feelings for Ms. Qin,
why don't you give her some flowers
and take the opportunity to coax her
and confess your love for her?
It's so late.
He hasn't even come to look for me.
He's not even worried about me.
Jerk.
Miss, are you satisfied with this lantern?
We have new styles too.
Take another look.
Forget it.
Considering you bought lanterns for me,
I'll let it go this time.
Why am I doing this?
Oh no, he's in danger!
Shen Zheng, someone wants you dead.
Die!
Let's go!
What's going on?
Why has my power been consumed so much?
Are you alright?
The bruises on their bodies
were caused by you?
Yes.
How else could I save you without using that technique?
You killed my father.
I...