Use the Q&A app to make a good decision
Use the Q&A app to write good wishes
Use the Q&A app to present good videos
Use the Q&A app to travel well
Use the Q&A app to answer smart questions
Use the Q&A app to answer the most powerful model AI assistant
This year, 5 blessings are one more blessing
A-Fu gives you a health blessing
Wow
Wow, there's a red envelope
Health is a blessing, ask A-Fu about health
Download the A-Fu app
Go to Alipay to get a red envelope
If you miss something, you can meet good luck
Upgrade clean ingredients, full of yellow rice and sweet fragrance
Delicious in all directions, cool and hot, suit your heart
Missing one bite, good luck
The new year's chase has 100 micro
The horse year has a rush, 100 micro invites you to watch
Exciting collection
Classic organic
For the person you love
Wipe the toilet
Dry and cool, breathable
New Wipe, refresh experience
The King's Avatar
Episode 1
Huaijin
Father
Why are you here?
The government officials are not allowed to enter the Taishi Bureau
You haven't returned home for five years
You and my father
We are both in the Western Jin City
And we are both in the court
I didn't expect
The meeting is so difficult
Before I came to the Taishi Bureau
I knew this
I know
Taishi Bureau officials
Can't come to the government
Even father and son can't
But the body
Is allowed to go home and invite relatives
You can't go back
I don't want to see you
What?
You want to kick me out now
Or report to the body?
Father
There must be something important
I don't know the case
The body
Let you help
The internal investigation
The investigation?
Father is still messing around
You mean
It's the County Magistrate Fuchang
He didn't recognize me
Maybe he did as the people said
I don't remember what happened that night
But the County Magistrate
Never asked anyone else to investigate
Why did you
Stay with him?
Father means
He pretended to be a corpse
The County Magistrate
Smart and sensitive
Deep in thought
Whether he remembers
You should stay with him
Keep distance
Father
Are you ashamed?
You're blaming me
I told you
Back then
I had no other choice
I have no choice
You don't want to
It's okay
But I
I'm thinking about you
It's getting late
I can't even go to the Grand Division
Xiao Qing can't stop you
I admire you
Xiao Qing
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 16
Why is Grand Preceptor here?
It has nothing to do with him.
I've been following him.
He didn't finish his work.
I'm here to see him.
Do you know her?
Grand Preceptor Chen Paixin?
She's a young maid.
Her name is Jiu Niang Cui Man Shu.
Yuan Lu is going to talk to her tomorrow.
I'm going to talk to her.
The blood is still dry.
The murderer has no effect.
The suspect found beside the stage
is all the blood in the palace.
The Taoism Grandmaster
You go that way.
You still suspect me?
I've never suspected you.
You can believe me.
You're the one who said Yuan Di and Hou Jia Yin.
This yard is not marked on the map.
I passed by here with Gu Si just now.
It's very close to the water area.
The place is not far from here.
But there's no sign on the map.
It's so hidden.
It must be the murderer who chose it.
I heard someone can find people with one trick.
Grand Preceptor Chen Jing also has such a skill.
I really didn't see the wrong person.
Is there any other clue?
The suspect is missing.
That's all for now.
Do you want to check it yourself?
Grand Preceptor Chen, please avoid.
The blood of the victim is flowing out of the wound.
With one stab in the chest,
it will take so much blood to leave a deep wound.
The person who killed you must hate you very much.
Who is he?
Three years later
The woman in the wedding dress is very pretty
What a pity
The Aburning unfortunate chronicles
It was destroyed.
Edicts IGN Recovery
This hormone content
Tertiary stations
go to knobs
What is the cause of the tumor treateng?
Tertiary stations
Come in.
There are firedrops.
Be careful.
volume
The firework on the stage is the same.
This small courtyard is indeed a place where the murderer hid.
From the look of these
The person has six limbs.
But because there are only hidden marks,
it is not possible to confirm that these footprints are common people.
Tomorrow, I will go to the Prime Minister's mansion.
To investigate the reason for the missing girl,
why she wore a wedding dress and appeared here.
A Yan!
Wan Shuai!
Mother!
A Yan!
You still came in?
Where is the real scroll?
There has always been only this scroll.
Fifteen years ago, on the night of Yuan,
King Duan was in a battle.
He was out of spirit.
The family's suffering and old age have led to a great madness.
He killed the whole family.
Then he committed suicide.
He was killed by the murderer.
That day, King Duan's only daughter, Li Peiyi,
was sick and was sent to the palace.
She was saved from the disaster.
Just because I lost the memory of that day,
all of you are lying to me.
The truth is like this.
Why would I lie to you?
That day, you had a fever and you were sent to the palace.
You were unconscious for three days and nights.
You were awake.
You were awake for three days and nights.
The tragedy had already happened.
It's normal that you don't remember.
His Majesty didn't want to tell you this.
Later, you kept asking.
His Majesty still couldn't bear it.
These words,
I've told you so many times over the past ten years.
Why don't you believe me?
Because Father wouldn't be so wild.
He wouldn't kill Mother.
There are things you don't want to believe.
It doesn't mean he wouldn't believe you.
It doesn't mean he wouldn't kill you.
Father, this case has been concluded.
Instead of being obsessed with the truth of the past,
it's better to get up and find the murderer who killed the princess.
Keep it.
The second happiness starts.
The next life is like a dream.
Lock the warmth with the wool.
The coordinates are determined by the mood.
Break the fire and fly to the second island.
The second snow is the eye of the eye.
If it's not suitable,
you can get it for free.
As a taste, search for white deer. New Spring New Year.
The super price is here.
No more roses.
How about using the moon sword?
This green sword is a rose.
Come on.
New rose.
The flower is fresh and the sword is clean.
New Year's Eve,
don't you need to wear white crowns?
The country's first fashion brand.
New Year's Eve, of course, white crown.
Star Fruits White Crown.
The sword is out.
I remember Manshu again.
I'm sorry.
If you want to meet me, you don't have to be polite.
I can sit here.
Okay.
Is the princess okay?
Manshu died.
I'm a brother.
I'm worried about your wound.
You must be very sad.
Two girls died in one night.
Your Majesty, I'm angry.
I'm not hurt.
I'm also heartbroken.
The late Chu and the late Taishi city
are so concerned about Manshu.
I'm grateful.
It's time for dinner.
A simple meal.
Please enjoy.
If you have anything else you want to know,
you can ask someone in the mansion.
Manёзu.
Yes?
ore picture
I can imagine.
Prince.
,
Did you go out?
I went back to the Prime Minister's mansion last night
But Yan Shoufang was killed
Yan Shoufang is very far from the Prime Minister's mansion
If Jiu Niang didn't go out by horse
Then she was taken away from the Prime Minister's mansion
And taken to Yan Shoufang
The Prime Minister's mansion is heavily guarded
It's impossible that someone would take the lady
Whose carriage did Jiu Niang take last night?
Be honest
Or I'll kill you
It's me
I took Jiu Niang to Yan Shoufang
After entering Yan Shoufang
Jiu Niang asked me to park the carriage outside the house
Then she got off the carriage
Then she asked me to go back
Is there anyone else in that little house?
Seven black pieces
There should be no one
On the way
Especially in Yan Shoufang
You can see a man in a single shape
Six feet tall
With a
I don't understand what they're saying
You have to help him
I dare not
You served Jiu Niang yesterday
Yes
Did she have any contact with anyone recently?
Or have a private letter?
My Lady
The servant can't forget the master's
This is a case of investigation
Not a case of discussion
My Lady
The Prime Minister really can't say
Can't say
Then you know
I don't know
Ok
Sisters, get up
Go and invite the mother in
Tell her
The girls are very clear
Yes
Please have mercy on me
I really don't know anything
I really didn't say anything
If you are driven out of the prime minister's house
I can only go to the Western City Shadow House
That kind of place to help
Then the servant really has no way to live
Jiu Niang, please
Found it
This is the original number of the house
The number that belonged to the first rich household
This number is short
The house is empty
No one dares to live
Later, Yichu gave a merchant
We finally found that merchant
And said that the house was rented to a
A soldier named Guo Hua
Did you find Guo Hua?
No
But I brought the contract from the merchant
Didn't you ask for the silver?
Waiting for you
You are so kind
Madam, give me a bowl of silver
Ok
The sisters from the Prime Minister's house asked me to find you
Cui Jiu Niang is injured
Madam, sit down
How did he die?
Murder
God has eyes
This is the most responsible
My name is Li Niang
This face is given by her
This is Yun Jian embroidery
I sold you to a man
But you can't even make it
This thread
Say something
When I was dizzy
I was careless
Then you sewed two yellow threads for me
You think I can't see it, right?
I'm not a woman
I'm a woman
You can't even sew it, right?
Since you are so clumsy
I'll teach you a good lesson
Little lady
What are you doing?
Little lady, please spare my life
Let go
What are you doing here?
Come and press her down
Come here
Little lady, please spare my life
Let go
Little lady
Press it down
Only the old donkey can do the work
I'm afraid I can't even wear a decent dress to support you
We are the nobles
I hate to kill him
But there are too many people who want his life
Why can't I?
The heaven is full of the righteous
His rich and wealthy life
I guess it's over
Life is really getting more and more rebellious
He is so human
The enemy is not rare
How to get friends
Stinky
Who are they?
Birthday
What's wrong?
Did Cui Jiu Niang mention the 15th Princess?
Of course.
Cui Jiu Niang is so domineering
and has bullied so many people.
Only the 15th Princess
let her eat other people.
So when she mentioned the 15th Princess,
she bit her teeth.
What happened?
I only heard that
Cui Jiu Niang bullied others
and was punished by the 15th Princess.
But what exactly happened?
No one around her dared to say.
After so many years,
someone finally
can punish this evil person.
The princess
will have good revenge.
She really deserves it.
If there is no solid evidence,
it's difficult for you to
interrogate these three people
in the name of Dali Temple.
The family of the powerful
usually focuses on face.
It's not good for both parties
to come to the door rashly.
The spicy pork in Yun Chui House is just right.
Five people, go to the third room on the ground.
I'll be there soon.
Why does the princess suddenly want to eat spicy pork?
The princess means
to pay respects to her three brothers
in the name of her.
She is invited to Yun Chui House
as a normal culture.
Low-key and decent.
Maybe it can reduce the wind.
It's so familiar.
The murderer can easily
transport the fire to the palace
without being discovered.
It must be a little skillful.
I'll go check it out.
The Imperial Household Department is full of people.
The princess is worried that she will accidentally go there
and cause trouble to Third Madam.
The Imperial Household Department has sent people to urge.
I dare not stay at home.
You ordered so many dishes.
The spicy pork is so delicious.
I'm so full.
I'm full.
It's not bad.
Did you see Cui Jiu last night?
Did you say you wanted to chat with me?
Why do you think I'm a criminal?
Why are you so
Do you know
why Cui Jiu went to the Yan Shou House?
Did she mention it to you before?
The nobles in the east of the city all say
that you should walk on the street of the pig.
You should have a little more dignity.
Not to mention
the place of the Yu Long mixed with Yan Shou House.
Man Shu will never go there.
Do you know
what's the relationship between her and the 15th princess?
I don't know.
Isn't He Lan here too?
Go ask him.
He is the closest to Man Shu.
Man Shu won't tell us some things.
But He Lan knows it.
Su He Xiang.
It's really good.
How is the annual goods in Chuxi?
There are not much money in the house.
I really don't have any discount.
No discount?
There is a discount.
The Tian Meng has a discount.
The annual goods are here.
Tian Meng's annual goods are really good.
There are more discounts.
This one has a discount.
This one also has a discount.
Everyone has a discount.
No discount.
Go to Taobao to buy annual goods.
Have fun and have a discount.
Theresa, are these the New Year gifts for Consort Shu?
The usual use in the palace
is behind every day
when you studio最正时,你统一入宫。
The daysition of Taishi City
besides using for every day
was to return the gifts artwork
for the palaces of Prince He.
andト procreative dress,
hexideals, and stock,
as well as the New Year gift for Consort Shu.
Miss Zhou,
do you give her gifts
every year?
In the past years,
only on her birthday.
This is the first time this year.
And I gave her three times.
Cui Man Shu and Yu Hai have nothing to do with me.
I want to go home.
Aren't you sisters?
She is the younger niece.
You are so generous.
I'm just a girl
who likes to fight with swords.
I'm not a stranger.
You raise your child like a nose.
Being a daughter,
for your master's sake,
you are also very kind
to your ninth aunt.
There's nothing to be embarrassed about.
Even that third aunt Wang said
Cui Man Shu is the best for you.
She told you a lot of things.
I always thought the county magistrate was smart.
I didn't expect
he was also a person from the Su family.
It's pointless to say more.
Goodbye.
Cui Man Shu is so stubborn.
He's just wasting his time.
Su He Xiang, who was awarded by Shu Fei,
Wang Yu Hua and Zhao Luo Shun
both have a share.
But you don't.
Cui Man Shu is always arrogant.
He never talks to
or teaches me.
You don't admit to being friends with him
because he only has feelings for you.
He has no feelings for you.
You're right.
Cui Man Shu is arrogant
and is easily deceived.
Of course.
I didn't want to be friends with him.
One day,
my father came back from the Prime Minister's mansion.
He was so drunk that he couldn't recognize me.
I only found out later
that the Prime Minister heard that I was a girl of high rank.
He didn't want to talk to my ninth aunt.
He made my ninth aunt cry.
So he invited my father
to solve the misunderstanding in the mansion.
There was no misunderstanding.
He just wanted my father to express his feelings
and teach me well.
We should get along well.
We should be sisters.
My father kept apologizing that night.
He was so drunk that he even choked.
My father didn't want me to be embarrassed.
It was my mother who couldn't help it.
She begged me to be safe for the Zhou family.
I had to be friends with Cui Man Shu
even if I did something wrong.
You're so stubborn.
Why are you standing there?
Pour some water for us.
Bring me the cakes.
He doesn't need me to be his friend.
He just wants me to be humiliated by him.
I can only do that
for my father.
But I didn't expect
that because he insulted me,
I didn't work for him,
and I would be hated by him.
It was Cui Man Shu's birthday that day.
I've made a red and red
tiger skin factory early in the morning
to give it to her.
Jiu Niang, this red and red tiger skin
is very rare.
Helan has been looking for a long time
to make such a factory.
I hope you can make it.
Mrs. Zhou,
the fur collar is very soft.
Jiu Niang is really a good person.
The so-called night is like a ball.
The fur on the collar
is made by a fox
who has just been bought for a year.
You're so bold.
Chen Man Shu, what are you doing?
I'm urging Jiu Niang to celebrate her birthday.
You're going to give me a fur collar
to celebrate her birthday?
Do you know
that the mother's surname is Hu
and the current Prime Minister's surname is Mu?
It's a great disaster.
It's very serious.
Don't make me lose my life.
Jiu Niang,
I didn't mean it.
We can't afford to take this charge.
If I didn't get along with Helan,
I would have made a scene in front of Consort Shu.
That would be a big crime.
Jiu Niang,
I'm willing to take any punishment.
But you can't let Consort Shu
and the Prime Minister know.
Really?
Any punishment?
Really.
Okay.
Then you can
bow to me
here.
You can only kneel to the heaven and the earth.
Why should you kneel to your parents?
Why should you kneel to your family?
No.
Okay.
Jiu Niang.
I'm willing to.
Please don't blame me
for being angry.
If you have anything to blame me,
don't make it difficult for my mother.
No matter what,
she's your regular concubine.
I'll be the one to blame her.
200 times.
I'll be the one to blame your family.
I wish you a happy family.
May you have a happy life.
Helan.
Your Highness.
Although you often insult others,
I heard that
the 15th Princess
once scolded her
and made her lose face in public.
Do you know why?
I don't know.
It seems that there are
many people who know this.
Do you know
why Cui Man Shu
went to Yan Shou Fang last night?
I don't know.
Give me your hand.
What?
You always
get bullied by Cui Man Shu
for not losing face.
Let me see
when you can meet a noble woman
who is too lazy.
You know how to read people's hands?
I know a lot.
On the 10th day,
there were only two cars
from the Zhou family.
There are records of people
who entered the Ministry of War.
One person was in the same team
and the other was in the same team.
There will be no mistake.
This is called Guan Gui County.
It's a place where you can find good people.
There are good people in the people.
It's hard to say
if you are a noble person.
Even if you know
how your fate is,
you still have to
go through it yourself.
Don't read it.
I haven't finished reading it.
He Lan,
you and Cui Man Shu
are not yet married.
There are secrets
that are hidden in your heart.
Nonsense.
I don't want to talk nonsense with you.
I want to go home.
You have been practicing
the relationship between Li Pian Qing and Cui Man Shu
from the beginning.
I know you are bullied by Cui Man Shu
and humiliated.
It's easy to see
in this world.
The real purpose of your relationship with Pian Qing
is to hide
things that are bad for you.
I gave you a chance.
If you don't say it,
I'll have to see it from your hand.
What can I see from my hand?
Of course you can see it.
This contract
is a reverse-propagation
of the right hand index.
Your right hand index
is also a reverse-propagation.
You rented the yard of Yan Shou Fang.
Why don't you admit it?
I didn't ask.
I don't have an index.
How can I prove it?
The index is unique.
Your index
is more unique.
It's okay if you don't want to admit it.
I'll go
and find that Hu Shang now.
Let him see this soldier,
Bo Huang.
Yes.
Wait.
What if I rent it?
Cui Man Shu's death
has nothing to do with me.
I went back to the mansion last night
and practiced swordplay with A Ye.
The Zhou family
can testify for me.
Cui Man Shu's death
has nothing to do with Zhou Xiao Niangzi.
What about the death of the 15th princess?
I checked the records
of the entrance of the palace this month.
On the 10th,
Zhou family sent
30% of the concubines.
But there were only two cars
that entered the palace that day.
One car
disappeared from the gate
to the concubines' palace.
Coincidentally,
someone saw Zhou Xiao Niangzi
going to the side door
with a car.
As for the thing in the car,
is it a gun?
I think the person
will figure it out soon.
No.
The death of the 15th princess
has nothing to do with me.
Cui Man Shu
married the 15th princess.
That's the day
Mother and I were humiliated.
Hurry up.
Don't delay my birthday banquet.
Wait.
15th Princess is here too.
Get up first.
This green pear is very fresh.
Just now, Jiongniang
treated us better.
His Majesty and Consort Shu also like it.
But His Majesty never asked
what the etiquette of the green pear is.
Jiongniang's loyalty
is clearly seen.
But His Majesty is so generous.
Jiongniang, please be generous too.
Since 15th Princess pleaded,
I'll spare you this time.
I'll go and get it.
What are you looking at?
Why aren't you opening your shoes?
Stupid thing.
Take your mother back to rest.
You're tired today.
Go back and rest early.
15th Princess saved my mother
and treated her as a thorn in her eye.
She kept insulting me
and trying to get revenge
on 15th Princess.
One day,
she suddenly found out
what the secret of 15th Princess was.
Every few days,
she secretly discussed with Wang Zhao
about what 15th Princess did.
If this gets out,
go to the yard and pick some flowers.
The flowers in the house have all withered.
They never
told me about this.
But one day,
she suddenly told me
that 15th Princess was going to have a big wedding.
She asked me to congratulate her.
Every few days,
she spread the news that 15th Princess
was going to get married.
Cui Man told me to do as she said.
Zhou Helan,
why didn't you tell me about this?
I...
Say it.
After I found out about this,
I prayed day and night
to ask 15th Princess to marry a good man
and stay away from the dispute.
But Cui Man
asked me to rent a house for her.
I found out that on the day of the wedding,
she met 15th Princess.
Although I don't know what they said,
the Princess
seemed to be going to His Majesty for a decision.
I was worried that I might be implicated.
I was too worried.
So I had to do as Cui Man said.
I pretended to be a man
and rented a private house
in the Yan Shou Fang.
At that time,
my parents were very happy.
They said they finally had a chance
to see Consort Shu.
They asked me to go to the palace
and give her a birthday gift.
My parents
prepared a lot of gifts.
But when I was about to go to the palace,
Cui Man
suddenly asked me to send a cart of things
to the side door of the palace.
She didn't allow me to see it.
I didn't dare to see it or ask about it.
I had to do as Cui Man said.
But the more I thought about it, the more I was afraid.
I had to peek.
It was the gunpowder.
But you don't know what the gunpowder is for.
What good can it do?
But it's too late.
The black paper
is the carriage of my Zhou family.
Although I was afraid,
I didn't dare to ask.
Until the day of the Shangyuan Festival.
I was scared.
I didn't know then
why he asked me to send the gunpowder to the palace.
I asked him if he did it.
Even the princess dared to kill him. He was crazy.
But he actually told me
it's better to die like this.
So you had a chance to stop it.
But you did nothing.
Right?
I didn't dare.
I was bullied for too long.
I don't know how to resist.
You pretended to be hurt and played with me.
But you know very well that you're helping the evil.
You know very well that those gunpowder
can kill a person.
As long as this person is not yourself,
not your parents,
it's none of your business.
Otherwise,
do you want me to die for the princess?
Do you want me to watch my parents
being bullied?
You've never been bullied like this.
You're the princess.
You're favored by His Majesty and Consort Shu.
You wouldn't say that.
You're innocent.
You wouldn't know
how it feels to have your parents
being bullied by others.
What does it feel like?
It's rude.
I'm ungrateful.
I saved the wrong person.
Whatever you say.
I'm ungrateful.
I help the evil.
As long as I don't die in the hands of Cui Man Shu,
you'll tie me up,
send the Ministry of Justice to arrest the Celestial Wolf.
I'll admit it if you ask me for three times.
As long as I'm in so much trouble,
listen to me.
Why did Cui Man Shu go to the Yuan Shou Fang?
I don't know.
I'm only responsible for the rental.
I've never been there.
The gunpowder that you made alone
can't kill the princess on the banquet.
Do you have any other accomplices?
Who is he?
Cui Man Shu won't let him know.
No one shall be touching my parents' throws.
Kelly,
I'm sorry to the Create Deception vault.
I'll get to the ends of theay.
Even my parents...
Xiaoduo.
Hold me.
Wang Dao and two women suddenly fainted.
Go to Zhao Laoshun's.
Weixiang wants to play.
The right hand is injured.
Zhong Chong, squeeze and release the blood.
Hurry up.
It's too late.
The blood is poisonous.
It's the poison of the Wudu.
The eight-day wind
is strong.
Take away all the people who have eaten these food.
Yes.
The county head just ate these dishes with the royal mother.
The county head didn't eat the cut.
The county head's back is very clean.
There is no
I didn't touch this dish.
The county head, the Wang family's little mother has not returned yet.
Mrs. Wang is looking for it downstairs.
Trouble.
We've been in there for so long.
Why don't you come out?
What should I do?
Go in and see.
You crowdess.
If you can't get everyone estaba.
You go search for the poison cr temporarily.
äm
Hurry up and go.
Go quickly.
Mommy.
There's no more time.
What I said just now, does he still remember?
What?
Right hand, right hand, middle, squeeze, and then release.
If you want to turn from black to red, I'll save you.
If you don't,
Your Highness!
It's up to you.
Daughter! Daughter!
Daughter!
I've been waiting for you for so long!
After an hour,
you've become like this.
Lady Wuchang, can you tell me
what's going on?
Your daughter was poisoned.
I'm investigating the person who poisoned her.
Li Pei Yin,
I call you Lady.
I have some respect for you.
My daughter shouldn't have come here.
She wanted to cooperate with you to help you investigate the case.
But she died in your hands.
If you didn't take her to the cemetery,
how could she die?
You actually...
You actually have an attitude of not caring about anything.
Lady, the County Lady is also concerned about the case.
Lady, why don't you take her back to the manor first and return her to her senses?
Also, let the County Lady investigate this case for you.
Investigate the real murderer?
Can the investigation of the murderer bring back my daughter?
Today, you all will definitely give a good answer
to all of us!
What answer do you want?
I'm crazy!
I'll go to the manor and fight you!
Who dares?
My Lady!
Ding Gui Er Qi Tian
Foreign Use of Cure
33-year-old Children's Medicine
Beauty and the Beast
Chinese TV Series Exclusive YouTube
Why should I be angry?
I want to be a man of my word
When I see your beautiful eyes, the moonlight is Surviveless
I wait to hear the thunderous thunder
and watch the truth Savior
I wait to hear the ruin and então what are you per army with
I know such a man showed in the past
Do not trust on communities
Sub hindsight pedal
The
Tr Amelia
name