[Kill My Sins]
[This is a work of fiction]
Isn't it pleasant?
We're lying here, enjoying the breeze.
It seems like
everything is calming down.
When you are in a bad mood,
you are welcome to come
and enjoy the peace only found here.
Sure.
[Episode 25]
[Find the Right Remedy]
Lass,
don't worry. You can stay here tonight.
Tomorrow, I will give you some money,
so that you can go home.
Where do you live?
Tongquan.
Tongquan?
It sounds familiar.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It reminds me
of an old friend.
He was from there, too.
It is far away from here.
Lass,
you were robbed.
It's better to report it.
I don't want to do that.
Why not?
I hate the officials.
Years ago,
my sister
was taken by an official.
The house she stayed in was set on fire,
and she was nearly burnt to death.
Later,
she was forced
to jump off a cliff
and died.
My parents
went through a lot
while raising my sister.
It was very difficult for them
to handle all these.
Do you think
I can trust any official?
Right.
It was
a lot
to bear.
[Dongqiao Salt Granary]
Where is he?
Over there.
Why is he
so persistent?
This...
General Wu!
Sir,
what brings you here again?
About the salt,
you've checked by yourself.
You aren't going to go on and on,
are you?
Don't worry, Mr. Gong.
I'm not doing it again.
Great.
That's great.
Because
it is not necessary anymore.
This is...
This is a statement made by a guard
of Dongqiao Salt Granary
and some of the illegal salt smugglers.
The man I've been investigating lately
used to be responsible
for guarding the salt granary.
His name
is Zhao Bu.
He would steal
the official salt
from Dongqiao Salt Granary
and bury it in the outskirts.
Then the smugglers would
take it out.
Unfortunately, Zhao Bu
was addicted to gambling.
He couldn't pay his debt,
so he took the risk
and put the salt
in his own pocket.
However,
the truth will out.
He didn't know
that once it came to light,
the one behind him
would kill him to cover everything up.
Mr. Gong, do you think
I've saved this guy?
Sir,
why are you still up?
I can't fall asleep.
They said
people would get confused as they age.
I am old,
but why is the past
getting clearer in my head?
Who are you
doing this for?
I don't know.
Truly.
What's wrong?
Someone is trying to kill me.
Who?
Who is trying to kill you?
You...
Who are you?
Why
are you
trying to kill this young lady?
She isn't any random lady.
Lu Wei,
do you know who she is?
She is involved in the Censor case.
Move,
or I will kill you as well.
Move!
Stop!
Don't!
What do you want?
He gave the order
and killed so many women back then.
And he forced
the three judicial departments
to make the final judgment.
Yu Qian's entire family died
because of it.
Wu Youjing has done
so many evil things.
Why does he have to
kill a woman?
If you want to kill her,
you'll have to get through me first.
Run!
I don't need to run,
and you don't have to die.
You...
You are...
Who are you?
Mr. Gong,
do I have to make everything clear
for you?
General Wu,
please don't trick me.
I don't know
who you're talking about.
I have him now!
If you want to deny it,
we are going to see Her Majesty
and find out the truth!
General Wu!
No.
You can't do that!
Now,
I have to tell you the truth.
I've been asking you to drop it.
It is
not only for me,
but also
for your own sake.
I didn't know
so many happened
in the years after I left the capital.
Here you go.
Here.
I thought
you were one of them.
But just now,
you were ready to die for me.
It means
you are not a greedy, deceitful person.
So why did you
make the judgment in haste back then?
For the sake
of their children,
parents would...
As the Chief Censor,
I supervise the enforcement
of the country's laws and regulations.
I get justice for the wronged ones,
or I fail the trust of the people
and of the ruler.
I don't give in to power or wealth
nor do I accuse innocent men.
Yu Qian is the backbone
of the Imperial Court.
It is immoral for me
to bring him down.
Your son
is serving in the Personal Guard
of the Court, right?
One day, he got drunk after the court
and raped a maid of the imperial palace.
My son sees me as a role model.
He is a righteous man
and would not have done
anything like that.
No?
But I think he did it.
Once you have a weakness,
sometimes you make mistakes
against your will.
Yu Qian
was someone I truly admired,
but look what happened to him
and to his family.
Everything was in vain
no matter how hard you tried.
Yu Qian was an honest
and honorable official,
but there were few like him.
Since then,
I couldn't look at my official robe
without guilt anymore.
That was why I resigned and left.
From a County Constable
to royals
and high-ranking officials,
this case is very complicated
and involves many people.
Young lady,
I'm an old man.
I don't have many years left.
Yet it is different for you.
Listen to my words.
Let it go
and do not confront Wu Youjing.
He is not someone you can mess with.
Don't get yourself killed
because of it.
I'm sorry, Mr. Hai.
Your Highness came
to visit me in person.
I guess
this is
where I'm going to spend my last days.
In the end,
we still end up
with this.
That's right.
It is an exchange of expendable pieces.
No one would have seen it coming.
You are suffering for me.
Back then,
you went to Tongquan for me
to rope Du Liang in.
Our goal was to take
the salt granary in Tongquan
into our hands.
There's nothing to regret about that.
Your game on salt
is halfway to victory.
The Li family
is counting on the Crown Prince.
They are waiting for a chance.
Her Majesty, meanwhile, doesn't favor
the eminent families
but promotes those with no background.
One day,
if Her Majesty passes away,
the Wu family
needs something to compete with them.
Salt
is the lifeblood of a country.
Only with salt in our hands
can the Wu family keep its foundation.
Prince of Kangping,
what should I do next?
Please tell me.
I will make a plea
to keep your family
from getting involved in this.
I see.
Ye Ping'an
can read the signs and see the trend.
She is a trouble in the chaotic game.
No matter what,
she has to be gone.
Ping'an,
I see that your thoughts are troubled.
You're in the capital,
but it is as if you're in a cage.
Have you considered leaving for a while?
To me,
everywhere is a cage.
Hai Yiping took his own life.
Yet I still feel
there is more behind this.
The end of the Censor case
didn't dispel all her doubts.
She still wants to look into the salt.
It could be a problem sooner or later.
Please make a plan in advance.
Father,
Ye Ping'an has to be gone.
She will figure
the Censor case out eventually.
It's not good for us to do it ourselves.
How about taking advantage
of the merciless official?
The Censor case?
Is it
all your plan?
And now, you want
Ye Ping'an dead?
Kang,
respect the rules.
Tell me what the rules are.
I'm back from Gong Shao's place.
Do you know what I found?
I always thought
the one
who was stealing the official salt
was Li Zongxu.
The Wu family
is prosperous.
Why would you do that?
Why?
Ankang.
You often mention that numerous people
died in the Battle of Jinyuan.
They died
because the Li family
was in charge of the official salt
and got in the way.
Do you want anything similar
to happen again?
No matter
who is in charge of the official salt,
it won't happen again
as long as all the officials
are honest
and upright.
Also,
what you are doing
is never for me.
You do it for your own power.
For that,
you stole the official salt
and ganged up with others.
You orchestrated the Censor case
and killed so many people.
It is
wicked
and sinful!
You are part of the Wu family.
We either rise
or fall together.
The reason why you became a general
and have been one step ahead of others
since you were born
is that you are from the Wu family.
Ankang.
Leave him alone!
He will figure it out.
You are part of the Wu family.
We either rise
or fall together.
The reason why you became a general
and have been one step ahead of others
since you were born
is that you are from the Wu family.
You are from the Wu family!
[Tongtian Gate]
- General Wu.
Are you visiting
Her Majesty for an emergency?
I need to...
General Wu,
are you...
My horse was frightened,
and I lost control. That's all.
[Flourishing Era]
[Anxin House]
Mr. Fan.
Miss Ye.
Please.
Her Majesty.
I'm here
to talk about
the way of treatment.
How dare I.
It's okay.
Your treatment
has a high reputation in the capital.
It's my honor.
On your feet.
Ping'an,
I have a question.
What do you think
makes a medicine effective?
Good herbs and ingredients
together with appropriate heat
and timing.
The right medicine
for the right illness,
that's what matters.
A light symptom
requires immediate treatment,
while a severe illness
should wait.
May I ask
how to treat
an unknown disease?
It hides in the dark,
and the patient often pretends
it doesn't exist.
As time goes by,
a light symptom becomes a severe illness
and eventually something incurable.
By that time,
even the most miraculous medicine
cannot change anything.
Keep going.
The pain of the people
starts from their tolerance.
They value
bonds and relationships,
so that they endure
being exploited.
I travel around
to treat the unknown diseases of people
and keep them safe.
Ye Ping'an,
I finally see
how you treat people,
but your treatment is too strong
and inappropriate.
Your skill
still needs some refinement.
Leave the capital.
Go somewhere else
to get the experience.
Master Suxuan, what are you thinking?
I'm confessing my sins.
I heard from those coming to pay homage
and learned about
what happened lately.
Why didn't you tell me last time?
I don't want you to worry
about the past.
Since you decided to help my father
back then,
you have no sins.
Helping your father at that time
was my first sin.
Leaving you behind
to run away from everything
was the second one.
You shouldn't take the wrong path
like me.
Master Suxuan,
you once asked me
to follow my heart.
I'm here
to tell you
that I've made my choice.
Prince of Kangping.
General Wu
caught a few illegal salt smugglers.
I'm worried
that it will lead him back to us.
Maybe you should stop him?
Kang is only holding a grudge
about the delay of grain and salt
during the Battle of Jinyuan.
Once Li Zongxu is taken down,
he will be done with it.
I'm afraid
that the Granary Magistrate, Gong Shao,
is involved.
Gong Shao?
Gong Shao.
Xu Qing.
I need to get a chance
to check the Dongqiao Salt Granary.
[Dongqiao Salt Granary]
General Wu will check the granary soon.
You
should be prepared.
Thank you for the notice, Miss Wu.
[Notice]
So Ye Ping'an
was the accomplice in the Censor case.
Father.
Do you know
about Ye Ping'an's identity?
She can be a good blade.
If it goes too fast,
we could hurt ourselves.
I understand
what you are trying to say.
I have a plan, Father.
Ye Ping'an has mental distress.
We can make use of that
and take her to a dead end.
I know you have great potential.
Ye Ping'an is capable,
but she will not listen to me.
In the future,
she will only be my problem.
Do you want to kill her
only because of the Censor case?
You and Father
are both involved.
I'm born to the Wu family.
I don't care about any noble reputation.
Don't listen to Prince of Kangping
because of me.
You are wrong, Master.
I am not doing it for you,
but for myself.
Xian'er.
I made it to the Editorial Director
of the Palace Secretariat
because I'm from the Wu family.
If anything happens to Father
and the Wu family is put to shame,
I won't be able to stay out of it.
Father was right about one thing.
The Li and the Wu
are at the complete opposite now.
If Her Majesty
wants the Great Feng to last,
the throne can only be passed down
to a member of the Wu family.
I won't allow anyone
to harm us.
How did you know Prince of Kangping
was the mastermind?
Madame Hua never thought
she would be drugged and die.
Before she died,
she grabbed a rosewood comb
and held it tightly.
Rosewood
is the Prince of Kangping's favorite.
She wanted to leave a message
before she died.
Prince of Kangping promised you
a high-ranking position,
didn't he?
If I were you,
I would make the same choice.
You should stay by his side
as close as possible.
You aren't not me.
Now I see it.
Wu Youjing covered the Censor case,
sold the official salt to others,
and ganged up with other officials.
He has been preparing for the battle
between the Li and the Wu
for a long time.
I will ask you one more time.
Can you let it go?
♪Past events turn to ash,
crushed into mud♪
I will escort your way
out of the capital,
and I will keep you safe
for the rest of your life.
♪Like a distant dream,
forever out of reach♪
♪Your breaths faded♪
♪In silence and distance♪
♪Thoughts form a chapter,
with a reluctant prelude♪
♪The storm of sorrow is beyond words♪
Look at the sun.
It dropped today,
but it will rise again tomorrow.
♪In a glance back,
no traces of the past remain♪
However, tomorrow, you and I
will be standing on opposite sides.
♪Lost in regret, tangled♪
♪Unwritten, unspeakable♪
♪Buried in time, too fragile to name♪
Don't hold anything back.
Sure.
♪A cup of cold moonlight♪
Ye Ping'an,
♪A page of faded tears♪
I'm looking forward to being your enemy.
♪Dreams, scribbled in haste♪
♪Fade into dust♪
♪A lone wild goose cries♪
♪Echoing through the sleepless night♪
[One Year Later]
♪Only to clutch fragments of memory♪
♪To soothe the remaining years♪
[Directorate of Astronomy]
The snow came earlier this year.
I'm afraid something is happening.
[Dingding Gate]
Emergency!
The Khan of Shuodan passed away.
The second prince of Shuodan
came to the throne.
He is sending troops to the border.
Emergency!
The Khan of Shuodan passed away.
The second prince of Shuodan
came to the throne.
He is sending troops to the border.
The Khan of Shuodan passed away.
Shuodan is sending troops to the border.
I plead to lead the army to the border.
I will guard the Great Feng
and keep the foreigners out!
[Dingding Gate]
General Wu Ankang
is appointed
as the Marching General of Yanbei.
He will be the commander of the march.
That is all.
I am lowborn.
I shouldn't throw the water on Mr. Yuan.
I am stupid.
I am lowborn.
I shouldn't throw the water on Mr. Yuan.
Let's go.
What did he do
to be punished this way?
Mr. Yuan took his son
to the Court of Judicial Review
for selling illegal salt.
The old man was mad.
He said his son did that
only because he was starving.
[Zhao Feng, Vice Minister of Justice]
He then threw a basin of water
over the head of Mr. Yuan.
This pissed the Underworld Lord off,
so the Underworld Lord
punished him to kneel here.
The Underworld Lord?
This is his nickname now?
That's right.
The Underworld Lord
used to be a nice guy.
He did a lot for the people
and helped Mang Gutter a lot.
But he has been
like a totally different person
since he was with the Mei alliance.
He is arrogant
and indulges in pleasure.
Anyone who crosses him will suffer.
He is cruel!
And the illegal salt smugglers
shouldn't take the blame.
The price of salt
dropped for a while last year,
but this year, it keeps going up.
The price of salt
is 400 wen per dou in the capital.
No one can afford it.
It is almost impossible
to have some salt.
I shouldn't throw the water on Mr. Yuan.
I am stupid.
Illegal salt smugglers.
[Mei Mansion]
The second prince of Shuodan
is ambitious.
The wedding was held
in the first year of Kangzhou.
After the Khan died,
he took over the throne.
He simply disregarded
the alliance with the Great Feng,
held Wu Liangchen as hostage,
and sent troops to the south.
He is a barbarian.
The second prince killed his brother
and seized the throne.
It's created an atmosphere
of fear and uncertainty.
To settle down the internal affairs,
he decided to send his army
to get the grain of our country.
It is a cold winter.
Our army is not experienced in fighting
in the snow.
This is
a long-planned move.
Master,
there's something I really don't get.
Why did you
ask the Vice Minister of Rites
to impeach you and say
you were extravagant
and only served for the money?
You ended up being punished
by Her Majesty.
You missed half a year of your pay
and got seriously scolded.
Do you know
what defines a corrupt, upright,
deceitful, or loyal official?
Well...
To be honest,
Master, you don't consider yourself
as an upright one, do you?
Well...
Yuwen Tai and Su Chuo
had this conversation before.
They said a good ruler
uses corrupt officials to gain power,
eliminates opposition by purging them,
and wins favor by executing them.
I'm afraid
I don't follow.
As a high-ranking official,
I have to make some minor mistakes.
Otherwise, Her Majesty
would have nothing on me.
However, I can't make any big mistakes.
If I do that,
all the commoners will hate me.
Yuan Shaocheng didn't
get into any trouble lately, right?
Not exactly a problem,
but he punished the father
of an illegal salt smuggler.
That old man
was out of his mind.
He threw a basin of water
on Yuan Shaocheng in this cold weather.
Yuan Shaocheng punished him
to kneel on the street
while holding
a basin of water over his head
and apologizing out loud.
Deceit and loyalty can be very similar.
Yuan Shaocheng is smart.
Master,
the Prince of Kangping
has the most say in the court now.
He has many followers,
and they are supporting
the Wu family, instead of the Li,
to inherit as the orthodox.
You should stay close to him
as usual,
why do you pretend to be sick
and avoid seeing him again and again?
You really didn't understand
a word I said just now.
The Prince of Kangping
asked me multiple times
to find him positions
in the areas with salt.
It was a big mistake.
Master,
the Prince of Kangping is here.
I told him you were sick
and not seeing anyone.
However...
Master.
Prince of Kangping.
Mr. Mei.
Why are you sick for such a long time?
You are an important official.
The court really needs you.
Recovery is a long road.
I'm just an old man.
I'm no use to anyone.
I was worried that you were held up
by some terrible physician.
I
found someone good for you.
Go.
Check Mr. Mei.
Prince of Kangping,
the problem with Mr. Mei is weird.
Once a stranger gets close,
his entire body gets itchy,
and there will be red rashes.
So it's better not to get too close.
So the disease...
is contagious?
Prince of Kangping.
So you are saying
that before you get well,
I shouldn't visit you anymore, right?
Have a good rest.
Master,
if the Prince of Kangping visits again,
what should we do?
He knew I was faking it,
so he wouldn't come anymore.
[Court of Judicial Review]
Did Zhao Feng see him?
Yes.
Zhao Feng started to investigate
the illegal salt in a rush,
and he asked someone to take away
the old man.
Isn't that good?
Zhao Feng is a responsible officer.
He cares a lot
about the commoners.
Sir,
I find it more and more difficult
to understand you now.
Why do you let others do the good deeds
and take the blame?
Someone told me
that reputation, whether good or bad,
is not relevant.
I agree.
Someone will be happy
to see the bad name on me.
Sir.
[To the Court of Judicial Review.
From Yangzhou]
Yangzhou?
The delivery man
said someone paid him a lot
to take it to the capital.
[I am a silk maker in Yangzhou.
I report He Yi...]
Are you going
to the Kangping Mansion, Mr. Yuan?
I can go with you.
It's okay.
Help Wenyu
organize the files there.
[To the Court of Judicial Review.
From Yangzhou]
I am a silk maker in Yangzhou. I report
[He Yi, Supervisor]
the Supervisor of Riverine Affairs...
Me?
He Yi,
for taking the transportation fee
for himself.
He serves for his own interest
and knows no limit.
Please investigate He Yi
and the other officers involved
and expose their illegal acts.
Prince of Kangping.
Please spare me.
It's my fault.
I'm to blame.
Mr. He,
the transportation fee you took
was nothing.
However, because of the letter,
all the transportation of salt
in Yangzhou
is going to be shut down.
Shut down?
Well...
No way.
Isn't it
not yet reported?
The official salt
through Yangzhou per year
is 500,000 dan.
If you sell 50,000 of it,
it is
100,000 liang silver per year.
If the letter
is not sent to Shaocheng,
but to someone from the Censorate,
from the Ministry of Revenue,
or to one of the merciless officials,
do you think
how many of you
can make up
for the 100,000 liang, Mr. He?
Prince of Kangping,
I will redeem myself.
Leave!
Yes, sir.
I'm going to find a new source of salt
to make up for my mistake.
Shaocheng,
you made another contribution.
I've always relied
on your support.
This is what I should do.
Unfortunately, after he was appointed
as the Right Aide
of the Department of State Affairs,
Xu Ling
didn't make many mistakes this year.
You may
need to be patient.
How about
we put the marriage of Xian'er and you
on the schedule?
I will have the auspicious date chosen.
It's my honor, Prince of Kangping.
[Yangzhou]
Jiangnan is snowing so early.
I guess the winter of this year
will be particularly cold.
The snow is beautiful,
but you never know
what's lurking underneath.
It's snowing.
The path will get tougher.
Ping'an,
it's time to get back to the capital
and visit Cailian and Danxin.
[Kangping Mansion]
Greetings, Prince of Kangping.
That's fast.
It's less than twenty days.
You got some news?
Yes,
but
the salt trader this time
is a bit different.
I don't dare to make the decision,
so I'm here to report to you.
Tell me about it.
After multiple searches,
I found an illegal salt smuggler.
The person is...
An illegal salt smuggler?
That's right.
Do you think you've lived enough
or do you want to drag
the Prince of Kangping
down with you?
Accurately,
the person is a middleman.
He claims to have
a huge amount of illegal salt.
About this.
Three thousand dan?
Thirty thousand.
What kind of middleman
has this amount of illegal salt?
Mr. He,
you won't believe it, will you?
Well, according to the middleman,
his salt
will be sold by batch,
and then he will look for a big buyer.
The most important thing
is that the price is 100 wen per dou.
A hundred wen?
That's right.
I thought it could be
a highly profitable deal,
so I didn't waste any time
and came to report in person.
Now,
we don't know
the identity of this person.
Mr. He,
maybe you can schedule
a meeting with this person,
and I will check it out.
Xian'er,
you should go with Shaocheng.
Sure.
[Zuiweng House]
It's a perfect spot
for an ambush.
If someone does want us dead,
I will be excited.
Are you here to see Mr. An?
Follow me.
What a coincidence.
I'm making money
from old friends now.
Who is
your friend?
As for the money,
you haven't
made it yet.
We haven't seen each other for one year.
Ping'an, when did you
make fishing a hobby?
Did you
get any fish today?
It all
depends on luck.
I am never
a lucky person.
It is only
for some fun.
♪Past events turn to ash,
crushed into mud♪
♪Like a distant dream,
forever out of reach♪
♪Your breaths faded
in silence and distance♪
♪Thoughts form a chapter,
with a reluctant prelude♪
♪The storm of sorrow is beyond words♪
♪In a glance back,
no traces of the past remain♪
♪Lost in regret,
tangled, unwritten, unspeakable♪
♪Buried in time, too fragile to name♪
♪A cup of cold moonlight.
A page of faded tears♪
♪Dreams, scribbled in haste,
fade into dust♪
♪A lone wild goose cries,
echoing through the sleepless night♪
♪Only to clutch fragments of memory
to soothe the remaining years♪
♪A cup of cold moonlight.
A page of faded tears♪
♪Dreams, scribbled in haste,
fade into dust♪
♪A lone wild goose cries,
echoing through the sleepless night♪
♪Only to clutch fragments of memory
to soothe the remaining years♪