[First Year of Kangzhou]
First Year of Kangzhou,
the Empress came to the throne.
The suppression of the eminent families
led to the conflict
between Li and Wu families.
Many merciless officials
abused their power with impunity.
The Right Chancellor
was exposed by one of them
and condemned for a crime
born of mere dreams.
Both the court
and the public
were surprised by the news.
Since then, to avoid any trouble,
people stopped discussing their dreams.
Ye Ping'an, a physician,
is the only one who does the opposite.
That's the psychiatrist.
Let's go. Don't look at her.
She is not a psychiatrist.
She's a witch!
It's bad luck.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Stay away from her.
Witch.
There she is.
Mother, a bell.
Don't look at it.
It will take your soul.
Mother, what happened to that man?
[Zheng Yuan, Left Rectifier]
Hu Sheng went crazy
and is hitting people!
Help!
Hu Sheng went crazy
and is hitting people!
Help!
Hu Sheng went crazy
and is hitting people!
Don't come over.
I...
I will kill you all.
Tell me.
[Li Jun, In-palace Enquiry Censor]
Who sent you here
to mess around in public?
I'm a soldier.
[Hu Sheng, a commoner from Mang Gutter]
I'm a soldier!
Soldier?
That's right.
Prince Yu Li Ke tried to rebel
and just got hanged.
He must be
one of the remnants of Li Ke's troop.
Grab him.
- Yes, sir.
As a soldier,
you should follow orders.
Who are you?
Hu Sheng,
I'm the general.
Don't you recognize me?
General?
I know no general.
I've been following the commander.
Your commander
is fighting against these people.
You should
know them then.
I will recognize them no matter what.
They are the wretched from Shuodan.
They killed many of my brothers!
He is losing control of his mind
and hallucinating.
What he said suggests
that he was once following Mr. Wu
and fighting against Shuodan.
He was definitely not with Li Ke.
Who are you?
[Ye Ping'an, a psychiatrist]
I'm Ye Ping'an, a psychiatrist.
I treat those with illness in mind.
Psychiatrist?
We've killed
a remaining follower with Li Ke.
Each of you will get a merit.
- Yes, sir.
[Kill My Sins]
[This is a work of fiction]
[Episode 1]
[It Is Destined]
[Anxin House]
Hu Sheng
suffered mental damage
after the battles.
[Handbook for Psychiatrists]
When frightened, he yelled
and twitched.
He would hallucinate
and see people around him as enemies,
with the tendency to hurt others.
- Go away!
- Get out of the capital!
Go away!
Get out of the capital!
[Anxin House]
Today on the street,
someone from Mang Gutter
suddenly went crazy.
You must have put a curse on him.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Life flows from birth to death,
as unpredictable
as the changing weather.
According to you,
will it be my fault
if you fall on the street?
You...
Stop it.
All you need to say
is if you are going to move out of here.
If you don't,
I'm going to burn it down.
Let's burn it!
Just try it, and see what happens.
She really knows witchcraft!
This is horrible.
I will count down from three,
and all your nightmares
will come true.
Three,
two...
The witch is making a curse.
Run!
[Anxin House]
I've heard the witch in the capital
can heal by reading dreams.
She can heal illnesses
through conversation.
[Yuan Shaocheng, Assistant Minister]
Healing was once seen
[of the Court of Judicial Review]
as a witchcraft,
but she is
using it
to get life-saving money from people.
She deserves it
even if she is burned to death one day.
[Longmen Arena]
Longmen symbolizes
the carp's leap to greatness.
Contestants here are nothing
but lowborn commoners from Mang Gutter.
They will risk their lives to fight
just to entertain you, my dear guests.
Injury or death is of no consequence.
Each fighter
[Red, White]
represents either the red or white side.
Winners and their children
will break free
from their inferior status,
receive land
and start a new life.
Now, let's welcome
the twin brothers from Mang Gutter
to face off in battle.
Ready? Go!
You don't look well, Mr. Zheng.
[Zeng Xuan, Assistant Officer]
Are you still suffering
from the lack of sleep?
I'm fine.
People are gossiping.
The Right Chancellor Fu Shengjun
was sentenced to death
because of his dream.
It had never happened before.
Just because of his dream?
He was dreaming that the rebel Li Ke
got onto Zhanlu Hall,
where Her Majesty rules.
[Du Liang, Director]
Having such a dream
[of the Ministry of Revenue]
is a huge mistake.
I understood.
Her Majesty
[Xu Qing, Chief Secretary]
is setting a harsh example.
Thank you for your reminder, Mr. Du.
Her Majesty gave the order
to collect military fund.
How is it going?
A total of 85,000 Liang
has been collected.
In less than four days,
it will be delivered to the capital.
In my report, it will be
80,000 Liang.
Be extra cautious.
Don't leave any record.
Understood.
Alright.
How is Zheng Yuan
doing?
I heard he had a strange illness
that kept him from sleeping at night.
He saw a few physicians,
but it didn't get any better.
I will bet on the white side.
Me too.
[White]
The most important thing now
is the military fund.
The Ministry of Revenue
has reported the amounts
to the court.
Du Liang sent someone to ask me over.
I guess it's time for us
to sit down and talk.
- Great!
Useless lowborn man.
They are twins.
It's a good fight.
Nobody dies. That's a shame.
Nice! It's a good one!
Congratulations to the red side.
You will be free from the inferiority
and receive your land.
[Xin, a maid of the Zheng Mansion]
[Anxin House]
Miss Ye,
I'm a maid of Mr. Zheng.
Mr. Zheng invites you
to visit his mansion.
I don't see any patient today.
You can come another day.
Miss Ye,
Mr. Zheng invites you
to visit his mansion.
Miss Ye,
Mr. Zheng invites you
to his...
What are you...
So you do know how to speak
instead of just repeating
those words.
It's getting late.
If I need to go over there,
the charge will be...
[Zheng Mansion]
Come in.
Master,
Miss Ye is here.
The liquor you asked for is over there.
Mr. Zheng,
how long
have you not been able to sleep?
Half a month. I will wake up
whenever I close my eyes.
I've consulted all the top physicians
in the capital,
but none could cure it.
I heard
that your skill was very unique.
If you can cure my illness,
you will be greatly rewarded.
Now, you can take my pulse.
I don't
observe,
ask about symptoms,
or take the pulse.
All I do is to take a glimpse
at your dream.
Now, please look at the bell in my hand.
Whenever you hear a ringing,
repeat the word "void" in your mind.
If I hadn't taken you to the capital,
you would have remained just an adviser
[5,000. Military fund]
rather than become the left rectifier.
Do you have something on me?
Mr. Du, please spare me.
Miss Ye,
your skill does work.
You said you could glimpse
at people's dreams.
May I ask if you see mine?
I did see a little.
I saw a scary figure.
Fear is the key of your problem.
What is frightening you?
Were you able to see the figure's face?
Not really.
I only know
that it's a woman.
If
you can tell me
more about her,
maybe it will help...
Keep going.
What else did you see?
I also saw
a letter.
A letter?
What did it say?
The dream is in disorder.
The scenes kept flashing.
I couldn't see anything clearly.
Mr. Zheng, your illness
requires a longer treatment.
It's too late.
The curfew is about to begin.
I will visit
another day.
Forget about it.
Do not let anyone
know about what happened tonight.
[Wanguoxiang Tavern]
♪I set off for the eastern hills♪
♪Yet I tarried, my return delayed♪
♪I come from the east♪
♪Drizzling rain veils the land♪
♪I journey home from the east♪
♪My heart grieves for the west♪
♪They wove garments, fine and new♪
[Nichang, a singer of Wanguoxiang]
♪So that warriors may fight no more♪
♪Caterpillars wriggle upon the earth♪
♪They gather across mulberry fields♪
♪Alone we lay, in solemn rest♪
[Madame Hua, the hostess of Wanguoxiang]
Wanguoxiang is indeed
the best tavern in the capital.
One more.
Mr. Du,
may I talk to you in private?
I would like to make a deal
with you, Mr. Du.
A deal?
Mr. Du, your ancestor
was a high-ranking official.
Thanks to that, you started your career.
First as a county official,
and then
you were promoted to the capital
and all the way as the director
of the Ministry of Revenue.
Qi Junshan was lucky
to have you as his sworn father,
but he only gives you
one fifth
of the gambling house's profit.
This is not fair.
You really know a lot about me.
If I can get control
of Yitai Gambling House,
I will give you
two-fifths of the profit.
Also,
I will show you the accounts.
What you are saying
is completely nonsense!
The former director
of Ministry of Revenue, Liang Junzhi,
was from a humble family.
He wanted to fight
against the Langya royals.
Now, nobody even knows
where he was buried.
He was from a humble family,
but you are even worse!
Being in the Mang Gutter
must have muddled your mind.
Do you think you will
have leverage in politics
just because you killed some enemies
in the battleground?
After you are done with this glass,
immediately
disappear from my sight.
She is gone?
Find her now.
Where is she?
No sight of her.
If Mr. Zheng looks into this,
it won't end well for us.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Zheng yuan.
Close the windows and doors.
Beware of thieves.
[The second hour of Hai]
Close the windows and doors.
Beware of thieves.
[Zheng Mansion]
Mr. Zheng, why would you
send people to kill me?
[Steward of Zheng Mansion]
Master?
There's a murder.
There's a murder!
Help!
Ye Ping'an?
It sounds familiar.
It is the witch.
[Court of Judicial Review]
What's your opinion?
You can be honest.
Last night, Mr. Zheng
invited Ye Ping'an to his mansion
for a treatment.
At the second hour of Hai,
after hearing the gong, the steward
went to check
if Mr. Zheng was sleeping well.
He then saw Ye Ping'an with a knife.
It's straightforward,
but I think it is suspicious.
Why?
[Gu Wenyu, Constable]
First, the anonymous report
was too immediately
and we got her too easily.
Second, the dagger in Ye Ping'an's hand
has no blood on it
and doesn't match
Mr. Zheng's wound.
Third, for any reason,
why would Ye Ping'an kill him
on the day when people knew
she visited on the very same day?
Wouldn't that only
make her more suspicious?
Wake up.
Wake up!
Get some water.
Are you
the officials to interrogate...
You fell asleep
even when you committed a deadly crime.
As expected from a quack of the streets.
No.
Behave yourself!
I am not a liar.
I was being hunted,
and that was why
I went to Zheng Mansion.
When I found him, he was dead.
It must be a trap.
Someone wants to frame me
and make me the scapegoat.
It makes sense.
So you are framed,
and there is something behind it.
Alright.
You can write down everything
that happened last night in detail,
okay?
Sure.
[I confessed
to the killing of Zheng Yuan]
This is
a confession?
You just said...
What did I say?
I was just continuing the story
you made up.
Don't waste my time.
Sign it.
Sign it now.
Don't keep us from handling other cases.
In the end, all I was waiting for
was a useless officer.
Maybe I should still thank you
for coming to the jail
and investigating me
for show, Mr. Yuan.
You know who I am?
Some say you hold yourself
to a high standard
and never gang up with others.
Others say you are cruel
and merciless.
You come from the Mang Gutter,
where there is no chance to rise,
but you did well in battle
and got to be a minor officer in return.
You made every effort
to compete for credits
and got promotions.
Finally,
you become
such a useless officer.
You...
Wenyu.
Fine.
You are good at making your point,
but it won't change your situation.
It makes no difference
whether you sign the confession or not.
Someone else will do it for you.
Really?
Alright.
I killed him.
Do you want to know how I did it?
I stared at his eyes
and performed my witchcraft.
I made him
kill himself,
just in the same way
like I'm staring at you right now.
Whether it is witchcraft
or a trick,
I don't care.
You are dead
to me.
[Anxin House]
I heard the one
who killed the official
was this witch, Ye Ping'an.
Did they say how?
They said she put a curse.
Come here. Hurry!
What happened?
Did you get any updates?
It was not just a curse.
It was about dreams.
The witch
can put you to sleep
and glimpse your dreams.
I heard that the witch
could get into your head.
Once you dream,
she will become the ghost
in your dream.
Mr. Zheng was scared to death
because of it.
[Wu Xian'er, Editorial Director
of the Palace Secretariat]
Bring it closer.
The issue of Fu's dream
is done,
[The Empress]
but now
I heard about another dream.
I also heard something about it.
I wonder if we are talking
about the same one, Your Majesty.
You can tell me what you heard.
The rumor goes that there is a physician
who can glimpse people's dreams
and treat their illness.
How can anyone
glimpse others' dreams?
I
have no idea.
Keep going.
She even
dared to
kill Mr. Zheng,
who was loyal and hardworking.
Someone
must want her
to be convicted immediately.
Loyal?
When Prince Liangping Li Qi
held his birthday banquet,
Zheng Yuan
was also on the guest list.
I wonder
who he was loyal to.
Pass it down.
Instruct the Court of Judicial Review
to bring her to Zhanlu Hall.
I'm going to interrogate her myself.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I guess Mr. Yuan
didn't expect to meet me
again.
You must feel like
you're burning all over again,
with blisters that sting,
just like when you were little.
Your Majesty.
It is said
that she could get into people's dreams.
Is that true?
She is a fraud instead of a physician.
The so-called "entering dreams"
is nothing but a deception
that people fall for.
As for the case of Mr. Zheng,
she used a dagger to attack him.
We have both witnesses and evidence.
She cannot deny it.
Your Majesty,
what Mr. Yuan said isn't the truth.
I cannot enter anyone's dream,
but I can take a glimpse at it.
I saw someone
who brought fear to Mr. Zheng
in his dream.
That person was the murderer.
Please grant me a chance,
and I will find out who the person is
and get
[Fan Cheng, Palace Attendant]
the evidence of the murder,
so that I can prove myself innocent.
Your Majesty,
she is lying.
She cannot glimpse
people's dreams.
Your Majesty, please allow
Mr. Yuan,
who doesn't trust my skill at all,
to help me prove myself.
You...
Minister Yuan,
just do what she says.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
whenever I glimpse people's dreams,
I need some liquor.
I know
that Your Majesty favors the finest.
May I
ask for a cup of it?
Let her have it.
Mr. Yuan,
you have a tough mind,
but when I tell you
not to think of fire,
do you
have fire
in your mind?
What's the most pleasant moment for you?
Let me guess.
It will be when you are back
to your most familiar place.
It's completely silent.
You are alone, on the boat,
on the river.
Your arms are under your head.
And at this moment,
you feel a second of peace.
Watch out. It's hot!
Mother!
Father!
Shaocheng!
Father.
Watch out!
Tell me.
Why did he
behave like that?
What did you see
in him?
Your Majesty,
it's hatred.
I saw a very intense hatred.
For whom?
[Power]
Mr. Yuan's hatred comes from...
My. Yuan reached his hand
because he saw the woman he loved
in his memory.
He was opening his arms,
but suddenly, there were two kids,
and they were asking for their father.
Mr. Yuan realized
that the woman was already
the wife of another man.
That's why Mr. Yuan
comes across as so aloof
and remains unmarried
even though he's no longer young.
That makes sense now.
Minister Yuan,
is she
telling the truth?
Your Majesty,
what Ye Ping'an said
was indeed true.
It seems
that you do have
the skill to tell people's minds.
If I keep you alive,
and you help others
to guess my mind,
wouldn't I be putting myself at risk?
Well,
being merciful is a virtue.
I would like to see
if you can
save yourself now.
You have one day.
Find out the truth
before the curfew of tomorrow,
and you will live.
Otherwise,
you will be dead.
One day?
Yes.
I won't fail
your kindness, Your Majesty.
You may leave.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
her ability to glimpse others' dreams
is not as miraculous
as in the rumor,
but it is
truly remarkable.
It's not about glimpsing dreams.
She is smart
and very brave.
Perhaps
she has potential.
[Zhanlu Hall]
However, her life
is in her own hands now.
I can barely stand.
Help me out.
You were eloquent
when you were
making up the story inside.
Aloof?
Unmarried?
I was afraid of death
and trying to survive.
As a gracious man,
you will forgive me, right?
How did you know
that I was once burned?
When you asked me
to sign the confession letter,
I saw the scar on your hand.
Before we entered the hall,
you mentioned
the blisters on my hand.
That's when you started
to compel me.
I told you.
You have a tough mind.
The common way
cannot put you to sleep.
Where did you learn the witchcraft?
If this is witchcraft,
then witchcraft is everywhere.
The embroidery on your collar
makes you uncomfortable,
but why are you still wearing it?
It's because you believe
that it shows your status.
After all, all the nobles
have embroidery
on their attire.
You want to be part of them,
so you do the same.
Isn't it also
a witchcraft?
The Court of Judicial Review has checked
the crime scene,
but I still want to have a look myself.
One day is not a lot of time.
Shall we immediately...
You are going to die tomorrow,
while I'm not.
Why should I care?
Your people
are guarding the Zheng Mansion.
I won't be able to enter without you.
If you don't want to go,
I will have to follow you all the time
to see where you go
and who you see.
If
I have to die tomorrow,
I'm more than willing
to tell everything to Her Majesty.
You don't want me
to drag you down, do you?
Alright.
Say one more word,
and I will leave you alone to do it.
[Zheng Mansion]
Since the coroner has checked the body,
you must know
when Mr. Zheng died,
and I was not
in the mansion at that time.
You can keep denying it.
The body was not moved,
so it was likely that the murderer
suddenly appeared behind him
and cut his throat
when he was unaware.
You are now
telling me what you did.
May I ask
who the Court has interrogated?
The coachman.
The steward.
Both of them proved
that you never left the mansion.
What did they say exactly?
You entered the mansion
at the first hour of Hai.
Everyone in the mansion heard the gong
of the second hour of Hai.
It was
in this hour
that you committed the crime here.
Something is wrong.
Because the curfew was about to start,
I left the mansion in a hurry.
When I was home,
I read the handbook for a while
and then I was hunted.
After that, I came back
to the Zheng Mansion.
It would take at least an hour.
It should be the first hour of Zi.
Stop pretending.
You never left.
Otherwise, how could an hour
be missing?
One hour was gone.
How was it possible?
Mr. Yuan,
have you asked
the watchman last night?
It doesn't matter.
It won't change the fact
that you killed Mr. Zheng.
Mr. Yuan, an honorable man,
could you please see it
without the assumption
that I'm the murderer, just for once?
Wenyu,
check anyone
who left the mansion last night
after the murder.
Yes, sir.
Sir,
after investigation,
two persons left the Zheng Mansion
last night.
The servant Xiao Quan
was found dead on the outskirts.
The maid Xin is missing.
All we know is she has
a plum-blossom birthmark on her neck.
Is this the servant Xiao Quan
who left the mansion after the murder?
Yes, it's him,
sir.
This is a dead end now.
How about the maid Xin?
Can you find her?
If she is indeed
part of the murder,
I guess
she will end up like him.
If she was lucky and survived,
she is probably
out of town now.
It is the second hour of You,
only two hours from the curfew.
Wenyu,
go with the steward
and check everything
about Xiao Quan and Xin
when they started
working in the mansion.
Yes, sir.
Follow me.
We can
ask the watchman some questions
in the last two hours.
It's not necessary.
You can start thinking
about the words
on your tombstone.
[Yuan Mansion]
[Zeng Xuan, Assistant Officer]
Sir,
Zeng Xuan is here for a visit.
Mr. Zeng,
it's late.
What brings you here?
Please have a look at this, Mr. Yuan.
How's everything, Danxin?
Was it fun?
[Xin]
It was great fun.
[Lu Danxin]
Following your plan,
I worked in the mansion for over a year
and finally earned Zheng Yuan's trust.
Three days ago,
I saw Zheng Yuan receiving a letter
about Du Liang's corruption.
I sent a letter
to Du Liang on the same night
and let him know that Zheng Yuan
[Zheng Yuan has evidence against you.]
had the evidence of his corruption.
I turned them against each other.
Zheng Yuan.
I also
added more powder
that would keep him from falling asleep.
After you got his attention
on his path...
I'm Ye Ping'an, a psychiatrist.
I treat those with illness in mind.
I suggested him to ask you for help
and made sure
that Du Liang's spy knew about it.
Zheng Yuan was killed,
[The military fund is 85,000 Liang.]
and as you expected,
[Put 80,000 on the report]
you were the perfect scapegoat
[and send the rest to the outskirts.]
in Du Liang's mind.
You could
redeem yourself.
According to the plan,
I switched several identities
and spread rumors about you.
It finally got the Empress's interest.
A decree from Her Majesty.
Am I
a good scapegoat?
Well, I'm also
a good maid.
The first step
is done.
It's time for the next move.
Du Liang didn't expect
that Zheng Yuan had a backup plan.
He wrote a letter
exposing the corruption
of the military fund
and gave it to his friend, Zeng Xuan.
A good friend of Zheng Yuan
reports that Du Liang
is behind Zheng's murder.
That will be more convincing.
Something's wrong.
Zeng Xuan went missing.
What?
[Accusation Letter]
I am the left rectifier, Zheng Yuan.
I would like to report
Du Liang of the Ministry of Revenue
for taking 5,000 Liang
of the military fund for his own use.
If I unfortunately die,
he is the one responsible.
Where did you get it?
Mr. Zheng is the left rectifier
with the power
to report directly to Her Majesty.
After knowing Du Liang's corruption,
he wanted to tell Her Majesty,
but Du Liang
was one step ahead
and asked questions to test him.
Mr. Zheng realized that Du Liang
might have known it.
Zeng Xuan,
keep this letter carefully.
Are you afraid
that Du Liang will kill you?
But you are a high-ranking official.
Even if he is...
You don't know how cruel he can be.
Years ago,
I was his adviser.
If anything happens to me,
hand it
to someone you trust.
Why bring it out now?
I have no power
and no means to have
a direct audience with Her Majesty.
I heard a female murderer was caught,
so I couldn't show anyone the letter.
I know you and Du Liang
have no common interest.
So only now, as this case
is being re-investigated,
do I dare to make it known.
Did anyone see you here?
No.
Someone was tailing me
as I left home.
I managed to shake them
before coming to see you.
Mr. Zeng,
to be honest,
not only Du Liang and I
have no common interest,
but we also have history.
You found
the right person for this.
Tonight,
you can rest at my place,
and tomorrow morning,
I will take you to see Her Majesty.
Great.
♪Evening mist blurs my sight,
winds shift, and cold dew falls♪
♪My heart drifts like a lone sail,
with the boundless seas as home♪
♪The moonlight fades into the night♪
♪Yet my buried longing never melts away♪
♪I'd rather wait in sorrow
for fate to turn♪
♪Than be left with nothing,
forever untied♪
♪Scattered apart, only sighs remain♪
♪Regret too deep to mend♪
♪Stars fall, the moon dims,
and a soul is too broken to rise♪
♪The night flickers
between light and dark♪
♪Yet you remain my guiding light♪
♪Each of us follows our destined path♪
♪Yet as you turn away,
caught in the whirl of time♪
♪I, like a drifting petal,
am swallowed by the abyss♪
♪Bound by destiny♪
♪Scattered apart, only sighs remain♪
♪Regret too deep to mend♪
♪Stars fall, the moon dims,
and a soul is too broken to rise♪
♪The night flickers
between light and dark♪
♪Yet you remain my guiding light♪
♪Each of us follows our destined path♪