[Kill My Sins]
[This is a work of fiction]
[One Year Ago]
Miss Ye,
I am Zhao Feng,
Vice Minister of Justice.
I heard
that you are about to leave the capital,
so I've been waiting here for you.
Mr. Zhao, what is the meaning of this?
I was asked by someone
to deliver this to you.
This is...
Please don't ask any questions.
I have fulfilled my duty.
Safe travels to you, Miss Ye.
[Episode 26]
[The Seemingly Useless
Can Be of Great Value]
You left the capital
without a word,
and I've missed you.
Where have you been
for the past year?
I've been to a lot of places.
Otherwise,
how could I be sitting here?
Stop beating around the bush.
Just tell me.
Why did you become an middleman?
Now that salt prices are so high,
who wouldn't want to seize
the opportunity to earn a little more
and live a better life?
Stop with the act.
Such a glib tongue.
How could she possibly
provide this much illegal salt?
Mr. Yuan, it seems
that you have
a strong prejudice against me.
Since you don't trust me,
feel free to leave.
I'll just find another buyer.
Do you really have
so much salt?
Huang...
Yi...
Min.
He is the biggest illegal salt smuggler
in the Henan region.
How do you know him?
Mr. Yuan,
you truly are forgetful.
How could you forget what I do
for a living?
After I cured
an illegal salt smuggler's headache,
he introduced me
to his leader.
Come on.
Here.
Take another piece.
All right.
Give it to me.
Here's a piece for you.
It tastes amazing.
Forgive me, Miss Ye.
Lives are always on the line
in this trade.
I apologize if I've offended you,
but I can't afford to take risks.
I understand.
[Huang Yimin, an illegal salt smuggler]
Huang Yimin
does have the nickname
"Iron Crutch Huang,"
but no one knows
how he got his limp.
It's a simple story.
His limp wasn't caused
by a physical injury
but by the deep anguish he endured
after his wife passed away.
So you treated him and ended up
forming a connection with him.
Exactly.
It's because of this connection
that he entrusted me
with some illegal salt business.
Your story
is really dull.
Stop wasting time on her.
Let's go.
Mr. Yuan, you haven't even become
the Prince of Kangping's son-in-law yet,
yet you're already trying
to control Miss Wu.
Be careful,
or he might exploit you.
You should worry
about yourself.
You could make a fortune,
but you might not live to spend it.
Enough.
Shaocheng,
how could I refuse
to do business with Ping'an?
If you truly know Huang Yimin,
pick a day
and bring him to see us.
That's very nice of you, Miss Wu.
How about this?
No matter how much
you make from this deal,
the commission
will be a fixed 800 liang.
Sure, no problem.
We'll leave now.
By the way, Mr. Yuan,
it's cold and the roads are slippery.
Be careful
not to fall.
I've warned you.
You're no match for her.
We can find
other ways to get salt.
Why bargain with a tiger?
Mr. Yuan, how well do you know me?
There's no need
to impose your own weakness
onto me.
Be
dutiful and devoted.
It's what I expect
when you're with me.
Who has the audacity
to block my carriage?
An anonymous tip has reached
the Ministry of Justice,
alleging the presence
of illegal salt in this carriage.
Sorry for the offense.
Search it.
- Yes, sir.
Sir,
we found this under the carriage.
Mr. Zhao,
you know us.
Why could we hide illegal salt
under the carriage?
We've clearly been framed.
Whether it's a frame-up or not,
I'll get to the bottom of it.
Without an official token,
I don't acknowledge any claims.
So once you see the token,
you'll let us go, right?
With it,
you enter the prison as an official.
Without it,
you enter as a commoner.
Have you thought it through?
No need to bother.
We'll go with you
as two commoners.
My friend,
may I ask where Mr. Zhang is?
Mr. Zhang is occupied
with official duties.
He'll only return after a few days.
Wait.
Please go
to the Court of Judicial Review
and tell them that Minister Yuan...
What are you talking about?
Luckily, no one saw it,
or you'd have ruined
my reputation that I've maintained
for years.
Miss Wu.
Ask General Xian to come and get me out.
Yes, ma'am.
[Ministry of Justice]
Miss Wu, are you all right?
Of course.
[Xian Guangping]
I heard from the jailer
[General of Left Yulin Royal Guard]
that Mr. Yuan is still inside.
Should I bring
him out as well?
No need.
He has his own way out.
Who would have the nerve
to frame you?
Who else could it be?
Of course, it's her,
Ye Ping'an.
Ye Ping'an?
Isn't she your friend?
Yes.
But sadly,
we can only be rivals.
I got you out of prison in the past,
and now you've helped me out.
I guess we're even now.
- Nice!
Keep pushing.
Steady yourself.
Hang in there.
Next.
- Excellent!
Stay steady.
- Just like that.
- Steady now.
To the left.
Good job!
- Amazing!
Impressive.
Your turn.
Miss Wu.
Why isn't Captain Xian
here today?
He's too proud for his own good.
A few days ago,
he had bad luck and offended
the Commander-in-Chief,
landing himself in prison.
The Commander-in-Chief
is someone who holds grudges,
so he might use this
as an excuse to have him killed.
Thank you for saving my life, Miss Wu.
I would do anything
for you.
Then stop being a captain.
I've made arrangements
for you to join my brother, Wu Ankang,
on the battlefield.
Earn some merits if you can,
but
I want you to return alive
and show me that you can be a general.
Yes, ma'am.
We can never be even.
I mean,
I'll always remember
the kindness you've shown me.
It's etched in my memory forever.
Is that so?
Would you
die for me?
Yes.
Good.
Go find
an illegal salt smuggler
who's met Huang Yimin.
I'll need them.
Yes, ma'am.
[Kangping Mansion]
What's the situation at the front line?
General Wu, with great valor,
led the charge, driving
the Shuodan invaders back dozens of li.
Our main force is now confronting them,
and General Wu
is preparing to seize an opportunity
for a surprise attack.
Advancing recklessly is unwise.
Tell him
not to hurry.
The roads are treacherous in the snow,
and salt,
provisions, and military funds
may be delayed.
Additionally,
inform the granaries along the way,
the Ministry of Works,
and the Ministry of Revenue
that anyone who neglects their duties
will face severe punishment.
Rest assured, sir.
I will take care of it.
Xian'er,
you've been out all day.
Where's Shaocheng?
He has something to take care of.
That person does indeed have salt,
and she claims to be acquainted
with Huang Yimin,
the largest illegal salt smuggler
in the Henan region.
The goods are his.
If it truly is Huang Yimin,
then the amount of salt makes sense.
How much
is the middleman's commission?
Eight hundred liang.
That's the market rate.
However,
you'll be surprised
by the middleman's identity.
She's Ye Ping'an.
There must be a hidden agenda
behind her actions.
If she truly knows Huang Yimin,
then we...
This approach won't work.
Let's try another one.
But Father...
Xian'er.
We...
You're probably not in it for the salt.
What you want is to prove
you can beat her, right?
A few days ago,
Li Yuncheng submitted a memorial,
right?
Yes.
He spoke highly
of the Crown Prince's virtues
and offered his full support.
Her Majesty's response
was just five words:
"No noise in the court."
No noise...
That was Her Majesty subtly warning him,
purposely letting you see it.
It's also a reminder for me.
Stay calm.
I'll have He Yi find another way
to obtain the salt.
[Zuiweng House]
Windborne snow on red silk.
Candlelight on green brew,
a soft tipsiness.
This kind of weather
is perfect for catching up.
Xian'er,
what good stuff
have you brought?
Naturally,
it's Wanguoxiang's signature dishes.
It's true that I haven't had them
in a long time.
You are the only one
who gets to eat the food I deliver.
Well, I feel most privileged.
Huang,
Miss Wu has brought
some delicious dishes.
Come and try them.
An official like her
isn't worthy
of sharing a table with me.
Our tastes in food
are likely different as well.
I've long heard of
the renowned Iron Crutch Huang.
And today, I finally got to meet you.
I never expected you
to hold such deep resentment
toward officials.
But if you won't even try the food,
how can you know
whether it suits your taste?
Even the crops from the same field
are different,
and so are officials.
Some of them are competent,
while others are not.
Huang,
I've tried the dishes from Wanguoxiang,
and they're truly good.
Why don't you try them first?
Some may hold official titles,
but beneath their robes,
they are nothing but animals.
While others, despite humble origins,
possess great foresight
and unwavering loyalty.
This is why I am here
to meet you.
A young girl like you
has come to meet
an illegal salt smuggler like me.
And you dare to face me alone.
I must say you are quite impressive.
Actually,
I didn't come alone.
I brought a gift
to show my sincerity.
I'm sure
you know him.
Miss Wu,
you are truly capable.
He was locked up in prison,
and I've been worried about him
for quite a while.
Hey,
what are you standing there for?
Come over here.
Let me get a good look at you.
Uncle.
Looks like you didn't fully trust me
after all, Miss Wu.
You brought someone
to verify his identity.
Well,
do you believe me now?
It's all
about business.
How much salt have you
brought here?
The winter roads are treacherous,
and
with the strict inspections
around the capital,
I've only brought
a thousand dan this time,
hidden in various parts
of the mountain.
Though the quantity is small,
this first deal will establish
some trust between us.
Future dealings
will be much easier.
In this case,
Ping'an,
I can only pay you
half of the money upfront.
Once the rest of the deals are settled,
I'll pay you the remaining amount.
I hope that's fine with you.
Of course, I won't make a fuss
over this, Miss Wu.
Allow me two days
to prepare the silvers.
After that,
we'll meet at Xiyun Mountain Gorge
to check both the payment and the goods.
Come in.
As the Vice Minister
of the Court of Judicial Review,
how come
you came out a day later than me?
I heard you just came back
from outside the city.
In the end,
you still went to do business
with Ye Ping'an.
So what if I did?
Does your father know about this?
He doesn't need
to know about something this small.
But
if you can provide a thousand liang,
I'm willing
to let you take part in this business,
and I'll give you thirty percent
of the profits.
Since you're in urgent need of money,
this deal
will likely go through
in the next few days.
As I've warned you,
there's something off about Ye Ping'an.
Do you think
I haven't noticed?
She's gone to such lengths
to make connections
with illegal salt smugglers,
which means she's laying
a trap for me.
Then why are you
insisting on doing business with her?
You don't seriously think
I actually want to buy her salt, do you?
I just want to see
who'll come out on top
when we face off again after a year.
If you insist on battling her,
I won't get involved.
Then why are you still here?
Are you waiting to watch me bathe?
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't left back then,
maybe none of this
would have happened.
Aunt, this has nothing to do with you.
[Tomb of Lu Danxin. Tomb of Cailian]
You and Danxin
are both the type to never look back
once you've made a decision.
Have you considered how much
this would break my heart
as your aunt?
I know I haven't been filial.
But I'm destined
to remain so.
Tell me.
Why do you
have to show up for the trade yourself?
You know
it will surely raise suspicion.
Playing a game alone for too long
makes one crave an opponent.
When Wu Xian'er discovers
that I've set a trap for her,
do you think
she'll take the bait?
Take it easy.
Careful.
So adorable.
Who has our Ning come to visit?
Come on, let your uncle
hold you for a moment.
Did your uncle's stern look
scare you?
Our Ning is born smart,
she could tell right away
that her uncle is a bad man.
What are you telling our daughter?
It's true.
Your brother is helping a villain.
Who knows how many people
are bad-mouthing our family out there?
I can't even hold my head high
when I go out.
I'm leaving.
Ning,
never follow in your uncle's footsteps.
Bai Sheng
may be harsh with her words,
but she actually used
the name I gave the child.
She has a sharp tongue but a soft heart.
By the way,
that He Maoshan
who's always keeping an eye on you
is a despicable man.
Why haven't you gotten rid of him yet?
Mr. Yuan.
You probably don't know what I said
to the Prince of Kangping,
do you?
What do you mean?
After the death
of Lu Danxin,
you and Ye Ping'an
went to her place and looked for
things she left behind.
I overheard
your conversation outside.
Well,
Mr. Yuan.
No need to tense up.
Take it easy.
When I reported
to the Prince of Kangping,
I only relayed Ye Ping'an's words
and didn't mention
that you were also present.
All right.
Why didn't you bring this up to claim
some credit from the Prince of Kangping?
How could I possibly claim any credit?
I'm just an insignificant official
in the Court of Judicial Review.
The Prince of Kangping
wouldn't care about me.
If I offend you,
will I rise in status?
Besides,
right now, the Prince of Kangping
values you.
Only by following you will I have
the chance to improve my position.
Since I see him for what he is,
I know how to use him to my advantage.
Has that missing Ye Ping'an
reappeared?
That's right.
Ye Ping'an has suddenly become
a middleman,
which is highly suspicious.
The Prince of Kangping
has yet to fulfill his promise
to recommend me
for the position of the Right Aide
of the Department of State Affairs.
But if I can get something on him,
I can secure
the Prince's favor.
Zhao Yu.
Yes, sir.
Where's Wenyu?
He went to see Chang Qing again.
Ever since he found out
that Chang Qing is Cailian's father,
he has treated him
as his own father.
Go and tell him
to keep a close watch
on Wu Xian'er in the coming days.
If anything unusual happens,
report it to me.
Yes, sir.
[Xiyun Mountain Gorge]
Miss Wu.
Why isn't Huang Yimin here?
If the buyer and seller are so close,
what's the point of having
a middleman like me?
All right.
Let's check both the payment
and the goods.
[Ministry of Justice]
Wait.
No need to pursue him.
I'm not his target.
[Illegal salt trade in Xiyun Mountain]
Bring some men
and follow me out of the city.
- Yes, sir.
I saw Wu Xian'er leaving the city,
so I sent someone to follow her
and mark the trail.
Get reinforcements
from the Court of Judicial Review
[Yuan Mansion]
and move out right away.
All the goods are here.
No need for that.
I have full trust in you
as my client.
I assume your salt
is measured fairly and precisely.
Since you're a valuable client,
allow me to see you off.
No need
for courtesies between us.
Farewell.
Stay where you are!
Go!
Arrest everyone on both sides!
This is a letter accusing He Yi
of embezzling river transport fees.
Wu Youjing is a prudent man.
Once he sees it,
he will surely shut down
all the transportation of salt himself.
He'll be desperate
[To the Court of Judicial Review]
to find an alternative.
Ping'an,
we can then make our next move.
Prince of Kangping,
I will redeem myself.
Leave!
Yes, sir.
I'm going to find a new source of salt
to make up for my mistake.
Are you really
only asking for 100 wen per dou?
Since Wu Xian'er considers me
a worthy opponent,
I shall grant her wish
and turn into a mouse,
letting her think
she has the upper hand
while delivering this cat
right where I want it.
[Psychiatric Commissioner]
[Imperial]
So, what was left in the jar a year ago
was the token
of the Psychiatric Commissioner.
Miss Ye, since you have returned
to the capital
and come to me,
you must be here
for something important.
There is an official
in the capital
manipulating the salt trade
for personal gain.
I intend to lure out this big fish.
Salt prices have soared,
leaving the people unable to afford it
and struggling to survive.
It's time to expose
the culprit behind this.
Miss Wu,
I received a secret letter
accusing you,
a court official,
of knowingly breaking the law
by using silver
to purchase illegal salt.
Mr. Zhao,
you've arrived just in time.
I also received a secret letter
claiming
that illegal salt was being traded here.
So I came to make a deal
and draw them out.
Sure enough,
we caught them red-handed.
Please, Mr. Zhao,
take her into custody.
Mr. Zhao,
Miss Wu accuses me
of selling illegal salt,
but buying and selling
are equally punishable.
The silver is right here as proof.
How can I be convicted
based on her words alone?
Sir,
we've found a set
of Mountain-Pattern Armor.
Miss Wu,
are we just going to leave now?
Should we put in place
what you asked us
to prepare?
Yes, do it.
Yes, ma'am.
Ye Ping'an,
you are truly audacious.
Not only do you sell illegal salt,
but you also secretly hoard armor.
Such actions
amount to treason.
I'm just a commoner.
How could I possibly have
this Mountain-Pattern Armor?
Only someone from the Wu family
would have such resources.
You might not have the resources,
but those behind you do.
If the Wu family falls,
the biggest beneficiary
would be the Li family.
Taking such a risk to secure
the Crown Prince's position
is hardly surprising.
Enough.
This is getting more and more absurd.
A matter of such gravity
cannot be determined
by one person's words alone.
This item
was hidden among the illegal salt.
No matter what,
Ye Ping'an can't wash her hands of it.
Someone!
Wait!
I'd like to see who dares
to make a move.
Mr. Zhao,
are you protecting Ye Ping'an
because you, too,
wish to commit treason?
Mr. Zhao,
I'll go with you.
Over here!
Hurry!
You should leave now.
Go!
This man is Ye Ping'an's accomplice,
Huang Yimin,
the biggest illegal salt smuggler
in the Henan region.
Hang on.
Where is his crutch?
Such a cunning act of deception.
This matter involves many parties.
Mr. Yuan,
please hand the person over
to the Ministry of Justice
for a thorough investigation.
I captured this person,
so naturally, the case
should be handled
by the Court of Judicial Review.
Mr. Yuan.
Mr. Zhao,
the suspect Ye Ping'an
escaped under your watch.
Even if it wasn't intentional,
you are still accountable
for negligence.
Stay out
of this matter.
Miss Wu.
Zhao Feng
once submitted a letter
to Her Majesty,
claiming that the Crown Prince
was the rightful heir.
Go to Xinkai Prison
and tell Zhou Mi
that Zhao Feng is involved
in the salt and armor case.
Zhou Mi knows
how to extract evidence
from him.
Yes, ma'am.
The criminal Ye Ping'an
is guilty of secretly trading armor,
resisting arrest,
and flouting the law.
She has fled to Luozhou.
- Luozhou.
Anyone who reports her whereabouts
will be rewarded
with 100 liang of silver.
A hundred liang?
Those who assist the authorities
in capturing her
will be rewarded
with 1,000 liang of silver.
[Wanted]
Anyone found harboring her will face
the same punishment as her.
Why is Ye Ping'an
involved in so many crimes?
Indeed.
Exactly.
Get up.
Quiet down.
Someone's trying to sleep here.
How dare you be so arrogant?
Do you even know where you are?
This isn't just any prison.
This
is the Court of Judicial Review Prison.
No matter how tough you think you are,
here,
you'd better bend
and behave.
What's your monthly salary?
With salt costing 400 wen per dou,
how much can you afford
with your monthly salary?
Wait. What's that supposed to mean?
Since you've dropped the disguise,
stop pretending
to be an illegal salt smuggler.
Now,
the crime committed by Ye Ping'an
is far worse than selling illegal salt.
She has hoarded armor.
According to the laws of Great Feng,
one set of armor equals
three crossbows
and three sets of armor
can result in execution.
You should know this, right?
It all leads to death anyway.
Whether the charges are heavy or not,
does it really matter?
I only have two questions for you.
First,
what is your relationship
with Huang Yimin?
Second,
where is Ye Ping'an
right now?
I knew
getting an unyielding man
like you to talk
would not be so easy,
so I came prepared.
How do you plan to torture me?
Just bring it on.
That won't be necessary.
Your real name
shouldn't have been traceable,
but I still found it.
Qiu Yin.
You were once just a farmer,
but you were forced into the life
of a vagrant
when your land was taken.
Only with the help of some friends
did you learn martial arts,
and become a hatchet man for a living.
Hence, the word "loyalty"
is etched on your heart.
How did you find out?
What?
Is something I said incorrect?
For someone like me,
loyalty is the most important thing.
There's no difference between friends
and family.
You corrupt officials
wouldn't understand.
Well said.
Today, I'll see
how you'll choose
between friends
and true family.
If I remember correctly,
you have a cousin
in Ruanyang County.
How about I bring him here
to visit you?
I'll go immediately
and make sure he's well taken care of.
No need.
I can answer
your first question.
Over the past year,
we've been exploring new sources of salt
because we know
Wu Youjing needs salt.
How did you know
that the Prince of Kangping
would halt all the transportation
of salt in Yangzhou
due to a lawsuit filed
by the local silk maker against He Yi?
Could it be that the letter
accusing He Yi
of embezzling the transportation fee,
which was sent
to the Court of Judicial Review
some time ago,
came from Ye Ping'an?
That's right.
As for Huang Yimin,
we don't really know him.
We only borrowed his name
because it is
so widely recognized.
She sure knows how to spin a good story.
The letter of accusation
didn't contain lies.
As for your dear father-in-law,
since last year,
he's been sending people
to the salt fields
under the pretext of capturing bandits
and guarding the salt fields.
He's used every possible trick
to seize land from farmers,
forcing many to become refugees
and resort to selling illegal salt.
You traitor,
how dare you slander
the Prince of Kangping!
Ye Ping'an...
Tell me.
Where is Ye Ping'an right now?
Open the door!
Come in.
What has he had?
Nothing.
He only had two bowls of water
when he came in.
Go fetch the physician.
If he dies,
I'll hold you accountable.
Yes, sir.
[Court of Judicial Review]
Ye Ping'an
doesn't speak a single word of truth.
She
has always
been a master of deception.
Let's find another way
to handle the salt issue.
Where did you get those sets
of Mountain-Pattern Armor?
If you want answers, you should arrest
and interrogate Ye Ping'an.
She's the one
hoarding the armor.
You know full well
that hoarding armor is a serious crime.
Why did you use...?
Had it not been for the armor,
Ye Ping'an
could have easily explained
the source of her salt.
Now that she's back,
the battle
is on.
This time,
we must take her down in one fatal move.
How is he now?
The prisoner is in poor condition
and unfit for interrogation.
Investigate it!
I'd like to see
who dares to poison someone
inside the Court of Judicial Review.
Pass down my order.
No one is to approach
this prisoner's cell
except for me.
- Yes, sir.
Sir,
I'd like a word
with you in private.
Get to the point.
That old man
wasn't wrong about everything.
With the meager salary I have now,
I can't even afford to use salt freely.
Those are just words
meant to sow discord.
Your salary
might be modest,
but hasn't the Prince of Kangping
given you
quite a few perks under the table?
So I guess
I was wrong
to expect you
to promote me.
I should have sided with
the Prince of Kangping from the start.
Sir,
do you think
I can still change my mind now?
This... This is the engagement gift
the Prince of Kangping gave you.
I wouldn't dare to take it.
This is your reward
once the task is done.
I planned
to give it to Wenyu,
but since you are so eager for merit,
I shall let you have it instead.
What's the task?
Go to Caozhou
and find the real Huang Yimin.
Persuade him to sell illegal salt to us.
I've asked around
and his salt is indeed quite cheap.
If you can make this happen,
you will have earned great merit for me
in the eyes of the Prince of Kangping.
But I have
no connections in Caozhou.
Even if I manage to find
the real Huang Yimin,
I doubt
he'd be willing to see me.
If I had no confidence in this,
I wouldn't have planned
to let Wenyu handle it.
Open it and take a look.
This is...
This is the token.
Huang Yimin, the illegal salt smuggler,
values profit
but cherishes loyalty even more.
He has a son
named Huang Qi.
Coincidentally, I have
a merchant friend
who once risked his life
to save Huang Qi
when he was being pursued
by bandits.
In gratitude,
Huang Qi gave my friend
this tooth he lost in the incident,
promising
to help him
whenever needed.
Rest assured.
I will not let you down, sir.
You have three days.
Get it done, even if your horse
collapses from exhaustion.
Yes, sir.
Past events turn to ash,
crushed into mud
Like a distant dream,
forever out of reach
Your breaths faded
in silence and distance
Thoughts form a chapter,
with a reluctant prelude
The storm of sorrow is beyond words
In a glance back,
no traces of the past remain
Lost in regret,
tangled, unwritten, unspeakable
Buried in time, too fragile to name
A cup of cold moonlight.
A page of faded tears
Dreams, scribbled in haste,
fade into dust
A lone wild goose cries,
echoing through the sleepless night
Only to clutch fragments of memory
to soothe the remaining years
A cup of cold moonlight.
A page of faded tears
Dreams, scribbled in haste,
fade into dust
A lone wild goose cries,
echoing through the sleepless night
Only to clutch fragments of memory
to soothe the remaining years