Encantadia,
is the land of four kingdoms
and territories,
a place overflowing
with mystery and power.
Here, you'll find
beings of wonder
creatures with strange powers,
magic...
and forms.
This is the home
of brave and valiant daughters
of the Queen Mother.
The sisters known as the
Sang'gre...
who, back then,
were still united
and at peace with one another.
They were the heirs and
protectors
of the four sacred gems
that gave life and protection
to the whole of Encantadia.
PASHNEA - An expression of
frustration or anger.
It's all right, Danaya.
This was a time
before all the chaos
and wars came
upon Encantadia.
Lireo is truly beautiful.
One day, I will inherit
my crown...
from our Queen Mother.
And I will rule not just Lireo,
but the whole of Encantadia.
Stop it, Pirena!
You are not even sure yet who
will truly win
in the competition our
Queen Mother is about to hold.
Why are you two even arguing
about who will become queen?
It's such a heavy
responsibility.
One that I...
will never carry on my
shoulders.
Enough, all of you.
Look over there.
A ferocious dragon!
Looks like we're in for a fight.
Get ready!
Animal!
Our Queen Mother needs to know
about this.
Let's go.
But, Amihan...
Our Queen Mother
will only scold us
because we stole the gems
from the chamber.
The beast has already been
vanquished.
So no one else needs
to know about this.
Witches!
Let's go home
and return the gems.
Before anyone finds out.
Come now.
Chapter I
“The Queen of the Cursed”
Back in the day, your mothers
were still headstrong
and stubborn, Adamus,
Flamarra, Gaiea.
But their courage
and love for Encantadia
were remarkable.
They risked their
lives for the freedom and peace
we enjoy today.
Just like Amihan once did.
She died fighting for our world.
Amihan...
She sacrificed herself
for all of us.
It's a pity that you never got
to meet
such a great and
nurturing queen like her.
Oh...
Forgive me, young sang'gre.
Let us return to your lesson.
Encantadia is divided
into four kingdoms
and territories...
First, Lireo in the East.
Home of the fairies.
Guardians of the Gem of Air.
Second, Sapiro in the North.
Now ruled by King Ybrahim .
His kingdom was
once the guardian
of the Gem of Earth.
And in the West,
there lies
the Kingdom of Hathoria.
Where we now live, Elder.
Correct, Flamarra.
And you, of Hator blood,
were once the first guardians
of the Gem of Fire.
And in the South lies my home...
Adamya.
Where my father also came from,
Elder.
Precisely, Adamus.
We were once the keepers
of the magical Gem of Water.
What happened, Elder?
Why are the Ada now the ones
guarding the gems?
Because of a greedy being,
Gaiea.
Hagorn.
He was once
the King of Hathoria,
whose burning desire
was to seize all the gems.
So that he could claim the whole
of Encantadia for himself!
Because of Hagorn,
great conflict
and war once erupted
across the land of the people
from Encantadia.
A war that claimed many lives...
And ended with Hagorn's death.
The death of the traitorous king
also ended all the strife.
And returned peace
to all of Encantadia.
I ask for forgiveness
for all the sins committed
by my ancestral king.
Forgive us all.
Flamarra...
You have nothing
to apologize for.
You carry no sin.
All of that is in the past.
That's true.
It's all in the past.
But why are you still
teaching us this?
So that you will never forget
the history of our land, Adamus.
So that if ever new invaders
come to our land,
you too will learn how to fight
and you'll fight for Ecantadia.
Land of the curse.
The Garden of Cassiopea.
CASSIOPEA - Goddess and “ Eye ”
of Encantadia
Who are you?
Who is being referred
to in my dream?
Who will kill me?
Arsus is here!
I'm sure he's hungry again.
Escape while you still can!
Child, just hold on to me.
Don't let go.
Hurry up!
Veshdita, follow now!
Why does he have
a strange sword?
Who are you?
Does my former Lord no longer
recognize me?
Mitena?
Yes.
Arsus.
What happened?
You've changed your appearance.
Prepare yourself.
For the day of my reckoning
upon you has come.
If only Amihan were still
alive...
things would've been more
peaceful and joyful
here in Encantadia.
True, Danaya.
But Amihan is already at peace
and happy in heaven.
Let us just be glad
for our sister.
Let's not burden ourselves
further.
Indeed, Alena.
We should go and fetch our
children from Adamya.
Their lesson with Imaw
must be done by now.
Someone is making their presence
felt.
The honorable Hara Durye
HARA DURYE - Ancient Queen.
What do you need from us,
Goddess?
I dreamt of my death
at the hands of a being from
another land.
Your death?
But it's impossible for a Hara
Durye to die.
And there is no other land more
powerful than Encantadia.
Cassiopea, it's just a dream.
Don't trouble yourself with it.
But my dreams always come true.
There is nothing my eyes see
that does not come to pass.
But who will kill you?
I need to know who it is.
I will find out!
Mitena...
you?
You will kill me?
The king...
and lord of all Minea-ve?
Prepare yourself.
Because I will capture you.
And eat you!
Right now!
I am no longer the Mitena you
enslaved for so long.
You wretch.
I will prolong your suffering!
Feel the wrath of vengeance
from the one you cursed.
She has slain Arsus.
Who could she be?
Take to heart and mind
everything you have learned
about Encantadia, children.
Yes, Elder Imaw.
Your Majesties.
- Mother!
Flamarra.
You go home first.
Leave us for now.
Go ahead, Gaiea.
Be careful, Adamus, okay?
Go on.
Yes, Mother.
Come now, Adamus.
It seems you have something
important to tell me,
Your Majesties.
We received troubling news,
Elder Imaw.
There is someone destined
to kill Cassiopea.
What?
And who could that be?
Whoever it may be,
I will never forgive the one
responsible
if what Cassiopea says is true.
But for what reason?
Why would someone want
to kill the Goddess Cassiopea?
That is exactly what we
are trying to figure out,
Elder Imaw.
Who is this being that
the Great Eye saw?
I am worried.
Because that being might have
ill intentions toward
the whole of Encantadia.
Who is it?
Answer me.
Who was it that my eyes saw?
Why won't my powers answer me?
Who really is this being?
I cannot believe the day would
come when Arsus would be slain.
We owe that Dariken.
DARIKEN - Female warrior.
But who is she?
And where did she come from?
Does anyone here recognize her?
Not a single one of you
recognizes her?
Could it be that she came
from...
a race of flesh-eating beings?
Like the giant?
That being has a different form.
I'm certain she is not one
of them.
That's right.
I agree with that.
I don't know her either.
Ever since I was born in
this land,
no one has ever bested
the giant.
And so we lived in fear,
in worry...
that maybe tomorrow,
it would be our turn to be
caught and eaten by Arsus.
Who would have thought...
someone could slay him?
That Dariken is not from here
in Minea-ve.
But where did she come from?
How did she end up here?
Leader.
The Dariken has arrived.
Beings of the cursed land...
from this day on,
I shall be...
the one you will call Kera!
Kera - Queen.
I will make you stronger.
I will train you and turn
you into great warriors!
And one day...
I will bring you to the land
of the Encantados!
So they may taste the wrath
of my vengeance!
From the hands of
the powerful fairies...
I will seize the land
I loathe the most...
Encantadia!
The Sang'gres are currently
training their children
in preparation for the dark
vision that your eyes have seen.
You must not be weak!
Especially since the enemy
we face
is no force to be taken lightly.
There has never been a vision
of hers that did not come true.
So if there is danger
looming over her life,
that danger may very well
threaten all of Encantadia.
Danaya's child,
who is yet to be born,
will be the true heir and
guardian of the Earth gem.