(Happy New Year)
(Intelligence Agency)
(Shrimp/Yellowtail Festival)
Hello, Merry Christmas!
Hello. We're from Paektusan Soju.
You're drinking “As If Your Last Bottle”, right?
Why don't you try Paektusan Soju
instead of “As If Your Last Bottle”?
If you order Paektusan Soju now,
we'll give you a hangover cure!
Would you like to try clean
and clear Paektusan Soju?
Ah, yes.
Thank you for choosing Paektusan Soju
on a Christmas day like this.
- Merry Christmas!
- Excuse me...
Could you possibly give me
one more hangover cure?
Well, this is actually not allowed,
but since today is a special day,
here's a Christmas gift!
Thank you.
- Merry Christmas!
(Oyster/ Yellowtail)
You're here?
It's snowing outside, isn't it cold?
This place again?
Excuse me, boss,
please bring what I ordered earlier.
I ordered ishidai fish.
Is that food more important to you
than Christmas?
No,
you told me to eat what I want.
But that didn't mean coming to
a place like this, did it?
I said I'd try to change,
but isn't this too much?
Where are you going?
Let's break up.
How can you say that
before the ishidai fish is served?
I'm leaving.
Hey!
Hey.
Ishidai fish is served.
Have a great meal.
It feels like chewing rubber.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- May I have some water?
- Yes.
(Hanwoo beef, pasta, salad 12 000 won)
- He's so handsome!
- I'm so shy.
- Hey.
- Could it be that he's aware?
Hey, did you see that?
He's crazy handsome!
It's not just his face.
He's got this mysterious vibe.
He even declined appearing on TV shows,
(Chef Park Kihoon, Goosoo Restaurant's owner
#HotChef)
- proving this place is a hidden gem.
- What are you doing?
- Can I take your order?
- Yes.
Two of today's special and
two draft beers, please.
Please accept our apologies,
but we don't serve alcohol here.
(Goosoo Restaurant)
(No Alcoholic Beverages Sold or Allowed)
We can't bring our own alcohol either?
I'm so sorry, dear customer.
Let's just eat quickly
and go somewhere else.
Please just give us our order.
Yes.
I really could use a beer right now.
- Forget it.
- What was that.
What a waste of handsome face...
(Giant shrimp grilled with salt)
Uncle, a bottle of soju and raw fish!
Uncle, another bottle of soju, please!
Have a great meal.
- Thank you, Uncle.
- Thank you.
- A plate of mulhoe, please!
Hey.
- You go get it.
- Piss off. You go.
Hey.
Hey, I broke up with someone recently.
And so was I.
How much longer do you plan
to be miserable?
Isn't it already early fall?
Ever been dumped on Christmas before?
Have you ever been struck speechless?
Geez, this jerk...
Hey, you know what?
You're using your broken heart
as an excuse to drink.
This is how I usually drink.
Yeah, from now on, you should only drink
to celebrate good things.
Honestly, it's really hard for me
to take care of you.
I'm the only one who does this much.
If it were other friends...
What?
I'll grab it after I go to the bathroom.
This jerk...
Should have done that from the start.
Your mulhoe is here.
Hello.
No, I didn't drink that much.
Yes,
right now?
Wait a moment.
Okay.
Where are you going?
My friend called me.
- They're in front of my house now.
- Shut up and sit down.
It's my treat.
Then I'll finish it all.
This sly jerk.
From now on, let's only have a drink
to celebrate good things. You and me,
okay?
You talk too much. Just Leave.
- I'll give you a call.
- Sure. Just go.
I want something refreshing.
Haa...
So hungry.
I should have finished the side dishes.
Tteokbokki, tteokbokki.
I want some tteokbokki.
One serving of tteokbokki, please.
Oh? Where's Grandma?
Grandma?
Grandma... Where is she?
I'm sorry, but it's break time now.
Don't you have tteokbokki?
I want tteokbokki right now.
This is not a tteokbokki shop.
Gosh, I'm starving.
- I want some tteokbokki.
- Please leave.
Sure.
I'll leave.
Fine, I'll leave.
I'm leaving, but...
- Please leave.
- Fine.
Is this really not a tteokbokki shop?
- Since when has this shop existed?
- Please get out.
I am leaving.
Where am I?
This is a restaurant,
and it's break time.
But you lost consciousness
and bumped into me.
I'm sorry.
But you seem to be fine.
I'm sorry. I'll leave now.
You see...
I digest well when I'm drunk.
Do you want some cold noodles?
It's our meal time.
Are you two acquaintances?
I just need to boil another serving.
If that's the case, thanks.
Thank you.
Wow, it's so refreshing.
Is he simple or clueless?
That hit the spot.
By the way,
do you have soju?
What?
I think it would be great with soju.
You behaved rudely while
you were wasted,
now you want soju?
No, I just thought
it'd go well with...
Food's good because of alcohol.
In a pleasant mood because of alcohol.
When you're moody, you demand alcohol.
We don't serve alcohol!
Is that something
to get so angry about?
I'm sorry.
I think it's best if you leave now.
Gosh darn.
What kind of unfriendly place is this?
Kind people are really hard to find.
But
at least the cold noodles were good.
Let's go.
If the cold noodles were good,
that's all that matters.
Haa...
Dammit.
- Hello.
(Hangover cure)
Yes?
Jiyu?
Did you drink again last night?
Just a little.
I'm fine, Deputy Chief.
I'm not asking if you're fine right now.
Do you think it's okay to come to work
smelling like alcohol in the morning?
Do I really smell like alcohol?
You smell rotten.
I'm sorry.
Keep your drinking in check
so it doesn't interfere with work.
- You know we have a meeting later, yes?
- Yes, I know.
Chef Choi Seongjoon rejected the offer
because the contract terms didn't match.
- So we're meeting with Chef Kim Seok.
- Yes.
I'll secure the contract
with Chef Kim Seok at all costs.
Gosh, it really stinks.
Keep fighting.
- Regrading the contract...
- My apologies.
Yes?
I really wanted to work with you,
but I've decided to quit cooking.
What do you mean?
Chef, you're doing so well these days.
My wife said what's the use of money
if you don't have time for us?
She handed me divorce papers.
I...
Love my wife.
Yes.
Please love her.
- We're not opposing that...
- No,
I made this decision to protect my love.
Goodbye.
- Chef. Chef.
- Please wait.
What the heck?
Can't he keep both his love and his job?
It's good for both sides.
This is driving me crazy.
What should we do now?
There is a list of
previous candidates, right?
Let's have a look again.
Goodbye.
- Mr. Jiyu.
- Yes?
We need to have a new list
by next Monday.
- Goodbye.
We have to finalize this next week.
I think I can manage.
It's not about whether we can or can't.
We have to.
What if we can't?
If we can't,
you might need to start
looking for another job.
That's scary.
If you want to keep your job,
you'd better find someone.
Yes.
What's all this?
It's for the marketing team.
They say it's for some project.
Free booze.
Wow.
Mr. Jiyu.
You still have the nerve
to think about booze?
This isn't a time to be celebrating.
Yes.
Please go ahead.
What is it now?
I just noticed no one is waiting in line,
so I was curious.
Darn it.
What's with those booze?
It's for work! Hey!
Wait!
So unfriendly, really unfriendly.
Would it kill him to help a bit?
Thank you.
So he does have a heart.
What are you doing?
Oh, you're here?
You didn't hear?
I know.
I'm going to eat and drink all I want today.
Don't try to stop me.
Kim Woosoo, that bastard.
Didn't you say we'd only drink
for good reasons from now on?
Oh, this is a good reason for me.
I broke up with that jerk.
That's a great reason.
- Isn't that right?
- Seriously.
Finding new excuses to drink.
Enough, go grab some glasses.
I'm starving.
I know.
Kim Woosoo, that selfish jerk.
How dare he break up with me?
Who cares.
- Hey, do I have no charm?
- You do.
- What about the glasses?
- Huh?
- Glasses.
- Glasses?
How vexing.
The glasses are here.
Are we going to drink from a wine glass?
How about soju glasses?
That's more like it.
Cheers.
One shot, alright?
Looks delicious.
I'm digging in now.
Wow!
This is seriously yummy.
Don't you know about this place?
No, I don't.
You're really clueless.
How can you not know?
This place is super hot right now.
Where is it?
It's in front of
the elementary school's alley entrance.
What's it called again?
Goosoo.
Something like that.
The word Goosoo
probably means delicious.
Anyway, it's really good.
Maybe this place could help.
- What are you talking about?
- Huh?
It's nothing.
The booze that you're drinking
it's for our launch party next month.
We're collaborating with
a chef on a project...
but we haven't found a chef yet.
We're still finding one.
See? Whenever you're having a hard time,
I always show up like a savior
and help you like this.
Right, you moron.
Just coincidences.
At least pretend to appreciate it.
Anyway, check out this restaurant.
The chef is super handsome.
I even follow him... Hold on.
Wait a minute.
Here.
Look, he's so hot.
Oh, it's him!
What?
Not bad.
Let's contact this chef.
But...
- Well...
- What?
You see...
- Do you have soju?
- What?
You behaved rudely while
you were wasted,
now you want soju?
Huh?
So what do we do?
We need to find another chef.
- Hello.
- Is everything alright?
- Yes.
Let's see.
This is very good.
Yes?
He's better looking than
Chef Choi Seongjoon and Chef Kim Seok.
He even has a mystique about him
since he doesn't appear on TV.
Not bad at all.
Let's go with this guy.
Well, you see...
We're still in negotiations.
How long are you going to negotiate?
We need results now.
Yes, understood.
I'll get the contract signed
by the end of the week.
Okay,
- I'll leave it to you, deputy chief.
- Yes.
- Keep fighting.
Goodbye.
What are we going to do?
We have to try.
- Yes, but how?
- You're not going to do it?
You know my style.
Even so...
Just be quiet if you can't do it.
Yes...
(Goosoo Restaurant)
(Mr. Jiyu, sorry, I'll be late.
Please wait inside.)
(Got it.)
Umm...
Can I order something?
- We're about to stop taking orders...
- Please, have a seat.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Hello.
I'm Han Jiyu.
I'm from Baeksundang marketing team.
We've met before but didn't
properly introduce ourselves.
Our company is launching a new soju.
We would like to collaborate with you.
No.
Pardon?
I said no.
If you're done eating, please leave.
My boss is sensitive about
anything related to liquor.
Oh, I know you don't sell liquor here.
We're not asking you to.
We just want you to handle the cooking.
We're planning a major
promotional event afterward,
which will help market your restaurant.
I said it's not needed.
Then I'll just leave my card here.
See you later.
Don't bother,
it'll be a waste of your time.
Did he need to be so rude?
Deputy chief, where are you?
Sorry. I'm heading back to the office.
Did you talk to him?
We might need to find another chef.
Why?
It's been reported to upper management.
Already reported?
Is there a problem?
They really like Chef Park Kihoon.
I have to go into a meeting now,
let's talk later.
Ugh! This is a disaster.
Mmm, yes.
Oh!
(Close for a day due to personal business)
What? Today's weekday.
What?
This shouldn't be happening.
But it is.
Wonder what's going on.
Yeah.
Looks like we came for nothing.
What should we do?
Nothing we can do.
Let's come back another time.
- You're done for the day, Mr. Jiyu.
- Yes.
Deputy chief.
Wait up, let's go together.
Wait for me.
Auntie!
- I'm here!
- Oh, you're here?
Stir-fried squid, please!
- The same as usual?
- Yes.
- Real spicy, please.
- Got it.
I'll have a bottle of soju!
Please go ahead.
Auntie!
Isn't that stir-fried squid mine?
Yours is right here.
- Oh.
- Geez.
We didn't even write it on the menu.
Two people ordering the same dish
at the same time.
I didn't know.
Hey, are you feeling better?
I'm perfectly fine.
At this rate, I can go to work tomorrow.
You can't serve with a cast on.
What about other friends?
I asked my friend,
he said he couldn't make it.
What should we do tomorrow?
Don't worry about it and just recover.
I'm good on my own, it's no big deal.
Maybe I should just come in.
No, you can't work in your condition.
It's bad for the restaurant's image.
Look at what you said...
Do I look like some demonic boss?
You only care about your own reputation.
My reputation is terrible now.
I'm just worried about you.
I'll hang up now.
- I'm going to eat now.
- Wait, Brother...
You have good taste.
This place has
the best stir-fried squid.
This hidden menu,
how did you know about?
Yeah, yeah.
Just eat your meal.
I went to your restaurant today,
but it was closed.
Is your employee sick?
Well?
Boss,
I'm here to propose again.
No.
Just eat your meal and leave.
Why don't you hear me out first
before deciding?
Well?
Please listen to me first.
- Then you can...
- Is it open?
Welcome.
Is it just the two of you?
They're open, come on in.
We're having a reunion,
and the place we wanted to go is full.
Aunties and uncles like us
are welcome, right?
Yes, of course,
what would you like to order?
Our children are gathered in one house.
Can you deliver some food to them first?
They're really hungry.
I'm afraid delivery
might be a bit difficult...
Of course!
Since you've come all the way here.
What are you doing?
We'll talk later.
You don't need my help?
I'll leave the delivery to you then.
Alright, leave it to me.
I have delivered the food.
Thank you.
The kids are absolutely lovely.
I thought you were only good-looking
but it turns out
you have a good heart too.
Thank you.
If you need anything
let me know anytime.
Alright.
Please enjoy your meal.
Can you recommend some menu items?
Also
are there alcoholic drinks?
We're not really in the know.
Can you suggest a good pairing?
We don't sell alcoholic beverages.
- You don't?
- Why?
How come?
An alcohol-free restaurant? Really?
We don't serve alcohol here.
What now?
But if you don't mind
I'd like to recommend
some traditional soju.
For free.
Really?
Would you mind filling out
a quick survey after trying it?
Of course, it's free, after all.
Thank you.
Today's dish
is a Korean-style pasta that was
seasoned with perilla oil
and salted octopus.
If you pair it with perilla leaves
it'll enhance the fragrance and texture.
This is tteokgalbi made with
Hanwoo beef.
If you pair it with water minari salad
it will help manage the greasiness
and enhance your dining experience.
Have a great meal.
Yes. Thank you.
- Wow that was tasty.
- Hope you get a lot of customers.
It was very delicious.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Please reconsider it.
My proposal.
It's a good proposal.
It will benefit me too.
But I can't afford to do that now.
Thank you for your help.
And your proposal too.
Then, how about...
How did you persuade him?
Well...
How about I help you out on weekends?
Sorry?
Aren't you understaffed?
I had many part-time jobs
at many restaurant during school.
It seems like you might have
trouble on the weekends.
What if he doesn't sign the contract
even after you help out?
Oh.
Then...
I'll do as you say
and look for a new job.
But I'm confident that I'll succeed.
Really?
Yeah.
Hello.
Please take a seat.
- Over here, right?
- Yes.
Two pastas please.
Alright.
(Goosoo Restaurant)
(Alcohol-free. No alcohol is allowed)
Thank you for your hard work.
- Are you hungry?
- Yes. So...
Enjoy your meal. I'll take my leave.
Yes.
Take care.
- Brother.
- Hey.
How are you?
I'm perfectly fine.
How's it going today?
Is the part-timer okay?
Well...
Not bad.
Are you smiling?
You seem to be happy.
I'm sulking now.
What? Smiling?
You saw?
No. But you sound happy.
It's rough but hang in there.
Keep fighting.
I'll go over and have a meal.
Sure.
See you later.
- Have a good rest.
- Yeah.
Hello.
What?
Come have some spicy chicken now.
I drank too much yesterday.
I have an upset stomach.
Drunk from celebrating?
Breaking up with that trash
- of course it's a celebration.
- Yeah right.
Don't drink. Just eat the chicken.
Didn't you hear?
I said I have an upset stomach.
I'd poop blood if I have spicy food.
Jeez I'm eating you know.
There are non-spicy options too.
I'm so bored.
You jerk.
Just end the call.
I already said
that I have an upset stomach.
Pooping blood is tough, you know?
Hello?
Perfectly spicy.
I can't stop eating spicy food.
Because...
I just can't stop.
If I stop
it'll feel like my mouth will tear.
(AS IF YOUR LAST BOTTLE)
Ouch that hurts.
Drinking alone?
Thanks for not helping at all.
Why should I help?
Forget it.
Anyway, what brings you here?
I want some fried chicken.
Why are you sitting here?
- Should I move?
- No don't.
Please sit.
I was just feeling bored.
Please eat.
Say
did you want some chicken because you saw me come in here?
But it doesn't matter.
I eat a lot huh?
I...
Live to eat, be it food or liquor.
I'm just indulging myself.
Eating delicious food and
borrowing some energy from alcohol,
and chatting with friends
can alleviate exhaustion.
That's happiness for me.
I'll sign the contract.
Come again?
Hello I'm chief deputy Kim Yeon-ah.
Hello I'm Park Kihoon.
I've heard a lot about you.
Thank you for signing the contract.
Thank you for your support.
What the...
He's so handsome.
Isn't he handsome?
Please take a seat.
- Give him the documents.
- Yes.
Here's the contract.
And this is the cooking area.
The facilities are not bad at all.
Yes. Sometimes I cook and eat here.
But
the structure here is different
from your kitchen.
So it might seem unfamiliar.
But rest assured there are no
other problems.
Oh and this is what you requested.
Here are the clams.
Thank you.
Excuse me then.
Where are you going?
Yes?
I'm off to work.
I have to be here all alone?
Yes.
I'll take my leave.
Yes deputy chief.
I need Mr. Han Jiyu.
Excuse me?
What do you mean?
It's not easy to come up
with a dish alone.
I'd like to proceed with Mr. Han Jiyu,
who is in charge here
to help me create with a new dish.
Oh.
If that's the case
I'll find someone more professional
from another department for you.
Creating a new dish
isn't a job suited for Mr. Jiyu.
He's perfectly suitable.
The Hah Jiyu that I know
is more knowledgeable about food
than he looks.
- And...
- It's true though.
Mr. Jiyu is very knowledgeable
about food.
Is that right?
Alright.
Chief deputy Kim
are you okay with Mr. Jiyu
working on that?
Supporting menu development
alongside his current duties
should be manageable.
Is that so?
Very well let's go with that then.
- Yes.
- Please take care of Mr. Jiyu.
What Chief? I'm not a kid you know.
He's not perfect but
I'll make use of him.
He's lacking a lot
so I hope you'll be prepared.
Use me?
Am I just some object?
- That's not what I meant...
- Forget it.
Let's get to work.
There's a menu that requires clams.
Shall we try cooking it first?
Yes.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I'm alright but your shirt...
I'm very sorry. I'm so clumsy.
It's okay as long as you're uninjured.
It will dry off soon.
But it looks like
I'm not the only one who's wet.
Oh right.
That's true.
It's like
a scene in a drama
don't you agree?
Let's get this sorted out quickly.
Oh right.
Let me see.
Hey
knowing the taste of soju
is helpful in developing a dish right?
No, you don't have to drink now.
Alright.
I'll try it when I'm ready.
Let's take it slow shall we?
Let's do it tonight.
Chef.
You're here.
Wow.
What's this?
This is amazing.
It's beautiful here.
It's the best place
to have a late-night snack.
Come on it's ready.
Wow! Okay.
Can I sit next to you?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Are you alright?
Yes.
It's been a while since I drank...
It's just a little bit of tasting.
We need to taste it to develop a dish.
Right.
Is this your first time?
No it's not my first time.
How is it?
It's good.
What a relief.
Chef.
Only one glass?
You can't sleep here Chef.
Chef.
Oh no.
(Chef)
Hello.
Are you still sleeping?
Oh yes.
Wake up wash up and get ready.
- There's no time.
- Come again?
Isn't today a day off?
There's a place I want to bring you to.
Where?
(Keumgang Restaurant)
Want to grab something first?
Sounds good to me.
Wow.
So many customers in the morning?
They say this place is a favorite
among the Gunsan locals.
There may be other delicious
places favored by tourists
but nothing beats
authentic local flavor.
Yeah.
Is this a full course meal restaurant?
Yes.
You can call it a
seasonal full course meal restaurant.
Just hearing that
makes my heart flutter.
Looks delicious.
Spoon and chopsticks.
Here's your spoon.
Thank you.
All done.
- Please eat.
- Yes.
I'm digging in.
Auntie.
A bottle of soju, please.
One glass of soju please.
Wow, thank you.
Please drink moderately.
Can you fill my glass for me?
Shall we sit here?
Sure.
By the way do you also use social media?
No.
Is that so?
I think it's the first time
I've seen you taking pictures.
It's good for studying and
helps with remembering too.
Oh, Chef!
You're pretty cool.
How was the meal today?
Everything
was absolutely delicious.
I can already tell.
How did you know Chef?
Only one bite
and you immediately ordered soju.
I mean...
You're the one who ordered it.
It'd be such a waste
so I had no choice but to drink.
That's right.
If I hadn't stopped you
would you still be drinking by now?
No way. I wouldn't.
Do you like drinking that much?
I said no.
Seriously no.
This is my first time here.
Let's go.
(Fish market)
What they sell here is really fresh.
Yeah.
Sigh...
Let's go.
You should've woken me up.
I'm organizing my thoughts.
What's wrong?
Are you still uncomfortable to work with me?
No.
I think I can finally forget everything
and start fresh.
I'll change from now.
Good.
I really like this place.
It's like I can set my heart free here.
Isn't it nice?
I wish time would stop...
Why stop time?
Our time is waiting.
I beg your pardon?
Nothing. Let's go.
Please go and have a rest.
Yes.
Thank you for the ride.
You've worked hard.
I didn't work hard.
You're the one who worked hard Chef.
Besides I had fun.
Me too.
Please go inside now.
Alright.
Then please drive carefully.
Why
aren't you leaving yet?
I'm leaving.
Chef.
You see...
Let's
have ramyeon together?
No.
I don't want to.
Please eat a lot. I have rice too.
No...
rice, thanks.
How does the ramyeon taste?
Is it good?
At a time like this
it's right to eat ramyeon.
Right.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I think it's time
for you to go home.
It's already so late.
Oh...
I should leave?
Yes.
You're not leaving?
No.
Take care on your way home.
Yeah.
The ramyeon was great.
It tasted better when we ate together.
Yeah.
It seems like
we get along pretty well.
Hey.
Can I call you brother?
Come again?
Aren't we already
close with each other?
Is that okay with you?
Do whatever you want.
I'll take my leave.
Right.
Us?
(Han Jiyu)
(Tomorrow should we...)
(Did you get back safe and sound?)
(Park Kihoon)
Mr. Jiyu.
Yes?
Brother.
Why still call me Mr. Jiyu?
Oh...
So what is it?
I was going to say
the dish is now complete.
Oh.
What do you think?
Delicious.
It's a new and refreshing taste.
But...
But?
I don't know how to explain it but...
Umm...
It feels like it's lacking something.
Lacking where?
No rather than saying it's lacking
it would be better to add something.
Brother!
It's still great.
You have nothing to regret.
Shall we call other people
later as well?
Get some opinions by
having them taste it.
Okay.
I'll try contacting Wan.
Yeah.
Next dish.
- You're here, Wan.
- It's been a while, Brother.
You're here.
- Hello.
Did you guys come together?
- I'm Choi Wan.
- I'm Kim Yeon-ah.
- I'm Park Jiha.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm not that close to him.
What are you saying?
Hey what are you doing?
Why?
Brother.
Oh.
What's the matter?
What should I do?
Jiyu already helped out.
So you can just sit.
Umm...
Everything's tasty.
Very delicious.
It's...
Not bad at all.
It's good.
Adding dried distillers grains
to the food
goes really well with the alcohol and
complements its flavor.
Excellent idea.
But
won't you feel irritated
removing the fish bones
when eating a full course meal
like this?
Thank you.
It is a little annoying.
That was great.
Be careful.
Let's eat more and
let's all have fun.
Thank you everyone for coming.
Take care on your way home.
Let's keep the fun going.
Come on.
Hey Park Jiha.
Hurry up and go home.
What the heck are you saying?
Nice meeting you all today.
Let's meet again.
Excuse me then.
- Goodbye.
- Hey Wan.
- Please see off the deputy chief.
- Sure.
- I'll see you off.
- Alright.
- Bye.
- Hey Park Jiha.
Go home already.
I mentioned feeling upset lately
remember?
- I know. Let's talk about it later.
- I won't hang out with you.
I'm coming too!
Hurry up.
Wait for the fattie.
Sigh.
You should get going too.
I'll clean up the shop.
No way let's tidy up together.
- Let's help each other.
- No need.
Go home.
Fine.
Brother.
Everything will be fine.
So...
please don't worry about it.
Alright.
A bit more effort should be okay.
Keep fighting.
I'll be leaving then.
I'll leave now.
Alright.
Han Jiyu.
Yes?
Why?
Regretting something?
Pouring.
Brother.
I'll have one glass.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thanks for your hard work today.
Not at all. I didn't do anything.
It's all thanks to you.
How nice.
What's nice?
Nothing.
What is it?
You're always vague.
That's right.
You're all red again.
Again?
It's always like that.
What? You only had one glass of beer
and you're all red?
That's right.
Cheers.
Mr. Jiyu!
A moment please.
Alright.
What's the matter?
How is Mr. Kihoon these days?
He seems fine.
Listen to me carefully.
It looks like the chief wants
to have Mr. Kihoon featured
on a cooking show.
What?
- Please keep your voice down.
- Yes.
What's the matter?
The thing is...
The chief mentioned that
during the launch event they want you to
go cook on stage.
No way.
Brother why...
Just now
he didn't answer my call
and hasn't replied to my texts.
What should we do?
Should we go to his house?
Let's not.
Let's give him some time.
Still...
I don't know anymore.
(Are you upset with me?)
(Are you upset with me?/I'm really sorry about today./
Let me buy you a coffee./Let's go drink./I'm hungry.)
Brother?
You said you were hungry.
Even so
at a time like this?
Have you ever heard of
stage fright?
Of course.
When you're standing
in front of many people
and your vision becomes blurry.
I definitely have that.
My visions becomes blurry
and I can't see clearly.
In that situation
I can't utter a word.
I see.
I wasn't aware.
I'm sorry.
Why are you laughing?
Is it funny?
When you're in front of me
you tend to talk a lot.
When your vision is becoming blurry
try to focus on pleasant thoughts.
- Pleasant thoughts?
- Yes.
That should help.
No one is as strong-willed as you are.
The courage to turn away customers
for refusing to sell alcohol
and the courage to admit your mistakes
when you're in the wrong.
Please make use of this courage.
What kind of courage is that?
Admitting something isn't easy at all.
After all we care about
how others view us.
Also it takes courage
to be direct like this.
Well?
If you put it that way,
I'll give it a go.
Then...
Shall we be a little more courageous?
You asked me why.
I don't selling alcohol.
Are you going to let me know?
Do you remember?
The tteokbokki shop
that you were trying to find,
my grandmother opened
the shop to raise me.
She had a hard time raising
her grandson alone
so she drank every day.
I hated it.
It made me feel like I was the cause.
The night before
the university entrance ceremony
she drank alone again.
At that time I believed that the alcohol
was the cause for my loneliness.
Looking back
perhaps she was trying to
congratulate herself
for raising her grandson safely.
Perhaps she was consoling herself
for enduring hardships.
I said something heavy, didn't I?
No.
I was surprised
that you said it so easily.
Is that so?
It was very difficult.
Anyway
there are only pleasant times ahead
so let's do our best together.
Sure.
Now that.
I'm by your side
you don't feel lonely right?
Who knows.
Brother seriously.
Can't you tell me honestly?
It's been a while since I last worked.
I'm so tired.
Why are you out here?
I told you to rest.
I need to prepare myself
since I haven't worked for a while.
Now that I'm here, I can help you.
And it's the weekend
we had a lot of customers today!
Yes there were a lot of customers today.
Time went by in a flash.
Shop hours fly by when
there are many customers.
Brother
today is your last day right?
Yes.
Drink this.
You must be tired from work.
Brother Jiyu said today is his last day.
We can't end it like this.
What do you want to eat?
Nice!
Let's eat expensive food.
Yes my treat.
Eat whatever you want.
Alright!
What do you want to eat Brother?
Beef?
Or sashimi?
Pork belly?
What's this?
I wanted beef more.
It looks delicious here.
How can pork ever be better than beef?
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
Hello.
Wow he really is handsome.
Hey, Han Jiyu,
are you going to expose this place?
If it's here...
I don't easily tell others about here.
Wow really?
Please allow me to grill.
I can do it.
Let me pour you a drink.
Thank you.
You two worked really hard.
Don't hold back.
Let's raise our glasses for a toast!
- Cheers!
- Delicious!
Now I understand why you chose here.
- Pork belly is the best!
What was that?
After eating some kimchi with pork belly
and then some garlic
you wait a little while
and then wash away the grease
with a refreshing shot of soju.
After the bitter taste of
the soju fades away
you take another bite
and the cycle repeats.
I think the most delicious thing
in the world is pork belly.
The pork belly that is eaten together.
It's amazing.
You gourmet passion
is quite philosophical.
I respect you.
It's nothing like that.
You're exaggerating.
- Mr. Jiyu.
- Oh, yes.
Mr. Kihoon.
I'll pour for you.
Thank you.
You two look great together.
What are you saying?
Let's raise our glasses.
- Cheers!
That was great.
Chief deputy when was the
last time you went on a date?
- Me?
- I'm curious.
I...
It's a secret.
Then what do you think love is?
As for me.
I already broke up!
- Oh no.
- When did you break up?
That jerk.
Absolutely selfish.
- The worst.
- Really?
He's a douche and selfish.
There's no one on the street.
You're right.
Time flies.
It's tomorrow isn't?
Are you nervous?
I would be lying if I said no.
But I feel better when
I think good thoughts.
I wonder what you're thinking about.
Do you want me to tell you?
That's alright.
Thank goodness.
Let's go inside.
I...
What's going on?
If...
- you want to continue hanging...
- Forget it.
Oh over there.
Hello.
Jiyu hi hi.
You're here.
I called him over to cheer for you.
Chef.
You are so cool.
You're already cool
even before starting.
It's not that big of a deal.
Are you nervous?
Your face is all red.
Really?
There's no need to be nervous.
What are you nervous about?
Planning to do something really awesome?
Just like we practiced.
Don't be nervous.
No need to be nervous.
Alright. The event is starting now.
I'd like to thank all of you
who came to the launch event for
Baeksundang's new product
'Gidalim' today.
I would like to introduce Park Kihoon,
who'll be cooking today
as a collaboration.
Let's give a round of applause.
(Baeksundang's launch event
for our new product 'Gidalim')
What should we do? He seems stunned.
What should we do?
Brother.
When your vision gets blurry
try to focus on pleasant thoughts.
Pleasant thoughts.
Yes.
That should help.
Pleasant thoughts...
Good people...
Pleasant thoughts.
I'll start cooking now.
The first dish that I prepared today
is arancini
made from fermented cucumber
and dried distillers grains.
The aroma of the dried distillers grains
will still be present,
so when paired with alcohol
the taste is even better.
I also added rice so that you
won't experience any stomach pain
from consuming alcohol.
For the second course
we have a Korean-style pasta that
was created based on the popular pasta
among the younger generation.
The grilled Spanish mackerel
and coriander pasta.
The mackerel is perfectly grilled
to retain its flavor
and it's served with coriander
which helps reducing the greasiness.
To make it easier to eat with alcohol,
I only selected proper fish meat
for cooking.
I created these dishes especially
for those who aren't proficient
in using chopsticks
or have stomach discomfort
from drinking alcohol.
These factors motivated me
to develop these dishes.
I hope everyone will
enjoy these dishes and
have a delightful meal.
Thank you.
How beautiful.
It smells fantastic.
It's so delicious.
Why is Kihoon so awesome?
Chef this is the CEO.
Bravo!
You are Chef Kihoon right?
Hello, I'm Park Kihoon.
Thanks to your effort
our customers are having a great time.
Thank you so much.
- It wasn't all me.
- Of course.
I've heard about it.
Thank you for your effort,
Mr. Jiyu and Ms. Yeon-ah.
- Thank you.
Excuse me. Ms. Yeon-ah.
Enjoy as much as you want.
Eat drink and have fun.
- This way, sir.
- Thank you very much, sir.
Thank you.
Corporate card from the CEO
let's fully enjoy ourselves.
Everyone worked hard.
Is everyone wearing pants
with elastic waistbands?
Of course.
- We need to make the most out of it.
- Hey.
Why are you sitting here?
None of your business.
Enough.
Mr. Kihun please give a toast.
I'm not good at doing
that kind of thing.
You were awesome just now.
Yeah. You didn't tremble one bit.
But Chef
weren't you only staring at Mr. Jiyu?
I don't know how to give a toast.
It's awkward
but I'll give it a try.
Let's be happy!
I can't make myself drink.
Let's be happy?
Just like an old man.
But you said being happy
is the most important thing.
Having good friends
enjoy eating and drinking together.
- It's nice.
- You're right.
I think our relationship will be strong.
- I'm happy too.
- Bottoms up!
- Let's be happy!
- I'm really happy.
- Yeah.
Absolutely happy.
- Eat as much as you want!
- Don't hold back.
- I'm digging in.
- I'll eat so much that I can't walk.
(AS IF YOUR LAST BOTTLE)
- Enjoying yourself?
- Yes.
- Please eat a lot.
Where are you going?
I'm going for a breath of fresh air.
Much better.
The heavy smell of meat and alcohol...
It's suffocating.
Shall we take a walk?
They should be alright, yeah?
I'm going for a short walk.
Shall we sit here?
Sure.
What were you thinking back then?
Pleasant thoughts like you told me.
Yeah but what exactly?
Umm...
It's fine. You don't have to say it.
You're also drunk Brother.
Everything...
is finally over.
Our collaboration
has come to an end.
Disappointed?
Sorry.
You asked about what my thoughts were
you were on my mind.
I had a blast today.
See you next time!
Don't just say next time.
How about next weekend?
Let's meet again next weekend night.
- Sounds great!
- Potluck party!
I'll find a location.
Let's go Sister.
I'll get going first.
- Bye bye.
- Take care.
Safe travels!
- You too.
- Why do I have to go too?
Just hurry.
- Take him with you.
- Hey guys!
I am not drunk.
Why is my stomach growling?
Be quiet.
This isn't the time.
Are you hungry?
You have ramyeon at home right?
Yeah I've got all kinds.
Today
I'll make a delicious ramyeon.
At night?
Which flavor do you want?
Are you really going to eat ramyeon?
What were you thinking?
What are you thinking?
We're having ramyeon of course.
Which flavor?
Then...
Shall we
have ramyeon later?
Hello.
Could you call the owner for us?
Yes this way please.
Chef.
Hello.
It's been a while.
You still remember us?
Of course.
It was so memorable
that I couldn't forget.
I want to apologize
for being rude back then.
No need.
To be honest
I also need to apologize to you too.
It'd be nice if we can
understand each other
and move on from it.
You're really kind.
Do you sell alcohol now?
Yes.
Then we can eat here right?
Of course.
I'll assume we're old friends,
I'll give you special service.
Enjoy your meal and come back often.
Thank you.
(Goosoo Restaurant)
Closed.
(Take away service)
(Closed for the afternoon due to personal reasons)
Hello.
What's this?
Everyone came first before me.
Oh I also ordered chicken.
Me too.
Is it a chicken party today?
It seems so. There's only chicken here.
That's why I said we should have
mentioned our menu first.
The one who asked me
to keep it a secret was you Park Jiha.
I already know!
I really like chicken okay?
I'll be chicken or dog
or anything today.
Yeah, just enjoy it.
- Isn't that right?
- Yes.
What to do?
It's just chicken here.
But they are all different flavor.
It's the first time
I've had five flavors.
Yes.
Usually you have to buy the mixed one
to get a lot of radishes.
It's fine. Let's dig in.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Who brought this flavor?
Me.
I love hot barbecue Brother.
- Excellent.
- But I can't handle spicy food.
Oh really?
You can try this.
It's garlic sauce. It's not spicy.
Thanks.
- Jiyu, don't hold back, okay?
- Yes.
I have something to say.
Wan and I are going out.
Yeah I know.
- I know.
- What?
Did you think we wouldn't know?
It was so obvious.
Was it obvious?
So annoying.
Sorry but everyone just leave please.
I will eat all the chicken by myself.
What a loser.
What?
Let's have a second round to celebrate
them becoming a couple.
Then why don't we go celebrate
at the rooftop?
- Okay!
We don't have to go anywhere far.
What?
It's just...
Yeah? Just what?
What's with him?
What?
It's just...
Yeah? Just what?
Are you copying me?
Hmm?
Do you like me?
I like you.
I like you too.
Cheers to everyone who became a couple!
Cheers!
What? Mr. Jiyu, you too.
Forget it.
- Cheers!
Leaving me all alone,
you guys are going overboard.
Cheers to you too.
Cheers.
Wow it's delicious.
- Very delicious.
- What wine is it?
Italian wine.
You're not making this up, right?
Don't tease him.
You really know how to pick.
Not at all.
- I like this type of bread.
- Try this.
Try it.
- Care for one?
- I'm on a diet.
Why? You're already so beautiful.
I'm going home.
Why?
- Where are you going?
I'm going to find love.
Don't try to stop me.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Hello.
- This is our part-timer.
- Hello.
- He'll join us too. Hope you don't mind.
- Of course.
- Hello.
I brought a bottle of wine
when I got the invitation.
What?
Well, weren't you leaving?
Do you like collecting wine?
Unbelievable!
I'm surrounded by
people who can talk
and laugh about anything.
Even the toughest moments
turn into small problems and,
as time goes by,
the person who helped me
through the tough times
is now laughing right beside me.
Happiness...
is right here.