As such, the prosecution is indicting Choi Cheol Woong the
fine for assault ₩100,000 (75 USD, $425 in 1975).
For Lee Doo Hak...
I'm sorry.
Didn't I tell you that I will watch a movie today?
I forgot.
I feel you're slacking off (lazing) these days.
Do you want me to hit you with my nunchucks?
One of them came, but didn't the other?
I should just beat up these guys!
Of course, he'll come. Just wait a bit.
Oh, that scared me!
Gosh, that took me by surprise.
Gosh, seriously!
First, I'll meet you.
But with whom?
I don't know. Let's wait and see for that.
How can I pick when I've only seen you a couple times?
How long will you wait and see?
For about a year?
Until then, we can meet as friends. Happy?
He really became gutsy (bold), hasn't he?
Would he dare stand up Oh Jung Shin?
Do you think he forgot?
"He forgot"?
You guys are just the same!
What are you guys, brothers?
Let's just go inside by ourselves.
W-Wait, let's not do that.
How about we wait for him a bit longer?
I'm dating you! I'm not dating Cheol Woong!
Cheol Woong doesn't know that yet...
I will tell him today.
It's time for the movie to start. Let's go inside.
W-Wait.
Gosh, I don't think we should.
Let's look around for Cheol Woong a bit more.
You just wait here.
I'll be right back after circling the block.
Hey!
Look! It's Choi Cheol Woong.
Come see our new and latest products!
Please come!
What? Look at this b*stard.
Where did you hide your money?
The money...
It's my family's bank so try going to the bank, you b*stard.
Gosh, look at this crazy b*stard.
Just see how he talks to a hyung.
You haven't had enough, you b*stard.
Cheol Woong!
- Are you okay?
- Oh my!
Go away.
I told you to go away!
Just leave me alone!
Hey, Choi Cheol Woong.
Is she your girlfriend?
She's so scary, much scarier than you.
What are you guys, thugs?
Piss off (get lost) before I report you guys!
Oh my! Oh my!
Let's go, Choi Cheol Woong, please!
Let's quickly go.
Hey.
Let go of me!
You f***ing pieces of trash!
This rude b*tch!
You f***ing son of a b*tch!
No, Cheol Woong! No!
Let's just report them! You can't do this!
Put that away!
Someone, save us!
I thought educated guys wouldn't use weapons.
Stay still!
I might have to start wearing a steel plate underneath my shirt.
You try wielding a knife at me again.
I'll crush you then.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Are you okay?
Are you okay? Oh, no...
You...
That f***ing son of a b*tch!
I'll kill him with my own hands!
No, Cheol Woong! It's okay.
- Don't fight him. Let's just report him.
- No.
I will pay him back ten, no, a hundred times for this!
No, Cheol Woong. Doo Hak will be here soon.
Let's just go to him.
Why?
Are you saying I should tell on them to Hyung?
Why are you being like that when we're friends?
"Friends"?
I'm back.
Hey, you don't stop by Cheol Woong's school after you finish school, right?
Oh, I went a few times, but Cheol Woong said I didn't have to come anymore.
Cheol Woong.
Cheol Woong!
Let's at least go to the pharmacy to treat your wounds.
Didn't you say we should stay friends for a year?
You said it,
that you can't pick since you only saw us a couple times.
My feelings just turned out like that.
I understand.
So quickly go home.
Cheol Woong. Doo Hak is waiting for us–
I don't want to see the two of you today!
That's how I feel!
Cheol Woong!
Cheol Woong.
It's me.
I heard you got hurt. Did you get in a fight?
Am I someone who would go around getting beaten up?
I got a bit hurt after tripping.
Did you get hurt badly?
Let me see your wound.
I'm fine so just go.
What are you talking about?
Come on, let me see it!
I told you I'm fine!
Who messed you up like this?
What do you mean someone hit me?
I told you I just tripped!
Just go away!
Mom.
Why are you here?
I was worried about the boy.
Whom did he fight with?
He says he just tripped.
Do you actually believe that?
Cheol Woong is too proud to admit it, even if he did get hit.
I told you to just leave, didn't I?
Cheol Woong, it's me.
Hyung just left a moment ago.
It's not about that.
I just heard you got hurt a little bit.
I bought this at the market last time.
It's made in the U.S.!
It's really good for bruises or sprains.
I tried using it before
and the next day, it didn't hurt at all anymore!
What are you doing here?
Oh, it's not like that, Ma'am... Oh, no...
I just heard Cheol Woong was a bit hurt
so I brought him good ointment.
We have first aid medication at our home, too.
Also,
even if we neighbors are comfortable with each other,
isn't it too rude of you to enter our place at this late hour
without permission?
I'm sorry.
Doo Hak, you, too.
Don't come here when it's late.
Okay.
Let's go.
Just get going.
Aigoo! I have no affection for her whatsoever!
She's so young, yet she thinks she's the wife of a lord!
But who beat up Cheol Woong like that?
When he was hanging out with you, things like that never happened.
Gosh, when your father said he'd send you to agricultural high school,
I should have done everything to stop him!
Are you upset that I went to an agricultural high school, or that Cheol Woong was beaten up?
I'm upset about both.
Both.
Gosh.
I'm sure I told you not to come.
I didn't come to go with you.
Jung Shin said she really needed to see you tonight.
She says she has something to tell you,
where we ate grilled clams.
What about you, Hyung?
I'll come later.
I'm ashamed of myself, Oppa.
He's quite an amazing man.
But would he reject our nomination and run independently?
I know it's like hitting your head against a brick wall.
I'll do whatever I can to make him reconsider.
We don't even have money so how could he run independent of a party?
He kicked aside a feast table for him. How do you stop him?
Madam Kang, you're going through a lot after marrying a lofty-minded man.
Okay. You can go now.
And take this with you.
- No, how could I?
- Just take it.
This is probably the money you gathered from your emergency funds.
Use it to provide for your household.
No, I–
I'm sorry, Oppa.
What's the likelihood Choi Young Shik will be elected?
Well...
I also spoke to Korea Central Intelligence Agency.
- What did they say?
- It's likely he will receive more than 30% of the votes.
So he may come out on top, winning the election.
Really?
He's got quite a following in the region as a familiar face,
and he has afterglow of his father being an independence movement leader.
Have you looked into his weaknesses?
His history is clean with both his business and women.
If you had not done something about it in advance,
it would have been quite the headache, Commander.
I am Ki Young Tak.
Do you want to get expelled and go to prison?
I'm sorry!
I won't ever bully these guys again.
I mean it, I swear!
What?
That's not what you need to do.
You know him, right?
Oh, yes.
He always goes everywhere with the guy he calls Hyung.
Choi Cheol Woong.
Yes.
Well, all you have to do is get beat up by Choi Cheol Woong a bit.
If you bleed, even better.
Excuse me?
Seriously.
Yes, yes.
Don't you love me?
Gosh, this b*stard.
How could you turn your back on me?
Gosh, this b*stard, seriously!
He's so weak!
I'll go to throw up.
What's this?
Jung Shin isn't coming.
Also, I heard what this b*stard did.
Did I ever tell you to do this, Hyung?
I was going to beat him up even without your help, Hyung.
What? Do you think I would lose?
Do you think that I would lose to someone like him?
Hurry up and ask for his forgiveness.
And say that you won't ever bother him again.
Are you joking?
You're a man, yet you bring another; can't you beat me on your own?
You idiot.
Hey, Ki Young Tak. What did you say, you b*stard?
Forget it.
You should stay out of this, Hyung.
Cheol Woong. You should stop.
I already beat him up enough.
I told you to move aside.
What are you going to do?
I can get over me getting hit,
but this b*stard...
This scum hit Jung Shin!
Even I can't forgive him so you shouldn't forgive him all the more!
Since you guys decided to go out,
isn't that right?
Did Jung Shin really get hit by this creep?
Hey, Ki Young Tak.
It's great not having your minions here.
I will fight you one-on-one, fair and square.
If you win, I'll give you money too.
But if you lose, you will die here.
You got that?
You talk too much.
- Hey.
- Let go of me!
You can't beat me, a**hole!
- Fight me.
- Get up, you b*stard.
Got it?
I told you to get up!
Don't come over here!
If you get involved, I won't hold back, even if you're my hyung.
The most disgusting people in this world are the ones
who rely on their connections to bail them out like you!
Don't ever act like you're all that in front of that girl.
Are we finished here?
I can go now, right?
Cheol Woong!
Get up and fight me again!
I told you to get up.
Ki Young Tak, wake up.
Young Tak!
Wh-What's this?
Is he dead?
Hey, Young Tak!
Ki Young Tak!
Gosh, darn it!
Doctor!
Yeosu Police Station received a call from a hospital.
Two students brought in an injured Ki Young Tak on their shoulders,
and he's currently in a coma.
He won't die, right?
Hyung, people don't die that easily, right?
He won't die.
He'll definitely live.
Cheol Woong.
Let's turn ourselves in.
Even if he were to survive, we should pay the consequence.
Hyung. I didn't do anything wrong.
This is self-defense.
Okay, so let's go to the police station and tell them.
I-I can't!
I won't go!
Also, is this my fault?
When did I ever tell you to bring that b*stard, Young Tak, to me?
You tricked me by lying to me.
You said Jung Shin wanted to see me.
Didn't you bring that rat, knowing full well
that I would do something to him if you brought him?
So all of this is your fault, Hyung.
Am I wrong?
I asked if I'm wrong!
You're right.
I guess this was all my fault.
It's all my fault.
No...
I must have lost it just then.
I'm the one who struck him with a rock.
All you did was try to help me, Hyung.
Right?
Hyung, I'm so scared.
If that b*stard dies,
I would become a murderer and go to prison.
Can my father become an assemblyman? Forget that! He'll face public shame.
And my mother, who sees me as her only hope, will collapse.
What should I do, Hyung?
What do I do?
Hyung.
Can't you please save me just this once?
Can't you tell them that you were the one who hit Young Tak with a rock instead of me?
Cheol Woong...
Hyung. Hyung, Hyung!
Please save me!
If you do this for me just this once, I will take responsibility for your life!
No, I will devote my life to becoming successful, and I'll give you all I have.
I know, Hyung, that you always gave up a lot for me.
But really, I'll let you live as the one on top instead of me.
Hyung... Please save me this once!
Hyung...
Why should I do that?
You're the one who did that; why do I have to take the blame?
Both my father
and I lived like your servants all our lives!
Why do I have to take the blame for something like this as well!
Is it fine for you to live and for me to die?
Is your life a human life, and mine a dog's or pig's life?
Hey.
What are you doing not going to bed?
Ahjussi, if something goes wrong with Cheol Woong,
I, my husband, and our entire family will die.
I'm begging you. Please save him...
You're my only hope, Ahjussi.
- The only one who can save our family–
- Ma'am!
I've never said no to anything you requested of me.
But...
But this... I don't think this is right.
How could I do that to Doo Hak just to save Cheol Woong?
Ahjussi!
Once my husband gets elected, he will make sure he gets out of prison in no time.
- I will make sure that happens!
- Darn it!
I will make sure to hire the best lawyer available.
Ahjussi...
If my husband loses the election, we will all die.
Only if he wins the election will we all live.
Please, I beg you! Save us!
Save us, Ahjussi!
Gosh, darn it...
Ahjussi, Ahjussi!
No, Ahjussi, please!
Save us, Ahjussi, please!
No, Ahjussi!
Let me go!
- No!
- Ahjussi, Ahjussi!
Ahjussi!
No, no! Ahjussi!
I'm really sorry!
Just this once,
please save me just this once!
Please save me this once!
- Please save me this once!
- Ahjussi!
Ahjussi...
Gosh, darn it, you b*stard!
Why did you do this, you b*stard?
Why did you do that?
- Ahjussi!
- Please, just this once...
Please save me just this once.
Doo Hak...
Wait!
You must have made a mistake.
My son is surely not someone who would do that.
Please look into it again before you come.
We're going to question him when we get to the police station so just wait a bit.
What do you mean by "question him"?
You can ask all in this neighborhood,
if there is anyone as studious and upright as my Doo Hak!
If you keep doing this, I'll also take you in for obstruction of justice!
Go ahead! Go ahead and take me in!
Take me in, too!
You can't take my child!
You can't!
Doo Hak, hurry and tell them it's not you!
Tell them that you did nothing wrong!
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
Hey, Officer Kim and Officer Park! Why aren't you doing anything?
Doo Hak...
Doo Hak, what's going on?
Gosh, what's with this girl now?
It's not you, right?
You would never do something like that. Right?
Hey, Lee Doo Hak!
Look into my eyes and tell me.
You're not the type of guy who would do that. Right?
It's not you!
Please step aside.
Please wait!
Lee Doo Hak! Lee Doo Hak!
Doo Hak, Doo Hak.
Cheol Woong, Cheol Woong, you know it, right?
Doo Hak isn't someone who would do that.
Choi Cheol Woong, Lee Doo Hak!
Answer me!
Please, just a moment! Guys! Just a moment!
Doo Hak!
Doo Hak...
do not forgive your father...
Doo Hak! You can't take my child away!
You can't take my child away!
No, you can't! You can't take him!
You can't do this!
- Mom!
- Doo Hak.
Doo Hak!
- Doo Hak!
- Mom! I'm sorry!
Doo Hak...
Those mean b*stards...
Take me with you!
You can't take my child away!
What? His friend confessed to the crime?
Yes, his name is Lee Doo Hak.
He testified that when he saw Choi Cheol Woong get severely beaten up by Ki Young Tak,
he struck Ki Young Tak with a rock.
This won't do!
Lee Doo Hak is useless to me!
Keep delaying the court date until after the election.
We must make Choi Cheol Woong, son of Choi Young Shik, into a murder accomplice.
Understood.
- Lee Jeong Nam, Lee Jeong Nam!
- Choi Young Shik, Choi Young Shik!
I am Candidate 2, Kim Wang Geun!
I'm Candidate 3.
Please. Thank you!
- Lee Jeong Nam, Lee Jeong Nam!
- Choi Young Shik, Choi Young Shik!
Everyone!
Shouldn't we end the dictatorial regime this time
and move toward the democracy we long for, everyone?
Thank you!
Yes, thank you!
Choi Young Shik, the father of a murderer, should resign!
Choi Young Shik, who raised a murderer, should go away!
Everyone! Yes, although there was an unfortunate accident,
- that has nothing to do with my son–
- Resign!
Resign!
Come to your senses!
So didn't you tell me that Cheol Woong was a material witness?
You said he didn't fight him!
Why did you lie? Why?
Supposedly, he did get into a fight.
But supposedly, Cheol Woong was getting beat up.
After seeing that, Doo Hak got angry and struck the guy with a rock.
No.
That's not true. The Doo Hak I know would never do that.
By chance, is our Cheol Woong responsible for this mess?
Honey!
Honey.
You're hiding something from me, aren't you?
Tell me the truth!
Mr. Choi.
That day, Doo Hak told me everything.
He said he did it.
Is that true?
Yes...
It's the absolute truth.
Then what about the fight?
Who was the one who started the fight?
W-Well...
- about that...
- Hyungnim.
Please tell me.
It's true that Cheol Woong started it.
It is true that my son was involved.
Because of a loser like me,
you all have gone through a lot.
I don't know what to say.
Truly, I'm sorry.
No, you can't!
You must not resign from the election!
The murderer is Doo Hak, not Cheol Woong!
Also, even if you are not elected as first place,
you could still be elected in second place!
It's all over.
How could someone so false like me serve in office?
It's not over.
- We can't let it be over!
- Honey...
Do you know how much money we poured into this?
If we back out now, we will lose our lumber mill and farmland too!
Did you... secure even the farmland as collateral?
Yes!
I bet my life on your election.
If you resign here... we'll be going down as a family.
Why a public attorney?
Didn't Cheol Woong's father say he'll provide an expensive lawyer?
Doo Hak's father... refused.
As such, the prosecution is indicting Choi Cheol Woong the
fine for assault ₩100,000.
For Lee Doo Hak, for bodily injury resulting in death,
a maximum of five years
or a minimum sentence of three years imprisonment.
Aigoo...
My poor child...
How on Earth?
Attorney. Last defense, please.
Defendant, are you regretful?
Yes.
Your Honor, the defendant says he's regretful.
No way!
This can't be!
Aigoo...
This is the verdict.
Do you call yourself a father?
How could you still call yourself a father?
Why didn't you let us use a good lawyer?
For what?
You also know well what Mr. Choi's finances are like!
Also, if he committed a crime... he needs to be punished.
The dead child's parents probably have a stake in their hearts!
How could we be shameless to lighten his sentence?
Doo Hak!
- Please stand back.
- Lee Doo Hak!
♫  I want to hold on your hand  ♫
♫  I want it to be like a birthday  ♫
♫  No matter you will be here, Forever Love, the only one  ♫
♫  I want to like that you're mine, hate me or nice  ♫
♫  Let me in your beautiful life  ♫
♫  Come over here, back in your love, in my life  ♫
♫  Let me go  ♫
♫  In my life  ♫
♫  Let me go in your life  ♫
♫  Love you, no more  ♫
♫  I want to be myself  ♫
♫  Let me go  ♫
It wasn't me.
♫  Let me go, in my life  ♫
Hey.
Hey, you.
Wake up.
He's about to die!
Call an ambulance, you punks!
What the heck are you doing?
Hey, Jung Shin.
Choi Cheol Woong?
Did you watch this movie?
Not yet.
What about this one?
I haven't watched...
that one yet, either.
Hey, don't you even have a girlfriend?
Not having watched stuff everyone else watched?
You're right.
Come to our theater.
Your noona (older "sister" of male) will let you in free at Projection.
Well, that sounds great, free movies.
By the way...
why didn't you let me know?
Oh, my dad's passing?
I didn't want to bother you to come down from Seoul.
It must have been hard on you.
I'm sorry.
A friend should have been by your side at such a time.
I'm okay.
My relatives are helping me out a lot, too.
Anyway, why are you going down when it's not even  vacation?
I'm going to Dad's memorial service.
Right. It was about this time of year.
Gosh, we're so in the same boat.
Never mind.
You're a college student, and I'm a business owner who quit school.
It will take you at least 20 years to become a business owner.
What about Hyung Doo Hak?
I haven't heard that name in a while.
I don't know.
I guess you can say he was gone with the wind?
What about you? You probably keep in touch with him.
I also didn't get to see him at all.
Why? Weren't you two like brothers?
He always refuses my visit.
Also, my situation is a little troubled.
What's wrong with your situation?
Aigoo, can they really catch spies like that?
Jung Shin...
seems we'll have to watch the movie next time.
Don't ever tell that you know me, okay?
Get that b*stard!
Hey, get that a**hole!
I see you got promoted. Are you going to Seoul?
Yes. I plan to transfer to the reserve force soon.
Why?
It's well known that the elder favors you a lot, Oppa.
I'm sick of wandering all my life, and the world has changed as well.
Sir keeps telling me to lead a different task.
What kind of...
Later.
I don't think I can visit too often once I go.
Hang in there. Contact me if you have any problems.
Okay.
Was your visit to Seoul all right, Boss?
Are we getting any customers?
As you see, we're selling out every day.
The audience is totally loving it!
Anyhow, just like "Raiders,"
if we just say the Hollywood punks made it, it's bound to be daebak (awesome)!
It's an African movie, you idiot.
By the way, the print is too worn out.
So I think we'll have to cut at least 10 minutes of it.
How much screen time do you think will remain when we cut it down then?
Since we'll cut out about 20 minutes of 109 minutes,
there should be almost 90 minutes left.
Will the audience understand the story then?
Don't cut out too much; just show it as it is.
I understand.
- Director Go!
- Oh my!
Are you back again?
I must get the print today, no matter what.
What's the deal with this little girl?
Who are you, Ahjumma?
If you don't want to get hurt, stay out of this.
How dare this little girl—
Move aside!
I'm sorry. Please come this way.
Okay!
- Without spending a penny, you'll get a lot of...
- H-Hey!
advertising tomorrow on the news about the theater!
What are you doing right now?
Is your nose not working?
Don't you smell something pungent?
Stop! Have you gone crazy?
Yes. I've gone crazy.
You won't listen to me when I talk sanely
so I must go insane. Am I wrong?
S-Stop! Put that match down right now!
Are you going to give it...
or not?
Darling.
The matches must be wet.
Use that.
It's guaranteed to light.
It's made in the U.S.A.
She's gone crazy, right?
Are you going to give it to me or not?
Are you the daughter of Namhae Theater's Mr. Oh?
I did hear your father passed away.
I felt really bad for not being able to attend the funeral as I was in Seoul back then.
- Director Go.
- Yes.
You attended, right?
Well, the thing is... I was also busy so...
Is that so?
Well, you are always busy with something, Director Go.
So the short story is you paid for half the sale price of "Bushman,"
and you were to pay the rest today,
but you will pay after showing it in Yeosu since your finances are in trouble?
That's what you're saying, right?
Yes.
- Director Go.
- Yes.
Did our distributing agency ever do that?
It never happened before and will never transpire in the future!
- Don't use fancy words.
- Okay.
How unfortunate, Agasshi (Young Lady).
He said it won't work.
Will you lend me that lighter again?
Oh my. Th-This wicked—
Director Go.
Yes.
As soon as we're done with the showing, give her the "Bushman" prints.
Sorry?
Give it to her.
O-Okay, Boss.
Boss, thank you so much.
Thank you so much, really!
I won't ever forget your favor.
Take your leave.
Thank you.
Wait, Boss. Why are you doing something you don't usually do?
Hey, you a**hole.
Discount her 20% as the print is worn out.
Discount 30% for not doing our human duty and skipping the funeral,
then we don't need the remaining balance.
Do you still think yourself human?
- This little...
- Oh my. It hurts.
- It hurts so much.
- Also...
two years ago, I'm sure
you wrote in the ledger ₩50,000 expense as condolence payment for Mr. Oh.
You embezzled that money, didn't you, you b*stard?
Boss.
Gosh, this little...
It hurts.
Boss...
Are you coming now?
Why are you sitting there, Uncle?
The chair was so nice and comfy
so I was just feeling it.
Having competence makes you a boss,
not just sitting in the boss' seat.
Honey, why would you say something like that?
Jung Shin works so hard to keep this theater alive.
So did it come alive?
I got the "Bushman" print so I can repay you a portion.
Please take your leave now.
"A portion"?
How much of a portion?
Are you even accounting right?
Your father alone took 50 million won ($38,000)!
I'll repay whatever it is, 50 million or 100 million!
So take your leave now.
How dare you raise your voice?
- What?
- Gosh.
You have nothing to say, even if I claim this theater as mine right now.
Gosh, Honey.
She said she will repay us.
It's not like we're loan sharks.
We can't do this to another family member.
You have no idea what that money means to me.
Since our father left all his inheritance to Oppa,
I had to work like a dog and an ox to
make that money, not spending a single won!
Is that why you're playing with interest like a dog and an ox?
What?
I have given you
more than the principal amount in interest already, Aunt.
It was secured as collateral anyway
so if I fail to repay you later,
you can take this theater.
But please take your leave now, I said!
You're finally showing your true colors!
All right.
If you don't repay me within this year,
- this theater is mine!
- Aigoo, let's go. Come on.
How dare she raise her voice when she owes us money?
What has this world come to that
scammers and debtors are so shameless?
Aigoo, Jung Shin, we're leaving now.
Aigoo.
What about Cheol Woong?
I waited at the station all this time, but I didn't see him yet.
What could be the matter?
He said he'll come down for sure, though.
What could have possibly happened?
The last bus comes one hour later.
So I'll go out to the station one more time and wait.
Okay.
The night air is cold.
So please go inside now.
I heard your father passed away.
And you left college.
I heard everything from Jung Ok.
I see.
I mean, Father has been sick for a long time.
So I've been preparing myself.
I'm okay.
I'm really okay.
Jung Shin...
please stop coming now.
Is something wrong?
I...
don't have the confidence.
Let's break up.
Hey, what the heck are you saying?
You can get back on your feet with no problem.
You passed the GED and you can get into a college, Doo Hak.
I've...
been thinking hard for a long time.
All this happened because of you.
What do you mean?
I wouldn't have competed with Cheol Woong if you had not shown up.
More than...
Cheol Woong,
when I heard you got hit by Young Tak,
I already
wanted to kill that b*stard.
It wasn't an accidental death by assault.
I really wanted to kill him.
Lee Doo Hak... are you filming a tear-jerker?
Do you feel sorry for me that my father passed away and I quit school?
So since you're a murderer whose future is doomed,
will you step out of my life for me, although it breaks your heart?
Is it something like that?
Did I say I'll marry you or something?
It makes me feel even more miserable if it was out of pity.
You're really...
Whatever you say doesn't matter to me,
but what's certain is...
that you're a worse prison than this place.
Please let me go now.
I mean it.
Lee Doo Hak...
Lee Doo Hak!
Down with dictatorship!
Fight for democracy!
- Down with dictatorship!
-  Down with dictatorship!
Fight for democracy!
Down with dictatorship! Fight for democracy!
Gosh, let me go—
He's the instigator.
Get that b*stard!
Who are you? What?
What are you scheming?
Take off the gas mask.
I don't know who you are,
but thank you anyway.
Hyung?
Hyung Doo Hak.
You.
What's the deal with you?
Do you want to get locked up that badly?
Didn't you say you'll take responsibility for my life?
You said you'll be successful in your life and repay me, you a**hole!
-  ♪ When 30 million are asleep, we stay awake! ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey! ♪
♪ On the day our farmer brothers ♪
- I went to see you many times.
- ♪  Were  ♪
♪ Crying out loud ♪
Did I tell you to come visit me?
- What did you promise me?
-  ♪ Promising upon ♪
- My, you changed a lot, Hyung.
-  ♪ Bitten fingers ♪
Where did the pure Lee Doo Hak go?
Don't you know our positions changed now?
Back then, my father owed your family a debt.
Now, you owe me a debt.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
Therefore, from now,
I'll have you work as my underling,
a very hardworking one.
Would there be any question about that?
Order me to do whatever you want, Master.
I'm not joking, you a**hole!
Hey.
Quit your protesting right away and
prepare for the bar exam.
If you put your mind to it, you can pass the bar exam.
Become a prosecutor.
"A prosecutor"?
By what I experienced in jail, prosecutors seem to be the most powerful.
Well, have you visited home yet?
Are your mom and dad doing well?
Jung Ok must be all grown up, too.
Where do you live now?
I didn't visit home; my mom and dad aren't doing well.
Jung Ok is grown up, and I live in Seoul.
Happy now?
Here's my address and contact info.
Your dad and mom...
probably miss you a lot, Hyung.
Oh, I also met Jung Shin.
She seemed to be suffering a lot.
She quit school and
from what I hear,
her aunt from Seoul is trying to take away the theater.
Don't even think of avoiding my contact.
Why would I avoid your contact, Hyung?
I'm pleased and glad to see you.
Pass the exam before graduation.
It's an order.
In that case...
what will you do in the meantime?
I must keep an eye on you.
Take care, Hyung!
Also, what's the name of my mother's younger brother?
What's the younger brother's name?
-  It's Soon Man.
- That's right.
Soon Man!
-  And also—
- After him...
That's right.
They found her. They did.
They're both fine.
-  Also, what's the name?
- Sorry?
The name of the girl...
Wait, are those punks coming or not?
I got my eyes on a good one.
Let's go and pluck fresh eyeballs (real estate scams).
Do we even have a target?
Wait, I think everyone is here.
Why don't you give details?
Wait a minute.
One more person will come, okay?
- It's a cop!
- What—
Gosh...
Hey, quickly come inside.
All right now. Gather around.
All right. Let me introduce the last member of our team.
Who's this baby?
How pretty.
How gorgeous.
Oh! Poop at home.
Did you bring it?
- Bring it in three days.
- Okay.
Hey!
- Why?
- Why aren't you doing your errand right?
I bought an apple just like you told me to.
Try taking a bite. You try it!
I told you to buy a Fuji apple, didn't I?
This is a Jonathan apple!
I mean, what's... what's the difference?
A-Aigoo, sh*t.
Gosh, I knew it. Noonim...
- Gosh, it's the same.
- This little...
The rice was cooked perfectly.
Well, it's not too bad.
- Are you happy now?
- Yes, l-let me see.
Aigoo, had you done this earlier, we wouldn't have had to raise our voices.
Aunt, you also stamp your seal here.
Gosh, why do we need a seal between us?
If you just repay the money, I'll give you the theater back right away.
She's right. There needs to be trust between an aunt and a niece.
That's true for other families.
Our family is exceptionally special.
Aren't we?
Aunt, Uncle!
You'd better not forget your promise.
Of course! Don't worry.
That's right.
We moved our office, Jung Shin. Okay?
Stop by when you come to Seoul. I will treat you to Chinese food, your favorite.
From what I hear, her aunt from Seoul is trying to take away the theater.
♫  I want to hold on your hand  ♫
♫  I want it to be like a birthday  ♫
♫  No matter you will be here, Forever Love, the only one  ♫
♫  I want to look at your mind, hate me or nice  ♫
♫  Let me in your beautiful life  ♫
♫  Come over here, back in your love, in my life  ♫
♫  Let me go  ♫
♫  In my life  ♫
You said one of your aunts owns a theater in Gwangju, right?
-  My mom's cousin.
- Get lost.
Don't meet Doo Hak again. Nothing good will come from being connected with him.
I'm not sure. He just seems changed as a person.
I don't care about the money, but you should give me that.
It has a proper owner.
Let's not live in shame.
We can't live shamefully.
Even in the worst situation, I did my best not to be shameful.
What's this place for?
Can't you tell from just looking?
Hyung, don't you want to go down to Yeosu once?
You also miss Jung Shin, right?
Gosh, go there if you want, you punk!
♫  No matter you will be here  ♫