[English subtitles are available]
[My Lovely Wife]
[Episode 6]
With all due respect,
as the influence of the previous prostitute scandal has been lifted,
you might as well claim
that you were deceived by Xu Nian
and you yourself are a victim.
It will draw public sympathy.
It'll be good for you in terms of public opinion.
What about Xu Nian?
Whether Ms Xu's scandal is true or not,
it's the best time to dissociate yourself from her.
Besides, you need to explain to your father, too.
Where are you going?
I'm going to explain to the reporters.
I'll take care of my own business.
Don't go.
Don't worry. I'll help you.
Inform the Technology Department to work on it immediately.
Yes.
Mrs. Xu, do you mean
the rumors online are all true?
Xu Nian is my stepdaughter.
I know her best.
Actually, we were surprised
when learned about her engagement
with Gu Mingyuan.
We didn't even have time to object.
As Xu Nian's parent,
I really don't want to see this happen.
I apologize to the Gu family on behalf of Xu Nian.
Mrs. Xu, I'm afraid
as a stepmother, you're not qualified
to be the spokesperson of my fiancée.
Everyone,
the intimate photos of Xu Nian and others spreading online
all have trails showing that they were tempered.
These are a part of the original photos restored by our IT Department.
We've reported it to the police.
Later,
a more authoritative organization will issue relevant evidence.
If anyone can prove
my fiancée's misconduct,
I'm willing to offer him 10 million.
But if I find out who slandered her,
Shanyu's Legal Department
will follow it up and through.
[Songlin]
Looks like Mr. Gu is going to support his fiancée.
You don't understand.
This is called crisis management.
There's no smoke without fire.
Even if the photos are fake,
that thing might be true.
Everyone has left.
Let's go too.
I thought that if I do Xu Nian dirty,
Gu Mingyan'd dump her.
I underestimated her artifice.
I told you
this wouldn't work.
We should have used the honey trap.
Honey trap?
All you know is honey trap. Use your brain.
Jiang Wanli.
Don't go.
Yao, go get the car.
Mom.
Who is she?
Go get the car!
Okay.
Lan, long time no see.
It's settled.
Don't think too much.
I helped you solve the problem
because I don't want to be seen as an illicit amour.
One problem is solved.
But there's another problem emerging.
You caused me so much trouble.
I should deduct
at least 50 points from you.
50?
Back to zero again.
When can I get the school back?
I'll go find my phone.
Mr. Gu, your father called just now.
He was very angry.
A puppet is gradually getting out of control.
Of course he'll be angry.
Are you referring to the thing
where Chairman wants you to marry into Shenlyu Group for business?
Now you are married to Mr. Xu.
Then you should fulfill what you've promised me.
I've given you everything I should.
Don't be too greedy.
I'm greedy?
You should know clearly if it weren't for me,
you couldn't have become Mrs. Xu.
Are you threatening me?
So what if I'm threatening you?
Why don't we talk to Mr Xu?
Miss.
Don't you leave!
-Let go!
-Don't go!
Miss, what's wrong?
Look, I found your purse.
Thank you.
Check if anything is missing.
Miss, is there a problem?
Can you take me to the person in charge here?
Okay.
Who is she?
She's a temporary worker here.
Her name's Ji Lan.
Mrs. Xu, time to have medicine.
Here.
Nian, stop playing. Go wash up.
Go upstairs and sleep.
Go and rest.
Do you have her number?
I'll find it for you.
Ms. Xu, she didn't answer.
Lan was my mom's caretaker.
After Mom passed away, Dad fired her.
But Jiang Wanli came in later.
Why are they connected?
I've given you everything I should.
Don't be too greedy.
I'm greedy?
You should know clearly
if it weren't for me,
you couldn't have become Mrs. Xu.
Are you threatening me?
So what if I'm threatening you?
Why don't we talk to Mr Xu?
Let's tell him about us.
Could it be
Mom's death is related to Jiang Wanli?
But now Lan is nowhere to be found.
I can't just wait.
I must go home and find out the truth.
Please ask Gu Mingyan for me for a few days off.
I need to go home.
Okay.
Where is she going?
Ms. Xu wants to take a few days off and go home.
She tried so hard to escape from Xu family.
Why is she going back now?
Ms. Xu seems to be investigating something.
She asked me to look for a staff member here.
Mr. Gu, do you want me to go and ask her?
No, let's go back to the office first.
Xu Nian, why are you here?