[English subtitles are available]
[My Lovely Wife]
[Episode 19]
Tell me.
What is it?
I want to talk to you about Xu Nian.
Xu Nian?
Xu Nian!
Stop looking. She's not here.
What did you do to Xu Nian?
Mingyan.
Don't be so nervous.
Xu Nian should be safe now.
No, maybe we should call her Gu Nian.
Half an hour ago,
she, my niece-in-law, just found out
that she's a descendant of the Gu family.
She couldn't accept it
and ran out.
What do you mean?
In that case,
I'll cut to the chase.
This is the result of the paternity test
my father had done for her before.
The report shows that
Xu Nian is the biological daughter of my brother and Song Yuzhi.
But the strange thing is,
my father knew Xu Nian was a descendant of the Gu family,
yet he actively facilitated your marriage.
This can only indicate one fact,
that you
are not my brother's biological son.
My father brought you back,
insisted that you're Gu Hongze's illegitimate son,
and supported you to fight for the position of the Gu family heir with me.
I suspected your identity once.
But you've been abroad for many years, always careful,
and with my father protecting you,
so I've never been able to verify it.
But fate is so magical.
Xu Nian appeared.
If you don't love her that much
and insist on marrying her,
I might not get the chance to verify it.
But now...
What do you want?
After all, it's a family scandal.
I don't want the Gu family to be criticized.
As long as you resign from your position as CEO,
renounce your inheritance, and leave the country,
and stop competing with me,
I can pretend that nothing happened.
If not,
if this gets out,
who will be the most hurt?
Public opinion can kill people.
Don't forget how Song Yuzhi died.
I'll give you one day to think about it.
When I graduated,
I joined Xinliang Group,
which was your grandpa's company.
At that time,
I wanted to create my own career
and make a world of my own.
After I joined the company,
I saw your mother.
I admired her.
But I could only watch from afar, right?
We had disparate social statuses.
Then one day, your grandpa informed me
that he intended to invest more in my development.
But the condition was
to marry your mother.
I was very happy.
I agreed without thinking.
Later I found out
she was pregnant.
She didn't tell me.
And I didn't ask.
So, did you know a long time ago
that I wasn't your biological daughter?
I've always known.
I've always known that you're not my biological child.
But power and status
were too tempting.
Besides, I admired her, right?
So I promised her
I would treat you like my own child
and take care of her forever.
Then later on? Why did you change later?
A marriage based on a monetary relationship
won't be a happy one.
Besides, when I was facing your grandpa and your mother,
I was under a lot of pressure.
Later Jiang Wanli appeared.
I gave all my love to Jiang Wanli.
Later she got pregnant.
She forced me
to divorce your mother.
I knew
if this matter were made public,
I would lose everything.
Your grandpa would kick me out.
Later,
there was the acquisition of Xinliang Group.
And the scandal between your mother and Gu Hongze was exposed.
So I wanted to shift all the blame
onto your mother.
Because I knew that only by shifting the blame onto her
would your grandpa have no reason to kick me out.
So, from then on, I had been using emotional abuse towards your mother.
But I really didn’t know
Jiang Wanli...
Jiang Wanli would do those to your mom...
Until...
Until your mother passed away.
Later, Jiang Wanli treated you like that.
I was not entirely unaware either.
But...
But Yao is...
Yao is my biological daughter.
I can not be fair.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
So I'm really Gu Hongze's daughter.
Then, Mingyan and I...
Mingyan and I are...
Hello.
Mr. Gu, we found Xu Nian.
Where is she?
At her mother's grave.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Mom.
Before I met Mingyan,
I always thought
that clearing your name
was my only obsession in this world.
But now someone suddenly told me
what I'd been persisting for so many years
was wrong.
Now I'm even in love with my elder brother.
Mom.
Tell me
what I should do now.
You're back.