What about me saving her life?
- How didn't I take care of her? - Shut up.
What you did was nothing compared to what she did for you.
She jumped into the water to save you.
What is it that ties you up
and keeps you from falling for anyone else
except Thian?
I am sorry, Moei.
Where is Thian?
Moei, wait. Where are you going?
Doctor said you need to stay longer.
So, you and me can find out
if we had to stay apart,
would we still love each other.
Mom.
- Aunt Pha, Hello. - Hello.
Moei and the babies are safe.
Mom.
You rascal.
Aunt Jee.
Hello.
Greetings, Dear.
How are you feeling?
I was so shocked when Thian called me, you know.
Aunt Jee.
We're really sorry for not telling you earlier.
It's all right. I'm not mad at you at all.
It's someone else I should be mad at.
And it's the one
who caused this whole mess.
Look. Right now, you are not alone now.
You have this little one in your belly.
I'm worried about you.
Please come back with me.
So you'll have someone to take care of you. Okay?
But Aunt Jee,
I'd really like to stay here.
I'd like to stay in the garden house.
I'd like to spend some time alone.
I feel happier that way.
Fine, I'll send my people to stay with you.
How many would you like?
Or would you like Thian to stay with you as a guard dog?
Hmm?
I'd really like to be alone.
And I…
don't want to go anywhere right now.
Mom.
Once Moei can get discharged,
I'll take her home.
Calm down, will you?
Didn't you hear she wants to stay here?
No, Mom. I'm worried about her.
Where's Sathit?
You tell him to get the car ready.
Thian, you say you're worried about her.
Do you even care how she feels?
Even now, you're still trying to force her?
Haven't you learned anything at all?
Want her to run away again?
Is that what you want? Then go ahead and do whatever you want.
Mom, wait.
Look.
Think.
Pull yourself together, will you? All right?
What do you suggest me do?
She's with child.
She can't be alone.
I don't care.
She can be mad at me, threaten me all she wants.
Today, she has to leave with me.
Thian.
You've been with her since high school.
Now you're having a child together.
But you don't know her at all.
You always got your way all this time
only because she lets you,
not because you're tough or anything.
Don't flatter yourself.
Moei is an iron fist in a velvet glove.
Didn't you see how she handled Pondej?
Jeez.
What should I do
so she let me take care of her?
It's your job to figure it out, not mine.
She has done so much for you.
Why don't you prove you can do the same for her?
What are you going to do next?
Huh?
Are you going to give up?
Can you not be so quiet?
Just tell us how you feel.
I won't give up.
- Yes! - That's my man.
I have to get Moei to forgive me
and give me another chance.
That's what I'm talking about.
But if you go see her like you did before,
she'll just run away.
If I can't see her, what else I can do?
I have a plan.
(Baan Suan Romruen)
Oh. Oh my.
It's been a while since I've seen guys around here.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Is this Moei's house? - That's right.
Well, are you here to see her?
- You're Gig, right? - Yes, that's me.
Gig, I'd like to ask for your help on something.
Sure, anything.
I promise that if you help us,
I'll give you anything you want.
- Really? - Yes.
Anything?
Anything.
Get me his Facebook.
His Facebook?
You need to work that smell though.
You little....
Okay, give me your phone.
This one, right?
- This one. - What?
- Just give it to her. - Well.
Do it quick.
Here you are.
Wait.
Now that I helped you,
you'll have to help me as promised.
Sure.
He's so cute. Oh, his Facebook!
- Got anything? - Have I ever let you down?
Moei's schedule.
Yes.
At 6 am, she gives food to the monks.
After that, she goes shopping.
During this time, Gig comes to clean the house.
Sometimes, she prepares food for Moei.
Moei gets home around mid-morning.
And takes a half-hour nap.
In the afternoon, she either works or arranges flowers.
Around 5 pm, she takes a walk.
Yes.
Gig says she does the same things every day.
She doesn't do anything else.
So you should know by now
the time you can go to Moei's house is…
late morning.
That's right.
If everything goes as planned,
Moei is all yours.
Oh.
- Whoa! - Gig.
- Are you surprised in my beauty?
Keep your voice down.
We weren't surprised, but terrified.
Hey, what did you say?
Oh, I said I wanted to eat some fries.
Here, the key to Moei's house.
- Thank you. - Of course.
Oh, there she is.
Hey, what now?
Come on.
Gosh!
Thian, go.
She has done so much for you.
Why don't you prove you can do the same for her?
Gig.
- Thank you. - Hmm? For what?
For these, of course.
White rose is my favorite flower.
- I see. - How did you know?
Come on. I have the sixth sense.
I know it all what you like don't like.
You don't believe me, do you?
You'll see in the next days.
I'll go clean the house.
So pretty.
Gig must think I might slip.
How thoughtful of her.
Moei keeps thanking me.
For the flowers, for the food,
and the latest, the non-slip mat.
It's good that she thinks it's you.
She doesn't need to know it's me.
- Mr. Thian. - Thanks.
So, does she seem happy?
She's very happy, I'd say.
You know, she seems a lot happier
than when she first moved in.
Thian. Well, I'm really curious,
aren't you tired
since you got up so early and took care of Moei's house,
then went to work after that?
Aren't you tired?
Hello?
Yes. Uh... I'm listening.
A little closer, Dear.
Just come closer, Dear. He won't bite.
Hope you don't mind me take this photo.
I want to remember the first day I came in this house.
(I'm pregnant!)
Today is the day I learn...
I'm carrying you inside me.
I was pretty shocked at first.
But in that shock,
I was filled with happiness beyond words.
All this time, I have been through so much.
Haven't Aunt Jee told you
that I'm going abroad to study.
Have you forgotten why we got married?
Let's get a divorce.
Thank you for letting me live
so I can learn what love is.
Where is he going?
He's going to Hong Kong.
I didn't really know what to do next.
I couldn't see my future.
All my life,
I never had any idea
if I could love anyone more than him.
You're six weeks pregnant.
Congratulations.
During the first three months,
you should take several precautions
to reduce the risk of a miscarriage.
For example, stress and certain diets.
For long-distance travel, if possible,
I suggest you avoid it or have it postponed.
But when I found out that you were here with me,
I have realized that I still
have much more love to give you.
I've chosen this home to raise you in.
As it feels warm
like the home in my memory.
where I was once happy
while sharing my life with someone.
I promise.
I'll do my best to take care of myself for you.
Six months from now,
we'll finally meet.
Please send your love to cheer for me.
Gig.
Have you seen my phone anywhere?
Where did I put it?
Gig.
She isn't here?
(Please come to Moei's now. She is back.)
Why does the door open?
Gig.
Moei!
Moei, I'm here!
I'm here! Oh, my.
I had to rush here. I was in the back.
What's the matter?
Oh.
I was actually swimming off your dock.
You caught me red-handed.
Yeah, I see you really rushed here.
Oh.
So why did you come back?
Right, I forgot my phone.
No, wait! You want your phone?
- Yes. - I'll get it for you.
- There you go. - Thank you.
You have to see the client, don't you?
Then you should leave now.
The traffic is bad, now.
Come on. Leave now.
- Okay. - Be safe, okay?
Oh, right.
Hang on. What else do you want?
- My laptop. - Oh, your laptop.
Have it.
Go now, or you'll be stuck in traffic.
- Don't forget anything else, okay? Go on. - Okay.
- Bye. - Bye.
She's gone.
Oh, this is so tiring.
Gosh, finally.
You know, you almost gave me a heart attack.
Thank you, Gig.
Wait, hold on. I'm curious.
How long are you going to keep doing this?
Moei really has no idea
what you've been doing here.
I'm also curious.
How can this get Moei to forgive you?
I don't expect Moei to forgive me.
I just don't want to see her work so hard like before.
Oh, wow. What a gentleman.
You are a real gentleman.
- Please excuse me. - Sure, go ahead.
Oh, my.
What a gentleman.
Look at me, I couldn't even put my clothes on.
This is where I left off.
Oh.
What is it now?
Hello? Moei, is that you?
Gig.
Have you done something with my crochet piece?
No, not a bit.
What's the matter, Moei?
No, it's nothing.
White rose is my favorite flower.
- I see. - How did you know?
Come on. I have the sixth sense.
I know it all what you like and don't like.
There you are.
It's just what I thought.
I told you, didn't I?
That I don't want you here again.
But I'm here now. What are you going to do?
Why can't you understand?
Do you think I was so stupid
to fool me like this?
If you were, you wouldn't be able to make me love you.
If I asked you directly,
you wouldn't have let me.
So what is it that you want?
- Are you going to leave or not? - No.
I think I've made myself clear.
If you followed me here,
I would run away again.
Do you think I can't do it?
Right.
I forgot
that you don't know me well enough.
I know you well enough.
You were born on September 19.
You like white roses.
You like listening me playing guitar.
- You like to eat... - That's enough.
If you knew me well,
you wouldn't keep doing this.
I always thought you had a kind heart.
It turned out you were even colder than me?
Didn't you say you loved me?
Didn't you promise you'd love only me?
That's why I was afraid
that if I gave my heart to someone.
They would toy and throw it away.
That's why I'm afraid to love.
Don't ever think that this is enough
for me to let you go.
You can drive me away all you want, but I'm not leaving you.
Wherever you and the babies are,
that's where I'll be.
Loud and clear?
- I'll move in. - No, you can't do that.
I told you.
I wanted to be here alone.
I'm not leaving.
I won't go anywhere until you let me stay.
Fine, I'll call the police.
Go on, do it.
- No, Moei. - I'm doing it.
- Moei. - Please go back.
She's really calling.
Hello, Officer.
There's an intruder in my house.
Please go, I'm begging you.
It's Baan Suan Romruen.
- Please. - In Nakhon Pathom.
Please hang up, Moei.
- Oh. - Thian, why are you still here?
You told me to get out, didn't you?
I'll be at the dock.
You need to go now.
No.
Please be careful.
Moei.
What the heck?
So you knew all along about what he's been doing?
I saw how determined he was. He was trying so hard.
But Thian and I had an agreement.
You might have an agreement,
and it might feel right for you.
But what about the babies?
Whatever you and Thian
agreed on or decided to do,
your babies know nothing about it.
Right now, it's not just you.
Whatever you do, you have to think about the babies,
not yourself.
Do you understand?
Right now, it's not just you.
Whatever you do, you have to think about the babies,
not yourself.
If you knew me well,
you wouldn't keep doing this.
You say you're worried about her.
Do you even care how she feels?
Even now, you're still trying to force her?
Haven't you learned anything at all?
Want her to run again?
Moei is an iron fist in a velvet glove.
Didn't you see?
The first boat leaves at 6 am.
Moei.
So, our work here is complete.
- Right, that part there? - Yes.
So we'll work on this part now and...
about all these things, you can…
Aren't you feeling well, Mr. Thian?
About these…
Mr. Thian.
I think you should go get some rest.
Whoa, whoa, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Thian, what's the matter?
Thian, what's wrong?
Oh, my.
Are you having indigestion?
Need help?
Oh, gosh.
Oh, that's why.
You don't have a lot of morning sickness
because someone gets it for you.
Don't tell me you are having sympathy pain for your wife.
Thian.
Maybe you should go home and rest.
- Gig? - Yes?
Do you think he can make it home?
He has to ride on a boat and then a bus.
No, Moei. No bus or boat is needed.
He can walk. He lives back here.
- What? - Oh.
It's so cozy and pleasant here.
You see, the owner of this place
got a job abroad.
So he asked me to rent it out.
Can I move in right now?
Wow, you're just as impatient as Moei.
That's easy. Show me the money, and the key is yours.
That's right. I rented it to him.
So he's close by.
Oh, poor you.
Thian.
Moei.
You're here.
Why do you look so startled?
I'm sorry. I was still hazy.
That's okay. I like it.
Moei asked me to check in on you.
She is probably worried that you might get sick.
Oh.
That's a real deal, new daddy.
Oh, my.
You know what's weird?
You can't stop puking.
But Moei can't stop eating.
She eats all day.
I just came back from work,
so I bought you some food.
I hear you have good appetite. Here, I got your favorite.
But if you don't like it, I can go buy you something else.
You're hungry, aren't you?
- What would you like? I'll plate it. - Thian, don't come near me.
You smell bad.
Moei.
What's wrong, Moei?
Moei. Gosh, Moei.
Why did you push me away?
Moei! Hey!
Moei.
It's just her allergic reaction to her husband.
That's why when she sees your face,
she wants to puke. Got it?
- Is that possible? - Of course.
Pregnant women have all kinds of things happening to them.
Got it? They can even hate the things they love.
You know what I think? You and Moei...
are having same pregnancy symptoms at the same time.
You know what this means?
It means you love each other so much.
That's why you're sharing the pains.
Mom, you know what I'm laughing about?
No.
Then why are you laughing?
I made you rice porridge. It's still hot.
You should eat now.
Uh, wait.
So, what's wrong with you?
What's with the mask?
Well.
You saw my face and you puked yesterday.
So I cover it up.
You won't puke.
(Appointment Card)
You have checkup today?
It's at 1 pm.
Then, I'll…
I'll pick you up at noon.
I'll be quick at work.
Then I'll hurry back.
You're now 16 weeks pregnant.
That's four months.
Today, we're going to do the ultrasound to see the baby's development.
What's wrong, Moei?
I'm afraid the babies might miss a leg.
It doesn't matter.
No matter how it is, they're still our babies.
All right.
Daddy, Mommy, can you see me?
Can you make it out?
Where's the head? Where's the tail?
Mommy is so funny.
There's only a head, no tail.
That right there, that's the head.
See it? Pretty big head though.
- Hold on. - Yes?
What's that little bud there?
Is that a hand?
I see.
That's not a hand.
That's his willie.
His willie?
Our babies are boys.
Mommy needs to eat a nutritious diet,
and get more rest than usual.
Don't lift heavy objects.
And most importantly,
no sexual intercourse.
Hang in there, Daddy.
Just only five months.
Don't work hard.
Be careful when you walk.
Eat a nutritious diet.
Don't just eat as you please, understand?
When I get off work in the evening,
I'll make you some food.
You don't have to.
I can take care of myself.
You have to work.
The site is close by. I can go there and back.
If I really have to stay on the site,
I'll check on you every hour.
- I'm hungry. - What?
You're hungry?
Hang on.
There you go.
You're hungry, aren't you?
You've changed a lot, you know?
Are you doing all of this for me
because of what I did for you?
Gratitude and love are not the same, you know?
I doubt you might be confused.
Moei, watch out!
Moei!
Our babies are boys.
Don't feel sorry.
Don't feel like it holds you responsible.
Just because I'm pregnant.
If you don't love me, even if we have a child together,
it's not going to work out.
If you leave now,
I think I can still get over it.
Look. If your empty stomach makes you think so much,
how about help me think
what I have to do
to make you never get over me.
So,
who was craving an omelet?
Chow down, okay? You have to eat for the babies too.
Here.
Hey.
I'm doing all of this for you,
you still don't know I love you?
Hmm?
Moei.
Oh.
Oh, Moei.
Moei, what's wrong?
Thian.
From now on, don't ask me
to leave again, okay?
And you should never leave me again, all right?
Let's start a family together.
Moei.
I'll go see Gig first thing in the morning.
I'll cancel apartment contract.
She surely will keep your security deposit.
She can keep it.
No, you can't.
How about this?
I promise.
I won't do anything.
Don't you trust me?
Of course, I trust you.
But I don't trust myself.
I may not be drunk,
but I can still get turned on.
I told you I won't be able to stop myself.
Oh, wow.
If I hadn't stopped, I would have lost my tee.
Right?
Ouch.
Stop that mouth of yours.
Let's exercise our brain a bit.
If our average age is 75 years old,
that means we have 27,375 days on this earth.
Every minute that passes
is a minute less we have to live.
How should I correct this?
Hey, Kaofang. What are you here for?
To see Kang?
Please give this to her.
What's wrong with her?
Here.
From her to you.
I heard that.
You won't read it?
Put it on my desk.
All right.
You won't read it, right? Then I will.
Hey, Tum. Tum, stop!
What's with her?
Now that we've realized it, it got me thinking,
if you want something, just go for it.
Don't keep waiting just because you're unsure.
If you want to go somewhere, just go.
If you want to do something, just do.
If it causes others problems.
If you want to confess your love, just do it.
Reimbursement documents.
Okay.
Hey, hang on.
I was wondering where Kaofang is.
I went into her office but didn't see her things.
She just quit.
She got her stuff and left just now.
Just now?
Kaofang!
If they reciprocate, your wish is fulfilled.
If they don't, then you can move on.
No more wasting time with uncertainty.
Hey, Kaofang!
Kaofang!
- Kang. - Kaofang!
I know you're still mad at me.
I just want to tell you I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I don't expect you to forgive me anymore.
Because what I did was so terrible.
I'm going to quit this job.
I guess you can be happier not seeing me around in the office.
Best of luck to you, Kang.
It's really my pleasure...
to get to know you.
From Kaofang, your awful friend.
So as they say,
you may never realize how much someone means to you
until they are gone.
Will I get a chance to see you again?
If there's something unresolved,
don't wait for them to come to you.
Don't bother thinking about who's right or wrong.
Because if we let the time pass,
we'll be the one who hurts the most.
If there's some misunderstanding,
just let go your pride.
Talk and reconcile.
There should be no win or lose between people who love each other.
If you lose, you both lose.
If you win, you win it together.
Sorry, we don't have any new employees named Natthamon.
Thank you.
Where are you going?
Up to 11th floor to see Mr. Baramee.
Please push Nine for me.
Are you here to pick up your order?
Here you are.
Hey, wait, Mister.
Don't leave yet. That's 60 baht.
You sure it's 60 baht?
20, 40, 60, thank you.
What can I get you?
Kang.
Excuse me, are you going to order?
What can I get you, Miss?
Today, it's "buy one, get one free".
The thing is I don't want any coffee, but…
can I get the barista's heart instead?
It's not for sale.
If you don't sell your heart,
how about we exchange them?
If I give you my heart,
will you give me yours?
About what you wrote in the letter,
that I'll be happier when I don't see you around.
is not true at all, Kaofang.
Since the day you left,
I found no happy moments at all.
I couldn't even smile.
I'm sorry, Kaofang,
for telling you how I feel about you when it's too late.
I know you won't give me a chance.
But that's okay. I understand.
It's me who was being too difficult.
So this served me right.
I came just to tell you this.
Now I see that you're happy.
I am happy for you.
Well, I'd better get going.
Go after her.
Just go.
I'll tell the manager for you.
Thank you.
For those who have a crush on someone, but have no courage to confess
because you're fear of rejection.
Don't be fear.
Because there are only two answers.
You'll have to know eventually.
Stop wasting time guessing it,
just go and ask them directly.
Is there any hope for me?
If they love you back, you'll be happy.
But if they don't, move on.
That is life.
(2 months later)
Yes, Sir. For the plans that I have already sent you.
As for the contract, I will send it to you soon via...
Chet.
What's this crazy girl doing here?
I'll have to call you back.
Uh, all right.
Chet, let's have a meal together.
Have a meal?
Oh, I'm good.
Why? I just want to have a chat.
Let's go outing. Anywhere will do.
I see. You guys are chitchatting.
No wonder you haven't called.
I asked Chet to join us.
But he said no.
No? Why not?
Well, I'm busy.
Maybe another time?
Sorry, I'm very busy.
- See you. - Okay.
Wait, Chet.
You can't say no next time.
What would you like to eat?
That blonde girl already knows everything,
I'll be friends with her.
I can't make Nott my man.
I guess I'll be friends with his girl.
Hey, Nott.
So, I think I'll join you after all.
Yeah.
Isn't that the same thing, Man?
- So? - I'll pick them up then.
- Thank you. - All right.
I wonder if he's okay.
- Toon. - What is it?
- You may have to go home by yourself. - What?
I think I found my soulmate.
- I'll be right back. - Hey.
Right, that's your type look like Puerto Rican.
Go for it, Man.
Hello.
Are you with anyone?
If not, you can join me at my table.
Are you hitting on me?
You can say that.
So, if I hit on you,
will there be a place in your heart for me?
Are you sure you want to hit on me?
Of course, I am.
With smoky voice and figure a Victoria Secret model,
you're totally my type.
Are you sure you want to hit on me?
You look familiar.
Beer.
Chet!
Chet.
Oh my god!
I'm going to you.
- Let's go. - Wait, Chet.
Are you Cha-Cha or what?
Whatever, just be my date for one night.
Chet, wait. Toon! Help!
- Help, Toon. - Here I come.
- Toon. - Hi, Kathy.
- Toon, help. - What brings you here?
What the heck, Man?
Come on, let's dance.
Oh.
What are you doing here?
You just startled me.
I got some ideas so I wanted to type it in.
- I was afraid I might forget. - I see.
Where did you came from?
Here. I went shopping for our babies.
You bought so many stuffs.
Here, let me show them to you.
I also got this, look.
Oh, wow.
So? Pretty cool?
Yes.
Do you think it fits him when he's born?
It's too big.
A newborn is so tiny, Thian.
What a pity.
That's okay. I'll keep it for him when growing up.
You know, I also saw dresses for girls.
So cute.
I think, maybe we should have a few girls too.
Oh, Thian.
I'm not a mother pig.
Here, I got a blanket.
You like it? Look, I got so many things.
I got some pants too.
Oh, Moei!
Moei, what's wrong?
I just…
I just got a little dizzy.
Want to see a doctor?
I'm fine.
I guess I was on screen for too long today.
That must be the cause.
I think, lie down for a bit will do.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Come, I'll walk you.
That's okay, Thian.
I can walk by myself. It's not that far.
You can stay here and admire all your purchase.
- Walk slowly. - I will.
Moei! Moei.
Moei.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you.
Am I...
in the hospital?
Yes, we're in the hospital.
Here, let me help you.
Ms. Natheerin, how are you feeling?
I'm feeling better.
But still a little hazy.
Do you have any trouble sleeping?
I sleep fine.
But I get tired very easily.
And I get dizzy a lot.
I see.
Let's do this. I'll to run a thorough test on you again, all right?
So we'll know what causes all these symptoms.
- Okay. - All right, excuse me.
Yes.
Thian, did the doctor say when we'll get the results?
Probably tomorrow.
He will call when it's out.
- Thian. - Hmm?
So…
our babies will be okay, right?
Our babies will be fine.
Don't worry too much.
They're surely tough boys.
Moei.
You can't sleep?
No, I don't feel comfortable.
Come here.
Easy.
There.
Come on.
Okay, you can sleep now.
I have a meeting at the site.
I'll be back once it's done.
- Hello? - Hello, Mr. Thiarawat.
I have Ms. Natheerin's results.
I'd like you to take her to see me at the hospital.
Is it bad?
We should talk at the hospital.
Doctor, if possible,
I don't want my wife to know about this yet.
I'm afraid she'll be worried.
But I promise you that I'll take care of her
as you instruct me to.
Of course.
What should we make today?
Hmm?
Oh, Dear, did you just kick me?
Right?
Just a moment, okay? Let me see what we have here.
Ms. Natheerin has chronic kidney disease.
This is probably caused by an autoimmune disease,
which I think she has it for some time now.
But we are not yet certain about its cause.
I have consulted with a kidney doctor on her case.
What we can do right now
is to continue with supportive treatment.
So, have we got the results?
Yes.
The doctor called when I was at the site.
Here they are.
- Let me. - So how are the results?
Well…
everything is normal.
That's a relief.
Look, don't get too confident.
You fainted once yesterday.
The doctor said…
it's probably you do too many things.
You should stay still. Don't do things all the time, understand?
I'll die of boredom, Thian.
You won't.
I'll soon be here with you all day and night.
Why? Did you quit your job?
No, not quit.
I'm just taking a vacation.
What?
Hungry?
You have to take these before meals.
What are these pills for?
Well…
they're prenatal vitamins.
Also, the doctor told me
to take you to get an injection tomorrow.
Why does the food look so bland?
The doctor wants you to control diet.
Not too much sodium, fat and sugar.
Let's say, we will need to do a regular examination.
What you have to do for me
is to take care of her diet and her lifestyle.
Any strenuous activity must be avoided completely.
- But it's tasteless like water. - Make sure Ms. Natheerin
move as little as possible.
Are you saying my food is not good?
It's good.
But... can I add a little fish sauce?
Moei, you shouldn't eat as you please during this time.
I understand.
Here.
Eat up, okay?
Should I feed you?
I'm good.
Have this, too.
Are you okay?
How are you feeling, Moei?
Any better?
Thian.
Are you tired?
Not at all.
But you must be.
You're carrying two babies inside you.
Thian.
Hmm?
Are you crying?
I'm not.
My eyes just hurt.
Don't lie to me.
You just got touched from what I said, didn't you?
Yeah.
I am so touched.
Moei.
You know, I might have been with many women.
Come on, let me finish.
But you...
are the only woman in my heart.
And I'm telling you that my heart,
once you're in, you can't get out.
This got me headache.
Moei.
Moei!
Thian!
Moei.
Moei!
Thian!
Moei.
- What's wrong, Moei? - Thian.
Are our babies gone, Thian?
Thian.
- Moei. - Thian.
Thian! Whoa!
It's just me, Gig.
Why did you sleep here?
I… I must have fallen asleep.
Don't tell me you slept here all night.
No.
- Excuse me. - Oh, be careful.
What's with him?
Moei.
What are you doing?
I'm putting these clothes away.
It's okay. Just stay still.
It's okay, Thian.
I can do this. It's not hard work.
- You can do what you have to. - It's okay.
Moei.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick some vegetables.
I'll do it.
(Baan Suan Romruen)
Moei, where are you going?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Are you going to do it for me too?
Do you want to use the bathroom?
No.
I was just waiting for you.
Come.
- You've been acting strange lately. - Hmm?
Since the day you went to get the results.
Are you sure there's really nothing wrong with me?
Hmm?
Nothing's wrong. You're totally fine.
Let's sit down.
Wait.
There's nothing seriously wrong with me?
Why won't you let me do anything?
I can't just sit back and do nothing, you know?
Come on, Moei.
Look.
It's our first child.
We have to take the best care of him, right?
Can you hear Daddy?
He's kicking.
Really?
He must've heard you.
Can you hear Daddy?
Hey, Thian.
You're crazier about him than I am.
Yes, of course.
You know, if I could get pregnant for you, I would.
Yeah, right.
Look here.
Tada!
Our bellies are equal now.
How to walk with this?
You walk like this.
You have to bend your back a little. It's really heavy.
Really?
- Our bellies are the same size. - Let's belly bump.
Let's sit down. You stand too long now.
- Okay, I'm getting sore. - Okay.
- Come on. - Are you all right?
You need more practice.
In case you can get pregnant.
Come on. Easy does it.
Come on.
Easy does it.
All right.
Oh.
Come, sit down.
Hold on.
Let me brush it for you.
Slowly.
Easy does it.
Oh, my.
It's not easy to move around.
Let me see.
What if we really were having four babies?
Maybe not. Come on, where were you?
- I'll get on with it. - You should.
Yes.
I'll back to work, okay?
Oh, I forgot.
- My belly is so big. - Yeah, right.
So overacting indeed.
Easy does it.
Moei, I brought some food.
Gig.
By the way,
Moei, do you think Thian has been acting weird lately?
Why? What makes you think so?
Well, I feel like
he seems so stressed out these days.
Is he like that when he's with you?
He is, right?
I know, right? He seems so...
Hello.
- Here. - What's that?
I brought you some food.
- You're gonna love it. - Let me see.
Oh.
I've been craving that, Gig.
How did you know?
Have you forgot that I have the sixth sense?
That's right. I guess I forgot.
- Then I'll dig in now. - Go ahead, I made it for you.
Wait. You can't.
Uh... you can't eat this.
- Gig. - Yes?
I'm sorry. Moei's with child. She should avoid strong flavors.
Moei.
How about something else? I'll make it.
I want to eat mackerel chili paste.
Let me.
Let's wait until after you give birth. Be patient, okay?
- Gig, please put it away. - All right.
No, I'll eat it.
Moei, no.
Moei.
- Let go. - Oh dear, please don't fight.
Oh, Thian.
Oh, my.
Come on, Thian. That's enough.
Moei, wait.
What else do you want to eat? I'll make it for you.
I don't want to eat anything.
Do you know how sick I am with your food?
For the past two weeks, I only had clear soup and boil vegetables.
The same thing all over again.
Only vegetables and everything was so bland.
I'm so sick of eating those food.
I just want to eat chill paste.
But you're pregnant.
You can't eat spicy food.
But I really want to eat it.
Moei.
Hey, Moei. Moei!
Gig.
Doctor wants Moei to control diet.
If I stop her, she won't listen.
So I'm begging you.
No strong flavors. Spicy, salty, sour, sweet, none of that.
All right.
Thank you.
Moei.
Are you mad at me because I ate all your food?
Yes.
- Moei, wait. - Go away.
I'm sorry, Moei.
- Moei. I'm sorry. - Go away.
I got a little carried away.
Not a little.
That's a lot. You ate all my food.
Did you enjoy it?
Moei, wait.
- Go away. - I'm sorry.
Hey, let go.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
Moei.
Please don't sulk.
Let me see.
Why are your legs swollen?
You're right.
I didn't notice it before.
Let's check your weight.
- Your weight is over standard. - I didn't eat a lot.
What's wrong?
Let's go see the doctor.
The results are out.
Ms. Natheerin has high blood pressure.
And there's high level of protein in her urine.
With these two things together,
it means that you have a pre-eclampsia.
Therefore, I would like you to be admitted right away.
I don't want you to go home.
When you start having a headache, a blurry vision
and an epigastric rising symptoms.
You may have a seizure right after,
which will be dangerous to both you and the babies.
Hello, Thian. What's up?
Why aren't you talking?
What's wrong? You don't sound good.
Hey.
Is it about Moei?
Mom.
Can you come to me?
I can't take it anymore.
We all meet
only to part.
I said no!
Didn't you promise me we would build a family together.
But it's not easy to find a kidney donor.
Doctor, her blood pressure is rising.
- Ms. Natheerin is having kidney failure. - What?