Pondej wants to have you and Natheerin killed.
Moei!
Moei, watch out!
Where are you taking her?
Let her study abroad.
It's her decision, not yours.
But I'm her husband.
Have you done anything to upset Thian?
I just...
- called off the wedding. - What?
Called off the wedding?
Do you want to leave be that badly?
Do you want to leave me that badly?
Have you forgotten
why I came here?
Pondej is no longer causing you trouble.
Let's get a divorce.
Arrange a vacation for Moei.
I'm taking her back now.
If you still have a problem,
I'll let her resign like you once wanted.
I won't her leave.
I really don't get it.
I have all problems taken care of,
- what else do you want me to do? - You don't have to do anything.
I've decided that you can't take care of her.
If you had taken good care of her,
all of this wouldn't have happened.
Thian, I love Moei.
If she's not happy to be with you,
you should let her go
for the sake of her future.
But we're married, Mom.
- And she... - Are you sure?
Why you got married with her, don't you remember?
That's enough, Mom.
Don't bring this up anymore.
I admit I married her because someone wanted to kill me.
Why is that important?
Since I no longer want a divorce.
Hey, don't you ever think
that there was an easier way to solve that problem?
I only had to send someone to deal with them.
Then everything would end long ago.
Was it really necessary to force you to marry her?
On the day your car went into the water,
did you realize you forgot your phone at home?
Moei saw the message Pondej sent you.
She was so worried that she went after you secretly.
Why won't you let me bathe you?
- Moei. - Hmm?
I'm going out. Watch over the house, you two.
Where are you going?
(I know you're meeting my wife. Don't come if you don't want to die.)
Ri, Thian is in trouble.
Send me the location now.
Don't do anything just yet. I'm coming now.
- Okay. - Did something happen to Moei?
It's not Moei, Mom. It's Thian.
What?
Boss, someone is here.
Damn it! Let's go.
Moei then called a rescue team to help me.
And you put me on a silver platter and served her
to express your gratitude.
If you mean that, I already knew.
That's good, then. That's why I'm mad
when you sent her to Pondej at his company.
What if he remembered her and wanted to kill her?
Have you ever thought about that?
You never took care of her like she did to you.
That's why I want her back.
What about me saving her life? How didn't I take care good care of her?
You're really...
How dare you say that you saved her.
What you did was nothing compared to what she did for you.
You know what?
Besides calling the rescue team,
She jumped into the water to save you.
Miss!
Can you find him?
Hello, sir.
- Oh, hello. - Hello, sir.
- Where? Where did my son fall? - A car went into the water.
- I'm his mother. - Please calm down.
- Where is he? - A woman just jumped into the water
to help him.
- What? Moei. - They haven't come up yet.
- Thian. Moei. - Thian.
Where are they?
- Mom, calm down. They'll be fine. - Can you find them?
Yes. They're right there.
Did you have any idea
how hard she tried to get you out of the water?
But unfortunately,
after she sent you over to the diver
who got you out of the water,
she lost her strength and nearly drowned.
- Oh, they found him. - They got one.
- Thian! - They found him, Mom.
They found him, Mother.
What about Moei?
- Thian. - Thian.
Wake up, my boy.
- Thian. - Wake up and talk to me.
They're looking for Moei, Thian.
- Thian. - Thian.
Thian.
- Let them do their work. - Thian is safe now, Mom.
Mother, let them help him.
Thian, please wake up.
The water was very deep.
Your whole car went under.
The diver said they had to use the grapnel to pull it up.
And what about Moei...
The tide swept her away.
They couldn't find her.
By the time they pulled her out,
she had stopped breathing.
Mom, they found Moei.
- Moei. - Moei.
Go check on her. Go.
- Mon, stay with mom. - Go now.
- One, two, three. - Moei.
Moei.
- Please help her. - Moei.
Thian.
Thian, my boy. Moei.
They're in a doctor's care now. They are going to be all right, Mother.
Let's sit down, Mom. Come on.
What have I done to deserve this?
Mon.
Tell Sathit to arrange a flight
for Prapha to come here right away.
Yes, Mother.
Doctor.
- Doctor. - How are they doing, Doctor?
Both of them are safe now.
- Oh, my goodness. - Thank you, Doctor.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you so much.
Thank you so much, Doctor.
Once I knew that you two were safe,
I was so relieved and happy.
But I also felt very guilty as well.
Prapha.
Jee.
I'm so sorry.
Moei almost died because of Thian.
It's all right.
It's all right. It was an accident.
I'm glad that Thian is safe now.
Okay, thank you so much.
I'm really grateful.
Why didn't anyone tell me?
Moei begged us
to keep this a secret.
Moei.
Is Thian all right?
Thian is fine now, dear.
He's taking a rest now.
He's just a little hazy.
As he suffered a concussion.
I thank you so much, Moei,
for risking your life to save Thian's.
- Aunt Jee. - Yes, dear?
Can you not tell him
that I saved him?
Moei.
- Moei. - I'm here, Mom.
Can I go see Thian?
Aunt Jee said he started to ask for me.
I don't want him to know
I'm staying in the room next to him.
Are you sure you're all right?
I'm all right, Mom.
Mom.
I can walk from here.
He might see me.
Will you be okay to walk?
Yes.
Hello, Aunt Jee.
Moei.
Look at her, Mom.
Where have you been?
What took you so long to show up?
You are mocking me.
I guess you're all right now.
Look at your grumpy little face.
Stop it now.
See? You're well now.
Since you're in the hospital, how about get a checkup?
Maybe your endorphins aren't working properly.
How come you're always in a good mood like this?
You still can laugh when I'm hospitalized like this.
Look, you're still smiling.
Well, you're not dead yet.
I assure you when you're dead, I'll cry for you.
You little...
Thian, are you hurt?
Of course I am.
It's not a cut on my finger to recover so soon.
How about this?
I'll pull 10 funny faces for you.
How?
The first one.
Is that funny?
Moei.
Why don't you take some rest?
It's all right, Aunt Jee.
I've had enough rest.
I'll go peel some fruits for you then.
Okay.
Moei.
What? What is it?
What's wrong with Mom?
She must be happy that her son is recovered.
Really?
Yes.
So, where have you been?
Why visiting me just now?
Didn't Aunt Jee tell you
that I've been swamped with work lately?
My boss keeps pressuring me.
I've worked so hard that I'm so tired.
- I'm so dog-tired. - I see.
That's why you're as pale as a ghost.
Just keep working hard.
It's good I come when you are awake.
Otherwise, I'd miss talking to you.
I came to see you many times, you know?
But you were always asleep.
Thian.
How about I tell you some funny stories?
You kept asking
what took her so long to visit you.
Actually, she didn't go anywhere.
She was in the room next to you.
The police officers said the water wasn't still.
The car could have been swept away
and couldn't be found.
If those who saved you
took action even for half a second slower,
your chance of survival would have been zero, Thian.
Moei was unlucky.
But it was my luck
that she decided to jump without hesitation
into the water to save you,
even when the water was opaque
and deep.
She said she couldn't see anything
and it was so difficult to find you.
Fortunately,
she got you out of the water.
Do you see now
why I had to give you to her?
Thank you so much, Moei
for risking your life to save Thian's.
Now that I know he's safe,
I'm okay now.
- Aunt Jee. - Yes, dear?
Can you not tell him
that I saved him?
I don't want him
to feel bad
that I saved him.
You want Moei to marry Thian?
She's the only one who can save him from that woman.
Will he agree to this?
He has no choice.
This time, he only has to do what I say.
I don't mean to be selfish.
For Moei sacrificed herself to save my son,
it's like she has given him a new life.
So, for the rest of his life,
I want him to be with a good woman
who sincerely loves and cares for him.
I am begging you.
Please let Moei be Thian's bride.
I thank you so much, Aunt Jee,
for giving me an opportunity that day.
But now, that is all over.
Mom.
Are you asleep?
Not yet, dear.
How are you doing?
How was work today?
Did you fight with Thian again?
Don't bother him too much.
You know he doesn't like to be bothered.
I know.
I won't bother him.
Well, Mom.
If I...
really go abroad to study,
will you be fine by yourself?
We have been living separately
since you went to college.
I'll be fine. Don't worry about me.
All right.
Well, at first,
Aunt Jee said she would pay for everything.
But I've applied for a scholarship.
If I am granted,
I'd only ask her to support me
for my allowance and accommodation.
And while I'm there,
I think I'll find myself a part-time job, too.
What do you think?
That's good.
I think after I have graduated,
I'll definitely get a lucrative job.
Moei.
Are you really going to divorce Thian?
Yes.
Mom, I...
I'm sorry for what I did in the past.
I won't do it again.
I didn't think well
that if anything happened to me,
how you would live.
How many times will you keep apologizing?
You only did what you felt like.
If you love someone so much,
it's natural that you'll sacrifice everything for that person,
even your life.
Just like how your dad sacrificed himself
and slid his side of the car into the tree during the accident
to let you and I could live until today.
Don't be sad and don't blame yourself anymore.
You're a good child.
In the future, you'll get to meet good people.
Yes, Mom.
Mom, when we meet next week,
can you cook my favorite dishes?
Of course.
See you, my dear.
What is it that ties you up
and keeps you from falling for anyone else
but Thian?
Love is always important.
But there are always more important things.
And if in this life,
Thian and I are not meant to be together,
I hope I can forget him soon.
And I hope.
I won't suffer from love anymore.
Moei.
I know everything now.
About how you nearly drowned
to save me.
I'd like to thank you and apologize to you.
Thank you for letting me live
so I can learn what love is.
It made me realize
that we can miss someone
even when we're right by their side.
I thank you for sacrificing your own happiness
to marry a guy like me,
a guy who hurt your feeling,
a guy who never cared about you
or cherished your heart.
And...
I thank you for loving me this much.
I won't doubt your love anymore.
I promise.
I'm sorry, Moei.
I'm sorry for always giving you hard times.
I'm sorry for being mean to you.
And I'm sorry
for never seeing your love at all.
Right now, I feel so guilty
that I can't face you anymore.
Now I've made up my mind I'll let you go,
so you can continue your studies as you want.
But I won't approve your resignation.
I'll let you leave without pay.
As for the divorce paper,
I've signed it for you.
This is the one thing.
I can do for you.
I promise I won't call or contact you.
I believe that time
will eventually melt away the guilt in my heart.
And I hope during the time we are apart.
I will learn...
Where is Thian?
Moei, don't you know he has left?
What?
Where is he going?
Please tell me, Beer, Nott, Toon.
He's going to Hong Kong.
This time, if I want to send you to Hong Kong,
it won't be difficult.
You have no right to send me as you please.
And I hope during the time we are apart.
I will learn
to love you
more than you love me.
And when that time comes,
I'll be able to sincerely say I love you
and then we can start all over again.
Just getting to marry you
already made me so happy.
The most precious thing in life
is you.
I don't know how much her love for me is,
and where it ends,
but this is more than enough
for me to choose not to let this woman go.
(Two months later)
if I weren't here with you,
would you be okay by yourself?
Can you see now how useful I am?
Hey, Thian.
When you finish eating,
you should throw the food away before you wash the dishes.
Otherwise this leftover will clog the drain.
Thian! Oh, my.
It is all clogged now.
Look, this is bad, you know?
I've told you so many times already.
Why won't you listen?
How many times have I told you
to put your dirty clothes in the basket?
If you keep them scattered like this,
I can't keep collecting them for you.
Thian.
Thian!
Sathit.
When did he arrive in Phuket?
He arrived yesterday, Madam.
But he told me not to tell you.
Why don't you wait until next week and tell me?
Actually, I was...
What? Can I do that?
I'm being sarcastic.
You should have told me the day he arrived.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, what a mess.
Oh, my.
It hit you hard, didn't it?
Moei thought you had gone to Hong Kong.
You know I help you hide this,
not because I think it's right,
But it's for Moei's sake.
I don't want her to worry about you again.
Hey, you can't keep slacking off like this.
Go clean up and eat something.
I'm not hungry.
Let me be honest with you.
I don't know whether the feeling you have towards Moei
is really love.
But if you love her,
you only have to prove to her that you do.
From now on,
I'll only watch you from afar.
I won't help you with Moei anymore.
When is my birthday?
Which month?
What color do I like?
What's my favorite flower?
What's my
favorite food?
Can you answer even one of them?
You want to have a perfect woman
as your wife.
You're married with me,
but you're still waiting for that person
because I'm not the one you want to marry.
Have you forgotten
why we got married?
I never thought
you knew how to use the water dipper.
Your mouth is full of foam now.
You still look cute.
- Let me. - Whoa!
- Good morning. - Holy Moly!
What do we have for breakfast?
Thian.
Hello, Aunt Pha.
Hello.
Why are you here?
I thought you are gone to Hong Kong.
No.
No?
But Moei told me
you were off to Hong Kong.
I just...
didn't want anyone to know I was here.
I'm here today
to apologize to you.
Apologize to me?
What is this all about?
What are you apologizing to me for?
I'm really sorry...
for not taking care of Moei.
I'm useless, good for nothing.
I didn't know
that Moei nearly died
because of me.
I'm sorry.
It's all right, Thian.
It's all right.
But Moei didn't need to help me.
I was never good enough for her.
My life is not that precious.
Please don't blame yourself.
Everything that happened,
Moei decided to do by herself.
I love you like my own son,
like how I love my daughter.
I could only raise her physically.
But it's her life.
Her heart belongs to her.
She made her own decision.
She chose to protect the person she loved.
Thian.
Let's get up.
Come on.
For everything that happened,
I've never blamed you at all.
If my daughter loves someone,
I'll love that person too.
I know
studying abroad
has always been her dream.
That's why I let her go.
I just wanted to do something for her,
even though it can't compare to what she's done for me.
I want to make her happy
as much as I can.
I want to tell you that I divorced her
not because I don't love her.
You have to tell her that yourself.
My daughter is headstrong.
Once she made up her mind,
it's not easy to change her.
Thian.
If you really love my daughter,
you have to find a way
to get her back.
Thank you.
I...
I'd like to ask you a favor.
I'd like you
to tell me about Moei.
What do you want to know about her?
Well, first of all.
I want to know when she
started to fall for me.
Well, no one knows that,
not even me
or Sajee.
Jee used to always come
and complained about you to us.
Moei always listened to that so heedfully.
At first, she was a little nervous,
but later she would laugh along with everything.
She once told me, even though you were a bully,
you're still adorable.
Every time when you called and she answered,
she would get so excited that she didn't know what to do.
Is this Mrs. Pha's house?
Can I speak to Madam Sajee?
Aunt Jee?
Yes, she's here.
Can you get her on the phone?
Okay.
What was that?
A snake?
Oh, it's a snake. A big snake indeed.
So she was afraid of me?
Yes.
So she was scared of me?
Once she knew, she was summoned to meet you.
Moei, Aunt Sajee wants you to meet Thian.
What?
She bumped into things,
and her hands got all clumsy.
It took her a while to collect herself.
Moei!
No wonder why she's so clumsy sometimes.
Only when she's with you.
She wanted to be close to you,
but she didn't have courage.
She was happy
and looked forward to the time she could see you again.
After you had gone to study in Bangkok,
I can still remember
how happy she was
to know she got into the same university as you.
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
What is it, Moei?
Mom, I made it!
I got accepted to the same university as Thian.
I'll get to see his face every day now.
Okay, okay.
He might get annoyed with you.
Well, that, I really don't care.
As long as I get to see his handsome face every day.
What?
Aunt Pha's daughter will be staying with us?
Yes.
Moei is like your little sister.
Both of you should protect and take care of her.
- But... - You're doing the right thing, Mom.
Right?
Right, by the way,
Congrats, you're a freshman now. Well done.
A little closer, dear.
Just come closer, dear. He won't bite.
One, two, three,
smile!
I was such a jerk.
I always picked on her.
When I saw she didn't get mad, I kept doing it.
Thian.
Hmm?
Hey, you wanna mess with me?
Want some?
What's this red thing?
Oh, it's chili powder.
That's why it's good.
Who was that?
(Thiarawat)
Thiarawat, you brat.
Jeez, just get it down already.
Can't you see I'm trying?
Just get to this side and reach for it.
It's not easy, you know?
Oh no!
- Thian! Bees! - What?
- Really? Run! - Thian!
Thian! Wait for me.
Hey, are you all right, Moei?
Whoa!
But she never got mad at you.
When she came home,
she always told me about you and her with joy,
as if in this world of hers
had only you.
Thian.
- Thian. - Thian, she's calling you.
I don't think she's calling me.
Wait, Thian.
I know you have to work on your project later until late,
so I bought you some food and water.
I'm not going to eat that.
- There he goes again. - But...
Thian.
What is it now?
Aunt Jee told me to go home with you.
- I'm not going home. - Wait, Thian.
Where are you going then?
It's none of your business.
Listen, stop following me around or waiting for me.
You know, everyone is saying that we're dating.
- Really? - Why are you smiling?
Nothing.
Look, Moei.
I don't want people to misunderstand
that I'm dating a nerd like you.
So from now on,
stop following me around. Don't wait for me.
Just go your own way.
Got it?
Hey.
Well, this is my way home, too.
Just keep some distance, then.
- Oh. - Oh.
Well, I came to buy some things.
Please keep raining,
so I can stay a little longer with him.
Aunt Pha,
I am aware
we can't change the past.
But I believe
that if we know what we have done wrong
and never repeat them,
everything will get better.
We'd like to officially welcome TecTien, our best friend,
back to our department
once again.
So please, Thian.
Let us crown you.
No, man.
- Let's put these on. - All right, guys.
That's enough for the welcoming.
Hey, I can't believe it.
You had the opportunity
- to work in Hong Kong, - Right.
but you ditched it and went to Phuket instead.
Are you out of your mind? I don't get you.
You've been friends with him for ages, you still don't get him?
- It's called the heart-healing period. - I see.
Thian.
I've assigned a new assistant for you.
Come in.
Hello, Thian.
I've heard so much about you.
I finally get to meet you.
This is Aoey. She's your junior from college.
She's good, dynamic, and tough.
Just right to work with you.
Please accept me in your care.
Hang on. Right now, I still don't know the workload.
Maybe I won't need an assistant.
Besides, I'm not supervising Hammoc anymore.
I think she can get back to her work.
Don't waste her time here.
Is that how you want?
It's better.
If I need an assistant, I'll summon you.
Well then, whatever you say.
Excuse me. Please don't think too much about this.
My friend just still can't get over his former assistant.
No one can replace this position.
- Come here, you foul-mouthed brat. - What's with you?
- Just shut it. - Stop talking.
Hey, Thian. Don't be sad, all right?
How about this? Since it's been quite a while
for us four buddies to hang out together, I say
- after work this evening... - Hey.
Are you sure about that?
I don't think his condition is ready.
- Where to? - There you go.
Nice! See?
Going clubbing, of course.
Since it's the last Friday of the month, we should go clubbing.
I'm not going.
- I can't believe this. - Thian, wait, man.
How long are you going to be like this?
We want the old you back.
Yes, Chet.
All right.
Supervise a site in Nakhon Pathom?
Well, so can you go...
- Sure. - What?
If it was before,
you'd send someone else to a small site like this.
Unlike Moei,
whatever work she's assigned to,
she never said no.
Well, I forgot to tell you.
For Nakhon Pathom's site,
it would be inconvenient to drive there
due to road construction.
It's all right.
- I'm not planning to drive there. - What?
So, how are you...
Hey.
(Om Noi - Mahachai)
Can you see now, Thian?
I told you taking a bus is quite comfy.
With 20 windows and cool breeze.
Do you believe me now?
I do now.
What are you saying, young man?
It's nothing.
Have a nice day.
(Nakhon Pathom - Mahachai)
Moei!
Here you are.
Look, I got you some papayas.
You can have them every day.
I assure you, you'll poop easily.
I have lots of them.
- Thank you. - Oh, wait.
What's that?
This?
Would you like some?
Can I? I'll take them all.
Let's exchange.
- I'll go now. - Okay.
Now I have Thai basil and chili.
I'll make stir-fried pork with Thai basil and share with you.
Here, your knife.
I already have lots at home.
This is so worth it.
It's very breezy, isn't it?
You'll totally be living in the nature.
You can see the boats passing by.
It's very beautiful.
It's very cool and pleasant.
I'm telling you, everyone likes it here.
What do you think, Mom?
I like it.
It's nice and pleasant.
I think it suits you.
You're totally right.
Okay, I'll rent this house.
But I'd like to move in tomorrow.
Are you in a hurry?
Yes, I am.
Studying abroad
has always been her dream.
That's why I let her go.
I just wanted to do something for her.
I must be seeing things.
Why would she be here?
Is Prapha not home?
Hello, Prapha. Where are you?
I... I'm home.
You're home?
Well, yes.
You got it, ma'am.
What is it, Jee?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's been quite some time, I thought we could get lunch.
I see. But I'm not free right now.
I have desserts to deliver.
All right, next time then.
Mom.
Whose voice is that?
Oh, it's the television.
I have to go now, Jee.
I have to finish baking or I'll be late.
All right.
Was that Aunt Jee?
Do you think she heard me?
- Madam. - So?
I peeked into the house, there's really no one.
That's what I thought.
But over the phone just now,
I think I heard Moei's voice.
Come on, Madam. That can't be possible.
Isn't she abroad right now?
Exactly.
She is abroad right now. So how can she be here?
Prapha and Moei must be hiding something.
That's why she lied to me about being home.
Copy that, Madam.
I'll look into this and find out
what's going on.
You seem to read my mind these days.
- Yes, ma'am. - Good.
- Just be quick. - Yes, sir.
Why did she lie?
Mom, are you thinking about Aunt Jee?
Yes, it worries me she might get suspicious.
You know how smart she is.
That's true.
Well then, tomorrow, I'll go back to Phuket.
I'll come visit you later.
I'll have to visit her once I get back.
Otherwise, she'll look for me at home.
That's a good idea, Mom.
Then, you should go back to Phuket.
Actually, you don't have to visit me often.
I'm all right. You don't have to worry.
I'll buy the ticket for you.
Thank you.
Let's go, Mom.
Mom.
Once you get to the airport,
please call me.
I will.
You, too.
Go straight home and don't stroll around.
Okay.
I'm going now.
- Bye. - Bye.
Is everyone here?
- All right. - Good luck.
Thank you.
Moei.
Moei!
Hey, don't cut in line.
I'm sorry.
Moei.
Moei!
Excuse me. Sorry.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Damn.
Moei!
Moei.
Excuse me! Please stop the bus!
Can you tell the driver to stop?
Stop the bus.
Excuse me.
Moei!
Moei.
I'm sorry.
(Would you like to block T.Navanawakul?)
(T.Navanawakul is blocked.)
Keep up, Moei.
You can do it.
I saw Moei in Nakhon Pathom.
You saw Moei in Nakhon Pathom?
Are you missing her too much?
How would she be in Nakhon Pathom?
That's what I thought.
But it's obviously her today.
It must be her.
Hey, I think you must have been seeing things.
I don't believe you saw her.
- Impossible. - I wasn't seeing things.
Why don't you check her Instagram?
- IG, you say? - Yes.
That's impossible. She blocked me ages ago.
IG, Facebook, Line, all blocked.
Okay.
Then we can't help you anymore.
Since she blocked the three of us too.
What?
- She blocked you too? - Yes.
Why would she do that?
You should get over her, man.
It's so clear now
that she doesn't want you to know her whereabouts.
I think
not only doesn't she want him to know her whereabouts,
she wants to remove him from her life.
I have to find out.
(Nakhon Pathom - Samut Sakhon)
I want to tell you
that I divorced her
not because I don't love her.
You have to tell her that yourself.
My daughter is headstrong.
Once she made up her mind,
it's not easy to change her.
If you really love my daughter,
you have to find a way
to get her back.
Baan Suan Romruen, please.
Thank you.
I'd like to follow that boat.
Okay. Twenty baht, please.
Twenty baht.
- Let's go. - Go.
(Baan Suan Romruen)
Who are you here for?
Oh my goodness, he's so hot.
Mr. Hottie
who are you here for?
- Is Moei here? - How are you related to her?
Are you her brother?
No, I'm her husband.
Oh, my.
Holy moly, where did she find such a hot husband? Oh, my gosh.
What did she do to get a hubby this gorgeous?
- If I were her... - Excuse me.
So, is Moei here?
Wait. Hold on.
Are you really her husband?
Why don't you know she's here?
We had a fight
and she ran away.
I don't buy it. You are this hot, I'm sure you have lots of girls.
- Am I right? - No. That's not it.
We fought over something else.
Then please wait here.
I'll let her know you're here.
No, wait.
- Why? - You can't tell her.
If you tell her, she'll run again.
Hello?
Yes. Well,
please give me a few more days.
And I'll send you the first draft.
All right, yes. Bye.
Moei!
Moei. Moei.
Moei.
Sajee.
It's okay. I'll help.
Why?
Why are you so surprised to see me?
Hmm?
I didn't expect you would come here.
You have lots of customers these days.
You made desserts yesterday, today you do again.
Right. Yes.
Prapha, stop lying to me.
I know Moei is in Nakhon Pathom.
Oh, my.
I'll clean this up. Please be surprised all you want.
- Madam Sajee. - Yes.
I looked into it and found out
that Moei didn't go abroad like she said.
Besides, after that day,
there was no record of her traveling anywhere.
Are you saying she's been in Thailand for the past two months?
That's right.
Jeez, Moei is really...
so good at covering her track.
There is no record of her
using her credit card either.
The most interesting part is this.
I have been told
there were people similar to Moei
and Mrs. Prapha started renting this place two months ago.
This matches the time when she said
she would go abroad to study.
So?
Did I get everything right?
So, what's wrong with my wife?
Oh, please don't worry.
It's normal for a pregnant woman to bleed
during the first 12 weeks of pregnancy.
However, it only occurs for a short while.
It will be gone in a few days.
- My wife is pregnant? - That's right.
What?
Moei is with Thian's child?
I'm sorry
that I didn't tell you earlier.
Moei doesn't want to be a burden to anyone,
so we have decided to take care of each other.
Goodness, Prapha. You're really...
How could you see me as a stranger?
You should have told me about something this important.
You made me feel slighted, Prapha.
You two have never been a burden to me.
You both are like members of my family.
I love Moei like my own daughter.
And I love you like my own sister.
I'm really sorry.
You're really...
Don't you feel worried
letting your daughter live alone and away from you?
I didn't agree at first.
But she's so headstrong that I had to let her.
You know how she is.
Once she decides to do something,
she won't change her mind easily.
I didn't want her to stress about it.
But I've been visiting her
- and the neighbor... - That's enough.
Now that I know everything,
you can't turn down my help.
Don't say anything.
I'll talk to Moei myself.
- Sathit. - Yes, ma'am.
- Let's go. - Yes, ma'am.
You come too.
Hello, Thian.
What?
- Moei passed out? - What?
Excuse me.
Please come to arrange the room for Ms. Natheerin.
All right.
The doctor would like to have you observed a little longer.
If there is no complication, then you can go home.
Thank you. But wait...
Yes?
So, who brought me here?
It was your husband.
What?
My husband?
Yes.
Excuse me.
Your husband is here.
Thian.
What are you doing here?
Moei. Wait, no.
Where are you going? The doctor said you needed to stay longer.
Moei.
Fine.
I'll stay.
But you have to go.
Weren't you the one who made the promise
that we would stay apart?
Why break your own words?
Well, you're not well.
How can you be by yourself?
All these times,
I always listened and did what you said.
No matter where you told me to stay
or what to do,
I always did it.
I was everything for you.
When you wanted something,
no matter how hard it was to find,
I'd find it for you.
Today,
I'm asking you to leave me alone,
won't you do that for me?
It can't be hard for you.
Moei,
but we're having a child together.
This is important. Why didn't you tell me?
From now on,
we can't stay apart.
I won't allow that.
Why?
What if you didn't find me today?
What if I went abroad, and I wasn't expecting a child?
Would everything still be like this?
When I told you I wanted to study abroad,
I just wanted the two years that we are apart
to be the time for you to think
whether you still wanted me.
But wasn't it you
who ran away without telling me anything?
Wasn't it you who came up with this silly condition
that we wouldn't contact each other?
And now,
you suddenly came back to me,
saying you want to take care of me.
You know, I'm totally confused now.
I...
I'm sorry, Moei.
I want us not to contact each other.
I want both of us
to do as we promised.
So you and me
can find out
and know for certain
if we had to stay apart,
would we still love each other.
How does that sound?
If you can't do this for me,
this will be the last time you see me.
Do you want that?
If everything goes as planned,
Moei is all yours.
Why don't you prove you can do the same for her?
I've chosen this home to raise you in.
As it feels warm
like the home in my memory.
The home where I was once happy.