(Guidelines were strictly followed
when filming with children.)
By the way, this man...
Is he alive?
Why isn't he moving at all?
Sir.
Sir?
Oh, he's breathing.
- What?
- My gosh.
Goodness.
Oh, that...
That man. Who is he?
He's my relative. A distant relative.
Then why is he here?
Is he ill or something?
He hurt his head
and lost his consciousness.
What you saw was just a reflex.
It happens occasionally.
I see.
We'll just leave the rice here, then.
Take care.
All right, thank you.
Have a good day.
You. Can you hear me?
Wake up already.
How amusing is this dream you're having...
that you still won't wake up?
Oh, boy.
Oh, my. This soup is so delicious.
- Did you use anchovy broth for this?
- Yes.
The two of you will go straight
to the restaurant after breakfast, right?
Then let's head out together.
I'm not going straight to the restaurant.
I have to stop by somewhere.
I have to stop by somewhere too,
so tell your dad
to go straight to the restaurant.
What?
Dad, Mom says
she has to stop by somewhere.
She wants you
to go straight to the restaurant.
Tell her I can't.
I must take care of something important.
What?
Mom, Dad says he has to
take care of something important.
As if what I have to do isn't important.
Then he should've given me a heads-up.
Tell him that.
Dad, you heard that, right?
I'm done. Thanks for the food.
I'm done too.
Dear me.
Goodness.
Seriously!
Does he think I'll be scared
if he grimaces like that?
Unbelievable.
Hey, Gwang Sik. Where are you?
Can we meet?
(Pro Delivery Services)
You're that deliveryman.
Hello. You must live around here.
Yes, I run a cafe in this building.
Are you here to deliver something?
No, I'm...
I hope you weren't offended
by what I said the other day.
Of course, I know how hard it is
to work as a deliveryman.
But it'd just be nice...
if you could try thinking
from the business owners' perspective.
You could give us a call
if you're running late.
You understand what I mean, right?
Yes.
Hey, Hye Sook.
This delivery guy is here again.
Since I met him again,
I told him in a way that he'd understand,
so that won't happen again.
Hey, Gwang Sik.
What? "Gwang Sik?"
You're here, Mother.
"Mother?"
No way. Don't tell me...
Say hi. This is my son-in-law.
You met her the other day.
Let me introduce myself properly.
I'm Heo Gwang Sik, the son-in-law
of Jackpot Chicken's owners.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
So?
I mean, everyone has a job.
Why is it so hard for you to get a job?
I'm not sure either.
I didn't get any of the jobs
I interviewed for.
So, what can I do?
What is it that you truly want to do?
Pardon?
You're struggling to get a job,
but that's secondary.
There must be something you want to do.
Do you not have any aspirations?
Of course, I do.
I want to start
my own business eventually.
Business? What kind of business?
Well...
A shop that sells tteokbokki.
Tteokbokki?
It won't cost a lot
to start a tteokbokki place.
Like the super spicy tteokbokki...
or the soupy tteokbokki
that are popular these days?
No, not those.
Mother, you know
about edible insects, right?
Edible insects?
Yes, what about it?
Fusion food is very trendy these days.
As you know, tteokbokki is
every Korean's favorite comfort food,
so I thought it'd be interesting
to combine it with edible insects,
the food of the future.
What? Insects with tteokbokki?
Yes. Mother, you won't be eating
uncooked insects.
They'll be deep-fried.
Like crispy fritters.
They won't look or taste weird at all.
If you put them
on tteokbokki as a topping...
You know those places that sell
tteokbokki with deep-fried bits on top.
It'll look just like that.
Don't even dream of starting
such an absurd business.
Just get a full-time job.
Tteokbokki with insects? Nonsense.
Go. I have to work.
You want me to leave already?
I was going to stay
and have your fried chicken.
Mother, since I've already brought it up,
why don't I get a few insects
from my acquaintance...
so you can try cooking them
in your deep fryer?
That's enough.
Aren't you leaving? Get out!
- Okay.
- Go, get out!
Goodness.
I'm so upset! My gosh.
It's me, Mom.
It's me, Dad.
How have you been?
Dad, I'm doing very well, thanks to you.
Dad, do you remember?
The neighborhood where we lived together
when I was young.
Everything else has changed,
but that neighborhood
hasn't changed at all.
Grandpa told me...
you grew up in that neighborhood, Dad.
So, I want to...
buy the house where I live now.
In the past,
I never once dreamed of owning a home
because I had no money.
But I won the lottery,
so I want to spend a big chunk of money.
Dad, you will help me again, right?
Excuse me, hello.
I believe we've never met before.
What are you doing here?
Well... Sir.
Do you know
who owns the plot of land here?
Why do you ask?
Are you perhaps a realtor?
Gosh, no. I'm not a realtor.
I'm interested in this plot of land.
I guess you own quite a bit of land too.
Gosh, no. I don't own any land.
Just a building.
A building?
Do you really have a building in Baeheung?
Not in Baeheung.
A little farther up north in...
My goodness.
Well, it's in Seoul.
Seoul?
Gosh, if you own a building in Seoul,
you must be a rich man.
Oh, please. A rich man?
I'm just a middle-class guy.
What on earth happened yesterday?
I remember drinking by myself
at the tent bar.
If there were a hole
big enough for me to fit into,
I wish I could go in there...
and just die.
You're pretty.
You're pretty just the way you are,
Seo Woo.
So, don't say that.
What was that? Was it a dream?
Whatever it was, it felt great.
Did you sleep well? Is your stomach okay?
Why would you ask me that?
What?
Are we close enough
to exchange morning greetings?
I told you, didn't I?
I'm really mad at you.
Then, shouldn't you be saying
something other than...
a simple greeting?
Do you not remember
how I apologized to you?
Apologize?
This guy told me he was sorry?
Of course, I remember.
I wasn't drunk, you know.
Can't you tell by how I got home
just fine on my own after I met you?
I'm just saying that...
this incident isn't something
you can wash away with a single apology.
Okay.
I was going to tell you again
when we were both clear-headed.
So, I'll tell you now.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
about Tae Hyung beforehand.
I mean it.
All right.
Let's say I accept your apology for now.
But I'm not sure
if my anger will go away or not.
When does Tae Hyung come back to Korea?
What? Why do you ask?
That's none of your business,
but you know when he gets back, don't you?
It's me.
Hey, boss.
You know those scary-looking guys
who came to the restaurant yesterday?
Yes, I was just about to ask you.
Who on earth were they?
Could they maybe be loan sharks?
What? Loan sharks?
I overheard that guy, Han Tae Ha,
talking on the phone a few times.
He was saying something like
paying back interest and whatnot.
Do you think they came here
because he didn't pay them?
Gosh, that punk.
I heard he blew all the money
he invested in that business.
Did he borrow money from loan sharks too?
What did you just say?
He blew the money he invested?
Oh, right. Tae Ha told me not to tell you.
He told you not to tell me?
You can't let on that
you heard it from me, okay?
Okay, so go ahead and tell me.
What exactly did he blow?
Well, he was going to do business
with a guy he knew from school.
He borrowed money from here and there
and made an investment.
But apparently, that guy
took all the money and fled overseas.
What did you say?
- Darn it.
- What? Hey...
- Come here!
- Han Tae Ha!
What?
- Darn you.
- Let go of him!
Don't you dare lay a finger on him.
I won't let it slide.
You're that girl
from the restaurant yesterday, aren't you?
Get over here, you...
- Hey! Run!
- Gosh, get them!
- Stop right there!
- You!
Stop right there!
Hey! Stop!
Where do you think you're going?
Hey, we have to go.
You're the one who saved me.
Do you want me
to get caught again so easily?
Do you really not know why I saved you?
Well, I'm sure you were being
a friendly neighbor...
as someone with a strong sense of justice
who couldn't pass by a guy in danger.
Wasn't it like that?
By the way,
you're speaking casually with me again.
Sense of justice, my foot.
If those guys drag you away,
who will pay me back?
What? Money?
Do you think I don't know that you blew
my 30,000 dollars while doing business?
But how do you know...
Tell me the truth.
You were going to take that watch...
and pay those people back, weren't you?
And what? Have me thrown in jail?
Hey, how about I have you thrown in jail?
How dare you blow my money...
and raise your voice at me as well?
Hey, give me back my money this instant.
Give me back my 30,000 dollars, you jerk!
My mom must've been so upset
to have done that!
Her daughter is struggling so much.
What kind of mom
would just sit back and watch?
Had I known this would happen,
I should've just listened to my mom.
I shouldn't have married you...
when my mom was opposed to it!
- Oh, dear.
- Come on.
Get out!
Grandma, what are you doing there?
- Go away!
- What?
Stop it.
It's nothing.
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
Seriously, I can't stand you.
I'm so embarrassed that I might just die!
Hey, come on.
My goodness.
Should I cancel my savings plan
and help them out?
No.
Back when Mi Jin asked me
to lend her money,
I said I didn't have any.
I shouldn't give her this money now.
Gosh, what am I to do?
I'm here to ask about a loan.
Yes, is there one in particular
that you looked into?
No.
(Nara Bank,
Cashier's Check: 95,321.55 dollars)
Here you go, sir.
Thank you.
Are you participating
in a real estate auction by chance?
How did you know that?
Oh, when people ask for a Cashier's Check
for a very specific amount,
they're usually making a bidding
in an auction.
I don't know about anywhere else,
but that is the case in our VIP room.
I see.
I hope your bidding is successful.
Thank you.
Then, do you have a source of income?
No, I don't. I'm just a housewife.
In that case, do you have any assets
that you could borrow against?
Something like your own home
or a building in your name.
No, I don't.
I'm sorry. In that case, it'll be hard
for you to get a loan from our bank.
A loan?
Yes, I understand.
What's this?
(Seoul Southern District Court,
Confidential)
(Notice of Auction)
(Han Mu Chul, Case Number 7709, Creditors)
What... This is our house.
I'm home.
Tae Ha. What is this?
What's what?
"Notice of Auction?"
Hey, here you are.
Hey, Mom. What's this?
Is our house being auctioned off?
What? Then, is that for real?
What will we do now?
Where will we live
if this place gets auctioned off?
What about the buildings?
We still have Dad's buildings, don't we?
They seized all of those too.
What? Then what will we do now?
Don't we have anything?
Wait, Mom. Are you sure?
Did all of Dad's buildings get seized?
Every single one?
Yes.
You guys have to figure out a way
to make it in this world too.
No way.
How could Dad just go and die
after getting into this mess?
How are we supposed to live?
How could he just die all by himself?
Darn it. He never did anything for us
when he was alive.
How could he do this to us even in death?
What is all this?
Everything is a huge mess because of Dad.
Who does Dad think he is?
Who is he to put me in this misery?
Gosh, seriously.
What will we do, Mom? Do something.
Darn it. I'm so angry.
Hey, honey.
I want to talk to you about something.
Okay, talk.
Look at me so we can talk.
Are you going to keep avoiding me
like that?
Are you going to help Mi Jin?
Or,
will you help Ah Jin
start her own restaurant?
Tell me.
How do you plan to help our children?
It's not about that.
Then I have nothing to talk to you about.
Fine, forget it!
- Oh, good day.
- Hello.
Where can I get a bidding ticket?
Oh, over here.
I see. Thank you.
(Landlord Choi Gyu Tae,
Tenant Han Jae Joo)
Thank you, Mr. Choi.
Thanks to you, I can now open my shop
in the Daewoon Building.
Oh, please. Don't mention it.
I told you I could help you out
if you were interested in this building.
I think I met you because Lady Luck
was smiling on me that day.
Oh, right.
Here. It's nothing big. Please take this.
Hey! You didn't have to do this.
My goodness.
It's red ginseng.
- Thanks for this.
- My pleasure.
By the way, the power of attorney...
had your name on it.
You and the owner of the building
must be very close,
seeing how he entrusted you
with a building like this.
Well, I wouldn't say we're that close,
but anyway...
He's overseas now and can't visit often,
so just tell me
if there's anything you need.
I have to collect rent for him
and send it to him,
so remember that.
- Okay, got it.
- Good.
Thank you in advance for your help.
All right. You'll send me
the security deposit straight away, right?
Is he not here yet?
Gyu Tae, you're here.
Hi. Did you take a look?
- What?
- I told you to take a look.
Is there one you like?
What? Why look?
It's not like I'm going to get a car here.
Anyway, why did you want to meet here?
Hey, take your time and browse around.
Let's buy a car since we're here anyway.
Here?
But they only sell new cars.
I wanted to get a used car.
Come on. Just pick something.
I'll buy you a new car.
What? Goodness.
The cars here are very expensive.
Gyu Tae, let's go.
A friend of mine is a used car dealer.
He said he'd give me a good deal.
Come on.
Just pick one, okay?
The truth is, I sold a building.
It was an expensive one,
so I got a nice commission.
So, don't worry. Just pick a model.
But still...
- Goodness. Come on.
- No, wait!
Next, it's Case Number 7709.
Haengbok-ro 7, Sujeong-gu, Seoul.
It's a house.
The property's appraised value
is one million dollars.
All bidders, please come forward.
Case Number 7709.
There are five bidders in total.
I will now announce
the highest bidder for Case Number 7709.
(Bidder's Receipt)
Oh, my!
A fully loaded brand-new 2025 model?
Gyu Tae, is this car really mine now?
Yes. Drive safe, always. Okay?
Sure thing! Thanks, Gyu Tae.
Oh, right. Do you know anyone...
who knows a lot about investing?
I do know an investment expert.
You do? That's great.
Introduce us next time.
You want me to introduce you?
- Here. Let's go for a drive.
- Oh, my!
My gosh.
(Court)
Case Number 7709. The highest bid...
was 953,215.50 dollars.
Mr. Kim Dae Sik.
Me?
Is it really me?
Dad.
Mom.
(Bidder's Receipt)
This car drives so smoothly.
Does it? Do you like it?
Oh, my. It's so smooth.
My gosh!
- Grandma.
- What?
- Oh, no. Mu Chul!
My gosh, Mu Chul. What happened?
Mu Chul. Oh, no.
Sit up.
My goodness.
- Grandma.
- Yes, my sweetheart.
Are you all right?
Grandma, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Gosh, you silly goose.
If you do this,
your parents up above
will be so heartbroken.
Don't cry.
Oh, no. Mu Chul. Open your eyes!
Mu Chul, open your eyes.
Mu Chul. It's me, your grandma.
Open your eyes, please!
Can someone please save my grandson?
Oh, no. Mu Chul.
Open your eyes, Mu Chul!
Grandma...
Grandma.
What?
What...
(Good Luck!)
Do you know when Jung Ah will be back
from her honeymoon?
Can we meet now?
Here. Gentlemen like you
who exude luxury...
should wear pure gold
as it suits you best.
But he has no money.
I went to a department store
and bought furniture.
Good.
- Oh, you're selling octopus.
- It's finally starting to feel real.
- Here.
- I, Lee Hye Sook,
can live it up, at last.
Mom, wake up.
Mom!
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)