My gosh.
What great luck this is.
At this rate, it's only a matter of time
before I can pay Mu Chul back.
Oh, right. I wonder if that guy
who looks like Mu Chul is doing okay.
(Han Mu Chul and Han Tae Ha's DNA
is a 99.99-percent match.)
(It is confirmed
that they are father and son.)
Wait, then...
That man is Mu Chul?
Oh, dear.
Grandpa.
Thank you for saving me
and taking care of me...
when I was found unconscious
on the street.
I can't keep on
inconveniencing you here forever,
so I'm leaving.
I will never forget
the warmth and kindness...
you showed me.
And this is...
the little bit of money I saved
from selling scrap cardboard.
Please stay in good health.
From Han Mu Chul.
That's right.
My family.
The time that I've lost.
I will find them.
Wait for me.
Han Mu Chul is coming!
Mu Chul! Han Mu Chul!
Open up!
(Number One Real Estate,
Properties for Sale)
No way.
That man really is Mu Chul?
Then,
is it really true...
that he got into an accident
and lost his memory?
Should I tell his family now?
No.
I should meet Mu Chul in person...
and talk to him.
My gosh. Anyway,
I told him not to leave the house.
Where on earth did he go?
Oh, boy.
So, this is really our home now?
I've never lived in a house this big.
I'm so happy that
I'm about to burst into tears.
My goodness, honey.
You said you didn't want to live here.
Do you like it?
Of course, I do.
This is our home now.
The two of us...
will live here until the day we die.
No one can tell us to move out anymore.
Now, we can put nails in the walls,
and I can change the wallpaper
whenever I want.
Honey, you're happy too, right?
Do I really have to tell you
how happy I am?
I feel like I'm dreaming right now.
I can't believe I own a home now.
I know, right?
Up until recently, we had no money
and had to worry about becoming homeless.
Who knew we'd win the lottery
at such perfect timing?
I've finished organizing my stuff!
What is it?
You two.
What were you talking about?
Nothing. Nothing at all.
That's right.
I'll go to my room and get ready for work.
- All right.
- Okay.
Hey!
What?
Anyway, I wonder how Mi Ja's move went.
She was throwing out her furniture pieces
as they were all too big.
My gosh. The place must feel so empty.
What is this?
What's up with this flooring?
And why is the house so small?
You said you wanted
to move into this house.
Then, shouldn't you be happy?
I am, but I didn't know
it would be this cramped.
My gosh, whatever.
Don't forget we're holding
your dad's 49th-day memorial today.
You should come home early
from work today and help me out.
Okay, I will.
Oh, my.
Nice, it worked!
What do you think?
You can't even tell, right?
I'm sorry.
This was the best house
that I could afford.
What are you talking about?
If I'm with you,
I don't mind wherever we live.
Well, the room is small,
so we'll be able to stick closer
to each other as we sleep.
All I can do for you now
is to hug you like this,
but wait.
I will work hard...
and let you live in a much nicer house.
I promise.
There's something
more important than that.
What?
Mu Chul, when you proposed to me,
you said...
that you'd protect me until the very end.
You can never go away
and leave me all alone.
You have to stick right by my side
until the day I die.
Okay?
Okay.
I will live one more day than you, Mi Ja.
I will protect you until the end...
and follow you.
Don't worry.
Promise.
Okay.
Gosh, this room is so tiny.
Whose room was this before?
What?
Isn't this my old room?
I could see a window like this
from my old room too.
Is it perhaps the neighbor's room?
Gosh, it's hot.
Why is it so hot all of a sudden?
Hey, there.
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey.
Isn't anyone there?
- What?
- How...
Is that your room?
Yes. Then, is that your room?
Yes, it is.
Gosh, I always looked at this window...
and wondered where it led to.
Why didn't I know until now?
I don't know.
When I wasn't home,
that used to be an empty storage room.
And all I ever did was sleep there
and leave early.
Oh, I see.
Hang on.
Hey, Ye Won.
What? You're in Korea?
Where are you now?
Okay, then. I'll meet you there.
Who was it?
The co-CEO of Farm to Market
and a good friend of mine.
A friend?
I have to get going now.
I'll see you later.
Okay, bye.
Was it just a friend who's a girl?
It sounded like a girl's name.
So, your room is right across from mine.
We'll be able to meet often now.
Hey, are you leaving already?
Yes, I have a lot of work to take care of.
But you only just got here.
You should stay for a few days. I'm upset.
Sorry, but now is not a good time, Mom.
I'll be close by now, so I'll visit often.
You could just live here.
Why did you find your own place?
We have an apartment unit in Seocho-dong.
Why would you find a studio apartment
on the outskirts of the city?
I feel more comfortable that way.
I'll stay there just until I'm done
with urgent business.
Then, I'm off.
Hey, wait! Stop.
Are you leaving already, just like that?
You're running off
without having a meal with your dad?
Why, you little brat.
I mean, you started a business
without even consulting with me,
and you won't even tell me
how things are going when I ask.
Can you really do this to me?
Dad.
Goodness, don't you know how she is?
She never wanted to accept your help.
Even her friend
who studied abroad with her...
thinks she is a poor working student.
- What?
- Oh, dear.
Just leave her alone.
I'll just sit back and watch
since I know you never get into trouble,
but you're going to learn a harsh lesson
if you think starting a business is easy.
Don't worry, Dad. Then, I'll be going.
- What?
- I'm off!
What? My gosh.
Go. Fly far away.
Yes, I'm the co-CEO of Farm to Market.
Couldn't you please reconsider
canceling your contract with us?
Who is she?
I haven't seen her before.
The opening has been delayed,
but it's just a delay.
It hasn't been canceled.
Yes, please get back to us. Thank you.
Hey, Seok Jin.
What? Do they know each other?
How come you're here?
You said you were going to stay longer.
Hey, aren't you even glad to see me?
What's with that face?
Sorry. It's my fault...
that we lost the investment
for Farm to Market.
What? This won't do.
- Let's duke it out. Darn it.
- What?
Why are you doing this?
Hey, is your life over?
Who said you could be so dejected?
This is why I came.
Stop looking so glum! You little...
Okay! Just let go of me.
Gosh, you punk.
All sorts of things happen
when you're running a business.
Why are you so downcast
over a mere thing like this?
I'm here now.
Let's start things over together.
Okay?
All right. Thanks.
Hey, you two must be close friends.
Who is this? Your girlfriend?
Oh, no. She's just a friend.
- Yes.
- Oh, I see.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
Seok Jin's friend.
Then, have a good time.
Yes, thank you.
Who is she?
She's a friend of my parents
from their hometown.
Is that right?
Since I'm here,
should I say hello to your parents?
Maybe next time.
We just moved today,
so they're pretty busy.
Move? Did you move? Where to?
Where did you move to?
It would be nice to say hello
since I'm here.
Hey, how is the house you moved into?
Well, it is what it is.
What about you? Do you feel better?
Yes, I'm doing much better.
I can walk around a bit now.
I won't get fired
once you get better, will I?
Come on. I doubt that. Don't worry.
You can work for me for life if you want.
Are you crazy? I won't stay here for life.
Gosh, don't even say
such a horrible thing.
Oh, by the way,
we're having
my dad's 49th-day memorial this evening.
I can go home early, can't I?
It's the 49th day?
Of course, you should go home early.
Okay. Got it. See you next time, Jin Tae.
Oh, gosh. This is so heavy.
Hey,
peel all of these by today and wash them.
What? I have to peel
all of these by today?
Hey, I can't.
I have to go home early today...
for my dad's 49th-day memorial.
I just talked it over with Jin Tae too.
Then work hard until you have to go.
If I catch you being lazy,
I'm going to dock your pay.
I've talked it all over with Mr. Choi too.
If you don't do your job properly,
I can fire you or dock your pay
in any way I see fit.
Why, that little...
What is this? A Chinese restaurant?
Why do we need so many onions?
I've made some side dishes
and left them on the counter.
Put them in the fridge once they cool off.
I worked hard all morning to make those.
Don't spill a single drop.
Yes, all right.
Gosh, it's no surprise.
Does she think she's the owner or what?
Gosh, when will I peel all of these?
My goodness.
Oh, no.
What? Shoot.
This is bad.
Oh, no.
No, this is dirty now.
It's not edible anymore.
Shoot, what do I do?
- It will cause food poisoning.
- Tae Ha.
Shoot.
What? Where did he go?
What the... What happened here?
Why did he toss it in the trash?
Darn you, Han Tae Ha!
My gosh!
So, I've left Grandpa's house,
but where should I go?
I have no one I can visit.
Goodness.
Oh, boy.
A fried chicken joint?
Dae Sik?
He is...
doing all right.
Dae Sik runs a fried chicken joint.
Oh, right.
Should I go to Dae Sik?
Let's say I find him.
But what if he reacts like Gyu Tae?
No. Don't give up...
without trying, Han Mu Chul.
Yes, let's go and find him!
(Number One Real Estate)
(Daewoon Building)
Oh, hello.
So...
how did your move go?
It went pretty well.
As I mentioned the other day,
you don't have to worry about the rent.
Just think of it as your own house
and make yourself at home.
Okay, thank you.
Did you get groceries?
Oh, we're holding
Mu Chul's 49th-day memorial service today.
I bought some groceries
to make a few simple dishes.
Oh, it's today?
I knew it was coming up soon.
What time will it start?
If you don't mind,
Gyu Tae and I would like to be there too.
We were just going to keep it simple
and have only the family there.
You can definitely do that,
but if the others hear
that his 49th-day memorial is today,
they'll all want to be there.
My wife, Gyu Tae, Geum Ok. As you know,
they knew Mu Chul for many years.
We'll do it in the evening,
so you can come if you'd like.
I'll be off, then.
Okay.
- Darn, why isn't he picking up?
- The person you have reached is...
- Gyu Tae.
- Hey, Dae Sik.
I just ran into Mu Chul's wife.
She said
Mu Chul's 49th-day memorial was today.
His 49th-day memorial?
It will be held in the evening.
Let's go together.
Should I tell him
that Mu Chul is actually alive?
It makes no sense to hold a memorial
for someone who's alive.
You'll come too, right?
Well, the thing is...
No. I should find Mu Chul
before I say anything.
If I tell him now
but fail to find Mu Chul,
I'll get chewed out
for not telling him sooner.
Yes, sure. We'll go together.
Gyu Tae.
Oh, Dae Sik. You were here too.
Hey, Geum Ok. I'm glad you're here.
Come to Mu Chul's house in the evening.
You mean, Mi Ja's place?
But why?
Mu Chul's 49th-day memorial service
is today.
It'd be nice to have you there too.
Oh, it's already been 49 days.
Okay. Of course, I should be there.
All right. I'm off.
- All right.
- Okay, have a good day.
Thanks, you too.
Gyu Tae, have you given it some thought?
What? What are you talking about?
The blind date.
So, have you thought it over and decided?
Well, forget it.
I can't do it.
What?
Why not? Did something happen?
Hey, Geum Ok.
Yes?
No, never mind.
Did you come here to ask me that?
Oh, here. Take this.
What's this?
Side dishes.
Keep them in the fridge
and eat them with rice.
You have rice, right?
Side dishes? I see braised soybeans.
I don't eat beans.
Hey, I won't eat these. Take this back.
What? Just eat them
instead of cup noodles.
Must you act like a little kid
complaining about side dishes?
I don't want it. Take it back.
Just listen to me and eat them.
Unless you want to die before you turn 60.
Hey! Why would you say I might die?
Why would I die so young?
It can happen to anyone.
Look what happened to Mu Chul.
He died before he turned 60.
Hey! Why are you bringing up Mu Chul?
I'm so frustrated.
My gosh.
(We only use fresh,
locally raised chicken.)
Is this restaurant owned
by Mr. Kim Dae Sik?
Do you know Mr. Kim Dae Sik?
Is your boss' name Kim Dae Sik?
Yes, Kim Dae Sik.
Kim Dae Sik.
His name is Kim Dae Sik.
Do you know him?
Who? Kim Dae Sik?
Yes. Oh, my! Do you know him?
Kim Dae Sik?
He's the one who runs Jackpot Chicken.
Jackpot Chicken?
The 49th-day memorial service is today?
Yes, that's right.
Let's go there together, honey.
Okay.
Right, about Mi Ja's rent.
What? Rent?
How much are you thinking
of charging them for rent?
Oh, that.
Well, what would be a good amount?
If you charge too much,
you'll look like a heartless man,
so make sure it's a reasonable amount.
And let them live there rent-free
for a few months.
All right.
I'll take care of it,
so don't worry about it.
Anyhow, Mi Ja and her family...
This is their first time
holding a memorial in that house.
Is this the right spot for these?
I'm pretty sure there are rules
you must follow to place these correctly.
I don't know. Just put them anywhere.
Do you remember?
Dad said we should eat
the flesh on the apple peels.
Of course, I remember that.
Not just apple peels.
"You should also eat the white part
when eating watermelon."
"When eating Korean melons,
eat the seeds too."
"And eat the grape skin too."
We could go on and on
just talking about fruits alone.
But I don't think...
my heart felt this empty back then.
Now that we've moved into this unit,
I feel Dad's absence even more.
What about you?
Me, what? Just go and bring the food.
Whatever.
Oh, hello. You're here.
Yes. Is everything ready?
Yes. Mom, the guests are here.
Oh, you made it. You're here too.
Yes, Mi Ja. It's my first time
visiting your new place.
So, I got this for you.
You didn't have to bring anything.
Thanks.
Were you cooking?
Yes.
Let's go. Let me help you.
It's all done.
What about Mr. Choi? Is he coming too?
Gyu Tae? Yes, he'll be here soon.
I see.
- Oh, hello.
- Aren't you that guy from the other day?
Excuse me, sir.
That guy who used to live here.
Do you know where he went?
He left.
He left? Where did he go?
He left a letter and took off.
What?
(Number One Real Estate)
(Jackpot Chicken)
My gosh.
This is it.
Dae Sik.
Oh, it's locked.
Where did he go?
Who are you?
Oh, hello.
I'm a friend of the owner here.
Do you know where he went?
Oh, Mr. Kim?
He said he had to go and do something
at home earlier.
Home?
This is...
What?
This place?
I was here before.
I see.
I guess my head hurt like that...
because this was Dae Sik's house.
Oh, "Kim Dae Sik."
What?
Which one should I press?
Wait.
What?
Where on earth has he gone off to?
This won't do.
I should hurry over there now...
and stop them
from having the 49th-day memorial.
Tae Ha.
It must be Gyu Tae. I'll let him in.
Oh, it's open.
Is that you?
Mu... What?
Oh, hello. I'm here to see Kim Dae Sik.
Mi Ja!
- I'm sorry!
- Mi Ja!
- I was just...
- Look.
Oh, my.
Mr. Han?
What?
What's all this noise?
Honey.
Mu...
Mu Chul?
What's going on?
Hello.
My name is Han Mu Chul.
(Good Luck!)
I'm a fraud and a divorced man.
Was I such an awful person?
You don't think Mu Chul is pretending
to have lost his memory, do you?
What if his memory comes back later?
I know. That can't happen.
So, tonight,
can I stay here?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)