Your Majesty,
I have something to say.
What is it?
Your Majesty,
Hunxiang Instrument is under construction,
but the shape of its top
remains to be determined.
I have been working around the clock,
hoping to relieve Emperor and your worries.
Finally, a few days ago,
I found two rubies the size of a melon
under a plum tree in Zilang Mountain.
They're rarely seen in the world.
It seems to be providence.
Therefore,
I asked hundreds of skillful craftsmen to weave
an auspicious golden treasure with them.
It can be placed on Hunxiang Instrument's top.
It's now presented for you to take a look.
Your Majesty,
in my opinion,
it's against the rites system to place
a golden phoenix instead of a golden dragon
since Emperor is the supreme ruler.
Mr. Liu, I disagree with you.
You may not know that
Empress Dowager was born in a plum forest.
These two rubies
happened to be discovered under a plum tree.
Zilang Mountain looks like a female figure,
even showing the shape of hands and feet.
It's a rarely seen phoenix nest.
I think
Hunxiang Instrument
can be named Immortal Instrument.
It symbolizes
not only the continuity of our kingdom
but also Empress Dowager's
virtues and longevity.
Such being the case,
it will be in your charge.
Your Majesty.
As you wish.
It's absolutely not right.
That's all for today.
Your Majesty, please reconsider it.
This is unprecedented.
Please strictly observe the rites system.
=A League of Nobleman=
=Episode 10=
(Xuanzheng Hall)
Xuan Ji surprised me.
He can read Empress Dowager's mind.
Simply being an alchemist
wouldn't make him favored by Empress Dowager.
Excuse me, Mr. Lan.
Mr. Liu, what can I do for you?
Emperor is not yet in power
and it's the weak time of his reign.
Xuan Ji presented the Phoenix Head today.
Empress Dowager must have known it in advance
and was simply coordinating with him.
Well…
Minister Gong has resigned.
You're in charge of the Ministry of Rites.
Just now in the Hall, you should
stand out against it in the name of rites.
I…
Mr. Lan.
Mr. Wang.
We have to submit the embalmer's case file.
We got to take a statement right away.
Mr. Liu,
it's important.
Please excuse us.
You…
Zhang.
Zhang,
I've been looking for you.
What do you want to do with reed leaves?
Wrap zongzi (glutinous rice dumpling).
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I can help you.
Choose fresh and large leaves,
preferably 16 inches.
For the two of us,
is it necessary to be so picky?
You know what?
When you're away in the last few days,
the noddle stall was almost overwhelmed.
Since you solved the big case
and won the fame of Detective Mr. Wang,
many people have been attracted here,
just like a school of carps.
You used the wrong words.
Whatever.
I've come up with a title for you.
From now on,
you'll be the capital city's
Detective Noodle.
Zhang,
did you hear me?
I'm thinking about the case in Moluo Village.
How could there be
the blood-mist effect?
What happened
to make the night sky as bright as day?
I've talked to a wall.
Besides,
who told the embalmer
about the legend of Injeeten?
Why did he do it?
How did the embalmer know Mr. Lan's father?
What's the connection
with the treason case 20 years ago?
We've got rid of that fuddy-duddy.
He
just wants you to bear the brunt.
But thanks to Mr. Liu,
the court is not completely
under Empress Dowager's control.
You mean
I shouldn't interrupt you.
Without you,
I could handle him by beating around the bush.
I didn't expect you to help me out
and owe you a favor.
Anyway,
what's done is done.
You owe me a favor now.
Mr. Wang,
Mr. Lan,
thank you both
for speaking for me in the hall.
Well,
Mr. Lan is the one you should thank.
I did it at his repeated request.
We're colleagues and should help each other.
Maybe someday,
I'll need your help too.
I get it.
I'll surely return the favor.
When will you return the my favor?
I won't return it since I owe you a lot.
Speaking of
the bet you lost to Zhang Ping,
when are you going to fulfill your promise?
He is waiting for you
to help him make doughs.
If you're not mentioning it,
I'd forgotten it.
Detective Noodle.
Dear folks,
let me formally introduce someone to you.
This is
Detective Noodle
Zhang Ping, a scholar from Xichuan County.
So he is Zhang Ping.
Detective Noodle?
I came up with the name for you overnight.
What do you think?
Isn't it good?
Detective.
Come on.
I learned that the embalmer went in and out
through a tunnel to commit a murder
and disappeared without a trace.
How did you catch him?
Moreover,
what about the poison?
Detective,
my nephew couldn't find his bamboo horse.
Can you help him find it?
Can you help me find my colander?
Calm down.
Just take a seat, order one bowl of noodles
and then tell your stories slowly.
We will answer your questions one by one.
Everyone has a chance.
Come on.
- One large bowl of noodles.
Add one more egg.
I'd like one bowl of noodles.
You must be happy.
Mr. Wang.
The two detectives
must have something important to discuss.
We'll come again later, later.
Don't go.
Wait, wait.
I lost the bet.
I made this
for making good on my promise.
Hot wonton.
(Hanhui Pavilion, Ning'an)//Would you like one bowl of wonton?
Would you like some? Meat stuffing.
(Detective Noodle)
What did Mr. Wang come here for?
He scared all the guests away.
Mr. Wang
did make a dough personally.
I'm really surprised.
It's not easy for Mowen.
Mr. Lan.
Mr. Lan,
please.
this long gown is plain in color,
looking really nice with the white jade.
Mr. Lan,
they're perfectly matched.
To be honest,
I'm here today
to ask you a favor.
This is the Red Gilding Silk
from Yunshang Community
Yes.
Empress Dowager
wants a dress made of this fabric.
Unfortunately, Miss Wu was murdered
before finishing it.
As the Minister of Rites,
I'm responsible for this.
Mr. Xu, would you please help me
study this?
Red Gilding Silk
is the culmination of weaving technique.
It's Miss Wu's secret craftmanship.
I've always wanted to figure it out.
I'll surely
try my best in this.
Then,
my future career is counting on you.
I feel almost back-breaking.
It would kill me
if we didn't close earlier today.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Zhang,
are you going to wrap zongzi now?
Why are you suddenly so generous?
You kept nagging me
for stealing one of your salted duck eggs.
It's great that
we'll have zongzi stuffed with egg yolk.
I'm looking forward to a good meal tomorrow.
Zhang?
Where is he so early in the morning?
He left me some zongzi.
All stuffed with red dates?
Zhang, where are those with egg yolk?
Come on, come on, everyone.
Please go back. Please go back.
Mr. Lan doesn't take gifts.
No gifts.
Why are there so many people there?
Stop.
Listen to me, listen to me, just listen to me.
Please go back.
Mr. Lan is not home today.
It's no use waiting here.
Mr. Lan doesn't take gifts.
Please go back. Please go back.
It's Mr. Lan.
Mr. Lan,
I'm bringing you some egg yolk zongzi.
Mr. Lan is over there.
Mr. Lan.
Hurry up.
Come on.
- Mr. Lan.//- Mr. Lan.
I'm Li Jing from Shunhua Cunty, Qing Prefecture.
I'm slow-witted
and there's a lot in the ancient books
that I don't quite understand.
Would you please give me some advice?
It's painted by Mr. Yan.
It's very expensive.
You must pay a lot for this.
It's just a token of my respect.
Please take it.
Mr. Lan,
this is mine.
A century-old ginseng.
Excuse me,
what is it in your hand?
It's the egg yolk zongzi I made.
It's delicious. You may have a taste.
Egg yolk zongzi.
Can you open it and show me?
It's really zongzi.
It's too worthless.
I would never give this as a gift.
Speaking of sincerity,
the zongzi shows more of his sincerity.
But no matter how expensive your gifts are,
I can't accept them.
I appreciate your kindness.
I hope you could keep studying
and go back
to bury yourselves in your studies.
- Mr. Lan.//- Mr. Lan.
Why is he leaving?
I spent so much money,
but he didn't even take a look at it.
Zhang,
let's sell zongzi instead.
It'll be surely more profitable.
By the way,
I'm just back from Xingye Community.
I saw a "help wanted" notice
at the entrance of the Court of Judicial Review.
According to the notice,
they're recruiting some new men
due to Empress Dowager's dissatisfaction.
What are the requirements?
Do I meet them?
Yes, you do.
But
they only want helpers.
I'm okay with that.
Zhang,
I don't mean to discourage you.
You can't get
even such a job
without a connection.
Well,
I have an idea.
But you may not be willing to do it.
What is it?
If you can get Mr. Lan's help,
the result would be different.
Well,
Mr. Lan has saved you several times.
You may go thank him with a gift
and mention this to him.
I went to see him,
but he doesn't take gifts.
What?
You already went to see him with a gift?
And voluntarily?
Then tell me
what did you give him?
And how did you give it?
I just gave…
Zhang Ping.
Mr. Lan,
what are you doing here?
Where is the zongzi for me?
Then I'd like one bowl of noodles.
No more noodles.
There's only millet congee.
Millet congee will be fine.
Salted egg white.
It's the leftover.
Mr. Lan,
Zhang means
you came late and there's no more zongzi.
There's only some egg white left.
He'll make some zongzi for you another day.
It's egg white,
but it tastes fresh and tender.
I used sheld duck eggs
and pickled them with Xinfeng Wine
and fine salt.
I didn't eat the zongzi, but thank you anyway.
I should thank you too.
Mr. Lan,
actually,
I've been meaning to ask you a favor.
What is it?
We'd better talk about it in your place.
OK.
Chen Chou, you clean this up.
Dear me,
Zhang has finally got it.
I want to use Water Illusion on you.
What did you say?
Why do you offer to do it this time?
After learning about what happened
in Moluo Village,
I've been thinking
what caused the scarlet mist sky.
And this case involves your father.
So, I want to find the truth.
Zhang Ping,
do you know the accusation against my father?
It's collision with the enemy.
That's a disgrace to the imperial court.
The subject has been a taboo
over the past 20 years.
Not to mention an investigation,
even asking about it
would cost your life.
I've thought it over
and I'm well prepared.
I won't tell anyone about it.
But you'll fall into a long comatose state
after casting a spell.
Aren't you afraid of losing your life?
I've been used to it.
I'll be fine after a sleep.
Then let me be straight with you.
What I'm really worried about
is your straight temper
You're reckless while looking into a case,
which may ruin what I've planned for years.
Then,
everyone in the know will die.
I give you my word and I won't break it.
The divine punishment for Moluo People,
the embalmer's poison,
the man who instructed him
to sacrifice to Six Sages
and your father's case
might all be correlated.
Therefore,
I want to find out the truth.
But what does these have to do with you?
If everyone cares about the truth,
there would be nowhere to hide for darkness.
That's what Mr. Mu Yesheng said.
I grew up
reading his detective stories.
OK.
You may do it.
Under a spell,
I would let down all my defenses, right?
Right.
You would
have no doubts,
no secrets
and feel no pain.
That's how you could clear your mind,
return to your true nature
and find the truth.
Sir,
if Zhang Ping asks anything improper,
I could…
Sir,
to succeed,
you must open your heart.
Xu Dong, you may leave.
Yes, sir.
Zhang Ping,
deep inside me,
you would see
a trapped bast.
Sorry for you to see it.
Everyone has a demon insinde
So do I.
The only clue I could remember
was a mysterious woman.
She went to the south
with my father.
As I remember,
she suddenly appeared
and talked privately with my father for days.
Then,
they left to the south overnight.
When my father returned,
he was accused of colliding with the enemy.
It's been 20 years.
I can't remember her looks.
I hope
you could help me recall a bit about her.
Sir,
please stare at the water bowl.
Is this
the realm of truth and purity?
You may meditate and recall the past here.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
This is the demon inside me.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Keep my mind as clear as ice.
Not afraid of the falling sky.
Stay calm in changes.
Relax my nerves.
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Keep my mind as clear as ice.
Not afraid of the falling sky.
Stay calm in changes.
Relax my nerves.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Keep my mind as clear as ice.
Not afraid of the falling sky.
Stay calm in changes.
Relax my nerves.
Keep my mind as clear as ice.
Not afraid of the falling sky.
Stay calm in changes.
The demon inside you came from your confusion.
I can't help you break it.
Every time I think of my father being wronged,
this children's folk rhyme would haunt my ears.
My father was not a traitor.
He was not a traitor.
Where
is the traitor?
Hanging
Father.
at the market entrance.
Who is the traitor?
Father.
Either a pig
or a dog.
Father.
Where is the traitor?
Mr. Lan,
you must settle your mind.
Who is
Father.
the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Where is the traitor?
Hanging at the market entrance.
Father.
You're not a traitor.
Who is the traitor?
Either a pig or a dog.
Father.
=A League of Nobleman=