Zhang Ping.
Can you calm down?
Let go of me!
Zhang Ping!
Let go of him.
Let go of me!
Zhang Ping!
If you want to seek revenge on
the Empress Dowager,
you should change into dry clothes
and have some ginger soup,
lest you should catch a cold and collapse
before you enter the palace.
Then you need to choose a magic weapon
or
you can't beat
the well-equipped Imperial Guards.
You also need to get skillful
in martial arts,
which will take you five years at least
to 20 years,
or
you can't beat
a hundred soldiers on your own.
(How can an ant shake a tree?)
(That's the Empress Dowager.)
The past
is way too heavy.
All you need to know is
I did come for Moluo Clan.
Moluo villagers were
unjustly slaughtered.
You were at the Court of Judicial Review.
How could you stand by and do nothing?
From the moment I learned this secret,
I could no longer be
the Mu Yesheng
who hated injustice like poison.
(In Lingnan Secret Realm,)
(there is a Moluo Village.)
(The water is clear)
(and the mountains are steep.)
(Dormant for 20 years.)
(Just wait for today)
(to kill the enemy with my hands,)
(and celebrate it with wine and music.)
Thank you,
Your Majesty!
(I can't do it.)
(You)
(and Mr. Lan)
(can't do it, either.)
(No.)
(I can do it,)
(but I won't do it like Mr. Jinghu.)
(I'll go home,)
(go back to Moluo Village)
(and find out the truth.)
(Then I'll revenge for)
(my master and my people in my own way.)
=A League of Nobleman=
=Episode 24=
(Three months later, Forest in the South)
(All you need to know is)
(I did come for Moluo Clan.)
(The past)
(is way too heavy.)
(When my plan is accomplished,)
(you will understand
the cause and effect.)
(There will still be an end.)
(Do you think I'm immortal?)
(No one will take away my Ping.)
(Kuruo.)
Where are you?
How can I find you?
How can I find Moluo Village?
(Sir.)
(It's just his side of the story.)
(Enough!)
(I'll send people to verify it,)
(but before we find any evidence,)
(we can't jump to a conclusion.)
(What are you going to do?)
(Go home.)
(I'll find out the truth about the past)
(and avenge the death of my master
and my people with my own hands.)
Sir.
How long has Zhang Ping been gone?
More than three months.
I wonder how he is now.
He's hard to kill.
I don't think he will collapse easily.
How's the investigation into Shulin?
I've had people following him every day
as you instructed.
But Mr. Gu only went out
to pick herbs in the mountains
or tend to his garden in the suburb.
He had no contact
with anyone suspicious.
What kind of herbs did he pick?
Herbs for burns.
(What Shulin did
after he came back this time)
(is too much of a coincidence.)
Peizhi.
I can't sleep.
I'm here to chat with you.
Is it because
there is something on your mind?
I'd be lying to myself
if I say no.
Are you still thinking about
what Zhang Ping said?
I can't pretend
that I didn't hear what he said,
and I can't pretend I didn't see
you've been decocting herbs
for burns these days.
I want to clear up my confusion,
so I have to ask you in person.
Even if I did offer medicine
to the Empress Dowager,
what's wrong with that?
You've always been unworldly.
How would you yield to power and wealth?
Unworldly?
If I'm really unworldly,
how would I go to the capital
to take the imperial exam ten years ago?
Peizhi.
Do you really know me?
(He's also infected with miasma.)
(His body is burning.)
(I'm afraid...)
You're awake.
Don't move.
You need more sleep.
Mr. Wang.
Why are you here?
I was going to ask you that.
You've been living well in the capital.
What are you doing here?
There's a lot going on in the capital.
I'm here
to find Moluo Village.
All the questions
can only be answered here.
What happened?
Is the Moluo Village you mentioned
really here?
I've been lost in the forest for days.
I haven't seen any sign of a village.
I remember it clearly.
The archives
of the Court of Judicial Review
say the village is here.
What about you, sir?
Shouldn't you be fighting at the front
with His Majesty?
Why are you here?
The war is not in our favor.
Although we have more soldiers,
our soldiers are ill-adapted
to the southern climate
and are infected with miasma.
Now our war with Nandong
entered into a stalemate.
I was ordered by the Emperor
to lead the vanguard to the South
to spy on their army.
Unexpectedly, we lost our way
just like you
and we were ambushed
by the people of Nandong.
The rest of our people
are either dead
or wounded.
Here.
Sir.
I'm not hungry.
You should eat it.
Sir.
Water.
Here.
Sir.
We've been stuck in the forest for days
and we're short of food and water.
We still have some pancakes left,
but there's only
half a bag of water.
You...
You shouldn't give it to him.
What do you mean?
I'm giving him my share.
But...
It's okay, Mr. Wang.
I'm not thirsty.
I have to go find Moluo Village now.
Take care, sir.
You're playing tough.
We're attacked!
Withdraw!
Get up!
Hurry!
Mom.
I will take you home.
The waterfall.
What did you say?
We should go in there.
Let's go in there.
There is no time to hesitate.
Let's go in there first.
Be careful.
Come on, be careful.
Sir.
The people of Nandong
didn't see us,
but Zhang Ping can't speak now.
What should we do next?
We don't know the situation outside.
Let's rest here tonight
and talk about it tomorrow morning.
Yes, sir.
He saved us
this time.
But
how did he know
there was a cave behind the waterfall?
He should be home soon.
(Your writing is generous,)
(casual and detached.)
(But your poems)
(are all seven-character octaves,)
like shackles in a cage,
trapping all your
calligraphic vigour and style.
Your sincerity
is difficult to display.
(If you do pass the exam,)
(I'll congratulate you.)
It's just that
I can't help feeling sorry
for the trapped true temperament.
Why does he know me so well?
Did he
come prepared?
(Mom.)
(I want my mom.)
What's wrong?
I want my mom.
Don't cry.
I'll find your mom for you.
Mom.
Hide-and-seek.
I remember it all.
Mom.
(Kuruo.)
(You have been baptized
by the water of the Sacred Lake.)
(From today,)
(I can teach you how to use magic.)
Try and catch me!
Kuruo.
Have you learned
how to use the Water Vessel?
No.
I got you.
You haven't learned it?
Calm your mind.
I got it.
Do you want it?
Okay, then be quiet.
Close your eyes.
Listen to the wind in the rice fields.
You have to be focused
with a calm mind
to master your Water Vessel.
Your eyes are open.
Don't run.
Kuruo.
Come here.
Come to me.
Do you know what
the Water Vessel is used for?
The people in the world
keep their suffering in their heart
which makes them deeply troubled
over time.
The Water Vessel can be used
to cure troubled people.
Is everyone troubled?
Of course.
I'm also troubled.
What are you troubled by?
I hid it under the water.
People hide what makes them
the most troubled
under the water.
When you learn how to use magic,
you'll know what I've been troubled by.
Come on.
Do it with me.
Close your eyes.
Let's thank the wind,
the rocks,
and the trees
for letting us feel the purest heart
in the purest place.
This is the purest place in the world.
You must feel it with your heart.
Mom!
I'm here!
Good boy.
I'll be back soon from the capital.
(Hanhui Pavilion, Ning'an)
(Lan's Mansion)
=A League of Nobleman=