♫ The preface of the love words is stained with lovesickness ♫
♫ Who is copying your handwriting? ♫
♫ Falling flowers and drifting through
generations of wind and rain  ♫
♫ Cannot abandon for the sake of fate ♫
♫ Going through sorrows and joys in the intoxicated dream ♫
♫ Who is testing my affection? ♫
♫ Several black and white chess pieces ♫
♫ Hard to differentiate triumph and loss,
love and hate, hometown ♫
♫ Going on these years ♫
♫ Should be good times ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, looking for love  ♫
♫ There is too much confusion ♫
♫ Holding green wind, picking chrysanthemums
under the eastern fence ♫
♫ Another difficult season ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, I reminisce in love ♫
♫ Prosperity hides too much wind and rain ♫
♫ Falling flowers singing a song ♫
♫ The person in the vague dream parted from me ♫
[Love in Flames of War]
[Episode 31]
Eldest Brother Shen! Shen Yanqing!
Are you saying you don't agree?
Shuyi, we are really unsuitable.
What's bad about me?
This is not a question of whether you are good or not.
Are you just like those friends who look down on me?
I don't look down on you.
It's just that I have always regarded you as my younger sister.
When a man rejects a woman, he always says that he only regards her as a younger sister.
Why are you using this same old excuse?
Enough, Shuyi. Stop throwing a tantrum.
Shen Yanqing, you don't have any feelings for me?
I'm sorry.
Not even just a bit?
I'm really sorry.
Shen Yanqing, I like you this much.
Will you die if you like me for a bit?
Shuyi, I'm sorry.
I can only wish that you will find the right suitable beloved one.
Hangjing.
Hold on. You don't need to leave.
I won't go in.
Seventh Aunt personally stitched this.
I will leave it here.
Third Brother.
- Third Brother, do you know this child...
- You don't need to say anything.
Don't worry.
I won't harm you, even more so the child.
I will accept him.
- Don't be a slave to a country that's subjugated by others!
- Don't buy Japanese goods!
- The Japanese government owes us an apology!
- Punish the murderers according to law!
- Don't be a slave to a country that's subjugated by others!
Third Brother, many students are protesting at the cluster of Japanese companies these days.
And they've gathered in many places in Beixin.
Obviously, the protest is organized and intentional.
They definitely won't stop in just one or two days.
The Japanese navy shot citizens in Changsha.
The students are doing this to show their support for Changsha.
Their call has received responses from across the country.
They also secretly called for the Education Council and Chamber of Commerce
and people working for companies in Japan to go on strike and boycott Japanese products.
Now businesses with the Japanese have almost stopped.
But Governor Jin once ordered that the Northern Territories have to provide preferential policies for foreign businesses.
I'm worried that these Japanese businessmen will report it to the governor.
Third Brother, shall we give an order to disperse these students?
The Japanese committed violence in public and killed our people.
Do we have any reasons to stop them from pleading for the people?
In fact, I do respect the leaders of the protest this time.
They're safeguarding our territories and fighting for our sovereignty.
Have you found out who they are?
It's not clear yet.
But it's very likely to be led by the Communist Party.
Communist Party?
Lady, you're awake.
Don't you think the weather is strange? It was raining so heavily just now.
And now it's sunny again.
Lady, are you okay?
- I have abdominal pain.
- Lady! Don't scare me, Lady!
Lady!
Help! Help!
[Beixin Jihe Hospital]
Heavens, bless Lady and keep her baby safe.
- Heavens, bless them...
- It's been so long, and they still haven't come out.
The doctor is there. It will be fine. Let's not worry.
Heavens, bless Lady and keep her baby safe.
[Surgery in Progress]
[Maintain Quietness]
Doctor.
How is my wife now?
Third Master, your wife hasn't woken up from the anesthetics yet.
The baby... is gone.
- The baby is gone?
- We've tried our best.
- Lady! Lady!
- Seventh Madam.
Lady!
[Beixin Jihe Hospital]
Don't leave me.
Don't go.
You're awake.
Where's the baby?
Give me my baby.
I just heard my baby cry.
Lie down here and don't move.
Hangjing, the doctor says you need to get some good rest.
My baby...
Hangjing!
I'm going to find my baby!
- Hangjing!
- I'm going to find my baby!
I'm going to find my baby!
- Stop!
- Don't stop me!
I'm going to find my baby!
- I'm going to find my baby!
- Your baby is gone!
I'm going to find my baby...
My baby...
I'm Young Third Madam's doctor.
When she's not well, I'll be called for sure!
How would I not understand the stakes in it?
Even if someone puts a knife to my throat, I wouldn't dare!
Then tell me exactly
how you diagnosed her.
Don't miss any detail.
As usual,
I arrived at the Xiao Residence at 3:00 p.m. to give her an infusion of antiabortifacient.
While Young Third Madam was resting,
I went to the side hall with Jin Xiang and asked her
if Young Third Madam rested well this week.
And I gave her some prescriptions to help improve her condition.
After about half an hour,
I returned to Young Third Madam's bedroom,
and gave her some advice on the dos and don'ts.
Did you leave right after you gave her that advice?
Yes. I was about to leave immediately,
but it suddenly started raining heavily.
So I waited for a while. After the rain stopped,
I left the Xiao Residence.
- Take him down.
- Yes, Sir.
- Move.
- Advisor Mo! I really didn't do it!
I really didn't do it! Advisor Mo! Advisor Mo!
How did it go?
The hospital checked the medicine that Doctor Sun used.
All of the infusion bottles were from the hospital. And they were sealed.
Only after he arrived at the Xiao Residence, he opened them while Sister-in-law and Jin Xiang were present. Nothing wrong with that.
I went to his personal residence too to check his personal belongings. There was nothing wrong with them either.
I also asked his friends who live nearby. He didn't see anyone suspicious recently either.
Jin Xiang.
Refill the basin with hot water for me, please.
- Here.
- Okay.
Third Master, I think you should get some rest. Leave this work to me.
It's fine. I'll take care of her.
Okay.
Third Brother.
- How did the investigation go?
- I interrogated Doctor Sun in person.
He didn't seem to be lying.
And he has more than twenty family members. They all live in Beixin.
There's no reason for him to do it.
Before we find out the truth, you must watch his every move.
Even if we have to turn the whole Beixin upside down,
I'll find that person.
Rest assured, Third Brother. I'll reveal the whole truth.
You can take good care of Third Sister-in-law, and yourself too.
You don't need to worry about anything else.
Here, Hangjing. Take the medicine.
Hangjing, the hearts of a mother and her child are connected. Seventh Aunt knows how painful it is for you.
You need to take care and get better.
And you'll have a baby again very soon.
No.
My baby is gone.
As the old saying goes, a child that has a destined bone with its parents
will come back to find its mother again.
So no matter what happens, you need to survive this.
Really?
The child will come back again?
Yes. If the baby knows you love it so much,
it will definitely come back to you soon
and have you as its mother again.
Let Seventh Aunt accompany you tonight, okay?
Uncles. Please sit down.
Beichen, if it's not because Wei Zhenliang has some sort of unusual move,
we wouldn't call you
back to the East Main Camp.
Right, Third Master. Have you settled everything at home?
Don't worry about it. How's the situation going?
Deputy Commander, please take a look.
Wei Zhenliang's troops used to station in the northwest.
Recently, they've been looking to the Japanese as their support and expanding their forces.
And their ambition has become even bigger.
Especially Beixin's ice-free harbor,
they're very eager to take over.
They not only re-arranged their military manpower,
they even delivered 50 units of cannons.
They use military exercises as an excuse, we should be prepared.
Their current location is facing our troops at Jin Yang and
Qin Guan; two defense lines. We need to be prepared.
We have got to make sure we're in battle mode.
That's right.
You skipped lunch again? You eat less than mosquitos these days. Have you found any clues?
I verified with Jin Xiang and Doctor Sun. All of the IV fluid they brought were sealed.
Also, it was opened right in front of them.
I wonder how those abortion medicines went into the fluid?
That's right.
All the bottles are made out of glass, and they're all sealed, how did it go inside?
It's a glass bottle.
What's the matter?
Look!
Did you see the little needle mark?
Here.
As you all know, Third Madam lost her child.
After careful investigation, someone in this house rigged the IV fluid.
Someone rigged the IV bottle? It can't be.
How is it possible?
That's why I want to know between 3:00 p.m. to 3:30 p.m. that day,
other than Jin Xiang, what were you guys doing?
I didn't do anything. I was in the kitchen.
Think carefully! Tell me one by one.
I went out to get a procedure done early in the morning.
I didn't come back until evening. Gatekeeper can prove that.
Fourth Lady has not been in a good mood these days. She locked herself in the room.
I was with her in the room.
How about you? What're you thinking?
That day, when I got a break,
I went out to gamble.
Hu Sanwan from Dong Mianhua alley can prove that.
How dare you sneak out to gamble?
Seventh Madam. Young Master Mo. Young Master Xu.
I took a nap in the room,
I've no alibi.
But I can use my entire family's lives to be collateral, it's not me.
Third Young Madam treated me so well,
I should give her my gratitude, why would I harm her baby?
Lift her up.
Come.
Next one.
That day, I was making Osmanthus Jelly in the kitchen for Third Young Madam.
Nanny Liu and Nanny Jiang can be my alibi.
That's right. I can confirm that.
Three of us were in the kitchen that day.
She delivered the Osmanthus Jelly right after 3:30 p.m.
After she left, we stayed in the kitchen and didn't go anywhere.
Next one.
After eating time, I was cleaning the dishes in the kitchen.
They can be my alibi.
That's right. I can confirm that.
My mother was sick, I wasn't in the house that day. I was taking care of my mother.
Miss Fengqi, will Young Master Mo find out I did that?
Your statement was flawless.
How will they find out?
But they've already found out the syringe hole.
If they found out, what should I do?
Even if they found out,
you should know what to do.
Don't forget, you're not done with your performance.
[Sales Contract]
Isn't this my sister's sales contract?
You need to ask your gambling-addicted father.
I helped your father pay for his debt.
Your father gave me your sister as a guarantee.
Get up.
If you follow all my directions,
I'll return this sale contract to you.
If you don't want to work with me,
I'll sell your sister to the brothel.
By then, don't blame me for that.
Lady, just eat a little bit.
If you carry on like that, it's bad for your body.
I said I don't want to eat.
Lady, I heard Seventh Aunt said
Young Master Shen is leaving Beixin in a few days.
Will... Will you really not send him off?
Why would I do that?
But you've been waiting for him.
His doesn't love me.
It will be shameful if I go.
You go get busy.
What's the matter? What's the purpose of your visit?
I'm leaving. I just wanted to say goodbye.
So soon?
I'm done with what I need to do.
Also, I heard about what had happened in your family.
Lately, you've been busy at work.
Seventh Aunt told me that you haven't been home in so many days.
No matter what happened,
you need to take care of yourself; don't exhaust yourself.
I don't even know what tiredness is.
Every night, no matter how exhausted,
whenever I think of that child, I feel like I owe him everything.
Losing a child is the biggest pain for parents.
You and Sister-in-law need time to recuperate.
That's why you shouldn't increase your mental burden.
You'll definitely have another child in the future.
You will love and take care of them by then.
The string in your heart,
don't stretch it too far.
Thank you, Eldest Brother Shen.
Report!
Instructor Du.
Perfect timing. Let me introduce you.
This is Shen Yanqing, Brother Shen. We grew up together.
This is Ying Army Independence Regiment Team Captain,
he was also my mentor at school, Du Heng, Captain Du.
Sir Shen.
- It's nice to meet you.
You're both Beichen's teacher and his friend.
Beichen is very lucky to have a regiment commander like you.
Thank you for your compliment, Sir Shen.
Beichen, I'll be on my way.
Okay. This way.
Eldest Brother Shen, take care.
Take care.
- Old Li, see him off for me.
- Yes, Sir.
Please.
This is the plan for sending soldiers to Jinyang Pass devised by the three-army joint garrison.
Lady, why are you here alone?
It's cold outside. Let me help you get inside.
Jin Xiang.
Look at the moon. It's a full moon.
Yes, My lady.
Lady, I'll check in the kitchen to see if your medicine is ready.
Please sit here and wait for me.
My baby...
You're in Heaven now.
Will you blame Mother for not protecting you well?
Poor little master. I'll burn more paper money for you.
Please find a good family for yourself on the other side of the world.
I shouldn't have kept this a secret from Young Third Madam.
Don't blame me! Don't blame me!
Young Third Madam!
Xiu'er, what are you doing?
I... nothing.
I heard everything you said.
Young Third Madam, it's not that I don't want to tell you. I just don't have the courage.
What do you know? Tell me everything!
It's... It's Third Master.
What did Third Master do?
Tell me!
It was Third Master who asked Doctor Sun to infuse aborticide to you.
I heard it.
I really didn't have the courage to say it. So I can only burn some paper money for the poor child.
Young Third Madam!
Young Third Madam...
The child is gone.
There's nothing you can do to change Third Master's mind.
I think you should just... turn a blind eye to it.
Don't worry, I won't hurt you.
Nor will I hurt the child. I accept the child.
Lady, I heard from Xiao Rongzi
that the war is about to erupt at the borders.
Third Master has been staying at the East Main Camp all these days.
Lady, but Third Master said
that he will come and visit you whenever he gets a chance.
Lady, you have to take good care of your body
for the sake of Third Master caring about you so much.
Jin Xiang.
No matter where I end up being,
you have to be happy.
Lady, why are you saying this all of a sudden?
No matter where you go, I'll follow you there.
I know.
It's fine. You can go back to your work.
Let me stay on my own for a while.
Okay. Have a good rest.
In the future, there will be no boundary between us.
And no marriage agreement. We'll take care of each other
and stay together for the rest of our life.
[Seventh Aunt,]
[I'm sorry for leaving the Xiao Residence without a farewell.]
Take a look at these two copies of the budget for equipment and supplies.
Okay.
Reporting!
Come in.
Deputy Commander, Young Third Madam is missing!
- Third Brother.
- What did you say?
Don't panic yet. What happened exactly?
We can't find her anywhere in the residence. Her personal maid Jin Xiang doesn't know where she went, either.
Seventh Madam already sent people to look for her.
We found out that a driver from Xinxing Car Dealer picked up a lady outside the back door of the Xiao Residence.
It's very likely to be Young Third Madam.
It is said that she got off the car at Jiangcang Hostel on Lindong Road, near the pier.
Miss Fengqi, we've arranged everything according to your request.
- Well done. Off you go.
- Yes.
Lin Hangjing.
Let's become friends again in our next life.
[Jiangcang Hostel]
Hurry up, on that side!
That side! Hurry up!
Pay attention to the direction of the wind!
- Quickly!
- Follow along!
Reporting to Commander. The fire already started when we arrived.
We're trying our best to fight the fire. But we didn't find Young Madam.
There's not enough water! Get some more!
Hangjing. Hangjing.
- Third Brother.
- Hangjing!
- Third Brother, you can't go! Third Brother!
- Third Brother! It's too dangerous!
- Hangjing!
- Third Brother!
Don't be impetuous!
- Hangjing!
- Third Brother!
It's too dangerous, Third Brother!
Hangjing.
No. Hangjing!
Wake up, Third Master. Don't scare me. Wake up!
Wake up, Third Brother! Don't scare me!
Open your eyes and look at me, okay?
Last night, at midnight, Wei Zhenliang's forces launched a general attack.
They've already broken the first line of defense in Jinyang.
We're holding on to the second line of defense.
Weiyi, do we need to let the Deputy Commander know of this situation?
Uncles, you know what's going on with Third Brother recently.
Let's not bother him if it's something we can resolve by ourselves.
His baby and his wife are both gone.
How can anyone possibly get through it?
So let's give Third Brother more time to rest.
Okay. We'll do as you said, Weiyi.
Now Regiment Commander Sun and Xu
have sent two infantry troops to counterattack them.
You two can just stay with Third Master
to get through this difficult time.
Then we'll have to bother you, Uncles,
- to handle the military matters.
- Okay.
Third Master, you're finally awake.
You've been in a coma for quite a few days. We're all worried about you.
Seventh Aunt, where's Hangjing?
Third Brother, why are you doing this?
Yes, you are completely smitten with Lin Hangjing.
But she's never been devoted to you.
You can even accept her child, even though you don't know who the father is.
But what about her? Has she ever been nice to you?
Shuyi!
Shuyi, don't say it.
I have to say it!
This ungrateful woman doesn't deserve your sad feelings for her!
- She's disloyal and unpure. She doesn't deserve you!
- Shut up!
Fourth Lady, how can you make such a baseless accusation?
My Lady has never been disloyal to Third Master. Her baby
- is Third Master's!
- You're still arguing over it!
- She got that baby because of her affair with...
- No!
The night before Lady left,
she was with Third Master.
How can you say that the baby is not Third Master's?
What did you say?
After Old Master passed away,
My Lady had been mourning for her father by fulfilling filial duties.
It's true that she stayed in Tingxiang Garden.
But that night, you got drunk.
And My Lady was worried.
So she came here.
The next morning, I asked Nanny Liu to prepare breakfast for the two of you.
Yes, Third Master. Everything Jin Xiang said was true.
She did ask me to do that.
- Third Brother, do you know that this baby...
- There's no need to say anything.
Third Master, if you still don't believe in me,
I have more proof here.
This is a list of names that my lady came up with for the unborn little master.
These were handwritten by My Lady.
[Names surnamed Xiao]
The last name of the baby is Xiao!
[Xiao Xingchen, Xiao Yuze, Xiao Haotian, Xiao Hongxuan]
I can assure you with my life
that My Lady is innocent!
♫  The windowsill sees the marks left by the pouring rain  ♫
♫  The hushing wind blows  ♫
♫  The solitude persists  ♫
♫  The dream drawn with ink is too far to reach  ♫
♫  There's no more need for words of promise  ♫
♫  For I have the memory to hold on to  ♫
♫  Smiles are like a song  ♫
♫  To which both you and I are drawn  ♫
♫  I in solitude choose to fall  ♫
♫  Love at dawn resurrects at the rise of the sun  ♫
Seventh Aunt, Hangjing has been residing in the Xiao family since I was a child.
Uncle Xiao is like a kind father to me, and Seventh Aunt treated me as your own daughter.
Hangjing will always be grateful to you for raising me.
However, Hangjing suffered the pain of losing my beloved father.
There is no longer any hope in my life, and I have shed all of my tears.
Please forgive me for leaving without saying goodbye.
As for Third Brother,
I wish we had never met each other.
I hope we can be forever be separated from now on,
and never see each other again.
♫  How am I supposed to blossom when I'm wounded and hurt  ♫
♫  The transient memory wipes out my hopes  ♫
♫  And buries my heart in the abyss  ♫
♫ Who is looking forward to the spring breeze? ♫
♫ Who is staring at the moving flowers? ♫
♫ Who is watching the galaxy in the summer night ♫
♫ Who remembers a shooting star going by in a moment? ♫
♫ Who is afraid of heartbreak, denies the heartbeat? ♫
♫ Allow loneliness to smear the other’s protective coloration ♫
♫ Who would be willing to pass the other like this ♫
♫ I also want to be a shooting star to make you warm ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ At least the flight will be smooth ♫
♫ Waiting for a promise my whole life ♫
♫ I cherish even the short-lived happiness ♫
♫ Leave some tenderness to the years ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫