♫ The preface of the love words is stained with lovesickness ♫
♫ Who is copying your handwriting? ♫
♫ Falling flowers and drifting through
generations of wind and rain ♫
♫ Cannot abandon for the sake of fate  ♫
♫ Going through sorrows and joys in the intoxicated dream ♫
♫ Who is testing my affection? ♫
♫ Several black and white chess pieces ♫
♫ Hard to differentiate triumph and loss,
love and hate, hometown ♫
♫ Going on these years ♫
♫ Should be good times ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, looking for love ♫
♫ There is too much confusion ♫
♫ Holding green wind, picking chrysanthemums
under the eastern fence ♫
♫ Another difficult season ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, I reminisce in love ♫
♫ Prosperity hides too much wind and rain ♫
♫ Falling flowers singing a song ♫
♫ The person in the vague dream parted from me ♫
[Love in Flames of War]
[Episode 21]
Mo Weiyi is just a jerk and a coward!
Did you forget?
We played together since we were four or five.
We were boisterous together. We've never separated.
After that, we went to school, the military academy, and the battlefield together.
We bled and sweated together.
From the bottom of my heart, I identified you as my older brother.
Trust me.
Trust me that everything will get better, all right, Weiyi?
You, let go.
I'm not letting go. I'm not letting go!
I'll say it again, you let go.
I'm not letting go!
You let go!
From the moment I leave here,
we...
we will have become strangers to each other.
[Frontier Army Command of Zhibei Region]
Mo Weiyi!
[Beixin City]
Old Mo.
Do you still remember back then,
how we, brothers, conquered this city?
Five days and four nights of a fierce battle.
- Watch out!
- How many brothers died?
At that time, I told you and Old Zhang to leave first.
- Charge!
But you said you'd also die if you went back home.
Might as well invade the city to feast.
Want to die, might as well be a full ghost.
In the end, we relied on this pride
and held on until
the enemy opened the city gate themselves.
We are victorious! We won!
- We won!
We were at this place.
It was this place
that we made a vow.
From that day forward, there would be no distinction between us.
We would be together forever, wholeheartedly.
Back then, we...
drank big bowls of wine and ate big pieces of meat.
We chatted about everything under the sun. How joyful.
Who would've thought we, two brothers...
would get to this point today?
Father, your skills are getting better.
I still remember when you cut my hair when I was young,
you cut my hair like a watermelon.
I tell you, I heard from the elders in the house
that when a father cuts his son's hair, it can get rid of bad luck.
It can make the son grow up healthily.
Madam, peeling this gingkos is mentally taxing and tiring.
You have been peeling them the whole morning. Rest a while.
It's okay.
Madam, I'll do it instead.
No need, no need. I'll do it myself.
Commander's lung was shot.
Even though the bullet was taken out immediately,
his lung is seriously infected and he is coughing persistently.
This ginkgo can nourish the lung and relieve the cough.
But you don't need to peel them yourself.
Whoever peels it, isn't it the same?
How can it be the same?
It's more sincere if it's peeled personally.
I only hope that Commander can get better soon.
- Be careful.
- I'm fine.
Father, why did you look for me?
This time I was shot in the lung, and I have not regained my agility.
Whenever it's nighttime, I'll cough persistently.
This doctor recommends that I go to America to do a complete recovery treatment.
Such a serious injury, is the doctor over there trustworthy?
He already found the doctor-in-charge for me. Don't worry.
Then, how long will you be there?
It'll be around half a year.
How about I go with you?
You see, the security over there is not as good as in our country.
Besides, me going with you can also...
Your eldest sister has already arranged properly in America for me.
Oh, yes! Fifth and Sixth are clamoring to go over there and see their eldest sister.
I'll bring them along and also let them gain some experience.
Father, what about this matter...
You must stay in
Beixin. East Main Camp and the house cannot do without you.
I thought about it myself.
Now I appoint you as
the Deputy Commander of the Ying Army.
After I leave, you will manage all military affairs on behalf of me.
Father, aren't you just making a trip to America?
I can manage the military affairs during the period that you are not around. This is not a problem.
But this position, you gave it to me too early.
The Suiling battle,
and the Old Mo and Old Zheng's matter,
I can tell that you can take charge.
I will also transfer the military power to you gradually.
You are the backbone of the Ying Army.
If you are not around, how can I stabilize the troops' morale?
There will be a day when your father is old.
Third Master, you have to learn.
Take on the responsibility of the Xiao family.
Yes.
Since you've already decided, I'll continue to command and arrange.
I, the family, and the whole Ying Army will wait for you to come back safely.
Good.
Drink it while it's hot.
Have you told Beichen about your trip to the United States?
Focus on your recovery. Beichen won't disappoint you.
All these years, East Main Camp has gone through many ups and downs.
Beichen can now handle them himself. I'm confident in him for this.
Why don't you ever say those words in front of your son?
I've told him things I'm supposed to say.
You've worked hard for taking care of this family.
Are you sure you don't want me to go with you to the United States?
Haven't we pinky promised on this?
You're managing the family home and Beichen manages the military camp, so I can go on this trip without any worries.
- Commander, I...
- Don't worry.
I'll recuperate well, and come back in excellent shape.
When I'm back, I'll hand over everything to Beichen.
Then I will have idle time...
to stay with you.
From then on, we can be a normal married couple.
Then wait for Beichen and Hangjing to give us a big fat grandson.
Also, Shuyi will be married to a good family.
Then, we can watch
Fifth and Sixth grow up.
That's settled then.
- Pinky promise.
- Sealed.
Governor, Xiao Haishan has already left to the United States.
Last time, during the Suiling battle,
he might have been injured but he set a great example and his reputation is roaring in the army.
Xiao Haishan retreats from his success and
stays away from the conflicts.
I see that is perhaps the best outcome.
But Xiao Beichen might be carrying a Deputy Chief Commander title right now,
but he has already taken over the entire Ying Army.
He is not easy to manage, I don't see him being on our side.
This Beichen...
became successful at a young age and has a card up his sleeve.
He won't follow the lead or easily be at someone else's order.
When I use people, it's all about loyalty.
As long as he is loyal, he will definitely become a good general below me.
What if he becomes disloyal??
Then I'll take out all his fangs and claws,
and strangle his throat.
No matter how much ability he has,
he is just a sick tiger in a cage.
Do you have a plan?
It's just a joke.
Hello?
Zizheng?
Where are you?
Brother Yong, how's my mother and Hangjing?
I arranged for your mom to be at a house in the rural area.
Her health is doing well,
she just misses you a lot.
I truly appreciate you taking care of my mother.
What about Hangjing?
And her father? They are all fine, right?
Hangjing...
What happened to her?
She and her friend
opened a girls school. She teaches in person.
Her father is safe for now.
Good.
Right, Brother Yong.
I haven't let down the organization.
I got back the map that the organization wanted.
[Map]
Okay. I'll give this to the superiors immediately when I get back.
Okay. Also, Brother Yong.
This time, I also found the Japanese
military map.
It's also in there, in the last few pages.
[Command Office]
Zizheng, what exactly happened in this time?
How can you get all this highly confidential information?
During that time, how come you're now associated with Jin Cheng?
Advisor Du.
Have you found something?
The villagers reported that this car has been abandoned here for days.
[Bank Advertisement]
[Shao Lizi refuses Zhong He Party.]
[Gambling chip]
Can you find out which casino uses this chip?
Yes, but the borders of the Suiling area
can be complicated. It might take some time.
As long as you can find out.
Got it.
According to you, it was you who saved Jin Cheng and his daughter?
I'm sorry, Brother Yong.
I know I shouldn't intervene in Jin Cheng's matters.
But his daughter saved my life.
And everything happened suddenly.
I only saved them accidentally.
I understand this.
You saved him, staying next to him is the best way to protect yourself.
Jin Cheng is very suspicious. If I leave suddenly,
I'm afraid it might be dangerous.
In all, just wait until I'm fully recuperated.
Once I'm recovered, I will find a way to escape.
There is no rush. I'm thinking...
perhaps this is an excellent opportunity.
What do you mean?
The South has already shown their desire
to end the dispute between North and South.
The Soviet Union sent a military expert named Yakov to the South.
He was carrying 2,000,000 rubles with him to obtain the allocation rights.
Beiyang Government announced internally that they want to arrest this person.
Last month, on the way to Dongping,
he suddenly went missing?
- Missing?
- Yes.
The South thinks that was done secretly by Jin Cheng's people.
Because this is a matter of great importance, the South is very concerned.
In order to quickly rescue Yakov,
they have been asking for assistance from different patriotic organizations.
They still haven't had any clue up till this point.
Now, you're by Jin Cheng.
You have the opportunity to find out.
I understand what you mean.
I...
will try my best.
Okay. Zizheng, you have to be extra careful.
The car was rented from Da Hongfa car company.
In the passenger seat, there are chips from the casino.
At the driver's seat, there were two footprints. The left print is lighter than the right.
It proves that this person's left leg is a bit weak.
For someone who didn't forget to bring gambling chips while carrying out an assassination attempt,
this means this person must be professional and very meticulous.
I think this is not a regular assassin.
I've already sent people to the casinos near by Da Hongfa car company for further investigation.
Instructor Du, Mo Xibai might be a traitor,
but Weiyi is my brother.
He loved his father wholeheartedly. So this person,
we must find him.
Don't worry! I'll definitely find out the truth for Weiyi.
Third Brother.
I'm heading out first.
Third Brother, Governor Cheng seems to have a situation.
Father, I've prepared some fish soup.
Have some while it's hot.
Okay, Rouke.
My daughter's hands are so agile.
I'm glad you like it.
Governor. Sister Rouke.
Zizheng, what has brought you here?
Last time, you said you would grant me a wish.
I have decided what I want now.
Okay.
Since you've decided, let's hear about it.
I'm a man. I want to pursue my career.
I used to be a journalist. If it weren't for the field work,
I wouldn't have been sent to a labor camp.
I nearly got myself killed there.
That's when I realized a pen would never be as powerful as a gun.
Say, Zizheng, let's get to the point.
Tell me what you want.
Okay.
I want to stay here to serve you and Sister Rouke.
You're on the right track.
Father, I have an idea too.
What is it?
How about you take Zizheng as your foster-son?
Foster-son?
I'm afraid I really don't deserve such an honor.
I'm happy just staying at your side.
On one hand, we can pay our gratitude for what Zizheng did for us.
On the other hand, it makes it reasonable for him to stay with our family.
Having a close friend at our side, isn't this "two birds with one stone"?
All you think about is him.
From now on, Zizheng is no longer an outsider.
He is one of us now.
You have a point, only...
Father, what else is there to hesitate about?
All right.
Zizheng, you saved my life.
I promised you I would fulfill a wish of yours.
And Rouke has said a lot for you.
Then, from today on,
I will give you this title.
Thank you, Father.
Zizheng, what are you doing? You should call him Foster Father.
Foster Father.
Thank you for taking me in. And thank you, Sister Rouke.
I, Mu Zizheng, from now on belong to the Jin family. I will serve the family with loyalty.
Good.
Beichen, there was an incident in the prison.
We need you here.
Young Master! Open the door, Young Master.
You haven't had anything for days. You should at least eat something.
Young Master! Let me in, Young Master.
Young Master, open the door?
Mo Weiyi.
He still won't come out?
Yes. He has locked himself in there.
Fox Mo. Hey, come out.
I brought you some good stuff.
Great wine of thirty years old. Want to come out and try it together?
Young Master Xu, this is...?
I'm telling you, he refuses to come out. Right?
He refuses to talk to anyone, right?
So I've come to sleep outside here.
I will wait until he comes out.
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
I will live here.
But your arm has been seriously injured.
It's not a good place for recovery. What if it becomes crippled?
There is nothing I can do.
My brother is like my arm.
I've lost my brother. There's no point in me keeping this arm.
Fox Mo, I'm telling you. I feel a little sleepy now.
I'm going to have a nap.
Be careful if you decide to open the door.
Don't knock the door into me.
[Xin Yue Tea House]
Brother Zizheng, Brother Yong is here.
Brother Yong, would it be possible that we're on the wrong track?
I have been secretly watching Jin Cheng for days. I've also tried getting knowledge from Jin Rouke.
I've also been to the archive room and Jin Cheng's study.
I have even been to the prison in Dong Ping.
But I've found nothing about Yakov.
But in Dong Ping, without Jin Cheng's order,
no one would dare to imprison a high-class Russian expert.
And to Jin Cheng, he must be more cautious than cautious regarding this matter.
It won't be easy to find the loopholes.
If that's the case,
then Jin Cheng must have a decision regarding Yakov.
I will be able to find some clues by then.
I hope this will be a lead.
Jin Cheng will soon set off to Beixin. I will go with him. I will continue my investigation there.
You are going to Beixin?
Yes. Is there an issue?
I meant to say we can meet up in Beixin now.
Yes. I can finally meet Hangjing and my mother.
[To Hangjing]
Brother Yong, I have a bad feeling about this.
Are we really not going to tell Brother Zizheng about Miss Lin?
He will definitely find out once he is in Beixin.
I really don't know how to tell him.
Let's leave it for now.
I'll explain to him when he is in Beixin.
Brother Zizheng.
Zizheng, what are you doing here?
Brother Yong, what were you talking about?
Nothing.
What happened to Hangjing?
Brother Zizheng, actually...
Brother Yong, just tell me what exactly happened to Hangjing.
I feel like your words have another meaning.
Zizheng,
Hangjing...
is married.
What are you saying? Don't joke with me.
It's true.
To whom?
Xiao Beichen.
Xiao Beichen?
That's impossible. Hangjing hates Xiao Beichen the most!
She wouldn't marry him. That's impossible!
Zizheng, calm down.
They got married suddenly after you left.
The Xiao Family had a grand wedding. Jin Cheng and Kang Jingxiong attended it, too.
That's impossible.
That doesn't make sense. Brother Yong,
did you give my letter to Hangjing?
I'm sorry. I didn't give it to her.
Why?
Zizheng, actually, at the time,
Xiao Beichen came to see me.
What do you mean?
We've never crossed paths, Third Master.
What's brought you here?
To be honest, I'm here today,
for a person.
I don't know who Third Master is talking about.
Mu Zizheng.
I don't know how Zizheng has offended you, Third Master.
Or... are you doing this for Miss Lin?
You're a smart man.
I'm warning you to only ask things you can ask
and do not mention the things you shouldn't know.
Don't worry. It's not Mu Zizheng's life I'm after.
I just want him to disappear from Beixin.
Kang Jingxiong was attacked. He won't leave the matter.
Even if you didn't bring up the matter,
we would try our best to get Zizheng out of here for the time being.
It's just there are some unsolved matters.
We need some time.
I want him to leave tonight.
According to what you said,
it was Xiao Beichen who wanted me gone and it was part of his plan?
Sorry, Zizheng.
What's the point of apologizing now?
You're my most trusted Eldest Brother!
How can you join forces with him and lie to me?
I was worried about your safety back then.
I didn't want you to fall into this love triangle.
Xiao Beichen is not something you can offend.
I wanted to move you somewhere else temporarily back then.
Once your mission had been finished, I would move you to another location.
I didn't know you would go all the way and investigate the Japanese military plan.
And you also lost contact with the organization.
Sorry, Zizheng.
If you want to blame someone, you can blame me.
Today, I'm standing here to receive your punishment.
Don't be like this, Brother Zizheng! All he did was for your sake.
Zizheng, what happened?
Zizheng, what actually happened?
You never drink this much.
Sister Rouke, do you know?
The girl I love...
is already married.
Who did she get married to?
She married the man whom you cannot offend in Beixin.
Xiao Beichen?
Yes.
How could that be?
Zizheng, if the lady you love is single,
no matter what happened, I would always support you.
- But now that Xiao Beichen...
- What about Xiao Beichen?
So I can't be with her? So I don't deserve her? So I have no right to fight for her?
That's not what I meant. What I said is for your own good.
I don't want you to get hurt again.
I'm sorry, Sister Rouke.
But don't worry about me. I believe Hangjing cares about me.
She married Xiao Beichen because she had no other choice.
Now I'm back alive,
I will never allow him to separate us again.
Drink the soup while it's still hot.
Don't drink anymore.
Thank you, Sister Rouke.
- Miss.
- Young Master Xu.
Give him my duck leg as well.
Okay.
I gave mine to you.
Mo Weiyi!
You don't have to eat it. Why are you taking out your anger with the duck leg?
I didn't even bear to eat it myself.
I know you'll be bored eating alone.
I'll eat with you.
Can you calm down and listen to me speak?
Living here these days,
I recalled so many...
so many things that happened when we were kids.
The most memorable things in the past for me...
are moments that the three of us brothers spent together.
It was like we never parted before.
Wherever you were, Third Brother and I were always there.
Wherever Third Brother was, you and I were always there.
Do you still remember our oath?
In the name of Heaven,
I, Xiao Beichen,
I, Mo Weiyi,
and I, Xu Zijun!
We swear today to be brothers by different surnames.
May the Gods of Heaven and Earth attest...
to what is in our hearts.
If we should ever do anything to betray our friendship, may Heaven and the people of the earth both strike us dead.
From today on, we'll entrust each other with our life and death.
Save each other regardless of fortune or misfortune.
Rely on each other regardless of weal or woe. And support each other amidst trials and tribulations.
Do you really think Third Brother didn't know you would save your father?
Without his permission, do you think it would be so easy for you to save him?
But my father... is still gone.
Are you still suspecting Third Brother for killing your father?
I can assure you with my life, Third Brother would never do it!
Mo Weiyi, don't you know this more than I do?
Anything else, I can convince myself.
I can give in and I can be open-minded.
But he's my father!
You should leave. Don't bother me here.
I won't leave until you come around.
You're a man. How absurd is it for you to stay here at my door?
It doesn't matter! I just want you to come back!
The three of us should be together!
Xu Zijun, I'm making it clear to you one more time.
You can stay here for as long as you like. But Xiao Beichen and I,
our brotherhood has come to an end!
Did I drool?
I know you guys are always laughing at me for being foolish.
I know I'm indeed not smart,
that's why I use the dumbest method and wait for you.
I'll wait until the day of your return.
Do whatever you want.
♫ Who is looking forward to the spring breeze? ♫
♫ Who is staring at the moving flowers? ♫
♫ Who is watching the galaxy in the summer night ♫
♫ Who remembers a shooting star going by in a moment? ♫
♫ Who is afraid of heartbreak, denies the heartbeat? ♫
♫ Allow loneliness to smear the other’s protective coloration ♫
♫ Who would be willing to pass the other like this ♫
♫ I also want to be a shooting star to make you warm ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ At least the flight will be smooth ♫
♫ Waiting for a promise my whole life ♫
♫ I cherish even the short-lived happiness ♫
♫ Leave some tenderness to the years ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫