♫ The preface of the love words is stained with love sickness ♫
♫ Who is copying your handwriting? ♫
♫ Falling flowers and drifting through
generations of wind and rain  ♫
♫ Cannot abandon for the sake of fate ♫
♫ Going through sorrows and joys in the intoxicated dream ♫
♫ Who is testing my affection? ♫
♫ Several black and white chess pieces  ♫
♫ Hard to differentiate triumph and loss,
love and hate, hometown ♫
♫ Going on these years ♫
♫ Should be good times ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, looking for in love ♫
♫ There are too many confusions ♫
♫ Holding green wind, picking chrysanthemums
under the eastern fence ♫
♫ Another difficult season ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, I reminisce in love ♫
♫ Prosperity hides too much wind and rain ♫
♫ Falling flowers singing a song ♫
♫ The person in the vague dream parted from me ♫
[Love in Flames of War]
[Episode 3]
Governor, please.
You still love making tea, Jingxiong.
It's just a hobby to kill time.
Tea tasting needs a peaceful state of mind.
I really hope one day I can completely drop the gun in my hand,
find a place far away, high in the mountains or near the sea,
practice meditation and Buddhism, and get away from the mundane world.
That state of mind is indeed precious.
But Jingxiong, I have one mundane affair to bother you with.
- What is it?
- If...
If Haishan betrayed me,
what should I do?
I'm not the right person to ask this question.
Why?
From an objective perspective, I trust that Xiao Haishan
is faithful and righteous. He won't work in the interest of our opposers at the expense of ourselves.
But from my personal perspective,
you clearly know that I will never forgive him
because of Lin'er's death.
So it's hard for me to judge him objectively.
You're honest.
I am a sheet of white paper in front of you, Governor.
There's nothing to hide.
Jingxiong, I respect you for being honest.
Frankly speaking, both you and Haishan are my right-hand men.
Naturally, I really hope Haishan will not betray me.
But what if he does?
I can't just do nothing about it.
You... have a plan already.
Jingxiong, if Haishan does betray me,
I'm going to hand him over to you to deal with.
Governor, if you trust Xiao Haishan,
then Xiao Haishan is my brother.
If Governor wants to get rid of him,
then he... is my enemy who killed my son.
Let's have some tea.
How's it going these days?
If you apologize and admit your mistakes,
I'll just forgive you for everything you did.
You're a despicable and obnoxious person. Why should I apologize?
Besides, without you,
I'm perfectly happy.
Maose. Hanyang.
Chase!
Maose! Hanyang!
That way! That way!
Lin Hangjing. Stand up!
[Cheat Sheet]
This is how you got your good grades?
Teacher, someone passed this note to me.
You're sitting next to Lin Hangjing. Did you see anyone throwing the note to her?
No, I didn't see it.
- Did you see it?
- I didn't see it.
Did anyone see it?
No.
Teacher, none of us has seen it.
I'm afraid only Lin Hangjing
- knows what's really happening.
- You all...
Lin Hangjing, what exactly is happening? Tell me the truth!
Teacher, there's no need for her to explain. It's so obvious.
It's in our school rules how we should punish people for cheating.
- Teacher, I...
- You don't have to sit the test.
Get out now! Sweep the corridor.
- Teacher, I—
- Go!
Get out!
Get out, get out!
All right. Go back to your test.
[Shengyi Girls School]
Look at her!
What's happening?
Young Master, I've investigated the matter with the newspaper.
It was Xiao Zhuo who told Concierge Liu.
As for Concierge Liu, there is a maid who is close to Mrs. Zheng. She told Mrs. Zheng.
Madam Zheng exaggerated the details and told Commander Zheng about it.
That brown-noser did some research and found that the newspaper did publish an article criticizing the warlord.
So he ordered the suspension of the newspaper's publication.
That's why. No wonder Lin Hangjing got so mad.
You did a very careful investigation on this.
I don't dare to not investigate properly the matters Young Master gives me.
Yeah. Then tell me.
Who told Xiao Zhuo about this?
You assume I don't know?
Article 7 of your Secret Book.
"Talk to girls more often." You have such a big mouth.
It's all my fault, Master.
The newspaper...
Fine. It's already suspended.
We'll just take off the paper seal a week later.
Take off the seal?
What? Do you have a complaint? Do you?
Do you have a complaint?
No. No.
Why is it so quiet today? Isn't Seventh Aunt playing cards?
Actually, the cards were already set on the table.
But Miss Lin happens to have a severe fever at that moment.
So severe that she seems to have lost consciousness.
So Seventh Madam called for a doctor, and they're busy taking care of her inside.
Let's go and see.
Third Master, it's great you're back.
Go to my room and get the pills for fever and detox.
It's right beside my wardrobe.
You always hide things in secret places. How can I find it?
Listen to your excuse!
Then watch over your younger sister. I'll go get it.
Okay.
I think you won't make it long.
I'm not going to ask you to apologize in public.
Here's what you can do.
Now there's nobody in the room,
you just say "sorry" to me quietly.
I'll just pretend that it never happened. Nobody will bully you again in the future.
How's that?
Put your hands in the quilt, or you'll catch a cold.
What the...
Okay, Deputy Officer Zhou. Thank you. I'll report to the commander.
What did they say?
Governor Jin will come to the mansion the day after tomorrow for a banquet.
We will leave early tomorrow morning.
The death of Shen Changhe hasn't been investigated until now.
Asking you to attend the banquet...
it doesn't seem right.
You should find a reason to decline.
Or we can bring more people.
Just having you along is enough.
How is that okay? If the situation turns against you, how will you get out?
Don't let anyone else in the mansion know about this.
Yes.
She's here.
Such a beautiful girl. How can you be here alone?
Please move. I don't know you two.
You have no relatives in this town.
Third Master Xiao used to take care of you.
You had nothing to worry about.
But now, you have broken up with him. Right?
- Let me go!
- We just want to have some fun.
- So what if you're unwilling?
Big Brother won't treat you badly.
Stop!
If you're selling kites, sell them somewhere else.
Don't irritate me here.
- What are you doing?
- I don't know if the two of you know about the regulations issued by Commander Xiao.
For harassing a woman in the streets, you will be whipped 12 times.
If the perpetrator is military, then the punishment will be doubled.
That's 24 times.
I don't think either of you, Young Masters, could bear that much.
Seriously, how would you know we're military?
Aren't you both wearing military boots?
If you two don't leave, I'll call the police.
I'm a witness to the harassment.
Okay. You're awesome.
You'll regret it.
I'll invite you to dance sometime.
Thank you so much.
How much are these kites? I'll pay you.
Miss, don't dirty your hands. I'll clean them up.
This road isn't safe. How about I find a car to take you home?
Rickshaw!
Can you please bring this young lady home?
Okay.
Are you a student of Shengyi Girls School?
This road isn't safe. It's best to ask your parents to accompany you.
Thank you.
It's nothing. Get on.
Seventh Madam, the school said Miss Lin did leave the school when classes were finished.
She didn't walk with anyone.
How come she's still not back? What about the people who went to find her?
They all went, but there's no news yet.
- You're finally back!
- You're back!
Hangjing, you're finally back. You scared me to death!
What happened? Where did you go?
I met two hooligans.
What?
Who's so brave? They even bully someone from the Xiao family?
Miss, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Didn't I tell you two to stop?
Yet you both went to scare her?
Hey, do you guys have any—
- Are you done...
- Hey!
Avoiding it? Kneel!
Look at you. All independent now, huh?
Bullying people, even your little sister!
How did I have such a bastard?
You bastard!
Deputy Official Guo, what's going on?
- The commander...
- I'll whip you to death!
Do you listen to my words?
- Commander, are you going to kill Beichen?
- Bastard!
How can I face Eldest Madam if you do this?
She's been so nice to me. You should kill me, too!
Finish everything.
Today,
I'll let you go because of your mother.
You still have enough audacity to mention my mother?
Bastard!
Let me tell you something, Xiao Beichen!
I'm going to send you to Xinting Military Academy.
I'll find the best instructor to teach you some manners!
Just because you say I have to go, then I have to go?
What? You want me to turn out like you?
Fighting and killing people out there all day. Fraternizing people,
and turning around to be their enemy instead.
You want me to go? I'm not going!
Bastard!
Let me tell you! You have no choice.
Get out there and grow up!
Once you've matured, then you can come home.
Get out!
Third Master...
Tell me.
What should I do with him?
Beichen has the temperament of a child.
He and Hangjing get along so well. How could he bully her?
All these years, I haven't disciplined him enough.
And you, look how you've spoiled him.
Isn't it because I care about him? He hasn't had a mother since he was young.
Don't you understand his suffering?
Talking about First Madam, he must have been so sad.
Beichen is a sentimental child.
I feel guilty about his mother.
But as a father, I'm responsible for him not being well-educated.
There's no discussion needed about the military academy. He must go.
Okay, I understand.
I'll try to plead with him.
Tomorrow morning, I have to go to the governor's mansion.
What are you doing there?
Did something happen?
No, no.
If you must know,
this...
The president and the premier are falling out.
Things are becoming more and more out of control.
The premier went to Jingmen.
I think he won't just let it go.
Before we know who wins and who loses, everyone feels imperiled.
I think the reason the governor asked me to go over this time
was to discuss this matter.
Really? You're not lying to me, are you?
What can I hide from you?
I'm afraid the military will be in chaos.
Our little bit of land here is a bit peaceful.
But if Governor Jin gets involved with the higher authorities,
and starts fighting with other fractions...
Don't worry about how they'll fight.
I promise to protect Beixin City.
Regardless, be careful.
I'm not worried about me.
It's just that it'll be hard for you, during this time.
This big household...
You're still so formal with me.
Don't worry about the household.
Miss.
Miss, it's a great day today.
The devil is going to military school.
I got some red papers from Sister Yunyi. Let's make some paper cutting of swallows for fun.
Okay.
Miss, you've got such a pair of deft hands!
Look!
Come with me. Come.
You can't just hold my miss's hand.
Hangjing, you have to come with me.
You have to tell my father it wasn't me who ordered the two guys to harass you.
And... my father wants me to go to military school.
You talk to him. Ask him to give up the idea.
Even if you didn't order these people to harass me,
even if it was your friends who pretended they had your order,
the whole thing started from you, after all.
I think you should be sent to military school, to learn a lesson.
Why are you making things even worse for me?
Third Master Xiao, if you still think courtesy is important,
please get out of here right now.
Third Master, why are you still not leaving?
If you don't leave, I'll have Seventh Madam come here.
You have to come with me. Otherwise...
Be careful. Don't hurt your hands.
It's just a cup. It's not a big deal.
I'll just compensate you for it.
That cup was handmade by my miss and her parents together.
Her mother passed away at an early age.
It's the only memento that she left for my miss!
How can you compensate for the love between mother and daughter?
Leave!
Leave! Go away!
[Music in Heyday]
[Sound in Harmony]
Her mother passed away at an early age.
It's the only memento that she left for my miss!
How can you compensate for the love between mother and daughter?
Mom.
I miss you.
Commander.
I think something is wrong.
Haishan.
Hey, Brother Kang.
Haishan, I haven't seen you for a few months.
You look smarter now.
I haven't congratulated you on your promotion in person!
Thanks to Governor's kind heart, the care for his subordinates, and promoting us often.
Haishan, you're not just good at wars, but speak nice words, too.
Conversing with you makes me lucky, too.
Thanks for your compliment, Brother Kang.
Everyone.
Governor.
Uncle Xiao. Uncle Kang.
I haven't seen Rouke for a long time; she's grown to be more elegant!
She's been quite busy recently.
Disaster relief, fundraising... she rarely comes back home.
Everyone, we'll have a meeting in half an hour.
I'll speak to Haishan first.
Okay.
We'll leave you to it then.
Rouke, take care of Uncle Kang for me.
Okay. Uncle Kang, this way.
Haishan, let's go to the study.
- After you.
- Please.
Haishan, you and I are brothers. We'll skip words of courtesy.
Shen Chenghe was secretly assassinated in Ziyun Hotel.
Are you aware of this?
Yes. I've sent people to investigate it.
But we didn't find who did it.
But you do not know why Shen Chenghe would show up in Ziyun Hotel.
Right?
That's true.
Then let me tell you now.
I sent Shen Chenghe to go on a secret trip down south.
To get a name list of the revolutionary party members who are spies at the central government.
I see.
Regarding this,
I've been thinking a lot, but there's one thing I don't understand.
Deputy Official Guo.
Deputy Officer Zhou.
Where are the bodyguards of Commander Xiao?
Don't let them wait outside.
We have good food and wine prepared in the side hall. Feel free to enjoy.
Thank you, Deputy Officer Zhou. Commander brought only me this time.
He did not bring a team of bodyguards.
The murderer seems to know Shen Changhe's itinerary very well.
And it was in your territory, Haishan,
that he was killed with no traces left behind.
It seems that the murderer is not just anybody.
Judging from what you said, Governor,
this is very strange indeed.
You can't be suspecting it was me.
Governor, think about it.
No matter how foolish and stupid I may be,
if I wanted to kill Counselor Shen, I wouldn't do it in my jurisdiction.
And with such obvious evidence left behind.
Besides, Counselor Shen and I
have no personal conflicts or anything to do with each other.
Haishan. Of course,
I don't want to believe that
this is related to you.
But please understand.
In a position like mine,
I can't afford to bet
on people's loyalty.
Understood.
So, it seems that I have made the right decision today.
Please review this, Governor.
[Letter of Resignation]
Resignation letter?
Haishan, why are you doing this?
Governor, back in the day, it was you who incorporated the small forces of ours
and gave us the chance to achieve something and have a career.
I can say that without you, Governor, I wouldn't have achieved what I have now.
I'm very grateful for being trained by you. There's nothing I can do to show my gratitude.
Those are just small things from the past.
It's not worth mentioning.
The battles in recent years
have made me feel too exhausted to fight again.
I hope you can say yes to my request, Governor.
The 30,000 soldiers of the Ying Army were originally your forces.
After I resign, these people
will definitely listen to your orders and stay loyal to you.
Haishan, look at you.
My words were a bit too serious just now.
Shen Changhe's death happened all of a sudden.
I wasn't blaming you for it at all.
As you mentioned, apart from you,
there are no worthy people by my side.
Governor, there are a lot of talented people in the army.
Just from those sitting outside: Commander Kong,
Brother Ma, and Brother Jingxiong.
Any of them can replace me. They will follow your lead.
As you mentioned,
Old Kong, Commander Kang, and you.
You have fought all your way with me at the risk of your lives.
You're not old enough to retire and return to your hometown.
None of you can be deserters!
Haishan, this letter...
Please, take back the resignation letter.
- Governor.
- Do I need to beg you?
I wouldn't dare.
- Commander Kang, thank you for your help last time.
- You're welcome.
I'll leave you two to it.
Commander, what's going on?
All the guns have been removed. Has the Governor changed his mind about killing Xiao Haishan?
I'm not surprised. It's all just a staged show.
It's all bluff and bluster.
Not only did he test Xiao Haishan's loyalty,
but also intimidated everyone here.
That's two birds with one stone.
As for us, we're just onlookers watching him play the game.
What are we supposed to do now?
When one round is finished, naturally it's time to get ready for the next round.
[Hound's Head]
[First Society Newspaper]
Sir, would you like to buy some flowers?
- Sir, come and buy some flowers.
- No, thanks
Young Master, we've been here for more than an hour.
What are we doing here?
You talk too much. Just wait.
[First Society Newspaper]
Hangjing, this is your payment for this month.
Thank you, Chief Editor Lu.
And what about the list of names and addresses?
I put them all in the envelope.
That's great.
- See you.
- Get off the car.
- Get off the car?
- Where to?
- Get off now! Anywhere!
[Fei Er Xi Bakery]
- You've come.
- I'm the editor from First Society Newspaper.
We heard that there was an incident at your office.
It may be difficult to find accommodation for the kids now.
It may take some time.
The funds we raised have been unblocked.
I believe it won't take long for us to find the kids' accommodation.
Oh, right.
This money is for you to buy new clothes for the kids.
You can cook them a good meal.
Thank you very much.
I was hired by the press as a caretaker.
It's my job to take care of the kids.
These poor kids.
Many kids are left as orphans as their parents died in the ongoing wars in the North.
They are all war-orphans.
Come. I brought you some maltose candy. It's very sweet.
- Here's one for you.
- Thank you, Miss.
Here's one for you.
It tastes so sweet.
- Here.
- Thank you, Miss.
- Good to see you.
- What are you doing here?
I'm taking a walk.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Where are you going? I can drive you.
No, thanks.
Are you going home? This is very far from home.
Come on, get in the car. I can drive you home.
I said no. I can walk home.
Xiao Rong.
Xiao Rong!
♫ Who is looking forward to the spring breeze? ♫
♫ Who is staring at the moving flowers? ♫
♫ Who is watching the galaxy in the summer night ♫
♫ Who remembers a shooting star going by in a moment? ♫
♫  Who is afraid of heartbreak, denies the heartbeat?  ♫
♫ Allow loneliness to smear the other’s protective coloration ♫
♫  Who would be willing to pass the other like this?  ♫
♫ I also want to be a shooting star to make you warm ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ At least the flight will be smooth ♫
♫ Waiting for a promise my whole life ♫
♫ I cherish even the short-lived happiness ♫
♫ Leave some tenderness to the years ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time
a shooting star passes, ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time
a shooting star passes, ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫
[Music in Heyday]
[Prosperity in Harmony]
- Orphanage?
- Open an orphanage?
Why do you want to open an orphanage, all of a sudden?
I don't see the reason.
Of course, it's to
house the homeless kids.
Nonsense.
Third Brother, what made you suddenly become a saint?
Who did you get the idea from?
You know, since a young age, my heart has always been with the poor.
The reason I'm here today is to talk to you about those kids.
I'm pleading with you to help those kids.
I do want to help, but you know my dad has all my money.
Big Fool Xu, you are up.
You.
- Your family is rich, right?
- I'm poor. He's the rich one.
Yeah, you're rich.
Come on, guys!
What's wrong with you?
All I asked is something in the mortal world.
Is it that hard?
How about this?
Though we seem to live a luxury life,
the truth is we are all jobless.
None of us has money, though we do spend a lot.
You see my pockets. It's as empty as it gets.
- We don't have any pocket money.
- None at all.
He's right.
Third Brother.
To be honest, even if we give all the money we have, it won't be enough to open an orphanage.
What you should do is tell your dad that you want to open an orphanage.
He will build three, even ten for you!
Yeah, that's right.
Without your family, you are nothing.
♫ Who is looking forward to the spring breeze? ♫
♫ Who is staring at the moving flowers? ♫
♫ Who is watching the galaxy in the summer night ♫
♫ Who remembers a shooting star going by in a moment? ♫
♫ Who is afraid of heartbreak, denies the heartbeat? ♫
♫ Allow loneliness to smear the other’s protective coloration ♫
♫ Who would be willing to pass the other like this? ♫
♫ I also want to be a shooting star to make you warm ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ At least the flight will be smooth ♫
♫ Waiting for a promise my whole life ♫
♫ I cherish even the short-lived happiness ♫
♫ Leave some tenderness to the years ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time
a shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time
a shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫