♫ The preface of the love words is stained with lovesickness ♫
♫ Who is copying your handwriting? ♫
♫ Falling flowers and drifting through generations
of wind and rain ♫
♫ Cannot abandon for the sake of fate ♫
♫ Going through sorrows and joys in the intoxicated dream ♫
♫ Who is testing my affection? ♫
♫ Several black and white chess pieces ♫
♫ Hard to differentiate triumph and loss,
love and hate, hometown ♫
♫ Going on these years ♫
♫ Should be good times ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, looking for love ♫
♫ There is too much confusion ♫
♫ Holding green wind, picking chrysanthemums
under the eastern fence ♫
♫ Another difficult season ♫
♫ Thousands of thoughts, I reminisce in love ♫
♫ Prosperity hides too much wind and rain ♫
♫ Falling flowers singing a song ♫
♫ The person in the vague dream parted from me ♫
[Love in the Flame of War]
[Episode 15]
[Harmony in Prosperity]
Cheers!
Third Brother will be the groom tomorrow.
I'm here wishing you everlasting happiness together and
the years ahead to be filled with lasting joy.
Third Brother, don't listen to his nonsense.
I'll wish you something practical, wishing you to have a bundle of joy soon.
That is practical. Let's drink.
Good wine!
In the play, it always says,
"A river of spring water is full of trees and peach blossoms as green mountains."
It's better to be long and lasting love.
I wish for you and Miss Lin to be together day and night and to have a long-lasting life ahead of you.
You've been worrying about me since I was young.
Here's a toast to you.
Cheers.
Third Master, Lan Lan and I want to make you a toast as well.
We came to Beixin City to seek shelter.
If it wasn't for you, who took us in, we wouldn't have such a good family.
You're the boss in our hearts, but you're even more our benefactor.
Third Master marrying the woman he loves is the biggest happy event in our Ming Yu Yue.
So, let's make a toast!
- Here!
- I see you've plotted it
that I have to drink with you one at a time.
I'm so jealous of your luck.
What are you moaning about?
It hurts me.
Where does it hurt?
My heart hurts.
Wasn't it because your sister hurt him.
Speaking of which, Big Fool Xu,
do you think you and my sister are a good match?
Well, Shuyi and I. Don't talk about me and Shuyi.
You and Miss Lin weren't getting along at the beginning either.
But look at you two now. You have no place to doubt about us.
You don't say. Such lucky twists can only happen
to me.
As for you, you can just wait.
Fine. Enough about me. Look at Fox Mo.
At least I have a girl in mind.
Fox Mo hasn't even got a shadow of a girl.
Drink your wine.
Come on! Let's raise our cups.
- Come on.
- Stop talking.
Cheers!
Come on.
Thank you.
Please come in.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Please come in.
Hi.
Deputy Officer Guo.
Here.
- There're quite a lot of guests.
- Right.
Governor. Commander.
- This way, please.
- Okay.
Commander Xiao.
- Commander Xiao.
- Governor!
Congratulations, Commander Xiao.
It's a great honor
to have you and Commander Kang here at my son's wedding.
I was chatting with Commander Kang on the way here.
- Marriage is the thing that can make a man reliable.
- You're right.
Your son and Miss Lin are a perfect match.
Brother Haishan, it's your blessing.
I'm flattered!
Commander Xiao, later, we
should drink a couple more drinks.
When it comes to it, I am
half a matchmaker for Beichen and Miss Lin.
Am I right?
Okay! You all don't leave until drunk!
- Master, it's the auspicious time.
- Governor.
Let's go.
Come on.
Old Zheng, hurry.
- Let's go.
- I'm not going.
Come on.
How come you have come?
♫ Your eyes are blocked by the falling leaves ♫
♫ The windowsill sees the marks left by the pouring rain ♫
♫ The hushing wind blows ♫
♫ The solitude persists ♫
♫ The dream drawn with ink is too far to reach ♫
You really bit me!
I'll bite you if you bite me again.
Careful!
I'm telling you. My patience has a limit.
Come to Ming Yu Yue with me this weekend.
I'm not going.
Lin Hangjing. Have you gone crazy?
Since the first day I met you,
I've looked down on you.
♫  How am I supposed to blossom when I'm wounded and hurt ♫
♫ The transient memory wipes out my hopes ♫
♫ And buries my heart in the abyss ♫
Now, the newlyweds should make their wedding vows.
I, Xiao Beichen, am willing to take Lin Hangjing as my wife.
I, Lin Hangjing,
am willing to have Xiao Beichen as my husband.
From today,
will you be willing to be loyal to each other and support each other
for better or for worse, for the richest or for the poorest,
in extreme sickness and health,
to love and protect until death do you two apart?
I will.
Now, may the groom and bride exchange wedding rings.
There will be a day you will really fall in love with me.
Third Brother, actually, you don't need to act so real.
You forgot? I'm Boss Jiu. I'm good at acting.
It’s late, rest early.
What are you doing?
Taking off my clothes and going to bed.
What now?
What is this?
[Xiao Beichen and Lin Hangjing Marriage Agreement]
Number one, when we’re alone,
it’s prohibited to have any physical touching.
Number two, one cannot intervene with each other’s freedom of making friends and going out.
Are you trying to set rules with me, Xiao Beichen?
Number ten, it’s not allowed to…
[Ten, not allowed to sleep on the same bed.]
I’m fine with the rest, but number ten. We cannot sleep on the same bed?
What do you mean? Cannot sleep on the same bed? How am I going to sleep?
We’re going to live in the name of husband and wife,
but it’s not a real couple.
It’s better to set up some rules ahead of time.
I understand this.
But we cannot sleep on the same bed? How am I going to sleep?
What are you doing?
I’ll sleep on the floor.
Third Brother, what are you going to do?
You set up rules with me?
You wish! Tell me the truth!
It’s not your turn yet.
I’ll sleep on the floor.
You’re back?
What are you doing?
Getting dressed.
Didn’t you put these out?
What are you doing?
This is our first day after the wedding. As the wife,
don't you think you should do something for your husband?
- Don't forget, we're just—
- Shush.
[Happiness]
The walls have ears.
What are you waiting for?
What are you doing?
You did the button wrong.
Please serve the tea.
Uncle Xiao, please have some tea.
Still calling me "uncle"?
Father.
Good.
Seventh Aunt, please have some tea.
Here.
As your father-in-law,
this is a present from me.
Remember, a harmonious family is a foundation for prosperity.
- Yes, Father.
- Thank you, Father.
I will keep it in mind.
Okay. You can get up now.
Beiyi. Beiwang. How do you feel about that?
Jealous of your brother?
Look at them. How sweet they are!
Lin Hangjing, you're a lucky woman, you know.
You caused us so much trouble and you still managed to marry my third brother.
Xiao Shuyi, don't you think you should change your address?
Change what address?
You have to call her sister-in-law.
No. I'm not used to it.
From now on, you have to change your address.
Why do you all help her bully me?
Have I become an outsider in this family?
Where are your manners?
Sister Shuyi, don't be angry.
You'll be a bride soon.
Who is the groom?
It's Brother Zijun, of course.
He is the only silly one.
Xiao Beiyi, what are you saying?
You naughty boys, enough.
- Yunyi, have you got the tea and snacks ready?
- They're ready, My Lady.
Let's go and have some food.
Let's go. Come with me.
Let's go.
There is no one around.
Well, it's not the evening yet.
From now on, you'd better keep your distance when there's no one around.
Yeah.
[Quarry. General Hills. A few households.]
Get up. Everyone, get up!
What happened?
What's going on?
It's the irregular search. If they find any extra items, they will kill you for it.
Search!
Where did you get it from? How dare you steal money!
- Report! The search is done.
- Go back to sleep!
I'm going back to the south. I will ask every one of my father's friends.
If there's really no way, I will beg Governor Cheng myself.
I'll go with you.
Hangjing, how are you now?
Is your father safe?
Hangjing, the men's wine table.
The women's Mahjong table.
Although it's a small table,
it entails every kind of
interaction and connection among people.
Now that you are married to Beichen,
and you have resigned from your job to write articles at home,
you still need to spend some time with the ladies.
They represent all kinds of forces.
This is the social activity you have to participate in as Third Young Madam.
But, Seventh Aunt, I really don't know how to play Mahjong.
How is this difficult? You will know how after a few rounds.
Come on.
Young Madam.
Come and save me.
- I'm the only losing one.
- Come and join us.
This is Hangjing's first time playing.
Teach her well.
I will make you all some tea.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Come. Let's get started.
Seven.
Get one.
Have you heard?
The second young master of Old Wang has a mistress out there.
Really? Does his wife know about it?
Of course, she knows.
He bought her a house out there.
His wife broke into her place
and had her face covered in scratches.
She deserved it. Where has this wild weed come from
and tried to be a peony.
In my opinion, wild weeds like her,
who have their eyes on the title and property, deserve to be hit.
Why bother? In my opinion,
it's better to spend time on a trip to Paris and buying new jewelry,
clothes, or rings.
Madam Song, when did you buy the ring?
My husband
asked a friend and bought it off a Russian nobleman.
It's this big, so it's all right.
If you're wearing a diamond of ten carats,
you won't be able to play Mahjong.
I'll never get a compliment from you. If I can't play Mahjong,
you will have no one to play with.
I don't think so.
We have a new player now.
Third Madam, we should spend more time together.
- Yeah.
- We can always get together when you're free.
How fickle you are!
Third Madam is such a beautiful young woman.
We're very lucky to have her join us.
You're right.
Third Brother.
Come in.
- Third Brother.
- Good to see you.
Anything from Instructor Du?
There's intelligence about Kang Jingxiong.
There's a person who visits Kang's residence every half a month.
He's from a book club in Beixin called Knowledge Bookstore.
The bookstore may be...
the secret communication station between them and Kang Jingxiong.
I was saying.
I was saying no wonder we couldn't detect any peculiars on the phone calls or telegrams.
I have sent people to keep an eye on them.
Our intelligence shows the owner pays particular attention to the book storage room on the second floor.
It's quite suspicious.
Third Brother, you can leave the rest to us.
We'll catch them red-handed.
Don't be reckless.
The owner must be one of them.
We can't alert him.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Sister Hangjing, can I still get it?
I'm very close.
Sister Hangjing, a little further.
A little left.
A little further.
Third Brother, when did you come back?
I'm back in time.
Is it you two being naughty again?
How can you let your sister-in-law do such a dangerous task?
I volunteered.
You can't let her do such dangerous things again. Do you understand?
- I understand.
Let's go.
Third Brother, put me down.
How loving!
Here is the medicine.
Show me your ankle.
See, it's swollen.
It didn't hurt the bone. It's not a big deal.
Why did you climb so high for no reason?
It's just to get a toy.
You should have asked Xiao Rong to such things.
- Um, I think it's better for Jin Xiang to do it.
- Right, let me do it.
She is probably needed in the kitchen.
I can do it.
Rubbing it like this can help it ease the pain.
How is it? Does it still hurt?
It doesn't hurt anymore.
We haven't seen each other in so many years since graduation.
When did you come back?
I came back at the beginning of the year. But I was busy.
Hangjing, when we were at school, you and Third Master Xiao were known enemies.
How come you two are married now?
Who made the first move?
We've only just met and you started to make fun of me.
How have you been?
How do you enjoy life as the wife of an army chief?
I used to work at the newspaper office.
But after I got married, my family felt it was better for me
to resign to avoid unnecessary misunderstandings.
Now I'm only writing articles at home.
But I'm not very productive.
What do you do in your spare time?
My spare time... I have really become an idle person.
I feel I'm wasting my time.
That's great. You can come and help me!
Help you?
During my years in Europe, I had been thinking of opening a school for ordinary girls.
A school for ordinary girls?
That's right. I want to found a school just for girls from poor families.
They either start making a living at a young age
or get married at a young age. They have no chance to get an education.
My transfer student friends and I raised a fund
which can be used to rent a venue.
Since I returned home, my friends helped me get a teaching permit.
It was not easy at all.
But fortunately, we have built the school.
We're recruiting teachers. Would you be interested?
But I have to ask my family first.
And I have never studied abroad. I'm not sure if my teaching philosophy matches yours.
Come on. Stop rejecting. You are an author.
You're great at Chinese literature. I'm sure you will be a good teacher.
Hangjing, just come and help me.
Okay. But I still need to talk to my family first.
I will let you know if they approve.
I will be waiting for the good news from you.
Hangjing, you want to be a teacher at a girls school?
Father, now that I don't work at the newspaper office now, I have a lot of time to spare.
I want to do something.
Of course. You're an advocate for women's independence,
and women getting an education.
It's all great.
But you are a daughter-in-law of our family.
Everything you do will have an influence
on the image of the Xiao's family.
Right? If you make some mistakes...
I've never heard of any women going out right after getting married.
That's too wild.
Hangjing, you just said
the school is a school for girls from poor families.
I think it's very meaningful.
It's a very kind gesture.
But at the moment, what's more important is that
you and Beichen should
allow me and the commander to have a grandson.
Well, Beichen. What do you think?
I think you are right.
But—!
So, Hangjing,
you two have just gotten married.
As for your work,
we will talk about it specifically another time.
I understand.
It's late now. You should rest early.
I'm not tired.
Are you mad at me?
No.
Just because I didn't help you in front of my father?
I said, I'm not.
Are you really so eager to teach at the girls school?
Even if I can't do that,
I want to help out as much as I can.
But it's really late right now.
You can go to bed first.
Third Brother, didn't we agree
that we'll be intimate during the day
and keep our distance at night?
There's nothing wrong for me to worry about my wife's health condition.
Thank you.
Suggestion for you. If you don't want anything to happen,
be obedient and go to bed.
Come in.
Father. Seventh Aunt.
What is it?
I'm glad you're both here.
I have something to discuss with you.
Then it must be a big matter.
You look so serious. Tell us about it.
Actually... I think allowing Hangjing to teach at the girls school
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
Well... tell us more about it.
Hangjing is the daughter-in-law of the Xiao Family.
If she helps children of poor families go to school,
teach them to read and write,
it represents the Xiao Family's attitude.
She can help the Xiao Family win the support of the people.
Commander, I think what Third Master said makes sense.
Girls nowadays are different.
They know the value of reading and writing.
If I were a few years younger, I'd want to go as well.
Father, Hangjing is pleased to do it.
And she can represent the Xiao Family to earn a good reputation.
Isn't that wonderful?
Okay. Okay. If you both agree,
then I will not object to it.
If Hangjing really wants to do it, then just let her.
Okay. Thank you, Father. Thank you, Seventh Aunt.
Don't let it delay you from giving us a grandson.
Okay.
[Seek Knowledge Bookstore]
Newspaper! Newspaper!
Sir, what book would you like to buy?
What's wrong with you?
Why did you put your garbage into our garbage can again?
How is this your garbage can?
This is in front of our shop! Of course, it's ours!
The garbage can is on the street! It's for everyone!
I'll get our boss to talk to you! Wait here!
Get whoever you want! Makes no difference!
Boss, be our judge! That crazy woman next door
is putting her garbage into our garbage can again!
How could she? Let's go.
- What's happening?
- It's a public garbage can! When did it become yours?
Boss, I made this garbage can!
The garbage can is made for throwing away garbage!
It is our own garbage can.
All settled. Go up quickly.
- The garbage can is full! So I didn't let her...
- Fine.
Go get the Black Cat. We'll handle it according to the rules.
Sure, go get them. Who cares?
The Black Cat will take you away.
You're threatening me with the Black Cat?
Sir.
What's wrong with you? It's almost pricking into my leather shoes!
- Clean it up now!
- I'm so sorry, sir.
I was in a hurry. Sorry that I alarmed you.
I'll clean it up now.
Sir, which book are you looking for?
If we don't have it now, you can order it in advance.
Um... what's the name? The Mount of Conte Cristo.
The Mount... oh.
You're looking for the Count of Monte Cristo.
Right. Right. The Count of Monte Cristo.
Great. We do have it. Let me find it for you.
The Count of Monte Cristo...
[The Count of Monte Cristo]
I think it was here. Why is it not here?
It's okay, take your time.
I'll look for it.
Fox Mo, hurry up! If you still don't come downstairs, I'm afraid I can't delay it any longer!
Big Fool Xu, hang in there!
[The Count of Monte Cristo]
I finally found it!
It's encrypted.
Sir, this is the book you were looking for.
The Count of Monte Cristo.
Yes.
It's the Chinese version?
I'm looking for the English version.
English version?
But... oh, we don't have it down here. I'll look for it upstairs.
Boss! Boss!
It's not that urgent.
Sir, please bear with me a few seconds.
Where is Fox Mo?
Found it. It's a bit dusty.
It's okay. The dust delays me from reading.
Thank you.
[Universal Department Store]
I thought that such a prestigious family like the Xiao's would definitely stop you from doing it.
I didn't expect them to be so open-minded.
Yes. At first, Father and Seventh Aunt didn't agree.
But somehow they changed their minds.
No matter what, it's great that they said yes. We can work together now.
There's a cloth shop ahead. They sell beautiful curtains.
Miss Jiaman is here! Miss Jiaman!
Miss Jiaman!
Miss, can I have an autograph?
Thank you.
That person looks familiar.
I feel I've seen her somewhere.
- Miss Jiaman, can I have your autograph?
- Thank you, Miss Jiaman!
Right! She's Miss Jiaman!
Jiaman? Who is she?
She's very famous among transfer students.
She studied in France.
And she was an actress in French movies!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Please sign your autograph here.
- Okay.
Thank you!
- It's done.
- Thank you.
That man is a thief! Catch him!
Stop!
Stop him!
Get up!
How dare you? Come with me!
Miss Jiaman, is this yours?
Yes. Thank you.
Thank you so much, Miss Jiaman.
You're welcome. I should be the one saying thank you.
I didn't expect that you two would be teachers at a girls' school!
It's my honor to meet you.
I hope we'll meet again. See you!
See you.
♫ Who is looking forward to the spring breeze? ♫
♫ Who is staring at the moving flowers? ♫
♫ Who is watching the galaxy in the summer night ♫
♫ Who remembers a shooting star going by in a moment? ♫
♫ Who is afraid of heartbreak, denies the heartbeat? ♫
♫ Allow loneliness to smear the other’s protective coloration ♫
♫ Who would be willing to pass the other like this ♫
♫ I also want to be a shooting star to make you warm ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ At least the flight will be smooth ♫
♫ Waiting for a promise my whole life ♫
♫ I cherish even the short-lived happiness ♫
♫ Leave some tenderness to the years ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ I draw your silhouette in the sky ♫
♫ Let me brighten your galaxy once again ♫
♫ If you still remember, when the next time a
shooting star passes ♫
♫ I used to miss your silhouette in the sky ♫