Mom.
Why do we live only inside here?
Where should I start from?
This started from my grandma's grandma and…
her grandma's grandma.
Long, long ago,
there were women who could see the near future of the person they touched with their hands.
Pigeons…
A flying arrow…
You can't avoid it!
If they knew the future ahead of time, they could avoid bad luck and
they could bring good luck.
We will have a daughter.
Then I will make her a princess.
No one knew where those women had come from.
It's just that the ability was passed on to their daughters.
For hundreds of years, they had served as the female shamans of prophecy next to the kings.
As the fate of the country declined and the world was in chaos,
they left the palace quietly and became a part of the world.
After that, in the war,
a woman of the shaman's blood found someone who could protect her.
Please take me with you.
Whatever you wish, I will make it happen.
The man who took the woman
seized the opportunity to succeed in times of war and turbulence.
He achieved great wealth and prosperity.
He snuck her into his secret space and made her his own lucky talisman.
Like that, the woman and her daughter,
and the daughter's daughter are
still separated from the world and living somewhere.
Episode 1
Chairman Seon.
Prince Jamil of Saliha Group contacted me saying something came up and
indefinitely postponed the investment contract signing ceremony with Geumhwa Biotech.
Without giving us any reason on the day of the signing ceremony?
We're trying to figure out why, but nothing yet.
Even institutional investors are backing out now.
Only if the investment contract with Saliha Group is signed
is the launch of Geumhwa Biotech possible as scheduled.
Everyone, please leave.
The chairman is on his way.
Handing over the bag…
Shaking hands…
That man…
Chairman Seon Il Joong.
Check if Eunsung Capital's Chairman Seon Il Joong is meeting someone from Saliha Group.
Chairman Seon Il Joong cooperated with Jinsung Pharmaceutical Company and
met and bribed an aide to Prince Jamil.
We secured the video and sent it to Prince Jamil.
Prince Jamil has promised to sign an investment contract with us as scheduled.
That's a relief.
Yes, Hyungnim.
Sam Joong, do you only think about how to get in my way?
No way.
We were already working on the business you tried to invest in.
Why are you suddenly trying to jump into the bio business?
Can't I do what you can do?
How can you not let me take even a piece of it?
You took the Geumhwa Group with your dirty tricks.
As time goes by,
you don't even feel guilty anymore, do you?
I didn't feel guilty 20 years ago either.
Then and now, you're the one who has a talent for the dirty tricks.
Sam Joong, this punk.
He's not respectful to elders.
Oh, right.
That child has grown so much.
It's about time her powers slowly show up.
Tell them to be extra careful.
Don't let anyone touch her.
Take this and this one out.
Where Did a Penny Go? | How to Make Money Selling Cookies
How many times did I tell you that books related to law, economy, politics, sociology,
and psychology are prohibited?
What are you doing now? Get out.
Lady Seul Bi.
New books!
Books! Books! Books!
What are these?
I've already read them.
I even read this 179 times!
Jellyfish
That book is worn out.
Turritopsis nutricula (immortal jellyfish) reverts to an immature state as aging progresses,
as if time goes backward.
If they were human beings, it's like they become old men
and then revert back to babies.
And then they grow again.
Since they repeat the process indefinitely,
they can live forever unless they are eaten.
This place is amazing!
Whoa, Min Joon, can we drink all that?
Aren't we going to get in trouble with Uncle?
I heard that my father went to the Busan conference.
- He won't be home until tomorrow.
- Nice!
Hey. So the chairman and you are the only ones living here?
After my mother passed away,
my father said he just feels comfortable here.
Wow, Seon Min Joon! How does it feel to use this entire hotel as a house?
It feels like I'm boarding.
Many people live together. They serve meals when it's time to eat.
Min Joon, let's exchange my father with your father so that I can board here.
Hey. Hey. Hey!
That's not okay.
My younger sister is engaged to the only son of the Geumhwa Group.
If he turns into Eunsung Capital's only son,
it seems like my sister is losing out.
Gong Su Gwang, what are you doing there?
- Come down.
- Come on!
Okay.
Lady Seul Bi, what are you doing?
Come here.
If you keep doing this, I'll report it to the chairman.
You are so petty.
Petty! Petty, times a hundred!
Bottoms up! Cheers!
Huh?
- Huh?
- Su Gwang.
- You have leftovers?
- Leftovers?
- You left some.
- I'll stop here. Seriously, stop.
Little Mermaid, do you really want to be human?
If you receive a kiss of love from a prince, you can become a human.
But otherwise, you will turn into sea foam.
Mom, when will I ever meet a prince?
When you grow up.
The chairman is going to let me meet the prince?
When?
When? I'm all grown up!
- Seul Bi.
- Yes?
Meeting the prince may not be so happy after all.
Mom, that's just a fairy tale.
Lady Seul Bi.
It's time for Ms. Mi Su to take a rest.
It's also time for you to take a nap, Lady Seul Bi.
I'm not sleepy at all though.
Su Gwang is really amazing.
He was a Geumhwa Group scholarship student from middle school to college.
He hasn't graduated yet, but he has already entered the company!
Hey, Su Gwang, you'll have to be loyal to Min Joon for the rest of your life.
That's Su Gwang's ability.
Not just any company can take the top business student from Hankuk University.
Only our company is able to afford him.
So let's get down and party, Gong Su Gwang!
Hey, it's boring! Let's start the music!
What's this sound?
I'm not sure.
Say ah.
Every time I eat this, I get sleepy.
Thump! Thump! Thump! Thump!
It's the biggest land animal and
uses its long nose to eat. Is it an elephant?
It's not an elephant, but a person?
A person?
Please stand up here. Let me introduce ourselves.
These are my friends. My name is Seon Dong Sik. He's…
- Are you insane?
- Oh, why?
It's been boring by ourselves!
Now we should have some fun. We've only been drinking!
Hello. What's up over there, Jang Geun?
Come out! You should say hello!
Hey, you, come out!
It's not supposed to be like that. Hello. Hello.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Please follow Jang Geun.
Two of you can follow me.
The atmosphere is great, right?
What's good when it's great? We should drink.
Prince?
What are you doing over there, Min Joon? Sitting still?
You sure do take after Uncle.
Are you a statue or what?
My uncle is...
Hi, Mom.
Are you at the dorm?
I came out to hang out with my friends.
- Why?
- Just because.
Have fun and eat well.
Should I go see you, Mom?
That's okay. It would interfere with your studies.
I heard your voice, so it's okay, my son.
No. I wasn't even studying anyway. I'll come home.
Then will you come over for some fresh air?
I will make your favorite stir-fried squid.
All right. See you later.
She startled me.
Lady Seul Bi.
Lady Seul Bi?
Hello.
- Aren't you going to pay the bus fare?
- Excuse me?
Hello.
Why don't you answer me?
Pay the bus fare!
- Oh, are you with her?
- Yes.
It's moving! It's moving!
Wow!
I'll eat it too. Squid.
At the Lucky Fish Shop. At Su Gwang's.
How do you know our shop
and also my name?
Look over there! There! Wow!
You've been following me from the hotel, right?
Are you staying at the Geumhwa Hotel? Are your parents also staying there?
Why did you follow me?
Prince.
Get off at the next stop and go back.
I'll take you there.
I don't want to.
What should we do, ma'am?
We can't find her anywhere.
Just wear them for now.
It's beautiful.
Lucky Fish Shop
Hello!
Belonging to the Beloniformes Scomberesocidae family,
you are a warm current fish, saury.
You are a mollusk squid belonging to the cephalopods family.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
I'm Seul Bi.
Do your parents work in a place like the Marine Ecology Institute?
Su Gwang!
- Oh my! My son!
- Mom!
Oh, my. Hey. I smell fishy.
It's okay. I like my mom's smell. I missed you.
I missed you so much too, my son!
How have you been?
Let me see you, my son.
Oh, hey! What happened to your shoes?
Oh, who is this lady?
- I'm hungry.
- Excuse me?
Squid.
Yummy! Yummy! It's yummy!
Thank you for enjoying it so much.
Take your time and help yourself.
I have to eat quickly and take her back.
I'm not going.
I'll stay here with Su Gwang.
She keeps calling me by name, "Su Gwang, Su Gwang."
Hey. Your parents must be waiting for you. How can you eat?
Oh! That's okay.
Take your time and eat a lot.
Bluefish...
Perciformes Scombridae?
Mackerel!
- Hey! Hey!
- What's the matter?
Mackerel!
- Hey! Hey!
- Mackerel!
- Hey! What's the matter?
- We need a lot of mackerels!
- Do you want to eat a mackerel?
- Mackerel! Lots! Lots! Lots!
- Are you saying you want to eat a mackerel?
- No, no.
We need lots of mackerel.
How many mackerels do you have here?
We need 200 mackerels.
We don't have that many.
We have them!
Someone ordered a large quantity yesterday and canceled it.
I was worried since I should throw them all away after a few days.
I'm so glad!
It's a relief for me!
I'm a school nutritionist.
But the delivery company said they couldn't come today because of an accident.
Thanks to you, I can serve a school lunch to our students today.
Please hurry up and give them to me.
- Okay. Mom, mackerels?
- Yes. There! There!
Mackerels! Mackerels!
Young lady, how did you know...
Don't call me a lady. It's Seul Bi.
Okay. Seul Bi.
By chance...
Mom, can I load all of these?
Yes.
Let me do it. Let me...
Alright!
Bye.
Goodbye.
Try these on.
I think they will fit well.
They fit perfectly!
They're so pretty! Aren't they?
They look so good on you.
Mom, why didn't you wear such nice shoes when you had them?
You wear old shoes all the time.
I saved them to wear to go to a nice place,
but I have nowhere to wear them.
I wore these shoes when I went to an amusement park with
Su Gwang's dad and Su Gwang when he was young.
It's a pair of shoes that only have happy and joyful memories.
Amusement park?
Is it where the train flips over in the sky and
the big ship moves like a swing?
- That's the place, right?
- That's right.
Wow! I want to go there too!
I want to go to an amusement park with these shoes on.
Gosh, she's so chaotic!
Hey, where do you think you're going?
Mom, I need to take her to the Geumhwa Hotel.
Amusement park!
- Come out now.
- Amusement park! Amusement park!
Mom, I'll buy you the best shoes when I get paid.
Let's go to many great places wearing them.
Okay. Thank you, son.
Hurry up and take her back to the hotel.
Goodbye!
- We're leaving, Mom.
- Okay. Take care!
Bye bye.
Maternity Notebook l Parenting Diary
Let me take a picture. Smile, Su Gwang.
Thank you so much.
- Look over there!
- Geez, this is crazy!
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- You want me to do it?
- Yeah, yeah.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
Drink it. Drink it. Drink it.
Now, cheers!
Clink! Clink! Clink!
It's really great, but I'm a little sleepy now.
Hey, stay awake.
Secretary Cha
Chairman Seon.
Lady Seul Bi is missing.
Go up to Seoul. Right now.
Geumhwa Hotel
Wow! It's an amusement park!
Amusement park!
They reopened?
Amusement Park Reopening, Free Admission Today
Oh, it goes round and round.
This is a merry-go-round.
I'm so happy!
It's my prince!
What is this? It's so childish.
Here. Let's go now.
There's no one here. It's scary.
Let's hurry up and go now.
No. Hurry up.
What the hell are you doing here?
Father.
Hello, Uncle.
What the hell were you guys doing here?
We were just drinking a little bit.
Who else was here besides you guys?
We were the only ones here.
Get out right now.
I'm sorry, Uncle Il Joong.
- But—
- Get out right now!
You. Wait in the hallway.
Where is your daughter?
She's been stuck here for 20 years since she was born.
So I'm asking where she is right now.
Since she has nowhere to go,
she'll be back soon.
Are you sure?
She's on her way back.
Come on. Let's hurry in!
Oh, wait a minute.
Who are you?
It's you, Su Gwang.
Father!
- Chairman.
- Why are you doing this?
You ungrateful bastard!
Why are you doing this?
Send the guest's child back to the room.
Yes, sir.
He attempted to kidnap a hotel guest's child.
Take him to the police station.
It's a misunderstanding, Father.
Su Gwang just came to hang out with me.
Take him.
Yes, sir.
Su Gwang!
Take away his cell phone too.
- Father.
- Chairman Seon.
Take it away!
Mom, I saw it.
The future of Su Gwang.
Su Gwang?
Follow me.
Who are those people?
They are female shamans of prophecy.
- Pardon?
- That girl is yours.
She will protect you from future misfortunes
and bring you good luck.
For that to happen, no one else should look at her, meet her,
or touch her.
She's a lucky talisman that exists only for you.
So...
don't let anyone take her away.
Tell me your mother's number.
I need your guardian to come here!
Tell me your mom's number quickly.
I'm here from the Geumhwa Group.
Your acceptance into the Geumhwa Group has been canceled. And...
you won't be able to get in touch with Min Joon anymore.
Complaint Service Room
I'm sorry, Mom.
That's okay.
That's alright, Su Gwang!
Is that the only company out there?
You will get into a better company with your ability.
My son.
You've been doing so well all this time.
I'm fine as long as you're okay.
Mom!
Mom.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Operating Room
Excuse me. The truck driver says he fell asleep behind the wheel,
so he doesn't remember what happened.
I took care of it so that people won't suspect us.
- And I took care of Ms. Min who was serving Lady Seul Bi.
- Chairman!
Chairman!
Ma'am, give us some chicken gizzards!
Min Joon, I heard that Su Gwang died.
He killed himself.
Only a suicide note and his shoes were left behind.
They couldn't even find his body.
Father!
You ungrateful bastard!
He attempted to kidnap a hotel guest's child.
Take him to the police station.
- Min Joon!
- Father!
Father!
I heard that Su Gwang is dead.
Are you throwing a drunken fit in front of your father?
Father, Su Gwang...
My friend is dead.
Should I cry over that or something?
What did you mean by that back then?
That girl is yours.
No one else should look at her, meet her,
or touch her.
By chance, did you do it?
From now on,
you take care of your belongings
on your own.
Father.
Could it be really true?
Please answer me, Father.
Min Joon, let's go.
- Father.
- Min Joon, let's go!
- Please answer me!
- Min Joon!
Father!
Please answer me! Answer me, Father!
He's gone for good,
so keep your daughter safe.
If this happens again...
You're going to kill my daughter too?
No.
Everything that happens from then on
is all your fault.
No.
He's not dead.
Su Gwang is not dead.
You're finally awake.
You've been lying there like that for three days.
Where is...
When I pulled up the net, it was so heavy that I almost broke my back.
So I thought I hit the jackpot.
I was happy thinking it might be a minke whale or a shark.
Unfortunately, some guy came up bleeding.
I felt like someone was trying to kill you,
so I called a health clinic doctor I knew and asked him to treat you.
Now that you've heard this much, you should thank me.
You should've let me die.
"He lost his mother and had a lot of debt,"
"so he got pessimistic about his life and committed suicide."
Are you the one the newspaper is talking about?
But it didn't seem like a suicide to me.
I wonder who was trying to kill you.
A pessimistic man in his 20s, with enormous debt, lost his mother. Threw himself into the ocean...
Mom.
I miss Su Gwang.
♫  On a sunny day with the warm light, suddenly   ♫
Seul Bi.
Why do we have to live like this?
Why did you live like this, Mom?
Seul Bi.
I want to be an ordinary person.
I want to be an ordinary person and live in the outside world.
♫  A strong wave is about to swell inside me, who used to be calm  ♫
Lady Seul Bi, it's time for your injection.
- What are you guys doing?
- Mom!
Take her!
No.
My Seul Bi.
- No! Mom!
- Take her!
Mom!
♫   Why are you shaking my heart that I’ve held back breathless for so long?   ♫
♫   What am I supposed to do if you do this to me now?   ♫
♫   Because I know I can’t let go easily   ♫
♫  I guess I’ve been waiting for you all day   ♫
♫  I've never hated the wind that blew at me  ♫
♫   Why do you bring back memories of you and shake me?   ♫
♫  I want to tell you not to come back  ♫
♫  I’m afraid you’ll disappear without saying a thing  ♫
This isn't much, but you will need it.
Thank you, Ajussi.
And this.
What is this?
Your name.
If you go up to Seoul, the people who tried to kill you might come after you again.
Use this name for a while.
Go Myeong Seong?
Identification Card: Go Myeong Seong
Strangely, he looks like you, right?
It's my son.
He died a year ago.
I haven't filed his death certificate yet.
From now on, you are my son, Go Myeong Seong.
2 years later, Seodong Market
Should I take a stroll?
You can't help but buy this.
Buy one, get one free!
And I will follow you for free too.
If you take this guy, it'll be your loss, ladies.
Geez, President Park! I'm not following you!
Why is it so hot today?
When the hell is this heat going to end?
Tell me about it. It's so hot, right?
- Hello.
- Welcome!
Yeong Wu's House
Here, here, here.
- Here.
- Hey!
- Sir.
- Give us one kkakdugi (cubed radish kimchi), please.
- Yes, here you go!
Honey, Kim Jeong Tae!
What the hell is this credit card balance?
Am I the b*tch making money, and you get to spend it, a**hole!
Seriously! Where are you going?
Don't go.
Hey!
Mr. Kim, fighting!
Oppa!
President, did you see Jeong Tae? Jeong Tae?
Come on. Why do you call your husband by name?
What husband? He's not even a human!
What's the matter?
Oh, you've opened up the store.
Oh my, oh my.
Oh my! It's Go Myeong Seong!
Avoid him! Avoid him! It's Go Myeong Seong!
Go Myeong Seong! Go Myeong Seong!
You haven't opened it yet?
You're saying I shouldn't come this way?
Don't worry. I'll be your first customer.
Please deliver one fried chicken to me.
I don't want to! If you are my first customer, today's business is screwed!
Gosh! I shouldn't have talked to him!
Go! Go!
Go away!
Oh my!
Hey!
Oh, this precious salt.
I'll use it well. Thank you.
Let's go!
Why did she sprinkle salt on him?
He's a Seodong Market legend.
A man who carries bad luck like the wind or the clouds.
If you talk to him once or even touch him once,
he'll bring you bad luck for three days. He's a devilish person.
Gosh, there's no such a person like that.
That person, Go Myeong Seong!
He's coming. He's coming. He's coming!
Hello, we just opened a flower shop.
Oh, yes. Nice to meet you.
By the way, you're so handsome.
You'll be in trouble if you touch me.
Is it true, Ajussi?
Yes. You should be careful too, Miss.
They talked! They talked! They talked!
You are overreacting.
Thanks to your prediction, our company won a competitive bid.
This is your gift.
Aren't you going to open it?
You don't say anything to me except when you predict the future.
Please let me go outside.
Just once.
Please.
Hey, we'll collect money today, okay?
Okay. Okay.
Hey, Go Myeong Seong, what day was it yesterday?
I heard you're smart.
You said you were accepted into Hankuk University.
So why do you keep forgetting the day you should pay me?
If you keep bothering me, I can't run the business well.
Then I can't pay you back.
This punk...
Hey. Are you saying it's my fault that you can't pay me back right now?
This punk must be crazy, Hyungnim.
Only flies buzz around these days  (business is slow).
Can you catch them with me?
- Geez.
- This punk!
- Oh, I missed it.
- Myeong Seong.
Hello, President Park.
Mr. Wang is here again.
You know, the Fisheries Center says they need a delivery man.
- I see.
- Do you have time?
Of course, I do.
You should let Myeong Seong go make money.
Alright.
Director Seon! Director Seon!
Oh my! Oh my! Wait, wait, wait!
Lady Seul Bi is not allowed to go outside.
No. She will go out.
Seul Bi should have this much freedom.
- If the chairman finds out—
- Ms. Kim.
If you don't report it to him, he won't know.
My father is in Dubai right now.
Thank you.
Let's go.
But if you leave...
Seul Bi, I'm different from my father.
I think of you as my partner.
I'll treat you the best I can.
And someday, I'll let you live in the outside world.
Wait a minute, Seul Bi. Let me go over there for a second.
Lucky Fish Shop
It's Su Gwang.
It's indeed Su Gwang.
He's Dr. Kang.
I've been asking around to scout him for Biotech, but it didn't work.
But I happened to run into him here.
As expected, you are the goddess of luck.
He's so cool. My prince.
Mom.
I saw Su Gwang.
I'll get out of here.
I'll go to Su Gwang.
Exit
Seul Bi.
Get ready.
It's hot! My hand! My hand! Hot!
Are you smiling?
Is she crazy or something?
Secretary Cha asks you to bring us.
Secretary Cha?
Secretary Cha asked me to bring you two.
He asked me to bring you two.
Secretary Cha...
asked me to bring Lady Seul Bi and Ms. Mi Su.
Secretary Cha asked me to bring you two.
What's going on, ma'am?
- Secretary Cha.
- Ma'am.
What's going on?
What?
Why am I here?
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Why are they...
Oh, gosh! What's going on here?
Get them! What am I supposed to do?
Get them!
What should I do?
Wait! Wait!
Nineteenth floor, A block, number 4. Check the screen operation.
Get them!
Wait. Oh, sh*t!
Raise this! Raise this!
Hurry up!
Mom, are you okay?
Hurry up and leave, Seul Bi.
- Mom, I'll just—
- You must go, Seul Bi.
Don't worry and leave.
For my sake.
You can do it, right?
What are you doing? Hurry up!
- Go. Go.
- Hurry Up!
My daughter.
I love you.
I love you, Mom.
Go!
♫  At first sight  ♫
♫  I knew you were the one  ♫
♫  Maybe you also knew that  ♫
♫  Looking at my trembling eyes  ♫
It's good to see you...
Gong Su Gwang.
♫  Please notice me  ♫
♫  I'll smile a little more  ♫
♫  I'll look at you a little more  ♫
♫  Please notice my heart  ♫
♫  Feel the feeling of walking on the clouds with me  ♫
♫  If you hold my hand, I can go higher  ♫
♫  I'm in love with you  ♫
Jinxed at First
Something's wrong with her, right?
She seems like she's a little slow.
I'm hungry.
She seems odd.
She's odd. Very odd.
We have secured all 160 CCTVs and are checking them.
We've set up a search team, so we'll find her soon, Chairman.
I'll find Seul Bi.
But if I find her, I'll treat her my way.
- Don't trust him!
- Thief!
You are right!
Call the police!
Su Gwang!