(Episode 7)
Look.
-Did you make all these? -Yes.
This is Soo-kwang and Seul-bi's home.
I feel like I'm dreaming right now.
Come here.
(Soo-kwang & Seul-bi Lucky Fish Shop Awesome!)
Soo-kwang. I won't leave you alone here.
I'll always be by your side.
-Don't go. -What's wrong, Seul-bi?
Don't go, Soo-kwang.
Where can I go?
Don't worry. I'm not going anywhere.
You look so beautiful when you're sleeping. I've been watching you for a long time.
Then I'll sleep a little longer.
No.
You look beautiful too when you're awake.
He came to the market last time, and so did this time.
I don't think he's here to buy anything.
-What are you doing alone? -I can't reach...
You can't reach it? Take it. It's okay now.
(Boiled octopus; Grilled eel; Octopus ramen)
-Excuse me. Can I help you? -Hello.
Hairtail.
Who are they?
(Octopus ramen; Spicy whelks; Spicy braised hairtails; Grilled shrimps with garlic&cream)
-I want to eat spicy whelks today. -Okay!
-Can you pack me a kilo of shrimps? -Okay.
-I'll grab something at the nearby store. I'll be right back. -Don't worry. I'll pack the shrimps for you.
-Thank you. -Okay.
You're good at making money.
-Isn't it pretty? -Yes, but you're prettier.
-Hello. -Welcome.
Hello.
What would you like to buy?
You need to take off the sunglasses to pick out better seafood.
For example, check their freshness.
Give me two kilos of shrimps.
-Okay. -Thank you.
Crustacean prawns of the Penaeidae of the Decapoda prawn family.
Wow, you're so cool.
-Thank you. Soo-kwang. Give her more shrimps.
Okay, okay.
-Hello. -Hello.
Welcome. Have we met before?
-Well... -Yes?
-Are the two at the Lucky Fish Shop lovers? -Oh, my.
Why are you curious about that?
They look perfect together, right?
-They're dating right now. -I knew it. Thank you.
-Buy one, please. -Give me three.
Gosh, you're so generous. Here you are.
-Can I pay by credit card? -Of course you can.
-Oh, by the why, that woman has another man. -Oh, my.
The man who comes to that fish shop every day is a grandson of a rich family.
Ah.
-Bye. -Bye.
So heavy.
Min-joon, what are you doing?
Where should I put this?
-What are these? -Plants and other things.
I personally like catchflies and sundew,
but I don't want to scare you,
so I picked these for you.
Okay. Thank you.
You haven't had lunch, right? Let's eat when we do the interview.
-Interview? -Did you forget?
You have to do an interview for my online novel.
You kept avoiding it, so the novel hasn't been progressed.
The Editor-in-Chief wants to fry me up now.
Can we do the interview next time?
You want to do the interview or get married with me?
Are you saying this to avoid the interview?
Jang Kyung, I'm busy right now.
I think I have to marry you.
Sweetheart, I have to beg you father to buy me a purse.
Isn't it tasty?
It looks delicious. I bought this at Seodong Market.
-Did you follow me? -Yes, I did.
I was angry because the interview failed.
So what did you find out at Seodong Market?
The woman who captured your heart is an owner of a fish shop!
Min-joon. This topic will be so attractive!
It’s totally my taste.
Where did you and that woman meet? How did you know each other?
Let's ... just get married.
You're so cruel to yourself.
Why are you so eager to protect her?
Hello.
Jung Hyun Tae was released?
-Secretary Jung was released? -Oh.
Do you still miss him? Your feelings for him will be back soon, right?
It's not love. It's guilt.
Why did you choose him?
-He's much better than you. You're ignoble. -What?
You were afraid of your father. You didn't dare to do anything.
You promised to let me go, but you never wanted to keep your promise, right?
Locking a witch like you here
is the best thing I have ever done.
It's scarier to release you outside.
You and your father Seon Ju-cheol...
Is he still in a mental hospital?
It's my mom who made him so. He had a long life though.
-Shut up. -You will be like that. After all, you inherited the same blood from him.
Shut up!
Let go of me!
Don't look at me like that.
It's yummy.
-Yummy? -Yes.
-It's yummy. -It's yummy, right?
-Nice job. -It's good, right?
It looks better than mine.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Praying.
What is praying?
When you need to thank the God or beg the God for something,
you can put your hands together and pray.
God. Thank you for letting me meet Soo-kwang.
We will always be together.
We'll meet again even if we are apart.
Even if we are apart again, we will meet again.
Let us love each other forever.
You fool. Praying is to say your wishes in the heart.
It'll be easier to be heard if you say it out loud.
Thank you!
Th God will listen to my prayers. Pray now.
What are you praying for?
You can't interrupt me with praying.
Say it out loud. Tell me yours.
You can wander around outside. I'll go find you later.
(I)
What are you doing?
What did you pray for?
It's a secret.
I'll keep it a secret too.
-What? -Secret?
-What is it? -It's a secret.
I caught you. Are you really not going to tell me?
I won't tell you.
It's a secret.
Tell me.
I choose this one.
Okay.
What size do you want?
Which size?
The size of your girlfriend's finger.
Oh, I see.
If you don't know now,
you can text me the size when you do.
Okay. I see.
Okay.
Myeong-seong, why are you at my flower shop?
I need flowers in a few days, so can I book now?
-Are you going to propose? -Shh!
(Stewed octopus soup; Spicy whelks)
Wow.
-Are you done delivering the goods? -Yes.
(Original fried chicken)
-What are you doing? -Nothing. Nothing happened.
See? I hung up the ad. for stewed octopus soup today.
I'm going to hang up all the seafood recipes here.
Is that so? No more space now.
Don't worry. I can make it. Fighting!
Hello?
Do you have something to tell me?
Nothing.
(Original Fried Chicken)
What is it? Tell me, now!
Well... If I want to buy a ring for Seul-bi,
which size should I buy?
-That's too much. -That's why I didn't want to ask you.
Size 7.
Thank you.
Lucky seven. Okay, size 7.
You scared me.
You're back.
I've delivered all the goods to six places.
Thank you for your hard work. Have a rest please.
Why is it lucky 7?
Size 7.
Even if you're holding a fish, you look like a figure coming from the comic book.
He's so charming.
Chasing bravely and never give up. This should be my attitude towards love.
(Keep it frozen to make it's fresh)
What should I do now?
I have nothing to wear on my finger. How pitiful I am.
The oil temperature to fry the chicken should be between 170 degrees to 180 degrees.
Sister.
What?
What oil is this?
It's used.
Look over there. That's mustard oil.
Aren't you going to the reading room? Why are you still here?
I've already had a choice, Mom.
I told you not to think about that.
There's no need to think about that now. Just submit your application form based on your scores.
No, I don't want to go to college. I'm gonna run a fried chicken shop.
There's no major in fried chicken in college.
-You... -Mom, it hurts.
You must've done a lot to avoid studying.
Go to the reading room now!
Even though I enter a big corporation after graduation, I still need to run a fried chicken shop.
Even thought I become a civil servant later, I will still run a fried chicken shop after retirement.
I am going to end my life with fried chicken anyway.
So I should just inherit the shop directly,
and become a BTS in the chicken industry.
Hey, you have a sister.
Who said you could inherit this shop?
Sis, you should marry him and run a fish shop.
I wish I could.
I can't live anymore because of you two.
-Have a good day. -Come again.
Thank you.
(Keep it frozen to make it's fresh)
Myeong-seong.
Uncle Gao.
(Keep it frozen to make it's fresh)
What brings you here?
You haven't showed up recently. I came to see if you were dead.
You should've told me in advance so that I could pick you up.
What is this?
I just brought a few beatfish. You need to put some ice inside.
(Keep it frozen to make it's fresh)
Wow, it's the flat sea fish of Paralichthyidae.
Hello, hitfish.
Hello.
She's my girlfriend.
What a beautiful girlfriend.
I told you before. This is Uncle Go.
The man who helped me when I was in trouble.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, nice to meet you.
This is Mr. Jung, our new employee.
This is ... my dad.
Your dad?
Are you leaving?
Let's go eat something nice tonight.
Let's eat something nice.
No, it's going to rain tonight. I have to go now.
I just need to see you.
I'm so sad. Are you just going to leave?
Yes, I'm leaving.
Dad, let's go eat something delicious.
You...
Why are you here?
Just run!
Mom.
Do I have a dad too?
Of course you do.
Where is he now?
In the outside world.
Do you love Dad?
Well...
Don't you love him?
I think loving him is the hardest thing in the world.
Why is love so hard?
Some people in this world think love is insignificant.
People like that will only use us to achieve success.
So we need to figure out
who will only take advantage of our ability,
and who will truly love us.
Why did you call me out?
Hey, Jung Hyun Tae.
Why are you with my son?
I didn't know he was your son.
What are you doing here? Why did you come?
What do you think? Didn't you see that necklace?
That's...
She... She is my daughter.
What?
How could my daughter get involved with your son?
Try to lay a finger on my son if you dare!
I won't let you go.
What else can you do?
I'm not who I was 20 years ago.
Do you know who my backer is?
If you mess with me, you're dead too.
Fine. Who's your backer?
Who sent you to my son?
Seon... Seon Il-jung.
Seon Il-jung?
Yes. So let your son leave my daughter.
Or your son will die.
Seon Il-jung.
Mr. Wang. What?
Don't you know who I am?
Of course, I do. My boss likes you so much.
If you do, you can't flirt with me like this.
Yes, I can't.
What do you want indeed?
Who's the big shot?
How could I know?
Then I'll have to send the photos to the boss.
Do you want to see some of the photos?
I really don't know.
Then find it out. You can check the boss's files and phone at all.
If I get caught, I'll die.
No. If you can't check it out, you'll die.
Seriously.
You're given three days.
I think it's in Seodong District.
If you find her, take her to the Cheongpyeong Villa. I'll see her there.
Okay.
This is the list of investment companies that can replace the Shalike Group.
You can negotiate with companies in Hong Kong and Singapore, right?
But they want to talk to you directly.
You said you didn't need the help of prophecy. And you're the one who needs to show your ability.
Give me more time, please.
You need to catch the right timing to show your ability.
If you miss the chance, you'll miss it.
No matter how high your expectations were, when did I let you down?
I really don't know what else I can do to meet your standards.
My standard?
No. It is the criterion to be the chief commander of a big enterprise.
Have you arrived?
Check every stores in the market.
Don't miss anything, okay?
Thank you. Come again.
Myeong-seong's wife.
What?
Just give me two hairtails, please.
Okay.
I don't want any whelks.
You called me Myeong-seong's wife, so gave you them for free.
Really? I'll call you that no matter what.
Myeong-seong's wife.
Yes.
(Call me Myeong-seong's wife, you can get more than you want!)
Master.
Master Pretty.
Me?
You knew you're pretty.
Please listen to me carefully from now on.
I've been a witch for 20 years.
It's my luck.
So,
if you can teach me a little bit of your ability,
I will repay you with what I have.
I'm not willing to.
I knew you'd be like this.
You're quite charismatic.
Please do me a favor. Okay?
I'm not a master. Call me Myeong-seong's wife.
Myeong-seong's wife,
please help me this time.
Just once.
Seul-bi.
You're here.
What's going on?
Hey, when did you put this up?
So what?
Then how about I let them call you Seul-bi's husband?
What?
Okay?
God of Heaven and Earth, God of Jade Emperor, God of Milky Buddha...
Om Mani Padme Hum.
Don't touch him.
My goodness. There's a person with such a clear soul in this world.
Gosh, you're so dazzling.
Are you buying fish or not? If you aren't, just leave.
I'll buy it. If you catch the cod with your pure hands,
I'll be able to make a pot of cod soup.
Master. I don't know the relationship between you two... Oh my.
Go over there. You go this way.
Ah, wait a moment.
I'm the chairman of the Chamber of Commerce.
Why did you come to our market? Are you here for group buying?
Have you seen this woman?
No.
Who is she?
You don't need to know.
They're coming in groups.
They're here.
That man of the political marriage...
They must be sent by that rich family.
Young-woo. Young-woo.
Go find Seul-bi right now. Tell them the bad guys are here to catch her.
Those bad guys...
Hey, Mrs. Smile.
There is a bunch of weird people in the market.
This is bad!
The bad guys are here.
-Young-woo, what's wrong? -What happened?
The bad guys came to catch Seul-bi.
This is really bad.
Hello. Welcome.
Hey, have you seen this woman?
Oh my, isn't this a whore?
My husband doesn't go to the Arisan club anymore.
Did you come from that club?
Are you from there?
Excuse me.
Oh, no.
I'm all wet.
-I'm sorry. -I'm sorry, sir.
-Are you okay? -You're all wet. Sorry.
-I've never seen her before. -Why don't you eat this? This tastes good.
Gosh, it's so wet.
Hello?
Director.
Did you find her?
Not yet.
Go check over there.
Have you seen this woman?
Oh...
Yes.
Where?
"Desperate Men". Isn't she an actress in that drama?
The weekend drama?
No, it's a morning drama.
Are they still here?
The marketing merchants said that you were interrupting their business.
You didn't buy anything and messed up the market.
We came as soon as we received the report.
Yes, they're here.
These people...
I heard you got in the way of their business.
What are you doing here?
We're looking for a missing person.
Did you report her missing?
Not yet. We're looking for her on our own for some reason.
Who went missing?
I can't tell you that.
You neither reported her missing,
nor can't you tell the police who she is.
And you're obstructing everyone's business in this market.
What's going on?
This is very suspicious.
Please show me your ID cards and your contacts.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
-Where are you going? -Hey!
Wait, please.
I may call you next time. Please cooperate with us then.
Hurry up.
I'll give it to you next time.
I told you to come.
I did well, right? I'm so nervous.
Me too.
Seul-bi.
You know Min-joon, right?
The people who came to the market to look for you
are from Geumhwa Hotel, right?
I first met you at Geumhwa Hotel two years ago.
But when I sent you back to the hotel,
the chairman was furious at me.
(Hello, this is the Personnel Section of Talent Group.) I'm sorry to tell you that you didn't pass the interview. Thank you for your concern and precious time. We wish you good health and good luck. Thank you.)
I finally lost the valuable chance to join Geumhwa Group.
What's your relationship with Geumhwa Group?
It's time to tell me the truth.
I want to know the truth too.
Soo-kwang.
If what you said is true,
If you were imprisoned because of that ability,
did my mom die because of that?
The day we first met two years ago.
Mom!
My mom was in a car accident
and someone tried to kill me.
Soo-kwang.
(Lucky Fish Shop)
(Director Seon Min-joon)
Soo-kwang.
What? Hotel?
You came to the hotel?
Let Seon Sam-jung go out. Where is the Chairman?
Gong Soo-kwang.
Let's talk.
Get back to work.
Hey, Seon Min-joon.
You knew everything too, right?
You knew what your dad did, right?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
You locked someone up and kidnapped someone who escaped.
You tried to kill people to avoid being found.
Is Geumhwa Group a den of criminals?
Soo-kwang.
Go up.
You...
Yes, I'm Gong Soo-kwang.
You're alive.
You were the one who caused
my mom's death, right?
Is it really you?
No, it can't be.
My friend's father... The person who recognized and sponsored me.
I regarded him as my father.
He would never do that to me.
I thought about it hundreds and thousands.
I thought it wouldn't be you.
But did you really do it?
Was it because of Seul-bi?
You call yourself a human?
Soo-kwang,
what you know is not true.
I will tell the world
what you've done.
I'll make sure you get punished.
Don't come to Seul-bi again.
Gong Soo-kwang.
Seul-bi is my woman.
What?
Seul-bi was already my woman before she met you.
You locked her up and said she was your woman.
I'm protecting her.
Seon Min-joon, you're disgusting.
Soo-kwang.
If the world finds out the secret about Seul-bi,
people will be happy and want to see her.
And those who can't get her will try to get rid of her.
Will these happen?
I didn't know... Gong Soo-kwang is alive.
Is what Soo-kwang said true?
Dad. You caused his mother's death
and tried to kill him?
No.
No?
No, I didn't do it.
Then why didn't you explain anything to him?
Why let Soo-kwang misunderstand you?
Is that so important?
Then what is important?
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Why did you...
come to me?
Soo-Kwang.
Thanks to your ability,
My mom passed away.
What brings you here?
Soo-kwang, I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Don't go.
Don't go! Soo-kwang!
Don't go!
Gong Soo-kwang is still alive.
You knew, didn't you?
He is alive.
You locked her up and said she was your woman.
Seon Min-joon, you're disgusting.
(Holy Flame Hospital)
You're here.
Come to us.
Or we can go to you.
Dad.
Kill that witch.
That's the only way we can get out of here.
She's a witch.
Mi-soo!
Drop your gun. Drop your gun. Mi-soo!
No, he deserves to die. I'll kill him myself.
-No! -No!
Mom!
Mi-soo.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
Mom! Mom! Open your eyes! Mom!
Mom!
She took advantage of us to find us.
We should kill that witch.
Chairman, are you okay?
Let's go.
I thought you'd come with the chairman.
Why did you come separately?
I came to check the medical records.
The chairman has been watching your grandfather's medical records.
No. What I want to check is not my father's medical records
but my dad's medical records.
Well...
I'm his guardian.
Soo-kwang.
Don't you think this place is small?
It's much bigger than there.
Because I can walk out whenever I want.
You've grown up.
I should thank you. You made me grow up.
How could you say that?
Move to a place where Min-joon can't find you.
I'll arrange a place for you.
I don't need your help now.
You can't stay here.
You should know what will happen, if you get along with people longer.
I want to be an ordinary person.
If Soo-kwang sees who you really are, would he still keep you by my side?
If it's easy to be an ordinary person,
your mom wouldn't have lived like that forever.
When I find a place to stay for you, I'll send someone to pick you up.
I want to see my mom.
As long as you agree to move out,
I'll consider it.
Myeong-seong.
These are the flowers you ordered last time.
Wow, my brother-in-law. They are beautiful.
I heard he's going to propose to her. I think it's true.
Hey, why don't you pick up the bouquet?
Come on. Sister.
How much is that?
100,000 won.
100,000 won? That's too expensive.
What's wrong with you?
Leave me alone.
Sister!
What?
Myeong-seong and Seul-bi are getting married. Really?
I don't know.
If you marry Myeong-seong. I'll possess the fried chicken restaurant.
You punk.
Do you think the reason why I worked so hard to give you education
is to let you run a fried chicken restaurant?
What's wrong with that?
Mom, you should be proud of your work.
I admire you for making delicious fried chicken.
You admire me?
Yes.
It's hard to do one thing well in people's life.
Our head teacher said that.
But you did two great things.
Two things? What else?
You raised us so well.
Eun-joo.
Hey, don't be so sentimental.
You just try to inherit this restaurant.
Hurry up. Do your homework.
Guys.
80% of the investment in the fried chicken restaurant is a loan.
I'm going to the reading room.
Son.
Whatever, I'm so touched.
Where did I put the exercise book of civil service examination?
(Seodong Market)
(Frozen enough to make sure it's fresh.)
Seul-bi.
Hello.
-Did you get home safely yesterday? -Yes.
You're so shy.
You're so cute.
You must be very introverted.
Myeong-seong's wife.
Sister.
Here.
I made this sandwich for you two.
So delicate.
Thank you.
Seul-bi.
These are couple shirts.
I found that when you took wedding photos, you must wear casual clothes.
A wedding photo?
It's the photo taken before the wedding ceremony.
You really don't know anything.
That's how she gets to know gradually.
-Thank you for the clothes. Thank you. -OK.
Hey.
You are all here.
This is for you.
What is this? Sister.
This is a cactus couple.
This is Myeong-seong. This is you.
I heard it's very reproductive.
Thank you.
Let me know if you need a hall.
I'll introduce you to a nice place.
Mr. Park, the chairman of Merchant Prosperity
will host the wedding.
I should go prepare a suit.
I'll sing a congratulatory song.
Stop it, everyone.
I'm sorry. I want to talk to her alone.
-OK. -Sure. Sure.
-You two talk. -OK.
-Take it. -Come here.
Don't come to the market anymore.
Soo-kwang.
I need time to think about it.
I was in pain when I saw you.
Soo-kwang. I will do better.
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault. Well...
Please leave.
Soo-kwang, I hate you.
Seul-bi.
What? Come here.
I think you two had a fight.
But how could you make a woman cry?
What are you doing? Let's go inside.
That's right. Don't believe him.
Men are ships and women are harbors. That's how it is.
Goodness.
Brother-in-law,
I heard you didn't want to see her and told her to leave you. Really?
Why?
Yes.
You live together, and you agreed to get married.
But you're pushing her away in front of us. Is it correct?
That's right. Myeong-seong, you did something wrong.
Which side am I on right now?
Let's go.
I'm not going back.
I didn't ask you to go back there.
Let's go our home.
Goodness.
Our home?
Okay.
Goodness.
Wait.
A woman should be cool sometimes.
You're too easy to please.
Goodness.
(Original fried chicken)
Yes.
What happened?
Just wait. It's serious here.
What do you mean?
I'll call you back.
What did he say?
I'm not sure.
We don't know anything. We are just waiting?
He's just trying to get more money, right?
Since the Geumhwa Search Team is here, that means Sam-jung knows it too.
How can we wait?
Since the search team went there, the police have been watching closely.
So I think we should wait a little longer, sir.
Darn it.
Did you buy this for me?
No.
No? Give it to me now.
I said no.
The size is perfect. So beautiful.
Thank you.
(Lucky Fish Shop)
What are you doing?
I'm packing up.
I won't go back.
Whether it's a single room or a study room, I'll find a temporary place for you.
If you don't want to go back to Geumhwa Group. Don't force yourself.
I'll find a place to stay.
No need.
Seul-bi.
You can't live here with me.
I told you I don't need a place to stay.
Pack up.
Soo-kwang.
That woman! That woman!
You must see that woman.
You must see her.
She's the one who came to see Gong Soo-kwang not Go Myeong-seong.
I knew it when I saw you at the market.
That's it.
It's been two years.
It's newly built.
It's perfect for newlyweds.
Wedding house?
Yes.
Myeong-seong is looking for houses with Mr. Kim, the real estate agent.
What?
I guess they were just having a quarrel. I was worried for nothing.
Right.
They're newlyweds. I'm so jealous.
So they won't live in my attic anymore?
Actually, that place can be used as a wedding house.
-Oh! -My goodness. You scared me.
So annoying.
This is your chance. The timing is perfect.
Hurry up.
(Original fried chicken)
-Eun-jung. -Oh!
What's wrong with him?
(Original fried chicken)
Seul-bi.
Seul-bi!
What do you want from me, Myeong-seong?
Seul-bi?
I haven't seen her today.
No, it's okay, bro.
I'll call you back.
Seul-bi, where are you?
Chief Wang! Chief Wang!
Seul-bi.
Seul-bi!
(Superstar)
But I hated myself.
I brought you back home that day.
(Preview of the next episode)
Let go.
Since you can see the future, why did you do that day?
Why were you so indifferent that day?
Soo-kwang.
I heard you've been in psychiatric care for a long time.
Seul-bi isn't a witch.
-She went back to the hotel. -Hey.
I told you to pretend to look for her. Why did you take her back?
I didn't catch her. She went back on her own.
She went back on her own?
-Myeong-seong's back. -You are back.
I'm Gong Soo-kwang from now on.