=Endless Love=
=Episode 14=
My Lady, you're awake.
Where am I?
Who are you?
My Lady, I serve you.
I'm your maidservant, Ke'er.
Ke'er...
Such a familiar name.
But
I don't remember anything.
Then what is my name?
My Lady,
your name is Liu Rushi.
You are the daughter
of the Liu family, a merchant household.
Unfortunately, your father,
Mr. Liu, passed away so early,
and now only your mother
runs the family business
in the south of the city.
Yes, that's it.
If you're truly feeling unwell,
then don't push yourself.
What exactly happened?
Just a small accident.
The porridge is being cooked.
I'll have to tell you
the rest another time.
I'm fed up with these memorials!
I want Lanpingmei and Dongxiangji!
Give them to me!
You are the King of this land,
yet you read that kind of filth?
Don't you read them?
Are you done?
Who are you people?
Who am I?
I've told you a thousand times,
you are the King of Xiling.
No, I don't believe it!
I don't want to be the King of Xiling
and be locked up in here!
I want to go out and have fun!
Go away.
Out of my sight.
I hate you.
Your Majesty.
You will understand soon.
Remember,
no matter what His Majesty asks,
how he pressures you,
you must never speak of Mu Ruyi.
If His Majesty dwells on it too much,
I fear
that his madness will intensify.
Understood.
Additionally, spread the word
that the King has fallen critically ill
and is in no condition to govern.
Whoever disobeys this
shall be put to death.
Yes.
(One month ago)
(Your Highness!)
(Thankfully, they are out of danger.)
(But they both have head injuries,)
(which is why they're unconscious.)
(It's here.)
(My heart is half an inch off
from where it belongs.)
(If you want to take my life,
then do it.)
(If you fail to save Her Highness,)
(I will take your life.)
(As you wish.)
(What is it?)
(At critical moments, this pill)
(is used for clearing
and expelling stagnant blood.)
(Then why not give it to Her Highness?)
(Its effects are potent.)
(Through it can promote blood circulation
and remove stasis,)
(addressing the immediate crisis,)
(those who take it
will suffer mental confusion)
(and lose
some critical emotional memories.)
(In ancient texts,
this herb is called the Oblivion Herb.)
(Forget about the memories!)
(Life is what matters.)
(I never knew
such a miraculous herb could exist.)
(Forget the love,)
(and people can be cured.)
(Thankfully, her twins were saved.)
(But her temperament
has changed drastically.)
My Lady, put down those pirated books.
The porridge is ready. Come.
(Shuixu Brothers)
Shuixu Brothers.
(Bride Snatch to the West)
Bride Snatch to the West.
(Drill of the Three Kingdoms)
Drill of the Three Kingdoms.
These are all my favorite books!
Mind your own business.
And you, Xia Ke'er.
Who sent you here?
I have porridge in the morning,
at noon,
and at night.
Do I look like porridge to you?
You've just recovered
from a serious illness.
Greasy food is not good for you.
Just make do for now.
I suspect you're not my maidservant.
You trade in human lives.
You won't even give me a bite of meat,
and you want to sell me off
for a good price!
If I wanted to sell you
for a good price,
I'd have to keep you nice and plump.
So you really do want to sell me!
With your talent for making things up,
you could be a storyteller
at a teahouse!
Great idea.
Time to treat myself to some meat!
I'm going crazy!
Did your memory just come bouncing back
like a performing monkey's?
Your Highness,
His Majesty is unwell today
and is taking a nap.
Did he mention the details?
He said...
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
Your Highness.
His Majesty put on a eunuch's clothes
and slipped out of the palace.
You're all going to give me
a heart attack one day.
Your Highness,
aren't you skilled in medicine yourself?
A physician cannot heal themselves.
What are you waiting for?
I'll find an imperial physician
right away.
What is wrong with you?
Find His Majesty now!
Boss!
Miss, please have a seat.
Do you have silkworm pupae,
centipedes, or scorpions?
I'll have a pound of each.
Miss, I don't have enough money
to make change for this.
Today is your lucky day.
Buy yourself a drink.
I'll be honest with you,
the last portion of the silkworm pupae
has already been served
to that gentleman.
Take all the money,
and I want the pupae.
Miss,
when people run a business,
they follow the principle
of first come, first served.
It's not about who is richer.
These pupae are mine today.
Is all my money
enough to make me
"first come, first served"?
What a beggar!
What are you?
Boss,
open your eyes
(Eunuch of Imperial Stables)
and see for yourself.
Here you go, sir!
Please enjoy!
What are you so cocky about?
It's just a piece of wood.
Do you really think I don't know it?
Seriously?
My money could buy an entire pig.
Are you sure you won't take it?
If you're so rich,
go buy a pig and eat it raw!
Dear guests, please calm down.
Cool it off.
Your Majesty...
I...
Do you know the token he's holding?
Your Majesty,
why did you slip out
in a eunuch's dress?
We've been searching everywhere for you.
Who sent you here?
Prince Mo said
you're not allowed
to leave the palace freely.
Is he above me?
Miss, do you know who he is?
Who? Just tell me already.
He's a eunuch from the palace.
A eunuch? What is that?
A eunuch is
a man who has been castrated
and then brought into the palace
to serve.
They can never have children
or share a bed with a woman.
They are living a hard life.
Oh, how pitiful.
He lost his manhood from a young age.
No wonder he's so petty.
Keep running your mouth,
and you'll end up as a eunuch.
But...
Leave!
Go!
Why are you so unreasonable?
This is mine!
Mister!
No,
sister!
How about we share?
Who says I wanted to share with you?
Give it back!
Who are you, really?
Why would I tell you?
You look quite  familiar.
Have you
ever crossed me before?
If it weren't for the fact
that you're a sister,
I would have beaten you already.
You are talking nonsense.
Shameless!
I'm shameless?
There's plenty more I don't know.
How about you show me?
You...
But you might disappoint me
since you're not complete at all.
What are you rambling about?
Eunuch, you dropped your badge.
Eunuch? What do you mean?
Isn't this your badge?
An imperial eunuch! Such a noble status!
Boss, I'll return the plate next time!
You pupa thief!
Pray you don't get caught by me!