=Endless Love=
=Episode 4=
Your Highness,
let me serve you in the future.
From the moment I met you,
everything seems to have been destined.
I still remember
when we first met,
you stabbed me
with a commanding presence.
Never speak of
the embarrassing past again.
It was improper.
The improperness
brought us here.
Am I right?
Ling Xiao,
from now on, it's just us.
(Yunlai Inn)
Waiter!
One bowl of stinky tofu rice noodles!
Coming!
Dear customers,
we're about to close for the day.
Now we only have one bowl of noodles.
Waiter, I was first, wasn't I?
Well...
I ordered it first!
It's mine.
Heard of "first come, first served"?
It's my indulging day.
I get this bowl of noodles,
and you get the money.
Nothing but an upstart.
Seriously? You won't take good money?
Miss,
I run a modest business here.
For just a bowl of rice noodles,
I dare not take so much.
See for yourself.
Imperial!
Here you go.
Now you have it.
Enjoy!
Wait...
Fight me for it?
You don't know what's good for you!
Smells so good!
You're not getting any!
Go on, lady, enjoy your meal.
You!
A decent woman doesn't fight with a man.
This isn't over.
All bark and no bite.
(Command)
Are you hiding something from me?
What do you mean?
That day, actually,
I happened to see
Physician Zhou's medical records.
You...
You often suffer from illness,
don't you?
It's just a common cold.
There's no need to worry.
Since I have been admitted to
your mansion,
I wish to be completely honest with you.
The palace residents are tight-lipped
about your illness.
The trials never explicitly mention it,
yet they all test whether a man
is willing to give his life for you.
In all of this,
isn't there a connection?
I don't want to be a puppet who
knows nothing.
This is a matter of my Mu clan.
Outsiders can never interfere.
I'm still just a carpenter's son.
Now I stand alone,
but I believe
that human can conquer fate.
If you trust me, then tell me.
Some burdens,
when shared by two,
are lighter than when borne alone.
This is the curse on the royal Mu clan.
Only the heart-blood of a beloved one
can break the curse.
I have so many scars on my body,
and I have bled so much,
I survived it all.
I am willing to offer my heart-blood
in exchange for our tomorrow
and break the curse on you.
If I stay by your side,
I can also have
the respect and dignity
I've longed for a lifetime.
I don't want you to sacrifice yourself
just to fulfill my fate.
We have love.
What is there to fear in sacrifice?
Your Highness!
Take the remedy first.
Don't scratch!
Don't hurt yourself!
Take it out on me instead!
Let me help you!
You are good now.
(I never expected Ling Xiao)
(to be the one who can break my curse.)
(It seems)
(I have truly fallen for him.)
(Eight years ago)
I heard your mother was a palace maid.
Though you share the surname of Ling,
you're an unfavored son of a concubine.
No wonder Dongqing sent you
as a hostage prince to Xiling.
For generation after generation,
you will always be our slaves.
Father will come for me.
Your father?
Our Queen's sword ended him long ago.
This is to repay the blood debt
Dongqing owes for
slaughtering our royal family.
After that battle,
the world no longer belongs to Dongqing.
People in Dongqing
are now Xiling's slaves,
including you,
Ling Xiao.
Your Highness.
Recently, we have executed
over 50 hostage princes.
This will be the last one today.
Your Highness, here you go.
This is Her Majesty's command.
Your Highness,
are you alright?
If I mark him as a slave,
will his life be spared?
The centuries-old hatred
between Xiling and Dongqing
cannot be resolved easily.
If you defy Her Majesty's command
and show mercy to a hostage prince,
he will definitely die.
I hope that one day,
this hatred can end with me.
Mother.
I wish to marry Ling Xiao.
Say that again?
You are Princess of Xiling,
yet you would take a lowborn wretch?
Have you no regard
for propriety or decency?
This match is completely impossible.
I never knew
that a lowly slave
harbored such deep schemes.
Guards!
Throw him out
and put him to death!
Who dares!
I came today
not to negotiate with Your Majesty,
but to inform you
that my mind is made up.
Have you forgotten your duty?
You would abandon your grand purpose
for a lowly slave?
For 20 years,
I have followed your commands.
I never once stepped out of line.
But now,
I only want someone I love.
You throw everything away
for personal desire,
and you abandon it all.
Eventually,
you will regret this.
Even if you don't agree,
he
is mine.
Your Highness,
do you remember the first time we met?
It was just like this,
you standing before me,
touching my face gently.
Since I met you,
every moment is so impressive.
What do you want?
Mu Ruyi.
Do you know
how long I've been waiting
for this moment?
Who exactly are you?
I am Prince of Dongqing,
Ling Xiao.
Why did you cure my illness?
Why not just poison me?
I tampered with the tonic
you take every day
to ruin your health.
Only by saving you
could I earn the chance to kill you.
Why were you willing to die for me?
I never was.
It was nothing but a trick.
Even our first encounter
and our falling in love
were all part of your scheme?
Now that you know the truth,
you can at least have a swift death.
Enough.
Your time has come,
Your Highness.