=Endless Love=
=Episode 21=
Jing Liuli,
it's been a while.
I heard you were kicked out for a while.
You dare show your face here again?
Who are you?
I'm not Jing Liuli.
Stop pretending!
You wretched maid.
In this vast palace,
everyone knows Jing Liuli
only gained favor because she resembled
the former Princess.
You said you're not Jing Liuli,
have you come up with
some new games to win favor?
I don't know what you're talking about,
but you're rude,
and you look nasty.
Go back to wherever you came from.
After all these days,
you have changed so drastically.
This must be your true nature.
Looking at your haughty
and overbearing ways,
I'd say you've harmed quite a few.
This slap
is to discipline you
on behalf of your parents
and to serve justice.
Jing Liuli,
are you insane?
My father is the Prime Minister!
I couldn't care less!
The slaps are all you get today.
Provoke me again,
and I'll tear you apart!
No way!
You're not Jing Liuli.
Where's your birthmark?
This scar...
I thought you'd never
play the zither again.
I never expected
you to win the King's sympathy,
and he even found you
the Nine-section Sweet Flag!
Could it be
that you've been taken over?
Who are you, really?
Forget about who I am.
You've got bigger problems of your own.
Snapping at everyone like a mad dog,
you've made countless enemies!
You're on the brink of disaster,
and you don't even realize it!
I advise you to write some letters
to your Prime Minister father
and ask him to show you the way!
Stop barking here.
It's annoying!
Mark my words,
your luck has run out!
Yours too!
How does she
know about the scar on my hand?
But this scene feels so familiar.
Mu Ruyi,
Jing Liuli,
and I.
There's simply no way
there can be three people
who look exactly alike.
Who am I, really?
Liuli this, Liuli that...
Who are you?
Rushi.
Shattered glass blooms
like a broken dream.
Cold rain on the windowpane
severs the last strands of yearning.
I think Your Majesty
would much rather
hear Liuli recite poetry
than listen to me.
You once said
that she's just a person from the past.
Only today did I learn
that this person from the past
turns out to be the one you dream of
day and night.
That's not true.
I look so much like Liuli,
so how does the Princess of Xiling
connect to me?
Do you really think
"misunderstanding" covers all of this?
Jing Liuli was just a court singer.
Why do you compare yourself to her?
Then why do I have
the same scar on my hand as her?
Does that mean I am her?
No, you are not.
You are no one's replacement.
You are unique.
We promised each other
that between us,
we would leave the past behind
and only look to the future.
I thought I could do it.
But Liuli's presence still lingers here.
I can't ignore your shared past.
She will always come between us.
I need some time to think.
You may leave.
Mother...
No...
- Mother...
- My Lady! My Lady!
No...
My Lady!
What happened?
Shouldn't you be addressing me
"Your Highness" instead?
My Lady,
what's happened to you?
Did Ling Xiao say something to you?
So it's exactly as I suspected.
I am the Princess of Xiling.
Jing Liuli, Mu Ruyi...
They were all me.
I just couldn't remember anything.
Some memories
are better off buried.
Everything has already
been fated.
If you don't tell me the truth,
I'll only suffer more
and keep living in doubt.
Actually,
the past between you and Ling Xiao
is what needs to be buried.
Now that Your Majesty
remembers everything,
do you still have headaches?
Mo Shuo, take a seat.
I think Ruyi has figured something out.
Your Majesty,
don't dwell on it too much.
What should I do
to stop her suffering?
Let me be the only one
to carry the pain of the past.
Your Highness.
Take it away. I won't drink it.
Your Highness,
your health won't improve
unless you take your medicine.
Your Highness?
I am no longer a princess.
I'm just a stray dog
locked in the palace,
with no past to call my own.
Trust me,
everything will be alright.
So,
I am that former princess
who was humiliated in every way.
I forgot all that hatred
and humiliation.
I fell in love with the man
who killed my mother!
And now that I know the truth,
I still can't feel the pain
as if it were my own.
Once you're better,
we'll leave the palace.
Do you really think
that leaving the palace
will let us start fresh,
as if nothing ever happened?
Your Highness.
Rushi.
Finish your medicine today.
Leave.
I don't want to see you again.
And I won't take the medicine.
Leave?
The entire palace is mine.
And you, Liu Rushi,
you are nothing but a tool I used.
Indeed, Your Majesty.
You are the supreme ruler,
master of the world.
You can go wherever you wish,
and toy with whomever you please.
Then I shall leave.
Take the medicine
or poisoned wine.
The choice is yours.
Absolutely not, Your Majesty!
If Miss Mu took the Oblivion Herb again,
I'm afraid...
There must be a way out.
There must be a way to make her
return to the carefree Mu Ruyi.
But she will lose more memories!
She may even forget
everything around her!
Nothing matters more than her life!
It doesn't matter who she remembers
or who she forgets.
I only care that she lives.
I understand.
But Miss Mu is bent on dying.
She won't take the medicine willingly.
Then we'll have to find a way
to compel her.