(James 1:12)
(A man who endured)
(the test Blessed is the man that)
(endureth temptation for when he is tried)
Hey!
(The Lord promised those who love Him)
(Because I will have the crown of life)
Your friend?
(When a human is tested)
We're almost there. Let's just go
(I am tempted by God. Do not complain)
(God is not tempted by evil)
(He himself has not tested anyone)
Could you just drop me here please?
Thank you
Sorry
My uncle, he just kept driving
Get on the bike
Hey
Ready?　-Hold on a second
Music?
Give it
Give it!
Take it quickly
What song did you choose?
Ready?
Off to go
Guys! You see that?
I am this much
Guys, This isn't fake
Please believe me
Oh my!
Goodness!
Oh my Partiya
Thank you for the 50 Likes
Oh, how long are you going
to keep him waiting?
Please accept my love soon
Please accept my love
before my shoulders break
I have to go now
See you in the evening
Bye
Jaenam?
Suhyun?
Hey
What are you doing?
Do the laundry
Can't you see?
Why do the laundry in the bathtub?
This T-shirt needs
hand-wash
wait!
Will it dry by tomorrow?
Not sure
Not sure?
What the..
How was the visit
to your father's grave?
Fine
By the way,
where were you coming from earlier?
School
School?
Yeah
Why?
Learn French during this vacation
You learn French?
Yeah
Suddenly why?
No reason
You're cheating me right?
You're not studying French
Say something in French
No, I don't want to　-Say something!
Say something!
When I see you smiling together
deep emotion
I was afraid of my love
What does that mean?
It means that
this shirt is hand-wash-only
"J'avispais mon amour".It means
you should wash the shirt by hand..
I'm not fooled
Stop it
Please Stop
Stop
Stop it!
Don't touch it
Stop it
Voila!
How do I look?
Pardon?
I said, How do I look?
You look.. great
I think so　-You look great
The recycled ripped jeans...
They seem eco-friendly and
functional as well with good ventilation
You could be close to mosquitoes
You, all
Have a death wish or something?
Suhyun, can you grab this end　-Yes
Hey
Let's all move to Seoul
No
Why would you move to Seoul
all of a sudden?
It's just boring here
and
I feel like I've completely
wasted the summer break
we're in high school
But you, guys, always do
By the way, What's up with the school
uniform even during the summer break?
It attracts more viewers
Ah...
Ah! it's annoying
Ah! Really...
Minhee, what's the matter?
Minhee　-Minhee
Are you mad at us?
You need a lot of money
to move to and live in Seoul
Minhee
Minhee..
I'm hungry
Uh?
Shall I make some ramen for you?
All right
-You don't have any ramen at home?
-Yes, Done
-I'll come with you to the store
-No, you can stay
You are moving up to Seoul, right?
Where did you hear that?
I heard my mom and your mom
talking on the phone
They said you are planning on
going to college in Seoul
Traitor!
I'm not moving
Why not?
you, guys, are staying
I can't move up there by myself
Hey, but...
I don't think your mom
would let you stay here
If you don't go to college,
Your mom might fall again
I don't know
Let's talk on the subject
for another time
I'm so hungry I can't think of anything
what are you doing?
You!
Uh?
You..
Remember you cracked my mobile screen,
And you promised
you would make up for it?
So?
Dance with me during the festival
You're to be my dance partner
No
You promised!
It's not going to happen
Hey!
I've already said on my show that
I am going to dance with you
You shouldn't have
You promised, Come on
Come on　-No way
Dance with me!　-No way, no way
Please, please
How do I do it
Place your right hand
on my left shoulder blade
And you firmly hold my hand
with your left hand
Firmly?
You don't let go of it
Ready?
I should get going
I need to my online show
Bye
Where are you going?
Home
I just bought ramen
Uh..
Thanks anyway
Good bye
I liked it
Guys!
Isn't it such a wonderful day?
Don't be surprised
Really...
I am..
I am no longer... Single!
Congratulations! Yeah!
There is this friend whom I have been
very fond of for long
He says..
To me...
something to tell me and has asked me
to meet him at the park
Is my make-up all right?
I'm not cheating you
He is going
to confess his feelings for me
And you, all are going to watch it
happening live here on my cam
Watch it!
You've waited long?
No, I just got here
Do you want a drink?
How thoughtful!
Thanks
It's a little awkward, isn't it?
If you have something to tell me,
I'm ready
Minhee　-Yes
About what happened yesterday,
Let's just forget that it ever happened
Pardon?
You are..
You're a popular and
probably the kiss means nothing to you,
But I just wanted to make it sure
Of course..
Yeah,
I'm fine
And I already have someone that I like
Is that so?
Yeah
Who?
It's someone that you already know
Suhyun...
We're still good friends, right?
I need to get going
Minhee
Can you keep it just between us?
Does...
Does He knows that you love him?
No
It's probably better that way
What do you mean?
Don't ever tell him
You just keep it to yourself
I will
We are,
still good, right?
Yeah
Yeah..
I'll go first
Hello Mrs Lee..
Is Jaenam there?
He has been out of contact lately
Jaenam?
He has moved to Seoul
He needs to focus on
getting into college
By any chance,
You've watched that broadcast?
You know Jaenam likes to make jokes
So You..Don't mind what he said
on that broadcast
You're a smart kid,
You understand what I am saying, right?
How have you been?
Fine
Are you mad at me?
No
Have you seen Jaenam lately?
He has already left for Seoul
Right
He is leaving today
I've been meaning to tell you
that I'm so sorry..　-Today?
Uh?
Yes, today
I thought you already knew
Jaenam...
is leaving for Seoul today
Yes,
We're leaving now
Okay, leaving
Jaenam
"Me, too"
What are you doing?
Are we leaving right away?
Yes, we are
I'll be right back
Where? I've got no time
Let's go, Jaenam
-I'll be right back
-Where are you suddenly going?
I don't want to hear it　-Let's go
Jaenam
Are you going to piss me off?
Your dad is waiting
Let's go, Jaenam
Quick
Jaenam　-I'll be back, mom
I'll be back soon　-Jaenam!