It's here, the final episode.
-Wow.
-Already?
-Didn't the time just fly by?
-[Eun-ji] Seriously.
-Time flies when you're having fun.
-Hey, but up until the end,
with Ji-su and that whole thing…
-What'll we do about Seung-li and Ji-su?
-[Eun-ji] Why, God?
I was sure that we'd have two couples
by the end of the show,
-but I don't know anymore.
-Right, right.
If you think about it,
there's really one day left
-until final choice.
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
I'm worried about what'll happen
with Ji-su and Seung-li,
because Seung-li didn't remember
-that really intense story Ji-su told him.
-Right. Exactly.
I'm worried that incident
will have a big impact on Ji-su
and things will get all shaken up again.
[enchanting music playing]
[birds chirping]
-[In-guk] Why am I only seeing one person?
-[Han-na] What? They slept separately?
[Ji-yeon] Are you awake?
-They're in the same bed!
-What? Hey!
[Car] What is this? What's going on?
-Wait, they were on top of each other?
-[Car] God, I can't believe it.
[Han-na] What?
I thought that was one person.
[pleasant music playing]
[Ji-yeon] Are you awake?
[Eun-ji] Oh, my gosh,
oh, my gosh, oh, my gosh!
Let's get up now. Sit up.
DID ANYTHING HAPPEN LAST NIGHT
BETWEEN YOU TWO?
That looks pretty.
That's a secret.
I'll let you imagine.
[Jeong-mok] I hope we all
have dinner together tonight.
[Ji-yeon] Totally.
I think it'd be nice
to cook for ourselves,
since it's the last dinner.
Like when we opened up the tent bar.
That was delicious.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Thanks. I'll make you tons of great food.
-[Han-na gasps] What?!
[Ji-yeon] Mmm.
-[Jeong-mok] I can't wait.
-Okay.
That was nothing
compared to some of the stuff I can make.
-[Jeong-mok] Really?
-Yeah.
[Car] Things really progressed.
[Ji-yeon] Oh, right.
We haven't written in the guest log.
[music fades]
-[Jeong-mok] Oh, the guest log. Right.
-Yeah.
What should I write?
[mellow guitar music playing]
Whatever you want.
-[Cupids gasp]
-[In-guk] What?
-[Han-na] They're so sweet to each other.
-[Eun-ji] What is this?
Wait, you're…
you're writing
almost the same thing as me.
-Really?
-Yeah.
No way!
I LOVE YOU, JEONG-MOK
LET'S COME BACK HERE AGAIN
[Han-na] Oh, "I love you, Jeong-mok."
[Car] Whoa, "I love you"? That was fast.
[Ji-yeon] Wanna check out
the back before we go?
[Jeong-mok] Yeah, let's go!
[pleasant guitar music playing]
[Jeong-mok] We were sitting
on the swing in the backyard.
The view was so pretty,
the weather was great.
It was such a memorable moment.
My heart felt so full
after our overnight date.
We had a little barbecue…
[inaudible]
…we sat by the fire,
and I got to know her better.
It was really nice.
I felt more and more sure of my feelings.
She's the one.
I feel like I can experience
new things with Jeong-mok.
And that makes me really happy.
I keep thinking to myself,
"How did I end up liking someone so much?"
[inaudible]
I'm really surprised.
[music ends]
Like, I think these two could start
looking for wedding venues right now.
-Seriously. We should be the MCs. Yeah.
-[In-guk] Oh, I like that.
I'll sing "My Baby U" for them.
-Do the dance too though.
-Of course.
-You can't forget the dance.
-Obviously.
[Min-hong] I mean… God, how do I put it?
I honestly thought
he was gonna ask me and Do
for, like, five minutes each,
and then…
[pensive music playing]
Did you think he'd tell you?
I thought he'd tell us, yeah.
He didn't?
-I guess he didn't. We were together.
-He didn't.
We were in that Lounge together.
So I just…
I mean, I'm just annoyed with him.
Seriously. You told him
you were waiting for an answer,
but he just went off to have fun.
Yeah, I mean, he felt bad,
so he didn't wanna tell me.
He kept avoiding me and then just left.
I feel like, ugh…
-He's being such a pathetic loser.
-Yeah.
I mean, yeah, such a loser.
Is it so hard to spit it out?
I get that it's hard, I know it is,
but… just do it, you know?
At this rate, he'll talk to you
five minutes before final choice.
If he does at all.
Will you talk to Jeong-mok once he's back?
I wanna wait and see.
-If he asks you to talk?
-Yeah.
-Exactly, he might not even say anything.
-Seriously, it isn't right. It's not okay.
[music fades]
[breezy music playing]
-[Ji-yeon] I don't wanna go back.
-[Jeong-mok] Me neither.
I don't want to leave.
Why can't we stay here?
I refuse to go.
[Han-na] These two
are so in their own world.
This trip…
it was one of the happiest days
in my whole life.
-[turn signal clicking]
-Agreed.
It was a happy excursion.
I had so much fun.
[Ji-yeon] Guys, we're back.
Oh, don't do that. Don't do that.
-Don't gloat about it.
-[Han-na] Don't rub it in.
-Please, guys, hide how happy you are.
-[Car] Yeah.
[music fades]
[Do crying softly]
[continues crying]
[Do] I cried…
[gentle poignant music playing]
Why am I crying right now?
Am I sad about this?
Wow, I must've liked him
more than I'd realized.
[continues crying]
[sighing wistfully]
[Ji-yeon] Newsletter?
[Hyun-kyu] This could be
the last newsletter, right?
Oh, wait, what does it say?
What?
What is this?
[upbeat music playing]
It's a "let-it-out date."
A let-it-out date?
[Yeo-myung] "If you have something
you feel the need to express,
lingering feelings or any last words,
please sign up via text."
Oh, because it's the last day?
Yeah, they should say what they wanna say.
-They should.
-It's the perfect time.
-Hmm.
-[Han-na] Their last chance.
Maybe I should…
Oh, you should, you should.
Do we just have to send a text?
[wistful music playing]
[Min-hong] I requested
to talk to Jeong-mok
because I think we need closure.
The feelings I've felt
while I've been here,
especially the bad ones,
I want to leave them in Jeju.
In this room, before I leave.
I think this experience
was almost like a dream.
Just a dream.
I think I signed up so I could do it
and then just leave it
behind me and move on.
[wistful music continues]
-[Jeong-mok] Min-hong came to mind.
-[Han-na] Oh, Jeong-mok too?
Well, with Min-hong it didn't really…
It doesn't feel like we had any closure.
That thought kept nagging at me.
I thought,
"I should have a final talk
with Min-hong today."
[Han-na] Oh, Jeong-mok
was worried about it too.
[inhales]
[sighs deeply]
-[In-guk] Oh, no, our dear sweet Do.
-[Han-na] What'll she do?
[Do] "Let-it-out date."
"Let…"
[Do] At first, I wasn't gonna do it.
But then, I realized that
I only want to see Jeong-mok
while I'm here in Jeju.
It'll be too hard
to see him again in Seoul.
So I signed up and thought to myself,
"Let's have one last
one-on-one date together."
[Han-na] Oh, she still did it.
She's gonna talk to him.
You signed up?
I haven't yet, no.
-[Hyun-kyu] You should.
-Did you?
-Hey, sign up.
-[Seung-li] Okay.
-Who'll you ask for?
-[Sang-ho] We should.
Sign up. Sign up.
[Hyun-kyu] "Should I do this or not?"
I kept thinking it over, but then I saw
that my fingers
had already typed out the text.
So, like, because it's our last chance…
[solemn music playing]
I knew it wouldn't happen, but I just…
I just wanted to hold onto something.
If I'm not her type, then that's fine,
but maybe she still feels
some sort of affection for me,
just not the way I do for her.
SEUNG-LI, JI-SU
[Seung-li] I asked to talk to Ji-su.
I thought a one-on-one chat
might help clear things up between us.
So, yesterday,
we were talking on the terrace.
But he didn't remember
what we talked about on our date.
I got so pissed off.
[Seung-li] What did you say…
What did you talk about
in your pre-interview?
Are you serious?
You forgot.
Ji-su, come on. I don't want to mess up.
[Han-na] That wasn't
a casual conversation.
[Eun-ji] It was a really serious,
deep discussion.
-What?
-[Min-hong] Oh, I'm not sure.
I can't sign up for this
and then go and be like,
"I'm so pissed you got drunk
and didn't remember anything."
Yeah, in the middle of a nice cafe date.
But, Seung-li…
I mean…
He could've responded that way
because he just panicked.
I just need to say these things
to let my anger out.
[chuckles]
It seems like she wants to tell him off.
-Oof, how are they gonna resolve this?
-[Han-na] Oh, my gosh.
-[serene music playing]
-[birds chirping]
[camera shutter clicks]
How pretty.
-[Han-na] Hyun-kyu!
-[Eun-ji] It's Hyun-kyu.
[chuckles softly]
[chuckles] Oh.
I made you wait in the heat.
Don't I always make you wait?
Not at all.
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I am. Of course.
Are you surprised?
No, 'cause I asked for you.
-[chuckles] Oh, really?
-Yeah.
[Han-na] Ji-su asked for Hyun-kyu too.
[Eun-ji] They chose each other.
You gotta show her your sweet
and sensitive side, Hyun-kyu.
[music fades]
How are you?
We've been together this whole time,
but we haven't really talked.
Right. I've been fine.
Good.
How have these last days been for you?
-I've just been thinking a lot.
-Hmm.
I read the letter you sent me.
You read it?
Yeah.
I'm so relieved to hear that.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Yeah.
"I don't want to say
something wrong here."
"But you know who I am now."
"I might seem a little robotic and stiff."
"Like someone
who only cares about efficiency."
-Oh, did you write something for this?
-I didn't wanna make mistakes,
-so I planned this out.
-[Han-na] He wrote things on his phone.
But this is a very peaceful space.
There are all these people taking walks,
-the weather is so beautiful today.
-Yeah.
So let's only say good things.
-Only good things?
-Yeah.
[amusing music playing]
-[chuckles] What's wrong?
-No, that's fine. You're right.
-You look so sad.
-You're right.
-Let's skip this thing I wrote.
-Yeah.
-We can skip it?
Just tell me. Did I do something wrong?
No.
Then it's okay.
-It's fine.
-Yeah.
I do regret something.
You said it sometimes
seemed like we were the same age,
-but then other times…
-Yeah.
-…it seemed like I was younger.
-Mmm.
And that sometimes
you felt like you were my age,
but sometimes you felt older.
But I never made you feel like
I was the older one
and you were the younger one.
I regret not doing that.
Would it have been different
if we'd had more time?
I'm not trying to give you
false hope, by the way.
-Could you, just a little?
-[laughs]
-Leave it open.
-Leave it open?
Even after this show is done,
I have a lot of time.
Ah…
I see. [chuckles]
I mean, we kind of know
how it would go, but…
[wistful music playing]
Hey, don't. Don't do that.
No, you don't need it.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
-How would it go?
-I was feeling stupid
for holding onto a sliver of hope
after everything.
But… at the same time,
I'm glad I still get to feel this way,
and… I've fully expressed my feelings
to you, so I have no regrets.
So,
you can give me hope.
[chuckles softly]
[laughs]
You know, like,
people usually start dancing
when they're a kid.
-Mm-hmm.
-If you start when you're young,
you can learn a bit more easily.
Right.
So maybe we couldn't communicate well
because we're learning
everything too late.
-Like dating.
-Yeah.
We're already too set in our ways.
I think I'm the type of person
who changes gradually.
-Oh, really?
-Without losing my identity.
[exhales] If we were
in the same class in school,
we would've sat next to each other.
-But I went to an all-girls school.
-Oh, that's right.
[Ji-su chuckles]
-And you're from Seoul…
-Just a hypothetical--
…and I'm from Ulsan.
-Ji-su keeps…
-[Han-na] Mmm.
…blocking him.
It's a wall. A wall you can't climb over.
-A thick wall…
-She's trying not to give him hope.
[Han-na] Right.
So us meeting each other here
was destiny, in a way.
We didn't know we'd meet on this show
like this.
-So it's a shame.
-But if we had met earlier,
we wouldn't have talked like this.
You were always studying,
and I was a student-athlete.
-You're right.
-Yeah.
-So, meeting each other here, like this…
…could've been our lucky chance.
[wistful music continues]
How sad.
It is.
-Mm. You okay?
-[cell phone chimes]
YOUR DATE HAS ENDED
[clicks tongue] Uh, yeah.
I'm sad. [inhales deeply]
Anyway…
I liked you so much, you won my heart.
-Mmm.
-You won my heart.
And I think I'll always
be grateful for that.
So, I wish you happiness.
I really liked you, Kang Ji-su.
-[Eun-ji and Han-na screaming]
-[Car laughs]
Ahhh! My Gosh!
-[In-guk] Where can I hide?
-Wow!
-I'll see you…
-[Han-na] Oh, my gosh.
-…on my Instagram Explore page.
-[Han-na] Please, Hyun-kyu.
Kang Hyun-kyu. 26 years old.
Come on my YouTube channel.
[Eun-ji laughs]
Let's have you do
an Avatar Blind Date, man.
No, you can't even pretend to do that.
[chuckles]
I really liked you, Kang Ji-su.
[sweeping wistful music playing]
Someone might think
-we dated for several years.
-[Car laughs]
That's how it felt for me.
-It was so long.
-Really?
I'll look you up later.
I'll be waiting.
Don't… don't wait for me.
It's too much pressure.
Just deal with it.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
You just go and have fun.
Okay.
-[wolf whistle blows]
-[Car laughs]
[music fades]
[sighing] Oh, gosh.
[sighs wearily]
-That was really intense.
-[Car] Wow.
-"I liked you, Kang Ji-su."
-Wow.
-"Kang Ji-su!" He just put it out there.
Man, Hyun-kyu
was so beautifully honest with her.
That's why it's "let-it-out date."
-He definitely let it out.
-Sure did.
I wanna let something out now.
-I kind of… I feel embarrassed for him.
-[Han-na] I think he did really well.
[Eun-ji] Yeah, you have
second-hand embarrassment.
When Hyun-kyu sees this,
he'll have to let it out again.
[Han-na laughs]
[mellow music playing]
BY CHANCE
[Car] Ah.
She's making a statement
with her hair up like that.
Does that mean she changed her mind?
"I'll say what I wanna say.
No holding back."
LET-IT-OUT DATE
MIN-HONG & JEONG-MOK
Hi.
Have fun yesterday?
-Yeah, I did.
-Good.
[chuckles softly]
[cell phone chimes]
-[Car] Oh, they requested each other.
-[In-guk] Right, Jeong-mok knew too.
I also… requested you.
-Huh?
-To talk.
Oh.
Yeah, I mean,
it's good to wrap things up neatly.
-[music fades]
-[clicks tongue]
And this isn't anything serious, is it?
-So, to tell you the truth…
-Yeah?
…you were the only one
I had my eye on here.
Because good communication
is important to me,
and I thought you did that well.
-But then, when we went to the sheep farm…
-Yeah.
…I asked you about it.
[solemn music playing]
-Am I, um…
-Hmm.
-Am I even in the running for you?
-Hmm?
At this point… [inhales]
are you considering me?
I am considering you.
Is it possible you won't know today,
tomorrow, or even the day after?
I don't know when, uh,
when I'll know for sure.
[music fades]
But to be honest, I knew that
I wasn't the one you were thinking about.
[Jae-yun] Before, Jeong-mok…
His top choice, it's Do.
And his second choice,
it changed to Ji-yeon.
-[breathes deeply]
-[solemn music playing]
Mmm.
I mean, maybe I was, but barely.
So I asked you, but you kept saying,
"I won't know tomorrow
or even the day after."
"I just don't know."
I really liked you as a person,
but as a guy,
you were going down in my estimation
-because of that. So…
-Okay.
I was kind of hoping you'd tell me
before going on your overnight date.
So, in the end, I was sort of
disappointed in you as a person too.
And I was really disappointed in you,
as a guy, for doing that.
That's how I felt, but despite that,
Ji-yeon is still someone
who I've really gotten close to here,
as a friend.
And now, I guess you're just someone
I used to have a crush on.
[chuckles softly]
[inhales]
Well…
[music fades]
So I just thought,
"I hope they have a lot of fun together."
"I hope they're not worried about me."
She's so cool.
She said she'd tell him off,
but in the end, she didn't.
[Han-na and Eun-ji exclaim]
There's nothing more to discuss.
We… we came here to be happy.
Thank you.
[Jeong-mok] There wasn't much
left for me to say.
She already knew what I would say.
And I know I should've told her earlier.
I was thinking, "She must've resented me."
"I should've told her earlier."
I felt bad about that.
Great.
-Good luck.
-[chuckles softly]
I'll root for you.
I'll sincerely root for you.
Thank you for being
honest with me, Min-hong.
[resolute music playing]
[Min-hong] In my opinion,
the people on other dating shows,
like Single's Inferno,
are like ceramics,
they're fixed and solid.
But we're not ceramics, we're clay.
We're in our early, mid,
and late twenties,
but we didn't do the things we should've
in our early twenties or teens.
While on this show,
I was able to get a sense of what I like,
what kind of relationship I want,
and what kind of person I want.
So that's enough.
So I think I can leave
everything behind me here,
without any regrets.
-[In-guk] Hmm. She's seriously so cool.
-[Eun-ji] Good job.
-She really is.
-Totally.
I didn't know Min-hong
would open up this much.
[Eun-ji] That was so nice.
Min-hong is
a pretty straightforward person.
-Yeah.
-[Eun-ji] Yep.
Some people could think
she's too aggressive,
but actually, she's really considerate.
Right.
And it must've been hard for her
after getting hurt by Jeong-mok,
-but she's cheering on this couple…
-[In-guk] Mmm.
-…that's beginning their relationship.
-Right.
-She really is so considerate.
And listening to Min-hong…
Jeong-mok obviously knew
what he did wrong before…
-[Han-na] Yeah, he knows.
-…and he certainly knows now.
-Also, he seems to feel it himself.
-True.
-Like, "I kind of regret that."
-[Han-na] Right.
-Isn't she the coolest?
-[Han-na] Yeah.
-Min-hong will be popular when this airs.
-Yes, Min-hong…
-She's such a charming person. Yes.
-People are gonna be lining up for her.
-[gentle sentimental music playing]
-[sniffles]
Watch your head.
Thank you.
Hi.
LET-IT-OUT DATE
JEONG-MOK & DO
How have you been?
Good.
My heart felt a little heavy.
But… I can't really let that show,
because it must be
harder for her than it is for me.
What should I drink?
Should I?
-Oh, if we wait, they'll probably…
-What?
-Will they come?
-Yeah.
-So…
-You've been here a while?
Yeah.
-If you have something you wanna say…
-Mm-hmm.
-…maybe you should go first.
-Yeah, I will.
Mmm. [clicks tongue]
-Okay. I think that'd be best.
-Mmm.
Right.
How should I put it?
-We promised not to say sorry.
-[chuckles]
Good.
Thanks.
[gentle solemn music playing]
Looking at you, mmm,
not solely in a romantic way…
I thought you were cool, I sincerely did.
-Out of all of the people here…
-Really?
-…you were one of the coolest.
-Yeah.
-What about me?
You work really hard.
Mmm.
You challenge things.
You're passionate.
I don't think I've ever been like that,
-so I admire you.
-[chuckles softly]
You make me want to be better.
-Really? [chuckles]
-Yeah.
I feel like I should be more proactive
and work hard like Do.
-Mmm.
-I've really thought about that a lot.
[Jeong-mok] Hmm. [inhales softly]
I just want you to know
that you're a very attractive person.
Thank you.
[both chuckle]
Are we being way too serious?
-I'll be even more serious.
-Too serious?
-Really?
-Let me know when you're ready.
-[laughs]
-[inhales sharply]
[exhales sharply, inhales]
-[Do] Mmm.
-Mmm.
[smacks lips] I…
-[Jeong-mok] Mmm?
-[music fades]
First…
[Do] Mmm…
-You're still…
-Mmm.
…it for me.
Mm-hmm.
So, I wanted to tell you that.
[sentimental music playing]
[smacks lips, chuckles softly]
This was a short period of time.
-Right.
-But I ended up…
[sighs softly]
liking you…
a lot more than I expected.
So I'm really sad.
And to be completely honest with you…
When I told you what I liked about you,
you said, "Oh, I didn't know
I'd become the popular guy."
[chuckles] Yeah.
-I thought this could help.
-Mmm.
So I wanted to tell you.
Up until our date on Day 3,
I have to admit that
I was actually more attracted
to Seung-li than you.
But I knew that Seung-li
wasn't interested in me at all.
-Yeah, but--
-And I was really sad about that.
-It seems like, usually…
-Right.
-…the person I'm interested in…
-I see.
…isn't interested in me.
So I was really sad and upset…
and frustrated about that.
But then you and I
had that spot date in the evening.
-It was a random date too.
-Yeah.
You got me twice.
-Yeah, it was great.
-Mmm.
[Do] Be good, Jeong-mok.
[music subsides]
[chuckles]
[music resumes]
Again?
-Oh, you're here again?
-We're matched again. [chuckles]
Wow. I mean, what is this?
-We didn't have time to talk until now…
-I know.
-…so should I get everything out?
-Mmm.
I was shocked just now.
If you get to choose
your date partner tomorrow,
-like we did today…
-Yeah.
…who would you choose?
I'll choose you, of course.
-Why?
-What?
I wanted to date you from the beginning.
-Really?
-Yeah.
And then,
during that date…
you expressed to me
that you were interested in me,
romantically.
So…
I…
[sentimental music continues]
Mmm…
[inhales]
Hold on.
Hey, I cry if I see someone else cry.
[both chuckle]
But I…
[music fades]
[voice breaking] So, at the time,
I thought…
[Do sniffles]
[inhales]
[sighs]
-You okay?
-Yeah.
-I thought…
-Yeah?
[inhales]
"Is this destiny?"
I let myself think it was.
[wistful music playing]
So I got really excited.
So, thank you for picking me…
Of course.
…when it was the guys' turn to pick.
-[Do sniffles]
-[exhales]
[sniffles]
-I'm okay.
-Really?
I'm okay.
[chuckles]
[sniffles]
[tearfully] I'm okay.
[sniffles] So…
Well…
[breath trembling]
Hmm…
[sniffles]
So…
I've never really
gone on a date with… someone…
[music fades]
…who actually liked me back.
[sniffles softly]
So that made me really happy.
-[nostalgic music playing]
-[inhales]
[Jeong-mok] Oh.
I was going to put this in the mailbox,
-but I'll just give it to you now.
-For me?
-Yeah. I'll give it to you now.
-This?
-Open it later. Don't open it now.
-Not right now?
[Seung-li] Oh, it's so hot here.
-Right. Why is it so hot?
-How long will this take?
-[Seung-li] I'm gonna wait in my room.
-You want to come to our room?
-Bye.
-[Jeong-mok] I'll wait with you.
[indistinct chatter]
As for your school… [inhales sharply]
I'll come over often.
My school? Ah.
Isn't it too far?
I should still go.
[chuckles]
Wow!
[Jeong-mok] What?
-[Do] Yeah!
-[Yeo-myung] What was that?
[nostalgic music continues]
It didn't work out for us in the end,
but those moments we shared this week
will stay with me as beautiful memories.
[Do] Mmm. [sniffles]
[Do sighs]
Especially because…
it was you, Jeong-mok.
Mmm.
[chuckles]
I wasn't gonna cry.
[sniffles]
-[giggles]
-[music fades]
[inhales]
I…
I'm not cool.
[Do chuckles]
-So I think…
-Mm-hmm?
-…this will be the last conversation…
-Yeah.
…I ever have with you.
We won't see each other in Seoul.
Mmm.
[sweeping sentimental music playing]
Take care.
-[sniffles]
-Take care.
Take care of yourself, Do.
I will.
[cell phone chimes]
YOUR DATE HAS ENDED
[Do sniffles]
[chair scrapes]
[sighs]
[sighs softly]
[music fades]
[Han-na sighs heavily]
-Right now, they're experiencing feelings…
-[Han-na] Yeah.
-…that you can't quite put into words.
-Right.
For Do, their relationship abruptly ended
right when she was starting
to really like Jeong-mok.
-Right.
-[Car] True.
That must've made it even harder.
-Do's feelings for him were this big.
-[Han-na] Right.
-Then she suddenly got cut off from him.
-[Car] Damn.
-That must've been so tough…
-Right.
…especially 'cause her roommate
-was Ji-yeon.
-It was Ji-yeon.
Right, so she'd see them
after their dates.
-So hard.
-Must've been unbearable for Do.
Yeah, and for Jeong-mok,
his feelings changed
while he was getting to know her.
So I totally get how they both feel,
and I just feel so bad for them.
But I think
it was such a beautiful ending.
Instead of saying, "You did this wrong
and you did that wrong,"
-it was constructive.
-[In-guk] Right.
-It was a good ending.
-Exactly.
-I couldn't have said it like that.
-Me neither.
-"I liked you. You said you liked me."
-[laughs]
-You suddenly… Yeah, yeah, seriously.
-This guy is ridiculous.
"Hey, did I do something?"
-Right."Are you playing with me?"
-[Car] "You said you liked me."
[both laugh]
Honestly, it was a beautiful scene,
but it was a little bit ridiculous.
It was.
For Do, he said he liked her first.
-[Han-na] I get that.
-Now he's saying something else.
And Do is just like, "I'm gonna
be myself," like what she always says.
-[Eun-ji] She has high self-esteem.
-She does.
-And she tries very hard to protect that.
-Mmm.
And Do even let some of that go,
-so she could open up her heart…
-[Eun-ji] Of course.
…but it didn't work out.
I think she must have been pretty upset.
[Seung-li] It's Ji-su.
[Ji-su] Of course. Who else?
[Han-na] Seung-li, Ji-su.
-Did you ask for me?
-Yeah.
-[Car] She still looks mad.
-[Han-na] Yeah, she does seem a bit angry.
It's a let-it-out date,
so say what you want.
-If you're upset, go ahead and say so.
-I'm not upset about anything.
You're not?
I really liked our conversation yesterday.
It was very impactful.
What?
He liked it?
He's really bad at reading the room.
Seung-li, get it together.
I think we said all there was to say.
-Oh, really?
-Is there more you wanted to say?
[mellow contemplative music playing]
Do you only want to hear
positive things right now?
Or do you want to hear my honest thoughts?
-Honest thoughts.
-Honest thoughts?
-I was irritated.
-Why?
-[scoffs]
-Because I left?
No.
You didn't remember
what I told you during our secret date.
That… that made me mad.
-[scoffs softly]
-No, I did remember.
Really? Then tell me. You're sober,
so you probably remember now.
-There was a lot of information, so--
-What did I say during our secret date?
I mentioned why I was looking
for a certain kind of person. [scoffs]
[inhales] Yeah, a very selfish person--
-Not that.
-Not that?
Who didn't pressure you…
Nope. [scoffs]
And that you needed time to think.
No.
There was just a lot.
You should be thankful
I'm wearing sneakers instead of slippers.
If I had slippers on,
I would've thrown them at you.
I'll think of it by this evening then.
Oh, forget it.
[tense music playing]
-Come on, just say you're really sorry.
-Yeah. Saying sorry is the right response.
I clearly told you that,
when I was young,
I… was a victim of somebody stalking me.
And that I didn't like
being the center of gossip,
and that it scares me
when people are standing behind me.
-Yeah.
-That took a lot of courage for me to say.
I usually don't even
talk to my close friends about that.
But… I told you, so you could be aware,
and you didn't remember it.
So I thought,
"Why am I talking to a drunk about this?"
[pensive music playing]
That was my fault, my bad.
I seem mellower now,
but I was really upset.
You must've been.
I could tell you were really upset.
[Ji-su] Mmm.
-So, I did mess up yesterday.
-Yeah.
[Ji-su] It made me like him less.
He said he messed up.
Will Seung-li's indifferent attitude
and my sensitive personality
mesh well? I'm not sure.
Because I was
already wavering at that point.
Did you request someone else too?
-Hyun-kyu.
-Really?
-[music fades]
-[Seung-li] Hmm.
[gulps] How was it?
Well… [sighs]
we were going to talk about
how we really felt,
but then we said,
"Let's only talk about good things."
-Mmm.
-So we did.
I get that.
Hyun-kyu is a good person.
Yeah, he is.
He might be different
in a romantic context.
-He's good in a romantic sense too.
-Mm-hmm.
-Right.
-If it was some random person,
I wouldn't feel bad turning them down.
Like, who cares if they cry?
But I liked him, so it did hurt.
[inhales]
Mmm.
Hmm.
[Seung-li] Hyun-kyu was there before me.
It didn't bother me that much.
I only thought, "What can I do for Ji-su?"
I was focused on myself.
But she's not liking it, Seung-li.
Please do better.
[Seung-li] I promise I'll remember it now.
[Ji-su] I can't trust you.
[quirky music playing]
-You're going to your room?
-I'm going to the Lounge.
-Then I'm going to my room.
-Seriously?
You're running away? That makes me sad.
Ugh, you're making me mad.
[chuckles]
[Seung-li hums cheerfully]
-Come on, Seung-li!
-[Car] Why is he so happy?
I don't think this is gonna work out.
"Ddururu." It's not the time for that.
Oh, is it because he hasn't dated before?
Since he's always been around guy friends,
he didn't really have to listen
to what they were saying.
And some people
really don't remember stuff.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
-[Car] Like, I have a friend
who can't remember things that
other people would normally remember,
regardless of the level of importance.
-I think he's really similar.
-[Eun-ji and Han-na] Oh.
But it doesn't mean
that he doesn't like that person.
-Right, right.
-He's thinking, "Is that important?"
"I just like this girl."
-That's his thought process.
-He is that type of person.
But the issue is that this wasn't just
any story she was telling him.
-It was serious.
-Normally, it'd be okay.
If it weren't, she'd be like, "It's okay.
Who cares if you remember or not."
"That's just how you are."
She might say that.
But she shared an important secret
that really mattered to her…
-Right.
-…and he couldn't remember it.
I think that's why she got mad.
-[Han-na] Right.
-He was the polar opposite of Hyun-kyu.
-Yeah, they're totally different.
-Hyun-kyu, yes… Hyun-kyu makes me say,
-"Wow, that far?"
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
-He has so much intense affection for her.
-Right, right.
-And Seung-li is a bit too indifferent.
-[Eun-ji] Agreed.
Okay, say they're
the last two people on Earth.
Which type would you two date?
Seung-li, Hyun-kyu?
I don't have to think about it.
-[In-guk] Oh.
-I'd pick Hyun-kyu.
-[gasps]
-[In-guk] Oh, really?
Even if they can be awkward,
I always prefer kind and sincere people.
"I liked you, Kang Han-na!"
Even if he says that?
-Hyun-kyu would be like this.
-No.
When Han-na is at a film shoot, Hyun-kyu…
-[amusing music playing]
-[laughter]
Look! He crossed his legs!
-Oh, my God, you crossed your legs!
-Han-na.
It's so cute because you can feel
how sincere he is.
-Assuming he's also a kind person.
-But, like, if you're on a shoot…
-Yeah.
-…and then he drives up in a coffee truck…
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Rolls down the window and says,
"I love you, Kang Han-na!"
-Can you handle that?
-No.
-Everyone's looking at you standing still.
-[Han-na] No, I can't handle that.
-The last…
-[both laughing]
And you're reading your script,
and he quietly comes over.
"I didn't know what you'd like to drink…"
-Wow! That's pretty good.
-The way he talks…
-"I have adlay tea but…"
-Just listening to that, I feel a little…
Wow, that's just like him.
But if they're the only two guys
left on Earth…
-With someone like Hyun-kyu…
-Yeah.
-…at least you can talk to him.
-[Eun-ji] I agree.
He could actually
fix some things about himself.
-[Eun-ji] Right.
-But I feel Seung-li
is just too indifferent about everything.
[laughs]
Seung-li probably
wouldn't notice if you left.
Yeah, whether I'm away on a film shoot,
if I'm off meeting friends,
-he wouldn't notice.
-"What drama?"
-[Han-na] "Is it a movie or a TV drama?"
-And… "Ddururu." "Guys, come to my place."
-Even after months of filming.
-"Ddururu." Nice!
-And he'd keep being competitive.
-[Car] Mmm.
If I had to choose,
I'd definitely choose Hyun-kyu.
-[Car] Mmm.
-I'd definitely choose Seung-li.
[Han-na] Seung-li?
-You're so consistent. Why pick him?
-Yes, I'm consistent, yes.
So, with Seung-li,
I think he could improve.
If you tell him,
"Why don't you remember that?"
"That really bothers me,
try to remember next time."
-He'd change. He's a simple guy.
-"Yes, sir!" Like that.
He'd be like, "Yes, sir!"
-No, he'd just forget.
-He'd be more comfortable to date.
-Wow, we're totally divided on this.
-Yeah, yeah.
-[cell phone chimes]
-[Sang-ho] You got that?
-[Car] The last Eternal Singles' Night.
-[cell phone chimes]
-[Do] Oh, a message.
-A message.
[Min-hong] It's the last
Eternal Singles' Night.
[Yeo-myung] Excited?
[Min-hong] I'm excited
to see what happens.
[Yeo-myung] I'm excited, but a bit scared.
"The Night of Truth?"
Ah!
"The Night of Truth."
[chuckles] What's "The Night of Truth"?
Seriously, what truth?
[Eun-ji] "The Night of Truth,"
on the last day? I like it.
-No, no.
-I'm okay now.
-Are we playing "Tie the Clam Shells?"
-[Sang-ho] Wow.
TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT OF TRUTH
PLAY "TRUTH OR DARE"
TO HEAR EACH OTHER'S HONEST THOUGHTS
-"Choose your punishment?"
-[chuckles] Jump over the fire?
[all laughing]
-Hey, is this a circus?
-You choose someone?
THE SELECTED PERSON CHOOSES A CARD
AND ANSWERS THE QUESTION ON IT
[Sang-ho] What should it be?
[Seung-li] Pour me some… Pour some soju.
There's a punishment.
They really have to tell the truth.
-[In-guk] The truth.
-The game of truth.
They could ask questions like,
"What did you mean by that?"
Clarifying questions. Yeah, yeah.
They have to lay it all out.
[Sang-ho] No, no.
[Hyun-kyu] Who'll ask first?
Sang-ho, you should ask first.
Okay.
Uh…
-Seung-li?
-[Mi-ji] Seung-li?
-[Sang-ho] Yeah.
-No, Seung-li…
He kind of glared at you.
-I did?
-[Ji-yeon] Yeah. [chuckles]
-[Ji-yeon] Yeah.
Uh, "What do you wish
your crush would say to you?"
[laughs]
Why did you pick me?
-[all laughing]
-[mellow music playing]
-Why are you laughing?
-[Hyun-kyu] Nothing.
[Seung-chan] Oh!
It's really simple. Maybe something like,
-"Let's talk tonight."
-[Sang-ho] Oh.
Just talking to her
-is always fun.
-Great conversationalist.
-[Mi-ji] The game's starting.
-[laughter]
-[Seung-li] You always chime in.
-Yeah, seriously.
-Sang-ho.
-Oh, it's me again?
Yeah.
"What's been
the most exciting moment in Jeju?"
Oh, in Jeju,
[Ji-yeon] Here you go.
Well…
Be honest. You had fun with Ji-su.
-And Mi-ji, too.
-[Sang-ho] Mmm…
-The dinners?
-[laughter]
-[gasps]
-[Cupids laughing]
[In-guk] I knew it.
-[amusing music playing]
-[laughing]
-Drink.
-You gotta drink.
[Yeo-myung] Drink for that.
-[Mi-ji] What is this?
-Drink it all.
-Drink it and jump in there.
-[laughing]
-[Sang-ho] That's too intense.
-[laughter]
-I wanna survive this.
-[Yeo-myung laughs] To a long life.
But at least you're honest.
[chuckling] You are.
-You need to pick someone first.
-Jae-yun.
-[music fades]
-[Sang-ho coughs]
"Tell us a moment
when you lied out of kindness."
-[Mi-ji] To Jae-yun?
-A moment?
[In-guk] This is
a really good question for Jae-yun.
-What?
-To Jae-yun?
-You really picked that?
-[Seung-chan] No, to Jae-yun.
[exhales, chuckles]
Hey, that… that was good.
There was a time when I lied.
I remember,
it was the night of the secret date.
I heard that she was interested in…
someone else,
so…
[mellow music playing]
-[chuckles]
-[Ji-su] Take your time. It's okay.
I lied and I said,
"I'm actually not interested in you,
you should focus on that person."
That's cool.
-[Seung-chan] Okay. Let's move on.
-[Min-hong] I see.
[Jae-yun] I wanted to
apologize to Yeo-myung,
because I realized my lie
could've made things hard for her.
So, I kept lying.
I wish I hadn't.
Yeah.
-I felt bad about it.
-Yeah.
After that happened,
I thought about it and… I realized…
I was wrong.
I get what you're saying. [chuckles]
Thank you. You've grown a lot, I think.
-I hope so.
-[chuckles]
So we were able to talk about that.
It felt like finishing
my last… assignment.
[Mi-ji] Jae-yun.
"What's the most charming aspect
of your crush?"
-Her smile…
-[Jeong-mok] Aw.
Her sunny smile?
-[Sang-ho] Oh.
-[Mi-ji] Sunny smile?
-[Jae-yun] Yeah.
-I'm jealous.
-Wow.
-She must be very beautiful.
[Mi-ji laughs]
[Seung-chan] Nothing like a great smile.
[Jae-yun] I was
very comfortable talking to her.
She felt like a close friend.
[Yeo-myung] Oh, yeah.
Jae-yun really did grow.
And I'm glad he did.
-Yeah, he really evolved.
-[Eun-ji] Really.
-They've all grown.
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
-I can see that he's grown…
-Right.
-…a lot.
-Of course.
-[Han-na] For sure.
-Throughout this show,
Jae-yun was always dear to my heart.
-Little by little…
-Mmm.
…he kept trying to do more,
-and I felt so proud…
-[Han-na] Right.
…but also anxious
because he's so inexperienced.
He made some mistakes along the way,
but today,
I really thought, "Wow, this kid
has grown a lot." I'm so proud of him.
-[Eun-ji] Mmm.
-Mmm.
Jeong-mok.
Yep.
"Who gave the most memorable
first impression?"
-Most memorable?
-Yeah, first impression.
[Sang-ho] That's different.
[tense music playing]
-[Jeong-mok] Well… One person?
-[Mi-ji] Most memorable.
[Han-na] Neither of them
can look at Jeong-mok.
-For me, Do.
-[Mi-ji] Do?
-Pink.
-[Seung-chan] Ah, pink.
[Sang-ho] Oh…
-[Seung-chan] So obvious.
-Pink princess.
[inhales sharply]
Hmm.
[tense music continues]
[music fades]
-Jeong-mok.
-[Jeong-mok] Yeah?
"Whose book did you open first
in the 5 Minute Library?"
Mmm…
Oh, Do's.
[Han-na gasps] It's Do again.
[Car] Well, he can't lie about it.
[sentimental music playing]
I want to ask Do a question.
"If you had one last date tomorrow,
who would you pick?"
The person I'd want one last date with?
Well…
This is hard.
There are too many attractive guys.
[Do laughs]
Too many seductive guys here.
Well…
I'd pick…
Jeong-mok.
[Sang-ho] Oh.
[sentimental music rises]
[Yeo-myung] These questions…
-[Sang-ho] Choose someone.
-[Ji-su] Who hasn't gone?
[Do] For both the first impression pick
and the 5 Minute Library,
it was me.
Jeong-mok was always honest.
So I thought, "Mmm… he's a cool person."
I'm still only interested in Jeong-mok.
I'm really angry with him
for the way he's treated me,
but I still like him.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[Sang-ho coughs] Whoa.
-[Han-na] Ah.
-Wow, this is uncomfortable.
-[Han-na] Oh, no.
-It can't be helped.
-Honest feelings are uncomfortable.
-[Han-na] It's weirdly uncomfortable.
I pick…
[music fades]
Who hasn't gone?
Ji-yeon.
[paper rustles]
"Describe the person you like
in just one word."
-[Sang-ho] Huh?
-Oh.
[Seung-chan chuckles] This should be fun.
-[Yeo-myung] This question's great.
-[Hyun-kyu] This is fun.
One word? Mmm… "Comfort"?
[contestants exclaiming]
[Han-na] They're already
comfortable with each other. Mmm.
[tense music playing]
Doesn't Ji-yeon look
kind of different now?
-[laughs]
-Yeah, she does.
Kind of like Madam Jeong from Tazza.
[Car] How did Ji-yeon
suddenly become like this?
-[Han-na] "Madam Jeong." Yeah, a little.
-[Eun-ji] Right?
I mean, yeah, she does.
Oh, kind of.
You all saw it too, right?
"Do you call that a question?"
-She looks so strong.
-"You call that a question?"
I think that question
annoyed her a little bit.
-Like, "That's my man."
-[In-guk] Maybe?
-[Han-na] Like a silent warning?
-[Min-hong] I don't know.
I pick…
Jeong-mok.
[Seung-chan] Oh, hey!
[inhales sharply] "How many…
Wow.
-…people are in your heart right now?"
-[contestants exclaim]
-[Seung-chan] He's a sniper.
-[Sang-ho] Wait…
Wow, how are the questions so perfect?
[tense music playing]
Man, this is intense.
-Way to put him on the spot.
-[Hyun-kyu] If you're not honest…
[laughter]
[Sang-ho] You're good at picking these.
You're Tazza.
-[laughter]
-Just one person.
[Seung-chan] Was this planned?
-[Jeong-mok] Just one person.
-[Seung-chan] Was this planned?
-[Eun-ji] My gosh…
-[Han-na] Her smile suddenly disappeared.
[Eun-ji] Oh, no, oh, no…
[In-guk] Yeah, and Ji-yeon
is smiling right away.
[tense music continues]
-[Car] Oh!
-[Han-na gasps]
[Han-na gasps]
[Do] Hmm…
I'm just feeling really heartbroken.
Being in the same space
as them is so hard.
[tearfully] Can't they stop showing off?
[sniffles]
[cries] That's what I thought.
[tense music continues]
[In-guk sighing] Oh, no.
[Car] He needs to be clear.
-Oh, man, this is rough.
-[Eun-ji] Her heart--
Do has really gone through
a painful last three days.
-It hurts to see that.
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
-But I think they're growing pains.
-[Eun-ji] Right.
First loves are always painful.
-[Eun-ji] Yeah, they are, that's true.
-They just always are.
-Can I go?
-Yeah.
Yeah, go.
Ji-yeon and Jeong-mok are the only couple
who went on an overnight date, right?
So are you sure about each other?
Do you think, after this show,
that you two will, uh…
Are you asking both of us?
[Ji-su] Yeah.
I am.
-[Ji-su] You're certain?
-Yeah.
-[Ji-su] Jeong-mok?
-I am too.
[Mi-ji] Oh, what? Can you two just drink?
[laughter]
[indistinct chatter]
[Mi-ji] I'm jealous.
Can I ask the same question
-to Ji-su and Seung-li?
-[Sang-ho chuckles]
If I say no, will you not ask?
No, no, I still will. Are you certain…
that you two will date after the show?
Me?
[Jeong-mok] Both of you.
I am. I… I am.
Ji-su?
-Do I have to answer?
-Yeah.
[Hyun-kyu] Or you can drink.
[pensive music playing]
90% certain.
Good question.
I have a question for Hyun-kyu.
So for a while,
-we were competing with each other.
-[Hyun-kyu] Yeah.
[Seung-li] So…
Are you uncomfortable with this?
Are we cool?
[Hyun-kyu] Well…
I think yesterday
was the most uncomfortable.
Today feels…
bittersweet?
[Seung-chan] Bittersweet?
[music fades]
[Yeo-myung] Hyun-kyu…
"Who do you want to
keep in touch with after the show?"
[Do] Oh.
-Hmm…
-[Sang-ho] Oh, damn.
[indistinct chuckling]
The person I want to keep in touch with?
[inhales deeply]
[sighs heavily]
-[Yeo-myung laughs] Okay, okay.
-[Sang-ho] That question sucks.
[Mi-ji] Oh, it doesn't have to be a guy.
It doesn't.
Such an annoying question.
[Seung-chan] You said you'd keep in touch.
Oh, didn't I have to choose a girl?
-It should be a girl.
-Right, it should be a girl.
-[Hyun-kyu] With the guys… Ah…
-[sentimental music playing]
I think it could be a little uncomfortable
to hang out alone with Seung-li.
That might be a little awkward.
I want to keep in touch
with everyone else though.
And for the girls, Ji-su is the one.
[inhales]
I want her contact info,
but maybe I don't.
Because if I can see her,
then I'm not gonna
be able to stop thinking about her.
I almost think I have to stop seeing her
in order to move on and do other things.
But if, by any chance,
I still have some hope with her,
then I wanna… [exhales]
I wanna keep trying.
[sighs]
[firewood crackling]
[music fades]
I want to ask Ji-su a question.
[Hyun-kyu] Hmm.
[Hyun-kyu inhales]
You said 90% certain.
What's the other ten?
-[chuckles, sniffles]
-[others chuckling]
Wow.
-[exhales]
-[pensive music playing]
-Good question.
-[Seung-chan] Drink.
Give her a break.
-I'm gonna drink.
-[Mi-ji] Oh, okay.
[Min-hong] Yeah, drink, drink.
[grunts]
[Ji-su inhales]
[sighs sharply]
[Ji-su] Jeong-mok and Ji-yeon
said they were certain they would date
after the show was over.
I was kind of…
jealous of that.
I also… [chuckles softly]
want to meet someone I get along with.
I wanted to be able
to tell that to Seung-li,
but I couldn't bring myself to say it.
So I was a bit jealous
and a bit sad too.
I do think that Seung-li is a good person.
But, mmm…
"Is this relationship sustainable?"
That was that 10% uncertainty.
[music fades]
-[Ji-su] Can I ask a question?
-[Mi-ji] Yeah.
[chuckling] It kinda feels like
I'm digging myself into a hole,
but did you ever resent me
or regret things
because I made you wait
for so long? [cries]
No, I didn't at all.
I still had hope.
[gentle solemn music playing]
You don't hate me?
I don't hate you.
[Ji-su] You don't?
I stayed because I wanted to.
How could I hate you?
[sniffles]
-You don't resent me?
-No, I don't. Of course, I don't.
-Right. You found someone new.
-Hey, come on.
[all laughing]
"Hey, come on."
I feel the same.
Did you answer?
Me?
I don't resent her.
I don't.
[sighs]
[music fades]
[Seung-li] I don't really
understand Ji-su.
She said she was 90% certain,
not 100.
That made me worried.
Really worried.
But… I still have hope.
[slow moody music playing]
So, Seung-li has only ever gone after her,
-but seems to be getting a little tired.
-Right, right.
Because Ji-su isn't reassuring.
Right, right. Gosh, what's gonna
happen with them? [sighs]
Okay, so everyone has to stay up.
-[Jae-yun] Okay.
-[Jeong-mok] Gotta keep going.
Are you gonna contact
Ji-su after the show?
-Me?
-[Ji-yeon] Yeah.
Shouldn't I, though?
-I mean, that's why we came here.
-[Ji-yeon] You should. You like her.
[inhales] But honestly, I, uh…
I just don't know.
How she feels?
No, earlier,
she said something about 90%--
-But 90% is basically all there.
-Right.
But I know, if it were me, like,
if I'm even just 1% uncertain,
-I kind of get defensive.
-[Ji-yeon] Yeah.
-Oh.
-I said so earlier.
[Jae-yun] Oh.
[Seung-li] Yeah, I don't know.
No, I… I don't know yet.
[Han-na] Gosh.
But this is the last night
before final choice.
I'm so curious
to see what Ji-su will choose.
Because she hasn't really decided yet.
-And Seung-li is starting to get nervous.
-[In-guk] Yeah. That's hard.
I think Ji-su will choose Seung-li
or leave the show single.
Exactly. I'm getting kind of nervous.
Maybe she won't choose anyone.
-I get that feeling too.
-[Han-na] I'm worried.
[enthralling music playing]
FINAL SELECTION DAY
[Car] So, the moment has finally come.
-[Han-na] The final choice day!
-[In-guk] Oh, man.
[Eun-ji] Finally!
5 MINUTE LIBRARY
THE FINAL SELECTION
1. CHOOSE THE DIARY OF THE PERSON YOU WANT
2. OPEN TO THE LAST PAGE
3. PLACE YOUR PHOTO IN THE POCKET
4. RETURN THE DIARY AND LEAVE
[door lock buzzes]
[music fades]
[door closes]
THE FINAL SELECTION
PUT YOUR PHOTO ON THE TABLE
IF YOU HAVE NO ONE TO CHOOSE
[enchanting music playing]
JI-YEON'S DIARY
MY FUTURE BOYFRIEND WILL BE…
[Eun-ji] That's what it says
on the last page.
[Han-na] Oh, I see.
[enchanting music continues]
[exclaims excitedly]
I'm imagining the face Ji-yeon will make
when she sees that.
[Han-na] Mmm.
FINAL SELECTION
JEONG-MOK CHOOSES JI-YEON
[music fades]
[mellow music playing]
-[In-guk] Just a goodbye.
-[Eun-ji] Ah.
YI DO
FINAL SELECTION FORFEITED
[In-guk] It kind of feels like that.
"Farewell to my time in Jeju."
[Han-na] Yeah.
[door closes]
[Do] I'm sad about how things are ending,
but I have no regrets.
I had never dated anyone before,
so I had all these fantasies
and dreams about it.
But after this experience,
mmm, I realize I don't feel the need
to date just yet.
I think I'll leave that door open.
Yeah, that's what I'll do.
[music fades]
[whimsical music playing]
-[Eun-ji] Yeo-myung?
-[Car] Is she choosing?
JEONG-MOK'S DIARY, HYUN-KYU'S DIARY
[music stops]
[whimsical music resumes]
YEO-MYUNG
FINAL SELECTION FORFEITED
[door closes]
[Yeo-myung] During my time here,
I learned a lot about
what kind of person I like,
and about what's important to me.
Well, I was just most attracted to you.
You're it… for me.
I didn't think
I'd feel this strongly about someone.
[chuckles]
[cries]
I think I discovered a new side of me.
[inaudible]
I still haven't escaped the single life,
but I think I will soon.
[chuckles]
Yeah, you'll meet
good people in real life.
She didn't find a boyfriend,
but she found herself. That's enough.
-Yeah, that's the important thing.
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
[music fades]
YEO-MYUNG'S DIARY
[exhales]
[hopeful music playing]
[Eun-ji] He made a choice.
Jae-yun is so cool.
-[In-guk] He really is. Good job.
-[Car] Yes, that's right.
He's gonna try until the end.
[Jae-yun] I don't expect anything.
I know that Yeo-myung
isn't gonna choose me.
But it was a good experience.
Most people seemed okay with
how I speak and how I communicate.
So I gained a lot of confidence
when it comes to talking.
He does have an oddly funny side.
-He can be funny.
-[Sang-ho] It's kinda addicting.
It makes it okay.
Oh, like that! Yes, right!
[Min-hong laughs]
-Amazing.
-[Seung-chan] He's fighting her.
-What is this?
-The chopstick thing.
-You're doing it?
-Yeah.
[Jae-yun] I became much more confident
about approaching someone,
and striking up a conversation.
I often feel that I'm not…
fully matured yet.
I couldn't escape the single life,
but I do feel like I've matured here.
[music ends]
Wow.
[Han-na] Wow, he went through
a total transformation.
Totally. I always joked about him,
saying, "Is he AI?"
Now he's a person.
-I'm really proud of Jae-yun.
-[Han-na] Yeah.
[Eun-ji] Same.
MIN-HONG
FINAL SELECTION FORFEITED
-No hesitation. That was great.
-[In-guk] She's not hesitating.
[whimsical music playing]
-She's relieved. I can see it.
-[Han-na and Eun-ji] Yeah.
-[Han-na] She's gonna be just fine.
-[In-guk] Yep.
[Min-hong] I didn't escape
the single life,
but I'm very satisfied.
Even though I didn't find someone here,
I think I'll do better
at dating in real life.
I learned what's important to me.
[upbeat music playing]
Good job. [chuckles]
SEUNG-CHAN
FINAL SELECTION FORFEITED
MI-JI
MI-JI'S DIARY
FINAL SELECTION
SANG-HO CHOOSES MI-JI
[Sang-ho] I could tell
she wasn't really interested in me,
but she's one of the people
I tried my best to impress
while I was here.
[inaudible]
I wanted to show her that I liked her,
so I chose her.
[music fades]
[inhales]
[exhales heavily]
JI-SU'S DIARY
[exhales sharply]
[sentimental music playing]
[Hyun-kyu] I know that
I don't have a chance.
Yes, Ji-su will make her own decision.
I know that. I do.
[sentimental music rises]
MY FUTURE BOYFRIEND WILL BE…
Yeah, I chose Ji-su.
Who else is there?
Regardless, thanks to her,
I felt things here
that I had never felt before.
It was fun. I felt happiness, I felt pain.
And I'm very grateful.
It was a short time, but…
I liked her a lot.
Ji-su, I liked you.
[chuckles] Yeah.
[music fades]
-[enchanting music playing]
-[breathing heavily]
[Seung-li] My feelings
for her are always 100%,
so I didn't even need to think.
[exhales]
[enchanting music rises]
MY FUTURE BOYFRIEND WILL BE…
[Eun-ji] Wow. From
the first impression pick to final choice,
Seung-li always chose Ji-su.
[Han-na] Yeah, that's right,
he only had eyes for Ji-su.
KANG JI-SU
KIM YEO-MYUNG
[Ji-su sighs heavily]
[music fades]
[Ji-su] Will I be able
to date Seung-li in real life?
[Car] She's still deliberating.
[Han-na] But with Ji-su, I don't think
she'll go for it unless she's 100% sure.
[Ji-su groans] Oh…
SEUNG-LI'S DIARY
Oh, so I guess I can pass.
[contemplative music playing]
[Ji-su] I've thought about it a lot,
and I might end up regretting this,
but I think this is the best decision
I can make right now.
What?
-She said…
-[music fades]
She said it was
the best decision she could make.
[Eun-ji] Yeah.
That could mean she put her card in,
-but it could also mean she abstained.
-Either makes sense.
-[In-guk] You know…
-[Eun-ji] Yeah.
…if she were here,
I'd want to tell her this…
I totally get that she's careful
because this is her first chance at love
and she has traumatic memories
from when she was young,
but isn't the process
of getting to know people
-also important?
-[Eun-ji] Right, very true.
You know, older people say that a lot.
We should try dating a lot
and meet lots of people
-before getting married.
-Oh, right, right.
I think doing that could help her
get up to 100% certainty.
I don't think there's anyone
who's 100% perfect for you.
[Han-na] True.
[mellow music playing]
[music fades]
[gripping music builds up]
[enthralling music playing]
What's this?
FINAL SELECTION
JI-YEON & JEONG-MOK
-Ji-yeon. Congratulations!
-We have our first couple.
[Eun-ji and Han-na exclaim]
They look so sweet together.
[enthralling music continues]
[music fades]
It's like a dream.
Right? I think so.
I don't wanna leave.
I feel the same.
You don't feel… overwhelmed?
I also didn't imagine that…
-that this would happen.
-Yeah.
I'm okay because it's you.
[enchanting music playing]
[gasps] "I'm okay
because it's you." Ji-yeon!
They're adorable.
They're so lovely.
-[Jeong-mok] Ta-da!
-[Ji-yeon] Ta-da.
Ta-da.
-Oh, no. We can't take it back now.
-Yeah, right, we can't.
-Yeah.
-It's here forever.
-Today is Day 1 for us.
-What do we do? Right.
Let's just be happy.
[music fades]
[sighs wearily]
-Why does he look so tired?
-[Han-na] Seriously.
[sighs wearily]
[mellow pensive music playing]
[Han-na] He's getting anxious
because she's not coming.
[Eun-ji] Ji-su…
[In-guk sighs] Why am I so nervous?
-[Han-na gasps]
-She didn't… I don't think she went.
[Han-na] Really?
-[Eun-ji] I don't think so.
-[gasps] Ji-su didn't choose him?
[music fades]
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles softly]
[music builds up]
Ji-su.
[enthralling music soaring]
Hi.
[Seung-li] Hi.
-[Han-na] She came!
-[screams]
Wow, that's great.
-It's our second couple.
-Oh…
Our second couple.
-You're so lucky, Seung-li!
-I got chills.
-[Eun-ji] Do better!
-What was that?
You really have to get it together.
-Get it together, you punk!
-Seriously!
-Listen closely.
-Don't drink too much, man.
That's right!
Please try harder to read the room.
As Cupids, we each had one person
who ended up with someone.
-We did.
-I was Jeong-mok's.
-I was Ji-su's.
-I was Ji-yeon's.
-I was Seung-li's.
-That's crazy.
Oh, but it almost seems like
we planned it.
FINAL SELECTION
JI-SU & SEUNG-LI
[enchanting music continues]
[Ji-su] I decided on Seung-li.
I wish he was more caring,
but maybe what I really need
is his indifference.
[Seung-li] There were
so many guys who liked you.
Was it hard to choose?
[music fades]
-No.
-Not at all?
-Oh.
[charming music playing]
Yeah.
But I saw that we had the choice
to abstain from voting.
[Ji-su] Yeah.
So when I heard that, I started to worry.
I thought,
"Oh, she could choose to abstain."
Was I so unclear?
No, I was just worrying.
Maybe 'cause I didn't work out today.
I think I felt anxious
because I didn't run.
-[chuckles]
-That's just me.
[both laugh]
-[Seung-li sighs]
-So…
[music fades]
-I read your book in the library.
-Mmm.
[chuckles]
In the ideal type part…
-Ideal type?
-Yeah. [chuckles]
You wrote that you liked girls with long,
straight hair and no bangs.
I did? Bangs.
[Ji-su laughs]
Ah.
-I remember reading, "No bangs…
-Straight hair.
…long, straight hair,
positive, kind, and doesn't swear."
Aren't you the opposite?
[laughs]
Oh, but I think
that's what I realized here.
I'm actually attracted
to the exact opposite type.
[upbeat music playing]
[Ji-su laughs] Ah.
[inaudible]
Look, it's all here.
I'm totally different.
"A girl who looks good
in neat and casual jeans."
-I was totally off.
-Yeah.
Even if you regret it,
you can't take it back now.
[Seung-li] Let's just throw this book
into the lake.
Oh, I'm gonna take it home.
I'll tease you about it forever.
[Seung-li] My first impression pick
was Ji-su.
-Are you…
-Yeah.
Oh, right, right.
[Seung-li] It was always Ji-su.
[inaudible]
She'll be my first girlfriend.
[Ji-su] I can imagine myself
getting frustrated with him. [chuckles]
But I also think that
when I get irritated,
Seung-li can take it.
[Seung-li] Aren't I good
at remembering things today?
-I think I did well.
-[Ji-su] Let's talk about that later.
[Seung-li] After the show.
You keep saying that.
We're already done, you know.
[Ji-su laughs]
-[inaudible]
-[upbeat music continues]
[Jeong-mok] Because I was single
for such a long time,
I was worried that I had a problem,
that I wasn't attractive.
My self-esteem was dropping.
I kept thinking, "Am I that unlovable?"
I was worried about that.
Being here,
I learned,
"Oh, I can be loved too."
"I can give someone love."
I feel certain of that now
and that feels great.
And I want to continue this relationship
even after the show.
Jeong-mok kept talking to me
about marriage.
Like, "Oh, we need to get married."
And… I think we might
actually do it. [chuckles]
I know it sounds crazy, but…
I think we will. [chuckles]
[upbeat Korean song playing]
[song ends]
[upbeat music playing]