[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 25]
I know you're single, but you can't
just act like this.
You're having sinister thoughts
when you see a happy couple like us.
But, your relationship with her is
practically the same as you being single.
Get out.
I've been waiting for you to say that
for a long time.
Let me call Gu Bai Zhi then.
Why are you calling her?
I'm curious about how you two
maintained your relationship
when you're a person like this.
There are three solutions to this.
They're suitable for
all kinds of situations.
Heat up the pan and put your steak in.
First,
you need to cook for her personally.
Because when both of you
are busy with work,
you two won't have opportunities
to eat with each other.
Time will always separate you two.
At this time,
someone needs to stand out
and break the balance.
The meal you prepared for her
will be your opportunity.
You're really lucky.
You have steaks for dinner these few days.
Next,
the way you speak is very important.
But,
flattery doesn't work.
You should ask her directly
and see what you can help her with.
Let her know that
you're there for her
no matter how tired she is.
I know you're worried about Suo Heng.
I know you have no time for me lately.
But, don't worry.
I will take care of myself.
You can tell me everything.
Not only am I your boyfriend, Zhou Chuan,
I'm your best friend, Mr Fox, as well.
Get her a present.
All girls like it when
boys give them presents.
Don't think that buying her accessories
is old-fashioned.
No matter how different she is,
girls will always be girls.
Why hasn't she returned yet?
Why have you only returned by now?
I was too busy.
Have you eaten?
No. I was waiting for you.
I told you that...
I've eaten already.
I need to work overtime later.
You need to work overtime
even though you're back?
Since when does Yuan Yue Publishing House
know how to extort their employees?
It's not that.
I'm going to the
printing factory tomorrow.
I have to prepare
all of the materials by tonight.
You...
I've prepared dinner.
Let's eat.
I thought you ate already?
Can you still finish the dinner I've made?
I feel hungry suddenly.
It's cold.
Let me heat it up for you.
Men who cook are the coolest.
But of course.
By the way, I've prepared a movie as well.
We can watch it later.
If you don't feel like watching the movie,
we can play some games.
We'll do whatever you want to do.
By the way...
[Chu Li,]
[Flying Elephant]
[I've encountered a problem
with Suo Heng's front cover.]
Were you caught in the traffic
when you took the bus?
Do you need me to send you to work?
I'll send you there and
pick you up as well.
Not only will you be able to
save money,
you'll be able to rest on my car
on your way there.
What do you think?
Enjoy it while it's hot.
Take your time.
I know you've been busy lately.
What I want to say is...
Mister,
I had my fill already.
Thank you for your dinner.
Although tonight was very romantic,
I still have work that I need to finish.
I'm not done with
Suo Heng's front cover yet.
I'll leave now.
Delicious!
So delicious!
It's really delicious!
I don't believe it.
It's so delicious!
I'm going to take a walk with my dog.
Do you want to join me?
No thanks.
You had a large piece of steak.
Don't you want some desserts later?
No thanks.
It hurts! I think I have a bone fracture!
Just kidding.
[Do not disturb]
♫ What time is it? You are still sleeping? ♫
No, this mustn't continue on.
♫ Chopping wood, keeping a dog, working ♫
♫ Where did I stop yesterday? ♫
♫ I can replay my feelings ♫
♫ Daydreaming in the dark of night ♫
♫ Chasing after you beyond the universe ♫
♫ Be a darling in the gorgeous castle ♫
♫ It's not like this ♫
♫ Oh, waiting for your signal, hello ♫
♫ My cutie is here ♫
♫ We have a date online and offline ♫
♫ Ding ding ding, my cutie is calling ♫
♫ Specialise in treating
charming laziness ♫
♫ Ding ding ding, my cutie is here ♫
♫ I simply treat you as the role model ♫
Breakfast is ready. Are you awake?
I'll send you to work
after we finish breakfast.
♫ Ding ding ding, my cutie is here ♫
I'm coming in.
♫ I fell in love with a mischief-maker ♫
Where is she?
Hello, Jiang Yu Chen?
Can I really trust you?
What kind of lousy solutions were those?
I...
Little Deity belongs to
the ancient Chinese novel category.
Now, we have two editions. One with
a hard cover and one with a normal cover.
But, regarding the one with a hard cover,
I need to inquire the price from
your printing factory beforehand.
And I'll make the decision
based on our budget.
Price?
Please wait a moment.
I'll go and check right away.
No need for that.
You can tell me the price tonight
after your inquiry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm new to the place.
I don't know
the price for this as well.
It's fine.
Okay.
By the way, you need to get this clear.
For Little Deity's
online pre-sale edition,
it contains unique stickers
outside its plastic wrap.
There will be gifts, posters,
and bookmarks as well.
All of them must be included.
You mustn't mix them up.
Take your time.
Don't be anxious.
I would rather you
jot everything down clearly.
She's too much.
She always follows me around
and addresses me as
Mr Zhou Chuan before we became a couple.
Now that we're together,
she's ignoring me
even though it's only been a few days.
This was supposed to be Full House.
But, why does it feel like The Break-Up?
Have a seat.
Do you know what you resemble right now?
A concubine who has been
banished to the Cold Palace.
Or a house-husband who isn't
satisfied with his married life.
You do know yourself well.
But, you're more like
a peacock that's seeking for attention.
You're spreading your tails like crazy
when no one is paying attention.
If I must say,
I think Chu Li was too busy
these few days.
She didn't catch what
you were trying to do at all.
You should stop imagining things.
You don't understand at all.
A relationship is doomed to fail
once someone neglects the other party
due to their work.
You should know that the best.
Didn't you and Gu Bai Zhi break up
because of the same reason?
Can you just focus on your own problem?
Don't try to drag me into this.
I know what kind of problem
I'm facing right now.
I shouldn't have asked for your opinion
in the first place.
If your solutions did work,
you would've been married with
Gu Bai Zhi long ago.
I shouldn't have asked for your opinion
in the first place.
In the end,
I still need to depend on myself.
Chu Li,
you're acting like
a capable editor now.
Many readers are
curious about you, you know?
I would rather become an editor
who's invisible.
Editors work behind the scenes.
It's great as long as we can help
the writers to publish their books.
There's no need for people
to know of our existence.
It's fine when there's no trouble,
but I'll be reprimanded
if I'm in trouble because of it.
What's wrong?
Your phone was ringing non-stop just now.
Is there anything wrong?
It's Mr Zhou Chuan.
I don't know what's wrong with him lately.
He has been forwarding
some weird articles to me lately.
What articles?
Can I have a look?
I want to read the things
my idol reads usually.
Come.
Why we go cold on our partners?
Why don't women leave men even after
falling out of the relationship?
Women who truly love you
will fulfil two of
the circumstances below.
What? Do you want to tell me something?
Chu Li,
have you been ignoring
Mr Zhou Chuan lately?
Why do you say so?
All these articles are
so blatantly obvious.
He's seeking for attention.
I don't need to work overtime tonight.
I'll make a feast for you tonight.
[I don't need to work overtime tonight.]
[I'll make a feast for you tonight.]
Listen.
Listen to it.
The candlelit dinner was useless.
Do you see
how good and efficient I am?
Please don't give me
any relationship advice in the future.
You're not good enough.
You should consult me
before you court a girl in the future.
I didn't expect myself to be a genius
at something else
besides writing.
Genius? My foot.
I've checked the advance copy
and the gifts.
They're fine.
But you must remember to key in
the online pre-sale edition
as a different entry from
the normal edition.
You hear me?
[Yes, madam.]
[Coming.]
[Sister Chu Li, I'll hang up now.]
[Don't worry.]
[I'll handle this for you.]
Mr Jiang,
I'm really sorry.
I can't attend your function.
Because I'm not done with
Ms Suo Heng's books yet.
You don't need to apologize to him.
You're my girlfriend.
Why are you trying to join him?
I need to correct something.
I didn't invite your girlfriend.
I invited my editor.
Mr Jiang, how about this?
Let Zhou Chuan join you for the function
since it didn't state that you need
a female partner to enter.
-Are you out of your mind?
-No thanks.
Mr Zhou Chuan, stop pretending.
When Mr Jiang gave me
the signed copy of
The Disappearing Amusement Park,
not only did you take it for yourself,
you didn't even let me
take a look at
the heart sticker on the book.
What's with that?
You're my girlfriend, you know?
Why are you curious about
the heart sticker left by him?
Are you done? Leave when you're done.
I can't stand you anymore.
You're not allowed to let him stay.
-I didn't plan...
-Don't worry.
I don't plan to stay for dinner as well.
Chu Li, see you next time.
See her? You're not allowed to see her!
You're finally skipping work
for me today?
So, do you want me to come home?
Will you believe me if I say no?
No.
Give me your hands.
I've been invisible to you
for the past few days.
Why did you buy a present for me then?
If I don't do anything,
we'll go through a breakup soon.
No way. We're in the middle of
our love bubble.
How are we in a love bubble
when we're barely talking to each other?
You don't let me kiss you at all.
It's not that I'm objecting to that.
It's just that
there isn't any opportunity.
Come on then.
I'm ready.
This is more like it.
Seems like the chapters
I've sent to you weren't in vain.
What? Chapters of your new novel?
I just sent them to your email.
I'm going to take a look at them!
I shouldn't have said that.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
Mr Nian Nian,
I've already started to
inspect your scripts.
By the way,
didn't you say that
my shampoo smelled nice?
I bought extra this time.
I'll send them to you later.
You're welcome.
Alright, see you.
Mr He Ma?
How is it? Have you returned to
the country?
I was planning to prepare
a welcoming dinner for you.
The weekend? I'm fine with that.
By the way,
regarding the writer of Luo Yi Monk,
Mr Yu Bo,
have you contacted him for me?
What?
You want me to bring Chu Li with me?
Mr He Ma,
Chu Li is very famous now.
You may not be able to meet her.
Even I couldn't meet her often.
How about this? I'll contact you
if I'm able to
arrange for an appointment with her.
Okay?
That's all for now.
Alright.
Ms Suo Heng, this is great.
The number of copies for
your first print run are increasing.
Thank you, Chu Li.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
Not at all.
You should credit yourself as well.
I didn't expect us
to receive 65,000 orders
from the pre-sale online and
the hard copies.
That means you'll be able to sell
70,000 books for your first print run.
I've contacted the printing factory
for the printing of your books.
Chu Li, it's all thanks to you.
Let me treat you to dinner tonight.
I appreciate your effort.
I can't have dinner with you tonight.
I still need to work overtime
to complete your book.
We can go and celebrate our success
after your book is listed on the market.
We must tell Chief Editor Yu
to join us as well.
You may not know,
but she went to check out the sequence
for your books this morning.
She hasn't even returned yet.
Is that so?
Thank her for me.
You want me to thank her for you?
You should thank her yourself.
I'm sure she'll be delighted.
I'm back.
Overtime shifts again?
Why is the living room always messy?
Can't you guys just clean it up?
Mum!
My baby.
Our house wouldn't be in this mess
if you didn't work overtime every day.
Baby,
after I'm finished with my work,
let's go and celebrate
your birthday in Disneyland,
okay?
That's great.
Mum, there's one more week
before my birthday.
Can I have the chocolate
Grandma left for me?
Baby, I told you before.
What will happen to you
if you consume too much sweets?
I will have a toothache, and worms
will attack my tooth.
Yes, my baby. You're right.
Just let him have one.
My mother bought it especially
for him, you know?
As adults, we mustn't spoil our children.
Just tell Mum
to stop buying sweet things for him.
My mother was the one who's been
taking care of him lately.
What's wrong with having a few sweets?
Qiu Qiu, let's go.
Let's take a bath.
After that, we'll go to sleep.
[Suo Heng]
[Thank you.]
Congratulations.
Why are you here alone?
Chu Li couldn't come as she has
an emergency to attend to.
Bai Zhi,
this is?
You must be Mr Jiang.
I've heard many things about you.
I'm Luo Wen.
I'm from Xin Dun Books.
Hello, Mr Luo.
People often told me that
Mr Jiang is young and talented.
Your reputation is well-deserved.
Mr Jiang, I'm an avid reader of yours.
I've been reading all of your books.
I hope that
we can work together in the future.
You flatter me.
Where's Yun Fei?
-Yun Fei...
-Yun Fei
is busy for the past few days.
That's why I'm here on his behalf.
I won't interrupt you guys then.
Please accompany Mr Jiang.
No problem.
Next time, you can find me.
What?
You can find me
if you lack a male partner.
Let's have a drink.
Mr Lu,
do you remember me?
I'm Luo Wen from Xin Dun Books.
I do remember you.
Please.
Alright.
Mr Lu.
Look at your Mr Luo.
He's following Mr Lu like a puppy.
Flattery doesn't work on
Mr Lu at all.
And I still remember that
last time...
Isn't this Mr Jiang Yu Cheng?
We meet again.
Your novel,
The Disappearing Amusement Park,
it sold like hotcakes.
I read the book.
I was so regretful.
How could I part ways with
an impeccable novel
like that?
Is that so?
What do you think about
Li Su's ending then?
Li Su?
He left a deep impression on me.
I think his ending is great.
Since Mr Jiang is one of
the best writers out there.
Li Su doesn't exist in the novel.
Yeah.
I think I'm getting too old.
My memories aren't as good
as they used to be.
Excuse me, but you are?
She's Gu Bai Zhi from Xin Dun Books.
Ms Gu from Xin Dun Books?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's an honour to see you here.
This...
This is my name card.
Ms Gu.
Mr Jiang.
So,
I won't interrupt you guys then.
Please continue.
Ms Wen Xiang,
this is my name card.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
I have many ideas that
I want to propose to you.
Hey!
I'm sorry about that.
It's fine.
Ms Gu, I know you didn't do it on purpose.
It's just an accident.
Give me a tissue.
Look at him.
He was enraged,
but he still pretended to smile.
If you work with a person like him,
he might stab you in the back one day.
That Wang Yang
has been trying to ruin your reputation
just because he couldn't publish
your book, The Disappearing Zoo.
I wanted to teach him a lesson long ago.
Why do you guys remember my affairs
more clearly than me?
You guys?
Who else is there? Zhou Chuan?
Yeah.
Back then,
Zhou Chuan and I were nobody.
We couldn't do anything about it.
We could only keep it to ourselves.
Besides,
I was your editor back then.
I've finally avenged myself
today.
I've reached home.
I'll go in now.
♫ They say strange things
and keep rapport ♫
♫ Guileless adults are reduced to a joke ♫
Wait.
♫ Unceasingly, here to stay ♫
Does it still count?
What do you mean?
♫ No dancing on the roof, but rain ♫
Last time, at the book fair,
♫ The loneliness has found
a place and moved out ♫
you said we could start again.
Does it still count?
What do you think?
♫ Guests sillier than me
argue and exaggerate ♫
♫ The moon is
outrageously beautiful tonight ♫
♫ Lend me the light on your face ♫
♫ I've been giddy from drifting
in a sea of people ♫
♫ Unwilling to admit my anticipation
of getting submitted to gentleness ♫
♫ I want to be led by you,
albeit a meager freedom ♫
♫ The Hand of the Creator
has finally seen to ♫
♫ The alien's call for help ♫
You're awake?
What is this?
This is a gift that I was supposed to
give to you three years ago.
You're going to be late for work.
Although I haven't finished it,
Mr Zhou Chuan,
your new novel
might be your new masterpiece.
Every book of mine is a masterpiece.
I'll go up then.
I still need to work overtime tonight.
You don't need to wait for me tonight.
You owe me some kisses.
Chu Li!
This is bad! Something happened to
Suo Heng's books!
I read the online reviews
of Little Deity today.
They said they didn't receive any gifts
from the online pre-sale edition.
Only those who bought the hard copy
received the gifts.
Have you asked the
customer service about this?
I did.
But they said they did everything
according to our preference.
I don't know what's going on either.
I'll go to the printing factory.
You should contact Chief Editor Yu.
Alright, I understand.
I'll be there immediately.
Alright.
Something urgent popped up.
Please send him to the kindergarten today.
I have an important meeting
to attend as well.
I mustn't be late.
I need to rush to the company immediately.
Just send him to
the kindergarten this time, okay?
Yu Yao,
you always give the same excuses.
Qiu Qiu,
pat his back.
Qiu Qiu?
Qiu Qiu.
Qiu Qiu, are you okay?
How do you feel?
Do you feel better?
How many times have I told you this?
You should stop Mum from buying
all those sweets for him.
My mother bought him some sweets
because she cared for him.
How could you blame this on my mother?
I'm not blaming Mum.
It's just that sweets aren't good for him.
Why do you always talk to me
with this kind of attitude?
Qiu Qiu, look at me.
It's fine now.
You can go to the kindergarten, right?
Okay.
Alright.
Send him to the kindergarten then.
Ask the teachers to observe him in school.
I'll leave first.
You're leaving just like that?
Suo Heng's books are in huge trouble.
I have to rush over there immediately.
Qiu Qiu is fine now.
I'm really sorry about this.
Yu Yao,
I tried my best to transfer my job
to this state
so that
our family can live together in peace.
But you?
Which is more important in your heart?
Is Yuan Yue Publishing House
more important than our family?
Qiu Qiu, let's go.
Hello, Chief Editor Yu.
Chu Li, what's going on?
Why aren't the buyers of
the online pre-sale edition
receiving their gifts?
[Now, the official website of
Yuan Yue Publishing House]
[is filled with their complaints.]
Chief Editor Yu,
I went to the printing factory just now.
The person in charge,
Xiao Wang, made a blunder.
He mixed up the two orders.
[Chief Editor Yu, I'm sorry.]
Enough. Just return here for now.
Stop wasting your time over there.
We need to resolve this
within one hour.
Alright.
Mr Zhou Chuan?
Why are you here?
Look at you, you look so down.
How could I return home in peace?
I've heard everything from Xiang.
Let's return for now.
Tell the circulation department
to stop distributing the current goods.
After that, you can prepare
for the compensation.
Before this happened, I told Xiang that
the readers mustn't know
the existence of the editors.
Because if something happens to the book,
we'll be reprimanded.
And now, I'm in trouble.
I think I'm a jinx.
Yeah, you're a jinx.
Alright, it's fine now.
I'm here for you.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
this concerns my work.
Please don't interfere.
I'm sure Miao and the rest will...
Their opinion doesn't matter.
It's fine as long as
I can help the readers
get their compensation.
I'll wait for you in the car then.
Chu Li,
what's the current situation
in the printing factory?
The person in charge made a blunder.
He mixed up the orders
for the two editions.
That's the reason behind this incident.
I suggest we print new copies
and send it to the readers
in order to calm them down.
Yi Wen is on a sick leave.
You can report it to us.
According to preliminary statistics,
most of the pre-sale goods have been
sent to the readers.
We've recalled all of the books
that haven't been sent out.
Even so,
there are 8,000 copies
on their way to the readers.
You guys heard that?
Of course you can print another copy,
but who'll fork out the postage?
One copy is around 8 to 10 yuan.
For 8,000 copies, it costs around
60,000 yuan.
Who'll pay for it?
Of course the printing factory
will pay for it.
We've told them time and time again.
We told them the gifts are meant
for the online pre-sale edition.
They were the ones who made the blunder.
Of course they need to
be responsible for it.
This is a breach of contract.
We've been working together with the
printing factory for so many years.
Next,
we need to work together with them
for the photo albums
and coloured comic for Role Playing Game.
If we fall out with them
at this crucial moment,
that means we will have to find
another printing factory which can
match our standards.
If we have to let go of
the projects in our hand
because of this incident,
we will incur a big loss.
Wait.
Why do I think
you're trying to speak up for the
printing factory?
You don't want to compensate them?
What about their feelings?
For this kind of matter,
we need to make it sound less serious.
I think our current readers
aren't that hard to deal with,
am I right?
I think they're
giving us such a huge reaction
because they want us
to give them an explanation.
That means
you want someone to be the scapegoat then?
Who will be the scapegoat?
For this,
I think Chu Li will
need to be the scapegoat.
Managing editor,
as the name implies,
she's the one managing it.
If you visit the printing factory
as frequent as you could,
I'm sure they won't have time
to commit such stupid mistakes.
But Chu Li has been frequenting the
printing factory as often as she could.
She would've stayed there
if she could do so.
Now, all the readers
are scolding Ms Suo Heng
on her Weibo account.
They said that they want to boycott them
because she's a liar.
They said she didn't give them
the free gifts she promised to give.
The person who made the blunder
is hiding behind the scene
while my editor needs to take the blame?
I don't agree with that.
I told you already. Chu Li is
the managing editor for the book.
It's logical for her to
admit her mistakes.
How could you say
I'm making her our scapegoat?
I believe Director Yang
would do the same as well,
am I right, Mr Liang?
Fine.
I'll shoulder the responsibility.
Because I don't want my author
to be disheartened.
I don't want her readers
to be disappointed.
This isn't their fault.
But I hope
the circulation department can
make the order by today.
Chu Li
will be suspended for now.
Suspended?
That punishment is too much.
Do you have a better idea?
I'm the chief editor here.
Did I agree to that?
Did Mr Xia agree to that?
She's lucky that she's just suspended.
Now,
we can't afford to fall out
with the printing factory.
Yuan Yue Publishing House
has to pay for all of our loss.
She's just suspended.
We would sack her
if she was someone else.
If Chu Li was the reason behind our loss,
I will be the first
to kick her out.
The problem is she's not responsible
for this mistake.
Why must she shoulder the blame?
It's an order from Director Yang.
Take a look yourself.
As for the period for her suspension,
we'll talk about it next time.
Are you guys done finding your scapegoat?
Mr Zhou Chuan, why are you here?
Deputy Editor Miao,
what's that under your feet?
There's nothing under my feet.
Oh, I understand now.
It's your repulsive character.
Since she's suspended,
I can take her away then.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
You're not allowed to cry.
You're just suspended!
Let's just treat it as a break then.
The key is I don't know
when my suspension will end.
I think I'm going to be sacked soon.
So what if you're sacked?
It's fine, I can support you.
I don't want you to support me.
I want to do my work.
I just want to be a good editor.
Alright, you can be an editor
all you like.
You're the best editor
in the world.
Why is this happening?
This is so unfair!
I left Yuan Yue Publishing House already.
Why should Yuan Yue Publishing House
cover their own loss?
Is it because they want to
maintain a good relationship
with the printing factory?
It's fine.
Let's think of a solution together.
Stop crying, okay?
Stop crying.
I'll be there after two hours.
Mr Liang.
Are you satisfied with the result?
What do you mean?
You've been here for more than 10 years.
I don't believe that
you're satisfied
for letting Yuan Yue Publishing House
cover for our own loss.
All of us know this deep down.
For this matter,
at most, Chu Li can be blamed
for her negligence.
If she's able to shoulder the blame,
no problem, just let her bear the blame.
The problem is, she may appear
to be responsible for it,
but Yuan Yue Publishing House is the one
who's taking all of the blame.
No matter if it's money
or people's opinions,
in the end, Yuan Yue Publishing House
will be the one at a disadvantage.
Yes.
But the solution was already out.
It's useless for you to say that.
Have you ever thought of
whether Miao
is truly trying to help
Yuan Yue Publishing House?
Or is he just trying to chase Chu Li away?
Are you sure that
you want to help the
current Miao Jian Ping?
Chief Editor Yu.
Suo Heng? Why are you here?
I saw the official website's announcement.
Why was Chu Li
suspended from her position?
You haven't been eating well lately.
You should eat up.
Later, we'll think of a solution together.
I deserved it.
This wouldn't have happened
if I went to the printing factory
instead of calling them.
I've let down Ms Suo Heng.
The printing factory is in the wrong here.
You did nothing wrong.
You're the best editor I've ever seen.
How could you know that
when you've barely even seen any editors?
You didn't speak in that tone
when you first became my editor.
[Chu Li,]
[Flying Elephant]
[Ms Suo Heng posted a post for you.]
[Take a look.]
Finish your meal first.
No, return it to me.
[The author, Suo Heng]
[I have]
[always been a weak person]
[who doesn't know how to
stand up for myself.]
[This is my first time doing this.]
[I feel that I need to speak up for her.]
[My editor, Chu Li,]
[she was the only one who didn't
give up on me]
[when I was in despair.]
[She was the one who rushed to protect me]
[from anything.]
[She's a person who will
sacrifice herself]
[in order to protect the writers.]
[Not only is she my editor,]
[she's an important friend
of mine as well.]
[So,]
[please, everyone, stop attacking her.]
[Because you guys don't know]
[how big of a chivalrous fool she is.]
It's fine.
Everything will be over eventually.