(Previous Chapter) You know the
kids here aren't like normal kids.
Look after our new friend, Tanrak.
I'm Barth.
Like basketball?
Like the saint. Bartholomew.
It's Grade 12, second term,
and you still got in?
What are you gonna do about it?
Barth! Barth! Barth!
But if you keep behaving like this,
I'll have to ask you to leave the school.
Do you really believe in God?
I believe God is real.
I believe my parents are with Him up there.
Maybe my God isn't as kind as yours.
“WHAT MAN AMONG YOU
HAVING A HUNDRED SHEEP
AND LOSING ONE OF THEM
WOULD NOT LEAVE THE
NINETY-NINE IN THE DESERT
AND GO AFTER THE LOST
ONE UNTIL HE FINDS IT?”
(LUKE 15:4)
Alright, let's go home.
Always causing trouble.
Sit down.
Kongkit was wrong for starting it,
but you two were at fault too.
He was just trying to help me, Father.
It's good to be kind,
but for something this serious,
you should've told me or Master Phak,
not help each other hide it.
What if it had gotten worse?
What would you do then?
I'm sorry, Father.
Barth.
You can go now.
I trusted you to look after the new boy.
I thought you could've handled
this better, Tanrak.
I'm really sorry.
From now on,
I hope you'll take better care of him.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, Father.
Please excuse me.
SCHOLARSHIP STUDENT REPORT BOOK
"Ticket to Heaven"
(Episode 2)
ANGER IS QUELLED BY PATIENCE.
What are you doing here all alone,
so studious?
I'm not studying. I'm being punished.
Master Phak.
Just call me P'Phak.
We're only a few years apart.
No need to be so formal all the time.
Hey, if you're being punished,
take it seriously.
Maybe using up the whole book
will teach you a lesson.
I still don't know what I did wrong.
Making me write hundreds of lines
won't change that.
P'Phak! Come play with us.
We're one short.
Yeah, I'll be right there.
Okay. Hurry.
Hey, can you play football?
Yeah, but I… don't know anyone.
So what?
You're gonna be here for a year.
Don't you plan to make any friends?
Well, join me if you wanna play.
Here I come.
Lord, bless us and this food
we are about to receive.
In the name of the Father, and of the Son,
and of the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Up to you.
Barth.
I can sit somewhere else.
Sit here. I was just kidding.
Why would you sit by the trash can?
Sit here.
You know all these kids
are scared that you'll punch them?
But I'm not scared of you.
Because God teaches us…
Love your neighbor as yourself.
Damn!
Hey, Kong.
Have you ever been punched
by your neighbor?
You're about to get punched by me.
Eat your food.
Well.
So is it true?
You knocked out a guy at your old school
with one punch?
Yeah.
Damn, a real boxer's move.
So if I piss you off,
will you punch me?
Just kidding.
Barth.
Were you mad about them teasing you?
No.
I didn't care. Why?
If you don't like it, I can tell them.
So there won't be any trouble.
Tanrak, return these catechism notebooks
to Class 12/1.
Did I... get full marks, Master?
Well, open it and see.
Tell anyone who got less than half
to come see me next Tuesday.
- Yes, Master.
- I'm off to class.
Goodbye, Master.
BODIN TUNGWONGWAT
Here, Chris. Collecting full marks, huh?
Not really.
This one's yours.
Can I move here?
I can't see the board at all.
That's Kongdech's seat. Ask him first.
Can I sit here?
Yeah, sure.
As long as you do well in class.
All right, everyone.
Don't rush home after class.
Go sign up for this year's Christmas
activity groups.
Scholarship students without a group
can stay in the same group as last year.
Do we have to do something
for the Christmas party?
Of course.
What do you like doing?
I don't know.
I don't like doing anything.
Do I really have to?
Yes, especially as scholarship students.
We have to help out. We have duties.
Oh, Bodin, you don't have a group yet.
Join the reception team.
If you don't remember your group,
come check the list with me later.
What group are you in?
Hm? I'm in the choir.
I'll join you.
You can't.
Since you don't like doing anything,
I think the reception team suits you.
You won't have to do much.
No.
I don't have any friends.
You're the only one I know.
You'll get to know more people
once you start working with them.
What are you doing?
Do you pray like this every day?
No.
I'm here to pray for redemption.
Redemption? For what?
Well, I was partly at fault
for what happened to you,
like Father said.
The only wrong thing
you did was to help me,
and now you're screwed too.
Don't help me next time.
If you feel bad,
then pass your catechism test.
Father assigned me to be your buddy.
Okay?
Then tutor me.
Why should I tutor you?
Because we're friends.
Since when are we friends?
Barth, can you stop breaking the rules?
I'm gonna get in trouble too.
I didn't see any sign saying
I couldn't leave school.
It's a Magdalene House rule.
Next,
lust means letting desire control us.
What if you can't stop it?
Then you fight it.
Why fight it?
Have you tried this roti
in front of the school?
Go off topic again,
and I won't tutor you anymore.
Yes, sir.
Want some?
Come on.
Just a bite.
Hurry up or I'll be
late for evening prayer.
Let me see.
What are you even looking at?
There are three people.
The Believer, the Lover, and the Lost One.
One always tells the truth.
One sometimes tells the truth
and sometimes lies.
And one always lies.
The Believer says
the Lover always tells the truth.
The Lover says
the Lost One always lies.
The Lost One says
the Believer doesn't always tell the truth.
So which one lies
and which one tells the truth?
Seriously?
Isn't your life stressful enough?
Why are you doing this stuff?
None of your business.
Okay. Off you go, everyone.
Kong, come on.
RECEPTION TEAM
Pairat.
Yes.
Korawit.
Here.
Bodin.
Where's Bodin?
No idea.
♪ Angels we have heard on high ♪
♪ Sweetly singing o'er the plains ♪
♪ And the mountains in reply ♪
♪ Echoing their joyous strains ♪
♪ Gloria in excelsis Deo ♪
Are you looking for someone?
Well…
Someone told me I was in this group.
My name's Bodin.
Really?
It's not here. There's no Bodin.
They said they asked Tanrak
to pass on the message.
What's going on, Tanrak?
I forgot. Sorry, Master.
That's okay. Can you sing?
If I can't, can I help
carry things instead?
We all have to help carry things anyway.
All right. Let's hear you sing first.
Maybe we'll get a new member.
Come up front.
Put your bag down.
What song?
I'll have someone play for you.
“Before,” please.
“Before” by Modern Dog?
Yes.
Okay.
Give him the chords.
Something like this.
♪ My heart had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love entered ♪
♪ Filling my eyes bright with colors ♪
♪ My side had had no one ♪
♪ Until your love had mercy ♪
♪ To empower me to keep going ♪
♪ In this cruel world ♪
Okay. Wow, that was great!
Give him a hand.
You sing well.
In that case,
you can have the same part as Tanrak.
He can help train you.
I'm counting on you, Tanrak.
Okay.
Go on. Have a seat.
That chair is fine.
You know the song we're rehearsing, right?
Yes.
Good. Then let's go again, everyone.
♪ Gloria in excelsis Deo ♪
Tanrak, tidy up the
room and lock it for me.
Yes, Master.
Bodin, help him out.
Yes.
Who's this?
Saint Cecilia.
The one who sang when she died?
She sang in her heart, even as she died.
That's why she became
the patron saint of music.
If she sang in her heart,
who would hear it?
God always hears us.
Do you know every saint or something?
Oops!
"Tan Kham Wa Rak"
"There is a truth I want you to know"
"Meanings words seem to hold"
What song is this? I've never heard it.
Tan Kham Wa Rak. Tanrak.
Why are you named Tanrak?
Huh?
So... Why are you named Tanrak?
Tan, where's Kongdech?
He's probably at the farm plot.
Oh. I thought you were together.
Come on, guys.
Let's help Kong at the farm plot.
My mom had a hard time having a child.
So she came here to pray.
When she had me, she named me...
Tanrak.
Because I was a symbol of the love
the Holy Mother gave her.
My mom offered this rosary herself.
When I miss her,
I come here.
And I tell the Holy Mother…
if I ever get to heaven,
please take me to my parents.
Next time I can come here with you.
Tanrak,
I'll help.
Since when are Tan and Barth best buds?
Yeah. When did they
become close friends, Kong?
If you wanna know, ask them.
Oh, Mr. Kong. I thought you'd know.
You're Tan's closest friend, aren't you?
Hello, Teacher.
Hello.
What? Where did it go?
Boys, come help me look at this.
Go.
I'm trying to save it, but it won't work.
What do I do?
It's gone now.
- This drive can't burn discs.
- Oh.
It's a CD-ROM. It only reads them.
What? But I need to save it on a disc.
How am I supposed to do that?
Come look at it for me.
Come here. Sit down.
It won't save at all.
Oh, the file's too big.
You'll need to split it across two discs.
Well, the academic department
told us to stop submitting paper copies
and send files instead.
And those are all the students' projects.
I'm not very good at this.
If your files disappear,
I'm dead. Totally dead.
They won't disappear. I saved them for you.
Just please don't close the program.
Oh. Okay.
You've got potential, you know.
If you ever change your mind about
pursuing the religious path,
you could go into science.
Or vocational college. Something practical.
How does that sound?
Let me finish Grade 12 first.
I'm already too lazy for school as it is.
Okay.
Anyway, Tanrak,
how did you two become close?
Oh, we're not close.
Huh?
I just felt sorry for him.
He had no friends.
The Mass has ended.
Go in peace.
♪ I will not fight alone ♪
♪ You who conquered death and sin ♪
♪ Walk right beside me ♪
Oh!
Who are they?
Cherry and Oh.
Childhood friends from my neighborhood.
Really just friends?
Cherry. Oh.
How have you been?
This is Barth. He just joined Grade 12.
Hi.
I'll go put my things away.
You haven't been to church in ages.
Yeah. I've been helping my mom at the shop.
She's been seeing the doctor,
so I had to cover for her.
Is Auntie Tim doing okay?
She's all right.
Did you know?
They're building a 7-Eleven
where your house was.
They tore it down?
How long ago?
It's about to open.
They demolished the house
and built the store so quickly.
What about the rose apple tree next door?
Is it still there?
That tree died
before they even tore the house down.
But do you remember
when we climbed that tree as kids?
I fell, and it hurt like hell.
My mom scolded me for a whole week.
You seem a lot quieter now, Tanrak.
Really?
Yeah. More grown-up.
We should go.
See you.
You guys go ahead.
I wondered where you disappeared to.
What are you doing?
Practicing for the Christmas party.
Play for me.
Sure.
I said I was practicing.
Tanrak.
If something's stressing you out,
you can tell me.
You know that, right?
Come on. Teach me.
How do you play?
Let's start with… C.
C, huh?
- What else?
- B minor.
- Like this?
- Yes.
Barth.
You're such a tease.
I never said I couldn't play.
I just wanted you to teach me.
Out of all the chords,
which one do you like?
Well... they all sound nice, don't they?
No. Say you could choose only one chord
for the rest of your life.
Which one would it be?
Probably...
C.
I thought you'd pick this one.
It suits you.
Really?
So what note do you like?
What note?
This one.
Why?
It feels...
out of place.
Like it doesn't belong.
Like it's somewhere it shouldn't be.
How about we play that song?
♪ There is a truth I want you to know ♪
♪ Meanings many words seem to hold ♪
♪ No matter how beautiful they may be ♪
♪ They fall short of what you mean to me ♪
♪ Everything I do for you ♪
♪ May reflect what my heart holds true ♪
♪ Maybe my eyes already show ♪
♪ The feelings in my heart that flow ♪
♪ But do you know it's so much more?
♪ Things I would like to give to you ♪
♪ I'd gather every star ♪
♪ To show all the love I have for you ♪
♪ And make every song belong to you ♪
♪ To tell you I love you more
than words could say ♪
♪ Through seasons change
♪ I'll spend with you
my every single breath ♪
♪ No words can replace ♪
♪ What my heart means
when it says I love you ♪
♪ Let this love song speak for my heart
which belongs only to you ♪
♪ Let it be the promise of our love
until the time is through ♪
♪ I'd gather every star ♪
♪ To show all the love I have for you ♪
♪ And make every song belong to you ♪
♪ To tell you I love you more
than words could say ♪
♪ Through seasons change ♪
♪ I'll spend with you
my every single breath ♪
♪ No words can replace ♪
♪ What my heart means
when it says I love you ♪
If I speak in the tongues
of men or of angels
but do not have love,
I am only a resounding gong
or a clanging cymbal.
Because we're friends.
Barth.
What are you doing?
I know who's lying now.
Lying about what?
The brain teaser.
The Lost One, the Lover, and the Believer.
I figured it out.
What's the answer?
- I think...
- Not ready to sleep yet, huh?
Did it have to be now?
I wanted to know now.
Why?
Because now I'm being punished,
writing down saints' names in the cemetery.
Hey.
Did you hear that?
I heard a weird sound.
You're scared, aren't you?
Then go by yourself.
You have to come with me.
You're being punished.
There's nothing there. Don't be scared.
Joanna Wattana.
John the Baptist.
Hey, that's my saint's name.
What's up, John the Baptist Tanrak?
You know,
Master Phak wouldn't know
if we just made up saints' names.
Yeah. True.
What does Master Phak even do all day
besides catching us doing wrong things?
Master Phak is a good person.
He's my spiritual mentor.
He's not actually that strict.
If you become a Master one day,
who's gonna be scared of you?
You look way too kind.
Really?
Nine... twenty.
Done. Let's go.
Hey, wait.
Since we're already out,
wanna sneak out for some roti?
Don't tell me
you've never snuck out of school.
Seriously? Come with me.
Then hold this for me.
It's high. Give me a boost.
One, two, three.
You really won't come?
Come on. I'll help you up.
Then wait here. I'll be back soon.
Lust means letting desire control us.
What if you can't stop it?
You really won't come?
Come on. I'll help you up.
Here. I bought this for you.
Have some.
Hurry up. I wanna sleep.
Help me.
Eat it.
Hurry up. I need to pee.
Here.
Pee here.
No need to be shy.
Nice aim.
The answer is the Lost One.
Because the Lost One
always tells the truth.
(Next Episode) When the human heart starts
beating, it naturally begins to seek love.
Why?
I just haven't seen you
smile in a long time.
Barth!
Barth is so cool.
Do you think he likes Cherry?
I don't know if he likes her,
but Cherry definitely likes Barth.
But the question is: does every
kind of love bring us closer to Him?