(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Filming complied with guidelines
for children, youth, and animals.)
Why are you doing this?
He'll know who I am
if you say Lucky Joy Tech co-CEO.
Lucky Joy!
I just want to meet the CPO.
- Why are you throwing me out?
- Lucky Joy?
Do you...?
Do you remember me?
Thank you for helping me.
Excuse me!
Catch her!
We told you to stop!
I have something to discuss with the CPO!
What's wrong with you people?
- Gyeol.
- Why are you doing this?
I just want to meet the CPO,
- so why are you treating me like this?
- Hi, Seung Ri.
Just a moment!
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
I'm not sure either.
If you're free, shall we grab some tea?
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
If you try to enter illegally again,
we'll call the police.
What kind of place is this?
What is this, the NIS or the Blue House?
Seriously.
A girlfriend?
That's impossible.
What? Who threw water on whom?
Hello? Mrs. Kang?
Seo Seung Ri, how dare you?
You're starting work next week?
Yeah, that's how it turned out.
I see.
I thought you were just visiting
because of the Chairman.
That was the plan at first...
How about this?
For now, accept the Chairman's proposal.
The reason he made that proposal...
is probably because he's worried
about the future of Kangsu Group.
I'm sure he knows
that you're not really into management.
If he knows that, then why...?
Perhaps the Chairman felt that,
for the future of Kangsu Group,
a check was necessary.
What kind of check?
If you win the race,
even without directly stepping
into management,
you'll hold strong decision-making power
as the largest shareholder.
You'll be a powerful force
that can prevent anyone's tyranny.
There's no guarantee I'll win the race.
Of course not.
But perhaps he trusts your abilities,
and by making him compete with you,
he also wants to make Chief Ko stronger.
You said you have a debt
to repay to the Chairman, right?
It's painful to say,
but the Chairman
doesn't have much time left.
Think carefully
about what's best for the Chairman...
and Kangsu Group.
Okay, I'll think about it.
So did you wrap everything up
in the U.S. and come back?
Not wrapped up, just on pause.
Coming back, I hadn't planned on working
at Kangsu Construction.
- Which department?
- SP, Retirement Community Task Force.
Really? That's the same department as me.
Is it?
How did you handle things...
that the developer came all the way
to the company and caused a scene?
What? I'm sorry, Chief.
If that woman causes another scene,
we'll seriously reconsider
bringing you on.
Hey, what's going on?
Do you know why Gyeol suddenly...
decided to join the race?
Maybe he got greedy.
So, do you have a plan?
Do you have a way to beat Gyeol?
I'm the Chief Planning Officer
of Kangsu Construction.
Do you think I can't beat
some complete rookie?
Gyeol is a rising architect
the world is watching.
He's not an easy opponent.
I know that too.
So please pay attention
to building the team.
For design, we'll outsource
to the best design team...
in the country. Just keep that in mind.
Didn't you hear what your grandpa said?
If I don't manage and supervise fairly,
I'll be eliminated from the race!
Then what, just sit back and lose?
Let's go.
I think I've taken too much
of your work time.
Okay, Gyeol.
Should I call you Team Leader now?
The official appointment is next week.
Mother.
Hello, Ma'am.
What, "Hello?" I ought to...
Could you step aside for a moment?
- You sit.
- Yes.
Is something wrong, Mother?
Didn't you hear? I said go your own way.
Okay.
Why are you doing this, Mother?
Did you really throw water at Min Ho?
Yes, I did. He deserved it.
What? What did you say? He deserved it?
Mother, I don't know what this is about,
but please don't do this here...
Are you two-timing?
Are you weighing your options
between Min Ho and Gyeol right now?
Ma'am.
There are many people watching.
Please stop.
Let go!
Answer me. Why did you follow him there?
Why did you go
to someone else's blind date...
and get in the way of Min Ho's future?
I didn't follow him.
Please get your facts straight
before speaking.
My goodness.
- Look at this insolence.
- Mother.
I've held back all this time
for your parents' sake,
but I won't tolerate it anymore.
Watch your behavior, understand?
Do you want to get some air?
No, I should get back to work.
I'm tougher than I look.
I'm going to get an apology for today,
so don't worry too much.
What? You threw water at Seung Ri?
Yes, I did exactly...
what she did to you.
Mother.
What a nasty woman.
She didn't even blink...
and told me to get my facts straight.
Yes,
you should've gotten your facts straight.
I did something
that deserved getting drenched.
You...
Enough! Have you all lost your minds?
You startled me.
Do you even realize what time it is?
What do you mean? What time?
Void the contract?
It's a signed contract.
How is that possible?
Theoretically, it's impossible.
So I was planning to appeal to emotions,
but that's been completely blocked.
What do you mean? Explain it to me.
"It's true that my seal is on it,
but I didn't stamp it myself.
So the contract is invalid."
I was going to try to appeal to them
on a personal level.
Do you think that would work?
It wouldn't, right?
So I gave it some thought,
- and I need to change my approach.
- How?
A company's image is everything.
To open the door for negotiation,
I think I need to make some noise.
Don't tell me...
you're going to hold a demonstration,
shouting "Step down" and "Down with them?"
A demonstration? What demonstration?
We're doing a demo day soon.
Again?
It worked last time
and secured investment.
If we do it again and get more investment,
even better.
I see.
But is it okay to be relaxing like this
while working from home?
Who's relaxing?
We're having an idea meeting right now.
That's right.
I may not look it,
but I'm a part-time special employee
at Lucky Joy.
Sort of like an idea bank.
Is that so?
Come out and have lunch.
Even remote workers should eat on time.
I'll go eat with Grandma.
I need to help prepare for the shop too.
I'm going.
Why not eat together?
Bibimbap sounds good, right?
I'm not really in the mood
to eat right now.
No one's chasing you. Eat slowly.
Your vegetable bibimbap is so good,
it could bring
a runaway daughter-in-law back...
At least it's a relief...
that you're not starving yourself
over a breakup.
I told you it's not a breakup.
(Ji Hun)
Wait, is that jerk a player?
Going around with different women...
Mom.
Or did his family
oppose your relationship?
Is his family that impressive?
Please don't ever bring him up again.
I'm completely over him.
Do the dishes before you go upstairs.
You don't have to tell me.
All done.
Hello.
Hey. What's all done?
It's a Kangsu Construction survey
targeting real estate agents.
Do you get anything for doing that?
They say there's a small gift.
Well, nothing in this world
is free these days.
Anyway, why is the office...
so empty?
There's not a single customer.
It's like this all over the neighborhood.
There's no development boom,
and the transportation isn't great either.
More importantly,
I'm thinking of quitting real estate.
What do you think?
All of a sudden? Why quit?
I want to travel the way I never could
when I was younger...
and enjoy life a bit.
Sure.
The whole family is doing well,
so there's no need to waste your life...
in a cramped real estate office.
The biggest regret people have
when they die...
is not enjoying life
when they were younger.
When you say it like that,
it makes me feel sorry toward you.
Don't feel sorry for me.
We're not in the same situation.
You have every right to enjoy life.
Can I really do that?
Of course.
As you get older,
your children become your status.
A professor, a doctor,
and even a daughter who's a company CEO.
They're the top of the top.
You have every right to enjoy life.
What? Make them compete with Gyeol?
This is like handing it over
on a silver platter.
Maid, give me some cold water.
Where's the maid?
Out grocery shopping.
What is it?
Did something frustrating happen again?
It's fine, I'll do it myself.
Stay on Mother's good side.
There's nothing to gain
from upsetting her.
She's going to give away
the remaining 20 percent?
That's ridiculous.
Are you preparing kimchi or something?
Why so much ginger?
I'm going to make ginger pancakes.
What about lunch?
I'll take care of it myself.
Have you eaten, Mother?
You're all here.
What's all this? You didn't have to.
I thought the Chairman
would need soft food,
so I made some steamed sea bream.
If you have time for that,
keep your daughter in line instead.
What? What do you mean?
I told you, didn't I?
Don't even dream of reaching...
for something out of your league.
Not knowing her place,
she followed Min Ho to his blind date...
What? Seung Ri went where?
Not only did she follow him,
but she also threw water at Min Ho.
How did you raise your daughter?
What's wrong with you? Stop it.
I just got back...
after returning the favor to Seung Ri.
Wait, so you threw water at my Seung Ri?
Yes. Poke me with a needle,
I'll come back with a sword.
Be thankful she didn't get slapped.
I don't know the full details,
but Seung Ri wouldn't have gone there
on her own.
If you returned it with words, then I...
will return it tenfold. Keep that in mind!
Got it?
What?
If you have something to say, say it.
Don't just glare.
Calm down and go sit over there.
I'll make some tea, Jeong Ran.
I'm sorry, Madam. I'll take my leave now.
Just as Min Ho is a precious son to you,
Seung Ri is a precious daughter to me.
So what?
That's all I'm saying.
Did anyone say she wasn't precious?
So why...?
What's wrong with you, really?
I trust my daughter.
You must've had a reason to throw water.
What are you talking about? Throw water?
It's nothing, Dad.
Tell me what happened.
I went to the Chairman's house today...
I had a bit of an issue with Chief Ko.
It's nothing serious, so don't worry.
It is serious. Is only her son important?
My daughter is important...
Don't get involved in the kids' affairs
without any dignity...
Doesn't it upset you?
Stop it, Mom. I went too far too.
And I'll make sure I get an apology.
Really? You'd better.
Otherwise,
I'll be too upset to live with it.
Why did you stop eating?
I made expensive steamed sea bream
for once.
I'm done.
I'll get up too. Thank you for the meal.
This is really upsetting.
It's hot.
- Steamed sea bream!
- It's hot.
It's hot.
I see that you sent another gift
to the Chairman's family again.
What did you say?
And you,
wearing your sister's clothes again?
- I told you not to wear her clothes!
- Wait...
Did I or didn't I?
Geez...
You make my life so hard, seriously.
Don't touch me.
You know how your sister gets!
(Kangsu Construction HQ,
Day Shift Team One)
Hello, it's me.
I have a bit of a situation,
so I don't think I can take
the Kangsu Construction assignment.
Could you switch my area?
Are you saying you want
to pick and choose?
Then quit.
There are plenty
of others willing to do it.
Hello?
- This is nuts.
- Honey.
Cho Eun Ae, Dr. Cho,
everyone, come out here.
- Why? What's going on?
- You called, Mom?
Sit down, all of you. What do you think?
A Western Europe package.
France, Italy, Switzerland.
Your 60th birthday is coming up.
Let's go on a trip to Europe then.
Right, Dad's turning 60 soon.
Dad still looks so young,
but he's already 60?
You should plan something like that
gradually over time,
not suddenly like this.
What do you mean suddenly?
I've been talking about traveling...
to Europe for your 60th for 10 years.
You can take about ten days off, right?
Days off?
You didn't take your summer vacation
and worked all through it.
If you combine that, you should be able
to take ten days, right?
I can't take ten days off.
Things at work don't go as I want.
You're an executive at a major company.
You have all your legal holidays.
How have you not taken a single vacation
since last year?
She's right, Dad.
Go on the trip this time.
You've been too tied up with work.
I'll check my schedule at work first.
Don't say you can't.
You've raised your children well,
and you've faithfully provided
for this family all this time.
You deserve to enjoy that much. Right?
Of course you do.
And don't worry
about how much you should contribute.
I know your situations well.
Hasn't your situation improved, Eun Ae?
You even received an investment
from a major company.
Well, yeah.
It's fine.
Look.
This is the savings account I've built
for a trip over ten years.
You saved this for ten years?
Mom, you really had a plan all along.
How much is it?
One, two, three, four zeroes...
You saved 10,000 dollars?
Why make a face pack at home?
There are so many good ones these days.
Those can't compare
to handmade natural packs by me.
Dad, will this make me prettier?
Of course.
Mom needs it to keep her skin hydrated...
because airplane cabins are so dry.
You're already pretty, Bit Na,
but this will make you even prettier.
Why do you have a bandage on your finger?
I put some ointment on it.
I'm sleepy.
Bit Na, go to sleep if you're tired.
I'll take the pack off later
and carry you to your room.
Hey, Eun Nim.
What? A trip to Europe?
Okay, let's get together soon and plan it.
Who was that?
It was Eun Nim.
Mom and Dad are going to Europe
for Dad's 60th birthday.
Who celebrates 60 like that these days?
It's more like a turning point in life
than just a number.
So if we could contribute
to their travel expenses...
What?
Travel expenses?
You have to leave it on
for ten more minutes.
The face pack isn't the issue right now.
Who's paying for the travel expenses?
Mom said she's been saving for it,
so we shouldn't worry.
How can we just leave it at that?
As the eldest son,
I should at least contribute something.
With what money?
Think about it, honey.
Among my siblings, I've received
the most financial support from them.
And they take care of Bit Na too.
Of course I want to help too,
but are we really in a position to?
I'll think more about the travel expenses.
Go ahead and sleep.
I still have some lecture prep to do.
Good night.
What? You're leaving for work already?
It's not even 5 a.m.
I signed up for a pool near the office.
I think I've been gaining weight.
I'll work out
and go straight to work from there.
Swimming?
You can't go out on an empty stomach.
At least eat something.
No, I'll just eat something
after working out.
Get some more sleep.
Starting tomorrow,
I'll prepare something simple beforehand.
Make sure you eat breakfast.
Okay.
That's a relief.
Gyeol accepted your decision so readily.
He hasn't fully accepted it yet.
I hope Min Ho and his father...
also understand my intentions
and do their part.
Stop worrying about the children.
Who's worrying about whom?
Now it's your turn, Mrs. Lee Yeong Hwa.
How about we grant each other...
one wish a day?
Grant a wish?
Where's Gyeol?
He already left for work.
He could've gone with me.
He doesn't even have a car.
The car is ready, sir.
Why come here
instead of going straight to the company?
I have something to report privately
in the car. Let's go.
- I'll be back.
- Yes.
Let's go, sir.
Mr. Ju.
Do you have anything important...
to report to me in the car?
Pardon?
I feel like I gave you
an important instruction recently.
Spying on the Chairman's office...
Just go.
I said go. Get out.
Go.
Mother, I'll see you later.
Maid, make me an espresso...
Nevermind. I'll make it myself.
Kangsu Construction, wake up!
Give me back Joy!
It started and stopped!
Seriously.
Kangsu Construction, wake up!
Give me back Joy!
Hey, catch her!
Get her!
Remember this.
Kangsu Retirement Community...
was not just my dream,
but your father's too.
Yes, I understand.
Now that you've joined the company,
I can finally set my mind at ease
and take some time for myself.
Your time, Grandpa?
I've missed too much while carrying
Kangsu Construction on my shoulders.
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
Hello?
To the CPO's office? Yes, understood.
- Is it Chief Ko?
- Yes.
Learn well from him,
and compete well together.
Yes, I'll be going now.
Looks like...
it's almost time for me
to leave this place as well.
(Chairman)
I wonder...
how many times
will I be able to come here.
Kangsu Construction, wake up!
I need to use the restroom.
What should I do?
(Kangsu Construction)
Right.
We scan from here to here,
and then from that end like this.
I don't know.
I'm protesting, but there's no reaction.
Why isn't that CPO even budging?
Excuse me, is the cleaning lady inside?
Excuse me.
(Head of Division's Office)
I'm sorry. I'll clean it up right away.
Why is Dad here?
What did he just do to my dad?
Hey, you jerk!
(Our Happy Days)
I'm not a suspicious person.
I'm the developer
of the program your company acquired!
Are you Cho Seong Jun?
The top student from school
is now a janitor?
- Apologize to Seung Ri.
- Hey, no!
If you don't apologize,
I'll keep punishing myself.
Are you crazy?
It seems you're finally ready to talk.
Shall we begin?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)