(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Filming complied with guidelines
for children, youth, and animals.)
What do we do?
Eun Nim isn't answering her phone.
Mom and Dad are probably asleep by now.
She's probably so focused
on her serialization right now...
that she hasn't seen it.
I'll send her a text.
She'll probably check it before bed.
At this rate,
we might end up sleeping in the yard.
What? It'd be freezing.
All right, let's see your phone now,
Team Manager.
- Come on, hurry up.
- What? I'd rather not show you.
Let me see.
(Childish Bunny)
Wait, "Childish Bunny?"
You saved me as that because I'm childish?
No, that's not it.
Remember what you said
when you got out of the holding cell?
- I'm...
- I'm a very weak...
and fragile bunny.
A very weak and fragile bunny.
So I meant
a bunny fresh out of the holding cell.
Something like that.
Change it right now.
How can you use that awful holding cell
in my contact name?
Then what should I change it to?
Flying Kick Cho Eun Ae?
Or Drunk Cho Eun Ae?
Seriously.
You even have a video?
Delete this right now.
Delete this one first!
What's with you?
Digging through someone else's phone...
is a violation
of information network laws.
There you go again with the laws.
- Seriously, delete this.
- What is wrong with you?
Wait, hold on...
I said delete it.
Well...
Why would I delete it? It's my lullaby.
A lullaby? At your age?
Has Eun Nim still not seen the text?
Why bother her when she's working hard?
She'll open the door eventually.
I guess so.
Are you cold? Want my jacket?
No. You're cold too.
Want to share this blanket?
Sounds good.
The night air feels nice and cool.
Probably because the air is so clean
after the rain.
Are you sleepy?
No. I think it's just my body telling me
it's time to sleep out of habit.
How about borrowing my shoulder?
Excuse me? No thanks.
Cho Eun Ae? Team Manager Ko?
Dad.
Honey, on your way back from exercising,
could you grab some milk...
What are you all doing out here
so early in the morning?
Well...
Eun Hyeong.
Hello, Mom, Dad.
Grandma.
My little puppy's here.
What brings you here at this hour?
And what's with that bag?
I was hoping you could watch Bit Na
for a few days.
Are you going somewhere?
I thought Ji Seon switched
to an office position.
Let's go inside first
instead of standing out here.
- Right. Everyone, come on in.
- Get inside.
Bit Na, you haven't had breakfast yet,
have you?
- No, Grandma.
- Get inside.
What happened to you two?
Well...
Dad, you're late.
You should get ready for work.
What are you doing? Come inside.
This is my Team Manager.
He moved into your old room.
This is my big brother.
I see. Hello, I'm Ko Gyeol.
Hello, I'm Cho Eun Hyeong.
- I'll head in first.
- Okay.
What happened?
Did we both fall asleep...
while waiting for Eun Nim
to open the door?
I think so.
But your father won't get the wrong idea,
right?
What wrong idea? Cho Eun Nim, this girl...
What's wrong? Did you catch a cold?
I can't believe this.
Bit Na's mom is going on a business trip?
But she works in the office.
Even office staff
go on business trips sometimes.
My classes end late at night,
so please watch Bit Na for a few days.
That's no trouble at all.
There isn't some other problem, is there?
No. What other problem could there be?
Mom's apples...
Apples? Bit Na, do you want an apple?
Okay.
I'll peel one for you after breakfast.
I'll set the table.
You should go wash up too.
Okay.
I almost forgot.
Can we go see that place this morning?
Not today. I'll schedule another time.
All right then.
Mom went to look for apples.
Why did you lie, Dad?
Mom will find lots and lots of apples,
and she's going to surprise
Grandma and Grandpa.
So until then, it's a secret.
Okay, Dad.
Is Mother very ill?
I've never seen her unable
to get out of bed in the morning.
How exactly
has Mr. Seo been handling things?
I'll have a serious talk with him today.
Stay out of it, CEO Ko.
Why interfere in something you don't know?
Father,
you should just tell him everything.
We're the only ones
not being told anything.
How are we supposed to know?
Breakfast is ready.
Thank you. Father, please come eat.
I'm not hungry.
Father, you need to eat
before taking your medicine.
I'll eat later with your mother.
You eat and get to work.
What...
Why are you all standing here?
Aren't you eating?
What are you talking about?
Of course we are.
Son, go eat. You too, honey.
Yes, Mom.
Crystal, could you maybe
work on your expression a little?
Why? What's wrong with my expression?
You sound worried,
but your eyes are smiling.
Was it that obvious?
I'll be more careful.
How can she be so transparent?
She never changes.
Why did you get up
instead of sleeping more?
I slept enough.
You need to take your morning medicine.
You should eat first.
Stop worrying about me and sit down.
Just one day,
and your face already looks...
This is why I wanted to look
without you knowing.
It's not like this is the first time
we've been through this.
I was just too impatient this time.
This isn't your fault, so don't worry.
Yeong Hwa.
We'll find her. We definitely will.
Before I leave this world,
I'll keep that promise no matter what.
Can you stay too,
and meet Yeon Sun?
Isn't that possible?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry to you.
No words can express it.
No matter what happened back then,
I should've taken Yeon Sun with us.
If only I'd gone looking for her sooner.
Excuse me, what happened?
Where did the original owners go?
Why? Did they scam you too?
- Sorry?
- That couple...
took people's money
and ran away in the middle of the night.
They ran away in the middle of the night?
Then what about my daughter?
My Yeon Sun. Where is she?
How would I know?
I only bought this restaurant
at an auction recently.
Yeong Hwa, are you okay?
What about Yeon Sun?
Don't worry, Yeong Hwa.
No matter what it takes,
I'll find Yeon Sun. I promise.
What about Yeon Sun?
My Yeon Sun...
- Yeon Sun!
- Yeong Hwa.
Yeong Hwa.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't be like this in front of you,
but the tears just won't stop.
It's rice gruel.
You need to eat this
and get your strength back.
Thank you.
Mother, please think of me
as your daughter from now on,
and let it go.
I'll be a good daughter to you.
You know what they say,
"Water is thicker than blood."
Enough!
I'm sorry.
Please have some gruel, Mother.
How can someone be so thoughtless?
You should eat the gruel.
You can't skip your medicine.
Right. Let's eat.
Maybe I should send this back
through Seong Jun.
Apparently, it was Madam's daughter.
But CEO Ko is supposed
to be the Chairman's only child.
I have no idea what happened.
People's lives are all the same.
Once you look closely,
every family has its own story.
(Ham Cho Rong)
(Grandma's Bindaetteok)
One, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. One, two, three.
Grandma,
you've really caught the dance bug.
What? The dance bug?
How did you hold it in all this time?
Yeon Ja,
can we go to the dance hall
a little early today?
I need to get there early and practice.
I'm sorry. I don't think I can go today.
What are you talking about? Why not?
I have to pick Bit Na up.
Eun Hyeong has classes this afternoon,
and Bit Na's mom is away
on a business trip.
I practiced all night
so I could show off my skills...
in class today.
You should go. Why should you miss it
just because I can't go?
What fun would it be going alone?
I go because we're together.
Don't worry and go to the dance class.
I'll watch Bit Na.
Will you, Cho Rong? I feel bad.
Well, that's perfect then.
We're off and running.
Straight ahead.
Right, Sun Bun.
Try not to give that woman
such a hard time anymore.
Who? That stuck-up woman?
Why?
I get a real kick out of putting her
in her place.
That woman is my husband's boss's wife.
You mean that woman...
is the wife
of the CEO of Kangsu Construction?
Yes. If things get tense between us,
nothing good will come of it.
I'm going to be careful too.
Seriously, why did it have to be her?
This is bad.
That investment scam really blew up.
What investment scam?
A stock-tip chatroom scam.
Looks like there are tons of victims.
Apparently,
a lot of homemakers and young people...
with little investing experience
got scammed.
That's awful.
They probably invested money
they worked hard to earn.
A chatroom? Someone was running
a scam from their room?
Whose house?
- Not that kind of room.
- Okay.
Never mind, Grandma. Dance away.
Hello, Mother-in-law. Have you been well?
I'm sorry we don't visit more often.
It's fine. Everyone's just busy with life.
I already feel bad enough...
that you secretly send spending money
every month.
Not at all.
I wish I could send more, but right now...
Mother-in-law, by any chance, Ji Seon...
Ji Seon's doing well, right?
Maybe she thinks visiting her parents
will create more worries,
but she hardly calls these days.
It's not like that at all.
We'll come visit together soon.
Yes. Have a good day.
Where on earth did you go, Cheon Ji Seon?
Even if the scam ring gets caught,
there's no guarantee
you'll recover your investment.
Staying here won't change anything,
so please go home.
(Honey)
What do I do?
What am I supposed to do now?
What happened?
I trusted you and invested
because of what you said.
What on earth happened?
I'm about to lose everything
because of you!
What? How is that all my fault?
I'm sorry,
but you're the one who decided to invest.
I only gave you the information.
How much did you lose, anyway?
I lost 50,000.
Only 50,000?
I thought it was going to be
hundreds of thousands.
Anyway, good luck sorting it out.
I'm busy right now.
Hello? Hey!
Only 50,000?
You have no idea what that money means!
Do you know what that money means to us?
(Kangsu Construction)
Seriously.
Are there no other sites besides these?
Something with a great view of Hangang,
excellent transportation,
and a perfect commercial district nearby.
Isn't there anything like that?
For a location like that, you'd need...
to increase the budget
by at least five times.
Five times?
That would mean
spending nearly 30 percent...
of Kangsu Construction's annual budget
just to secure the land.
I told you not to argue with me
so many times.
What are you, my boss?
My mentor?
Why do you keep analyzing, criticizing,
and advising me?
Dae Chi.
Yes, Seong Jun.
What did you say?
Did you just call me by my name, Mr. Cho?
Yeah, I called you by your name,
Ko Dae Chi.
Let me ask you one thing as your friend.
Why did you hire me as your assistant?
What are you talking about?
You asked me to help you.
So despite my shortcomings,
I came here
believing I could offer advice...
from my experience and business knowledge,
and that you'd actually listen.
Right. And I'm grateful for that.
But if you're going
to completely ignore my opinions,
is there any reason for me to stay here?
Mr. Cho, what's gotten into you?
You're scaring me.
Okay, I went too far.
I apologize. I'm sorry.
I'll listen more carefully from now on.
I'll look for more sites
that meet your requirements...
and submit a revised report.
I'm counting on you.
This is driving me crazy.
How does he...
calmly tear someone apart like that?
He completely steamrolls me,
and I'm the CEO.
How am I supposed to tame him?
Why is my heart racing? He's my assistant.
Do you have a cold?
Excuse me? No. Maybe allergies.
Can rhinitis be contagious?
Why are you both sneezing
at the same time?
Is there a cold going around the office
or something?
Just say what you need to say.
Administration requested
the budget materials...
for the second round of evaluations.
Yes,
I'll send them as soon as they're ready...
Everyone, be careful not to catch a cold.
Why did it have to happen
to both of us at once?
I didn't even feel cold.
What's this?
Cold medicine.
It's important to treat a cold early.
Thank you, Manager Seo.
Were you with the Team Manager yesterday?
Sorry?
You know there are two things
you can't hide in this world, right?
A sneeze and love.
Manager Seo.
Ms. Cho Eun Ae,
do you like Team Manager Ko?
Do I have any reason...
to answer that question?
- Did you two make some kind of pact?
- What?
I asked the Team Manager
the same question.
Whether he likes you.
And he gave the exact same answer.
Gyeol and I...
lived under the same roof
for over ten years.
After my dad's business failed,
we lived in the annex
of the Chairman's house.
I've had a crush on him for a long time.
I think I was 21 when I confessed.
But he rejected me.
He said he was someone...
who could never love anyone.
Not long after that, he went abroad,
and everything stopped.
Wait a minute, Manager Seo.
Why are you telling me all this?
Will you just listen?
At the very least,
I think you should know.
After he joined Kangsu Construction,
my feelings for him grew again,
much deeper and stronger
than ten years ago.
I'm sorry, Manager Seo,
but I won't listen anymore.
I'm not feeling well right now.
Then...
Please take good care of my Gyeol.
As you know, once this competition ends,
he'll go back to where he belongs.
Until then, please be there for him...
and keep him from being lonely.
I don't think that's something...
you should be asking me to do.
What?
Before this moment passes
Enjoy it
This world made just for me
Don't the lyrics of this song
really speak to you?
Sure, I guess.
But why are you so full of energy today?
I don't know.
It's like everything's on my side.
You know what they say,
"You make your own luck."
Lately, I feel like the whole universe...
revolves around me.
What do you mean?
You know how Mother thought
she'd found her daughter?
That turned out to be a bust.
Really?
Poor Madam. She must've been so hopeful.
But is that really such good news for you?
Of course it is.
We almost had to split everything
into fractions of fractions...
Sis, come in.
Kang Yeon Ja, you're here.
Welcome, ma'am.
Welcome, Mrs. Cho.
Excuse me?
You got here early, Min Ho's mom.
Yes,
I wanted to practice the new choreography.
Did you get much practice in, madam?
Why do you keep calling me madam?
Just call me by my name.
How could I do that?
Your husband
is my husband's executive assistant.
I should call you madam.
Just call her that.
Sounds like she likes hearing it.
When did I say that?
Stand in the center.
No, you take this spot.
I'll graciously step aside
with my ocean-deep heart.
What's gotten into you?
By the way, Yeon Ja,
that tea you gave me yesterday...
smelled wonderful. What was it?
Burdock tea. I roasted it myself.
No wonder.
You'll have to teach me sometime.
Seriously? You met her without me?
What's your intention?
What intention?
- Hello.
- Ready?
- Yes.
Shall we enjoy ourselves again today?
- Yes!
Ready, five, six, start.
- The car is ready.
- Good.
Hello, Chairman.
Good. Settling into work all right?
I'm trying my best.
Mother still can't get out of bed today?
She's doing better than yesterday,
so don't worry too much.
Goodness.
She must've been devastated.
It's already been four days.
Don't go anywhere today.
Stay by Mother's side.
Is Madam ill?
I'll explain on the way.
Mr. Cho, as you probably saw in my notes,
don't forget the heated seat for CEO Ko
on the way to work.
Excuse me? The heated seat?
The seat warmer.
CEO Ko has hemorrhoids.
Seriously...
I'll get going.
I'll take my leave.
Bonne journée. Have a nice day.
Bonjour, my foot.
When did I say bonjour?
I said bonne journée. "Have a nice day."
Chairman,
would you like to take a walk
through the garden with me?
The roses are in full bloom.
Sure, why not?
Please put these in Madam's room.
Bonjour...
She needs to get better and go out again,
so I can open the safe.
Maid, did you finish making porridge?
(Kangsu Construction)
I told you to get off
where you usually do.
What if someone sees us?
We got here 30 minutes early.
Who's going to see us?
And I'm a patient, remember?
You're not the only one with a cold.
Can I ask you a favor? Today,
could you please be careful
with the coughing?
Like I can control when I cough.
Go on before someone sees us.
(Our Happy Days)
Your daughter and Team Manager Ko
seem to be dating.
That can't be true.
I think you've misunderstood.
He's leaving for the U.S. in a few months.
I wonder what got into him.
I'm going upstairs to pack some things.
I left a lot behind
when I moved out in a hurry.
Honey, where have you been?
Do you know how worried I was?
Eun Hyeong, let's get a divorce.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)