(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Filming complied with guidelines
for children, youth, and animals.)
(Episode 48)
Isn't this the place we came
with the Chairman last time?
You're right.
Is this really the address Gyeol sent?
Yes. This is it.
Well, look who it is.
Hello.
What brings you here?
Here for some bindaetteok again?
No, not this time.
Where exactly is this?
This is Eun Hyeong's house.
It's the address
of the real estate office?
Yes, 9 Jeongdam-ro 4-gil.
It's inside the real estate office.
What brings you here?
Ma'am, what brings you here?
Then this is...
Is my grandson renting a room
in your house?
Yes, that's right.
What? Gyeol is living at Mr. Cho's house?
Is Eun Ae's Team Manager your grandson?
Don't just stand out here.
Please come inside.
Okay.
I never thought...
Gyeol would be living in this house.
It's a small world, isn't it?
I should've told you sooner,
but Team Manager Ko told my husband...
not to tell his parents, so we couldn't.
I understand.
When I heard he even eats breakfast
and dinner with the landlord's family,
I wondered what kind of family
he'd ended up with.
Now that I know it's your family,
I feel much more at ease.
We just set out one more spoon
at the table when we eat.
We're not doing anything special for him.
By the way, why did you bring all this?
It's just some kimchi
and a few side dishes.
I felt like we've been imposing too much.
Imposing?
We charge him rent and meal expenses.
Right, are you fully recovered now?
Yes. After eating the soup
you made for me that day,
I got my strength back.
Thank you so much.
Don't mention it.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
I almost forgot. I heard your daughter...
works on the same team as Gyeol.
Do you know Eun Ae?
Yes. Long before we met,
there was a time
I almost collapsed on the street,
and your daughter helped me then.
I also saw her once
when my husband was in the hospital.
When I heard from Gyeol
that they worked on the same team,
I was so happy.
What an incredible coincidence.
I know.
His room is upstairs.
Would you like to take a look...
since you've come all this way?
Should I? Gyeol did tell me...
- to check out his room.
- Sure.
Okay.
Thank you for the food.
By the way, I heard that Team Manager
renting a room here...
is from the Kangsu Group family.
Yes, that's right.
He's Chairman Kang's second grandson.
Then that elderly gentleman
who came here before...
He's the chairman of Kangsu Group.
I thought he was the chairman
of some seniors' association.
A seniors' association? Come on.
To tell you about Chairman Ko Kang Su,
on April 10, 1980,
- he founded Kangsu Construction...
- Grandma.
I'll go pick up Bit Na.
Okay. Yeon Ja has guests over,
so go on and come right back.
But...
Why are you all dressed up
just to go pick up Bit Na?
Bit Na hasn't looked
very energetic lately.
I thought she might feel better
if her pretty aunt showed up.
Ta-da! Here's hoping it works.
I'll text Eun Ae's mother
and let her know I'm picking up Bit Na.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
That's strange.
Where have I seen her before?
The room is pretty small, isn't it?
Leaving a large, nice room
at the chairman's house...
to move into a place like this...
No.
This whole house feels warm and bright.
Now I understand
why Gyeol looked even better...
after moving out of the family home.
Not at all.
Please make yourself comfortable here.
It's almost time to pick up
my granddaughter from kindergarten.
I need to go out for a bit.
No, I should get going too.
I'll come back another time
when my grandson is here.
Why don't you stay until he gets off work?
I think it'd be nice if you saw him
and had a meal together.
I'll do that next time.
- Will you?
- Yes.
One, two, back rock.
One, two, back rock. One, two.
Back rock. One, two, back rock. One, two.
Back rock. One, two.
Ma'am,
have we really never met before?
I told you we haven't.
We're complete strangers,
so why do you keep talking nonsense?
Okay, I'm sorry.
One, two, three, and...
At the lobby...
What the heck?
Are you trying to hit on me right now?
Are you asking for a beating?
Are you done talking?
Yes.
Please continue looking after my grandson.
There's no need to ask me.
They say that as people age,
their whole life shows on their face.
But I don't see any trace
of life's hardships on yours.
You look like you've walked nothing
but flower-lined roads.
Come on.
Fate really is...
Sorry?
Well...
Fate is such a mysterious thing.
That's all I meant.
I should go pick up my granddaughter now.
Take care.
No,
Cho Rong already went to pick up Bit Na.
She said she'd text you.
Really?
I haven't checked...
You're right.
I almost forgot.
My husband loves the bindaetteok here.
Could I get some to go?
Of course.
Just wait a little.
I'll make you a special batch
fresh off the griddle.
Hello?
Yes, long-term rentals
are hard to find these days.
You're coming now? Okay, I'll wait.
I have a customer coming.
Then you should get going.
Please come back
when your grandson is here.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
So, did you talk to your daughter?
She's got a thing going on
with Team Manager Ko, right?
I don't think they're dating yet.
What are you talking about?
I guarantee you those two are dating.
I'm telling you, it's obvious.
How can you be so sure?
I told you
I saw them eating lunch together before.
I was shocked.
Gyeol has never opened his heart
to anyone before.
Anyway, it's a fact.
Are you okay with it, sir?
With what?
With my daughter dating your son.
If they are, then they are.
What's the problem?
I'm not that narrow-minded.
Do you know how free-spirited
and open-minded I am?
Mr. Cho,
can't you tell just by looking at me?
Come on, take a good look.
Look at me. Does this look
like a corporate CEO's fashion?
With my physique and everything,
I look more like a model or an actor.
Right.
Take a good look around.
See this?
The colorful palette,
the dynamic furniture.
I picked all of it myself.
Good grief.
Did you think I would...
oppose them
over some family alliance nonsense?
It's not even Min Ho. Why would I object?
Seriously, I don't care at all.
I told you already.
Gyeol is going back to the U.S. soon.
You think a few months of dating
means marriage?
If they love each other,
that could happen.
Why not?
What?
So you're saying...
you and I could become in-laws, Mr. Cho?
Listen, I guarantee it.
That will never happen. So stop dreaming.
Seriously, that's hilarious.
Right.
And what was that thing from before?
Factorial or whatever it was.
You said you could figure out
the password with that.
How do you do it?
Why don't you find another way?
Either way, you'll lose your finger.
What? Wait.
Is Cho Seong Jun upset with me?
Because I told him to stop dreaming
about becoming in-laws?
That's ridiculous.
Let me carry that. It looks heavy.
I'm fine.
From now on, call me
when you have something heavy to carry.
Why all of a sudden?
Don't you know I'm strong?
Got it, Intern Cho?
And my grandma talked things over
with your mother...
and headed home.
Really? She won't tell
the rest of your family, will she?
Don't worry.
Come on. Let's go to the meeting.
- I'll stop by the restroom first.
- Okay.
You look pretty today.
All my usual clothes are in the wash,
so I didn't really have a choice.
It doesn't suit me, right?
What do you mean?
Your outfit practically screams
that you're in love.
How could you not look pretty?
What?
Do you have plans after work?
No, I don't.
Really? Then could you make some time
for me tonight?
Yes, I transferred the membership fee.
My daughter is in the Gold tier?
How many matches can you arrange at most?
Of course I prefer professionals.
As you can see from my daughter's profile,
quality matters more than quantity...
No, please make sure
you find someone truly worthy of her.
Yes, thank you.
Wait, what was that about?
What's this Gold tier,
and preferred professionals for matching?
You don't need to know.
Don't tell me you're trying
to put Seung Ri on the marriage market.
- What?
- That's exactly it.
You're trying to auction off
Seo Seung Ri...
through a matchmaking agency.
Auction her off? What nonsense.
I'm just trying to help her
find a good match.
Then what about Min Ho?
What about Min Ho?
You invited him over before...
and treated him like a son-in-law already.
Min Ho is done. I told you that.
If nothing's happened in ten years,
then it's just a waste of time.
I can't stand watching your sister
suffer anymore.
I'm going to find her a respectable man...
and get her married as soon as possible.
What a traitor.
I'm telling Min Ho
and Seo Seung Ri everything.
Just try running your mouth.
I'll shake you down
and hang you out on the balcony.
How terrifying.
Madam Yu Jeong Ran, who did this to you?
Who turned such a delicate, graceful lady
into this?
What? Gyeol is living at Mr. Cho's house?
Yes. As you've probably felt too,
the couple is very kind and warm-hearted.
I think Gyeol has adjusted well there too.
I'm glad to hear he's doing well.
Since Gyeol doesn't want
other people to know,
please keep it to yourself.
I already told Mr. Ju
to keep his mouth shut too.
I understand what you mean.
Mother,
you're already back from Gyeol's place?
Yes. Where did you go?
Well,
I've been under a lot of stress lately.
And there's nothing better than shopping
to relieve stress.
Mother, when you visited Gyeol's place,
didn't you notice anything?
- Notice?
- Signs of a woman.
You know, women's clothes,
long strands of hair, matching pajamas...
Watch what you say in front of Father.
I'm done eating.
Do you think Gyeol moved out
for no reason?
He did it
so he could freely date that girl.
You saw the photos
saved on his computer last time.
The intern from the Planning Office.
Turns out she's Mr. Cho's daughter.
Those two are completely smitten
with each other right now.
What?
Did you hear that from him?
Well, not exactly.
Then why are you making such a fuss
when nothing's even confirmed?
I'm not making a fuss.
And besides,
is Gyeol's love life
some kind of spectator sport?
Please try to think like a mother
for once.
Think about why Gyeol...
ended up drifting so far away.
Why am I getting blamed? What did I do?
I think we have enough ideas now
for a companion version of Joy.
How would
the Senior Dating Coach app work?
Ms. Cho Eun Ae, are you listening?
Sorry?
The dating coach app.
Well, that idea isn't fully organized yet.
I'll submit it by tomorrow.
Okay.
You have the statistical data
on profitability organized, right?
- Yes, here it is.
- Okay.
There's no need to be so nervous.
There's something important
I wanted to ask you.
Okay.
And don't tell Team Manager Ko.
He might not like it
if I take up the time of a team member...
who's busy preparing for the competition.
Okay.
Then I'll see you after work.
What does she want to talk about?
Let's wrap up today's meeting here.
Joy seems to be upgrading smoothly.
Your contribution to the second round
has definitely been significant, Eun Ae.
The meeting ended early too.
Then I'll head out first.
- Good work today.
- See you tomorrow.
Bye.
What's wrong? Is something bothering you?
What? Something bothering me?
No, not really.
Then shall we meet at the bus stop
in ten minutes?
You should go home first.
Something came up.
What came up all of a sudden?
Don't tell me you're all dressed up
for a blind date or something.
A blind date? Give me a break.
You go ahead.
I'm home.
Welcome back. Perfect timing.
You're here.
Why are you alone... Where's Eun Ae?
She has something to do,
so she'll be a little late.
Really? Right. You know
your grandma stopped by today, right?
Yes, I know.
Is there anything I can help with?
Go upstairs, change your clothes,
and come down.
Your grandmother brought tons of kimchi
and side dishes.
I didn't really do anything.
Okay. I'll be right down.
All these side dishes came
from the chairman's house?
That's right.
That elderly lady is incredibly attached
to her grandson.
But doesn't it seem strange?
Usually when a child moves out,
it's the mother who worries more
than the grandmother, right?
I told you.
The mother in that family is completely...
Bit Na.
You need to eat a lot tonight.
Not just a tiny bit like yesterday.
Okay, Grandma.
Why do you seem so down, Bit Na?
You need to eat well and stay cheerful
at Grandma's house...
so your mom will be happy
when she gets back from her business trip.
Cho Bit Na,
why are you crying all of a sudden?
Do you miss your mom?
Bit Na, your mom will be back soon. Why...
Honey, call Eun Hyeong later...
and tell him to come home
and sleep here tonight.
Bit Na can't go on like this.
Okay. He's probably teaching right now,
so I'll call him a little later.
There. Don't cry.
That's my pretty Bit Na. There.
What's this appointment anyway?
Could it really be a blind date?
What? You want me
to tell you everything about Han Ji Hun?
Yes. You've worked on Joy
with him for five years.
You should know him better than anyone.
That's true, but I'm not sure
what exactly you want me to tell you.
What I want to know most is...
how much Han Ji Hun contributed
to Joy's development...
and what his actual capabilities are.
I shouldn't be saying this
in front of a member of the opposing team,
but while preparing for this competition,
I've started to seriously question
Han Ji Hun's abilities.
The second round is largely evaluated
on how Joy is utilized.
And from what I've seen,
it's hard to believe Han Ji Hun played...
a key role in Joy's development.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I don't think I can answer that.
Sorry?
You know
Han Ji Hun and I are on bad terms...
because of the company acquisition issue.
If I say anything,
it wouldn't be objective.
And now that we're working
on separate teams,
honestly, I don't even know...
how far Han Ji Hun's abilities
have progressed.
I feel like I've put you
in an uncomfortable position.
Yes, honestly,
it isn't a comfortable question.
Well, if it's difficult for you to answer,
there's nothing I can do.
I'm sorry, Manager. Then I'll...
Wait.
I took up a lot of your time,
so let me drive you home.
What? No, that's okay.
I can just take the bus.
I'm heading home anyway. Don't say no.
Otherwise, I'll feel terrible.
- Let's go together.
- Wait...
Why are the two of them together?
Wait, so Mother went to Gyeol's place?
That's what I'm saying.
She packed up all kinds of food...
to give to the landlord's family.
I mean,
Gyeol isn't even her biological grandson.
I don't know why she's so devoted to him.
Maybe Gyeol is her weak spot.
Don't even get me started.
She practically scolded me today,
telling me to be a proper mother.
Enough with the nonsense.
Crystal, we just need to focus
on opening that safe.
Right, the safe.
This isn't the time for me
to be worrying about other things.
Honey, I've got it.
An absolutely brilliant idea.
What is it?
A staged robbery.
A staged robbery?
We'll make it look like burglars
broke into the house.
Masked robbers.
Masked robbers?
Who's there?
At that moment,
I'll cut the power.
- And you'll grab the entire safe and run.
- Thief!
Thief!
A thief?
Thief! Thief!
Mother, are you okay?
Meanwhile, I'll go into the room
and buy you time to escape.
We'll just steal the whole safe outright?
Exactly. Then we'll hand it over
to a trustworthy company...
and have it forced open.
Everyone at home will think
it was the work of burglars.
Crystal,
that's actually pretty innovative.
But do you think it'll really work?
There's an emergency alarm...
next to Father's bed. An emergency alarm.
Don't move.
Who are you? Get over here.
Hold still, you punk.
Let's have a look.
Lift your head.
"You punk?"
Dad!
No!
I mean, Min Ho may have served
as a cook in the military,
but he was still a Marine.
If he catches you,
something's definitely getting broken.
And if I get crushed,
are you going to take responsibility?
Did my imagination go too far?
Way too far.
Please get a grip, Crystal.
Now, red sun.
I don't know.
Then what are we supposed to do?
We need to open the safe to find out
where Father's remaining shares are going.
So the best solution
is to find Mother's biological daughter.
Then if we can just learn her birthday,
we can...
Wait, but if we find her,
you only get a fraction of a fraction...
So that's not going to work either.
If that idiot Gwon Sik would just talk,
it'd be game over.
He's just too tight-lipped.
What? A matchmaking agency?
Yes. I need to find Seung Ri someone
as soon as possible.
I can't keep watching her suffer.
Do you think Seung Ri
will obediently agree to blind dates?
Of course I won't tell her
it's a blind date.
Who knows? Maybe she'll unexpectedly meet
someone wonderful.
I don't intend to keep watching her suffer
because of Gyeol.
Who does Gyeol like?
Don't tell me it's Ms. Cho Eun Ae.
Yes. And she likes Gyeol too.
I'm going to make Seung Ri happy,
no matter what.
What is she worrying herself sick
about today...
that she's still not home?
You should head back now.
We're almost there.
I said I'd drive you all the way home.
Where do you live?
Just a little farther.
Thank you for the ride.
Come to think of it,
your parents and my parents
all know each other.
Since we're already here,
should I stop by your house and say hello?
What? My house?
(Team Manager Ko Gyeol)
Ms. Cho Eun Ae.
You said you had plans.
Your plans were with Manager Seo?
What? Yes...
Manager Seo gave me a ride home.
What are you doing here, Gyeol?
Why are you at Ms. Cho Eun Ae's house?
I live here.
What? What did you just say?
Exactly what you heard.
I live in the same house as Cho Eun Ae.
I'm sorry, Manager.
Team Manager Ko moved in
without knowing this was my house,
and I only found out afterward...
Why are you apologizing, Ms. Cho Eun Ae?
Was I supposed to tell you where I live?
Gyeol.
Team Manager.
Considering you came all the way here
this late,
it seems like you already know everything.
Am I wrong?
Stop it!
(Our Happy Days)
What did you just say? You got divorced?
Divorced all of a sudden? Why?
Let's go to Eun Hyeong's house.
Let's talk things through
with Ji Seon together.
Ji Seon left.
Make some time tonight.
Why?
Because I want to have dinner with you.
Where are you? I'm here already.
What? A blind date?
I'm leaving, and I'm never coming back.
Then what about me?
What am I supposed to do if you leave,
Team Manager?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)