(All characters, organizations,
and events in this drama are fictitious.)
(Filming complied with guidelines
for children, youth, and animals.)
(Episode 35)
Found you.
My goodness!
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
You call that okay?
That must hurt.
You're so careless.
Why did you suddenly show up like that?
Do you know how startled I was?
What's wrong?
What's this?
It's my lucky charm. Why?
Your lucky charm? Let me see.
Where did you get this?
My first love gave it to me. Why?
Your first love?
Yes, my first love.
Wasn't there a name written
on the flagpole?
Yes, was it Han Byeol? No, Han Gyeol...
But how do you know that?
Don't tell me
you're that boy from back then!
Are you okay? That must hurt.
Stick this in here.
What do I do?
It's okay.
If it collapses, we can rebuild it.
This is a lucky flag.
My dad made it for me.
If you have it,
you won't be scared when you're alone,
and it gives you courage.
Give it back next time we meet.
I come here every Saturday.
Next time, I'll make you a house
out of ice cream sticks.
Bye.
No way. How...
How could that boy be you, Team Manager?
I know, right?
That little kid was you, Ms. Cho Eun Ae?
Unbelievable.
But the kid I knew...
was really cute and adorable.
How did you turn out like this?
Look who's talking.
That boy was so brave and cool back then.
Now...
I was brave and cool, wasn't I?
So that's why I was your first love.
First love? I was only five back then.
Is something wrong with my hearing?
I'm pretty sure you said "first love."
That's just how I put it.
But why did you change your name?
I thought
your last name was Han back then.
So you were originally Ko Han Gyeol.
Well, yes...
You liar. You trickster.
What? Liar? Trickster?
You said you came here every Saturday.
Do you know how long I waited here
every Saturday?
- You waited for me?
- Yes.
After a while, I even went
to that apartment construction site.
Tell me. Why didn't you keep your promise?
When did I ever make that kind of promise?
This is ridiculous.
You're talking as if I'm making this up.
You said your dad was throwing you
a birthday party that day. Did it go well?
Yes, it did.
So that person was CEO Ko Dae Chi.
What a small world.
What is it?
Come here.
The password was 000.
It's so simple, it puts me to shame.
Stop. Freeze.
Crystal, I don't think this is right.
You said we need to know the enemy
and ourselves to win.
Well, we need to know
what Gyeol will do for the second round...
to come up with a plan, right?
- That goes without saying.
- Right.
- You know for sure, right?
- Yes.
What are you two doing here?
You startled me.
What are we doing?
Wait, what were we doing here?
What do you mean, what?
We're just trying to get some info
in case Gyeol takes your spot. Why?
Stop what you're doing and come out.
Let's talk in my room.
I've told you several times, haven't I?
Please trust me.
Of course we trust you. Who said we don't?
Then why?
What are you trying to get
from Gyeol's laptop?
You know, that "Know your enemy" thing...
I said I don't need anything,
so why are you doing this?
Are you getting full of yourself?
If you mess up...
Then I'll be the one to fall,
and I'll be the one to step back.
I'm going to compete
with Gyeol fairly this time.
I told you before, Dad!
You did, yes.
So from now on, I'm neutral. Neutral gear.
How can you be so spineless?
Just a moment ago, you were on my side,
and now you're siding with Min Ho?
Hey, didn't you see
your grandpa's eyes last time?
It's not over till it's over.
Gyeol has already...
Please stop talking about Gyeol!
Just leave already.
We were about to leave. Retreat.
All right, retreat.
Hurry up and go.
Where have you been?
Mom, did you clean my desk?
No, why?
How can you be like that?
I know Min Ho dotes on you, but still...
Did Chief Ko come into my room?
He wanted to see your childhood photos,
so just for a moment.
- Mom, seriously!
- What?
If you weren't my daughter...
Who would put up with that temper?
But isn't it amazing
the more you think about it?
How could we meet again like this?
More than that, I'm amazed...
that you still have that clover piece.
What's this?
Your tone's been getting more casual
since earlier.
Because I'm older.
That brave and cool first love.
That's all in the past.
You're not going to ask for this back,
are you?
I can't do without this.
All right.
But what's going on?
What?
You look a bit different from usual today.
Why are you so dressed up?
What? Who's dressed up?
I usually wear this at home.
So you dress like this casually at home?
What I wear at home
is none of your business.
- Go on inside.
- Yes, you should go too.
Right, what did you urgently want
to discuss about the second round?
We didn't get to talk about it.
Let's talk about it at work on Monday.
All right. Get home safely.
Goodbye.
What a coincidence.
(Room for rent, Deposit - 10,000 dollars,
Rent - 500 dollars)
A 10,000-dollar deposit
and a 500-dollar rent?
Is that cheap?
(Room for rent, Deposit - 10,000 dollars,
Rent - 500 dollars)
It's been so long...
since the whole family sat together
for a meal like this.
Since Dad became unemployed...
No, since he lost his job,
this is the first time.
Bit Na, your bright memory is impressive,
but do you really have to shine a light
on Dad's dark past too?
So you got a job
at a children's writing cram school?
Yes, even though
it's a small neighborhood cram school,
it's very rewarding and enjoyable.
Being with children full of pure hearts...
and limitless imagination...
makes me feel like
I've gone back to those days.
Ji Seon, could you bring more japchae?
Sorry? Right, okay.
Please, be more mindful.
Am I not mindful?
Well, you're not exactly known for that.
Don't talk like you're any better.
You're just as clueless, you know?
Well, what can you do?
You all take after me.
Right? Isn't that so?
All right, let's eat.
Eat up.
You're not satisfied
with his cram school job, are you?
Since he lost his job,
he has to earn money,
so I understand he has no choice.
You heard him.
He says it's rewarding and enjoyable.
I wonder if he still plans
to return to teaching at a university.
I still stand by what I said.
- Sorry?
- I ended up...
coming back home like this,
but you're still young,
so make the right decision.
Don't worry about what anyone thinks,
and think only about your life.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Mom's japchae really is the best.
I love your zucchini pancakes, Mom.
- Eat a lot.
- Same here.
All right,
I have something to say to all of you.
In life, you can lose your job,
get scammed, or have accidents.
From now on,
if anyone is going through a hard time,
don't keep it bottled up.
Just talk about it.
We kept things quiet
and hid things in consideration,
and look what almost happened
to our family.
So there should be no secrets
among family, right?
You catch on the fastest, Bit Na.
Dad, actually, this morning,
the omelet rice you made wasn't that good,
but I said it was
because I didn't want to disappoint you.
Family means sharing everything.
Not just the good things,
but the hard, exhausting,
and painful things too.
Right, I'll start with myself.
From now on, I won't carry burdens alone.
I'll do the same right away.
I made it seem like I was teaching
at a university, not a cram school,
and I almost got divorced because of it.
- Seriously...
- Eun Hyeong,
isn't that too much to do to your wife?
Exactly. You scolded me
for hiding that I dropped out.
You dropped out? When?
A while ago.
Everyone, don't lose confidence
just because things don't go as planned.
Hold your heads high.
With a family like this,
what's there to be afraid of?
Everyone,
pick up the glass in front of you.
I'll lead, so shout, "Don't be scared."
Our family!
- Don't be scared!
Where's Seung Ri?
I don't know.
She's in a bad mood
and locked herself in her room.
You shouldn't have invited Chief Ko
without asking.
Someone had to step in.
No matter how much effort
she puts into Gyeol...
Things will go as they're meant to.
Can you really change that?
What are you doing? You keep fidgeting.
Are your phones all fine?
I mean, my phone is fine.
Why am I not getting a call?
It's here. It's the writer.
Really? Answer it. Put it on speaker.
Wait, I'm nervous.
Hello? Who is this?
Didn't you save my name?
Of course I did.
Then why ask who it is?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
This punk...
Let's meet tomorrow.
Yes, where should we meet?
Our fateful and inevitable Café 67?
Yes, be there by 1 p.m.
The producer will be there too.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, writer.
Mom, Dad, I did it!
Congratulations, son.
But why is that writer so cold?
Who does she think she is,
treating you like that?
Whether she treats me
like a rat or a loach,
I, Seo Seung Wu,
finally get to turn this writer's novel...
into a webtoon.
It's too early.
Didn't I tell you not to count
your chickens before they hatch,
and to wait until the contract's signed
and the money's in your account?
Why wouldn't I count my precious chickens?
It's good.
So, how was your date?
It wasn't a date.
What is it?
You've got something to tell me, right?
As a novelist,
what do you think of an event where...
I reconnect with someone
I met just once 25 years ago?
We've been next to each other
all this time without even knowing it...
Don't tell me your team manager
is the one you met 25 years ago?
You're like a psychic.
That's fate.
Fate, my foot.
Anyway, it was really strange.
At first, things were so twisted,
we were practically enemies.
You like him, don't you?
Hey, no way. Why would I like him?
What do you mean, no?
Excitement is written all over your face.
It's not.
And he's someone I shouldn't like.
What do you mean?
Actually,
there's someone who really likes him.
She's liked him for a very long time.
I don't think
I should get in the middle of that.
Do you have some kind
of good-girl complex?
Or is he married?
Hey! Don't talk nonsense.
It's not like that.
Based on my extensive dating experience
and my instincts as a novelist,
and everything I've overheard
through the wall between you two...
"Everything I've overheard?"
What did I do?
I heard it all.
Dating using rehearsals as an excuse?
You and that team manager
have already started something.
Hey, don't say something so ridiculous.
Don't you dare say anything weird
in front of Mom and Dad, okay?
What does she even know?
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
You call that okay?
That must hurt.
Come to think of it,
he's just like back then.
How come I didn't recognize him?
Dad, I met that kid.
The one I met at the playground
on my birthday.
Back then, you praised me
for helping someone weaker.
Come to think of it,
that was the last time
you ever praised me.
Who is that? You made a friend?
She is younger than me.
The neighborhood kids were bullying her,
so I helped.
She said she was waiting
for her mom over there.
Really?
You know how to help those in need now...
You're all grown up, Gyeol.
Let's go. I made a reservation
for your birthday dinner.
Yes, Dad.
Dad,
I think I have feelings for that kid...
No, right? I'm leaving soon anyway.
Come in.
Grandma.
You miss your dad a lot, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Let's have breakfast together
on your birthday this year.
Grandma, I...
I know it's hard for you
to even celebrate...
when it's your father's
death anniversary..
Still, this birthday...
Who knows if we'll be able...
to spend it together
with your grandpa next year?
I'll think about it.
And how about changing
your laptop password?
Why? Did someone use my computer?
Well, not exactly,
but you might as well change it
since you're in the competition.
Well, I'm sure you'll handle it yourself.
- You should sleep.
- Yes.
Good night, Grandma.
- All right.
- Yes.
By the way, how are you going to start
your first day with a cast on?
I guess I'll have to ask the CEO
for his understanding tomorrow.
You'll ask the CEO yourself?
Right, your salary...
There I go again.
What does the salary matter?
These days,
I should be grateful you even have a job.
Right,
I'm thinking of renting out Eun Ae's room.
What? Then what about Eun Ae?
She'll just share a room
with Eun Nim again like before.
Do you really have to go that far?
After Eun Hyeong got married,
Eun Ae and Eun Nim...
were so happy
to finally have separate rooms.
They'll just have to deal with it.
We still have a lot to do.
Eun Ae and Eun Nim's weddings,
and preparing for our retirement.
I'm sorry for everything.
Instead, let's definitely go on a trip
for your 60th birthday.
I'll keep that promise no matter what.
From now on,
we need to take care of our health first.
Don't you know that health
is the greatest asset as we get older?
I like listening to you nag like this.
You're so easy to please.
So, your janitor friend is starting
at the secretary's office next week?
Yeah, but...
he agonized over that decision so much,
I thought I'd grow a tumor from stress.
Unbelievable.
Why hesitate when a friend sets you up...
as the CEO's secretary?
But if you think about it
from his perspective,
it makes sense.
A guy who used to be top of the class...
now working as a friend's assistant
at his age. That's not easy.
Still, it's better than cleaning.
- True, that's true.
- Yeah.
And speaking of which,
how about inviting him and Gwon Sik over
next weekend,
with their spouses?
Invite them over? Why?
You guys should just have dinner together.
Come on.
I want to show Mr. Seo that Seong Jun,
who's even more capable than him,
is my secretary.
It'd also be nice for the wives
to get to know each other.
You just want to show off, don't you?
Show off? Me?
Well, yeah.
Friends who were top of their class
and went to top universities...
are now both working
as assistants for our family.
I'll bring in a five-star hotel chef...
and throw an amazing garden party.
Are you out of your mind?
Father is sick,
and you're talking about a garden party?
Just keep it simple at home.
Mother's cooking is great.
Right.
Then how about making Mother
the head chef...
and having the housekeeper and Jeong Ran
assist her?
Do whatever you want. What will you do?
Me?
I'll be the general director of the party.
I have to go to the salon,
oversee the food, the flowers...
There's a lot for me to handle.
Wait. Let me do it. I'll do it.
- Seriously, you...
- Here.
This reminds me of our newlywed days.
You used to tie my tie like this
every morning.
How did you not even know
how to tie a tie back then?
There, it's done.
It's not that I couldn't tie it.
I just liked you doing it for me.
So I just pretended.
What?
Congratulations on your first day
at Kangsu Construction, Dad.
What first day?
I've been going there all along.
Hurry, Dad. We'll be late.
I'll be going now.
It's nice seeing a father and daughter
go to the same company.
- I'm heading out too.
- Okay.
- Take care.
- All right.
- You too, Eun Ae.
- Yeah.
What? To Gyeol's father's columbarium?
I'd go myself,
but in this condition, I can't.
So could you take Gyeol?
Since he can't drive, use my car.
Yes, actually today is...
Seong Jun's first day
at the secretary's office,
so I was going to the company
for the handoff.
I'll take Gyeol around lunchtime.
All right, I appreciate it.
Why seaweed soup?
It's Gyeol's birthday today.
How could you not know that as his mother?
Honestly, how is he supposed
to eat seaweed soup...
on his father's memorial?
He's never had a proper birthday meal
because of that.
I made it so that won't happen anymore.
Did you sleep well?
Tell Gyeol to come down.
He left early.
Right,
and he asked me to tell you he's sorry.
I told him so many times
to have breakfast together today.
(Kangsu Construction)
Where is Team Manager Ko Gyeol's seat?
It's over here.
Flowers?
It's a company tradition.
The admin team sends a flower basket
on employees' birthdays.
What? It's his birthday today?
Shouldn't we throw him a surprise party?
Right. Should I go buy a cake?
Let's just keep it low-key.
Okay. Good morning, everyone.
From today, let's start fresh...
and give it our all for the second round.
Team Manager Ko took a half-day today,
so keep that in mind.
What? A half-day?
(Ko Gyeol)
Mr. Seo.
Team Manager Ko.
(Our Happy Days)
- What? A studio?
- I'm good.
- We're now...
on the same boat. We're comrades.
I want to see him properly settled
before I go,
so please help him out.
Team Manager Ko doesn't even like cake,
so you didn't have to go to the trouble.
Well, Manager Seo
always takes good care of things.
Still,
I wanted to congratulate him sincerely.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)