(A restaurant in Seoul)
(Why have the three siblings gathered together?)
(We will send you on a vacation abroad.)
(Congratulations on going on a vacation abroad.)
(The new youngest sibling who will join them, Kim Hye Yoon)
(How will the vacation of the four siblings go?)
(This is a vacation?)
(This itinerary...)
(can be changed!)
(Was that so?)
- This is it! - Right!
- Yes! - Yes!
(I don't want to work!)
(After a desperate struggle to secure their vacation,)
(the itinerary for their trip abroad has been completed.)
(We did our best for this. Where are we going?)
(It's the Maldives, isn't it?)
(Where will the four siblings go for their vacation?)
(Bohol, Philippines)
(Gosh, hello?)
(Screams can be heard instead at the peaceful vacation spot.)
(The spectacular vacation begins.)
(The ruler of the mangrove forest awaits the four siblings.)
(The tyrant of the mudflat)
(Alimango)
(Catch the alimango!)
(I want to go home.)
- Are you okay? - No.
(The four siblings get exhausted by the tough labor.)
(After working for a while...)
(It's huge!)
(Jun Myun manages to make the first catch!)
(After Jun Myun's catch,)
(Dex also catches one!)
(Laughing)
(Try to catch one, Jung Ah.)
(It's my turn this time!)
(Will the four siblings manage to complete their work?)
I'll also look for one.
I'm Kim Hye Yoon.
The girl who has managed to make bread.
(She tries again with the same tenacity to bite on the bread.)
Let's poke everywhere I can.
Poke everywhere.
(She pokes everywhere.)
Give it a poke.
Let's poke everywhere I can.
Why am I not hearing any sounds?
I have to find one.
Hold on.
(She has been poking countlessly.)
(This isn't being replayed.)
Where on earth are the crabs?
(Going blank)
Where are they?
(Panting)
(Rage)
(She has been poking for a while while being filled with rage.)
I should go when Dex isn't watching...
and steal one from his basket...
to pretend I was the one who caught it.
This won't work.
(The bright character gets possessed again.)
What do I do? Gosh.
Hold on.
Hold on!
Why are bubbles coming up here?
Look here. You see the bubbles, don't you?
(She starts raking without hesitation.)
(It feels like a catch is near this time.)
(Hye Yoon picks something up.)
I...
(Did she finally meet the alimango?)
caught a cute clam, everyone.
(Peek-a-boo!)
(Has she lost it?)
Why is a clam here? I just don't get it.
(While Hye Yoon is poking at the mudflat,)
Gosh.
(Leader Yum is poking as well.)
(Let me find just one!)
What?
(Did she sense an alimango?)
What? There's...
something here.
(Shaking)
(Her rake gets caught on something.)
(Did Jung Ah finally find an alimango?)
(She grits her teeth.)
(However, she doesn't manage to get anything.)
(I'm sure there's one here.)
(Jung Ah tries digging one more time.)
(Hitting)
I hear something, Jung Ah.
What?
Did you find one?
(Did you really find one?)
I can see its legs!
Is it there?
(The pincers can be seen slightly.)
Crab!
(She rakes even faster after seeing its pincers.)
What?
- Did you get it? - Is this a crab?
(Jung Ah, please...)
(The alimango reveals itself from the mudflat.)
- Did you catch it? - Yes.
(The alimango finally gets caught by Jung Ah.)
(Amazed)
(- Did you catch it? - Yes.)
- Jung Ah caught one! - Yes!
It's so small.
(But it's so small.)
(It's small and precious.)
- She caught one! - I managed to catch one.
(It's a cute size that fits in one hand.)
It's too small.
Jin Young!
(She still wants to boast about her small but precious crab.)
- It's so small, isn't it? - It isn't that small.
(They reach their goal of four with Jung Ah's alimango.)
We can leave now since we have four.
- Hye Yoon! - Yes?
We have four.
Really?
Thank you.
(Choking up for no reason)
(They reach their goal of 4 in 2 hours and 30 minutes.)
I really want to catch two more.
We can get another coin if we catch two!
(Crab catcher Dex is still hungry.)
Can you give me the knife, please?
(Dex gets equipped with the knife.)
(This was filmed safely while being supervised by a local.)
(The crab hunter goes through the tropical rain forest...)
(while wielding his machete.)
(Let's hit another shell.)
Come out.
Look at Kim Dex continuing to search for more.
(I can't stand here watching.)
(The crazy siblings are back.)
At least one more.
(It's better to have more coins to change the itinerary!)
(He gives it his all to find another one.)
Where on earth is the crab hole?
Crab hole!
We've been around this area for too long.
- It's hard to know what's the hole. - Right.
- It's confusing with our footsteps. - Right.
(It's hard to distinguish the crab holes from the footsteps.)
I can't tell what the crab holes are.
Is this a crab hole?
Or is this a crab hole?
(Must we be satisfied with just one coin?)
Sometimes, the baby crabs live here.
- Sometimes. - Baby crabs? Sometimes?
Is that so?
(There are crabs between the branches as well?)
(He changes his plan right away.)
(Find the crab trees instead of the crab holes.)
(Looking carefully)
Gosh, he must've found another one.
What? What is this?
Is this not it?
(Little strokes fell great oaks?)
(He looks for the alimangos hiding between the trees.)
(Approaching carefully)
Okay!
Isn't this it?
- A baby crab? - Yes.
Baby.
Really? You got another one?
There's a crab hiding here.
(The crab appears.)
(Even a small crab must not be looked down on.)
Baby crab!
No! Baby crab!
(He misses the baby alimango.)
(Tearing apart)
Grab onto this! There you go.
(It grabs the rake!)
There you go.
(Did you really think I would grab onto it?)
(An unexpected battle is happening in the crevice of the tree.)
(Dex looks for the crab hiding with tenacity.)
I got it!
- Here. - Kim Dex is amazing.
(Another alimango is added.)
Okay.
- He never disappoints. - Right.
Very good.
He's amazing.
(They can have 2 coins if they catch 1 more crab.)
(Jun Myun and Hye Yoon try their best again.)
Is this not it?
I will go my own way.
We just need one more.
(They just need one more for an extra coin.)
(Stopping)
It's a crab!
Are you serious?
- Are you serious? - Right. It's a crab.
(The alimango between the tree gets spotted by Dex.)
It's a crab!
(I just need to catch this one!)
Gosh, our Jin Young is amazing.
Hey, come here.
Come here!
Hey! Come here!
(Tearing apart)
(The alimango is hiding in the crevice of the tree.)
I must get my hands on you.
It's a crab! I got another one!
- Really? You got another one? - I got another one.
I got another one.
(It grabs onto the rake with its pincer.)
- Awesome! - I got another one.
- He's amazing, isn't he? - He's not one of us.
- Yes. - Our Jin Young got another one!
- That's our Kim Dex! - I did it!
I managed to get another coin before the end.
You're amazing.
(Three hours have passed.)
(They managed to catch six alimangos.)
- Let's go! - Let's go!
- Okay! - We have a long way back.
(How do we get out of this place?)
(Her legs have almost given out.)
(Her limbs feel heavy.)
Okay. Let's go.
(The mudflat of the forest still slows them down.)
(Humming)
(Their hearts feel light as both hands are full.)
Isn't this a crab hole?
(He's still looking while leaving the area.)
Is he still looking for more?
(Looking around)
(He naturally pokes at a crab hole.)
Isn't this a crab hole?
(He starts poking out of habit.)
(He starts poking as if he's possessed by something.)
(He spills his bucket while falling down.)
No! The crabs are getting away!
(The alimangos get away.)
(He grabs one with his hand out of hurry.)
No!
(I can't let you go like this.)
(Groaning)
- Be careful. - It got away!
Look! It's huge! It's getting away!
- Over there! It went in! - Over there!
(I can't lose it like this.)
- Dex! - My crab!
It got away!
- It's here. - It was really big.
The crab got away.
(Struggling)
It's right here.
(The tyrant alimango won't stay still.)
- Gosh! - This one was mine.
We have to get out first.
Let's get out.
I think I see the way out!
I have survived!
Are you okay?
I should film a drama.
(Kim Hye Yoon's Cinema Special)
(Panting)
Did we make it out alive? Gosh!
We made it, Hye Yoon!
- Right. - We made it.
We're here!
- Help us! - We need help!
I see light!
(They're glad to see the streak of light.)
There's light.
There's light!
(They embrace the light with their whole bodies.)
Are we out? What year is it right now?
It's 2023.
How many years were you in there for?
What? We went back in time.
- What happened? - We went back in time?
Is that not it?
(Struggling)
(He kindly helps out his younger sister.)
Thank you, Dex.
- Move inside. - You're so reliable.
(They get on the boat with their exhausted bodies.)
(She takes off her gloves as she takes her seat.)
All of the mud got in between the nails.
Right.
It's a mess, Jung Ah. It's the same for the toenails.
(The traces of their hard work can be seen right away.)
- Look at her. - Let's see your face, Hye Yoon.
(Is Hye Yoon looking okay?)
Gosh, thank you.
(Affectionate hands of the eldest sister)
Gosh, that must feel itchy.
You get it now, don't you, Hye Yoon?
Looking pretty...
- won't last long. - She looks prettier like this.
- Right. - Did it last ten minutes?
Exactly.
She looks prettier like this, and it feels more natural.
- She's pretty. - Right.
- Go home! Please go home! - Please go!
(It's time to leave the mangrove forest.)
We still managed to get it done.
(They head back after completing their first work session in Bohol.)
- Go home! - Gosh, Jung Ah.
I can't believe we went to a place like that.
It was no joke.
(They felt the worth of labor done with their sweat once again.)
Gosh, it feels refreshing.
I love it!
(With the cool river breeze that is blowing,)
(they cool off their sweat.)
(They arrive at the dock.)
We made it back alive!
- I can't believe I'm back on land! - We made it back!
Go ahead.
(Eyes of resentment)
Was this the vacation you all were talking about?
Darn it!
How is this a vacation?
(It's true that they don't look like they're on vacation.)
Right.
You've all gone through a lot to catch the alimangos.
- Right. - How many of them did you catch?
We'll show you.
We need to count them first.
- Gosh. - Can we put them on the ground?
(They get taken out from the bucket to be counted.)
One, two, three, four, five, six.
- There are six of them. - Right.
(The small crabs have been released afterward.)
There are six of them.
(We did well, didn't we?)
It was really tough. It really was.
Then, in total,
- we will give you two coins. - Two coins?
Thank you.
- Thank you! - Thank you.
- Go and get them. - Right.
(The treasurer hurries over to get the coins.)
Thank you! This is our hard-earned money.
- Make a draw right away. - Right.
(They draw a vacation activity right away.)
Please!
(Which activity will the siblings draw?)
A five-star foot massage!
- Okay. - I want the full-body massage!
Please!
(Their vacation activity gets decided by one draw.)
There we go.
Let's get the full-body massage!
I will open it.
(Our exhausted bodies need a massage.)
(Will their wishes come true?)
(Please!)
Five-star foot massage!
- What? - Five-star foot massage!
(Screaming)
Are you serious?
Gosh!
(Greatly excited)
I'm getting a foot massage!
A five-star foot massage! Gosh!
(They got the activity they wanted.)
How did you manage to draw that?
Right. That was fascinating.
We have to get that next.
We should get a foot massage after enjoying a high-end meal.
- Give us the high-end meal coupon! - High-end meal coupon!
We want it!
(Will they get what they want again this time?)
(Let's enjoy a meal out.)
- Local health food? - Local health food?
That is good enough.
Local health food.
Isn't it a creepy dish?
I'm sure it's not, Jung Ah.
- It's health food. - Right.
- That sounds great. - We got these two.
Where should we place these two?
Do we get a foot massage right away today?
- Yes. Let's get it today. - Today?
- We have to wash up. - Wouldn't that be a waste?
- It would be a waste. - That's too much of a waste.
- We have to head home as well. - But...
- you use it or lose it. - Hold on!
Use it right away. You never know what will happen.
(Make it happen right away.)
- Why are you living like a mayfly? - Gosh.
- What's with you today? - No.
- I'm serious. - You're acting like a mayfly.
In my opinion, it should be used after Dive into the Jungle.
That's when the five-star foot massage should come.
- Right. - Let's use it toward the end.
- Okay, then. - Right.
When should we try the local health food? Tomorrow?
The second day.
- The second day sounds reasonable. - Right.
It will be eaten as a snack before we cook.
- Right. - We don't know what to expect.
- Right. Let's plan things out. - Right.
You can get changed first.
- Sounds good. - Okay.
You did well to draw them.
- You're the best. - You're the best.
- Right after we talked about it. - You're the best, Hye Yoon.
Let's see.
(Excited)
Cooling wipes.
- Would you like to wipe yourself? - I'll take one.
My neck is full of dirt.
- Me? - Me.
Would you like a cooling wipe, Jung Ah?
I'll wipe it for you. You won't be able to see it.
Come this way, Jung Ah.
- It's a cooling wipe. - Really? Thanks.
- It's great, Hye Yoon. - Really?
What's great?
- What's great? - It's great to have an underling.
(It's great to have an underling.)
(Annoyed)
Oh, my gosh. Why would you think I'm your underling?
You're younger than me. You're a year younger than me.
I eat...
almost three times more than you.
- When were you born? - I was born on June 9.
What about you?
- What about you? - You're really older than me.
- What about you? - I was born in November.
There's a big difference.
Of course. That's seven months.
Was I the first one to catch the crab?
Right.
I knew you caught one by the sound you made.
It was incredibly thrilling.
I thought you were getting eaten alive by it.
You were screaming so much.
I've always been a laggard.
What do you mean?
- I have always... - You're good at plenty of things.
You aren't saying more than that.
After a short break, I got...
- my appetite back. - Yes.
- I can eat now. - I'm hungry.
Actually, I'm hungry.
Let's get going.
Hello? Honey.
Jung Ah is so affectionate. "Honey."
Since 6am today, we had been...
catching crabs in a jungle.
We caught crabs that live in the mud.
It was very hard.
Now, we're going to get some local Filipino food...
with the money that we earned.
Sir, it's very hard.
Jin Young is telling you that he's having a hard time.
You must look so cool.
- No. - He's very cool.
- I'm sure he is. - No, I'm not. Thank you.
- Honey. - Stay strong.
Enjoy your meal.
- Gosh, that's so sweet. - I know.
I don't plan on contacting my husband for a week.
- Why? - Hand me his number.
I'll call him for you.
- I must tell him how you're doing. - Goodness.
He just needs to know that I'm alive.
Jun Myun, please contact your husband.
- Don't you agree? - Don't be like that.
- Once he knows that I'm alive... - He must be so curious.
Shall we play Hye Yoon's music?
- Oh, my. - Connect to Bluetooth.
I feel embarrassed.
- Come on. - My playlist...
Let's see what kind of music...
- you listen to. - Really?
- Connect. - The playlist is...
(Which song will Hye Yoon select first?)
("JUMP" by BLACKPINK)
(The latest popular dance song plays.)
(Dancing)
(Feeling embarrassed for no reason)
Is this the song you want to start with?
No, I just...
I played it to see your reaction.
"Endangered Love" by Lee Chan Hyuk.
- Okay. - Right away.
- I mean... - Okay.
(I will play it right away.)
("Endangered Love" by Lee Chan Hyuk)
This is your type of song.
- Isn't it nice? What do you think? - It's nice.
(Moving up and down)
(It's here)
(For real)
(The siblings are here in the Philippines.)
(The deep blue sky that's full of clouds)
It looks like storm clouds are gathering.
- You're right. It might rain. - The clouds are coming.
It's raining.
(In an instant, the rain starts pouring.)
Mark, does it rain all of a sudden like this?
- Suddenly raining... - Yes.
(She brings out advanced English to communicate.)
All of a sudden? I see.
It's raining quite a lot.
- It's better that it's raining. - Right.
Otherwise, it's very hot.
Jung Ah, we never made kimchi jjigae, did we?
We couldn't make kimchi jjigae...
because we could never find sour kimchi.
That's why. You're right.
We couldn't get kimchi easily.
- Dex. - Yes?
- Is kimchi very famous in Korea? - What?
Is kimchi famous in Korea?
- Yes, it's famous. - Very famous?
It's very famous in Korea.
Kimchi is delicious.
- Kimchi is delicious? - Yes.
(His mouth is watering.)
Mark says that he also likes kimchi.
- Really? - Yes, Mark likes kimchi.
It's Korean comfort food.
(I see.)
What's comfort food for Filipinos?
It's morning glory.
- Morning glory? I see. - Morning glory?
It's so delicious.
Shall we buy some morning glory and stir-fry it?
- That sounds good. - Yes.
- Do you mean water spinach? - We just need garlic.
Yes, it's water spinach. We just need garlic.
- We can add garlic... - Oyster sauce.
and oyster sauce.
I'm hungry.
Does talking about food make your stomach react?
(Talking about it makes her hungry.)
I'm very hungry.
I can't wait to find out local food...
in the Philippines.
(At what kind of place will the siblings have their first meal?)
Oh, is it a cow?
(Full of anticipation)
(The restaurant that the four siblings are visiting)
(Filled with authentic Filipino vibes)
(Packed with a variety of dishes you can only try in the Philippines)
(There's also alimango.)
(A local favorite loved by both locals and tourists)
There's also seafood.
- It looks like a tasty restaurant. - That sounds delicious.
(Welcome)
(The four siblings take a seat.)
Don't you think you'll pass out...
- right after eating? - Right.
I feel a bit drowsy.
- Right. - You know what I mean?
We chatted a lot on our way here,
but everyone feels...
- Right? - I feel slightly sleepy.
What's famous here?
We should try their signature dish.
Menu, please.
(Here is the menu.)
What's your signature dish?
This one. This is a soup.
Kare kare, sinigang with pork,
pork barbecue, and pork fried rice.
Inasal paa. This one.
- This one. And this too. - Okay.
(They're flustered by the pouring recommendations.)
I'll look up the name.
(Hye Yoon uses the chance to search the reviews.)
I don't know what "sisig" is.
Someone said that he'd come back to eat this again.
I saw it in the back.
I think it's this one.
- Isn't this it? - Gosh, it's so expensive.
We can use up to 2,000 pesos.
We should spend about 1,500 pesos here.
(How much...)
(is the food?)
(Recommended dish in the review, sisig)
(370 pesos, about 9 dollars)
All of these are expensive.
(On average, a dish costs 600 pesos.)
(An expensive dish costs over 1,000 pesos.)
Here's a mud crab.
(It's 390 pesos per 100g.)
(1 crab costs about 3,510 pesos.)
- It's too expensive. - What's that?
(The dishes are too expensive for them.)
What was the expensive dish?
(Gloomy)
Here's what I think.
We should eat this much.
We can order four garlic rice...
- Right. - and 4 that costs 75 pesos each.
We have to try the morning glory.
Yes, let's get some morning glory.
Jung Ah, let's order one morning glory.
Shall we order a few...
And 4 that costs 75 pesos each.
Really?
(Leader Yum who's been watching the younger siblings)
Let's eat first. We'll insist later and use the credit card.
- Should we just eat? - Yes.
Let's try all the recommended dishes.
Seriously?
(Staring)
Hye Yoon, you start.
The first page.
Kare kare and fried jokbal in the back.
- Fried jokbal, kare kare. - Morning glory,
- sisig, rings. - Yes.
- Crispy pata. - Crispy pata.
And pork barbecue.
Garlic rice.
And karak karak.
Kare karak?
Kare kare.
- Kare kare. - Kare kare?
- Kare kare. - She understood.
One kare kare.
- And morning glory. - Yes.
One. Okay, thank you.
Are we spending all the money that we got today?
Will it be okay, Jung Ah?
How many?
- The smell is making me famished. - Seriously.
Jin Young, can you take a photo of us?
Jun Myun, stop taking photos.
- Give it to me. - We should take a photo here.
It's also raining.
When will we ever come here again?
She's right. We should take a photo when it's raining.
One...
Show the rain in the background.
You have so many requirements.
Oh, come on.
(The Siblings Are Waiting For Food)
Jun Myun makes souvenirs for us.
Of course.
It looks great.
(Satisfied)
"Gosh, your shoes are very small."
- That's what they said. - This is sisig with egg.
(The first dish grabs their attention.)
(Savory pork topped with a simple, light egg)
- It looks very good. - It looks delicious.
(The first dish, sisig with egg)
- This is barbecue. - Okay.
(Food keeps being served.)
- Kare kare? - Is this kare kare?
Gosh, the smell.
It would taste good with fried rice.
(A peanut-based Filipino stew made with oxtail and vegetables)
(The second dish, kare kare)
Gosh, we ordered a lot.
Here you go.
Let's put this in the middle.
This is the main dish.
(The main dish, crispy pata)
(A signature Filipino party dish of crispy fried pork feet)
(Featuring sour onion sauce)
Here's your morning glory.
(They meet their favorite dish.)
Morning glory.
Is this what morning glory looks like?
(Filipinos' comfort food, stir-fried morning glory)
- Bon appetit. - Bon appetit.
What should I start with?
I'll start with this. I wanted to try it.
Go ahead and eat.
Help yourselves.
You told us to order a lot.
I did.
(How does it taste?)
(Humming)
Jin Young, do you want some kare kare?
Yes, just a little for tasting.
A little? Here you go.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Hye Yoon.
(One serving for Hye Yoon)
(A bite of kare kare)
(Hye Yoon also tries it.)
(She takes a spoon of rice immediately.)
(An explosion of savory taste)
- It's delicious. - Yes, it's good.
- It suits my taste. - Yes.
Me too.
Everything is slightly salty.
The chicken is really delicious.
I don't think it's chicken.
- It's not chicken? - Isn't it pork?
It's jokbal.
(Fried jokbal that's as crispy as chicken)
(Trying it with the sour onion sauce)
(Crunch)
- Did you eat this? - Yes.
Jung Ah.
- Is that good? - It's delicious.
Try the piece...
- with some skin. - Try this too.
(Fried jokbal that's perfect for the Korean palate)
Try this. It's very delicious.
It's crispy.
(Dex tries a bite on top of the garlic rice.)
(Jokbal tastes the best when you tear it with both hands.)
(Eating)
(Staring)
You seem to enjoy it.
It's tasty. It's seasoned perfectly for my taste.
Which dish do you like the best?
- This. - Is that good?
You like that? I like this one.
(Tearing and enjoying every bite)
The food is generally salty,
- so it increases my appetite. - Yes, it's delicious.
It's so big that it looks overwhelming.
(Hye Yoon tries sisig that was recommended in the reviews.)
(Will it be delicious like the review said?)
(Humming)
(Dex also takes a bite with rice.)
(Crunch)
Is there mayonnaise in it?
It's exotic,
yet it suits our taste perfectly.
- It's not completely foreign. - Right.
(A Filipino dish that goes well with rice)
It's delicious.
It'd be perfect with some kimchi.
- Yes. - Right.
I agree.
When you crave kimchi, have some morning glory.
(Roll it around on the spoon.)
(Taking a bite neatly)
(The second eldest takes a generous amount.)
(Taking a mouthful with indulgence)
(Like the older sisters, the youngest slurps morning glory.)
(Humming)
It's good.
It's very good.
(Slurping one more time)
(They were so caught up in eating.)
(The plates become empty before they know it.)
I should finish it. It's so tasty.
It's impossible to eat here...
- without morning glory. - Morning glory.
- Hye Yoon. - It's impossible to eat.
Let's buy a bundle of it and stir-fry it.
- I'd love that. - Every day...
- Jung Ah, let's buy some fruit. - Fructose.
We're in the Philippines, so let's get some fruit.
- That sounds great. - What's with the look?
- I want some fruit. - On my list,
there's no fruit.
- Fruit is a must on my list. - Oh, my gosh.
Jung Ah, we're in the Philippines.
- We should have some fruit. - Definitely.
Let's have some mangoes.
- I agree. - There are so many mangoes.
Why would you eat that? It's sweet.
It's refreshing, crunchy, and delicious.
- I'd love to devour it. - It'd be refreshing.
I was the first to catch a crab today.
- Okay. - Throughout all three seasons,
I pulled off something big.
But that's...
- You're right. - Be generous with me,
- Jung Ah. - Let's celebrate.
Now that we're almost done, I'm a little worried...
as the treasurer. I have to admit.
We can earn more money later.
We have to work.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
(The siblings go in somewhere after leaving the restaurant.)
(A small, local supermarket next to the restaurant)
(A paradise of diverse and fresh fruits)
(Clusters of bananas hanging)
(Heaps of yellow mangoes)
(A local market where you can buy fresh fruit at affordable prices)
(There are also fresh vegetables.)
- There are napa cabbages. - Shall we get one?
(The siblings plan to make kimchi.)
Mangoes are 150 pesos per kilogram.
If it's 150 pesos per kilogram,
- That's affordable. - it's not bad.
(Let's get some immediately.)
(Many mangoes)
- Nine hundred. - Nine hundred.
- Okay, good. - Good.
It's a good deal.
(As the treasurer, she settles the bill efficiently.)
Thank you.
- We bought as much as I wanted. - I agree.
- Three hundred. - Three hundred?
(Full flex again at the supermarket)
We spent everything except 300 pesos.
Thank you.
(Returning home after shopping casually)
(Looking around)
- We must be there soon. - We must be close to the house.
I recognize this place.
- Is this it? - What?
(Soon, the car enters the alley.)
(Glancing)
- All of a sudden... - Gosh.
Is our home farther away?
What?
(It's here?)
(Deserted)
- Wait a minute. - Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
There's no convenience store in front of the house?
- Why is there an excavator? - What?
- What? - How did they find this lodging?
(Worried)
- What? - What's going on?
(Smiling)
- This is... - It looks nice.
(As they turn the corner, it comes into view.)
- What? - There are two houses.
(Two houses?)
Are we supposed to manage two houses?
No way.
The houses look amazing.
(The 4 siblings enter the tidy yard of the 2 houses.)
"The siblings' house."
(She spots the nameplate.)
- Get out. - It looks pretty.
Unbelievable.
(They came to the right place, the siblings' house.)
(The impatient eldest sister is on the move first.)
(Quickly)
Is there such a house...
- Thank you. - in Bohol?
(Flinging open)
- Do we take off our shoes here? - Oh, my.
(Shouting)
(Spacious)
(Is this reality, or are we dreaming?)
(The siblings' house in Bohol)
(After a long tunnel of palm trees)
(At the end of a slightly suspicious alleyway)
(Our home is nestled in a lush green forest.)
(This place will be a resting haven for the four siblings.)
(A spacious living room that feels like a getaway)
(An open kitchen to be filled with the smell of cooking)
(The sea of Bohol in the blue wallpaper)
(The plants in the house hold the spirit of a mangrove forest.)
- The house is really beautiful. - It's very beautiful.
(You can enjoy the feeling of being on vacation.)
There's also a motorcycle.
That's for Jin Young.
- It must be. - Yes.
(You can go on drives with the scooter.)
(That's not all.)
(Grabbing her attention)
(Stuck)
What? Is it amazing?
There's a swimming pool. Go and take a look.
(Exclaiming)
Isn't it incredible?
(When you open the door to our amazing house)
(A swimming pool just for the siblings)
- It's the best. - I knew it.
(It looks like a whole beach had been brought here.)
(A small getaway just for the siblings)
Are they really giving us such a big reward?
This place is romantic.
We can cook here.
We can season it with chili powder here too.
- We can also cook outside. - Yes.
(An outdoor kitchen next to the swimming pool)
This place is equipped with everything.
(It has everything except what's missing.)
(Two cozy bedrooms)
It's really nice.
What?
(Then where is Dex's room?)
(Congratulations, Dex gets the annex.)
(Laughing)
It's really nice.
It's romantic. Bunk beds?
(Romantic Dex loves it.)
(Exclaiming)
It looks nice and comfortable.
I can't believe this.
(Impressed)
(He's moved by the private bathroom.)
What's this?
It feels like I got my own room, so it's fascinating.
Why are there beds...
for two people?
- Jung Ah. - Yes?
I'll get going.
- Drive safely. - Okay.
- I'll go and work out. - Have fun.
(He's about to head to the gym.)
(The scooter was in the rain.)
(He wipes off the rain carelessly like it's nothing.)
(After putting on a helmet instead of a raincoat,)
(he sets out.)
I'll get going.
It feels refreshing.
(Once you pass the alleyway in front of the house...)
(and run through the wide open road lined with palm trees)
(Swoosh)
Now it feels like I'm in the Philippines.
(Laughing)
It's refreshing.
This is great.
It feels different to be driving on a scooter.
(Roaming the streets of Bohol surrounded by locals)
Children are returning home from school.
Hello.
(Hello)
(In sync)
Their smiles are so innocent.
(Hey)
(He's very popular among the children.)
(Riding in the cool breeze and enjoying the drive)
(Exclaiming)
(A gym sign comes into view.)
So this is the place.
It looks nice. There's a place like this?
(10 minutes on a scooter from our house)
(In Bohol where heavyweights are)
(A place where the strong ones gather)
It has a nice facility.
Excuse me.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, nice to meet you. - Hello.
This part is for legs.
- Legs? - Yes.
The second floor is for the chest.
- The chest? - Yes.
The third floor is for the biceps, triceps...
- and the back. - Okay.
(A view of the outside)
Let's see.
There's a sandbag.
(He finds a sandbag.)
(Swoosh)
This is romantic.
(The romance lover is totally satisfied.)
Then today...
(Which part should I train first?)
I'll start with my least favorite, the lower body training.
I'm going to work out every day while I'm here.
So, for today, I'll do a lower-body workout.
I'll do my lower body and shoulders.
Tomorrow, I'll work out my chest and back.
I'll work out my lower body and back the day after that and so on.
(Dividing the workout into a 2-day routine)
Goodness.
(Dex finds a squat machine.)
(Grabbing)
Recently,
I'm into the old days, so I bought an MP3 player.
(Romantic Dex seeks sentimentality even when he works out.)
I paid and downloaded these songs.
They have the vibe from the Cyworld era.
(Dex's emotional playlist feat. Cyworld background music)
I paid to download these.
(Emphasizing that he downloaded them from an official site)
You know "This Song" by 2AM, right?
(Dex's sentimental playlist: "This Song" by 2AM)
"I Don't Care" is on it too.
I work out while listening to ballads.
MC Sniper. G-DRAGON and T.O.P.
("Don't Leave" and various genres)
(It is a workout playlist.)
The Cross.
The playlist includes about 19 songs.
It's almost an hour long.
When the playlist is over, my workout is done.
Okay.
(Now, he's about to work out.)
(Glancing)
(Surprised)
(Heavy)
(A leg-day brother on his right)
(Across the leg-day brother is...)
(Amazed)
There are many robust brothers.
(It's his leg and shoulder day too.)
Some jacked brothers.
(Good.)
(Timidly showing his respect)
(After checking the power level of the brothers on each side)
(His first weight training: Squats)
(Warming up lightly with 20kg)
(Getting into position)
(Going straight down)
(Effortless)
(Speeding up)
(The leg-day brother looks into him, realizing he's serious.)
(The warm-up squats are over in an instant.)
(Adding another 20kg without a break)
(Adding 20kg)
(Current weight: 60kg)
(He still seems relaxed without shaking.)
(The secret behind it is probably...)
("This Song" that's hitting him deep.)
(No one would have guessed the ballad he's listening to.)
(I listen to ballads when I work out.)
(He clears the 60kg set with ease.)
(Current weight: 100kg)
(Squating while holding his breath)
(Dex easily handles 100kg too.)
(After finishing the 1st set of 100kg...)
(Staring)
(Nodding)
How many kilograms is this?
It's 160kg plus...
(Upper side: 10 plates of 15kg, Lower side: 8 plates of 20kg)
It's 330kg.
(Plus the weight of the machine)
He's a monster.
(It's a compliment at a gym.)
(Glancing at the shoulder brother)
(There are too many tough people in this world.)
Are you a bodybuilder?
- No. - No? Really?
(Are you really not a bodybuilder?)
It's just a healthy lifestyle.
Lifestyle? Just a lifestyle.
How many years have you worked out?
- About 10 years. - About 10 years?
- Yes. - I see.
- How about you? - Do you live...
No, I...
It's the same as you, but...
we look very different.
I'm small, but you're big.
I think we look similar.
No. I have nothing here.
(The shoulder-day brother humbles Dex.)
- You're a big guy. - There's a stronger one over there.
I feel the same.
(Staring)
- You're a big guy. - There's a stronger one over there.
I feel the same.
(Staring)
(An apex predator at the gym)
- Can we work out together? - Yes.
And...
Will you teach me?
(Accepting to do it happily)
- I need to do three more sets. - Okay.
Yes. And I'll go to you.
Okay. Good.
I've found a teacher.
(Dex has obtained a personal trainer.)
This will increase the workout efficiency.
(While Dex is fired up to work out among the brothers,)
(the raindrops have faded away.)
(Now, the clear sky is here.)
Gosh.
I want to take a photo.
(And an unexpected guest has come to visit the sibilings.)
My goodness.
How does it look?
- Gosh. - Isn't it crazy?
It's a real rainbow.
- It's a matter of course. - Hye Yoon, it's a rainbow. Look.
(A real rainbow has appeared.)
- It's really pretty. - It's so pretty.
How can it be so vivid?
(A gift from the ever-changing weather)
Hey. Goodness.
(With Jun Myun's encouragement,)
Gosh. Right now,
you look so pretty.
(she's in an adorable Maltese mode.)
(The show's bright female lead)
It's been years since I saw a rainbow like that.
Seriously.
(We have to capture this moment.)
But the duck is staring at me.
It's overwhelming. What should I do with it?
(Peeking out)
Where's this rainbow?
- The rainbow is... - Jung Ah, you have to see it.
- Jung Ah, wear those shoes. - Come and see.
Come here.
You can't see a rainbow like this in Korea.
- Where is it? - Over there.
There. It's straight ahead of us.
Right. I see it.
- Jung Ah. - Yes.
You sound cynical. Stand over here.
- She's not interested. - Let me take a photo. Come on.
She's not interested at all.
I should take a photo of you in front of the rainbow.
I'm wearing a rainbow shirt.
- That's true. - Will you stand right there?
You look pretty. Okay.
I'm done.
Good job.
(Meanwhile, Dex with a new personal trainer)
Do you come here every day at 2pm?
(He made new friends.)
(Student 1: Senior disciple, Personal trainer)
I see. Okay.
(Student 2: Junior disciple)
- Okay, my friend. It's 68kg, right? - Come.
"Come?" Okay. Ten.
(All of a sudden,)
Okay.
(the back-muscle battle between the disciples is on.)
(Warning: He is super excited.)
Ten?
(His 10-year experience in working out is at stake.)
Okay.
(This match matters to Dex only.)
(The mission is 20 reps of 68kg lat pulldown.)
(The senior disciple calmly works on his reps.)
(Focused)
(While all you can hear is heavy panting,)
(the senior disciple gives up.)
(Look at him.)
Really?
(I still have a long way to go.)
(Dex wins.)
(The gym-goer in his 10th year regains his honor.)
(The personal trainer respects him too.)
He must be more muscular than me without the clothes.
No.
Maybe you and I look the same.
- No. - You have a good body.
He's a bigger size. You're a medium. I'm a small.
(While the guys are talking about muscles,)
An OG is here.
(an extra-large size is here.)
(The final boss starts with 100kg.)
Gosh. He's intimidating me.
(A lat pulldown with 100kg)
(A hush falls over the gym.)
It's quiet all of a sudden.
Isn't it hilarious that everyone went silent?
The real deal is here,
so everyone is humbled.
(The lesson of the day)
The world is big, and there are so many strong people.
So many people are stronger than me here at this gym only.
(He finishes his workout with a sad lesson.)
("We Were in Love" by LYn)
(The sisters are relaxing, listening to Jung Ah's playlist.)
(You said all you wanted was me)
(Glancing)
(Is she grooving all of a sudden?)
(Dancing)
(A dance performance is held in the room in front of hers.)
(A concernt in the room just for Jung Ah)
(Laughing)
(The much-anticipated highlight)
Does it sound okay?
(A perfect harmony)
(While the bandana sisters are busy performing a duet song...)
I'll do it.
(Driving)
(Dex arrives.)
- Delivery. - For goodness' sake.
- Did you work out a lot? - Yes.
- How was the facility? - What?
- How was the facility? - It was better than I expected.
It was beyond expectation.
I made some friends too.
I beat the Chinese buddy.
(Bragging about beating a friend)
- With... - With the number of kilograms.
- With weight? - With weight.
The fact that we stayed home like this.
And Jin Yong went to work out.
It does feel like a family, doesn't it?
- We did our own stuff. - He said, "I'll be back."
- We did what we needed to do. - Yes. We did our own stuff.
- I'll take a shower. - Okay.
(The whole family has gathered now.)
- I'm back. - He's back.
He's back. Dex is back.
- What have you been doing? - We've been waiting for you.
- We'll get ready and cook now. - Yes. We'll go outside.
Today, actually...
We want something spicy.
Jun Myun will cook spicy beef radish soup.
We'll make kimchi too.
- And steam the crabs. - They're good crabs.
We'll steam them lightly and cook crab fried rice.
Why don't you two make the crab fried rice?
We'll try. I think we can do it.
(Today's main ingredient)
(They caught them in the mangrove forest themselves.)
(The Philippines' premium ingredient, alimango)
I'll extract the crab meat and make crab fried rice.
(Today's main chef, Dex)
You're a chef-owner.
- This is a collaboration. - Right.
(Always on standby next to the main chef)
(Capable assistant, Hye Yoon)
Here we go, Hye Yoon.
(Will the two of them cook the alimango dish successfully?)
I'm hungry. I'm starving.
Let's hurry.
(The four siblings' first cooking in the Philippines starts now.)
Where is a steamer?
I haven't seen one.
We need to steam them, right?
Why don't I steam them first?
Are they dead?
They're still conscious.
- Have you steamed crabs before? - Yes.
I do make steamed dishes at home.
- I use a cypress steamer. - I see.
You're good.
I know how to clean the crabs too.
(Should I start...)
(cleaning the alimango?)
(The main chef gets ready to operate.)
Gosh. I have to kill the crabs.
(He obtained a tool.)
Gosh. They're big.
(Cracking)
(With a scary sound, he takes alimango out.)
(Trying to attack him)
Gosh. It hurts, my friend.
Be careful. It has sharp claws.
(Testosterone-fueled Dex cleans it without hesitation.)
(Beating it completely)
(He removes the impurities from the crab first.)
I'll get rid of the parts that will smell bad.
(Chef Dex's tip)
(Drain out the blood after removing the underside and mouth...)
(to reduce fishy and earthy smell.)
Because it was in the mud, we might get mud in our mouths.
Exactly.
I have to clean them thoroughly.
(Cleaning them thoroughly under running water...)
(without leaving any mud)
(He skillfully prepares the first alimango.)
(Assistant Hye Yoon comes to help the chef.)
Is it alive?
- It must be dead. - That one's dead.
These ones are alive.
Don't touch them. You might hurt your hands.
Watch your hands.
Okay.
(Testosterone-fueled Dex is so kind to the younger sister.)
(He takes out the next alimango.)
(Thrashing)
It's strong.
(For attempting to escape,)
(it's sent to a pot jail.)
He's pushing it down.
(A miserable end of the fugitive)
Gosh. Look how hard it grabs.
It might cut my finger off.
(It doesn't let go of the scissors.)
Will you pass me the knife?
Did it take your scissors?
Here's a small one.
- Do you need a big one? - No. A small one is fine.
(He has obtained another tool.)
(He barely knocks it off with 2 tools, a knife and scissors.)
(Scary)
(After cleaning the alimango enthusiastically...)
- Jin Young, let me wash my hands. - Okay.
Gosh. Is this all right?
It's not clogged, is it?
It got clogged right away.
What do we do?
The water goes down after a while.
- Should I unclog it? - What?
(Will it work?)
As for this one...
There must be something to lift it up.
(For some reason, she looks very professional.)
Right.
(The sink is unclogged with a few moves by her.)
Nice. You unclogged it.
Yes. I lived by myself before.
(The vibe from living alone)
- You're good. - Of course.
(She's on top of everything.)
When I hand it to you after killing it,
- Yes. - check for any mud in it.
Wash it with water.
(She helps him clean the crabs without a problem.)
You're doing great.
(Thanks to the skillful assistant Hye Yoon,)
Mission complete.
(the alimangos are cleaned and prepped.)
(What is the skillful assistant's next job?)
Sort them out, Hye Yoon.
- Okay. - Pick and throw them away.
- Pick out the bad cabbage. - Okay.
Take out the damaged leaves like this one.
- Damaged like this? - Yes.
(Checking if there are damaged leaves)
This one is a little...
(Totally focused as if she's looking into a microscope)
(After preparing the napa cabbage for a while...)
- There's a lot. - I know.
When I brine these,
- They'll shrink. - they'll shrink a lot.
We have to eat kimchi for days.
(It's the amount for the whole vacation.)
We need to wash the napa cabbage inside.
Is there a big strainer?
- I found this one. - That won't work. Is it in there?
Gosh. They look good.
(The assistant doesn't understand how generous Jung Ah is.)
What about this one, Jung Ah?
That looks good.
- Thank you. - No problem.
(After washing it under running water,)
We need to salt the napa cabbage.
(salt the napa cabbage with coarse salt until it wilts.)
(At one corner of the kitchen...)
(At one corner of the kitchen,)
(Jun Myun crouches to clean the radish.)
(She chops the radish into big chunks.)
Gosh.
(Tasting it like always)
Okay. Now, I put...
Jung Ah, do I marinate it with soup soy sauce?
- Yes, with soup soy sauce. - Soup soy sauce?
Yes.
(Is Jun Myun asking Jung Ah for the recipe?)
No. I'll teach you.
Chop the radish and marinate it in soup soy sauce for a while.
Drain the blood out of the beef.
- Add minced garlic. - Add a bit of minced garlic.
Instead of using oil, stir-fry the meat with cooking wine.
I see. You use cooking wine to stir-fry the beef.
- Don't put any oil in. - No oil.
- For spicy beef radish soup. - It'll taste cleaner.
Yes. It will taste very clean and light.
(She learned the recipe perfectly.)
(Now, it's time to cook.)
(Jung Ah's recipe for spicy beef radish soup)
(1. Marinating radish in soup soy sauce)
(Next, it's time to drain blood from the beef.)
I rubbed the blood off.
(2. Remove the blood from the beef completely.)
(Adding lots of minced garlic to remove foul odor)
(3. Add minced garlic to the beef.)
(4. Stir-fry the beef with cooking wine, not oil.)
Does the gas stove work now?
(It's time to stir-fry the beef with cooking wine now.)
(Is she turning on the gas for the pot of radish?)
(She stir-fries the radish confidently.)
I marinated it in soy sauce. Now...
You need to stir-fry the beef first.
You can just add the marinated radish later on.
- Is that so? - Yes.
What should I do with it?
Did you add just a little bit of the soy sauce?
- Yes. - You should've added much more.
Stir-fry the beef in another pot.
No, I'll redo it.
I think... Can I do what I think?
- Sure, do what you like. - I mean...
I think it'll work this way...
- or that way. - Okay.
Sure, do what you like.
(What will become of spicy beef radish soup?)
(Spicy beef radish soup...)
(I'll revive you, no matter what.)
(Lips tightened in resolution)
(She adds two spoonfuls of chili powder to make it spicy.)
(Beef enters.)
They say add cooking wine when stir-frying it...
for the clean taste.
I'll make it spicy and clean.
(The kick to having clean-tasting soup)
(Surprised)
I'll add water and boil it now.
It smells good.
- It smells delicious, right? - Yes.
- It'll be spicy. - Yes.
(The scent of Korea fills the air of Bohol.)
(When the beef is almost cooked, add some water.)
Let's make it pretty spicy.
And refreshing.
(Adding green onions to make it refreshing)
(Soup soy sauce, tuna sauce, seasoned salt, pepper)
(Season it using 4 types of seasonings.)
It needs to cook.
(Let it boil for a bit.)
- I'll do it my way. - Okay.
- I'll make it spicy. - Okay.
(Will she be able to satisfy Chef Yum?)
What should I do with this?
- Is it all salted? - It's done, right?
- Hye Yoon, can you check... - Yes.
- if the rice is ready? - Okay.
If it is, can you mix it with a rice scoop?
Okay, will do.
I need it to make kimchi.
Rice.
"Check if the rice is ready."
"If it is, can you mix it..."
"with a rice scoop?"
To check if the rice is ready,
I should taste a bit of it.
(How to check if the rice is ready? By tasting it.)
Is this how you eat it?
(Satisfied)
It's firm.
Mix it.
(The smart assistant executes the commands one by one.)
If we have this with soup or jjigae...
That'll be amazing.
(Just imagining it makes her happy.)
This should be enough, right?
Exactly. My goodness.
Is she narrating?
I mixed it so many times. This should be enough, right?
(She's talking to herself.)
I'll report to Jung Ah.
Jung Ah, I finished mixing it.
My goodness.
The rice is very firm.
- It's so delicious. - I purposely made it firm.
(We'll reveal Chef Yum's kimchi recipe.)
(Overseas version)
You're not making glutinous rice paste, right?
No. I'll just blend them with rice.
(I'll blend the ingredients with rice.)
(She replaces the missing ingredient with cooled rice.)
(One whole sweet onion)
(Adding apples to enhance the sweetness)
(Fermented shrimp)
(Plum extract)
(Put the cooled down rice straight into the blender.)
(Chef Yum's tip: You can replace glutinous rice paste with rice,)
(which both has the effect of the kimchi sauce...)
(being absorbed well by napa cabbage.)
(Put all the ingredients in and blend them finely.)
(Finely-ground kimchi sauce base)
(Adding a generous amount of Korean flavor)
(Minced garlic and chili powder)
(Add the refreshing taste with anchovy fish sauce.)
(Add tuna sauce for enhanced umami.)
(Mix them together.)
How is it?
(How does the sauce taste?)
It's spicy.
The chili powder is very coarse.
(The perfect spicy Korean flavor)
- It's done. - It's done?
(It's time to mix them nicely.)
Some spring onions.
(Add sharp spring onions.)
(She mixes it with her generous hand.)
Two bowls of rice.
You can have geotjeori with rice as you make it.
Would you like to try? Have you tried it?
- Let me put one in your mouth. - Please.
(How does kimchi made in the Philippines taste?)
(Expressing the taste with her whole body)
It tastes ripe, right?
- Yes. It's tasty. - The napa cabbage is...
(She moves the generous amount of kimchi into a kimchi container.)
(Not leaving out any sauce)
We'll rely on this for the next few days.
(It'll take care of the siblings' meals...)
(during the vacation.)
Hye Yoon, let us get started.
- The water is boiling. - Okay.
This is for the steam?
Add half a bottle of rice wine...
to sanitize it.
(Pouring rice wine into boiling water)
The rice wine smells nice.
(Add rice wine when steaming crabs to remove the fishy smell.)
(Cleanly-washed alimangos...)
(are placed in the steamer.)
(While alimangos are being steamed)
I'll cut the ingredients for fried rice.
Use this to make green onion oil for fried rice.
Just cut simply and put them in here so I can blend them.
(Blend them finely using a blender.)
(Lightly beat the eggs too.)
Fry the rice now.
(The ingredients for crab fried rice are ready too!)
Do you need anything else?
(Let me think.)
What about honey? Syrup?
Why'd you add syrup to fried rice?
I actually can't tell if this is honey...
or that cinnamon thing.
What about MSG?
(You're funny.)
I only make use of the natural taste.
- Okay. - I don't use condiments.
Okay.
Let's prepare some.
- MSG? - Yes.
- Place it close to me. - Okay.
- MSG. - But don't let others see it.
- Okay. - Cover it with something else.
I got you. Like this, so it doesn't show.
- That's it. - Okay.
The new part-timer must be pretty good.
Yes.
- She... - We hired a clever one.
She's competent.
She looks clever.
I hear she's academically bright too.
Are you the one who went to Seoul National University?
(She doesn't know what to do.)
- Respond to her. - The university's medical school.
I heard that you study medicine in Seoul National University.
Yes, I guess so.
- My gosh. - "I guess so."
Did I?
It...
- Did it turn red? - Yes, the inside turned red.
That's amazing.
They're being steamed.
- Jung Ah, I turned on the heat. - Thanks.
What are you going to make?
The sauce to go with crabs.
For the sauce, butter and garlic.
(She cuts the butter, which will add the savory flavor.)
(Let it melt in the frying pan.)
(When the butter is somewhat melted,)
(add some minced garlic.)
You need to use low heat to stir-fry garlic gently.
Salt and pepper.
(Sprinkle salt and pepper.)
You're making a golden sauce.
That's a nice color.
(Jung Ah's golden butter garlic sauce)
(How does the golden sauce taste?)
(Humming)
- Jung Ah. - It's seasoned well.
(I approve.)
(Hissing)
(Slurping)
(Blowing)
Are you having a meal?
(What are you doing?)
- No, I'm tasting it. - What are you eating?
- What are you eating? - Radish soup.
You keep blowing something.
- In a mug? - I thought you were having a meal.
Jun Myun.
That's practically one serving.
I asked you to taste it.
I mean, I need to check if it smells gamey...
- among many other things. - You're checking?
My goodness.
No wonder there's so much.
(Embarrassed)
I think it's a bit bland.
(Another spoonful)
- Does it taste okay? - It's okay,
but I think it's a tiny bit bland.
It's bland?
(When you're not sure,)
(take another mouthful.)
(She adds some soup soy sauce to finish it...)
(and then starts the 2nd round of her meal.)
- We're not yet... - I'm tasting it.
Haven't you been tasting all this while?
I added more soy sauce because it was a bit bland.
I see.
- You're tasting it again? - Yes.
(It's a must to taste it after you season it.)
I'll try it again.
She scooped up another ladleful.
- This is her second round. - I mean...
- Jun Myun. - This is good for me.
This should do.
Would you like to try again? I seasoned it one last time.
- It's impossible to resist. - Really?
(It's impossible to resist.)
I'll give you two pieces of radish.
- All right. - I'm being generous.
(She generously gives her 2 pieces of radish.)
The seasoning.
The radish is cooked well.
(Looking forward to her reaction)
(Both humming)
I'm not doing this just for fun.
- You keep getting drawn to it. - Right?
I'll add a bit more pepper one last time.
Pepper.
And you'll taste it again, right?
The final tasting.
The soup is ready.
(Spicy beef radish soup, the final seasoned version)
It should already be 6pm, right?
Now? Yes. It's 6:30pm, Jung Ah.
We should eat at 7pm.
(Current time: 6:30pm)
It needs to steam for 25 minutes.
There's still ten more minutes to go.
- Ten minutes? - Yes.
We need to be quick.
I'm starting to feel rushed.
I'll give it a go.
We can do well.
- You guys better hurry. I'm hungry. - Okay.
Depending on how fast we are...
- That'll decide our dinnertime. - That's right.
(10 minutes which felt like forever pass.)
The alarm rang.
Okay, let's go.
- Okay. - Shall we check it out?
(Pausing)
You open it.
Why? Why would you hand over such a tense moment to me?
(Feeling very pressured)
(Shimmering)
Look at the color. That's amazing.
- The color is really... - It's pretty.
The color is amazing.
It's scarlet, not red.
I've never seen this color on crabs before.
(They're a lot more scarlet than Korean blue crabs.)
- You're going to remove the meat? - Yes.
- Yes. - This is the crucial part.
Be fast.
- Hye Yoon. - Yes, boss.
- Bring over the plate. - Okay.
Hurry up.
My goodness.
(Speed is of utmost importance now.)
- It's hot, right? - It's fine.
- The color... - It's so red, right?
(Even when looking at it again, it's such a bright color.)
Let's set the prettiest three aside.
Sure.
- What do you think? - That's nice.
This is done.
- Here. - Put them here.
Now.
Do we do one by one?
No. That's right, good job removing it.
It'll be better to squeeze it out using our hands.
Isn't it hot?
- It must be very hot. - Exactly.
(Squeezing out the meat that's filling up the shell)
This...
(Gasping)
- It popped out. - That's how it is.
Collect the meat here.
(Ecstatic)
- Taste it. - It's okay.
I held myself back.
I should hold myself back for this.
(Suppressing the urge to eat it, they pile up the meat.)
(And the highlight of alimango)
You're good.
Like this.
(And the highlight of alimango)
- My gosh. - The claw sure is...
- It's full of meat. - The claw sure is...
the real deal.
It looks so delicious.
It smells so good.
(You can only taste it in the Philippines,)
(which makes you become even more curious about the taste.)
Are you almost done?
- Yes. - Yes.
I'm so hungry I could die.
Please work a bit faster.
I got it.
(Jun Myun's hunger has reached its limits.)
I'm starting to feel rushed.
You need to stir-fry the rice too.
You're right.
(Rushing)
That's it. Done, right?
That's all.
(Eating)
Is it good?
(Dex tries it too.)
It's very sweet.
(Eating hurriedly before they get caught)
- It's very creamy. - Yes.
Right?
It's tasty.
- Hye Yoon, clean up. - Yes, sir.
Sir, take this.
(After the perfect crime, they pretend to rush.)
I'll get started now.
Okay.
Nice. I'll start, Hye Yoon.
(Apply a generous amount of oil onto the wok.)
I'll make green onion oil first.
(Making green onion oil, the foundation of fried rice)
What will you season it with?
I'll use dark soy sauce...
- to season it. - Pass him dark soy sauce.
Okay.
Salt too.
Salt is here.
(Once enough green onion oil is released...)
Just a bit of carrots.
(A tiny bit)
- You should add more. - I don't really like carrots.
It's the owner's preference.
(Childish Dex's taste in food is ever so consistent.)
Eggs.
(Add the eggs that were beaten beforehand.)
(Pouring in firm rice cooked by Jung Ah)
Thank you.
(Coat it with savory golden color.)
You're such a great cook.
(Feeling shy)
I'm serious.
(To Hye Yoon, who can't cook, he's on a deity level.)
(When the rice is stir-fried nice and fluffy...)
(He pours soy sauce in the corner?)
They say soy sauce tastes better when it's slightly burned.
I heard it from somewhere.
(Stir-fry soy sauce as if burning it to add the smoky flavor.)
(You've improved a lot, Jin Young.)
(He pours stir-fried soy sauce onto the rice.)
(Stir-fry it once more so the smoky flavor can permeate.)
Prepare sesame oil.
Sprinkle one round of pepper.
- Me? - Yes.
Sesame... Pepper?
- Take it slow. - You want me to do it?
Yes, sprinkle the pepper.
That's right.
- Is this enough? - One more round.
(Adding a bold amount of pepper)
Is that enough?
Get sesame oil ready.
Here it is.
- Pour the oil. - Okay.
One big, bold round.
Like this.
That's it.
(Mission accomplished)
Get the crab meat ready.
- Crab meat? - Yes.
Crab meat. Didn't you add it in?
Crab meat?
(When did I add crab meat?)
Crab meat...
I didn't add it.
(Guess what's here.)
- Hye Yoon, what happened? - False...
Spreading false information.
I thought you already added it in.
- Here it is. - Pour it in.
(The assistant is all over the place.)
(The protagonist enters.)
I'll make it look as plentiful as possible.
(The harmony of savory fried rice and sweet alimango)
Bring a spoon.
Okay.
- It's for tasting, right? - Yes, and you'll be tasting it.
- Me? - Yes.
(The assistant's new mission: Tasting)
(How does alimango fried rice taste?)
(Blowing)
(Taking a bite carefully)
Let me know if it's bland.
It can't be too salty because we have the side dishes.
- Is that so? - Yes.
But...
(Chef Yum tries a bite too.)
- It's bland... It is, right? - It's bland.
It's definitely bland.
(Definitely bland)
It can't be too bland.
(She couldn't bring herself to say the truth.)
(He immediately adds extra salt.)
- Here. - Again?
Yes. Taste it.
(Tasting it the 2nd time)
(What about this time?)
Actually, I can't tell if it's seasoned enough or not.
I think it's just nice.
It's so bland.
(Hye Yoon should just stay as an assistant.)
It's bland.
(He adds more salt and stir-fries it one more time.)
(Tasting it the 3rd time)
(Nodding)
(Hye Yoon, who's lost her taste, tries again.)
I think it's fine.
- I think it's good. - Yes, it's good.
This alone tastes good.
It's done.
(After ups and downs, alimango fried rice is done!)
Done.
(The golden fried rice...)
(goes onto a wooden plate, which looks very local.)
Put it down if it's heavy.
Okay.
There's quite a lot of rice.
(A generous amount fills up the plate.)
- Guys. - Yes?
- Yes? - How does it look?
- Doesn't it look delicious? - It looks so delicious.
(The second oldest prepared a dessert.)
Since we're in the Philippines, we should have some mangoes.
(The Philippines' representative fruit, mango,)
(which is very sweet and sour)
I can't wait to find out how it tastes.
Me too.
(Add Chef Yum's butter garlic sauce on top of it.)
I'll put the butter sauce on it.
It looks good.
(Soft, savory, and flavorful steamed butter garlic alimango)
- You went all out. - It's so good.
(Full of alimango's sweet taste, alimango fried rice)
And suddenly, we're in Korea.
It smells incredible.
(Refreshing and spicy beef radish soup)
- You can eat just with this. - That's right.
(And kimchi, which is a must for a Korean meal)
It looks legit.
(The siblings' fusion meal...)
(of Korean cuisine and the Filipino cuisine)
- Thank you for the meal. - Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meal.
(Glancing)
Would you like some fried rice?
(Hye Yoon distributes alimango fried rice.)
(She serves Jung Ah first, the oldest.)
(She distributes the fried rice strictly following the age order.)
Thank you.
I'd like 2 servings that look like 1.
- Two servings that look like one? - Is it the other way round?
If I press it like this...
(I scooped 2 servings and pressed it to make it look like 1.)
- How is it? - Hye Yoon, take yours.
I can scoop for myself.
No, I'm the youngest.
- Thank you. - It's Confucianism.
(Heartwarming)
(Scooping a lot for Dex since he worked hard making it)
Thank you.
(Lastly, Hye Yoon scoops the rice for herself.)
(They start their dinner in earnest.)
(How does Dex's alimango fried rice taste?)
(Glancing)
It tastes a bit bland, but...
- No, it's nice. - It's not bland.
- Really? - It's just nice.
It tastes like what they sell in restaurants.
- Go ahead. - Yes.
- If we had more crab meat... - Exactly.
It tastes like what they sell. You did a great job.
It's so good.
He's good.
This is so good.
- It's well-cooked. - It's so good.
(At their compliments, Dex starts eating in relief.)
(Dex successfully debuts as an alimango chef.)
(Hye Yoon, who assisted him well, takes a bite too.)
It's seasoned just right.
(The Generous Chef says the alimango fried rice is seasoned perfectly.)
- You don't need more or less. - Really?
- It's really good. - It's seasoned just right.
Gosh, I love geotjeori.
(Freshly made kimchi is Dex's favorite.)
The geotjeori's good, right?
I'm tasting fermented seafood. What is it?
Fermented seafood.
- It's fermented shrimp. - It's fermented shrimp.
There's fermented shrimp...
- And anchovy fish sauce. - and anchovy fish sauce in it.
(No wonder it's good.)
The kimchi is so good.
- Is it? - It has a clean taste.
When it ferments a little...
(The kimchi master is proud.)
(The beef radish soup that Jun Myun made following Jung Ah's recipe)
It's spicy and delicious.
(She takes a bite of the alimango fried rice...)
(and a spoonful of spicy beef radish soup.)
(Hye Yoon can't stop eating.)
I didn't think we'd get to eat Korean food here.
All of a sudden, it's like we're in Korea.
(Their first dinner in the Philippines...)
(doesn't feel unfamiliar at all.)
These precious crabs. They were so hard to catch.
I want to taste how good they are.
Let me do it.
(Dex prepares the claw so it's easier to eat.)
Be careful, you'll hurt your hands.
(Crack)
I do this and...
And then you use the scissors?
Yes. When I split this, we'll see the gem.
(When he removes the shell with scissors,)
(the juicy flesh is revealed.)
Here, Jung Ah. Have this.
- It's clean, right? - Since you're giving it to me,
I should eat it.
(The first claw goes to the eldest sister.)
(The second claw...)
- Here, Jun Myun. - Thank you.
(How does the alimango taste?)
(Yum)
(The sweet flavor of the alimango spreads in her mouth.)
(Jun Myun loves it.)
(Hye Yoon, the youngest sister, goes for the crab's top shell.)
(Scraping it clean)
(It's good.)
You...
You put this sauce on the flesh.
Spread it all over like this.
(Crunch)
Isn't this crab creamier?
Yes, it is.
It has a richer flavor too.
- The flavor, right? - Yes.
(It's creamier and has a richer flavor than the Korean blue crab.)
And it's sweet. It's very sweet.
The flavor feels a bit aloof.
What do you mean?
The crab is aloof?
(He's never heard the flavor of a crab be described as aloof.)
The Korean blue crab has a more umami flavor,
while this tastes sweet at first and clean at the end.
So the flavor is aloof.
(Aloof: When a food has a clean after taste)
(Jun Myun ate a lot of food in an aloof manner.)
(That's cute.)
(Just then, as the four siblings were lost in the alimango feast...)
I'm scared.
(Squeak)
(The strange sound won't stop.)
What is that?
(Even the production crew is starting to murmur at the sound.)
(Squeak)
(They look up at where the sound is coming from,)
(but there's nothing there.)
(So creepy)
What's that sound?
This is my first time hearing it, but that's the sound a lizard makes.
- That's a lizard? - Yes.
- Where is it? - You're lying.
(Squeak)
- It's true. - You're lying.
I'm serious.
Seriously?
Are you pranking me?
Gosh.
I asked because I heard it earlier.
(Squeaking)
(It is indeed the sound a lizard makes.)
(This is a male lizard's mating call.)
Really?
That's great.
It's as if the lizard is wearing a mic.
- It's pretty. With floral prints. - That's a bit scary-looking.
(I failed to find a mate yet again!)
We'll have to sleep with the windows closed.
Have some mangoes.
Cutting them wasn't easy.
Since we're in the Philippines.
Since we're in the Philippines, we should have mangoes.
I love mangoes.
(Taking a bite)
(Yum)
(Dex, the siblings' picky eater)
(And the youngest, Hye Yoon...)
It's so good.
It's really good.
(They all take bites of the mangoes while holding them like harmonicas.)
I love mangoes.
(As for Jun Myun, who prepared the mangoes herself)
(Her 1st mango slice)
(Her 2nd mango slice)
(Her 3rd mango slice)
(She had three mango slices in a row.)
(Amazed)
I had three slices by myself. I'll stop now.
Have some more.
No, I had enough.
I thought you were going to stop eating.
No, I lied.
(Her lie was exposed just 15 seconds later.)
I lied.
- She lied. - I had to lie.
(Mango Park, the liar, is eating her 4th slice.)
You really love mangoes.
Mango isn't the only thing she loves.
Jung Ah! How could you?
We're in the Philippines.
We should be getting along, if anything.
(Absolutely hilarious)
Mangoes are ridiculously cheap here.
They were the cheapest, right?
They were 150 pesos per kilo.
How much is that?
I think 100 pesos are equivalent to 2.5 dollars.
- Gosh. - Then that's...
- That's 2.5 dollars for 6 mangoes. - That's so...
- That's so cheap. - That's very cheap.
(These local mangoes taste great for how cheap they are.)
- In Korea, mangoes are... - They're very expensive.
They're expensive in Korea.
- I especially love apple mangoes. - Apple mangoes are really good.
It costs 25 dollars to buy 1 apple mango.
To buy one?
- For one apple mango? - Yes, so it's my dream to become...
someone who doesn't suck on the pit of an apple mango.
(A truly ambitious dream)
(Laughing)
What are we going to do with those?
- The pits? I'll suck on them. - The pits.
I'm not that person yet.
(Of course Mango Park has a plan.)
You'll have to find a blind spot with no cameras.
Or take them into the bathroom.
I feel pathetic for not even eating the pit.
Sucking on the pit is the best part.
You know how to enjoy your food.
(Mango Park will continue to shine.)
How are we going to make up for all the money we spent today?
We have to cover all the money, but how?
(They're starting to worry about tomorrow's groceries.)
Even if you don't have money,
if you earn coins,
you can use them to get our "local market pass."
It comes with an unlimited budget.
The coins are all you need.
You get food too.
(They can earn coins to get items...)
(from the drawing machine, which they can add to their itinerary.)
(They can even eat out without any money!)
(The siblings are on a vacation with the all-purpose coins!)
How are we supposed to earn the coins?
How were the games you played at the pre-production meeting?
- They were fun. - They were refreshing.
It was like "Family Entertainment Show" was brought back to life.
(It was like "Family Entertainment Show" was brought back to life.)
Like a family game show.
You can play a game...
- to win coins. - Let's do it.
What is the game?
(Will the siblings be able to earn as many coins as they want?)
All right. Day One is over as of now.
We finished cooking too.
(Day 1 of their vacation abroad is over.)
I think there are new items here.
"Drinking Mohitos in Bohol." This is the first time I'm seeing that one.
"At-Home Cafe Unlocked?"
An at-home cafe?
- Those are new. - They've been added, right?
Things like "Korean Delivery Pass."
These are actually...
- We can order delivery. - That's awesome.
- These are great. - They're awesome.
- We don't have to cook. - We can pass on cooking dinner.
I think they keep adding new ones to replace the ones we use.
I think so too.
So the more coins you earn through these games,
the more lavish your vacation would be.
- I see. - Got it.
Let's get going. What game are we playing?
(There's a crazed look in Jung Ah's eyes.)
The game you'll be playing today...
- is a revenge match. - Okay.
- A revenge? - Yes.
To be honest, we were weak-hearted,
- so we let you win. - Right.
- Sauce Park? - Yes.
(Wearing a blindfold,)
(taste the sauce...)
(and guess all the ingredients used to make that sauce.)
(Jun Myun took on the challenge for her honor as Sauce Park.)
(Soy sauce?)
(Is soy sauce spicy to you?)
(Her identity was exposed as fake.)
That was so disappointing. She had a reputation to live up to.
- I turned out to be taste-blind. - Right. She used to be Sauce Park.
We'll give you another chance.
Thank you.
But since this is an important game...
- with coins at stake, - You won't go easy on us?
you get to discuss and decide who will be taking on the challenge.
(They must find the next ultimate taste expert.)
- Not Jun Myun? - No.
Jun Myun can play again, of course.
No, I'm okay.
I've already been exposed as being taste-blind.
- Then who... - Who's the best taster?
Who's the best taster?
Can you tell apart flavors?
(Hye Yoon can't cook, so she's an exception.)
What about you, Dex?
- I'm not that confident. - That leaves you, Jung Ah.
- Jung Ah has a sensitive taste bud. - Me?
What do you say?
(Thinking)
You got this.
- I think you'll do great. - Of course.
Sure. I'll take on the challenge.
The lady of the house should do it.
- We have faith in you. - Yes.
I just brushed my teeth, so I'm all set.
Won't that get in the way of tasting?
No, everything's set.
- Really? - Yes.
Bring them out.
- Bring them out. - Start the game, please.
- Put on the blindfold first. - Right, the blindfold.
Here goes the blindfold.
Our queen.
Jung Ah.
- I have faith in you. I actually... - Yes?
was embarrassed last time, after the game.
(The result of the game was very shocking for Taste-Blind Park.)
I have faith in you.
- I'll give it a try. - Okay.
What is it?
(Today's sauce is here.)
Okay.
The sauce has three ingredients,
which you have to guess correctly.
- I have to get all three right? - Yes.
(Jung Ah succeeds only if she guesses all 3 correctly.)
(Dex starts off by sniffing at the sauce.)
(Gosh)
It's made of three ingredients.
(What on earth is in it?)
We'll tell the rest of you what the answer is in advance.
Okay.
(Answer: Prepared mustard, soy sauce, vinegar)
This isn't going to be easy.
Here, Jun Myun.
Feed it to her like a court lady.
- Your Majesty. - Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, please taste this.
(Park Jun Myun: An actor known for court lady roles)
You're good at this.
Jung Ah, smell it first.
(Answer: Prepared mustard, soy sauce, vinegar)
(What?)
- It smells good, right? - Yes.
(Did Jung Ah notice an ingredient already?)
What were you able to guess by smelling it?
Prepared mustard.
(She got one, using her sense of smell only.)
I'll put it in your mouth now.
- Is that okay? - Yes.
(Savoring mindfully)
Go with your instinct.
Would you like to guess?
- No. - Gosh.
(Jung Ah has no clue about the other 2 ingredients.)
- Here. - This isn't an easy one.
(Jung Ah returns to smelling the sauce.)
Should I put it in your mouth?
- No, give me a second. - Not yet?
I feel like there's soy sauce in it.
- What? - Soy sauce.
(Jung Ah has a dog-like sense of smell.)
Follow your gut.
(There's hope.)
Soy sauce, prepared mustard.
Can I have a taste?
- You want a taste? - Yes.
Here.
(Her 2nd time tasting the sauce)
This isn't an easy one.
- Right? - Right.
Prepared mustard, soy sauce.
(All she has to guess is vinegar!)
Can I sit here and think about it until tomorrow?
(Jung Ah's competitiveness is coming through.)
(She'll stay up all night if she can.)
Do you have an idea as to what the three are?
- No, I don't know the last one. - The last one.
I got prepared mustard and soy sauce.
I feel like I can taste a bit of vinegar.
(She finally mentioned vinegar!)
Prepared mustard, soy sauce, vinegar.
Can you shout out "Answer" and repeat that?
Answer! Prepared mustard, soy sauce, vinegar.
Correct.
- The ultimate taste expert! - Amazing!
Jung Ah is truly the ultimate taste expert.
- The soy sauce was tough for me. - We earned a coin.
And the prepared mustard overpowered the vinegar.
The vinegar was hard to guess.
The prepared mustard overpowered the other two.
I could tell by smelling it.
When she guessed the prepared mustard and soy sauce... Gosh.
We're off to a great start.
We are. I told you we could do it.
This is great.
- Bring on the next game, please. - Right.
The next game we've prepared is...
an upgraded version of the ultimate taste expert test.
It's called "Taste Talks."
- Okay. - Taste talks?
One person will taste the food...
and express what it tastes like to the remaining three.
Then the three will guess what the food is.
(If the others guess using the taste descriptions only, they succeed.)
(The person gets 3 chances to express the taste of the food.)
- You can't mention... - Exactly what seasoning was used.
the exact ingredients that were used.
For example, let's say I ate tteokbokki.
I would say that it's chewy and spicy.
- Is that how this would go? - That's right.
- Got it. - Okay.
Go ahead and discuss...
who will take on the challenge.
(Who will take on the challenge of Taste Talks?)
- Dex, you go. - No, I think...
Hye Yoon will be able to describe the tastes will.
But you were the chef today. You made the fried rice.
- Then... - What should we do?
Hye Yoon should express the taste and Dex should choose.
What do you think?
- What do you mean? - That doesn't...
- What is that? - mean anything.
- Are you tired? - Yes.
- Jun Myun. - I could use some iced Americano.
Hye Yoon, do you think you can express the taste well?
(She's clearly not confident about this.)
Go. We got this.
- Let's do this. - Let's do it!
Let's do it!
- I'm taking on the challenge. - You got this.
I got this.
The guessing part is actually kind of fun.
Yes.
(Here comes the food.)
(The food is revealed.)
(Laughing)
- Let us know when you eat it. - Okay.
Okay!
You got this!
I'll begin.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Slurping)
(I'm sucking on it...)
(like this.)
(Jun Myun is practically asleep while listening to Hye Yoon's ASMR.)
(Spitting out)
Are you eating?
- Let us hear you eat. - Are you eating or spitting?
Hye Yoon, we can hear you spit something out.
I don't know what it is, but let us hear you chew on it.
- Why are you spitting it out? - I can't figure it out.
(Braised chicken feet)
(She sucks on it...)
(and spits out the bone.)
(I expressed it perfectly!)
- Gosh. - This is so hard.
- She spat it out. - Is it dirty?
She sucked on something and spit it out.
(That's right!)
(Did Jung Ah figure out the answer?)
I think it could be crabs, watermelon, or grapes.
But if it were crabs, we would have heard a crunchy sound.
So I don't think that's it.
But I think you're right. It could be some kind of fruit.
The answer is grapes. Look.
(Slurping)
You're right. I think it's a fruit.
(Spitting)
- The answer is grapes. - Yes.
Grapes. Or it could be watermelon.
(Actually...)
She can describe the taste to us.
Shouldn't she describe the taste to us?
- She can do it now. - Yes.
Can you describe the texture to us?
- The texture. - Yes.
(Let's see.)
It's soft and chewy.
(Soft and chewy?)
Maybe it's mangoes.
- No, she wouldn't spit out seeds. - There's nothing to spit out.
I really can't figure this out.
What is this? It's becoming more and more of a mystery.
I'll describe the flavor then.
Okay.
- It's spicy. - All right.
It's spicy?
Soft and chewy?
(Hye Yoon had to spit something out.)
(The texture is soft and chewy.)
(It has a spicy flavor.)
- Braised chicken feet? - Something spicy she spit out?
Braised chicken feet?
- It's soft and chewy. - You have to spit out the bones.
- Something spicy she spit out. - Soft, spicy, having to spit out.
I think you're right.
- It must be braised chicken feet. - What else is there?
- I can't think of anything. - It's chewy.
It's spicy.
- Let's do braised chicken feet. - Should we?
- All right. It's all or nothing. - Spicy braised chicken feet?
- Braised chicken feet? Okay. - Yes.
One, two, three.
- Braised chicken feet. - Braised chicken feet.
Correct!
(Braised chicken feet!)
- Gosh, I can't believe this. - Goodness.
What I ate was braised chicken feet.
Gosh, I didn't see this coming.
I was like, "Why is she spitting it out?"
- Jun Myun carried this one. - You did great.
- You did. - I give you credit.
- You pulled it off. - I pulled it off.
You did it.
- I did it. - Yes.
I may not be the ultimate taste expert, but...
- We're bringing in the coins today. - We're doing good today.
- We haven't failed once. - Thank you.
Amazing.
- I think you underestimated us. - There's nothing we're bad at.
(The two sisters' game-playing skills were underestimated.)
- Treasurer Kim. - Treasurer Kim.
Yes.
- Put in the coin. - Okay.
- Should I go ahead? - Yes.
Hye Yoon's good at this.
Really? I don't do much.
Please.
Let's go.
- I have a good feeling. - Hye Yoon's good at this.
Just don't draw "No prize."
Okay.
(She drew their first capsule.)
There's actually something I'm hoping for.
What is it?
- The high-end meal coupon. - The high-end meal coupon.
I want the full-body massage coupon.
The high-end meal coupon and...
- the full-body massage coupon? - I want the company card perk.
I actually want the company card perk.
The company card perk can actually cover everything,
including high-end meals. We can do all these things.
I think what I drew isn't bad.
I caught a glimpse of what it is.
What is it?
- "At-home cafe unlocked." - At-home cafe.
In the morning, we...
Are we going somewhere to get brunch?
We're providing you with a coffee machine like you wanted.
(They'll be provided with a coffee machine.)
You're setting up a coffee machine here?
Hye Yoon and I are the only ones who drink coffee.
I don't drink coffee anymore.
I only had one earlier to wake myself up.
Jun Myun, your eyes are about to bulge out.
- Should I take them if they fall? - Yes, take them.
- They were about to fall right out. - Got it.
- All right, we'll drink coffee. - Good.
- Let's see the next one. - Okay.
- I'll turn the lever. - Okay.
Turn it!
(She drew their second capsule.)
Please.
(The second item to be added on their schedule is...)
- Nice. - The local market pass.
- The local market. - We can get anything there, right?
Yes, when you buy groceries there.
- That's good. - This is a big one.
(They can buy an unlimited amount of fresh local ingredients.)
When should we go to the local market?
The market...
Should we go after work?
We'll work, get groceries, come home and cook.
(Day 3, when they have nothing besides work on their schedule?)
We'll work and...
(They decide to go to the local market on Day 3.)
- You're fine with this, right? - Yes, that's fine.
It's decided then. We did good today.
We'll be back next time.
She said, "I'll be back."
(The Fresh Off the Sea Vacation Schedule Games will continue.)
I wonder why we're so good at playing games.
We have zero intention of losing a game.
- Are you going to drink? - Yes.
- Can you bring him a glass? - Okay.
We've already been drinking.
Dex, you should come here.
I can't reach the glass.
Gosh, that's sad.
- I couldn't see the glasses. - How cute.
I didn't want to make a mistake.
We'll just wake up in the morning and dance with the turtles.
What?
We'll wake up in the morning and dance?
(It's frustrating to think about dancing with turtles.)
Just think of it as an aerobic workout in the morning.
I think it's hopping.
I'm starting to get worried.
(During dinner a while ago)
What could it be?
(Curious)
We might find out if we look it up.
Ask your friend.
Was it Gemini?
(Rummaging)
(Will Gemini know the answer?)
(Typing)
(The hopping tour is a way to dance with the turtles.)
(Hopping tour)
"Hopping tour?"
This is what a hopping tour is like.
What's a hopping tour?
A bunch of people get on the same boat.
The boat reaches a certain spot,
and the people can enjoy the area while being underwater.
But people dance on the boat.
- Club music is played.
- Really?
What do we do?
(Chuckling)
The one that I saw was like that.
What did you just read? Tell us.
- It's similar to what she said. - Oh, my gosh.
It's a tour to see turtles and dolphins.
(Gemini's description is just like what Hye Yoon said.)
- People dance on the boat. - They dance?
- They dance? - People dance on the boat.
(They dance on the boat?)
With their rash guards on?
How are we supposed to dance with the turtles?
My gosh.
Like this with a dress on.
What's with those moves?
- Just like this. - What's with him?
He's practicing to dance with the turtles tomorrow.
I danced during my fanmeet event.
- What's with the way she talks? - And...
- That's the official way she talks. - It's so annoying.
Do you have a problem with that?
Right!
- So... - What did you dance to?
It was "NOT CUTE ANYMORE."
A song by ILLIT.
(Hye Yoon is working on ILLIT's song.)
It's that one.
I was watching my video,
and I wondered if I had some talent in dancing.
She's a great dancer.
- Really? - She has amazing moves.
She didn't look funny.
You speak like that,
- and you dance well as well? - Show us the video.
- Show us. - I know that song.
It's hard to believe.
You might not be able to find me because I'm too good.
- Was this released? - It wasn't released yet.
- Is she the one in the middle? - Look for me. Right.
- This one in white? - Right.
(Hye Yoon)
(Focused)
Gosh, look at her! She's just like Park Nam Jung.
- Gosh! - "Look at her."
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- What was that? - Gosh!
(They're like parents watching their child's talent show.)
Are you sick, Jun Myun?
This is a song I like.
We should wake up at 6am if it's at 7:10am.
We have to dance with the turtles.
- See you tomorrow! - Okay!
Don't worry and head inside.
(They turn off the lights one by one.)
(The four siblings experience the first night in the Philippines.)
(The tiring first night comes to an end.)
(The morning of the start of their vacation has come.)
(Surprised)
(Jung Ah sleeps in as she seems to be tired.)
(The other siblings are fast asleep as well.)
(Twitching)
(Jun Myun wakes up at 6:15am.)
(She makes her bed as soon as she gets up.)
(She gets changed into the perfect turtle outfit.)
Gosh, I feel so tired.
Me too.
(She relieves her fatigue from yesterday through stretching.)
(Groaning)
(Her short stretching session comes to an end.)
(Passing out)
(The aftereffect of work hits Jung Ah belatedly.)
(This person is quite diligent in the morning.)
(Surprised)
The mango pit from yesterday.
That's the pit?
(She can't let go of the mango even while explaining herself.)
- The pits? I'll suck on them. - The pits.
I'm not that person yet.
(She keeps her word well.)
Have some of the coffee.
(The sisters share the coffee.)
We're going to see the turtles.
I wonder how much I must doll myself up.
(This much)
You look so cute in purple, Hye Yoon.
I must take a picture of this. What's with you?
You're so cute. Stay right there. Let me take a photo of you.
(Photo Park has come all the way to the Philippines.)
Gosh, look at her legs.
(She's ready to meet the turtles.)
Kim Hye Yoon.
(She finds her to be cute.)
I had no choice. I had to take a photo of her.
(Dex comes in as the photos are taken.)
- Good morning! - Hey.
(Shall the siblings head out now?)
Hello.
(Hye Yoon comes out first in her purple swimwear.)
(Mark was waiting outside.)
Good morning!
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
(They give each other a morning hug.)
Let's set off.
(The four siblings get in the car.)
Are you okay now? Is your body much better now?
Does your body ache all over?
- I'm not aching as much. - Same here.
- I'm fine now. - We were so worried yesterday.
I feel a bit of muscle pain from my workout yesterday.
(Dex feels a bit of muscle pain.)
Why do you feel muscle pain when you work out all the time?
Did you work out after taking a break?
This means the workout was successful.
Muscles grow bigger as they recover from being torn.
Why tear up your muscles?
(She might be right about that.)
"Why tear up your muscles?"
(Her funny comment is said one more time.)
I'm feeling fine right now.
I can dance with the turtles.
Get ready. I'm going to put on a fantastic performance with them.
I'm ready to dance.
You're going to scare the turtles.
(After moving in the car while chatting and laughing,)
I slightly saw the sea.
(a refreshing scenery can be seen.)
It's the sea!
(The sun's glitter feels so bright.)
(The bottom can be seen from the clear sea.)
(There's a beautiful white beach as well.)
(The real vacation in Bohol begins.)
(Amazed)
It feels different here.
Gosh!
This is awesome.
(Amazed)
Where are the turtles? The turtles.
(Shall we head out to the sea to meet the turtles?)
Can we dance with the turtles if we move this way?
You must get on the boat.
(You must get on the boat to meet the turtles.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Today's dance mates)
Thank you.
Hello, everyone. It's a pleasure to meet you all.
- Hello. - Hello. This is Dex.
(Bring up the atmosphere.)
(Please take your seat.)
(Why must I feel embarrassed for him?)
(He gets stopped right away.)
- Please stay seated. - Oh, right.
One, two, three.
(The crew members push the boat to help the boat sail off.)
Who was the one to eat so much last night?
(Laughing)
(They manage to set off.)
(Where are the four siblings headed to?)
It was very cloudy today.
I think the skies have opened up for all of you today.
We will transfer to a bigger boat after moving for five minutes.
The first thing we'll do is to meet the dolphins.
- Dolphins? - We'll meet the dolphins first.
We'll swim with the turtles after that.
(A tour)
(Today...)
(it's Dance with Turtles.)
(Hopping tour)
(Once you dive into the water,)
(a whole new world of Bohol unfolds before you.)
(Wonderful coral reefs and colorful fishes)
(In this beautiful sea,)
(will they be able to meet dolphins and wild turtles?)
("Dance with Turtles" was the hopping tour.)
Did you all have breakfast?
- No. - No?
You will be served with mangoes first.
(Mangoes?)
I love mangoes.
- You do? - Yes.
She eats four mangoes at once.
(Four?)
There's enough for each person to have five.
Right. Please give us a lot.
I'm going to dance after eating the mangoes.
(They are heading toward the mango party boat.)
There's our boat. They're waving at us.
Really?
(Our mango party boat?)
(Surprised)
(He grasps his head.)
(Why did the siblings get surprised?)
(It's such a big welcome.)
(The greeting dance is getting wilder.)
(Oh, dear.)
Their energy is making me feel shy.
(Covering her mouth)
(At a loss for words at the unexpected energy)
(This is bad.)
What you did just now was nothing.
(I wasn't hoping for this much energy.)
(Regardless, they're very hyped up.)
(They're getting more energetic.)
(They've barely started.)
(Welcome.)
Is this really happening?
They maintain that energy for six hours.
Six hours?
(Shocked)
They're way too hyped.
(Can the siblings survive in the dance nightmare?)
One, two, three.
- Hello! - Hello!
(They enter the energetic course.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(They're changing to a bigger boat.)
At 8am in the morning.
- Hello. - We're in trouble.
(Moaning)
(The welcome ceremony hasn't ended yet.)
(The crew welcomes them passionately.)
(It's nice to meet you.)
(Welcome.)
(The 1st crisis in his 8 years of life)
(The siblings have never experienced such a welcome ceremony either.)
They perform for you.
(A welcome dance)
(I like a performance.)
(Preheating the excitement)
(He's slowly getting engrossed.)
Yes.
(Impressive stunts follow.)
(Eyes wide open)
Amazing.
(From breakdancing...)
(to acrobatics)
(What did I just see?)
(Flying)
(Sliding down)
(She's beat even before seeing a turtle.)
This is bad.
It's fun.
- Really? - Yes.
We don't dance with turtles.
We see turtles, and we dance.
- I think so too. - Together.
We dance and see turtles.
I want to see turtles.
(We're getting closer to turtles.)
- Isn't the weather fantastic? - Yes, the weather is nice.
(Absorbing the weather)
My gosh.
The sun isn't too strong. It's perfect.
The wind is breezy.
(The perfect weather for a hopping tour)
It's so nice.
In 2 to 3 minutes, we'll arrive at the dolphin area.
It's my first time seeing dolphins.
Really?
It's my first time seeing one at the sea.
- Right, at the sea. - Yes.
You don't get to see them up close.
(How will the dolphins greet us?)
(The boat sails nonstop to the dolphin area.)
(They've finally arrived.)
All the other boats have gathered here.
You're right.
(The sea is still silent.)
(They wait nervously.)
Why won't they come out?
(Dolphins, let us meet quickly.)
(Is it not time yet?)
- There! - What?
(Could it be?)
(Something's there!)
(Surprised)
There they are. Can you see?
Yes.
(The dolphins finally show themselves.)
- My gosh. - Nice.
Look over there.
Goodness.
(Swimming powerfully)
There are so many of them.
- There are a lot of dolphins. - Right? There are so many.
(They swim across the blue sea and say hi.)
(This is how they look in the water.)
(The dolphins move beautifully.)
(They just observe in a daze.)
(They try to capture every dolphin with their eyes.)
So cute.
(They do a welcoming stunt too.)
(The happiest person right now)
They're so cute.
Jump!
(Dolphin, jump one more time!)
(Laughing)
Are you embarrassed? Are you?
- Kim Hye Yoon. - No.
- Can't you see I'm doing my best? - How could I...
be embarrassed by you?
(Looking at the beautiful dolphins makes their happiness level rise.)
(As if to meet their expectations, they jump again.)
(Are they saying hi to us?)
A baby dolphin.
- How cute. - This is fascinating.
(Everyone here will remember this moment forever.)
It's a dolphin!
(She's happy.)
(Since we met the dolphins, let's go dance with turtles!)
(Shouting)
(What is this?)
(Welcome to the 1st row of a water festival.)
(The nightmare of energy starts again.)
(Clenching her eyes)
(Crying out)
(I'm totally drained!)
(This isn't right.)
(Their vacation turns into survival in an instant.)
(Drop the anchor now!)
(The final dance)
(Gosh, stop it now!)
(Can we see turtles at this rate?)
(Will the plan to meet wild turtles go up in smoke?)
(The four siblings are completely exhausted.)
(I can't even go back and cook!)
(For the first time on the show, they go on a dinner strike?)
(The kitchen is closed today.)
(The reality hits her.)
(Let's go, please.)
(Glancing)
(Francis?)
("Men in Black?")
(And elegant actresses)
(What's the mysterious night out about?)
(And...)
(It's a winding mountain road.)
(I have a bad feeling about this.)
(They arrive at a mysterious workplace...)
(after driving up the mountain for one hour.)
(What unfolds in front of the four nervous siblings...)
(is an expansive field about 33,100m² big.)
(Harvest everything...)
(that grows on this field.)
(We need to go around the whole field?)
(In the wildest wild...)
(of the show's history,)
(the four siblings collapse in the end?)
(Will they be able to survive?)