Are we going to see the turtles now?
- I'm excited.
- I saw the dolphin.
I saw the baby dolphin.
The baby dolphin was this big.
- How adorable!
- It was the size of a puppy.
- Right.
- It was so adorable.
How adorable!
(She's focused on something.)
Gosh, there are the mangoes!
(The mangoes were spotted on her radar.)
- Thank you!
- Enjoy!
Thank you.
Go ahead.
- Didn't we get too much?
- Right. We got so much.
The fruits in the Philippines are definitely plump.
(She starts eating in earnest while grabbing it with her hand.)
(Chewing)
It surely tastes great.
It's really good.
Mangoes are the best.
(Chuckling)
(They're not as enthusiastic as Mango Park, )
(but the younger ones enjoy the mangoes as well.)
It's good.
(Why doesn't Jung Ah have a plate?)
Are you okay?
- Are you not going to eat?
- I don't want any.
Please tell us.
(Jung Ah is actually feeling seasick.)
The mango tastes great.
(Try some.)
- It's good.
Have all the mangoes you want while you're here.
(Feeling sick)
Mangoes are the best.
(Mango Park was peeling off the flesh from the peel.)
(She spots something.)
Hey, Kim Hye Yoon!
You have to eat like this!
I'm sorry, Jun Myun.
You have to tear it with your mouth.
We will take pictures for you.
This is how they should be eaten.
Like this.
(I will watch you.)
(Taking a bite in a tough manner)
You should eat like a teto-girl.
Are you a teto-girl?
I'm totally a teto-girl.
- Totally a teto-girl?
- Of course.
You're so funny.
(You're so funny.)
I'm totally a teto-girl.
(Ye Seo has grown up to become a teto-girl.)
Anyway,
- this is so delicious.
- Right.
- I'm serious.
- You are?
- Right. I'm the Fruit Queen.
- Congratulations.
"Congratulations."
She's getting a refill for mangoes.
Gosh, Jun Myun.
(Desperate hands)
She must be insane.
(She's at the late stage of her craze for Filipino mangoes.)
- Have a lot.
- "Have a lot."
Stop eating, Jun Myun!
But they're mangoes!
- Hey!
- Dex!
Have all of them!
- Why is she so funny?
- Dex...
Enjoy this moment!
Enjoy this moment if you can't avoid it!
She's right, though.
I had great energy at the start.
I went, "Put your hands up!"
But I felt intimidated after meeting the real masters.
(Intimidated)
- You became quiet.
- Right.
I got exposed in front of the real masters.
Are you done?
- Yes.
- Yes. I'm done.
- How was it? Was it good?
- Thank you.
- It was really good!
- It was good!
- It was so good!
(This is a story of a woman...)
(who has fallen in love with mangoes.)
(Farewell has come without notice.)
- It was so good!
- It was good!
(Mango Park isn't ready to send the mangoes away.)
(Desperate)
You can have more! We have more!
(That's enough.)
Just give her a whole box.
We'll take a whole box.
(Is she wailing?)
(The traces of you are still here.)
(Mango Park will return.)
(Soon)
We all were able to laugh thanks to Jun Myun.
She's so adorable.
(There are 30 minutes left until the dance party with turtles.)
You're so pretty!
Hye Yoon!
- You're so pretty!
- Thank you!
- This is driving me crazy.
- You're so pretty, Kim Hye Yoon!
This is driving me crazy.
- Say that louder!
- Gosh!
Kim Hye Yoon!
- Kim Hye Yoon!
- What's wrong with her?
She's starting to enjoy it.
You're so pretty, Kim Hye Yoon!
Thank you!
She's thanking people even while she's doing that?
You're so pretty!
Can I get on my back?
(Getting on her back boldly)
(Is the young one going loose?)
Gosh!
(He doesn't understand why she's being like this.)
Who is that? My gosh!
(The youngest daughter of your family)
- I'm sorry!
- I feel so embarrassed.
She isn't part of us!
She isn't part of us, everyone!
Take pictures of us as well!
Come on.
Why are you being like this? Hey, move away!
Gosh, I'm getting scared.
She's being like this all of a sudden?
This is hilarious! I'm having so much fun!
(The photoshoot of the youngest comes to an end.)
We must warm up before we go swimming, right?
- Right.
- But we don't have any warmups.
That is why all of you must participate.
(There are no warmups when we're going into the water?)
Everybody!
- Clap!
(Here's how we warm up.)
(That was amazing.)
(The intro of this song sounds familiar!)
("Kung Ddari Sha Bah Rah" by Clon)
(Singing)
(Including Jung Ah, who was struggling with seasickness, )
(the guests who felt awkward all start dancing.)
(When you feel depressed and frustrated)
(Go up the mountain and make a shout)
- Everybody!
(After starting with the shoulder dance, )
(they start to warm up in earnest.)
(Different methods of handling the dance session)
(Getting up right away)
(This is exciting!)
Let's go!
(Sending the ones sitting by)
Let's go, kids!
Follow along!
(Getting dragged out)
(Refusing to go)
(Shall we warm up ourselves now?)
- Let's go!
- Okay!
What are we going to do?
(Chicken, banana)
Gosh, they're doing this one.
It's the famous song.
Let's go!
Chicken, banana.
(If you can't avoid it, )
(enjoy it.)
(Loosening up)
Chicken!
(He takes the stage with his energy.)
Let's go!
(The crew members show him their respect.)
What's wrong with him?
(Can you feel it?)
(The gunman appears.)
Shoot!
(Let's go, Dex!)
(He's a funny one.)
It's the whole song.
(Shooting away his joy)
(Someone stop him.)
(Dex's dancing was super effective!)
One, two, three, go!
(Crazy warmup)
(There's a rush of dopamine!)
(Shouting)
(They have been warming up for 20 minutes.)
(The youngest on the boat will perform the finale.)
- Let's go!
- You can do it!
- One, two, three!
(Spinning)
Good job!
- He's so cute!
- One, two, three!
- Thank you!
That was great! You're the best!
That was impressive! Nice one!
- The B-Boy.
- Good job!
Was it fun to do?
It was fun but a bit scary.
Can we meet the turtles?
(After having a great time...)
Turtles, after all of this?
(They're out of energy.)
The water is so clear.
I realized this after getting to my senses.
- The water is so clear.
- Right?
- Right. It's amazing.
- You can see the bottom.
(The color of the sea is clearly different.)
(It's so clear that it feels glorious.)
(There are people enjoying snorkeling.)
(The emerald sea that can be seen in Bohol, Philippines)
(Balicasag turtle point)
(The pearl of Bohol, Balicasag Island)
(All kinds of tropical fish live in the pure sea.)
(Will they be able to meet the turtles here?)
The waves are a lot stronger here, right?
Because of the waves and the tidal current,
everyone will swim with the life jackets on...
excluding the free divers.
(Everyone will wear life jackets and will be with a guide.)
(The sea doesn't feel peaceful unlike its clear color.)
The waves are really strong.
I feel sick.
(It's sickening just to watch.)
(The tidal current around Balicasag Island is strong.)
(That was why it was used as a prison camp in the past.)
(The boat keeps shaking because of the strong waves.)
Gosh, I feel sick.
(The seasickness gets even worse.)
There's one reason why we're swimming around this area.
It's because there are a lot of turtles here.
(Around 500 turtles live in this area.)
That's what we'll do.
(Jung Ah thinks to herself after looking at the waves.)
(She decides to swim at the next point.)
(Everyone starts putting on the snorkeling gear.)
(The mates that are ready head off to start snorkeling.)
I want to go down quickly!
(Let's go and meet the turtles as well.)
(Disappointed)
(I should still see them off.)
Okay. Wait right there.
- No!
- This way.
(Dex's camera is ready as well.)
(The youngest who enjoys water activities dives in as well.)
(The second sibling also dives in while holding onto Dex's hand.)
(The shoot was taken with the help of a guide...)
(while following the safety guidelines.)
(Let's head off to find the turtles!)
(They explore through the water while holding onto the tube.)
(Dex moves freely on his own as a former UDT soldier.)
(The three siblings enjoy the clear sea.)
(It finally feels like a vacation now.)
(We will find the turtles.)
(Before looking for the turtles in earnest, )
(the youngest gets reminded of someone.)
I want to give it to them.
(The eldest sister who is left alone)
(You're doing well, right?)
Gosh, our Hye Yoon is back alive.
(Jung Ah!)
(We'll come back safely!)
(See you later.)
(It's time to look for the turtles.)
(Looking around)
(The turtles aren't seen right away.)
(The ones who wish to see them must find them.)
(She seems to feel uncomfortable with her snorkel.)
(The youngest stops for a while.)
(The older brother steps up.)
(He helps her grab the tube.)
Take it off.
Take it off and shake it.
Bite onto it again.
(The snorkel is put on again.)
Okay.
(He acts as an older brother again with his specialty.)
(The youngest starts exploring again.)
(A turtle is found!)
It's a turtle!
Over there!
(Screaming)
(Amazed)
(The three siblings go wild.)
Hey! Turtle!
(The turtle swims peacefully.)
It's a turtle!
(Awesome!)
It's fascinating!
(Here's something even more fascinating.)
Turtle!
(Two turtles!)
(Kissing)
(It starts eating off the ground...)
(as if nothing happened.)
(The turtles are seen up close for the first time.)
(The three siblings look at them in awe.)
(With the turtle that eats off the ground in peace, )
(they dance.)
(A dance session underwater)
(Dances with Turtles)
(Shouting)
(Exclaiming)
I'm so scared.
- Hurry.
- Here you go.
I got it.
(Dex's camera)
Gosh.
(The turtle is coming up.)
(They meet a turtle that comes up to breathe.)
(We have to see this!)
(Puff)
(Gurgling)
(It's close enough to touch if you stretch out your hand.)
(The turtle's breathing that Dex filmed)
(It's illegal to touch turtles.)
(This was filmed in accordance with local laws.)
(Hello)
(Goodbye)
Unbelievable.
- Oh, my.
- It was so adorable.
- It was very...
- It was so cute.
The turtle must have come up to the surface to breathe.
(I can't believe that I saw a turtle breathe.)
It was amazing.
(While the turtle that had given them a rare sight...)
(went back to grazing, )
(the three siblings arrived on the island safely.)
Okay, thank you.
(Exhausted after swimming)
Okay?
- I'm okay.
- Breathe.
Jun Myun, why are you also speaking to me in English?
I'm speaking to you in English.
(Laughing at Jun Myun's speaking English)
(Collapsing)
- That's right.
- It's so comfortable.
Stay like that.
I'll cover Ms. Actress with a blanket.
Thank you.
(Jun Myun makes her laugh, and Dex covers her with a blanket.)
It was a fun activity at the sea.
- I agree.
- Yes.
- It's rare to see turtles.
- Right.
(They also danced with turtles that summer.)
Gosh, it's so beautiful.
(She's taking a walk on Balicasag Beach.)
Shall we go over there?
(Walking along the white sandy beach)
(With gentle waves drifting in)
(Surrounded by relaxed travelers)
(Both the body and the mind are unwinding.)
(Restoring her energy with a promenade)
(Pausing)
Won't it take a while to get here by swimming?
(Enjoying a picturesque scenery while waiting for the siblings)
(Balicasag, a treasure island for divers)
(At a quaint seaside restaurant)
(People gather, still damp from the water.)
(She's supposed to meet her siblings here.)
(Jung Ah is all alone.)
(The restaurant begins to get crowded with customers.)
(She even sees her dance mates from the same boat.)
(Watching in silence)
I guess they're having a lot of fun.
There's no sight of them.
I'm the only one with separation anxiety.
(While the eldest sister is enduring separation anxiety)
We got to see a turtle that came up.
It was so cute.
- We saw it very close.
- I know.
I also made a wish.
What? What did you wish for?
- A bunch of things.
- I see.
Take a guess.
- Our show's spin-off...
- That it becomes a hit.
For a safe shoot...
I didn't wish for that.
- What?
A safe shoot for Fresh Off the Sea's spin-off.
You should've wished for that.
That's needless to say. It will go well.
It will be fine.
Did you wish for a girlfriend?
- Jun Myun.
- Yes?
If I tell you, it won't come true.
- That's true.
- Really?
(Wishes only come true when they're kept secret.)
Gosh, look at the sky.
It looks so beautiful.
- Goodness, this is really...
- The sky looks incredible.
(Clear and blue sky that looks just like the transparent sea)
My goodness.
- This is a real getaway.
- Seriously.
We're really on vacation.
- It really feels like a vacation.
- Yes.
(In full vacation mode)
(While they laugh and chat, )
(she's waiting anxiously.)
(When are they coming?)
They're coming.
(She spots Dex.)
(Springing to her feet as she's happy to see him)
Jung Ah.
- How was it?
- It was fun.
I took the boat.
We saw so many turtles.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Was it fascinating?
- There were so many underwater.
Are we done with swimming?
- No.
- We're doing it once more.
We're going in to see some fish. I'm thinking of going in.
You should.
- We came all the way here.
- Will I be able to breathe?
- Of course, Jung Ah.
- Definitely.
The water is really beautiful.
I see.
(Here comes today's meal.)
(Her jaw drops.)
What's this?
(Her eyes are fixed on it.)
(A lavish, unfamiliar feast is laid out before them.)
(On a large banana leaf)
(Fish and meat)
(Fried food)
(Grilled skewers)
(Fruit and more)
(A variety of traditional Filipino dishes with rice)
Oh, my. This is amazing. It looks really beautiful.
Shouldn't we take a photo of it?
Yes, we really should.
We can't eat this anywhere else.
(A sight that you want to save)
- "Bohol." - "Bohol."
Bon appetit.
- Bon appetit.
(Glancing)
Go ahead first, Jung Ah.
(The youngest who's a polite, Confucian girl)
(Then I'll start with fried squid.)
(Deep-fried until crispy that looks mouthwatering)
(How does it taste?)
(Crunchy and chewy)
(The youngest follows the leader and pops one into her mouth.)
(Eyes lighting up)
(Jun Myun follows the trend and takes a bite too.)
Oh, is it fried squid?
- Isn't it good?
- It's good.
This is good.
(Dex also takes a bite.)
(What is Jung Ah's next dish pick?)
(One fish that looks golden and crunchy)
(The Philippines' national fish, grilled milkfish)
(Separating the meat carefully...)
(and putting it into the mouth)
(Nodding)
- It's good.
- It's like grilled fish in Korea.
The fish is also delicious.
The fish is good like grilled fish in Korea.
It's similar.
- Right.
- This is nice.
(They can't stop eating it.)
(After good food, rinse the mouth with sweet pineapple juice.)
Gosh, it's made with real pineapple.
It's real pineapple.
- The pineapple juice is excellent.
- It's made with only pineapple.
It's delicious.
(The food suits everyone's taste.)
This restaurant must be quite good.
Jun Myun, didn't you eat a lot of mangoes before?
- Now...
- Mango isn't...
- a meal.
- That doesn't count.
(What's wrong with this young man?)
Come on. You know better.
Goodness.
(I made a mistake.)
I already have a plan.
- What's your plan?
- What is it?
I'll finish the meal with some mango.
(Her favorite mango comes last.)
She's eating mangoes...
- to her heart's content.
- I'll clean the palate with it.
She's eating mangoes to her heart's content.
I can eat mangoes endlessly.
For me...
(Foodie Jun Myun is a total J when it comes to eating.)
(Here's your mango.)
Have mine too, Jun Myun.
- That's funny.
- Leave a piece for Hye Yoon.
Hand me Dex's mango too.
Are you serious about eating it all?
Of course. Why do you even ask?
Will you be okay?
Gosh, Jung Ah.
I'm starting to get worried.
What if something goes wrong with her?
- Why?
- Here's why.
She had mangoes in the fridge as soon as she got up.
I saw her picking at the mango seed this morning.
You can't do this.
- You'll be in big trouble.
- This is for Hye Yoon.
I don't want any.
You'll go into shock.
What? No way.
I won't go into shock from eating mangoes.
She will go into shock from eating mangoes.
What's wrong with you?
(Jun Myun's love for mangoes is willing to risk a shock.)
Let's go to a mango farm on Wednesday.
For labor.
(We have a mango-friendly worker.)
We'd earn a lot of money that day.
What's the point? She will eat them all anyway.
(The story has a set ending.)
Jung Ah.
I also like mangoes a lot.
Compared to Jun Myun, I'm not someone who likes them.
- I can't say...
- Don't go around and tell people...
- that I like mangoes.
- that you like mangoes.
I can only say...
- that I eat mangoes.
- You know how to eat them.
- I know how to eat them.
- Right.
- This is what it means...
- What's with you?
- to be a mango fan.
- Exactly.
That's what Jun Myun showed me.
- She's Mango Park.
- Mango Park.
Mango Park.
She isn't Sauce Park anymore.
(Mango Park finished getting her sugar fix.)
That's so funny.
- My gosh.
- Jun Myun is the only one...
- who makes you laugh with mangoes.
- Seriously.
What's wrong with everyone?
(Shall we go back to the sea?)
(They get back on the island hopping boat.)
(It's time to swim again.)
(Dancing)
(Today's second swimming spot is...)
(a fish sanctuary point.)
(Also known as Nemo Point)
Isn't the water much calmer than before?
If you know how to swim,
you can go in with your life vest on.
(Jung Ah, who was seasick, gives it a try this time.)
(Shall we go meet the Nemos?)
(Actually, this is Jung Ah's first time snorkeling.)
If you're ready, please go to the front.
All right.
Okay.
(A beginner swimmer who doesn't know how to use a snorkel)
(Although she's a beginner, she leads the way as always.)
(That's how Leader Yeom's first attempt started.)
(Jung Ah, you can do it.)
(While holding on to the swim ring carefully, )
(she goes in the water.)
(Following the brave big sister who's a beginner)
(Both the youngest...)
(and the second eldest enter the water.)
(The third, Water Dex)
(He goes for a straight dive.)
I can see very clearly.
(The three sisters set out.)
(She can't put her head underwater.)
(To find Nemo)
(However, )
(Jung Ah still can't put her head underwater.)
(Snorkeling is still unfamiliar to her.)
Are you okay?
(Nodding)
(The 2nd and the 3rd eldest are at ease.)
(Exclaiming)
(The youngest lets out a shout as if she found something.)
(Hesitating)
(Whatever)
(When you dip your head in, )
(you can see a school of tropical fish.)
(Their eyes are fixed.)
(Colorful tropical fish weave through a mesmerizing coral forest.)
(Leader Yeom is captivated by the underwater world.)
(Kicking hard)
(Completely adapted)
(Hye Yoon's perspective)
(She reaches out her hand cautiously toward the fish.)
(The three sisters are fully enjoying peace in the water.)
Gosh, it's salty.
(Laughing)
(Meanwhile, Dex is swimming with ease.)
(Diving all the way down)
(Total freedom)
(We envy you.)
(The underwater world shown by Dex)
(At the end of a coral tunnel)
(Nemo's house)
(While Dex roams the ocean freely)
Okay. One, two, three.
(The eldest who's already tired is being pulled out.)
Okay.
(The second eldest tries to follow her...)
(but fails.)
Okay.
(Laughing)
One, two, three.
(The danger of mango addiction)
Okay.
(Just then, Dex stops in place.)
(Over there!)
(Did he spot something?)
- There's a turtle underwater.
- Really?
A turtle.
(Where's the turtle?)
(There it is!)
(Dex dives immediately.)
(A sea turtle is swimming peacefully, )
(and Dex follows right behind.)
(The youngest is watching it all.)
(Amazing!)
(One more time)
(Up close)
(Shouting with joy)
There was a sea turtle here.
(Moved)
I'm jealous. I want to go down too.
(I want to go down too.)
- I saw a turtle.
- That's amazing.
It was amazing.
(Finding Nemo ends.)
- Did it go well?
- I saw a sea turtle.
You did?
Was it nice?
You can't see the ground when you're underwater.
- Right.
- Yes.
Did you see me swim up a while ago?
It's where I was talking about.
Jung Ah, I'll write about it in my diary tonight.
- No, that's not necessary.
- "Today, Jung Ah..."
"For the 1st time in 55 years."
(In 55 years for the 1st time since she was born)
- "In the sea in Bohol..." - I didn't even snorkel...
- during my honeymoon.
- She went into the sea today.
I'm in a good mood. Have another mango.
Really?
(Now is the time to go back to the land.)
When you're hungry after a swim,
nothing is better than eating ramyeon on a boat.
(Radiant)
This is crazy.
Ramyeon on a boat is exceptional.
(Everyone, don't you know what it tastes like?)
(The well-planned foodie reached her goal again.)
- Try it.
- Eating ramyeon after playing...
- in the water is the best.
- Right.
This is the best.
It's so good.
- Korean ramyeon is the best.
- It's ramyeon.
(This is the taste.)
(Dex devoured it with satisfaction.)
(Glancing)
What was your favorite part of today?
- Seeing the turtles.
- The turtles, right?
I also liked that.
Yesterday, we caught mud crabs.
We worked after coming all the way here.
We went to a marsh.
- We bought and ate them.
- You did?
You bought what we had caught.
- Enjoy the rest of your trip.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
After a swim,
he came back to life.
I'm going to die soon.
(A bowl of ramyeon after a swim)
(Post-meal drowsiness hits everyone on board.)
(Quiet)
Drop the anchor. Raise it.
(Collapsing)
All right, you want some more?
- More.
- Who wants some more?
(I'm not going to watch it.)
(Smiling uncomfortably)
- It doesn't end.
- Let's do it.
(Please save me.)
(Passed out)
Clap.
(Am I dreaming?)
("Let's Go On a Vacation" by Lee Seung Gi)
(On a green hill)
With a backpack... It's a song that I know.
On top of that, it's an uplifting song.
(The sun...)
(As always, the sacrificial lamb is chosen.)
(Ice water)
(A splash of cold water)
(Yelling)
(A tingling kick that chases off the food coma)
(It must be refreshing.)
(Her over there!)
(Tossing)
(The second eldest is selected.)
(Goodbye...)
(An electric shock)
(Goodness)
(Laughing heartily and forgetting drowsiness)
(Filling every moment to the brim with joy)
(While looking at the sky, we sing)
(Hear the echo return)
(To find the sea turtle in the ocean)
My sunglasses.
(Toward that place)
(We set off on a journey)
- Hear the echo return - Hear the echo return.
- Leading us to a flowing stream - Leading us to a flowing stream.
- To that place - To that place.
Hey!
(Dance party with turtles...)
(ends in success.)
Mark.
(They reunite with Mark after returning to land.)
Hello.
- Thank you.
- Was it fun?
(Dex is about to get in first.)
Should I lay this down?
(Their bodies are wet after coming out of the ocean.)
Good.
(They lay down the towel in a respectful manner.)
I turned off the air conditioner.
Okay. Thank you.
Because you'll feel chilly.
(Dex acts thoughtfully so that the siblings won't catch a cold.)
I turned off the air conditioner.
Why does today feel so long?
- It's crazy.
- It was long yesterday too.
It's only 2pm right now.
- "It was long yesterday too." - It's only 2pm, Jung Ah.
Were there many turtles?
- Yes.
- Yes, there were a lot.
Brother, did you dive?
- Yes. It was 7m deep.
- Was it?
It was 7m.
(I even went down to a depth of 7m.)
- Did you swim with turtles?
- Yes.
(Of course.)
- Like this?
- Yes.
(He tells his adventure with turtles to Mark.)
It was here.
(It was about this distance.)
Stay there.
Did you go 7m deep?
Yes. I heard it was between 7m and 10m.
(He's incredible.)
Actually, 7m isn't that deep.
(To a former UDT, 7m is like a neighborhood pool.)
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Go.
It's "tayo" in Filipino.
- Tayo.
Tayo.
(Off to their house!)
(While leaving the emerald green ocean behind, )
(they hum...)
(on their way back home.)
Today, to be really honest,
I feel like I'm on vacation.
- After the activity today?
- Yes.
Yesterday, it felt like I was shooting Fresh off the Sea.
Today, seriously,
it felt like I was on a vacation as a reward.
Really?
Okay. We're coming.
(They are near their house before they know it.)
(Peeking)
Dex, you have great stamina.
- Thank you.
- What?
It's because I won't be able to work out if I sleep now.
I'll get too relaxed.
So I can't sleep before my workout.
I envy...
your perseverance.
And your efforts.
I know. His self-management.
(His efforts and self-management)
I just love lying down.
I love it too.
I love lying down too.
- Thank you, Mark.
- Thank you.
- See you later.
- Take it easy.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Yes.
- Enjoy your workout.
- Okay.
Bye.
(The sisters will take a break for a moment.)
(Jun Myun comes out from the after-swimming shower.)
(Throwing)
(Mysterious clothes cover her bed.)
(Prudent)
(Jung Ah and Hye Yoon's room)
Should I try the dress on?
(Dress?)
(Two days ago at the Incheon International Airport)
There was something like...
(Something like a meal coupon)
(I've prepared...)
(an amazing party dress.)
(The siblings brought party costumes for the high-end meal coupon.)
(Yesterday at the siblings' house)
Tomorrow, we'll play a game to win a meal coupon.
(Here it comes!)
(When are we doing it?)
(Burning with passion)
(We'll put on the dress right away tomorrow.)
(Our outfits...)
(Their outfits call for a photo wall.)
(No matter what, )
(let's do a photo session in the living room.)
Even if we failed to win the meal coupon...
(The siblings have prepared dresses as you can see.)
You look like you're at an award ceremony.
I'll be so upset if we can't eat out after doing this.
We're at an award ceremony like the Baeksang Awards.
(As the siblings asked for a photo wall...)
(Meal-coupon Awards)
(Dining Awards)
(The ceremony begins now.)
(Dining Awards' food carpet)
(Dining Awards' photo wall)
(Stars are entering.)
I'm Participant One.
(Trying not to laugh)
I'm Park Jun Myun.
(Turning)
(Embarrassed)
(Tango Park)
(Tango Park enters with the sound of a boiling kettle.)
Gosh. This is hilarious.
- We'll take a photo.
- Photo? Let's take photos.
(As an a-list star from Korea makes an appearance, )
Are we good?
(the press is heated.)
Here are the hearts.
(Extras for her fans)
What's your dress code tonight?
(Sighing)
I have an acquaintance who I owed a big time.
And she has a wedding in the Philippines.
(The kettle is on.)
So I've prepared the outfit for the wedding.
Isn't it for a funeral?
(Flustered)
That's an option too.
It's good for both occasions. It's multi-black...
(Turning quickly all of a sudden)
(Laughing)
I'm wearing black. Thank you. I'm Participant One.
Are you giving points? No?
(Sullen)
(The actress leaves the carpet.)
(Another actress heads to the food carpet.)
(With a totally relaxed smile, )
(she walks briskly.)
(This actress is...)
(a former Miss Korea runner-up.)
(Looking)
I have to look at each one.
She's a former Miss Korea.
- We'll take photos.
- Okay.
Please give us a heart.
(An old-style heart)
Please give us a cheek heart.
(Flustered)
(She masters a newer heart too.)
I have a mark on my cheek from the swimming goggles.
(The aftermath of the boat tour)
What's your dress code tonight?
Actually, I wore this,
expecting to go to a high-end restaurant.
So I chose a dress that goes well with wine.
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
(Will she go to a fancy restaurant as she wishes?)
What's happening?
I'm so nervous.
(An actress enters nervously.)
(Clumsily)
(Shifting her vibe suddenly)
(Laughing)
(Giggling)
What?
(The first actress to enter the runway...)
(while snickering)
(Focused)
From left to center. Forward. Downward.
To the right.
Thank you.
- We'll have a brief photo session.
- Okay.
Please give us a heart.
(Laughing)
What's your dress code today?
Today, I wanted...
to look like a little princess.
Her nickname is My Melody Princess.
(Boasting about her little sister)
Yes. I've prepared to look...
like My Melody Princess or a little princess.
Aren't your shoulders too exposed?
My shoulders? They are...
The sleeves are crawling up a bit.
It's making me uncomfortable.
(Actresses' competition)
Well... Right. I don't think I can cook.
So I have to eat out today.
(Declaring a boycott on cooking tonight)
(I'm going to eat out tonight.)
Thank you.
Come here.
What are we doing?
Will Jin Young be over the top?
- I can't wait.
- I didn't get to see him.
He was in the restroom the whole time.
(He's busy in the makeup room getting ready for the finale.)
(Rustling)
- Why were you nervous?
- I don't know. I was so nervous.
(Chatting while waiting for the finale)
(Opening abruptly)
(Glancing)
- I knew it.
(Did you expect it?)
(Screaming)
(Here's the cheer.)
(Walking confidently in a black suit)
(Looking somewhat uncomfortable in contrast)
(Uncomfortable)
That look on his face.
(Awkward)
What's with the look on your face?
(He has a food-carpet fright.)
Please look to the left side too.
(Photo session)
I think he's feeling very awkward too.
What?
(That's correct.)
(Feeling extremely awkward, he gives two thumbs up.)
I think he's broken.
Thank you all for coming today.
I've come with a heavy heart, expecting a big award.
That's how I've gotten here.
Right. And the concept of my outfit is an agent from "Man in Black."
I'll complete a mission.
- Thank you.
- What is this?
- Cool.
- You've prepared a lot.
He came prepared.
- He was well-prepared.
- He wrote a script.
No, that's not true.
Now, we'll go straight...
- Let's play the game.
- to the game.
Okay. Quickly.
Right away? Is it all over already?
- We'll get ready for the game.
- Okay.
(Please forget about how I looked just now.)
(Back to reality)
It's game time.
Gosh. I'm nervous.
- This is Fresh off the Sea, right?
- What?
- Is this Fresh off the Sea?
- Yes, it is.
Yes. I've come here with a very heavy heart.
I was so nervous.
Hye Yoon and I fixed our makeup more than we did...
at an actual award show.
- We were fierce.
- We kept fixing our makeup.
Seriously. I can't cook now.
- Seriously.
- Not now.
I don't want to cook.
How can we cook in this outfit?
I can't see the ingredients because of my sunglasses.
I can't even grab a plate from the top shelf right now.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
Please. We have to go out.
When you look at the back,
the schedule for the dinner on the second day is empty.
- Yes.
- What? That's right.
Will you fill the empty slot with a low-end meal coupon?
(Low-end meal coupon)
Or will you fill it with a high-end meal coupon?
(High-end meal coupon)
Or is it going to be cooking?
Today's game will decide it.
Yes.
Right. The game with the meal coupon at stake is...
Close-Up Food Quiz.
Are you going to show only part of a dish?
Actually, while you were on Fresh off the Sea,
you cooked various dishes.
- And you enjoyed eating them too.
- Yes.
We'll use the dishes you had on this show.
(We've cooked so much.)
(Countless dishes by the siblings)
We'll give you a total of ten questions.
- Okay.
- Of the ten questions,
when you get 0 to 3 questions,
you have to cook at home.
(Scoffing)
From 4 to 7 correct answers,
we'll give you a low-end meal coupon.
- From eight, it's the high-end one.
- Yes.
We have to get almost all of them right.
That's right. We can only miss two.
- Are you ready?
- Yes, we're ready.
Then we'll give you the first question.
- Rice grains.
- That's corn.
- Corn in rice.
- Isn't that it?
- I put corn kernels in...
- Okay.
Samgyetang. No, it wasn't samgyetang.
I made a chicken dish with corn.
- Was it chicken soup?
- Yes.
I made something like that with corn, didn't I?
I think so.
Isn't that a corn kernel?
- But for me, on the other hand, - Yes.
It looks like webfoot octopus roe.
Right. The protruding roe.
What's the yellow thing in the middle, then?
I'm confident that it's corn.
- It's corn.
- It is corn.
The ones around it are rice grains.
(Analysis complete.)
- It's samgyetang with corn.
- Yes.
- I think so.
- Samgyetang made with corn.
- We harvested corn that day.
- Yes.
It was the hottest day on Earth.
- It was in Goseong.
- We got it.
- We got it. It's samgyetang.
Samgyetang with corn.
The answer is...
(Kimchi and bean sprout porridge)
- It's bean sprout porridge.
- Are those bean sprouts?
Was it the head of a bean sprout?
It wasn't corn.
Is it bean sprout ramyeon?
- We made bean sprout porridge.
- I think it's porridge.
We used the leftovers for breakfast.
- We made it.
- It was Namhae.
It was when Hwang Jung Min visited us.
(For the first guest of the show, Hwang Jung Min, )
(this dish showed the siblings' overeating restaurant.)
(Man-in-Black mode is off.)
It's kimchi and bean sprout porridge.
Right. I found it extremely hot.
- Why did you zoom it in like that?
- Seriously.
(Because that's what this quiz is.)
You got 1 question wrong. You've scored 0 points so far.
- It's so hard.
- It's quite difficult.
Okay. Next question.
One, two, three.
That's... I think that's dried radish green.
- Dried radish greens and...
- Gamjatang?
Yes. We made gamjatang.
I heard Ji Yeon loved it.
- She kept thinking about it.
- Hold on. Is it gamjatang?
- Is it not?
- Dried radish green gamjatang?
Dried radish greens...
- Or it's...
- I think that's a bone.
- Right.
- That protruding piece?
- Yes. I think you're right.
- Am I wrong?
I think you're right. That protruding piece like a hill.
Right?
(Staring)
I think that glossy thing in the upper right corner...
is napa cabbage kimchi.
That goes well with gamjatang.
(While the popular opinion is that it's gamjatang...)
- Yes.
- That ingredient goes well with it.
(Here is the answer.)
(The dish is none other than...)
(mustard green kimchi jjigae.)
- The bones.
- They are dried radish greens.
- We made...
- Mustard green kimchi.
- Mustard green kimchi was...
- We didn't use it to cook, right?
- We didn't use it to cook.
- What?
- No.
- No?
It looks like mustard green kimchi.
We got it. It's gamjatang with dried radish greens.
You were so close.
- Is it kimchi jjigae?
- It's mustard green kimchi jjigae.
Quit it.
(My goodness.)
It's because I can't remember it.
- Can't you remember it?
- No.
When did we have it?
Let's stop playing this.
Quit it and let's cook now.
- Why do you give up so quickly?
- We don't have time, anyway.
- We don't have time.
- Jung Ah.
- Okay, Jung Ah.
- I'm hungry.
Don't say that...
with your lips so red and with that look on your face.
It's scary.
(Here is the third question.)
What is that?
(This dish is...)
(anchovy pasta.)
- Isn't it pasta?
- It's pasta, but...
Back then, Jung Ah...
- What is that? A snail?
- "A snail."
There weren't any snails.
Did you catch snails?
Hey. That's expensive.
- We are not in France.
- Why did you say that?
Isn't it a black olive?
- Blave?
- Black olives.
Then Jung Ah, you made...
Hold on. We have to think what we harvested.
- You put those in.
- Yes.
Hold on. It's that one.
You pickled that fish.
It's manchovy pasta.
- It's machovy pasta.
- It's anchovy.
- It's anchovy pasta.
- Anchovy.
It's anchovy pasta, but...
- Right. Capers.
- Yes. I put capers in.
I think that's a caper.
- We got it. Anchovy pasta.
- That's right.
- Yes. That's correct.
- Gosh.
(Finally, the first correct answer)
We're so sharp.
- Let's get the next one right too.
- We were very sharp.
- Let's continue to do so.
- Next question.
(The siblings gain momentum after their first success.)
I made it if it has lots of sesame seeds.
Aren't those blue crabs?
- Gosh. It's spicy marinated crab.
- Blue crabs?
- Spicy marinated crab?
- They are blue crabs.
Spicy marinated crab.
(Answer: Spicy marinated crab)
(Staring)
What is that?
It's gimbap.
It's the end piece of a gimbap.
It's gimbap, indeed.
- We made gimbap on Ganghwa Island.
- It's gimbap. Yes.
- It's gimbap.
- He made gimbap with ssamjang.
It's ssamjang gimbap.
- That's right.
- It was way too salty.
- Gosh.
- Yes. With perilla leaves.
(Answer: Ssamjang gimbap)
- That's right.
- With one more correct answer,
we can go out, right?
(They can avoid cooking.)
Yes. That's correct.
We're so sharp.
We're eating out.
- We're eating out now, right?
- Yes.
I need to remove my lipstick first.
In order to eat something.
Her lipstick.
- That's correct, right?
- It was correct.
(After getting them right consecutively...)
We got the low-end meal coupon already.
We have to get everything right to get a high-end one.
- We got two questions wrong.
- Already.
It's a high-end one when you get all the remaining questions right.
With one question wrong,
- you'll get the low-end one.
- The low-end one. Yes.
You don't have to cook at home.
- No.
One, two, three.
(Surprised)
We have to look really carefully this time. That's...
(Careful)
Rice?
Is that jjigae or what?
Exactly.
(As expected, it isn't easy.)
Isn't it cheese pork cutlet, Jung Ah?
(Surprised)
Isn't it?
It does look like melted cheese has dried.
But its color isn't that of a pork cutlet.
I don't think so.
It was dark like that back then.
- Really?
- Yes.
That little thing at the end of the right side...
is probably the sweet potato trying to come out.
We put sweet potato mousse in it.
- We harvested sweet potatoes.
- We did put it in.
Gosh. This is really hard.
(This dish is...)
(sweet potato cheese pork cutlet.)
That's hardened cheese. What do you think?
Exactly. We didn't have ingredients that looked like that.
Also, we made a dish with cheese only once.
Usually, we cooked Korean dishes.
We didn't really make Western dishes.
But I don't think it's a pork cutlet.
There are some red spots here.
Yes. It's red.
- It's something spicy.
- It's chili powder.
It's either chili powder or pepperoncino.
I don't think it's a pork cutlet.
Isn't it a pork cutlet?
(A variable has occurred.)
What's your opinion about it being cheese?
I thought it was an onion at first.
Onion, garlic, or...
It's onion or garlic.
If it's onion and garlic...
I mean, if it's garlic, it has to be that one.
- Gambas?
- It has to be gambas...
to include garlic and peperoncino.
- Right. It's not cheese.
- Gambas?
- It's garlic.
- You think it's garlic.
- Should we go for garlic?
- Right.
Then it's gambas. We put garlic to make it.
- Gambas, then?
- Yes.
- We got it.
- We got it. It's gambas al ajillo.
The answer is...
Hold on.
We got it. It's gambas al ajillo.
The answer is...
Hold on.
Is it gambas al ajillo?
- Gambas al ajillo?
- It's not pork cutlet.
It's not pork cutlet? Then it's gambas al ajillo.
(In the end, the siblings go with gambas al ajillo.)
I'll reveal the answer.
(Sweet potato cheese pork cutlet)
(The high-end meal coupon flies away with the sunglasses.)
- Which part did you take?
- I'm sorry, I really am.
(They can't believe this is really happening.)
But how... Hold on.
You and I should get lost.
It's a promise, so...
- I'll go back to Seoul...
- Dex is mad.
And invite you to a high-end restaurant.
- Me too.
- I'll treat you.
I'll buy an expensive drink.
- Yes.
- I'll buy an expensive drink.
Can you give us one more chance?
Let's dress in these clothes and meet again there.
- Which part did you zoom in on?
- Wait.
- Even that...
- Here?
Hey. There's no point...
- to glare at it.
- I'm sorry.
- This was really delicious.
- Yes.
- It was so good.
- It's the best pork cutlet...
- in my life.
- It was so good.
Jung Ah, get the coupon.
Good. We get...
- the low-end ones at least.
- Exactly.
- I'm glad we don't have to cook.
- Yes, Jung Ah.
I'm glad we don't need to wash the dishes.
- Shall we...
- Okay.
Look forward.
(Low-end Meal Coupon)
Jung Ah, you look like an auntie who lives in LA.
(Going out with the LA auntie for a meal)
Shall we go?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- To use the low-end meal coupon.
- Let's quickly go.
Let's go.
(Just in time, a suspicious car approaches the siblings' house.)
(Low-end meal package deal)
(We'll serve you in a tuk-tuk.)
(Please get into the tuk-tuk.)
I can see nothing.
Hello.
Good night.
(Taken back)
(The most perplexing passengers the driver's ever met)
(Struggling)
- We get to ride this at least.
- Yes.
We acquired the low-end meal coupon,
so we're on the way...
(Laughing)
To the restaurant.
I'll eat a lot today.
- Sure.
- Let's go, please.
We're eating out.
- We're eating out.
(An eating-out vlog with "Men in Black")
We get to ride this.
- Right? We get to ride this.
- You're right.
Exactly. I'm just glad we're eating out.
Yes. We don't have to cook...
- or wash the dishes at least.
- Exactly.
- Let's be grateful.
- The dishes will take forever.
I agree with you.
I'm so relieved.
At least we don't get to do the dishes dressed like this.
Exactly that.
(Glancing)
What will the driver think of me?
Goodness.
- He might be scared of you.
- His face...
(Glancing)
It's funny how we're dressed like this.
I think it'll be fun...
to dress up like this and go to a diner.
(It's a first even for them.)
- It'll be fun.
- You're right.
- Rather than a luxurious place, - Yes.
- This is more fun.
- a diner might be better.
Yes.
- It's nice.
- Yes.
It's quite breezy.
It's not that hot.
Yes.
(As they drive with the cool wind...)
(They arrive at a street with a strong local vibe.)
It's a night market.
- A night market.
It must be somewhere around here.
(They arrive at today's dinner place.)
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- This way.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- It must be this way.
Our attire...
The restaurant looks fine.
(Light steps)
(Surprised)
(Amazed)
Hello.
- Hello.
Good evening.
(They exclaim as soon as they arrive. Where is this place?)
(Bohol's flashy night)
(A "night market" is set up.)
(Out of the countless markets, )
(the siblings will dine in...)
(a local skewer shop.)
(They grill the skewers of your choice on charcoal.)
(A local skewer shop with great value for money)
(The relaxing night market vibe is a plus.)
(Let's go eat skewers, shall we?)
- What's this?
- Like a buffet?
We get to choose? That's amazing.
Looks like we can choose what to eat.
Can I choose them all?
Amazing. This is nice.
But I can't see what it is.
Let me see.
(Getting in the way)
The dress gets in the way.
I can't move my arms well.
- Exactly. It's cumbersome.
- What's this?
- These are chicken feet.
- I see.
(Jun Myun picks without hesitation.)
What is this?
This is chicken intestine.
It's chicken intestine.
I'll try one.
(She gives it a go without hesitation.)
(Let's see.)
Is there no mango?
Get a lot of vegetables.
(Instead of a mango, there are many vegetable skewers.)
(Taking whichever...)
This looks good too. The skin.
(And however much they want)
This...
(He stacks meat on top of meat.)
It looks like pork belly.
This should be enough.
(The skewers will be ready soon.)
- There's ramyeon too.
- Let's have cup noodles too.
Okay.
Four, please.
I like the vibe here.
It's nice.
(Sitting there dressed nicely...)
- Cheers.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
- Cheers.
(Makes it feel like they're at a nice party.)
(She looks at the youngest members in front of her and grins.)
It looks like they got married today,
- and we're at the reception.
- Goodness.
- We're the only ones...
- My gosh.
- at the reception.
- You're right.
Like you only invited your close friends to the wedding.
- A small wedding.
- Yes.
- You two got married.
- It's a small wedding.
(A small skewer place in Bohol, the Philippines)
(We're getting married.)
(Bride, Kim Hye Yoon, Groom, Kim Jin Young)
- Let's take pictures.
- I'll take some.
It looks like a small wedding.
(They even take pictures.)
(They got married in Bohol.)
(A small wedding done at lightning speed)
- Jin Young, my son-in-law.
- Yes.
You're suddenly his mother-in-law?
Yes, Mother-in-law.
- Jin Young.
- Yes.
My youngest may not look it,
but she'll provide for you no problem.
But she's a poor housekeeper.
- I can't cook, sorry.
- She can't cook. So you...
So move into my house.
Does she have two moms now?
- My gosh.
- I don't know who's who.
Who is the real mom?
It's nice to eat out.
- I agree.
- Yes.
This doesn't even look low-end. I'm very happy with this place.
As we say that, we're eating cup noodles.
We're eating cup noodles.
- Can I have some ramyeon?
- Yes.
Jung Ah, your lips look scary.
With these lips...
I hope the lipstick doesn't come off.
Your lips are striking.
(Taking a mouthful of ramyeon with her red lips)
(Slurping)
Eating cup noodles in a suit...
makes me look like I have a sad story.
- Yes.
- Right?
"Did he get fired from work today?"
Oh, soju. Excuse me, a bottle of soju, please.
You said I'd get the promotion this time.
This is how it is, Manager Kim.
Goodness.
Manager Kim.
(Deeply engrossed)
- Senior Director Park.
- Yes, Executive Director.
(Intimidated)
- What are your roles?
- Who are you?
Just what are your roles?
It changes every second.
How funny.
(Meanwhile, smoke rises from the grill.)
It smells delicious.
(The skewers are being grilled nicely.)
That looks so good.
(Vegetable skewers which taste amazing when grilled...)
(and corn skewers drenched in butter)
(The starters are served first.)
(Miss Korea elegantly takes a bite first.)
(Taking another bite right away)
(Humming)
(Surprised)
- Is it seasoned?
- Yes, it's good.
Is it salty?
(Vegetable skewers are salty because they're seasoned with salt.)
(Hye Yoon takes a bite too.)
(Satisfied)
The bell pepper tastes good.
(She takes another bite of potato.)
She looks coy.
(Secure my lips at all costs.)
(She clears 1 skewer while securing her lips.)
It's...
The corn looks good too.
(I'll try it.)
(Angry eyebrows)
Gosh, corn.
(Buttered, savory corn)
(It's right down her alley.)
(For now, she's Corn Park, not Mango Park.)
(Everyone is enjoying the starter.)
(Spacing out alone)
Try this.
I'm waiting for the meat.
- I got tons of meat.
- Sure, eat meat.
(Staring with white eyes)
(The starters are over.)
(It's time for protein.)
(Filled with smoky scent)
(The meat is grilled nicely into brown color.)
(The meat party starts now.)
This is a birthday feast.
(He first tries chorizo, the sausage.)
(The frown lines tell the truth.)
It's good.
(Jun Myun goes for the chicken intestine first.)
(Satisfied)
It's tasty.
(Hye Yoon takes a bite of a skewer too.)
(Surprised)
(She seems to like it and immediately takes another bite.)
It's delicious.
(Dex finishes the skewer in a flash of light.)
Don't you like this kind of sauce?
- Yes, I really like this sauce.
- Sweet and salty.
Totally.
- The barbecue sauce?
- Yes.
(Sweet and salty barbecue sauce which Dex likes)
And the smoky flavor.
It's so good.
(The meat is very smoky.)
The sauce is good.
(Sauce Park acknowledges it too.)
(This time, he tries a pork skewer.)
(He finishes a skewer with two bites.)
Delicious.
(It's worth the wait, it seems.)
It's so good.
(Happy to see him enjoy)
- This.
- Try one.
(After seeing Dex eat it, Jung Ah tries the sausage too.)
It's fascinating.
- This...
- Gosh, my lips.
Pass me a tissue.
I need to manage my lips.
(Tapping)
(She never loses her dignity.)
(Red lips are Jung Ah's pride.)
(She coyly takes a bite as she protects her pride.)
(Hye Yoon elegantly takes a bite of pork belly too.)
(Humming)
Is it good?
(Whirling)
- Is it good?
- Yes, it's good.
(The better it tastes, the faster her hand moves.)
(At her strong reaction, Jung Ah takes a bite.)
(Jun Myun follows.)
It'll be perfect with rice.
(Satisfied)
The fat is very chewy.
(Eyes shining)
This is so delicious.
- It's just how you like it.
- Yes.
Eat up.
(She eats a mouthful of rice too.)
(Pork belly)
(A lot of pork belly)
This is the best and most familiar taste.
(They're drawn more to pork belly because it tastes familiar.)
(Dex quietly takes a bite of pork belly.)
(A mouthful of rice)
(A fierce bite)
(Obsessed with skewers)
(Open your mouth and let the meat enter.)
I'm starting to lose my sanity.
What should I order next?
Ma'am, one more rice.
(First, I'll refill the rice.)
I'll get those that were good.
(Standing up)
More.
(He starts to refill the meat.)
This was really good.
It's similar to tteokgalbi in Korea.
(Dex's favorite is the Philippines' chorizo.)
Sauce, a lot of sauce.
- A lot of sauce?
- Yes.
(The skewers are placed on the grill once again.)
(While waiting for the meat, he takes off his blazer.)
(He rolls up his sleeves and gets ready for Round 2.)
(While he's at it, the rice is refilled.)
Thank you.
It's meat.
(Cooked meat is refilled too.)
(The skewer goes into his mouth at once.)
(He stuffs his mouth with rice too.)
(Unmindful of his surroundings, he just eats the skewers.)
- Look. You need...
- What is that?
To clench your fist like this.
Why would that go up? That never happened to me.
- You make a fist like that?
- It sticks out, right?
(He keeps the routine of eating rice after eating a skewer.)
You must like this, Dex.
He likes this.
The sausage-like skewer.
(Dex is in love with chorizo.)
It's like Korean tteokgalbi.
- Yes.
- You're right.
- It tastes like tteokgalbi.
- Yes, it's like tteokgalbi.
(He finishes the last skewer.)
I'm done eating.
- I'm full.
- That was a good meal.
I'm so full.
- Are you done eating?
- Yes.
I'll make an announcement regarding tomorrow.
This season is a spin-off.
The title of the spin-off is...
Fresh Off the Sea in Calape.
- Calape.
- So tomorrow,
just like the title,
we'll go to Calape.
What is Calape?
- It's the name of a region.
- I see.
(A peaceful region in Bohol)
(Calape encompasses the ocean and the forest.)
What is Calape?
(We need to go to Calape and do something else?)
Calape?
(Looking it up)
A field, trees, or an orchard.
- It must be something like that.
- I think so.
Coconut maybe?
Are we going to have to harvest coconuts?
Or bananas?
(Or bananas?)
It must be mangoes.
Mangoes.
Jun Myun might eat it while working.
(Mango Park, join us.)
(Let's eat together.)
Coconut, pineapple, mango...
(It must be one of the tropical fruits.)
Durian.
I say it's mango.
(Salivating)
- It's a farm.
- Well,
whatever it is, you must include mangoes somehow.
Yes. It's a farm.
(What kind of labor will they do in Calape?)
(The four siblings come back from their dinner.)
- I'll wash quickly.
- Okay.
(As soon as he returns, he changes out of the party outfit.)
(Everyone is getting ready to rest.)
(She isn't sleeping.)
(She's listening to music.)
(The ukulele, which was hung on the wall, fell.)
(She doesn't care and goes back to listening to the music.)
- I can't be bothered to wash.
- Me too.
I don't want to wash.
How dare you act cute? Go and shower.
Why is it so bothersome to shower, Jung Ah?
Me too.
(Squirming to express her distaste in shower)
Shower after having fun, then.
- Are you done washing?
- Yes.
(Dex who finished washing and came to have fun)
I don't want to shower.
You haven't showered yet?
- Good job today.
- Good job.
Tomorrow is already the third day.
We're leaving after two nights.
It feels short.
(Their time in Bohol feels shorter for some reason.)
Goodness.
(Hye Yoon suddenly has a flower in her hair.)
(Staring)
Since she was 17, Hye Yoon...
- Started acting?
- Yes.
She's been acting for many years.
You've done it for a long time.
(Hye Yoon has been acting for 14 years already.)
You played student roles for a long time, right?
Yes, even after I became an adult.
Student 1, Student 2. She's played countless of those.
She really did a lot.
(Hye Yoon started with small roles.)
I really liked it when you went on "You Quiz on the Block."
I didn't know you were an unknown actress for so long.
Exactly. People think...
you suddenly appeared with "SKY Castle."
(Hye Yoon went through many years as an unknown actress.)
The process was so hard.
I got rejected because of my height...
for shootings and auditions.
Because of my height. "Her height is a bit..."
That happened so many times.
But even then,
when they mentioned my height, I just thought...
the role wasn't for me.
I'm sure there's someone out there who loves my height too.
That's what I thought.
I'm 159cm.
Compare your heights.
- You...
- I'm shorter than 160cm.
- Me too.
- You do look it.
"You do look it."
(Suddenly comparing heights in the middle of the night)
Your shoulders are at a similar level.
Goodness.
You're really about one centimeter taller.
- Really? Jun Myun is?
- Yes, around one centimeter.
- Jun Myun is taller.
- Is she 158cm?
Isn't Hye Yoon's short height her charm?
Yes. Tiptoeing to kiss the actor and so on.
That's so cute. You know what I mean, right?
- And...
- Tiptoeing like this.
It's 11pm now.
I should shower. I'm going to bed first.
- Okay.
- Good night.
(Jun Myun leaves, and the three remain in the living room.)
(A new guest arrives to fill Jun Myun's empty spot.)
(Watching them)
It's a cat.
How cute.
(She's drawn to it like magic.)
(Positioning herself right in front of the window)
(They just look at each other forlornly.)
Hye Yoon likes cats. She's a cat mom.
(I'm leaving, Korean cat mom.)
(I'm here this time.)
Gosh, they're having a neighborhood party.
You're right.
How many are there?
(Having a Bohol dog gathering)
Four.
(They get caught right away, so they quickly disperse.)
(After the animal guests leave, it's just the three of them again.)
How old were you when you got married?
Thirty-five.
I met him when I was 34.
How many years and above is long for dating someone?
Seven to eight years.
- Seven to eight years.
- Ten. Seven to eight years,
up to ten years.
Jin Young, you should do six months.
(Of dating and getting married)
She was just talking about people dating for 7 to 8 years.
- But that's way too short.
- Jin Young should do six months.
Have you ever cried because of a woman?
I don't think I have.
Really?
So you don't know this feeling?
- It hurts here.
- Your heart...
- Like your throat hurts.
- Why?
Because you scream?
- No.
- It's when you like someone...
so much that your heart hurts.
You don't know what an aching heart feels like? The pain?
- That's not a bad thing.
- No.
But you're sad.
But you don't always marry the person you feel that way about.
To me, marriage feels like...
the College Scholastic Ability Test.
I thought I'd never take the College Scholastic Ability Test.
It's such an important and huge occasion.
So I couldn't believe that...
it would come to me.
- And then...
- So marriage doesn't feel real.
No, I can't even imagine it.
Like "Would I ever experience that?"
(Marriage feels so far away that Hye Yoon can't even imagine it.)
I never thought I'd become a father.
(I never thought I'd get married, let alone become a father.)
But if it comes to me, I think I could do it.
- Marriage...
- Marriage isn't the answer.
(Marriage isn't the answer to life.)
But when you love someone,
that person makes the world seem beautiful.
And the way you perceive the world changes...
when you have children.
I'm sure it's the same for men too, but that's motherhood.
Marriage is something worth experiencing.
(Jung Ah gives them wholehearted advice.)
Getting married changes your life.
Why don't we wrap up for the night?
All right, let's go to sleep.
(They go to sleep so they're ready for tomorrow.)
(The sky slowly turns blue.)
(It's their third morning in Bohol.)
(As always, this morning in Bohol is full of energy.)
(People are busy starting their day.)
(What kind of day do the siblings have ahead of them?)
(Wake up!)
(Rooster crowing)
(Jung Ah woke up at the rooster's morning alarm.)
(She's the first one to get ready.)
(Stretching)
(After a quick stretch, )
(Jung Ah mops the floor.)
(Don't forget the kitchen.)
(Jung Ah's morning routine remains the same, even in Bohol.)
(Jun Myun wakes up.)
(The younger siblings are also up...)
(and quickly getting ready to leave.)
(The 1st thing on their schedule for Day 3 is...)
(labor.)
Today's outfit of the day.
(Hye Yoon's OOTD)
(Pink, cute, labor outfit of the day)
Hello.
Did you sleep well?
(Before they leave, she's unpacking a pair of shoes to wear today.)
(Looking around)
(Hye Yoon is looking for something.)
Did you perhaps... My shoes.
There's only one of them.
- You only have that one?
- What's going on?
(Kim Hye Yoon, the youngest, She's suddenly Cinderella.)
My shoe.
(Hye Yoon's shoe is actually...)
(Around 3am in the morning)
(The puppy came over to play again.)
(It walks up to the front door.)
(Rustling)
(The rustling sound seems suspicious.)
(The puppy had something in its mouth.)
(It's Hye Yoon's shoe.)
(It picks up the shoe in its mouth...)
(and runs off with it.)
I think we should bring our shoes inside.
A puppy took one of my shoes last night.
Goodness.
I went outside and there was only one of these.
So I was like, "I only have one of my shoes."
Mine is the only one this happened to.
(She lost her mind.)
This is so funny.
(There's never a dull moment at the siblings' house.)
- Good morning.
- You're up.
Yes.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Did you sleep well?
(He checks the mirror...)
(and puts something on his face.)
What are you putting on by yourself?
Sunscreen. Did you put it on?
Not yet. We have to.
- I have to too. I didn't, yet.
- Before we leave...
for work, we have to put sunscreen on.
- This is a sweat-proof sun stick.
- I see.
As we sweat, it blocks more UV rays.
- It's a specialized...
- Do you have only one?
- I have one more.
- Let's share this.
You can share that.
It's gentler than other sunscreens.
You can even apply it like this near your eyes.
(Dex applies it thoroughly behind his ears too.)
We're working today.
I keep layering it,
- You should.
- but it's not pilling at all.
Right.
- It feels soft and matte.
- Right, I like it.
Right.
(They thoroughly apply sunscreen to make sure they don't burn.)
- Are we ready to leave?
- Let's go.
(Now that they've taken care of their skin, they're off to work.)
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good morning, Mark.
- Good morning.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Good?
- Yes.
(Everyone buckles their seatbelts.)
- Jin Young, this is yours.
- This is Jin Young's.
- I'll just have a little.
- This is Mark's.
- This is Jin Young's.
- Mark.
- Thank you.
Jung Ah and Jun Myun made these.
- Sure. It's for later.
Let's go.
(Let's head to Calape, where they are working today.)
(They eat before they have to start working.)
This is so good.
It's so tasty.
(Jung Ah eats an end piece of her gimbap.)
This one looks better since you made it.
(Jung Ah's gimbap still looks pretty.)
Thank you for the food.
- Have some of this.
- No, I'll eat this one.
It looks full of protein.
Jung Ah wanted to make sure you get your protein.
Our Jin Young.
- Early in the morning.
- I made yours separately.
Thank you.
When did you have the time in the morning?
It's very good. This is so tasty.
I'm glad.
It's so tasty.
(Proud)
(It's tasty!)
Thank you. It's really good.
I'm glad.
I'll just have one more.
It's good.
(They eat during the drive.)
That would be great. Thank you.
- This is...
- Where are we?
It's... What was it?
- Hangola?
- Cal... What was it?
- Calam...
- Calapu!
- It's Calape.
Jung Ah.
Calape.
You're as bad as Dex.
- You're so bad with names.
- Calape.
- I'm just quiet.
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
- Maybe it's not Calape.
(We were definitely told it's Calape.)
- No, he's keeping it a secret.
- It's a secret.
- I see.
- Okay.
- I don't know.
- No, you know.
(We won't get fooled by your "I don't know" anymore!)
- Dex.
- Yes?
How to become cool like you?
- How to become cool?
- Yes.
- Confidence.
- Confidence?
- Yes.
- I see.
But I don't have confidence.
Why? You look so cool.
No.
I think you'll become famous.
You'll be known as Assigned Marker.
You look so good.
Dex.
(Mark)
- I love you.
- "I love you?"
Me too. I love you too. Thank you.
Thank you.
Have some water.
Have some water, Mark.
(Dex helps Mark drink water with love.)
Gosh. You're so sweet, Dex.
Mark confessed his love for me.
(Fresh Off the Sea in Calape, Loaded with Love)
(As they drive, loaded with love, )
(the view outside, which was full of buildings, )
(is now full of trees.)
I'm seeing lots of coconuts.
Coconuts here, coconuts there.
(There are coconuts everywhere.)
Are we headed to a coconut farm?
All I can see are coconuts.
- Really?
- There are coconuts everywhere.
(All they can see are coconuts.)
(Will they be picking coconuts for today's labor?)
I can't predict what we'll be doing.
(They can't predict today's labor.)
The road is getting bumpier.
It is. We're going up a winding mountain road.
(To makes matters worse, the road is getting rougher, )
Gosh, the road.
(and the car is bumping along.)
Gosh, this is rough. Gosh, my butt.
We're going deep into the mountains.
Right.
We're almost at the top of the mountain.
Yes, we're almost there.
Is that the sea?
- Gosh, that's amazing.
- It's so pretty.
(The car is high up in the mountains.)
I feel dizzy from all the winding.
I feel dizzy.
I feel like there's going to be something huge.
Me too.
We keep going in deeper.
(They drive for 20 more minutes...)
(before the car starts slowing down.)
- What?
- Are we here?
- This is it.
(The car reached its destination.)
- What?
- Why? What is it?
- Goodness.
- What's this?
It looks like a field. What is this?
(A field of sharp, pointed objects lay before them.)
Are these cacti?
Aren't these aloe plants?
- Over here.
- What are they?
What are they?
(The vast field is covered with unfamiliar, sharp-looking plants.)
(Sudden silence)
Are these aloe plants?
- Gosh, I never would have guessed.
- Aren't these aloe plants?
(They get out of the car in fear.)
What is this?
What could they be?
(What are the mysterious crops they will be shipping today?)
- Are these aloe plants?
- I think so.
Aloe plants.
(They carefully approach the plants.)
What are they?
Gosh.
The fact that there's a field like this on top of a mountain...
- Right, it's amazing.
- is amazing.
The view is beautiful.
(Behind the vast field...)
(lies the open sea.)
(The refreshing sensation clears their mind.)
(Between the exotic palm trees, )
(a majestic tropical canyon.)
(Something you usually only see in movies)
(A surreal landscape)
(What kind of work awaits them...)
(in such a beautiful place today?)
(Goodness!)
This is...
a large farm located in Calape.
If you look to the side,
you'll see Filipino pineapples.
They're so cute! I didn't know pineapples grow this way.
(Calape)
(The most naturally abundant area in Bohol)
(In particular, the mountainous region of Calape is...)
(a tropical fruit paradise on limestone soil.)
(Among them, pineapple is the most famous.)
So this is how pineapples are grown.
(The sharp plant that scared them turned out to be...)
That's amazing. I thought they grew in trees.
Your mission for today is...
to harvest everything you can from this Calape farm.
(Harvest everything you can from this Calape farm!)
This entire farm?
Gosh.
And how do we do that?
(Stunned)
(Actually, this field is...)
(a massive field of about 33,000m².)
(They must harvest everything here to earn a coin.)
We'll divide it into sections.
(And they need the coin to make changes in their schedule.)
Are we supposed to do a raid?
(They're all standing still, speechless.)
Everything here?
(Jung Ah gets ready to work right away.)
(Before they get to work)
(Is this your first time seeing a pineapple plant?)
(Let us introduce you to pineapples.)
(If you think they grow on trees like other fruits, )
(you're seriously mistaken.)
(Similar to rice or corn, )
(a pineapple is a herbaceous fruit that grows on the ground.)
(It goes through the process of blooming and withering, )
(eventually forming a single fruit.)
(In normal cases, only one fruit is produced per plant.)
(That's why pineapples are precious.)
(Filipino pineapples are especially sweet.)
(They account for 90 percent of pineapples imported into Korea.)
(That's how popular Filipino pineapples are.)
(Let's go harvest them, so they can be shipped overseas.)
This is great. I've been craving pineapples.
This is a pineapple.
And it's ready to be harvested.
You pick something like this and put it in the basket.
So don't pick something too small. Got it.
(Not ready to be harvested, ready to be harvested)
When you find the right one...
Okay.
Easy.
(Twist the fruit off with both hands.)
It's easy.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
(Simply pick the pineapples and collect them in a basket.)
Okay.
Like he said, only pick the ones that are big enough to harvest.
Do not pick ones that aren't ripe enough.
(Before she's done explaining, Jung Ah begins working.)
(We're supposed to pick everything here?)
(The mission awakened Leader Yum's dormant drive to act.)
(Her willingness to work is 100 percent.)
I have a question.
Can we eat the pineapples here without ripening them first?
They have to be ripened too? I see.
(Jun Myun suddenly lost her willingness to work.)
Let's get started.
So we can't pick the small ones.
Should we each take a row?
How should we do this?
Yes, let's do that.
- Hye Yoon.
- Yes?
Don't go diagonally. Go straight.
- Okay.
- Go straight.
(They each take a row and work facing the same direction.)
(Dex, the efficient worker, sets how the work will be done.)
(He picks one right away.)
(He's off to a fast start.)
(While Dex pulls ahead quickly...)
That hurt!
Gosh, that hurt!
They're so prickly.
(Hye Yoon is stuck at the entrance of the field.)
Goodness.
Gosh.
(Stumbling)
(And so is Jun Myun.)
I'm getting pricked through these pants.
- Right?
- Right? It hurts.
I'm already scraped up.
Gosh, it hurts.
(The pineapple leaves with sharp, hook-like edges...)
(are lush along the path between the fields.)
Please let me go through. Excuse me.
(Hye Yoon has become overly respectful toward the pineapples.)
(Gosh!)
(They're off to a rough start.)
(Goodness)
(Hard)
(Shouting)
(Panting)
(Exclaiming)
Let's see who wins. You or me.
This is big enough, right?
(The pineapples hurt Leader Yum's pride.)
(She's fighting back by grabbing them by their hair.)
(And she claims an immediate victory.)
(Leader Yum quickly fills her basket.)
No. It's too heavy to carry on my back.
(Not even 10 minutes in, her basket is already too heavy.)
(This time, )
(she picks two in a row.)
(Then she goes hunting for another pineapple right away.)
(Jung Ah finds one immediately.)
(Leader Yum is like the hyena of the pineapple field.)
(She picked three in a row!)
I should empty these out somewhere.
(She can't fit any more pineapples in her basket.)
Should I empty my basket somewhere?
(Grunting)
(Hyena Yum is the first one to fill her basket.)
Gosh, that sting!
(Meanwhile, Hye Yoon, who could barely walk around, )
I can't tell.
(has no clue which pineapples she can pick.)
I think this looks all right to pick.
(Or not?)
I'm too introverted to ask.
- How about this one?
- No.
- No?
Really?
I can't tell how big they should be.
(Confused)
These are all pineapples.
These ones too.
(But which ones can she pick?)
This one.
(Unable to watch any longer, a local worker steps in to help.)
- This one?
- Yes.
Okay.
(I see!)
They have to be about this big.
The length of my palm.
About this big.
(Thanks to the worker, she is getting an idea about the size.)
(She picks another one...)
(and immediately compares its size with her palm.)
(Taking it in)
(Thinking)
I think the hair has to be full too.
What do you think? Do you think it's full enough?
(The pineapple's hair?)
Does the hair have to be fuller?
The pineapples' hair.
(The pineapples' hair?)
The pineapples have to have a full head of hair,
and they have to be as big as my palm.
(A full head of hair and as big as Hye Yoon's palm)
Ones with a full head of hair.
(As Dr. Hye Eoon is reciting her research findings, )
(Jun Myun is working in the next row.)
I can't believe I'm harvesting pineapples.
(Jun Myun adjusted quickly and picked quite a lot.)
(She picks a pineapple.)
(She picks a 2nd pineapple.)
(She picks a 3rd pineapple.)
This is satisfying.
(Exclaiming)
(Unlike Jun Myun, who is pulling off the pineapples with satisfaction...)
The ones with a lot of hair.
They're around one handspan.
(Hye Yoon is still going over her research results.)
This one feels similar, doesn't it?
(After thorough research...)
The ones with a lot of hair.
(and comparison, )
(Dr. Hye Yoon finds only the perfect pineapples.)
(Along with precise handspan measurements, )
(she finds the ones with a lot of hair.)
The ones that are like this?
(This one looks nice as well.)
(She's finding the ones of the best quality.)
I think I can pick that one as well.
(She spots another perfect pineapple.)
I spotted a yellow pineapple!
If I pick this...
(Dr. Hye Yoon spots a gold pineapple.)
(Jun Myun, who was also next to her...)
- It's very yellow in color.
- Yes.
(She spots the gold pineapple.)
Yellow color.
- Yellow color?
- Yes.
- Good?
- Good.
This must be very ripe.
(The yellow pineapple looks incredibly sweet.)
Gosh, there are yellow ones.
- Very sweet?
- Yes.
(Gold pineapples taste great with any after-ripening needed.)
(Excited)
Pineapples are...
Philippine bananas.
(Dex was collecting the pineapples smoothly.)
(He collects a whole basket after Leader Yum.)
(Around 40 minutes have passed after the start of their work.)
(Jun Myun and Hye Yoon...)
(also fill a whole basket.)
(There are quite a lot of pineapples stacked.)
I expected us to get done with this quickly...
as there weren't a lot.
It isn't over yet.
(What are you saying?)
(Sighing)
(Today's mission: Collect everything on this field.)
(There are still a lot of pineapples left.)
(Area left to clear)
(They are around 50 percent done after 40 minutes.)
(To earn the coin, )
(they most move a lot more.)
(Dex rushes into the field without hesitation.)
(Picking easily)
(He grabs onto the leaves with great strength.)
(He removes the leaves in a tough manner.)
(The powerful worker of the siblings never disappoints.)
(The second basket gets filled quickly.)
(The pineapples get torn out helplessly by his hands.)
This is going to end quickly.
(His basket is quite full already.)
It's heavy.
(Jun Myun's basket is full as well.)
(The pineapple falls off as the basket is full.)
(Looking around)
(She quickly puts it back in before anyone spots her.)
(Get inside nicely.)
Gosh.
(She slams it to the ground this time.)
(Collecting 1 pineapple)
Gosh.
(Looking around)
(She puts it into the basket...)
(and twerks again.)
It's really tough...
to move the pineapples.
(Leader Yum has also filled up another basket.)
Aren't you doing this too quickly?
What? I must be quick.
(After pouring out one basketful, )
(she moves out to collect another basket.)
(Hyena Yum mode is on.)
(She charges forward as soon as she spots a pineapple.)
(She hunts down the pineapple right after spotting it.)
(She manages to hunt 3 in a flash.)
(Wherever Hyena Yum's...)
(feet and eyes head toward...)
(Snapping)
(The pineapples are wiped out.)
(Taking big steps)
(It's a horror movie from the pineapple's point of view.)
(Okay. I found another one.)
Okay.
(Shaking)
(The pineapple cries.)
That side is wiped out.
I think we're done after doing this much.
(They took down the pineapples down as a team.)
It's really over. They were annihilated.
- They were annihilated.
- We're done.
(The pineapple annihilation is done within 1 hour.)
(The owner comes to check the pineapples.)
I will check the pineapples to see if they are okay or not.
- Okay.
(Teofredo Asoy, Calape farm owner)
Okay.
(Checking the pineapples that were collected)
I think these two baskets are okay.
These ones together.
(Did the siblings collect the right pineapples well?)
(He checks the pineapples with great care.)
(How did they do?)
Okay.
It's okay. All of them.
It's okay.
(Relieved)
You did a good job with all of them.
- Good job!
- Thank you!
Also, this one. This one is nice.
Nice!
- Very okay.
Very good.
That's a nice pineapple.
- The yellow ones are very sweet.
- They're very sweet.
(Eyes fixed)
I don't think I've ever seen a pineapple like this.
Gosh.
These are the pineapples seen in cartoons.
(An unrealistic color seen in cartoons)
These pineapples taste really good.
I want to try some.
(She speaks the truth.)
Let's go down.
I'll prepare a snack for you.
(Food?)
- We will eat? Lunch? Okay.
- Yes.
(Smiling brightly)
Okay. Let's go.
Gosh, thank you!
(Is their collection mission a success?)
Let's take a picture.
- The weather is great.
- Sounds good.
(They head down with excited hearts.)
The weather is great today as well.
- Right.
- It's really nice.
Isn't Kim Dex the weather fairy?
Isn't it Hye Yoon? Isn't the great weather...
all thanks to her?
(Dex's sudden flirt attack)
I'll take that as a compliment.
(Hye Yoon feels shy about her older brother's compliment.)
Should I carry that?
- What?
- Should I carry that?
No. It's fine.
- I can...
- You should carry that much.
- You're capable of doing that.
- Of course.
(As they come down while acting silling...)
Gosh, it's beautiful here!
Look over there.
(Amazed)
- It's beautiful, isn't it?
- It is.
(The siblings arrive at the snack spot.)
It's beautiful.
(It's a beautiful view...)
(that feels different from the pineapple field.)
(Along with the gentle breeze, )
(the open hill feels refreshing.)
What's that?
Gosh, what is that?
They're bulls!
Are they water buffalo?
I think they're just regular bulls.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The animals feel at home...)
There are animals.
(and rest in this place in peace.)
Hi.
(At this quiet place, )
Let's sit like this.
(the siblings take a break.)
Gosh.
Gosh, it's a baby chicken!
It's so cute!
Gosh, the chickens here are huge.
Right.
(They have all fallen for the peaceful vibes.)
(Amazed)
Gosh!
Gosh, there are dogs.
What?
(Following)
What is all that?
Why are they carrying so much?
(Hands full of food)
(The generosity of the people of the Philippines is extraordinary.)
This is for you.
Thank you!
(The generosity of a large farm owner)
(Snack time is on another level in the Philippines.)
- What is this? Coconut?
- Coconut.
(Freshly-picked wild coconuts...)
(of the Philippines)
(The siblings worked hard to collect them.)
- Gosh, this is amazing.
- Gosh!
(Philippine pineapples)
(A hearty snack for the siblings who have worked hard)
(Approaching)
(Enjoy the food.)
Would you like to drink the coconut?
I want some.
Coconut water.
- Coconut juice.
I want some.
Gosh, it's a big knife!
(The terrifying giant knife appears.)
(The machete is an essential item for working in the Philippines.)
(Hitting)
(Amazed)
(The shell of the coconut is harder than it looks.)
It must be hard to open.
(Amazed)
(The hard coconut shell gets sliced with the machete.)
(After a few hard hits...)
There it is!
(The coconut water finally appears.)
Gosh, these are natural coconuts.
(Fresh coconuts that were caught within 1 hour)
Awesome! Thank you so much!
- Straw.
- Right.
Poke it in.
(A straw is poked in after removing the shell.)
I love coconut water.
Try some, Jung Ah.
Try some.
- You're a tough guy.
- Use the straw.
(What will the coconut lover think?)
How is it, Jung Ah?
(Slurping)
- It's so good.
- It's so good?
Right. It's the bland taste that I like.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
(Right.)
(This is it.)
It's a bit different from the coconut I tried before.
I think the coconut flavor is stronger with this one.
The one I tried was bland, but this one is sweet.
(In paradise)
It will be really good when chilled.
After keeping it in the fridge.
Then it would taste like sikhye.
(With a strong coconut flavor, it tastes mildly sweet and nutty.)
(Humming in approval)
We have to slice it in half first.
(Freshly picked golden pineapples are next.)
- Pineapple.
- The pineapple looks good.
(Freshly picked golden pineapples are next.)
Gosh, this is real.
(Gasping)
(Gulping down her saliva)
It's naturally grown.
Here you go.
(Full...)
(of anticipation)
(A bright yellow look that makes your mouth water)
(How will it taste?)
(Humming in satisfaction)
(An intense and shocking level of sweetness)
It's really good.
It's very good and very sweet.
- Delicious?
- Yes.
- Gosh, it's delicious.
- It's good.
It's my first time eating yellow pineapple, and it's good.
Its sweetness is much more intense than its sourness.
(Sweetness on a different level that he's never tasted before)
It isn't sweet in an unpleasant way.
- Right.
(Jung Ah who doesn't like sweets keeps eating it.)
(Sweetness that never gets old)
(The fragrant scent also attracts bees.)
It's so sweet.
- It's very good.
- It's really good.
- Seriously.
- Right?
(As they worked hard to pick them themselves, )
(the pineapples taste even better.)
(Satisfied)
By the way...
(Squeezing out the juice)
It's really delicious.
(It's really delicious.)
What's wrong?
(Laughing)
What is it, Jung Ah?
Seriously, it's so good.
(Exclaiming)
(Slurping)
(As expected, Filipino pineapples are on a different level.)
(Mango Park is followed by Pineapple Park.)
What's wrong?
(Giggling)
What?
You also had so many mangoes yesterday.
(Feeling guilty)
What's the matter with you?
At a pineapple farm, we should...
- fully enjoy the pineapples.
- Of course.
(Slurping)
Enjoy them to your heart's content, right?
Stop sucking on that.
Wipe your hands.
Wipe them as you eat.
"Wipe them as you eat?"
(Laughing)
(Dripping)
Gosh, don't make me feel...
- You can't eat freely?
- conscious about eating.
Here you go, Jin Young.
Why are you giving me your used napkin?
Don't give him a used napkin. Give him a new one.
What's the matter with Jun Myun?
(I'm fine.)
It's her used napkin.
Why is he smiling so much?
Hey, puppy.
(Another viewer dog that was watching Jun Myun eat)
Why are you sitting there?
- He wants something.
- What's your name?
Is your name Pine?
Why is it Pine?
Because Jun Myun is eating it.
(Her head is filled with thoughts about pineapples.)
What is it? Do you want to say something?
I think he wants something.
I don't know what dogs can eat.
It's seasoned.
(What should I do?)
What... This is covered with seasoning.
(She's scared to give him something bad.)
Your friend is leaving. Is that okay?
Where's your friend?
Your friend is over there.
(Staying close to Hye Yoon despite his friend leaving)
He's getting closer to you.
Right? He's way too close.
(Hye Yoon)
- I was very...
- What?
What's this? I feel flustered.
(Is the dog in love with Hye Yoon?)
Look at this.
- Oh, my.
- Gosh.
It definitely looks like he has something to say.
(Laughing)
He's gentle. He doesn't jump on you.
He's very gentle.
(Only in love with Hye Yoon)
It's so delicious.
Do you want some?
This isn't edible.
(In no time, they become lovey-dovey.)
(Pleased)
This place looks so peaceful.
If only there was some wind...
(Enjoying a break as sweet as the pineapples after work)
That'd be wonderful.
It's very peaceful.
Thankfully, it's not very humid.
The sun is strong today.
Yes, the sun is very strong.
(Suddenly, the staff becomes busy as if they're preparing something.)
(A mysterious vehicle comes into the field.)
Gosh, the weather is really...
(Someone rushes out of the car.)
(Grunting)
(He takes out the luggage in a hurry as soon as he gets out.)
(Changing into a rash guard in this heat?)
(Who is this person with an unusual behavior?)
(Lee Si Eon?)
(3 hours ago at Bohol International Airport)
(Wary about his surroundings, one brown bee arrives secretly.)
Gosh, the weather is...
In order to see Dex...
(Si Eon came to see Dex.)
(Si Eon is Dex's closest friend who's older than him.)
I came here for Dex.
I would like to surprise Dex.
I could stand still in the field like a scarecrow.
Or I can pretend to be a local...
and say, "What kind of work is this?
(Just thinking about it makes him happy.)
(And the sacrificial lamb has no idea about it.)
(What does the fate hold for them?)
(We'll move on to harvesting the next crop.)
- What?
Is there more?
(Were pineapples not the end?)
(It's not over until it's over.)
(The labor continues.)
(Mission: Harvest everything on the Calape field.)
(What's the next crop that will turn this peaceful place into inferno?)
(It's very hard to handle one of these.)
(Is the labor too much for the siblings?)
(Its difficulty level is high.)
(It's beyond whatever you imagine.)
(Just then, someone shows up in front of the siblings.)
Who is it?
(I'm the surprise guest.)
(Get ready. We'll treat you properly like a guest.)
(The siblings' over-the-top restaurant opens for Si Eon.)
(Is it too much?)
(A pot of stir-fried spicy pork by Generous Jung Ah)
(Dex also prepares a heap of barbecue.)
(And plenty of other dishes)
(A sumptuous feast to welcome the guest)
(He eats...)
(endlessly.)
(The guest is fully satisfied.)
(What are we doing tomorrow?)
(Jungle...)
(expedition)
(Exclaiming)
(A suspicious jungle?)
(Gosh, I'm scared.)
(The siblings are gripped by fear.)
(Gasping)
(What happened to the four siblings in the jungle?)
Dramaday.me