=Betrayed Love=
=Episode 14=
Miss Guan.
How is it going with our partner?
When can we resume work?
Although the plagiarism issue
has been clarified,
our partner has disposed of
the fabric inventory it held.
Thus, it can't go into production
anytime soon.
After we got married,
we didn't play chess once, right?
You have never won before.
How can you win now?
The clothes have not been delivered yet.
How will you cope with it?
If it's hard for you to say it,
I'll talk to the board of directors.
The longest day is bound to end.
I'm also a member of the company.
I also want to help.
You tried to threaten me
claiming I am a plagiarist.
You want to replace me?
I won't deny it.
In the first place, you married me
just to obtain the group, didn't you?
Didn't you get married to me
in order to get the group a loyal dog?
Since I was a university intern,
I have been doing
all the hard work of the group.
Don't you think
I have fulfilled my duty as a loyal dog?
If your feelings in the past are fake,
you can be said
to be a qualified loyal dog.
Now I want to inform you of the divorce,
and you need to give up everything
you have in the company.
Without me,
the company
would not have gone this far.
Now I can't be dismissed
just because you say so.
You're really different now.
But don't forget, Shen Zhuo,
Guan Group Company
will always belong to the Guans.
Even if the group might be torn apart,
I will fight you on this to the finish.
But you don't want to see this happen,
do you?
By the way,
you, Xu Jing and me,
we three can actually live together.
The three of us live together?
I couldn't imagine you to say that.
People are social animals after all.
I think the three of us
can live happily together.
You are crazy!
I am sickened
by the fact that I ever loved you.
People always need to be responsible
for their own choices,
don't they?
Checkmate.
Now you are like
this chess game.
It's a hopeless case.
There will be ample time ahead.
I am showing you the greatest kindness
by asking you to leave our marriage
with nothing.
If you don't agree,
see you on the battlefield.
I'll sleep at Xu Jing's house tonight.
I thought we would succeed
after the conclusion of this conference.
Just wait. She can't clean up this mess.
The company will be mine
sooner or later.
Is the company that important to you?
Even without this company,
we can still be happy together.
I just want to
invite some friends
and have a simple wedding on the beach.
A wedding is just a formality.
It's not important.
Our love for each other
is the most important.
I am telling you now
that this formality
is very important to me
because I want to stand beside you
as your lawful wife
and get blessings from others.
Is it that difficult?
Okay, okay, I got it.
Miss Guan,
we found a new fabric factory.
When can the start-up reserve fund
of the factory be approved?
Then the project emergency fund
will be put into use.
Miss Guan,
we need to pay a huge penal sum
for breach of contract.
How can we rake together the money
the factory needs?
Now there is not enough circulating fund
in our company's account.
What's the matter this time?
I came to tell you
what Shen Zhuo said really makes sense.
It seems that
the three of us can live together.
You know clearly Shen Zhuo
is having an affair with me
behind your back.
Why haven't you divorced him yet?
Because this will make you a mistress
all your life.
Your mother and father
will be a mistress's parents.
Your children will be illegitimate.
You can't stand beside Shen Zhuo
as his lawful wife until you die.
You and your family
will be criticized as long as you live.