=Betrayed Love=
=Episode 18=
Look,
you are the only son of your Guan family
and you possess your mother's shares.
Why does Guan Xin guard against you
as if you were a thief?
Even if
the amount of my shares is small,
I can't handle them
without getting her signature.
What am I in her eyes?
She treats me as a beggar.
She said she would provide for me.
You have never thought of
taking the helm of the company?
There is no man without ambition
in this world.
But you know
that I used to be in the background
and I was inconspicuous.
I was happy
that I was not an eyesore to Guan Xin.
I used to loaf around,
but it is all in the past.
On the day of selling shares,
I realized that Guan Xin went too far.
Thus, now I want
to take control of Guan Group Company.
After it's done,
you will be the group's only Chairman.
Mr. Tang, how about
I raise the price a little more
and you transfer some shares to me?
(Is there any trouble?)
No, no trouble at all.
(Glad to hear that.)
(From now on, I won't have a hand in)
(the management of the company.)
(After all, you are a family.)
(Please discuss with Guan Xin.)
It seems that he will not participate
as long as we do not harm his interests.
After the success of the event,
your annual share of profits
will increase by 20%.
In other words,
now together,
we are holding over half of the shares,
so we can ensure
we have decision-making power.
What are you here for?
After thinking it over, I still believe
under the current circumstances,
you are no longer suitable
for this position.
Don't worry,
no one is more suitable than me.
Yes, I admit you are capable,
but do you know how much compensation
we will pay
to all the business partners?
You need not worry about this.
Various rumors are making a huge impact
in our company these days.
It all happened after you came back.
You have no right to say that.
Things have turned out so bad.
You still won't step down?
Moreover,
you can't solve the funding problem.
Well, Mr. Shen, are you jumping the gun?
Why can't you
resign yourself to being a housewife?
Why just the two of you?
Where are the others?
They made excuses and didn't come.
(Guan Group Company)
How is the emergency loan
application going?
Because the ready-made clothing cycle
has been affected,
several banks
that have business relations with us
have rejected our loan application.
They also urged us
to pay our existing debts.
I have never expected
that Guan Group Company would stop here.
There is another way
to solve the urgent problem.
There is a foreign hedge fund company
that will grant us emergency loans
with your shares as collateral.
That's enough
to get the whole group back on track.
Use shares as collateral?
This is too risky.
Are we gonna helplessly
watch the entire group be dragged down?
(Guan Group Company)
Well,
Mr. Shen, why did the Board of Directors
convene suddenly?
To get out of the current predicament,
our group must adjust
its internal administrative structure.
At today's board meeting,
a new Chairman will be elected
through a new vote.
Mr. Shen, if I remember correctly,
you have been suspended from office,
haven't you?
Mr. Wang, you won't stand by
with folded arms, right?
Let's see the voting results first.
Mr. Wang, what do you mean by that?
What right do you have
to re-elect the chairman?
Do you have enough votes?
Everybody, Mr. Wang, Mr. Li and I
unanimously decided to hold
today's meeting.
Without the Guan family members present,
what's the point of
holding the board meeting?
Mr. Shen,
you are carrying this joke too far.
He wanted to join hands with me
to control Guan Group Company.
He was really naive.
(I asked you for money,
but that didn't mean anything.)
(How can I help an outsider?)
(See you later.)
Okay, I see.
Guan Peilin has no interest in
running the company.
He only wants to see the company
belong to our Guan family.
But if you want to take it from us,
he will take sides with our Guan family.
He's my elder brother. Just stop it.
Wang,
at that time,
we shouldn't have believed
Shen Zhuo's lies.
It's no use complaining now.
If we are in the wrong team,
we may be kicked out of
the Guan Group Company this time.
Right. Miss Guan needs us now.
Let's side with her.
It is the wisest decision.
Then we won't take sides with Shen Zhuo?
Of course not!
Let's go somewhere else.
I'll buy you a drink.
Let's go.
Will you leave me too?
I won't.
I will be right here with you.
It's Guan Xin's fault.
I will revenge you on her.
For your sake,
all the hard work
is worth it.
Our love for each other
is the most important.
Why are you so serious?
Whether you revenge me or not,
what difference will it make?
Nothing can come back.
Why do you think so?
You are the only thing I have now.
If I lose you too,
what should I do?
I...