=Her Disguise=
(Adapted from Shuiyue Xianling's novel, "Her Disguise")
=Episode 1=
Not only did you come to me,
but you also tried to steal my things.
Isn't this too much?
Second Young Master Lu.
Master Qin made you
the leader of the merchant world,
but you kept the military map
he asked you to find.
(Lu Haoran, Second Young Master Lu)
Master Qin is angry.
If you don't hand over the map,
I will let you
die before a woman.
Is this the gift Master Qin said
he would send me?
I have no choice
but to return the gift then.
Ms. Lin. This way, please.
Young Master is busy.
Please sit here and take a break.
Second Young Master likes tranquility
and is sleeping upstairs.
You shouldn't disturb him.
(Lin Mange)
Qin just won't quit.
One is not enough. He sent two.
I'll send both of you to your death.
I'm a family doctor.
I do acupuncture.
Acupuncture?
You do look like it.
Don't move.
You are stronger
than the previous woman.
Unfortunately,
the end is still the same.
Stop.
Guanghe.
When treating a woman,
you should be gentle,
Haoran.
Guanghe.
(Lu Guanghe, Young Master Lu)
Guanghe,
you know her?
Who is she?
My personal doctor,
Lin Mange.
There's a problem with this woman.
I'll find you another one.
Besides,
she is my fiancee.
From today onward,
call her sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law?
Guanghe, you just called me your...
Mange, I didn't do that out of anxiety.
I called you here
not only to ask you to become my doctor.
Promise me. Consider the possibility
between us, all right?
All right.
Your leg is healing faster
than expected.
You won't be needing a cane soon.
Mange,
Haoran has been managing
the family business.
He is used to being willful.
Don't take things to heart.
Later,
send Qin's gift back to him.
Don't let anyone find out.
No problem.
Second Young Master,
Qin is really evil.
We should be more careful.
Also,
we don't know
who that woman was.
Who is she?
Investigate her.
Second Young Master.
Can we talk about this?
Give me some help.
Help me out.
Fine. This counts.
(Yuning, Lu Family's Cousin)
Ms. Yuning, you're back.
For you.
Thank you.
Haoran?
Why are you here?
I...
What is this?
This is...
That is my baggage that just arrived.
Send it to my room.
No problem.
Who are you?
I am...
Thank you, Second Young Master.
What? Did I hurt you?
Who are you? You are so clumsy.
I'm sure it hurts a lot.
It's fine.
You need to disinfect your wound.
I have medicine in my room.
Let me bring it for you.
I have antiseptic here.
Can you give me your hand,
Second Young Master?
You can trick my brother with your act,
but it's still lacking here.
Sister-in-law.
Forget it if you don't need it.
I won't leak your matters
to anyone, Second Young Master.
I just want to stay in the Lu family
to fulfill my wish.
Wait.
You did so much
just to enter the Lu family.
I'm sure you are here for me.
This orchid is well-drawn.
Second Young Master drew it with a servant.
Unfortunately, the servant
had impure intentions
and was already gone.
You entered with a weapon.
You called yourself a doctor?
I do acupuncture.
I just treated your dislocated shoulder.
Second Young Master,
don't be angry for no reason
and don't be so bloodthirsty.
Stop.
I accidentally disturbed Second Young Master.
Lin Mange is my fiancee.
From today onward,
call her sister-in-law.
You will be the madam
of the Lu family in the future.
This is your room.
(Lanlan.)
(I'm here, Lanlan.)
(I will avenge you.)
(I'm sure you enter the Lu family)
(for me.)
(I am here for you,)
(Lu Haoran.)
♪Bye, weakness♪
♪Missed opportunities sink
into the ocean with the setting sun♪
♪Butterfly leaves the land of taboo♪
♪The rotten mud rots away the malice♪
♪The fallen naively wipes away to color♪
♪The soul wakes up
in the dangerous forest♪
♪Crushing the mundane
and everchanging mask step by step♪
♪The crow stops whispering in the fog♪
♪Black rose blooms
at the end of the abyss♪
♪It is a beautiful scar on my wound♪
♪Overcoming hardships♪
♪A strong armor
wards off criticisms and disputes♪
♪My brilliant life♪
♪No matter who says anything♪
♪I won't be hurt anymore♪
♪If kindness goes away,
I'd rather be sharp♪