Because I trust you.
You trust him?
That's worse than sleeping together.
Welcome home.
Sorry about earlier.
No, I should be the one apologizing.
Don't.
I just...
got too jealous, that's all.
But it's ultimately my fault.
You're the only one I choose, always.
Togo...
It's the end of my journey (in Italian).
What?
Wh-Wh— Togo?
You are my destiny (in Italian).
W-Wait a second!
I can't wait any longer.
Togo, stop it!
Come on, that tickles!
Togo, well...
Leave while I'm taking a shower.
The plan was a success.
Is that so?
Then we shall both get what we desire.
I'm truly grateful you were my accomplice.
This will save both my father and his company.
Thank you so much.
My sister and her husband finally became an established couple,
only to make an enemy of a formidable foe.
Now, their love for each other is being tested as we speak.
[Kissing the Ring Finger: Episode 8]
Excuse me...
Could we talk...
I'm home!
Oh, Ayaka.
What's up?
I'm staying for a few days.
In that case, welcome home.
Welcome home to you, too, Negi!
You are getting bigger.
Togo's on a business trip and won't be home for a while.
- Are you hungry?
- I am.
Will leftovers do?
Of course!
[Haneda's Fishcakes]
[Kamiyama Kento]
[I want you to tell me the truth.]
- Then in true Haneda fishcake style...
- Eat heartily.
Okay.
Nothing beats breakfast with family!
You're too hyper for early in the morning.
Go home already.
- Sorry?
- Stay here as long as you want.
Sora's the only good kid here.
With another coming, it'll be cramped.
I hope Eco is born soon.
- "Eco"?
- Eco-friendly. The motto of our time.
[Eco]
That didn't start recently, though.
You've got it written down and everything.
- Have you chosen a name yet?
- No, still thinking.
I like the name "Honoka" better.
How about "Kuuko," written with the characters "air" and "port"?
She'd become Haneda Airport (an airport in Tokyo).
Right, no wonder it rolled off the tongue.
Hello? Yes, thank you.
- Answer your calls later. Right?
- Yes.
Since it's the Reiwa Era, how about just "Rei"?
(T/N: Japan's current era name, 2019-present)
I don't feel the love in that way of name-choosing.
- I like Eco!
- Honoka.
We'll come back to this over dinner.
Seriously, go back already, Sister.
Say what?
- You spent the night out?
- Be quiet! They'll hear you!
Well, of course he'd be angry.
Yes, I know.
How did Togo-san take that?
He kicked me out, so here I am for now.
What do you mean by "for now"?
Look, can you handle today while being low-spirited?
Hopefully...
Orihime and Hikoboshi reunite once a year.
(T/N: Tanabata folklore: "The Cowherd and the Weaver Girl")
Now, allow me to introduce them to the stage.
She's so cute!
[I love Ayaka-chan!]
King!
(T/N: Hikoboshi is a cowherd)
♫ You're everything I'll ever need because it's your love I want to keep ♫
♫ I'm never gonna say goodbye ♫
Orihime, I've come for you.
(T/N: Orihime is the weaver girl)
I've missed you.
♫ You're everything I'll ever need because it's your love I want to keep ♫
♫ I'm never gonna say goodbye ♫
Do either of you have a wish this year?
(T/N: Making wishes is a Tanabata festival tradition)
Oh, he's cute!
Let's see...
If I had to say, my wife's wish is my own.
And you, Ayaka-san?
My wish...
is to always be in love with Togo.
What a beautiful display of love!
If anyone here feels destiny tying them together,
please consider La Blanche for your wedding needs.
Stand back please.
[Tell me "I won't choose anyone!"]
Togo, wait!
I have business at headquarters.
[Chairman's Office]
Pardon me.
Good evening.
I assume you've met Sakuraba-kun.
Yes, back in Hakone.
I'm honored that you remember.
Of course.
What brings Sakuraba-san here?
I've decided to leave La Blanche to him.
Guide me well, Sir.
Sakuraba-kun, I'm counting on you.
If you'll excuse me, then.
What is the meaning of this?
Although our contributions aren't drastic, La Blanche is well on the rise.
So why a transfer at this time?
Are you suggesting I quit La Blanche?
Exactly.
I decided to transfer Togo back to headquarters.
Is that true?
Yes.
I'll have him begin studying up to be my successor.
Does this mean you recognize Togo's efforts?
Something like that.
I've also decided he'll be succeeded by Sakuraba Arata-kun from our Hakone branch.
Is that so?
Then I'll be off.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Did you hear the rumor?
- Seriously?
- Yes.
When I passed the President's room earlier...
Did I miss something?
Apparently, there have been some changes in leadership.
- What?
- That's our reaction.
- Don't you know anything, Queen?
- True.
He's here.
- Sasaki-san.
- Yes?
I'd like to introduce Sakuraba Arata-san, the new managing director.
- Who's that good-looking guy?
- The manager of our Hakone branch.
- He gives Hakone vibes.
- Real Hakone vibes.
- He smells like trees.
- Totally!
Does he?
No, it's this pole.
Could I have all your attention, please?
With my transfer to headquarters cemented, it's been decided I'll step down as president of La Blanche.
King, you're joking.
Going forward, you'll answer to Sakuraba Arata-san,
who previously worked as manager of our Hakone branch.
My name is Sakuraba Arata.
I have been working as manager of La Blanche's Hakone branch for two years.
I'm pleased to meet you all.
- Pleased to make your acquaintance, Sir.
[President's Office]
What's going on, Queen? You must've known!
- Sorry, I—
- I can't stop thinking about the details!
Sorry, we'll talk later!
Why are you running?
What is it?
Nitta Holdings is hosting a dinner tomorrow.
You'll be attending as my wife.
Was this transfer arranged far in advance?
No, it was sudden. Is that all?
Sorry, I'm short on time.
[Tenerita]
Are you suggesting I quit La Blanche?
You'll return to headquarters
and begin work as my successor to Nitta Holdings immediately.
With due respect, Sir, my contract to help La Blanche was for a year.
Your promotional work with Ayaka-san revitalized it plenty.
Great work.
In fact, One-Loan Holdings is offering to purchase the place.
- You'd sell La Blanche?
- It's favorable.
Almost too favorable, in fact.
I am against this buy-out.
- As President of La Blanche—
- Togo.
You are my successor.
Taking into account his achievements at La Blanche,
my chosen successor will begin learning the business at headquarters in the coming year.
Once again, allow me to introduce you all.
Welcome, Nitta Togo.
Thank you all for your precious time today.
My name is Nitta Togo. It's an honor to be here.
Nitta Holdings currently faces a great challenge.
Service industries must be attuned to their changing customers.
Because of social media, information gets around faster.
Therefore, the amount of information available to customers has changed dramatically.
He's still plenty inexperienced. Please aid him as you can.
- Of course.
- Thank you both.
Likewise.
Truly, a dependable ally.
Togo-san's mother was born into a distinguished family
as their one and only daughter.
[Asagiri]
Your posture.
- Her parents raised her strictly.
- Left first, remember?
Marrying for love was beyond unforgivable.
Nevertheless, she fell in love with a man.
And the two had a child.
However, she could not abandon her family name.
Leaving her child to the father,
she determined to live solely for the Asagiri family.
Thirty years later, she is greeted by none other than...
I believe we haven't met, Ma'am.
My name is Sakuraba Arata.
It's an honor to finally see you in person.
Shizuka, he is the new president of La Blanche.
Sakuraba-kun, I expect great things from you.
Yes, Sir. If you'll excuse me then.
Yes Sir. If you'll excuse me then.
He's a great young man, isn't he?
Yes.
Smile, Togo-san!
Yes. Got it! Okay.
- You two really are inseparable!
- We are.
My wife loves you two and would love to meet over a meal...
- Of course. Ayaka?
- With pleasure.
She'll love that! You'd better keep your word.
It's a promise, indeed.
Just like our collaboration, yes?
As expected of the King, clever as ever.
Then I'll be seeing you.
Togo...
Kamiyama-kun, I know something is up.
That's why you're lying, right?
[Investigation Report]
[Subject: Kamiyama Kento]
Yes?
Togo, open up! Let's play!
So how many days has it been since Ayaka-chan left?
- How did you...?
- Of course, I can tell.
Why did she leave anyway?
Because I told her to.
What? But you want her back, right?
Then just say so. I would right away, though.
- Don't you have a shred of pride?
- No, not at all.
I love Sayo-chan so much.
You're a strong guy, Hachi.
I know.
Why do we even call you "Hachi"?
Seriously? You're the one who gave me the nickname.
You said I was like Hachiko, the loyal dog.
(T/N: Waited for his owner for 9 years following his death)
- I'm a nasty guy.
- You sure are,
especially on a surface level.
Shut up.
But you are such a great guy under all that.
That's why I want you to be happy.
Hey, shall I cook something?
Can you?
- Forget it. Let's go to the store.
- I'm staying.
Let's choose what you want together!
- It'll be fun.
- Aren't you the loyal dog? Go by yourself.
Come on already.
Why together?
I'm home.
Ayaka, could we talk?
What is it?
Isn't there something you're not telling us?
No.
You sent us 10 million yen after the wedding, isn't that right?
Yeah.
Where did that money come from?
It was money the Nitta family set aside for our ceremony.
Was that really all it was?
Did you think we wouldn't notice?
You married for the money, didn't you?
Did you do that for us, for family?
Of course not.
I did it for my own sake.
I wanted money, so I entered a year-long contract marriage.
You know, I've always admired luxury. Wearing fancy clothes,
living nicely, lavish lunches, and all that.
Basically, to be the envy of all.
I wanted out of this lifestyle,
to experience what wealth was like, you know?
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
If anything, I'm sorry for lying.
The contract only lasts a year.
We'll make sure to act the part until it's over.
So don't worry about me, okay?
Sis...
[Kids' room]
They found out.
You should've told them the truth—that it was for us.
This might've been for the better, though.
Here you are.
Thank you.
I'm sorry for visiting so early.
No worries.
What did you need? Apologies for the rush. I have work soon.
I've heard everything from Ayaka.
As I understand, this was all a contractual marriage.
What a disappointment.
Seeing you with Italian hot pot,
I truly believed you loved Ayaka from the bottom of your heart.
I'm terribly sorry I've deceived you, Sir.
I want to believe it wasn't all a lie.
Togo-san... don't you feel anything for my daughter?
This is our new seasonal dress.
The sparkling flowers along the chest-piece
and glittery skirt is recommended for garden ceremonies.
Togo-san, don't you feel anything for my daughter?
[President's Office]
- Please finish the documents I shared with you.
- Yes, Sir.
Nitta-san!
Is the project I left you with going well?
- Yes, thankfully.
- That's good to hear.
How has work been?
Though the role of "President" still feels unfamiliar,
Hachi-san and the wonderful staff have helped me along.
Many reliable staff members have stayed. Please treat them well.
Of course.
Perhaps I also feel uneasy having my own room.
How so?
I come from a large family; there was always a room shortage.
A large family... sounds lively.
What about your family, Nitta-san?
I'm acquainted with your father, but not so much with your mother.
My apologies; that's prying.
No, it's fine.
I'm sure to continue fumbling about, so I eagerly await your guidance.
Of course. Good luck.
Hachi-san, when should we get drinks?
- I'll check your schedule.
- Thank you.
How about you join us, Nitta-san?
I'd love to.
Sounds great.
You are "my" loyal dog; remember that.
[Kamiyama Precisions]
I've decided to close up shop.
Sorry, Son. I know you were trying.
But I'll be fine. Go back to America.
I promise, I'll be fine.
Because... I trust you.
I know for a fact that something is up.
Ayaka.
Come, sit.
Yes?
Your feelings have come across loud and clear.
You're such a terrible liar. You always have been.
Ayaka, leave the nest.
We've already returned the 10 million to you.
Ayaka, your mother and I will manage.
We want you to go build your own family.
Don't use your life for your parents, your siblings, or anyone.
Live for yourself.
I expect you out of the house by tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
You should sit.
The doctor told me I need the exercise.
You're a tough lady.
Kin-chan...
was I too harsh on her?
I'm terribly sorry I've deceived you, Sir.
I want to believe it wasn't all a lie.
Don't you feel anything for my daughter?
Nothing at all?
Not at first, no.
However...
my feelings now are true.
Ayaka...
is my one and only.
It'll work out.
Togo-san will make it work.
Togo, I brought us a drink to celebrate.
Where is Ayaka-san? Still at work?
I bet you came because you knew she wasn't here.
Goodness, what makes you say that?
You are always good at telling lies.
A terrible assumption, indeed.
Nevertheless, I'm quite worried that she's out so late.
There's no need. She's currently visiting family.
Then you must be hungry for dinner.
Shall I cook?
No, thank you.
Did you and Ayaka-san have a little argument?
You would know that better than anyone.
After all, you had Kamiyama-san approach Ayaka in the first place.
That sort of stunt won't break us apart.
Whatever are you talking about?
Please end this farce.
I've tried to live up to your expectations,
always, without fail.
Your cruelty had me in its clutches.
What are you saying?
I am your mother.
You loved my rice omelets best of all.
It's so good!
You are not my mother.
♫ I was crying ♫
♫ And recalled your face in order not to lose it ♫
♫ Before it turns into a mental bruise ♫
♫ I want to hug you tightly ♫
[Prenuptual Agreement]
We want you to go build your own family.
♫ Something like forgetting is also important ♫
♫ Your spoken lines that don't suit you at all ♫
♫ The colorful thoughts overflow ♫
♫ Nobody gets to see them ♫
♫ I couldn't breathe ♫
♫ When the time stopped ♫
♫ I just kept looking into these eyes ♫
♫ The reason for the falling tears ♫
♫ You showed to no one ♫
♫ Pretending to be tough ♫
♫ I want to protect all of this ♫
♫ The glittering bright heart tumbles through the air ♫
♫ The flickering, floating heart becomes the wind ♫
H-Hello?
Hey. It's been a while.
It has.
Togo... we need to talk about Kamiyama-kun...
There's no need.
What?
It's over.
Anyway, we have filming to do. Get here quickly.
- What?
- We'll start filming our morning routine at 7:00 a.m.
At 7:00 a.m.?
Don't forget Negi.
Give me prior notice!
Riku, wake up.
Get ready. We're filming today.
I see.
Stop, I'm bare-faced!
- Stop!
- You look cute, though.
Hey.
- No running.
- You're too close!
Terrible! This is seriously disgusting!
No problem! At least they're getting along.
Right...
It's disgusting but... relieving, I guess.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
I'm begging you to stop that.
It's eco-friendly.
That watered-down liquid isn't tea. Go check your tongue.
It's perfectly functional.
- Is not.
- Is too.
Are you sure they won't get a divorce?
Honestly? Not too sure.
Enough.
I'll do it instead. Have a break.
Thanks! I've been waiting for you to say so!
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Welcome home.
Thanks.
- One bag per cup.
- What?
- That's such a waste!
- No, it's not.
I apologize if I kept you waiting.
I'm honored.
Part of me assumed you'd ignore my invitation.
I've wanted to meet you...
Mother.
Why won't you say a word?
You...
You are no son of mine.
Why...
won't you see me for who I am?
Togo is my only son.
I don't know what you're conspiring,
but please don't involve yourself with the Nittas any longer.
The other day...
Father passed away.
Before passing, he told me the truth.
I always assumed you had abandoned me.
But I had it all wrong, didn't I?
You left my side...
to protect me.
Please raise Arata for us.
I want this child to lead a life of freedom, of happiness.
I spent my days with Father and his relatives.
My life has indeed been happy.
Still...
I've always wanted to meet you, Mother.
Father loved you dearly.
He was constantly worried about your happiness.
So he left his will with me.
- Mother—
- Stop calling me "Mother," I beg you.
I cannot become your mother, not anymore.
Do not concern yourself with my affairs.
Thanks for coming.
I'm sorry about how I acted the other day.
I know an apology isn't enough.
But those lies aren't easy to write off.
I'm really, really sorry for tricking you.
You had your reasons, though, didn't you?
The truth is, my father's factory has been on the verge of shutting down.
With that blackmail against me,
I was given money in exchange for breaking you two up.
By whom?
Nitta-san's mother.
Why would she do that?
I don't know.
But I promise that's the whole truth.
She'll most likely keep at it until you two are apart.
Mother.
♫ Although we are the worst couple ♫
Kamiyama-kun is a precious friend of mine.
Why did you use him?
I'm well aware I'm a disproportionate bride.
But please spare the people around me.
- Even Togo-san—
- You know nothing at all.
Take care to treasure your family and do them no harm.
What do you mean by that?
♫ I rush to you as if by chance ♫
Is everyone okay?
What? Yeah?
Nothing's gone wrong?
No. Why?
Never mind, then it's fine.
Sorry about that.
♫ Hey, together, one, two step ♫
♫ I'm dedicated to you, dear my lover ♫
In the moment, my sister remained blissfully ignorant.
[Haneda's Fishcakes]
♫ Let's hope for the best  ♫
♫ And live in the blissful here and now ♫
♫ I will protect only you from now on, by all means ♫
♫ I vow, in sickness and in health ♫
♫ I'll dedicate my love to you ♫
She had no idea an uncontrollable storm...
was already at her doorstep.
I'm home.
You're late.
Oh, Negi!
Hey.
What about me?
♫ You see? Here we go again; we are invulnerable ♫
♫ Impregnable, even when facing an enemy ♫
♫ We'll challenge them head-on ♫
- Oh?
- What?
Nothing.
♫ If I'm with you, it will never ever end ♫
- What?
- Yeah?
Expecting something else?
Excuse me? No.
Welcome home.
She could only assume their love was eternal.
[Preview]
I think I'm happier than I've ever been.
Thanks for marrying me.
We are very sorry.
No matter what you might do, we won't give in.
Are you sure about that?
Weren't you supposed to make my sister happy?
- I'm just tired of everything.
- You said you wanted us to be family.
You're irritating me!