SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Toki
"The Sparkle in Your Eye"
(Episode 8)
I just wanted to make a good film,
but ended up kissing up to those big shots.
This is Su Yi's celebration
not your networking event!
I will leave with him soon.
You may enjoy and celebrate.
So,
you are still leaving me?
Yi Wei, you are drunk.
Let's talk when you sober up.
I'm scared that I won't
get the chance when I do.
I'm scared
that when I wake up,
you'll just treat me like a friend.
I'm scared that you
will be a coworker only.
We won't go back to how things were… right?
Yi Wei,
we've already changed.
Is it because I changed?
I don't know.
But I know
even if we get back together now,
we may
break up again for some reason one day.
I can't do that all over again.
So what is the reason?
Is it because
I'm not someone
who deserves your love?
No.
Because I'm too weak?
Because I don't even care
what crap I'm filming now?
No.
Because I try to please people like a dog
and I can't even do that right?
No.
Because I know everything
you said was right,
but I never listen?
No.
Because I never cared how you felt?
Yi Wei, please, stop.
Stop it.
You know what's really pathetic?
The most pathetic thing
is that I don't even know how to change.
I even never thought about it.
I...
I thought I was doing fine.
But I was wrong.
I was so wrong.
We're not who we were.
We can't stay the same.
But I want to be better.
I know we can't go back.
But I want to be someone
you'd be willing to accept me again.
Give me one more chance, okay?
Idiot.
Why are you dressed like that?
If I'm not dressed like this
and we get photographed,
we're done for.
Come on, no one noticed us.
Hey.
Did you just roll your eyes at me?
How did you know?
Your eye rolls are loud.
Even on set I can hear them.
Good ears.
Blind people have good hearing.
You're not blind.
Alright, I get it.
Hurry up.
Wait, stop.
Peace sign.
Both hands.
Put one down!
♫ Starlit reflections ♫
♫ Hiding secret ♫
Are you sweating?
How's it?
Let me see.
It should be good.
♫ This must be destiny ♫
♫ Unraveling the mystery ♫
Give it to me.
Look,
look at this photo.
No one will recognize you.
Hey,
put it on.
They will see you.
Take one more with me.
What?
Okay.
This way.
Ha-ha!
Cute.
You pulled my mouth crooked.
This one's nice.
And this one!
This one is also good.
Why are they all so good?
Here, look at this one!
Since they are good,
should we put them up?
Sure, where?
Let me see.
♫ Starlit reflections ♫
How about your forehead?
♫ Hiding secret ♫
Your forehead's perfect for it.
I think that's perfect.
♫ This must be destiny ♫
Right?
Wait, ticklish!
♫ Unraveling the mystery ♫
Break time.
Fine.
(You may come to the company
to sign the contract this weekend.)
Official signing's set.
This weekend.
So soon?
Yeah.
Mr. Fang wants to hold a press conference.
You'll have to go too.
You are... upset?
No.
I'm happy for you.
If it's what you want,
Meeting you on that set
was the best part.
Who's this?
Pei Jia! Pei Jia!
Look over here!
Pei Jia.
Pei Jia, look at the camera.
Hi everyone,
welcome.
Thank you for supporting Pei Jia.
But today's spotlight
is Su Yi.
Su Yi, say hi to everyone.
Hi, I'm Su Yi.
I'm still new
to acting.
I hope to learn from Pei Jia
and improve myself
to have wonderful works, thanks.
Learning from just me may not be enough.
Ha-ha.
Okay,
starting today,
Su Yi is officially part of our company.
He'll have lots of chances
to learn from everyone.
Please keep him in mind.
And don't forget to check out
our upcoming film
starring both Pei Jia and Su Yi!
Okay, now it's time for open questions!
Mr. Fang,
any expectations for this film?
None.
But I think they'll
connect with the audience.
As long as we break even, we're good.
Pei Jia,
this is your first BL series, right?
How does it feel?
Well,
I think it's like any love story.
It's all about sincere emotions.
There's no real difference.
What's new for you
in this performance?
As for that,
I guess meeting Su Yi,
such a sweet newcomer,
really helped me...
Well,
He really helped me dive deeper
into the role.
Su Yi,
what was it like working with Pei Jia?
Well, I feel great.
Mr. Pei is a very nice senior to me.
He helps me a lot on set,
very supportive.
Did you ever
run into Pei Jia's rumored partners?
No, I haven't heard anything like that.
Excuse me,
I'd like to ask you two
if portraying a couple
sparked any real emotions between you?
Any sparks between you two offscreen?
Well, in fact, on set,
we become the characters
and feel what they feel.
That's our job.
But for offscreen, we are good friends.
Yeah, we get along
with each other offscreen.
Pei Jia! Jia!
Pei Jia! Pei Jia!
Have a good rest!
So cute!
Pei Jia, have a good rest!
Pei Jia!
Everyone,
this way please.
Pei Jia's event is over.
What? Tired?
Sort of.
Already?
What about the party later?
Will that be worse?
You didn't attend one before?
No.
It's fine.
It's just chatting with
rich people over drinks.
Stick close to me,
talk less,
smile more when you
have no topic to chat about.
Got it?
Got it.
It's like conveyor belt sushi.
Want anything?
Nope.
They are here.
Congrats
on the signing!
Thank you, Director!
Work hard.
I will.
Su Yi, drink less.
Don't wander off alone, got it?
Don't worry, Bai, I'll be fine.
I'll watch him.
Okay, enjoy yourselves then.
See you later.
Okay.
Come on, have one.
Good.
It tastes nice.
Pei Jia, my old friend!
Come on.
Hello, hello.
It's been a while.
Long time no see.
Nice to meet you.
This is Ms. Li from the platform.
Oh!
Hello, Ms. Li.
This is Su Yi.
Working on any new projects?
Yes, planning a new one.
Good.
Any role for him?
Thanks.
He's been a fan of martial arts.
I read many novels about it before.
Mr. Fang,
not drinking with them?
Looking forward to your new film.
Mr. Li,
do give Su Yi a chance.
I think you two are promising.
It's my honor.
My honor.
Thanks, thanks.
See you later.
My pleasure.
Jia, Mr. Fang needs to see you.
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
Mr. Fang is meeting an investor.
That investor wants to meet you.
Just go.
I'll go with Su Yi then.
It's not proper...
How come?
Su Yi is the star tonight.
But Mr. Fang wants to meet you alone.
I can't help it.
Just go.
I'll be fine.
Remember,
don't drink too much.
If anything happens,
find Su Bai and Yi Wei.
Alright,
just go.
Come on.
Thanks.
Please have a seat here.
Mr. Fang is coming.
Nice to see you.
You are talented. Hope
to work together soon.
Sure,
no problem.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you for your support.
Amazing and talented.
Thank you.
Let's work together.
I have strong empathy,
so I can get into most roles easily.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Friends of Pei Jia are mine too.
Yeah...
Okay.
No problem.
Sure, no problem.
Thank you so much.
Okay.
Yes, totally understand.
You have to wait a bit longer.
Mr. Fang is still busy.
Pei Jia?
Where are you taking me?
Pei Jia...