SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Subbers: Toki
"The Sparkle in Your Eye"
(Episode 7)
Su Yi,
don't go to his agency.
I will think about it.
(Pei Jia, I've thought about it. It's a good
chance for me to enter Mr. Fang's agency.
(Don't...)
(Mr. Fang is holding a party
for me. Are you coming?)
(One year ago)
You're an actor now.
Work's different from before.
So, how's it going? Getting used to it?
I am, Mr. Fang.
I mean, I used to do this anyway.
Really?
Relax.
Didn't you say you're used to it now?
Well, I still need more practice.
Get more used to it.
You're with my company now.
If you have any requests for projects,
or want support,
just come to me.
Got it?
I still have a lot of fans supporting me.
If I need anything, I'll let you know.
Fans?
What can fans help you?
When you have to quit
from show business,
it's exactly them who berated you.
If not for me,
you'd probably still be
passed out drunk in some club.
The only reason I signed with your company
was because one fan told me
that he'll always be right there for me.
Well.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
Aren't we grabbing
drinks later with Su Yi?
I thought I'd swing by
so we could go together.
That's not on the way.
How is it not?
Same starting point,
same destination.
Still not on the way.
Weird, huh?
Where's Su Yi anyway?
Su Yi!
He's working.
It's our family affair, not your concern.
Didn't he sign a contract?
Why hasn't he quit the bar job?
When did you find out he signed?
Don't look at me like that.
I just found out too.
See?
- (- Director Yi, I've decided to go to Mr. Fang's.
- (Are you sure? - Yeah, I've thought it over.)
Still so hostile toward Fang Runzhi?
You know what kind of person he is.
What?
You mean...
the rumor he sleeps with his actors?
But that's consensual, right?
What if it's not?
If someone was really forced,
wouldn't they have spoken up by now?
Fang Runzhi asked you to change the script,
cut scenes, swap actors,
and you didn't want that either.
Did you expose him?
Where are you going?
To drink with Su Yi.
This early?
Come on, cheers!
Mr. Fang told me
that he'd contact
Schwarzenegger,
The Rock...
Hey, Su Yi.
Someone's here for you, go say hi.
I'm kind of lucky...
You know him?
I didn't know
you were a fan.
I'm not.
When you were the cleaner,
he was here almost every night
for a week.
Really?
He's weird.
He always ordered one drink,
and sat there till close.
He looked familiar,
so I searched him online.
What's his name again?
Jia?
Pei Jia.
Exactly!
Pei Jia!
By the way,
I've told the boss
I can't help with guests tonight.
It's fine.
Come on.
It's a big day.
Stop working.
Here,
let's celebrate for Su Yi's
new agency!
Cheers.
Thank you.
Su Yi, you invited
us to drink.
You have to drink with us.
Well...
I called you here because I wanted
to say thanks for everything
you've done for me.
This one's for you all.
Cheers.
Alright,
we are all close.
No need to be formal.
Come on.
We're here to have fun.
Just enjoy yourself. Drink up!
Bai.
Su Yi,
now that you've signed,
you are officially in the industry.
As someone who spotted your talent,
let me give you some advice.
In this industry, there
are things you can't say,
and people you can't offend.
There's too much of that.
Like me,
I just wanted to make a good film,
but ended up kissing up to those big shots.
Right?
I wanted to be like your brother,
giving up the scripts
he has wrote for years.
This is Su Yi's celebration
not your networking event!
Alright.
Take your drama home.
Don't kill the mood.
Come on,
let's drink.
Congrats.
Thanks.
♫ By the sea with fireworks,
you're standing near ♫
♫ Shifting warm and cold
through the seasons clear ♫
♫ Like emotions pulling
us both far and near ♫
♫ You're so gentle, chasing away my fear ♫
Well.
Nice alcohol.
♫ You're so gentle, chasing away my fear ♫
♫ I pray to rewrite the ending we know ♫
Well,
I will leave with him soon.
♫ To guard you, trust my fists can
take the blow ♫ I will leave with him soon.
♫ To guard you, trust my fists can take
the blow ♫ You may enjoy and celebrate.
♫ To guard you, trust my
fists can take the blow ♫
♫ Don't cry in a world where I can't go ♫
Okay.
Here.
♫ Don't cry in a world where I can't go ♫
Drink!
♫ Watching the starlit
reflections with you ♫
♫ Hiding secret feelings in silence ♫
♫ In that fleeting moment of eye contact ♫
♫ My smile betrayed what I truly felt ♫
♫ This must be destiny ♫
♫ Unraveling the mystery
with my own hands ♫
♫ Certain that I love you ♫
♫ If you feel the same too ♫
Didn't you say you'd come for a drink?
Why are you just staring at me?
Need help with something?
Can you mop?
Nope, the cleaning lady does.
Wash dishes?
I don't cook, I order in.
Then what can you do?
Fine.
Just drink.
That suits you more.
Want anything else?
A drink made by you.
Anything's fine.
Why aren't you drinking it?
Cough...
Who even drinks absinthe?
You're drinking it too fast.
You know what?
Van Gogh drank too much absinthe
and hallucinated.
Then he cut off his own ear.
What?
Absinthe causes hallucinations.
You don't know?
So what I'm seeing now is a hallucination?
Yeah.
Ha-ha.
I'm kidding.
So you made this just to mess with me?
Not really.
Why absinthe then?
It looks cool.
Does it have a name?
Not yet.
I haven't decided its name yet.
Why don't you
name it?
Me?
Yeah.
If I quit acting and go back
to being a bartender again,
I can tell the customers
that this drink was made by Pei Jia,
the super star.
Maybe you'll be more
famous than me by then.
Don't say that.
Hmm…
Let's call it…
Hallucination.
Hallucination?
That's it?
Yeah, imagine,
one day,
a customer walks in,
snaps his fingers and says,
“Give me a Hallucination.”
Cool, right?
Right now, you feel like a hallucination.
Now I do think
Hallucination sounds perfect.
Quite direct.
Life feels less and less real lately.
Less real than absinthe.
Don't sign with the company,
Su Yi.
Why not?
Relax.
Didn't you say you're used to this?
No reason at all?
Pei Jia even taught his partner how to act.
It's a good chance.
Not everyone gets that.
Listen.
Fine.
Go ahead.
Not bad.
Fine,
let me guess.
You look down upon me.
You think I'm a clingy sidekick.
Now that I've joined
your company,
you're annoyed.
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm Pei Jia.
I just think he's a newbie.
I'm just playing along.
You think I'd fall for him?
Right?
I don't look down on you.
No,
you don't,
you pity me.
You feel guilty,
trying to bribe me.
I don't pity you.
And I'm not bribing you.
Then why say all this?
Because I like you.
I want to be good to you.
So that's the best excuse
you could come up with?
Why do you think it's an excuse?
From the note to this confession,
what's even real?
Why are you walking alone?
Long time no see.
They'll always be right there for me.
But I've been trying to tell you
that even if I lie to myself
that I simply like you,
but from now on,
I love you.
They'll always be right there for me.
Jia, I brought you the chips you want.
And sweets.
Yes?
She didn't call you.
It's fine.
I'll sign one for you.
If you can invite anyone to dinner,
who'll be your pick?
Finish.
You.
They'll always be right there for me.
Do I know you?
This is our first time meeting.
We really never met each other before?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said all that.
So, you don't like me?
That's not it.
I'm telling you not to sign
because of Fang Runzhi.
Mr. Fang?
I'm afraid he may…
What?
Please.
Don't sign.
But I still want to.
Why?
Because it's my fastest shot at fame.
You're young,
there'll be more chances.
Remember that game?
The ten questions?
I said I had a secret
hunch about the future.
You have a secret
hunch about the future?
Yes.
I've had bad eyesight since I was a kid.
You don't wear glasses.
I wear contacts
for the camera.
Hear me out.
Before high school,
I thought it was just nearsightedness.
But during the big exam,
I looked up
from my math paper
and everything spun.
Afterward,
my left eye went blurry.
I thought maybe
it just got worse.
Then the right one did too.
My eyes felt a bit off.
Your eyes?
Yeah, just a bit dry.
Did you go to the hospital?
I just got glasses.
But even during the college entrance exam,
I couldn't see anything clearly,
even with them.
Sometimes I felt sick and wanted to vomit.
Stress can do that.
It's normal.
How about now?
I went to the hospital.
They sent me to oncology.
CT showed a tumor.
Here.
You dropped something.
The doctor said
the tumor's too close to the optic nerve.
It's very risky.
There's a 50% chance
I'll go blind.
No way.
Yi, your admission letter's here!
Everyone's waiting!
Tell them I'm sorry.
Sorry? For what? You did great!
Where are you?
Sorry, Mom.
Tell me,
what's it like to be blind?
You won't be.
They say
being blind
is like closing your eyes.
Like this.
But you won't go blind.
You won't!
It's like closing your eyes.
You can't see anything,
but you can still sense a bit of light.
I just hope
I get that much.
I told you, you won't go blind.
What are you doing, Su Yi?
Careful!
But I'm scared.
Pei Jia.
I'm not scared of dying.
But I'm scared
of the slow loss.
I may lose my vision.
If the tumor grows,
I may lose hearing,
mobility,
until
everything I love is gone.
Then I die.
It's still too soon to bring this up.
No,
not at all.
Do you know why I agreed to Su Bai to act?
Because I wanted people to see me.
Even if I go blind,
I want to be remembered.
I see you.
I already do.
I want to sign.
I want the world to see me.
Do you really enjoy acting?
Yes. I want everyone to look at me.
As long as they see me.
Because it may be the only chance
for me to act in a film.
Well done!
Cut!
Happy wrap!
Thank you all!
Okay,
I won't stop you then.
You have to catch me then.
I will.
I'll make sure the whole world sees you.