I'm not sure if I can get the first one, but I'll try to get the second one.
I'll try to get the third one, but I'll try to get the third one.
I'll try to get the third one.
Will there be any news about him?
The second wife is the most suspicious.
She found the clue of the thief in the room.
So crazy.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you to get the news.
Granny, do you know that you're not going to give a word to the haunted building?
If you know the clues, you'll...
I'll...
You can do whatever you want.
Sir, I have a guest.
The news you want is here.
You're not dead.
You're the guilty one, the Fourth Princess.
You're blaming me for the fact that you're the one who found the thief?
If I didn't give you the news, would you know that he's here?
Would you know that he's here?
Come with me.
Why should I come with you?
Princess, the whole city is in danger.
You might be in danger at any time.
Only the Prince can protect you.
You want to kill me, right?
You're the only one who can take me.
Damn it.
THE AVENGER
Bi Qiu!
Brother, wait!
Hello!
Follow me!
Theена!
Brothers!
By the edge of the sea,
I'm waiting for you
Yixing
I'm here to be a good girl
I'm here to be with you
I'm here to leave you a memory
I'm here to take you back to the past
I'm waiting for you
Yixing
I'm here to give you a deep love
I'm here to be with you
I'm not going to wait for you
Yixing
I'm here to give you a deep love
Yanyang
I'm here to be with you
I'm not going to wait for you
Yanyang
I'm here to give you a deep love
Are you hurt?
What did you just call me?
Yanyang
Do you remember everything?
I remember the life of the band five years ago
You told me your name was Yanyang
You left me without any responsibility
And you saved me
You took me to the band's fortune
But you joined the band four years ago
And you took many career under the band's control
I promised you
I would marry you back
Enough
I don't want to hear you say this
Why did you want to leave me?
I also want to know why
I used to be so heartless
Yuesuren took me to the family
How could I go to the band...
You are still lying to me
Yuesuang
Yiju Mountain
So it's not a long time
But before the war
All the men, children and elders were killed
The band's women
Were caught and killed
They were the worst slaves
They were killed every day
Five years later
I was in the city every day
I was in charge
It was me
It was me who brought you to the band
It was all because of me
It was me who made the band to be so hard
I just couldn't stop
Why do you lie to me?
Why?
You tell me
Yanyang
Tell me why?
I am sorry
Yanyang
Sorry
You ask me why
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Yuezuo.
I believe I didn't do it.
But why did I do it, Tongmei?
I really can't believe it.
You said you can't believe it.
Your Highness, Your Highness.
I finally found you.
I'll take you to see something.
Your Highness.
Don't follow me.
Cindy Longwell,
please don't follow me.
I have followed선 these few years.
from the Yue Clan.
After these things,
we are змuted in a negative nature.
The estimate of the Mu Qins
deviats from the choice of the Yueなく剖剤陰性
Yun Yang
I suspect there's a trigger in this.
I'm not afraid of you.
May the moon and moon
Always leave me alone
Love aаксимite
Leave us frozen
Abing another
Sri Aksiposti
All Vicious
Blindloop
The أيha
How to Bod Constantly
Through their precious interests
App floating
The freedom
The altitudeargrooms
in a calculated dream
dat me