I'm going to use the same technique as the other one.
This technique is perfect.
I think it's gonna be better for today's experiment
because it has more details in it.
The second method is to get the second method.
So, definitely make an experiment
which you are going to level with.
Actually, I'm unconscious.
Please simply don't get up yet.
Be quiet.
It's lunch time.
I'll come clean.
Brother!
Yu shuffle.
Zhao He%.
I gave this to you.
Today,
you dare to step forward again
and blame me for being ruthless.
Yun Ya,
Xiao Zhi is my brother.
I can't just watch him die.
Brother Hao,
leave now.
You will die.
Please let him go, okay?
Please kill me.
Don't kill my brother, okay?
Brother Hao!
Brother Hao,
leave now!
Brother Hao, leave now!
Don't care about me!
Don't!
Brother Hao!
Brother Hao, I beg you!
Leave now!
You are a traitor!
Do you know what they look like
when I killed your family?
They are pitiful.
You are dead!
They are helpless.
But I am not even blind!
I am not blind!
I will kill them all!
Kill them all!
Xiao Zhi!
You should all die!
You are dead!
I will never give up!
Xiao Zhi!
Brother Hao!
I love you the most.
I will protect you.
You have protected me.
Now,
I finally protect you.
Now, I am not.
Xiao Zhi!
Xiao Zhi.
Xiao Zhi
Xiao Zhi, wake up!
Xiao Zhi!
Xiao Zhi.
Wake up.
Xiao Zhi!
Wake up, Xiao Zhi!
Xiao Zhi.
Xiao Cheng,
I didn't protect you well.
I didn't teach you well.
I really did it.
Brother, this wood is so similar to you.
This is the gift from you.
Then I'll let it stay with you and keep it with you.
Just like you've been by your side all this time,
okay?
Thank you, uncle.
Xiao Cheng,
I'll keep it safe
and never let you get hurt again.
Lord Yan will have to rest for worse.
Who would ever want to carry off this段?
When the celular with the stone in our hands
will rfire,
how bright we shine in thisregard!
Yesterday,
the Lord passed into theます and thar has come back.
And the worldawan dreames.
Until the end.
Today,
the daughter of the greater clan
',
wants a light of Camp fire
I will show you my glory.
Tell me.
How are you going to punish me?
I love you.
Why are you like this?
You look so strange.
You turned me into this.
You locked me in the room.
You made me see her for the last time.
We are sisters.
Do you feel so bad for me?
I don't understand.
We have been through so much suffering.
And she
is the one who tortured us
to the point of catching Taibushu.
Why did you help her?
Because I am willing to do everything for her.
I will watch over you
from the moment you came to the King's Mansion.
I will tell her everything.
And I will make the needle
that killed Zhao Zhe.
Every time,
every time,
I saved her.
Every time, I saved her.
Why did I do this to her?
Why?
I was not with her when she died.
Yuan Zhi.
Think about it.
She killed the people in the Moon Tribe.
She killed so many innocent people.
She didn't deserve you.
She knew it!
She took the person who was in the wrong
as my face.
She killed the person I wanted to kill.
That person tortured me.
He didn't deserve my father.
What do you mean?
Stop!
See if your mother knows.
Get out of here!
I don't have money.
No money?
You're a loser!
Father, stop gambling.
We don't have money anymore.
You're a loser!
How dare you blame your father for gambling?
You're a loser just like your mother!
That's all?
Tell you what.
This money is not enough.
After three days,
I can't get the money to pay the gambling debt.
I will sell you to the brothel.
Do you know that?
Get out!
You're a loser!
You don't have money
after three days.
You don't want to live anymore.
I can figure out a way
to make more money.
No.
I have a girl who doesn't know how to make money.
If I can't pay the money,
I will give you her.
I thank him.
I thank him for saving me from the brothel.
Now you understand.
I'm different from you.
You're the daughter of the bandit on the high court.
And I'm just the one who was killed.
Half of the body is dead.
I can't live like this.
I've been a big boy.
I'm a big boy.
I've been used to living in the dark and the rain.
He doesn't belong to me.
He's nothing to me.
Only Zhao Zhe
makes me feel like someone is protecting me.
I'm willing to be hurt by him
and be his little rabbit.
Don't be obsessed with him.
He doesn't love me.
He doesn't love you at all.
He loves me!
I love him too!
I love him.
You don't understand at all.
Yun Chi.
Listen to me.
A person who really loves you
won't hurt you
or use you.
He won't let you be a dead man.
Actually,
the person who really pulled you out of the garden
wasn't him at all.
But you.
You can live better.
I really don't want to see you
do this again.
Yun Yao.
I've never felt
I was wrong.
Love has no wrongs.
He can see
everything I did.
Because he's hurt.
Full of regrets.
Attention.
Why don't
he leave us with you?
Hope.
Don't touch me.
I can't help to do this.
For you,
you're the reason I did him.
The Breeze Seeker
But you don't make it, vilum.
You just ...
I will introduce you and it's up to me.
That's right.
Can you?
I will.
You are a receptors.
It will be there.
You mustınıt you.
It seem to be attracted.
I will let you know my future.
You need to show it,
to have a better family.
Don't you dare to give her up!
Have a look at the coin cup.
Go gets her name.
This death is harsh and tough.
Perhaps we'll have chance,
yet it's a kind sword.
Lies are sharp enough to pierce lovers.
Don't fall for my love.
The night is different.
You dream too much.
That you whom I firmly believe in.
I'm not afraid of you.
I'm afraid of you.
There are many diseases can't be explained byções.
You ona in my dream.
I walked hundreds of thousands of miles.
Following your connector.
I 적 in hundreds of thousands of miles.
Look for your тобern.
I walked hundreds of thousands of miles.
pass through darkness.
When did we have toene vous attaque!
In memories, too, in my whole existence.