Gongxi
Why are you here at this hour?
Uncle Dong, it's so late.
Where are you heading?
We're missing one for mahjong.
I need to go help out quickly.
I heard about it.
That was a beautiful win.
It's time for that Qin Wuyao kid
to get a reality check inside.
This time,
we really owe it to Uncle Dong.
Save the thanks for later.
I'm in a hurry.
You planned all of this,
didn't you?
Long time no see.
Do you still remember me?
Uncle Qin
Gongxi,
you won.
Qin Wuyao, he...
No,
it's not your concern.
He made mistakes,
so he must face the consequences.
Uncle Qin,
you're not here to talk about this, right?
I know what you're thinking—
to protect Beimen Street.
But is your life now
really what you want?
You think you're sacrificing your life
to protect the community.
But maybe
someone planted that idea in you.
Gongxi,
sometimes a piece on the board
doesn't know who it's playing for.
I just want to run a small teahouse
in my family home.
You had Zhao Zhao find me
and persuade me to compete.
Then you gave up your spot to me.
I always thought it was all by chance,
but it wasn't.
Yaode Group wants Beimen Street.
Cangwu isn't even a match.
You couldn't step in yourself,
so you wanted me to help you
deal with Yaode.
Or do you
want to hand Beimen Street to Qin Wuyao?
Qin Wuyao never wanted Beimen Street.
It was Qin Defeng.
Are you scared?
He warned me.
Tell me.
You gave me your spot
just to use me against Qin Defeng.
And I
am just a piece in your game.
Why are you laughing?
Most of your analysis is correct.
But the part that's wrong—
Xiao Yun
Uncle Dong
Go wait for me downstairs.
Yes.
Back then,
the three of us started a business together.
Your father led the way.
Qin Defeng was hardworking,
and clever too.
But his ambition
would never
let him stay beneath anyone.
Why can't we do it?
No means no.
Opening a gambling house in Beimen Street—
are you trying to ruin everyone?
But—
No buts.
As long as I'm here,
it's impossible.
Fine.
This is as far as you go.
Defeng
But what does this have to do
with Beimen Street?
Back then,
he was driven out by the people
of Beimen Street.
They kicked him out.
After all,
who could tolerate someone
who harmed them?
That's why Qin Defeng hates Beimen Street.
So that's
the reason he's obsessed with Beimen Street.
You're a smart person.
You got one thing wrong earlier.
I never saw you as just a piece.
I want you to be a player.
I'm not interested in these grudges.
I just want an ordinary life.
That's enough for me.
I won't interfere with your choices.
But you should know
you have choices now
all because of your father.
It's because of him
my sister and I suffered for so many years.
Why do you insist
your father went out gambling?
Uncle Dong
What do you mean
by that?
You've grown up.
It's time to think carefully.
Uncle Dong
Where are you really going?
Once I help you figure things out,
I'll tell you everything.
Who is it?
Xiao Yun
Don't scare her.
Director Dong
Please let me go.
A Cai,
you're really wasting a good life.
Just tell the truth.
From now on,
you won't have to hide.
Zhao Zhao
You've finished reading the letter, right?
All this time, I didn't see your mom
because she had someone else in her heart.
But that's all in the past.
I've reached out to friends in the US.
Afterwards,
we can transfer your mom there.
They're quite authoritative in this field.
You...
Don't feel pressured.
I hope you can understand me.
I never meant to hurt your mom.
I'm sorry.
Dad.
Don't apologize.
From now on, the company...
will depend on you.
But I still...
Wuyao brought this on himself.
You did the right thing.
We're the real family.
The Chen family drove us out.
Your mom and I were both hurt by Chen Zhengli.
Get out!
If you truly want to do something for her,
then come with me
to seek justice for your mom.
I know.
That's all.
It really was him.
You need to testify against Qin Defeng.
I've said everything I should.
Please.
He's capable of anything.
You think if you say nothing,
he'll let you go?
You have no choice.
You must testify in court.
Do you understand?
Xiao Yun,
what exactly happened?