Four foie gras nigiri
And sashimi
Sukiyaki
And some premium tempura
Ziwei
I'm not very hungry
Do you not like what I ordered?
Then I'll order something else
Japanese-style raw beef
Salmon nigiri
And two orders of sea urchin
One order
One is enough
Alright
And two bottles of sake
Ziwei
Let's skip the sake
It's fine, sake is low in alcohol
Just have a little with me to cheer me up
Just one bottle
Okay, whatever you say
That's all, thank you
Ziwei
I'm going to the restroom, you wait here
Gongxi
Don't get involved with people from Yaode Group anymore
Do you understand?
Those people should be gone now
They'd better not bother me again
Come on, cheers
Brother Gongxi
How long have we known each other?
About eight years
Eight years
So what do you think of me?
You're great
You took good care of me when I stayed at your place
I'm not talking about before, I mean now
You're like a sister to me
Always have been, always will be
But you helped me so much at the club
It's natural to help my sister, we've known each other since we were kids
No
You don't like me
I do
But it's the kind of affection a brother has for his sister
Chen Gongxi
You mean
You don't like me
If you mean that kind of love
No
Ziwei, stop drinking
If you don't like me, why do you care?
I'll take you home
What's in the drink?
Brother Gongxi
I've already given you a chance
If you really liked me
I wouldn't turn you in
Turn me in for what?
They said if they catch you
They have countless ways to make you play Mahjong for them
And my father's debt will be cleared
But don't worry
I won't let you help me for nothing
Brother Gongxi
You said
If you pay off my debt
I'll spend one night with you
Then we'll be even
We meet again.
Are you feeling dizzy?
Don't get too worked up.
Otherwise, the medicine will hit you harder, you know?
You just lack experience.
Chen Gongxi.
Back at the club,
I tried to talk sense into you, but you wouldn't listen.
You insisted on ending up like this.
This outcome.
Despicable.
Enough talking. You guys come in.
Where are they?
I told you to come in.
I'm the one who stopped them from coming in.
Long time no see.
Wu Yao.
That's Chen Gongxi.
So you're just going to
try to take him away like this?
Sister.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand at all.
Stop pretending.
Take your accomplice and leave now.
You're with Yaode too. If Dad—
Should I call the police?
Wait for the police to come.
Let them see what's going on.
My brother is so smart.
He'll know what to do.
Take that woman and get out.
Are you deaf?
Who is she?
Did you forget how your dad died?
It's been three years. You haven't played Mahjong since.
Why did you play again?
Mom.
I'm sorry.
I did it for—
What are you trying to say?
You mean you—
Did it to save me?
That's just an excuse.
Do you know your expression when you play?
That focus and calculation.
You know it in your heart.
This is where your talent shines.
There are so many Mahjong players in the world.
Why is it impossible for you?
No.
I promised my mom.
I can't.
Gongxi.
What do you think—
was the reason I died?
You're awake.
Is it that serious? I'm not going to eat you.
Why are you here?
I—
Hello, Chen Gongxi.
Chen Gongxi.
Hello.
I'm representing Cangwu Group.
That's too formal.
Chen Gongxi, name your price.
Name your price.
He doesn't look like he wants money.
Just passing by.
How did I get back?
You have the nerve to ask?
Someone on a motorcycle brought you.
What's up with him?
How could he do that?
The one on the motorcycle?
Was it a man or a woman?
You don't know, and you're asking me?
Weren't you awake?
I—
A woman.
Not bad, Chen Gongxi.
Girls seem to like you.
Isn't one Ziwei enough?
You have to bring another one too. By the way—
Why did Qin Wuyao ask me to play Mahjong?
Because you're skilled.
Yeah.
I saw you at a tournament three years ago.
You were wearing a mask back then.
I couldn't see your face clearly.
But your Mahjong skills made a strong impression.
So why is the Qin family looking for me?
I have some disputes with the Qin family.
What kind of dispute?
Well,
It's about an equity transfer in a company.
Beimen Street and Alley.
After Lü's company won the bid, they delayed development.
Now the business is struggling.
They need to transfer equity.
And bring in new investment.
Now Yaode and your Cangwu group
both want to acquire the equity.
Then let’s compete at the negotiation table.
Cangwu isn’t afraid.
Your two groups are evenly matched.
Lü’s company doesn’t want to offend either side.
That’s why they asked me to step in.
It’s a business association tradition.
The older generation wants to keep the peace.
So they play a round of Mahjong.
My suggestion is,
you two should have a Sichuan Mahjong professional match.
Lü’s company will negotiate first with the winner.
As for the outcome,
it depends on your negotiation skills.
Beimen Street and Alley.
Yeah.
Both groups want to get involved.
Yes.
If Qin Wuyao gets it,
he’ll tear this place down.
Wouldn’t your family do the same?
I think
I actually like this place.
We could persuade Lü’s company
to submit a new development plan.
Like turning it into a cultural district.
Miss Bai.
I promised my mom
I wouldn’t play Mahjong anymore.
It’s okay.
I won’t force you.
But you don’t mind being friends, right?
Chen Gongxi.
Call me Xiaoxue.
Miss Qin.
Uncle Dong.
Did you see him?
Yes, I did.
And I even fell for a childish trick.
That’s all thanks to your brother.
Uncle Dong.
He’s not my brother.
He’s still your half-brother.
Blame your father for being biased.
You promised me.
If I help you,
you’ll help me in return.
Of course.
Right now,
you haven’t really helped yet.
I don’t understand.
Why do I have to help him?
You should know
whose son he is.
Of course.
My father’s old rival.
Chen Zhengli’s son.
The enemy of my enemy
is a friend.
But Uncle Chen
is already dead.
Because Chen Zhengli is gone,
your Qin family and the Bai family
are fighting over that land.
If he were still here,
who would dare?
Uncle Chen was a good man.
So
you should help him even more.
But why does it have to be me?
You know,
in this game right now,
only Chen Gongxi can make the move.
Besides, you have some history with him.
If you don’t help him, who will?
So what,
do you actually dislike him?
He's a bit silly.
But I don't dislike him.
Then that's settled.
I'll leave this to you.
Gongxi.
I'm back.
Do you really not remember me?
Who is she?