Let me introduce you.
He is the famous Chen Zhengli's
Uncle Dong.
If you insist on hurting him today,
then you'll have to go through me first.
You're fighting alone,
while the whole Yaode Group
has hundreds of people working in secret.
How can you possibly fight them?
Let me help you figure things out.
I'll tell you everything, no secrets.
Gongxi.
My condolences.
Where is Qin Defeng?
When Uncle Dong had his accident,
my father was with me the whole time.
I understand.
This
is your choice.
Gongxi.
Calm down.
We don't have any evidence yet.
I'm calmer now than ever
before.
Gongxi.
What are you going to do?
Let's talk.
What do you want to talk about?
Uncle Dong is dead.
I heard.
He was a good friend of mine for years.
It's a shame.
But A Cai is still alive.
You know him well.
He used to be your driver, after all.
You mean him?
How did my father really die?
Your father?
What do you mean, how did he die?
Back then, everyone said he was gambling overseas
and jumped into the sea to his death.
But the only one with him at the time
was you.
I think
maybe you've misunderstood something.
Whether it's a misunderstanding
we'll know when A Cai wakes up.
Hello?
This is Qin Defeng.
You haven't eaten all day.
Have something to eat.
I can't eat.
I spent a long time making this.
It's fine.
Young Master Chen.
Miss Bai.
Something happened.
What exactly happened?
Gongxi.
You're here.
Why are you here?
Zhaozhao.
According to Wenhua International's board,
Mr. Dong Zhongping's transfer of shares to Chen Gongxi
has not yet taken effect.
Mr. Dong has no legal heir.
According to company regulations,
his shares are repurchased by other shareholders.
Yaode Group has completed legal procedures
to purchase Wenhua International's shares.
They are now the largest shareholder.
Gongxi.
As your elder,
let me give you one more piece of advice.
Leave here immediately.
Otherwise,
security will escort you out.
I'd like to see who dares.
Sister Xiaoyun.
Let's go.
You heard it just now.
I have nothing left.
You don't have to follow me.
Young Master Chen.
I've followed Uncle Dong for sixteen years.
You're not the only one who wants to take on Qin Defeng.
There are others too.
Alright.
What about you all?
Young Master Chen, we're with you.
Alright.
Thank you.
Young Master Chen.
What do we do next?
He's fallen into the trap now.
We wait.
Wait for what?
A Cai.
How is he?
Young Master Chen.
Just as you said,
he really showed up.
We've already called the police.
He's been taken to the station to assist with the investigation.
Got it.
Hello.
Hello, we're investigating Qin Defeng.
Please cooperate with us.
Alright, understood.
We already have some evidence.
Chen Zhengli.
I'm his son.
You look
so much like him.
He
He was
What?
murdered.
What did you say?
Excuse me, please.
Please make way.
Notify the emergency room quickly.
Okay.
Dad.
The truth is about to come out.