Chen Shao
Is it good news or bad news?
Beimen Alley
I don’t know what to do.
Sit down.
Tell me.
Qin Wuyao played dirty.
He tricked the villagers out of their houses.
Cheated.
Do you have any proof?
No.
People’s hearts...
are like bottomless pits.
If they weren’t greedy,
they wouldn’t have fallen for it.
I grew up relying on neighbors’ kindness.
I believe
after this experience,
the villagers will remember this lesson.
But I promised my mom
to protect them.
Yes.
Protect my sister.
Give back to the community.
Never get involved in gambling.
Don’t you think you’re carrying too much?
I have to do it all.
Every single one.
Uncle Dong
Why are you laughing?
Seeing you like this now,
reminds me of your father.
Beimen Village
That place isn’t good for investment.
Old Dong
Not everything
can be measured by money.
Beimen Village
Everyone chipped in
to send me to college.
Now it’s my turn to give back.
He is him.
I am me.
But there’s one thing you lack compared to him.
What?
Watch closely.
You lost.
At least your father understood this.
You’re a leader with no support.
Yaode Group, top to bottom,
hundreds of people sneakily plot.
What do you have to fight them?
Even if we take a step back,
they paid for the houses.
Can you stop them?
You’re young.
Naive.
Bold and stubborn.
That’s normal.
But
if your father were here now,
think about it.
What would he do?
Uncle Dong
I want to borrow something from you.
No, wait.
More than one thing.
What you want,
I’ve wanted to give you for a long time.
No, it’s returning it to you.
He said
I couldn’t.
He wanted me to give it to you myself.
But I had to wait for you to ask for it.
Here, if you don’t sign, forget it.
Wait, I’ll sign.
Hold on.
Who are you?
Do you know where this is?
Qin Shao
Someone wants to see you.
Give the houses back to them.
The money—
I’ll repay it myself.
I noticed after not seeing you for a few days,
you’ve learned to joke, huh?
You’ll repay?
Tell me,
how will you pay?
Uncle Dong’s intention—
That’s starting a feud.
Uncle Dong voluntarily transfers his assets
and shares to Chen Shao.
He won’t get involved in your dispute.
He’s not participating.
I don’t care about this little money.
Please tell Uncle Dong
the feud is set in stone.
Dad
Uncle Dong has made his move.
Alright.
Don't let me down this time.
Okay.
Zhengli,
My son won't lose.
Elder
You need something from me?
According to the competition results,
Cangwu gets priority to negotiate share acquisition with the Lü family.
Yaode is buying property now.
What are they planning?
Don't break the rules.
They're desperate to pay off their debts.
Isn't repaying debts the right thing to do?
I lent them money to help.
How does that break any rules?
If it's just about money,
then do me a favor.
Let Gongxi buy the house back.
Call you Elder,
and you really think you're the Elder now?
Let me tell you,
I accept the competition results.
But now,
I set the rules.
Let's go.
Wait.
Return the houses of the Beimen villagers
back to them.
Money—
I'll give it to you.
What did you say?
Money.
Yaode doesn't lack this kind of money.
The initiative is in my hands now.
Chen, besides money,
do you have any other way?
Qin,
why not hear my proposal?
Xiaoxue,
I heard Uncle Qin wants a marriage alliance between our families.
If you agree to Mr. Chen,
I can give you a chance.
Think it over.
Xiaoxue,
No need to think.
I'll take this chance.
But I have one condition.
You have to compete with me.
As long as you join,
you can buy the house back at the original price.
No other stakes.
I just want to see you completely defeated.
Is that okay, Xiaoxue?
Sure.
Alright.
I accept.
It's settled.
But this time,
we won't play mahjong.
We'll play dice.
President Qin,
You—
It's none of your business.
It's decided.
Xiaoxue,
One week from now,
at Jiangcheng Palace.
Don't be late.
Xiaoxue,
No matter what, don't joke about yourself.
You're not a bargaining chip.
You're overthinking.
I only listen to my dad.
If you win, it's good for the Bai family.
If you lose,
I'll accept the outcome.
No.
Just because you say no, it's no?
Do friends really interfere this much?
That day, Sister Zhao came to me drunk.
I just made sure she was okay.
There's nothing between us.
Who cares about that?
Xiaoxue,