So which one is P'Nuea?
The one that got the loudest scream, That's P'Nuea.
Ai Toh! You took such a handsome photo of P'Nuea!
So...
what is the status of our relationship now?
[Secret Crush On You | The Series]
♫ I can't let you know that I'm secretly watching you every day ♫
Hello. I'm Saint Suppapong.
I'm an executive producer, co-producer, and actor of "Secret Crush on You, The Series"
[Suppapong Udomkaewkanjana, Executive producer & Actor]
[How "Secret Crush on You, The Series" came about]
We started by establishing the company known as Idolfactory.
Among our main objectives for establishing this company,
we wanted to give opportunities to young talents in the entertainment industry,
including the ones I have known, to work together in the same company.
This is how Idolfactory came about. Then, I wanted to grow and expand further.
One day I felt that I could pass on this good fortune and opportunity.
So, I felt like making a TV series to give young talents an opportunity,
as well as to carry on the goals I have set.
That eventually led to the birth of "Secret Crush on You, The Series"
[Roles as an executive producer and actor]
Being the executive producer or co-producer
is a new territory, a new role, for me.
That's why, as I said before,
I had to experience so many things.
There were lots of trials and errors
I had to invest myself in learning about different things.
I feel that this was something that brought me happiness.
I didn't create a series, film, or soap opera,
but I created something in my heart that happens to be
where happiness occurred from seeing everyone enjoy watching the series.
Everyone is happy about the series' content.
Everyone gets to see the different characters.
The young actors have the opportunity to improve their talents.
They have a way to start their career in the entertainment industry.
As the executive producer,
I think I've created something beautiful.
Before the series came about, before choosing the novel,
before forming the production crew and arranging key staff,
while dealing with the obstacles that come up,
the best classroom is the one where we experience ourselves.
These practices teach me a lot of things.
It taught me how to grow up.
It teaches me more about management skills
It taught me to become an adult
who knows how to take up different responsibilities.
And that I have to be responsible for not only myself
I have to be accountable for the livelihood of the whole production crew.
I need to think how I can take care of them best.
["You seem quite happy, Toh!"]
I need to think how I can manage it best with the highest efficiency.
As for being an actor,
this is probably what I'm familiar with the most
because I've been an actor for some time now.
But in "Secret Crush On You"
I only appear as a guest star playing the role of "P'Thep"
Since I get to play this character
there are some new and different things.
I can add many things to this character to create more excitement.
This character takes the role of contributor and backer
to both the main characters, Nuea and Toh.
The character is there to support,
and create more situations for them.
I think it's a fun character to play
since this supporting role can move the plot forward.
[Similarities and differences between "Saint" and "Thep"]
To be honest this character doesn't have any background story before this.
Thep's dialogues are as few as 3 pages for the whole series.
I felt that I had to create P'Thep's background myself.
So I worked on that before I took the role as P'Thep.
I had to think about what I had to prepare to be the character.
What should I do? What should P'Thep's story be?
How would his character be involved? I brainstormed on my own.
It was as if I wrote a separate novel about P'Thep's entity.
And I felt that I wanted to create P'Thep to be
somewhat similar to myself.
[Why did you choose "Cheewin" as the director for "Secret Crush On You, The Series"]
Why P'Cheewin? Actually, I've been close with P'Cheewin for a while.
I usually call P'Cheewin "Grandma"
I had a chance to work with Grandma Chee before in another series
We've been working together. We're familiar with each other.
So, when we started doing this project,
as I said, I only had little experience
I knew I needed experts
["Everyone seems very focused"]
who had the know-how and skills to guide me through.
Grandma Chee was one of the first people I decided to consult.
Then, we agreed to work together.
We talked about the plot, the script,
and adjusted the script by re-writing it ourselves
until it became "Secret Crush On You, The Series"
[Your feeling towards being the director of "Secret Crush On You"]
[Cheewin - Thanamin Wongsakulpach, Director]
First thing first, I was glad
I was glad that they saw something in me
that made him want me to be the director.
It started with P'Chen and Nong Saint giving me the opportunity to be the director.
After that, I read the original novel
["Don't make me angry!!"]
and thought to myself that this novel had a selling point.
And there're interesting issues that can be conveyed to the public.
I'd like to thank them for giving me this opportunity
so I can meet the young talents and a lovely crew.
["Secret Crush On You" plot summary]
It all started with a boy named "Toh"
He has a crush on his "Magic"
who is "P'Nuea."
He had to find his love, have a secret crush, and admire from afar.
[What are the reasons for matching the actors with the roles?]
[Let's start from the character "P'Nuea" by Billy]
For Billy's character, we had a rough idea in mind
about how we wanted him to be. We had a draft.
When we first met P'Billy, we thought
he quite matched the image we had of Nuea.
["Nuea is superb"]
P'Billy is fairly confident in himself
He has this old soul within him dubbed "Billy the Uncle"
"Billy the Uncle"
Billy the Uncle
["We're doing our best"]
has P'Nuea's soul in him.
["Nuea is so dope"]
Then we added other bits and details
until we got this version of P'Nuea we see on screen.
In the end, he came out to be what we wanted.
Then, we blended his character with P'Nuea's.
I think P'Billy and P'Nuea's personality overlap a lot
He is mature and P'Nuea's maturity level is also high.
He's a warm-hearted man.
When I look at him,
he makes me feel that he's ready to protect the person he loves.
He makes me feel his desire to protect Toh.
But sometimes the way he's protective,
isn't in a way where it's straightforward.
He can do it with just his gaze.
In which P'Billy does really well by bringing this out in P'Nuea.
Well, if I have to talk about Billy who portrays P'Nuea's character
I'd say he really is the magic, like how Toh describes him.
The first time I met Billy,
I thought he was good. He exuded potential.
During the filming,
I feel that he's very hard-working and well-prepared.
Simply put, he's a front-row student.
[Billy - Patchanon Aounsa-ard as "Nuea"]
I saw the casting call for "Secret Crush On You"
I'm someone who likes to be prepared.
Before I go to each audition for each product,
I would look it up on YouTube.
I need to do the homework before entering the field.
For "Secret Crush On You", I read the novel first.
I read both volumes.
Honestly, I've never read a novel before.
I read books, like textbooks
but I never touched fictional novels
[Surely, a person like Nuea isn't afraid of this!!]
because I enjoyed watching films and series more.
As soon as I read the novel, it was really good.
Boys normally read comics and graphic novels
which have illustrations to help visualize the story, right?
But for a novel, there are only words.
So, it surprised me how the narration
creates such clear images inside my head.
It was as if I became a child once more after I read this novel.
I enjoyed it so much that I couldn't stop reading
I'm impressed by many of its characters.
It never really occurred to me that I would get chosen as P'Nuea.
I thought to myself if I get to be a part of such a fun story,
I could make the audience feel the same joy I had when I read the novel.
Then, P'Chen and Saint called me to cast for the role.
When I got the role the first thing I felt was happiness.
Then, it hit me that I had to play P'Nuea
I was beyond nervous.
I was like "What should I do? I have to play P'Nuea.
Where's the Mr. Cool guy side in me?"
All the questions flooded through my head, and I started to panic.
I was happy, but I also freaked out.
I was wondering how I could best portray P'Nuea in a way that the audience would enjoy.
I wasn't confident that I could be P'Nuea.
When I first attended the workshop,
I heard some comments saying
"Can he really play the role of P'Nuea well?" and all that.
Did they discourage me? They did.
But I came all the way to this point. I had to go forward.
I had to pull it off.
I had to be the P'Nuea that people would enjoy and love.
["Toh" played by Seng]
We followed the same steps in choosing Seng.
At that time, we...
we wanted Seng to try Toh's character
["Stretch and refresh"]
I remember during the casting process,
Seng still struggled to find Toh's character
Again, we tried different methods on him.
[#Alcoholsarebad, This is a prop for filming]
We added the colors yellow, red, orange, and purple
[Surely, Toh is talking about work]
and Seng slowly became the character
[You just wanna say that Toh is good?]
With adjustments, he gradually embodied Toh's character.
There were adjustments made but Send is very good.
Because you can kind of see the balance between Seng and Toh.
[Someone is putting pressure on him!!]
That being said, they weren't too far apart.
I think that Seng did really well to change himself and portray Toh.
And he made people believe that he really was Toh.
There were quite a few moments off the screen
that the audience didn't get to see Seng likes receiving tender loving care.
He likes to plead cutely.
Normally, when you pull a prank or tease others,
you just do it without thinking too much. You just have fun with them.
But Seng is different. When he finishes teasing others, He's going to sit down and start wondering,
"Will they feel down and sad?"
"Will those people take revenge on me?"
"Or maybe I should apologise to them in case they're really upset with me"
That's how Seng is as a person.
And all these are the characteristics that Toh has. He overthinks.
At first, Seng didn't realize these feelings can became the basic foundation
that can bring forth Toh's character.
When we brought out the bits of Seng's character,
we eventually got the Toh you see in the series.
As for Seng...
I've actually met him before.
And now we work together again on this project.
At the beginning, I had a couple of worries about him
because I thought he was so different from Toh.
People who have met him before or his fans
definitely know that he has his own specific style.
But during the workshop
I got a glimpse of what he was capable of
that could turn him into Toh.
Today, he's proved himself as a perfect Toh.
[Seng - Wichai Saefant as "Toh"]
The first thing that hit me was excitement.
I really wanted to play the role well.
This is the first series I get to play a lead role.
I received an opportunity given by P'Chen and P'Saint.
They told me to try this role.
They told me they chose me for this project.
That made me want to try my hardest
[Toh, you're making the director nervous]
not to disappoint them.
[by showering him with compliments]
From reading the scripts and the original novels
to working out all the details, I worked hard in every area.
I'm glad I was part of this story and was able to convey this series to the audience.
I went all out with everything I had.
What I got in return... I just felt that I put my 100 percent.
I gave everything I had at the time.
And all I wanted was to make the audience smile
and be happy with the series. That was it.
[Heng as "Sky"]
Khun Heng, our own "P'Sky."
Needless to say, he played as himself.
Let me tell you this, among our 4 main characters
he's the one whose character overlapped with the character he played (Sky) the most
since the initial casting.
When I saw his profile picture and all,
[Your way of trying to make up with him]
I thought they had a lot in common.
[is making him bashful]
Even the way he walked was the same as how I pictured Sky walking.
They were that similar.
So I thought this friend of mine
[Refreshed. So refreshing]
was perfect as Sky.
Heng is a handsome man.
He was handsome and cool the moment he walked in.
He carried this mysterious aura with him wherever he went.
I thought he was mysterious. There was something about him.
He had this cool and handsome vibe.
When we unveiled this part of his, we can see that Sky
was hidden somewhere inside him.
So we pulled the shadow of Sky out.
We amplified and drew more of that part of him out.
Among the 4 characters, it took Heng the least time and effort to adjust to the character.
I'm so glad we got Heng to play this role.
He made Sky loveable as a character.
I think that both Heng and Sky like to plead cutely.
Heng likes to joke around and tease people around him.
And being playful and cheeky are Sky's character.
When we put that with Heng's cool aura, Sky's character is complete.
And that's how Khun Heng is.
Actually, I met Heng before.
When we met this time round
I thought he was a stubborn kid
(7:00 A.M.)
But when we started working together,
I realized he was kind-hearted man.
(This is how we energize ourselves during the filming)
He's a caretaker and he pays attention.
To put it simply, he could really be Sky in real life.
He's loyal and faithful. He's a diligent kid.
But he's also a whiny kid.
Not whiny like being selfish, but he's sensitive as a person.
(Heng - Asavarid Pinitkanchanapan as "Sky")
To say "it's beyond the wildest dreams" is not an exaggeration
because not many people receive such an opportunity
and not everyone is this fortunate.
When I saw the character during the workshop,
I started asking myself how come this character and I were so much alike,
from our background stories to something deep down inside.
I don't think this is a coincidence
Our acting coach, Teacher Kla, told me nothing is a coincidence.
There will be something that leads the character and myself to meet.
Each character chooses the actors to perform the roles,
so the actors could portray the characters as much as possible.
I talked to my character every day. I'm bonded with him.
So the feeling has long since surpassed gratitude.
It was an experience that gave me the courage to step out of my comfort zone.
I didn't even believe that I could do it then.
(Surprise as "Kaojao")
Kaojao or our very own Khun Surprise.
All 4 of them always hang out together
But Surprise has the 'youngest sibling vibe' ever since the first time I met him,
even during the casting process, he seems like the youngest sibling in the family.
He makes you want to protect him.
Kaojao's main characteristic is the love of eating.
Surprise always asks, "Can I eat this?"
"How about this one? Can I eat this one?"
"Can I trade this one for that one?"
I felt that they had something in common there.
This might seem like a trivial issue.
But, Surprise is also a little sensitive and a bit sulky at times.
Which I really like.
So I told him to utilize this part of himself
and put it in Kaojao.
And that made Kaojao more complete as a character.
It would make Kaojao even more adorable and delicate as a character.
This was the assignment for Surprise to do.
He understood it and blended who he was and his character together.
He delivered everything I pictured in my head and created such a loveable Kaojao.
And that was how it played out.
Surprise.
I have to tell you that Surprise checked off many factors on the list
as an actor who would get to play Kaojao.
He interpreted Kaojao and interpreted it well in his own way.
I feel that Kaojao's loveliness as portrayed by Surprised
had many astonishing moments.
(Surprise - Pitikorn Siripornsawan
as "Kaojao")
I'm delighted to be a part of this series
When I studied the character,
I thought Kaojao's character matched me so well, simply because I also enjoy eating.
I put so much effort into this role.
Before I started playing Kaojao, my weight was 64 kilograms
and I tried to lose weight because I didn't know the character well enough.
But when I read the scripts I realized
Kaojao should be a little chubby, healthy and plump.
So I tried to eat more to portray Kaojao's appearance the best I could.
I've been with this character
for a long time.
And I love this character so much.
[Secret Crush On You | The Series]
(Similarities and differences between you and the role you play)
(Differences between Billy and Nuea?)
P'Nuea is calm, cool, and very mature.
He's someone who examines things attentively.
Everything that he does has been well planned
and thought out. Like what does he have to do, to get this done?
He lets his actions speak louder than his words.
You will see that in each scene
he maintains his composure and communicates through his gaze.
And this is why it's difficult for me to play P'Nuea.
As for myself, I speak first
before I take action.
Do I have a plan? Yes.
Am I as meticulous as P'Nuea? No.
But what I think P'Nuea and I
("I've been keeping a serious face all day.)
have in common is we both like to take care of people around us
(Let me pull a funny one now)
We always support the younger kids and people around us
("Toh, you're making it tough on Nuea")
We put others before ourselves.
One more similarity that we have is our, "coolness."
Although I try to be cool, it appears as, "wanna-be cool."
(Finally, Toh gets to wear Nuea's clothes)
But P'Nuea is cool from the inside out.
Also, I think I've learnt so much from P'Nuea.
The version of Billy you see now has P'Nuea as his idol
in the process of maturing.
I think this character makes me a better man.
(Toh's heart is racing because of Nuea)
I'm so glad I get to play P'Nuea.
I've adopted P'Nuea's personality into my everyday life these days.
(The differences between Seng and Toh?)
Our similarity lies in our energy. We're both playful and lively.
I think this makes us click with each other.
We both like to make people laugh.
We can't stand the awkward silence.
Toh likes to lighten up the mood I really appreciate that.
This extends to his love life.
He's very dedicated to love.
(Take cover once)
When he loves someone he gives them 100%.
(Take cover twice)
He's always ready to support the person he loves.
I think we're quite similar.
(Nuea's handsomeness has such a powerful impact)
When I have fallen for someone I want to give the person my support
I want to be by their side to fully back my loved one up.
Within the group of friends
(Eh? Whose hand is this?)
and the love among them,
(Toh is in shock)
I think Toh fully loves and supports his friends.
He doesn't want his friends to be sad or unhappy.
He doesn't want to see them cry
And when I see my friends like that, it makes me upset.
It makes me want to help them solve their problems.
As for our differences,
I think it's the way we handle things.
Toh is extremely observant, especially in what he likes and is interested in.
This becomes clear to me when I play as the character
I thought I paid attention to details
But when I got to know Toh,
I can tell that he pays attention in every aspect.
That includes the time, what the person he likes enjoys, and what he himself likes.
He will even know the release of certain items,
the details of each photo,
or even the small details of what the person he likes, like to do
on a day-to-day basis.
I think this is how I'm different from him.
Unlike him, I may not remember all the details.
Also, we're different when it comes to food.
I felt that we're really different in the beginning
because I didn't know that Toh rarely eats. Before I took this role, I had to change my physique and weight.
My weight was 68-69 kilograms, I think.
When I got Toh's role
I had a talk with P'Chen and P'Saint about my appearance and weight
And we thought Toh might be slimmer and smaller.
Right before the filming started, my weight went down to 52 kilos.
During the filming, I was completely unaware
that I ate so much less and that my health had also changed.
I realized this when people started noticing and commented, "Why are you eating so little?"
"Why are you eating just that?"
That's when I knew that when I changed my eating habits my physique and health changed too.
My dietary requirements also changed.
For me, this is another big difference between me and Toh
(Differences between Surprise and Kaojao)
There're both similarities and differences.
What we have in common is the fact that we eat lots of desserts.
We both enjoy eating. Very much.
When we eat, we don't think about anything else. We just eat.
As for the differences, I think it's about sports.
I love playing basketball. I play a lot of sports.
But Nong Kaojao doesn't really do sports.
He enjoys taking photos, being by himself, and hanging out only with his friends.
He doesn't socialize as much because he's shy.
(What do you like in the character that you play?)
(Nuea)
I like... how witty he is.
I like everything about him from his maturity to his calmness.
He has his way of playing.
He has his own ways of communicating.
He doesn't always speak out what he feels.
He can be tight-lipped but he knows all the possible outcomes of what he decides to do.
During the filming, I hardly had any time to watch the playbacks.
I got to see the final product when the series aired.
I saw that the words in my head were delivered through my gaze.
And this was the assignment P'Kla and P'Cheewin gave me since day one.
In the beginning, I didn't have any required skills. I couldn't communicate with my eyes,
and my ears aren't great. P'Nuea has a good ear.
So I did so much homework on eyes and ears
I watched Korean series as my references
to understand those male characters
that speak little but communicate with their eyes.
How they have lots of inner monologues and how they delivered them with their gaze.
I did a lot of homework. I also watched the Hollywood shows.
I watched Benedict Cumberbatch and Andrew Garfield, for instance.
Normally, I watch them for leisure
But now, I have to stare intensely at the screen.
It's like I get to practice the skill as well.
That's why I like how P'Nuea talks through his eyes.
(Toh)
Actually, I like everything about Toh.
I like his viewpoints, possibly all of them.
But if I need to name one, I like his attitude towards love.
The way he gives love to someone,
he doesn't need anything in return.
I think Toh is a faithful person when it comes to love.
He gives 100% and all that he's got for that person or thing he likes.
I feel like I see the different perspectives of Toh when he likes someone.
He's willing to give all his time, heart and soul for his beloved.
From the activities his loved one enjoys doing
or whatever his loved one likes.
Toh is attentive and always gives encouragement
to the one he likes.
And he never expects anything in return or expects the other person to reciprocate.
I think his feeling of love is so pure.
This part of Toh impresses me so much.
(Sky)
There're many things I like about Sky.
Sky is playful, yearning for love, and flirtatious.
That said, he's warm-hearted.
His character is interesting.
Even for me, I think this type of person is charming
I want to be him the best I can.
He's an athlete and a musician.
He has many friends. He's lively and attentive.
It's the kind of character I want to be like.
Most importantly, he may seem like a playboy
but as a person who's been playing as Sky during the past year
I can confirm that when he stops playing around,
it means he's very serious about his feeling
I'm not bragging (selling my point) but I'm selling a pipe dream.
Yes, that's about it.
(Kaojao)
How he cares and loves his friends.
He truly cares for his friends
and does his best to give them the support they need.
Another thing I like is his eating habits.
Yes, I like it because he eats a lot. Like... a lot
When he eats, he doesn't think much about the calorie intake unlike me.
[Secret Crush On You | The Series]
("Inspirations" in designing the scenes)
The inspirations for each scene... Let's go back to the beginning.
I feel that for Y series',
the creative imagination, the voices in the head and the thoughts about them,
have disappeared from Y series for a while.
But when I started working on this series,
I felt that I wanted to bring these elements back once again.
And I thought these elements would go well with the characters in this series.
If we're talking about the scenes that I came up with,
I'd say, that's me putting myself in their shoes.
For instance, if I encountered something like this with someone,
this is what I would do with that person.
Or I would want to go all the way as much as possible,
visualizing what the characters would do.
And Nong Seng presented his character well. He went above and beyond.
Sometimes, I think it even went beyond my briefing and direction.
(Your most "memorable scene")
If I say every single scene impresses me it'll probably be too much though that's the truth
But if it's the scene that impresses me since the first glance
I think it's the "Like a Star" scene.
I think the scene is perfect by itself with all the elements:
the ambience, music and communication
I like this scene a lot.
Another thing is the friendship among Toh and his friends.
I think he's lucky to be surrounded by such good people.
including P'Nuea, P'Sky, P'Khongkwan, P'Fon, and P'Touch.
They came into his life and made Toh's ordinary life so enviable,
because he's surrounded by such good people.
There's also this scene with P'Sine.
(Sine - Intira Charoenpura)
At the time we were filming, it must have been around 7 pm.
It was the final scene of that location.
As we finished setting up and were ready to shoot.
3, 2, and... action. All the lights went out.
I was like "Oh my, what do we do now?"
P'Sine put her hands together and mumbled something.
Then, I walked towards her. She said that this was normal.
Once she finished what she was saying the lights came back,
and we could finish our filming.
It was unbelievable.
Do not disrespect it even if you don't believe in it.
Everything was set and the camera were already rolling.
Everything was ready. The electricity suddenly went out.
That was perfectly normal. It's considered something good.
Such things happen all the time.
Every scene is full of joy. I particularly enjoy the early episodes.
I like the fact that P'Nuea is full of tricks.
He was as sweet as a field of sugar cane. So flirty.
This is so clear in the first and second episodes. Especially when they play the Kung King game. Like, oh wow.
During the Kung King game that I had to play around.
It's like I was having fun teasing and that I got to play around with Toh.
When, in fact, I more or less liked him since the first time I laid my eyes on him.
But I also wanted to make sure how much this person liked me
and how serious this person was towards me.
Because P'Nuea has a composed persona.
From the way he looks
he might seem composed and has to keep his cool look all the time.
But everyone can see the differences after he has become Toh's lover.
He is ready to throw such images away.
There's this dialogue in which he says to Fon, "If I like someone, I'll make sure the person knows"
He lets his actions speak.
He drops his composure and pours his heart out.
He tells the world he's Toh's lover. I love him for who he is.
I love the clumsy kid wearing glasses named Nong Toh.
Even in the episodes when they're dating already he still enjoys teasing Nong Toh.
For P'Nuea, in his eyes everything that Toh does is adorable.
It's pure joy.
It's like there are only two of them in this world.
Nothing else matters. It doesn't matter if there are people around passing by.
He has tunnel vision.
He's crazily in love with Toh. That's right.
The scene that I enjoy the most is the one where everyone plays games together.
It's in Ep.2 or 3 where we go to P'Nuea's house.
Another one is where we go to the beach.
I think it's the scene that all the actors
both the Engineering and Comm Arts groups get together and play games.
I felt that we enjoyed ourselves a lot.
I get to see what each character wants.
I also enjoy the overall carefree and cheerful vibes.
It's where everyone can enjoy and laugh out loud. Yeah.
It's fun. At the same time, it's challenging
because "Kung King, do as you're told" is the main game of our Engineering squad.
Each person is different. Like P'Nuea has a cool composure.
Khongkwan and Fon are glued together.
So Sky has to boost the energy so that everyone can have fun.
I felt so stressed shooting this scene
Because one, the dialogue was quite long
And this scene was a reshoot.
It didn't reach the emotional feel that they wanted from us.
So I kind of blamed myself for not being able to do this scene better.
I thought I had to do better. I asked myself if it was my fault that they had to reshoot.
I had many things inside my head. So, to me, the scene was difficult.
On top of that, this reshoot is put
as the final queue of filming, "Secret Crush On You, The Series"
Frankly speaking, that day we'd completed 99% of the filming
I thought I fully understood everything.
I understood the character. I understood how I should play.
I knew the most important thing was to relax.
I needed to go out there and give my best shot.
I was prepared and remembered my lines because we had filmed it once before.
As for the rest, I just had to play the scene with my friends
the hardest I could to make people believe that
it really is the game that we all enjoy.
When I finally pulled it off I was so happy that I told myself I made it.
That's why it was the most difficult but fun scene.
It's one of the most memorable for me. That's it.
The scene in which I had the most fun playing
is probably the one I played with my friends,
Toh, Som, and Daisy.
It's the scene where we snuck to hang tangerines on P'Nuea's car.
Which was a very silly scene.
In that scene, everyone has to act like ninjas to hang the bag of tangerines.
We pretended to be trees and Kaojao acted as a rock.
For this scene, P'Cheewin didn't brief us on what to do.
So we had to think of the details ourselves.
Like should we pretend to be a tree or something else?
Or maybe Toh should hide under the car?
The scene was very hilarious.
It's one of the opening scenes of the series as well.
I really like that scene. It's fun. And it was so energy-consuming.
("Flirting Scene" that you like)
Billy and Seng's bathtub scene.
For me, I don't see it as a heavy NC scene.
But I think the plot is realistic.
I like how well the message is delivered.
This is for real. It's terrific.
Should we call this flirting or teasing?
P'Nuea has his own way of doing things.
To be honest he's tried to make a clear statement
since Ep.1 and Ep.2
Then... how should I put it?
He slowly works his way to his prey.
But for Nong Toh, what Nuea does isn't enough for him
to be aware that P'Nuea is pursuing him.
Of course, P'Nuea just waits for Toh to finally realize it.
If he does one thing and Toh still has no clue
he will level up his actions more and more.
"Do you understand now?" If not, he'll do more and more.
This continues until the waterfall scene
where Nong Toh finally understands P'Nuea's feelings.
That eventually marks the beginning of their relationship as lovers.
While we know P'Nuea initiates the romance, but Toh doesn't realize this at all
That's the scene before their relationship starts
But after they start dating I'd choose the barbeque pork scene
on the rooftop after we return from the camp Toh waits for P'Nuea to come.
It's when their relationship has just begun
so he has a lot to learn about each other.
He's still being very much considerate of P'Nuea.
He tries to respect P'Nuea's personal space.
He tries to make P'Nuea understand that he wants to be with P'Nuea always.
He's not trying to cross the line.
He doesn't want to invade P'Nuea's privacy. He tries to show that he trusts P'Nuea.
So we can see how Toh tries to put his trust in P'Nuea That's what I think.
It's a difficult question.
Well, of course there're scenes that I like
but what I like better
is how every single move Sky makes can turn Jao's world upside down.
I enjoyed doing that every single time.
The more I did it, the more playful I acted
Surprise's ears show what he feels whenever he gets shy or embarrassed. His ears turn red.
When I saw that his ears turned bright red,
I felt that I delivered the mood. I played my part well.
He got shy for real and it made him lose his cool.
And that makes Sky falls for him even more.
I enjoyed every single moment when Sky drops all his sweet talk.
He just says whatever he wants so that he can see Jao's reaction.
I really like it when Surprise's ears turn red.
That's it.
The couple or romantic scene with Sky that I like the most
is in Ep.13 Yeah, it's in Ep.13
I really like this episode.
It's the scene after Kaojao receives a plushie from his admirer, and P'Sky gets jealous.
I like it because Sky gets jealous and frustrated
but it makes me happy because Sky teases Jao a lot. It's payback time.
Another scene is the one where he takes me to his room
It's the scene in which Kaojao opens up his heart the most.
To me who played the role of Kaojao that day,
I think it's the scene that makes me feel most comfortable
because I now accept that I like this person. I've opened up my heart to him.
I like this scene very much.
(Favourite "dramatic" scenes)
Mine is in Ep.13
It's when P'Nuea sees Toh's entire collection
of all the photos on the wall.
That's a tough scene to pull off.
It's tough because I had to turn and look at Toh.
There were misunderstandings and so many questions.
Like, "Toh, why do you need to have so many photos of me?"
Yes, I do know that he has been collecting items related to me
but it's beyond my wildest imagination that he keeps so many of them and puts them on the wall.
He can't make sense of Toh's actions.
He also feels sad
because he truly loves Toh for who he is.
Many questions flood through his mind
And there's a dialogue in which Nuea asks Toh to tell him everything.
And after hearing what Toh had to say, P'Nuea understood it right away.
P'Nuea then explains the reasons why he loves Toh.
He tries to clear up the misunderstandings
and miscommunication between them. He explains everything.
There're all sorts of emotions in that scene.
Once you see that scene you'll see that it was cute and left a deep impression.
If I need to choose one I'll probably choose the one in Ep.13
It's the one which P'Nuea pulls down the curtain
and sees my photo collection and the rest of the items.
I think it's a crux of the series
Those who read the novel can definitely tell
that this crux or this hidden issue is Toh's greatest secret.
Ep.13 unfolds this issue.
If you haven't watched this scene I'd like to invite you to watch this part.
This scene isn't all about being dramatic
there are other emotions involved. It's also about moving forward.
It's about accepting one another.
It's also about listening to what the other has to say.
And it says something about having secrets.
At the end of the day, there's no secret in this world.
I really hope you would tune in to this scene.
Mine is in Ep.4
It's the first episode that Sky starts pursuing Nong Jao for real.
As Sky, I know it won't be easy to make Jao open up to him
but I made up my mind that I'll show him that he's serious about this.
It's the first time Sky makes a real big move.
Also, the scene where I drag Kaojao out of the pub
and take him back to his dorm
was the last scene of the day. What happened was it started to rain
And it was about time we had to wrap up the shooting.
The crew almost called the scene off, to film it another day.
But for some reason, we tried shooting one more time.
The staff, even Cheewin, all said this would be the final take.
It was all right if we couldn't do it. We could do it afterwards and such.
So I felt more relaxed
and gave it my all I have nothing to lose. I just wanted to do my best
And I had faith in my co-star.
We clicked and we pulled it off despite the time limit.
And it came out so well that after this final cut was released,
Prise came up to me and said, "Hey, Heng, you did well in this scene"
When I saw the final cut during the broadcast,
it remains the most memorable scene for me.
It shows the love and care, and the earnestness.
It shows different dimensions of the character.
It shows the earnest side of a playful guy.
Especially when I take him to the car and drop him off at his dorm.
Also, scene when we were chatting inside the car,
or when Sky waits until Nong Jao turns off the light in his room and goes to bed,
it gives me a warm fuzzy feeling when I watch it.
It's hard to move on from that scene.
So it's the best melodramatic scene for me. Yes.
The melodramatic scene that I love so much is in Ep.4
It's the scene where P'Sky and Nong Kaojao return from the pub.
It's during the 7-day flirt remark.
There's a scene that leaves a deep impression on Kaojao.
It's the scene where Kaojao tries to step out of his comfort zone to go to P'Sky.
But he's unsure if Sky is just playing with his feelings or if he's serious.
When I played this scene, I teared up and cried
because I don't like people to play with my feelings
And I think P'Sky made him feel that way, that's why he felt uneasy.
[Secret Crush On You | The Series]
(What obstacles did you encounter during the filming process?)
Our location was flooded.
The picture I had in my head collapsed.
The rice field turned into a river.
It became a river. Water was everywhere.
It was impossible to do the filming. So we had to cancel the filming.
There was also the Covid situation.
There was a lockdown.
(Social distancing)
So we couldn't do the filming.
(Wearing masks at all time)
The situation prolonged the filming process.
When we set the time frame for filming,
we thought we would have finished filming by then
We should be doing the editing.
The broadcast schedule was moved.
There's also an issue with the swab test
People may think doing swab tests wouldn't cost a lot of money
But would you believe me if I tell you
(SWAB test for everyone )
it made the budget surge
(and every time)
because we had to do it every time we filmed
We had to be strict. We had to take care of everything.
The overall budget rose. It went way over the budget
So I talked to to the director, producers,
and people who also work behind the scene like myself
They told me this was a welcome party for new producers
Fortunately, I got to work with the crew of "Secret Crush On You, The Series".
They're all professionals.
They taught me to look from other perspectives,
they told me, "You should try to think differently,"
"you should do this." All those things
I would embrace and think about their suggestions
so that we could take their advice and make-do
And that made "Secret Crush On You", the series you see today.
Let's skip the on-set experiences.
Allow me to talk about the touching moments on the set.
I've been working for 7-8 years. And I never had my own single
I must thank the cast of this series for giving me a solo track
Here are the people who produced the song, the two people here.
- Ready 1, 2, 3!
- Go.
Three times. Let's go.
♪ Wanna be a star Wanna be a star Wanna be a star? Be quiet! ♪
♪ Wanna be a star Wanna be a star Wanna be a star? You goldfish! ♪
♪ Wanna be a star Wanna be a star Wanna be a star? Good job! ♪
♪ Wanna be a star Wanna be a star
Wanna be a star. Character blocking! ♪
(We're glad we get to be a part of
"Secret Crush On You")
Right, last but not least I'd like to thank
all the important people
who have been walking alongside us
all this time, our filming crew and staff
I thank everyone in the team.
I thank P'Chen, P'Chen is the one who
initiated this project.
He dedicates himself to this project.
I want everyone to see how
P'Chen lost his sleep doing this project. He was so determined.
He was living and breathing
for this project
He wanted it to turn out well. He wanted it to be as beautiful
as it could.
He wanted to make everyone happy. He wanted the young talents to make
the best out of this opportunities.
I must thank everyone. I thank P'Cheewin
for giving me all the tips and guidance.
I thank all the producers, directors, and crew members
who gave me advice. Everyone guided me.
Thanks to the cast for putting
their effort to make this project successful.
I'd like to thank everyone
who is involved in this project.
I'd like to thank
the author of this novel for giving us the opportunity
to adapt such a good novel
into a good series.
Lastly, even if there's a book
but there's no reader, this book probably
wouldn't be what it is
But when the readers pick up this book, they add more value to the text
It can also bring happiness, love, smile, laughter, and tears to many people
I thank our readers, our audience
I sincerely thank you all.
for walking with us, for reading this
"book" from the beginning to the end.
I thank you for crying together
and having fun together, like I said before,
I must thank you for staying by my side
I'm truly grateful.
I'd like to thank everyone.
I thank our fans.
I thank you for loving this series.
Also, I'd like to thank
the production team that capture and convey the story
for the audience to see so that we can all enjoy
the series together.
I thank those who initiated this project
for introducing us to get to know one another
and letting me be a part
of Idolfactory family.
I'd like to express my gratitude
to Saint and P'Chen. I have no idea
what they saw in me when we first met.
I didn't even believe in myself but they said they had faith that I could do it
That encouraged me
to break through my limits.
It wasn't easy to step out of my comfort zone to do something
I always felt insecure about. I said, "Could I do this well?" "The character is written well."
But I didn't give up.
I fought side by side with Sky. I told myself that I was chosen,
so I must do my very best to show my appreciation to Sky
who picked me to be him.
This meant more than
an acting role to me.
It's a lifetime experience. It's freaking worthwhile.
Lastly, I would like to thank each and every one
who plays a part in this project.
This includes the production team and all the fans who give us their support.
And thank you all the actors who have been working tirelessly
for the best of this series.
♫ Is this real or am I just dreaming? ♫
♫ The one standing right next to me
is you... the one  ♫
♫ We've been side by side
through the thick and thin ♫
♫ In the end you chose me, is this real? ♫
♫ I'm not as good as anybody else,
but you didn't look past me ♫
♫ You prioritize me in every moment that I need you ♫
♫ You are the one who stands beside me ♫
♫ Even on the day I had no one ♫
♫ I thank you for staying right here every single day ♫
♫ It's like a dream ♫
♫ that I dare not to wish it come true ♫
♫ Everything that happens ♫
♫ Every warmth, Every embrace ♫
♫ How you say you love me dearly
with all your heart ♫
♫ No matter what kind of person I am ♫
♫ You've never disappeared ♫
♫ Away from me ♫
♫  I'm not as good as anybody else,
but you didn't look past me ♫
♫ You prioritize me in every moment that I need you ♫
♫ You are the one who stands beside me ♫
♫ Even on the day I had no one ♫
♫ I thank you for staying right here every single day ♫
♫ It's like a dream ♫
♫ that I dare not to wish it come true ♫
♫ Everything that happens ♫
♪ Every warmth, Every embrace ♪
♫ How you say you love me dearly
with all your heart  ♫
♫ No matter what kind of person I am ♫
♫ You've never disappeared ♫
♫ Away from me ♫
♫ I can't let you know that I'm secretly watching you every day ♫
♫ I won't be able to control it if you start to notice ♫