(Gen Z)
(Episode 22)
It's been some time since I saw you.
Ms Meng
is pregnant.
Really?
The two-child or three-child policy
is the trend nowadays.
Our government is providing
plenty of benefits to them.
Ms Meng always wanted a child.
Now, she's finally pregnant.
-Yeah.
-It's great news.
What are you doing here?
Tomorrow's the weekend.
I was thinking
that I would bring Le Le back with me
and let him spend the weekend with us.
Do you remember the wrong date?
Le Le will only head
to his father's place next week.
I'll send him there by then.
It's just a difference of date.
It's not a big deal
if I bring it forward by one week.
The court gave me custody of Le Le.
And, they also designated time
for his father to visit him.
Besides, I've never	forbidden
you guys from visiting Le Le, right?
But you see,
you came here today to pick the child up
without notifying me.
I don't think I can accept that.
Besides, we already made arrangements
for this weekend.
My baby!
Granny.
Come here.
-Do you miss me?
-Granny.
Granny, I miss you so much.
I miss you too.
Look at what I've brought for you.
I brought your favourite snack.
Oh yeah,
I brought yogurt for you too.
Yogurt.
You must be thirsty.
Let's go.
Le Le, do you like visiting
Granny's house?
Le Le.
Do you like it or not?
I missed you.
-What are you looking at?
-Le Le.
Le Le.
Have you forgotten
our promise with Ms Jian Xi?
She's going to visit us this weekend.
If you go to Granny's place,
we'll be standing her up.
We should be honest
and trustworthy, right?
Le Le,
Long and Yan Yan
will be coming to our house
this weekend.
Didn't you say you missed them?
You love to play with them, right?
Your father even ordered
kids' set meals for you all.
There will be many big sisters
playing games with you guys.
We have a huge castle
and Disney characters too.
Mum, I wish to see
my brothers and sisters.
I'll play with Ms Jian Xi next week.
Goodbye, Mum.
Let's go.
Le Le.
Promise me then.
You have to be a good boy
when you go to Granny's place.
Don't cause trouble, okay?
I promise.
Please look after him then.
Please send him back by Sunday night.
He has school on Monday.
Alright. Don't worry.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
(Quan,)
tell me something.
How much
do you earn per month?
Mum,
I started working not long ago.
I don't earn that much.
(That's why I don't have
a lot of savings.)
(It's like this.)
(There was a cold spell
during late spring.)
(Half of our fry)
(were dead.)
(Our investment went down the drain.)
Your younger brother will be attending
junior high this year.
We need to support him too.
Mum,
I understand now.
Dad,
I'll save up all the money I earn
and send it back to you.
(Dad, Mum,)
I didn't save up much this year.
But I prepared red packets for you two.
Happy Chinese New Year, Dad.
Happy Chinese New Year, Mum.
That's all you have?
So, a doctor doesn't earn much, huh?
Why are you sitting here alone
while pulling a long face?
It's nothing.
Nothing?
I could tell you were troubled.
Tell me.
Even if I tell you, you can't do
anything about it.
How would you know
without telling me in the first place?
It's about my future.
I stopped looking for other jobs
after I joined the apprentice class.
I never expected the apprentice class
to face suspension.
I'll cease to be a fresh graduate
by the end of this year.
It'll be tough for me to get a job.
It's not as serious as you think.
When one door shuts, another opens.
Yeah, it opens for you.
Not for me.
You don't understand how I feel
when you're not in my shoes.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
Let me do it.
It's fine. We can do it together.
Ms Dong,
I assume you've heard about the issue
our apprentice class is facing.
Mr Ren told me about it.
Great things take time.
Mr Ren
is trying to contribute to our nation
and its people here.
He's not doing it for his sake.
The apprentice class
will be fine.
You're making the apprentice class
sound like a noble thing.
It may look
insignificant now.
However, it'll affect
the entire environment in the future.
What do you mean?
You see,
Mr Ren
graduated from a professional course
and got himself a mentor too.
He held this class
in hopes
that people can be more aware
of their health
and learn
how to care for their wellness.
Don't you think
he's contributing to the nation
and its people here?
At least it can help people
to save on medical insurance.
Don't panic.
There will surely be a solution to this.
I realise
that you're calmer than Mr Ren.
It's because I know
God is testing him
whether he has enough determination
to proceed with this.
Once he overcomes these obstacles,
he'll be able to overcome all of them.
And, there will surely be someone
who will help him on his journey.
Ms Dong, I'm not
as optimistic as you.
Ms Dong,
I've studied TCM
for over a year now.
I know the teachers who taught us
are amazing.
However,
I only understood the meaning of life
after learning from you.
I also saved people with
the techniques you taught.
I don't know about the others,
but I know
it's time
for me to do this.
That's why I wish
you can take me in
as your disciple
so that I can learn techniques from you.
Even if the apprentice class
is cancelled,
I can come here every day
and learn from you.
I believe that I have
strong learning capabilities.
I'm sure I can inherit your techniques
if I work hard enough.
What about the rest of
your classmates then?
That's on them.
Everyone has their own destiny.
Since you're saying that,
that means
you're not ready
to be my disciple yet.
I can't take you in.
But why?
It doesn't feel right.
Ms Dong,
you once said
that feeling is the core
of your techniques.
Senior Master also said
that the most important part
in learning TCM
is to follow your feeling
and travel with the flow.
However, what does "feeling" mean?
You know this. I'm a rational person.
To me,
it's something mysterious
and untouchable.
Have you been in love before?
To be honest, no.
I think falling in love
is a waste of my energy and time.
And, it also impedes me from improving.
Initially, I plan to stay single
for the rest of my life.
But now, I'm willing to get married
in order to get a child.
The "feeling" we mention,
it refers to Hexagram 31, Conjoining,
from the Book of Changes.
All beings are born from the conjoining
of Heaven and Earth.
It refers to the moments
when young boys and girls
encounter each other.
You've already missed out on
that moment.
Therefore,
it's hard for you to imagine
how wonderful it is
for people to spend time
with each other
without any ulterior motives.
You cannot imagine the feelings
I described.
On a human body,
there are Heaven and Earth.
There are peaks and rivers.
There's a galaxy in it.
It's because you blocked off
the path.
You're confusing me
here.
Don't tell me a single woman
cannot study TCM?
Don't tell me a person
who has never been in love
cannot pass down the legacy of TCM?
I just hope
that you can unblock
your path of emotion.
When you do so,
you'll detect people's kindness.
Sometimes,
it's not just other people's kindness
that can touch your heart.
It might be their appreciation
for the peaks,
rivers,
flora and fauna.
All these experiences
will make your heart skip a beat
and make you shed tears of joy.
You won't be able to experience them
without unblocking the path of emotion.
This "feeling" we mention,
it's more than just love.
It also refers
to a grateful heart.
Do you know what's gratefulness?
The grace of dripping water should be
reciprocated by a gushing spring.
When people
treat you nicely,
you have to return the favour
instead of just accepting it blindly.
When you can detect
other people's kindness
and reciprocate the act,
you've established
a path of Yin and Yang
that resembles a cycle.
It's the same for my techniques.
First, a patient is a human.
Once you establish
an emotional connection with them,
when you're able
to detect the cycle of Yin and Yang,
only then will you be able to
decode the message
on his body.
When it comes to applying techniques
and being a doctor,
the most important thing
is to devote yourself to the act
from the bottom of your heart.
Love is the strongest power
within the galaxy.
(It's the same for life.)
You only care about
accumulating knowledge.
You don't disperse
or implement your knowledge.
You'll surely be crushed.
In and out,
Yin and Yang,
that is the way.
(When it comes to applying techniques)
(and being a doctor,)
the most important thing
is to devote yourself to the act
from the bottom of your heart.
(Love is the strongest power)
(within the galaxy.)
Cheng Ying, thank you
for taking care of Jian Xi.
Why are you being so courteous?
I'm alone during the weekends anyway.
When she's here,
at least I have someone to talk to.
Now, it's strawberry season.
Ms Song said
strawberries could invigorate
the spleen and nourish the lungs.
Let Le Le eat more of them.
Thank you so much.
You shouldn't be so courteous
in the future.
You always bring things with you
whenever you visit me.
-You're too kind.
-It's what I should do.
I know the medical centre is busy.
But how's the apprentice class?
The medical centre is doing pretty well.
But the apprentice class
is facing a major crisis.
Professor Ren pulls
a long face every day.
Although he never smiled
when he was together with us,
we could feel
that he's in a bad mood this time.
He might be stressed out.
He has to take care
of so many students after all.
If so, I'll wash the strawberries first.
-Le Le isn't back yet?
-Almost.
They said they were on their way.
Who is it?
So, it's our baby.
Our precious boy is back.
Hi, Auntie.
Hi, Le Le. You're so polite.
Le Le.
Hi, Ms Jian Xi.
Ms Jian Xi, look.
I took all of these pictures.
Le Le, you had fun, huh?
Where did Granny take you?
Granny took us to a huge hotel.
There was a huge lawn.
There were swans too.
Le Le,
where did you get this camera?
Auntie Qian Qian gave it to me.
Auntie Qian Qian?
So, Le Le, you attended a wedding?
Look, he wore a suit.
You're so dashing.
Dad married Auntie Qian Qian.
I was their ring bearer.
Granny said I was
the most handsome guy around.
Mum.
Le Le.
Didn't you spend the weekend
at Granny's place?
No. Granny took me
to Dad's new house.
He told me and Da Long
to roll around on Dad's bed.
Yue Liang and Yan Yan
aren't living together.
But Granny told me
that my younger sister
was inside Auntie Qian Qian's tummy.
I'll be a big brother soon.
Mum, what's wrong?
Go and wash your hands.
Auntie Zhu Xia bought you
some strawberries.
Go now.
Thank you, Auntie.
You're welcome.
Xia,
I don't think I'll keep you guys around
for dinner tonight.
Let's meet again next week.
You should return with Jian Xi.
Cheng Ying,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
That man is no longer related to me.
Alright. We'll make a move first.
Listen.
That Liu Chang Qing
is truly infuriating.
Tian Zhen almost died
in order
to harvest the rare ginseng.
But now, he's saying
that he can't find it.
How could someone like him exist?
Enough.
Stop complaining about him.
He has no obligations
to help us out.
He did it out of compassion.
No one
expected this to happen.
It must be fate.
I think you're right.
This might be fate.
Maybe fate is telling you
to cancel the apprentice class.
Think about it.
Ever since you started the class,
there were issues
every day.
I think this is pretty good.
We can cancel the apprentice class
and let the students
return to their normal lives.
Master,
Madam,
I must continue
holding the apprentice class.
Maybe fate is telling me
to seek another path.
Please don't worry.
I'll definitely figure out a solution.
Why didn't you notify me
when it was such a huge deal?
Cheng Ying,
what's the matter?
(You told my son)
to be his father's ring bearer
and to roll on his bed.
What gives you the right to do so?
Did you get my permission?
Why did I need your permission?
Besides, didn't I tell you
that I was going to bring Le Le home
so that we could spend
the weekend together?
But you didn't tell me
that you were bringing him
to attend his father's wedding.
(It makes no difference.)
Besides,
you found out, right?
(We didn't notify you)
(because we were afraid
that you might be infuriated.)
Look at how you're responding to it.
This is bad for your health.
Do you think you could get away with it
just because you didn't tell me?
Listen up.
From now on,
you'll never get to see your grandson.
What do you mean by that?
You're strange.
Le Le is my grandson.
I can see him whenever I like.
Why are you stopping me now?
You guys better stop crossing the line.
Your son was the one who betrayed me
and our family first.
(Cheng Ying,)
(I know my son had let you down.)
(But now,)
(we have given you the house)
and our money.
You even got custody of my grandson.
(Now, my son has a new family.)
(Cheng Ying,)
(you need to learn how to
get over the past.)
(You still need)
(to live on.)
And, I don't care
if you like my son or not.
Your son
will have a younger sister.
They're a family.
You cannot
deny that fact.
Fine.
Since you're getting
a granddaughter soon,
you can treat it as if
you don't have a grandson.
(From now on,)
the Feng family
should stay away from my son.
I won't allow you guys to approach him.
And, listen.
My son is the sole child of the family.
He doesn't have a younger sister
when I say so!
This...
She must've lost her mind.
Hello?
Hello, Le Le's Mum.
I have something to tell you.
From now on,
no one else
is allowed to pick Le Le up
except for me.
Not even his father
or his grandmother?
They picked Le Le up before.
(Especially them.)
If I find out
that they take my son away,
I'll call the cops on them.
You see, our kindergarten
cannot make that call.
Why don't you two talk this over?
(You guys should sign an agreement)
(that states that only his mother)
can pick him up.
You have to provide us
with written evidence
before we can follow your instructions,
don't you think so?
Ms Zhang,
you're a woman too.
How could you side with them?
(You misunderstood me.)
(I'm not siding with anyone here.)
I just think
that our kindergarten
cannot make the call here.
You see,
(why don't you)
(discuss it)
(with his father again?)
(We shouldn't let the conflicts
between adults)
(affect the kids, don't you think so?)
Hello?
-Sell the house?
Yes.
I wish to sell the house.
Once I have cash in hand,
I can hold the apprentice class
like normal.
Which house are you selling?
Where did you get the house?
It's our house.
Our house?
You didn't pay a single cent
from its purchase
to its renovation.
How dare you say
that you want to sell it?
I give him my permission.
I did fork out the sum.
That's useless.
Your name isn't on
the property ownership certificate.
Ling Lan,
you mustn't be so narrow-minded.
Your husband, which is my student,
will achieve something phenomenal.
We're his
assistants.
In the future, if he manages
to raise great students
and if his name goes down in history,
your name
will also go down in history
as you're his wife.
Tell me then.
Confucius's name
goes down in history, right?
Do you know
the name of his wife?
He had 3,000 disciples, you know?
He didn't have one.
He was divorced.
I guess he got divorced
after selling the house.
Times have changed.
Now, the apprentice class
is facing a crisis.
I can't just let my class
be disbanded
after putting in so much effort
to bring them together.
Even so, you can't just
think about the apprentice class.
What about our son?
Our son is at the age
when he should get married.
Tell me then.
Which lady
is willing
to get married into
a family
that doesn't even own a house?
Tian Zhen has
a great family inheritance.
We've provided him
with quality education.
However, if he's sponging off
his parents just to seek a partner,
he can
forget about getting married then.
Ling Lan is right.
Your son is a grown-up now.
He'll definitely care about his dignity.
We can't just
live without a house.
Now, you're siding with
the right person.
If so, he can sell my house.
Dad!
Only my name and your mother's name
are on the
property ownership certificate.
I'm giving him my permission.
You have nothing to complain about now.
I...
Mum.
He's the head
of the family.
Yang leads while Yin follows.
I make small decisions
while your father makes
important decisions.
The three of you are over 200 years old
combined.
How could you guys be so wilful?
Think about it.
Where should we stay
if we sell this house?
Your disciple is staying with us too.
Where will she stay then?
We won't live on the streets.
When we were young,
your mother, me,
Master,
our parents,
and our siblings,
the ten of us
lived in a 30m² house.
Even so, we managed to pull through.
Ling Lan,
you have it
too easy.
You're unlike your mother at all.
Your mother
is a dauntless woman.
She can cope with both happy days
and unhappy days.
When it comes to that,
Xin Zheng,
your wife is
inferior to mine.
Why don't you divorce me?
What are you saying?
Get me the property
ownership certificate.
Mum.
Mum, are you serious?
Of course.
Master,
I'm sorry.
Although I'm passing down
our legacy,
you still have
to bear responsibility for my decisions.
That's not true.
It's a test.
Our ancestors are in the sky.
They're observing us.
They want to see how determined we are
to pass down our legacy
to the next generation.
The current society
is too impatient.
They rush everything.
Speed is of the essence.
Just look at our community.
There are three real estate agencies
and four smartphone shops.
However, we're the only ones
who open a medical centre.
We operate it for two decades.
And,
we do our best in
nurturing future talents.
It takes ten years to nurture a tree,
but a hundred years to train a man.
I'll be 100 years old soon.
I'm going to impart everything I have
to you.
Just focus on your mission
and pass down our legacy.
Thank you, Master.
Alright.
Dear,
don't panic.
We're capable people.
We can make money
whenever we like.
When do you feel like making money then?
Do you think I don't want
to pass down the legacy of TCM?
to continue holding
the apprentice class?
I don't agree with your decision
to sell the house
because I think
it's wrong
from the start.
Think about it.
You're a renowned figure in society.
And, you're leading such a poor life
at this age.
What do you think your students
will think about you?
Do you think any good talents
will come to you?
Those who are sensible
will learn how to invest
from Warren Buffett instead.
99% of his fortune
are made
after the age of 60.
Dear,
we have to take the righteous path.
Only then, the way of the world
will be preserved.
We need to be friends with time.
We have to be able
to withstand loneliness.
As doctors,
we can't just work to make a living.
If there's a talented student
who wishes to take the path
to quick riches,
I will
never take him under my wing.
People who wish to study TCM
must be focused wholeheartedly.
They see that I'm having a rough time.
Even so,
they don't leave me.
That's what you call a great student.
For those who know
that Warren Buffett has
tens of billions of dollars
but never know
that he's donated his fortune,
I'm sure they won't be able
to master the art of investment.
If they come
to study TCM under me,
I'll reject them.
That's right.
We should learn from farmers.
For farmers,
it's no pain, no gain.
Sometimes, they might not gain
even after experiencing pain.
Even so, they still do their work.
That's the way of Heaven.
That's the path we need to take.
Coming.
I heard that women
are good at stashing money away.
Didn't you buy other houses in secret?
Honest people like me
don't do such things.
Wait.
Are you sure about that?
Is this the only house you own?
Master, Madam,
I cannot take your house.
I was just joking with you.
Humans only take up five feet
when they lie down.
Five feet is enough for us.
Ling Lan,
you can provide for me when I grow old.
Of course she'll provide for you.
What nonsense are you saying?
Give it to me.
No, I won't.
He can provide for you.
Thank you, Master,
Madam.
Are you sure you don't blame me for it?
Your daughter chose her husband herself.
And, you chose our successor yourself.
Now, both of you are my family.
I'll submit to fate.
A bet is a bet.
Aren't you afraid
that I might be wrong about him?
It's not like Xin Zheng is going
to indulge in worldly pleasures
with the money.
He's going to hold a class.
Sometimes,
they fail.
Sometimes, they succeed.
It has nothing to do with his character.
However,
it has everything to do
with his capability.
Aren't you worried
about his capability?
Let me ask you this then.
What does a TCM practitioner treat?
Of course it's illnesses.
To think that you're a renowned
TCM practitioner.
It's people.
I wasn't wrong about you
when I was young,
let alone now.
Listen.
Xin Zheng
will achieve something phenomenal.
He'll be the next guru of our era.
You should say that
to your daughter
so that she won't
give my disciple a hard time.
No, I won't.
But why?
Do you like it when they argue?
A man who cannot withstand
his wife's petty behaviour
cannot achieve success.
I believe in Xin Zheng.
Moreover,
society is much crueller
than his wife.
Aren't you embarrassed?
You're still sponging off
the elders at this age.
I have no choice.
I'm not that capable myself.
Sell my house then.
Return my parents' house to them.
No.
Are you trying to go against me?
If I sell their house,
Master and Madam
won't make things difficult for me.
But if I sell your house,
you'll make things difficult for me
every day.
I was going to do that anyway.
This doesn't make any difference.
Give it to me.
Thank you!
You should return
the property ownership certificate
to Master.
I don't want him to find out this early.
I'm going to tease him for a few days.
I'll give you a suggestion.
You should treat me better.
You see,
I'm a renowned figure too.
I have millions of fans
on Weibo.
And, I have plenty of female disciples.
You shouldn't feel threatened by them.
Say that again?
I'm just worried that you might
lose your sense of security.
Is there any female disciple
who will sell her house for you
so that you can sustain the class?
If so, please tell me immediately.
I'll pack you up
and send you
to her with no hesitations.
I'll even fork out the delivery fee.
And,
the goods are non-refundable.
The delivery fee is pretty expensive,
you know?
I can at least afford that.
(As the temperature rises,
the snow melts.)
(Rain gradually increases. This solar
term is known as Rain Water.)
(On such days, married daughters
usually visit their parents.)
(Rain Water)
(Qibo Medical Centre)
-Here.
-Thank you.
Tian Zhen,
Professor Ren has been
staring at that map
for a few days.
Even now, he hasn't found a place yet.
That shouldn't be the case.
Professor Ren
is a famous physician.
I'm sure he has a lot of
local connections.
If he makes a call,
I'm sure everyone else will answer it.
Ms Xia, you have no idea.
My father and Senior Uncle
take two different paths.
He doesn't like to
entertain rich people.
He always leaves them
to Senior Uncle.
He only treats the poor.
He cannot seek help from the rich
as they're not close to him.
He cannot seek help from the poor
as he can't bear to beg them.
In the end,
it's all Liu Chang Qing's fault.
When I think about it...
Zhu Xia,
another two students from the
apprentice class have applied for leave.
If so, we have to rearrange
the schedule then.
Yeah.
A lot of them have applied
for leave lately.
I think we need to hire a professional
to brew herbal remedies.
We should.
We can't just expect our students
to do it all.
I'll leave this to you then.
Don't worry.
Meng Meng, what are you doing?
I'm washing Tou Tou.
-Zhao.
-Ms Xia.
You won't leave, right?
Even if we're going to
recruit new people,
we won't be able to get them
to work immediately.
Since you're a professional,
you mustn't leave us, okay?
Ms Xia, the others are
only applying for leave
as they have other
opportunities out there.
You should stay here
and work for us.
It's pretty good here.
You see,
you can join your mentors
during consultations sessions
after three to five years.
After that, you can do your rounds
as a physician
after another three to five years.
By then,
you would be the best
at your field.
You would be recognised
for your capability.
Ms Xia,
although that's the case,
life is
unpredictable.
You see,
if the medical centre couldn't find
another pharmacist as good as me,
I might have to work here
for the rest of my life.
But you see,
I have
a Physician's Practice License.
Am I right?
You'll be worse than me then.
I can travel the world
and treat patients
after five years.
Successor, you're the best indeed.
We have different backgrounds.
Life is different for all of us.
It's tough for everyone.
Tou Tou.
Jian Xi.
Stop looking around.
I'm the only one here.
Let go of me.
Let me show you something. Come with me.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
(As Meritorious As
A Good Prime Minister)
Liu Zi Hong!
Help!
Calm down!
You!
How could you fall out with me
just like that?
-Stop.
-I'm here to deliver this treasure.
Why are you biting the hand
that feeds you?
Stop! Quiet down!
I thought you already changed your ways?
Why are you so violent today?
I promise
I won't kill you today.
Zhao Li Quan.
It's your turn.
Meng Meng, go ahead.
Go now.
Seems like there's a fungal infection
in your lungs.
Look, it has already spread
until here.
Why are you only here now?
I've been taking anti-fungal treatments
overseas
for over two years.
It keeps coming back.
At first,
they gave me Voriconazole.
But I couldn't stand it.
I threw up whenever
they gave me the shot.
You threw up?
Yes.
After that, they changed
my prescription.
They gave me medicine to take orally.
I took it for over a month.
But it wasn't
too effective.
I've taken so many medications
to date.
Now, the doctors suggest me
to go for surgery.
I wish to give it another try.
That's why
I flew across the globe
to seek you out.
How did you hear about me?
I read
Learning TCM, which was written by you.
It contains cases
similar to mine.
They had the same condition.
And, you treated them.
That's why I came to seek you out.
Madam Ba Li.
My surname is Bai.
My name is Jasmine.
(Bai Mo Li)
You can call me Mo Li (Jasmine).
Mo Li?
That's right.
Bai Mo Li, huh?
Just like jasmine flowers.
(The prescriptions and remedies
used in this drama)
(are referenced from relevant
traditional Chinese medicine books)
(Do not use without medical advice)
(End of Episode 22)