(Gen Z)
(Episode 9)
Tian Zhen,
call her family member.
Tell him to bring their child here
to see her one last time.
Okay.
Professor Ren!
Holding onto me won't help you.
Master,
I just saw a dead person
for the first time in my life.
What are you looking at?
You scared me.
You took the words out of my mouth!
I'm exhausted.
Besides giving patients diagnoses,
I have to stay on my toes
because of you.
I'll bring the cops to you
when they're here.
Cheng Ying isn't dead.
Why did you lie to her?
You did great today.
When you first came in,
I thought you would run around,
shouting that she wasn't dead.
Am I that stupid to you?
Although I don't know
why you're doing this,
I know we're on the same side.
I have to play my part well.
Don't you think so?
My master was right indeed.
Even a dense person
can become intelligent.
That was respectable.
What do you mean by that?
Get me a cup of water.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
Professor Ren,
if they do arrest me,
can I entrust Jian Xi to you?
In my life,
there's no Ding Jian Xi.
She's your daughter.
Okay.
If so,
I'll apologise to them.
I'll kneel
and kowtow to them.
I'll give them all my money.
I'm fine with anything
as long as they let me off
and let me take care of Jian Xi.
Why are you expecting them
to let you off?
Cheng Ying bumped into
your daughter, right?
She's dead, right?
What else can I do?
You're giving them all of your money?
How will you save your daughter by then?
As long as
she's alive,
I'll find a way to save her
even if it means that I have to sell
my house, even my kidneys.
Don't do that. Please get up.
Professor Ren,
you're a benevolent person.
You have a benevolent mind and heart.
Can you take me and my daughter in?
I can do anything.
I was once an accountant.
I can work as an admin.
I can even be your janitor.
I'll do anything you ask me to do
as long as you take me
and my daughter in.
You'll be imprisoned soon.
How could you work here?
Do you have any relatives?
If you do, you should contact them.
How will I deal with your daughter
after the cops arrest you?
Hurry and make your decision.
What should I do?
I'll be imprisoned soon!
If I die now,
I have no one to entrust my daughter to!
Cheng Ying isn't dead.
Get up.
She's not dead?
She's not dead.
I checked on her just now.
She's alive.
It's just that she's seriously ill.
She's not dead.
Really?
Really.
I get to decide whether she dies or not
when I'm around.
Professor Ren,
I'm begging you.
Please save her
on the account of my daughter.
Alright.
Get up.
Come.
Be careful.
Have some water.
Do you still hate her?
You felt pure joy after
experiencing pure sadness.
How do you feel?
Let me ask you something.
Did you ever think about
joining your husband
when he departed from the world?
When one is dead,
nothing will be left.
Your source of hatred and grudge
will be gone.
What if you departed together with him?
What will Jian Xi do then?
Alright. You've already gotten through
the worst moment in your life.
Anger
makes slaves of people.
When you get angry,
you'll become your own slave.
We forgive people
to face
our conscience.
It's not like you've lost everything.
You still have Jian Xi,
right?
Have you found your tile?
Look at you. You have been
spending all your energy
on trying to sue people, demanding money
and cursing them out.
What will Jian Xi do then?
I'll look for it.
I must save Jian Xi.
That's why you should spend your energy
on the things that matter.
When you were angry,
you forgot that
Jian Xi was by your side.
What if Li Quan didn't save her?
What if the wheelchair fell?
Have you ever thought of
the consequences?
Forgiving people means
forgiving yourself.
You have to let go.
You must be starving.
Jian Xi hasn't eaten yet.
Yeah.
"Aiding with the Best Medicine"
Mr Ren.
Something's up?
Yes.
I hope you can do me a favour.
Thank you for what you did today.
It was my job.
What is it? Tell me.
My parents want
to celebrate the Dragon Boat Festival
here with me.
Before this, I told them that...
Stop hesitating.
Speak up.
Before this, I told them
that I already found a job.
So,
can you tell them that I'm working here
if you see them?
Can you tell them I'm a staff here?
Why would our medical centre
even hire staff in the first place?
I know that's not the case.
But can you tell them that?
You want me to lie to them?
Listen.
I never lie.
And, I will never lie for your sake.
Once you lie, you need to lie ten times
to cover up your first lie.
If you wish to obtain something,
you must strive to obtain it.
Do not rely on expediency.
Understood?
Sorry for being late.
I couldn't recognise you in this outfit.
What kind of outfit is this?
I don't like the smell of kitchen fumes.
Sorry then, Ms Yang.
You haven't ordered any food yet, right?
Listen,
the roasted kidneys here
are amazing.
I... I forgot.
You're a vegetarian.
Their roasted chives and mushrooms
are great too.
Don't order food for me.
I waited until now
to reject you directly.
The tuition class between us
is over.
Okay? Let's go on our separate ways.
What are you doing?
Return my bag to me.
You can keep this bag
with me first.
I'll return it to you once
the tuition class is over.
-You!
-Madam!
Give us ten roasted lamb skewers,
ten roasted kidney skewers,
one roasted mushroom skewer
and one roasted chives skewer.
-Just like the usual.
-Alright.
Didn't I tell you already?
I'm not eating.
Don't order anything for me.
I don't take junk food.
I ordered them for myself.
Delicious.
It's a shame that
you're not trying them.
Let me tell you this.
I came here today
because I thought it was closer
to your hospital.
But it won't happen again.
Yeah, yeah.
But according to
my limited life experience,
only bars and roasted skewer stalls
are still open at this hour.
Bars are too loud.
I don't think we can hold
our tuition class there.
Can't you change it
to another time then?
I'm having tuition classes
during my night shifts
so that I can head to the medical centre
during my rest days.
Alright.
Let's begin.
You're taking
something this oily and salty at night.
Your lifestyle is so unhealthy.
Just finish your yogurt
and be done with your preaching.
You're a doctor, you know?
I study Western medicine.
However, I'm giving you tuition
regarding TCM.
TCM focuses on wellness.
Focusing on one's wellness should be
prioritized above treating illnesses.
So, according to your TCM theories,
at this time, you should
leave your phone in the living room
and lie on the bed, right?
You're staying up to teach me about TCM.
I can only repay you
with such a method.
For this chapter,
we focus on
the relationship between
one's nature, heart, and body.
According to Mr Ren,
even if we do retain our fitness,
we're only 10% there.
The other 40% comes from
the health of one's mentality.
And, the one leading our health
is the health of our nature.
Look.
I'm right, aren't I?
TCM and Western medicine
are finally coming together.
One's diet isn't important at all.
If I do die early, it must be
due to a lack of sexual activities.
That wasn't what I was referring to.
It means disposition
and spirituality.
It's an element
that's above one's heart.
It's the inner core of life.
According to
Yellow Emperor's Inner Classic,
somatic and spiritual harmony
are of utmost importance.
A healthy body
requires a fit physical body
and a healthy state of mind.
We should be tranquil
and have a sound mind.
That's what I meant by nature.
Our teacher said this during our class.
Language represents
the evolution of thoughts.
What were you thinking about?
I'm just here to give you a tuition.
Fine. Seems like you're done
with studying anyway.
-It's over.
-You're angry now?
You're a lawyer, right?
You're studying TCM too.
Being emotional is detrimental to us.
You cannot be emotional
when you're in the court.
When it comes to studying TCM,
we need to be indifferent
when we're happy, angry, sad, or joyful.
Only then, we can retain our hearts.
What do you think? I did do my homework.
I'm not angry.
I just want to head back
and take my beauty sleep.
Alright.
I apologise to you sincerely.
You're both a great teacher
and a great student.
It was tough for you to teach me.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a good student.
If I were one, I wouldn't
need to study TCM.
But why?
I learned many things in the past.
I excelled in all of them.
But even now, I still don't understand
the meaning of life.
In the past, I strove to improve myself
to make my mother happy.
I worked hard to make money
so that I could sustain her life.
But after her passing,
I suddenly realised
that making money and improving myself
were pointless.
Do you know something?
Some time ago,
the opposing lawyer of a lawsuit
fell unconscious in front of me.
He died just like that.
After that, I thought about
all the law articles I learned.
Why did I learn them in the first place?
Mr Ren was right.
Even if you're knowledgeable,
that doesn't mean you're cultured.
We transform people through culture.
Forget about transforming other people.
I can't even transform myself.
You're transforming me right now.
I'm not that capable.
You're a stubborn soul.
You're taking junk food
in the middle of the night.
I have a good nature.
I'm broad-minded.
I don't take things too seriously.
That's the root of good health.
Broad-minded, huh?
Explain why you came
to cause trouble for our class
and got into a fight
with a patient's family member.
Why do you know all of my secrets?
How did you know that I was a spy?
It wasn't a secret at all.
Mr Ren knew it from
the day you joined us.
You were scrolling your phone
during class.
And, you kept causing arguments.
I'll be honest with you.
I only came here to give you tuition
because of Mr Ren.
If not, do you think
I'll waste my time with you here?
Mr Ren knew about it?
Of course.
If so, why did he still send you here?
Mr Ren
has placed himself and his lesson
on a microscope for you to see.
Western medicine focuses on
the patient's illness
while TCM focuses on the sick person.
You can cause an argument
and create trouble all you want.
But Mr Ren intends
to cure you of your rowdy nature.
Madam,
get me another bottle of yogurt.
-Okay.
-Get me a sugar-free yogurt.
Coming.
What are you doing here?
Did you tail me?
You...
You know how to ride skateboards?
I know plenty of things.
Ren Tian Zhen.
This is pretty cool.
I want to learn this too.
You want to learn
how to ride skateboards?
Yeah.
-Really?
-Yeah.
But I don't feel like teaching you.
If you don't teach me,
I'll tell your parents
and grandparents
that you're playing with something
as dangerous as this.
It's very dangerous.
It's lethal and dangerous.
I'll tell them right away.
Are you a primary school student?
You want to complain
to your teacher now?
Go ahead then. You'll be exposed
for joining me too.
That's fine.
I'm parentless anyway.
No one is keeping me in check.
But it's different for someone else.
You're their beloved baby.
Your grandparents will surely nag you
after they find out.
You have to stand there
and endure their nagging
without talking back.
If Meng Meng sees that,
-Stop!
-as a man...
Stop.
I'll teach you.
But you have to swear.
Only you and I know about this.
Never tell a single soul about this.
I swear I'll never tell a single soul.
If you break your promise,
may you starve for
the rest of your life.
That's pretty brutal.
I promise. When will you teach me?
Meng Meng's medicine is ready, right?
What medicine?
Oh no!
Remember to teach me next time!
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Hello, Madam.
-Hello.
-Madam,
I'm here to pick up my parcel.
I'm Xiao Ming from Dorm 312.
312, Xiao Ming.
Here.
-Thank you, Madam.
-You're welcome.
Hello, Madam.
Hello.
What's the matter?
I guess
we have another power outage.
What's going on?
The power tripped again?
We have another power outage?
Sorry about that.
Open the door!
Hide! Hurry up!
Why did the power trip again?
Coming.
You must've used something
that you were not supposed to.
I knew it.
Didn't I say that you couldn't
bring this here?
You were actually
cooking dumplings here?
Sorry, Madam. I was starving.
I won't do it again.
I'll never do it again.
-Okay?
-How many times have I told you?
Yes, Madam.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Madam.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
You were chased out?
Where are you staying then?
I found a cheap place online.
One day costs around 30 to 40 yuan.
Can you take a bath there?
Take a bath?
I'm lucky enough
to find a place to stay.
It's easy for you to make remarks
when you're on the sideline.
I'll find a place for you.
See?
When you want to sleep, just bring
this bed to the storeroom.
This is inappropriate.
What's inappropriate about it?
I'll be here for you
if you get into trouble.
Besides, you're truly stubborn.
If I were you, I would try to be
a medical assistant here
and survive first.
You and I are different.
Say, if I do work in this medical centre
like my other seniors,
even if I do get my own
consultation office after ten years,
do you think people will
seek my service after that?
In this industry,
value comes with age.
You're different.
You had a silver-spoon upbringing.
You grew up in an esteemed family.
No matter which mentor you get,
they're the cream of the crop.
But me?
I can only say this for myself.
If one of the mentors
takes a liking to me,
and if I learn under him,
maybe I can be independent
after five years.
Tell me then.
What will I do
if I don't depend on the medical centre?
Free opportunities for people
to learn under a mentor
were created for people like me,
you know?
These are the keys
to the medical centre.
Just remember
to bring the bed back and hide it here
before work hours.
Got it.
You don't intend to thank me?
Thank you so much.
You're too courteous.
Why did you transfer money to me again?
I made some pocket money
when I joined Grandpa
in his consultations.
Of course I need to share
good things with my buddy.
Your grandfather actually
split the money with you?
Nope. It's all mine.
We had a promise.
He'll work for me as long as
I'm willing to join him
in his consultations.
If so, I won't stand on ceremony then.
There's no need to stand on ceremony.
Mr Ren.
What are you two doing here?
We're here on cleaning duties.
So, you don't need tools for that?
We'll get them at once.
-Mr Wu.
Kid.
How did it go?
You must've received
the invitation by now.
I received it yesterday.
Fellow Zhang will be
the honorary chairman this year.
You will be our main speaker.
I still want Huang Wei
to be our speaker.
You should give
the younger generations a chance.
Which student do you intend
to bring with you?
Tian Zhen, Li Quan,
and Sun Tou Tou.
Sun Tou Tou?
Do you think someone will take her in?
Were you referring to Sun Tou Tou?
Sun Tou Tou
is the successor of the Jiang family's
acupuncture sect after all.
She already assumed her position.
She has to go there no matter what.
I'm just worried that she might
bring disgrace to TCM Acupuncture.
This is TCM Acupuncture's
first appearance.
Just look at her primitive behaviour.
What do you think people
will say about you
and TCM Acupuncture?
That's their business.
It's her business whether she can become
a worthy successor or not.
It's my business
whether I bring her there or not.
We all have our parts to do.
You're making it too simple here.
You can afford to take it lightly
since you don't have any position.
Now, I'm attending the forum
as the academy's principal.
But you?
You're trying to link my academy
with your so-called students,
which have complicated backgrounds.
What do you think people will say
about our industry as a whole?
Besides, you shouldn't forget.
I'm holding on to this position
for your sake.
You have to consider my feelings.
That's your business.
But...
I'm sure it's everyone's business
to maintain our reputation, right?
Reputation, huh?
Meng Meng,
sesame seeds
are good for injuries and deficiencies.
It also nourishes the five viscera.
Try it.
It's nice, right?
This is for Wu Jun.
He has to get twice the dosage.
Ms Xia?
So,
Jian Xi's follow-up visit
is in two days, right?
What are you guys doing here today?
Not only will we come today,
but we'll also come here every day.
What do you mean?
Ms Xia, listen.
Sometimes, you need to let go.
Calm down.
I'm not here to stir up trouble.
I'm here to help.
I told Professor Ren
that I worked as an accountant before.
From today onward,
I will work as a volunteer here.
Today's my first day of work.
Really?
I never heard about that.
Weren't you here too back then?
If so, have you stopped
looking for the tiles?
Of course not.
I've already hired someone
to inquire about them for me.
I'll depart immediately
once I receive any news.
By then, I will leave Jian Xi...
-No problem.
-Meng Meng.
Meng Meng.
It'll be fine. Go now.
Come here.
Meng Meng.
Meng Meng, come here.
I'm not here to fight today.
I must've scared you guys back then.
Not at all.
Go now. It'll be fine.
I'm not here to fight.
Everything's fine.
Don't be scared.
Zhu Xia, you're here?
Dr Song.
Who's afraid?
Listen.
That's right.
This ledger contains
this month's records.
Take it.
Take a close look.
Yes. Meng Meng loves to draw.
Familiarize yourself with our accounts.
I'll leave this to you then.
Now that I'm here,
you don't need to worry.
Jian Xi.
Dr Song.
Say,
she did change a lot.
This is amazing.
Your master is amazing, right?
He's pretty amazing.
Meng Meng, that looked great.
(Plantable grains)
(lose their effectiveness
after this season.)
(This solar term)
(is the time when the South plants
grains and the North harvests wheat.)
(Grain in Ear)
TCM is the manifestation of the term
"technique and integrity".
However, without integrity, you can't
make it far with technique alone.
Even if you have excellent
medical skills,
without harmony between nature and men
and a broad philosophical view,
you won't be able to understand
the meaning of "integrity"
when it comes to medical skills.
That's the difference between
TCM and Western medicine.
In my opinion,
Western medicine will
develop into a detailed
and meticulous field.
As for TCM,
it should develop in
a broader direction.
For our lesson today,
we'll talk about
the largest disharmony in humans.
What is it?
It's disharmony between humans.
Everyone,
do you know who's the star of
our TCM industrial park?
Who?
It's Ren Xin Zheng.
Professor Ren?
He's pretty famous.
What? Is he here?
We are friends for many years.
Now, he's hosting a class
at my place.
He's the representative figure
of our industrial park.
He's hosting a class?
We plan to build
a first-class national
TCM talent training centre.
Right now, the projects that
occupy most of your land here
aren't in the direction
we're investing in.
They lack Internet thinking.
Besides,
building a school
was a great way to develop
one's land in the last century.
But to put it bluntly,
it'll take a long time
before we can gain profit from it.
Great minds think alike indeed.
We're implementing Internet thinking.
The class is free.
We attract talents first.
We've invited many renowned figures
to teach here.
Once news of this gets out,
those who wish
to join the TCM industry
have to join us
before they can establish
a foothold in the industry.
We can brag about this shamelessly.
This is
a business academy for TCM.
Other business academies
earn hundreds of thousands easily.
But your academy is offering
classes for free.
How could you compare yourself to them?
When we're emotional,
when we have hatred in our hearts,
when we're frustrated,
what do you think we should do?
Do you think you'll be fine
after getting surgery
and taking medicine?
Obviously, that won't work.
What should we do then?
According to the Doctrine of the Mean,
when joy, anger, sorrow,
and pleasure have not yet arisen,
it is called "moderate".
But guys,
we, humans, aren't
deities in temples.
When we have anger,
we must vent it out.
Here comes the latter part
of the saying.
When they arise to their appropriate
levels, it is called "harmony".
We already know
that our emotions have deviated
from the central path.
What should we do when it has
already harmed our bodies?
There's still a way
we can regulate our bodies.
Next, we'll talk about
how to regulate our unstable emotions.
The Chinese culture relies on practice.
Integrity needs practice.
Morality needs to be instilled.
If language does not transform one,
there will be no culture.
So, what do we transform?
What do we transform?
Guys, what do we transform?
We transform our negative emotions.
If someone has negative emotions,
you must transform them
with your actions.
Avoiding and procrastinating
will harm your body severely.
I think there's an issue
with your mindset.
I agree with Mr Liu.
We have to attract traffic first.
After that,
you can continue
with the Internet thinking.
We'll earn money from
the surrounding businesses.
The trading of herbs,
online prescriptions,
and the recommendation
between TCM and Western medicine,
all of these will make huge money.
The largest benefit of this academy
is that
it'll produce batches and batches
of new talents.
That's right.
This is a great concept.
If we organise it,
it'll be a complete proposal.
The most valuable assets
in the TCM industry
-are its people.
-That's right.
As long as he's here,
your industrial park
will thrive.
That's right.
There's one more important point.
We cannot talk about
the profit model first.
Only small projects
talk about their profit model
at the start.
We have to talk about
visions and dreams.
Just like Elon Musk.
He talked about migrating to Mars
after he assumed his position.
A world without borders.
He made all those tycoons
excited.
When it comes to talking about dreams,
Mr Liu, you're not the right fit.
Think about it.
When you stand here,
people will definitely think
that the culture of your enterprise
only focuses on profit,
not dreams.
Professor Ren is a great fit.
If he comes to talk about his dreams,
everyone in the world will be convinced.
What about this?
We have a peer advisory board meeting
next month.
You can invite Professor Ren
to tell us
about the vision of TCM development.
As for the rest, we'll package them.
This feels especially out of place.
It's decided then.
Let's go.
Hello, Professor Ren?
Today was supposed to
be your follow-up visit.
I'm already done with my class.
Why haven't you arrived yet?
Actually, I was there.
(I was at the classroom's door.)
(I heard your lesson about emotion.)
(I was suddenly enlightened.)
(It feels like all of my troubles
has been lifted.)
I feel like I'm cured.
Congratulations then.
Thank you, Professor Ren.
Grandson!
I'm here!
Where's the skateboard?
Wait, where's the skateboard?
You brought nothing?
What? Are we here to eat?
Today,
you shall acknowledge me
as your master first.
What's wrong with you guys?
Why do you guys like
such ceremonies so much?
Do you like it that much
when people address you as Master?
You're so childish.
If you wish to travel
the pugilist world,
you must get a famous master.
Since I've already agreed to teach you,
we need to make this official.
If not, what if you...
If I do embarrass myself out there,
I won't rat you out, okay?
Deal.
Alright.
You're so troublesome.
What are you doing?
We have to be particular
with the ceremony.
Look.
This is an excellent wine that
my grandfather has kept for a long time.
It's definitely good.
What do you think?
Don't you think I'm nice?
I'm sure this has a huge kick then.
Of course.
You can stop craving for it.
Go ahead.
Rebecca.
Rebecca,
I don't think it's appropriate
for us to just drink yogurt
without ordering any food here.
Can you please focus?
My time is expensive.
You kept playing with those threads.
How can I focus like this?
I'm done.
Does this shirt cost
tens of thousands as well
when it looks this cheap?
I ordered this from Taobao.
It's meant for people
to wear to food stalls.
It costs 55 yuan
from top to bottom.
And, it's disposable.
By the way,
it's 80 yuan if you include
this disposable bottle as well.
What? You use Taobao too?
I had no choice. You forced me to do it.
That's pretty good.
Share the link with me later.
By the way, I have
something to tell you.
The Dragon Boat Festival
is a public holiday.
Our tuition class
will be suspended for the time being.
But why?
Are you going on a trip?
I'm going to join the TCM forum.
But your name wasn't included
in the name list.
Besides, people won't invite
half-baked physicians like us.
This time,
I'm going there because
the organiser invited me.
What gives?
Why didn't he invite me then?
The organiser is an
old client of mine.
I'm going there to visit him mainly.
I'm just joining the forum
since I'll be there anyway.
I think you're just going there
to join the forum.
Take me with you.
A spy like me
needs to head to the enemy's nest
to eradicate them once and for all.
Take me with you.
You're a renowned figure.
You need to have a servant beside you.
Besides,
the mountain path is rugged and uneven.
I checked the schedule too.
We have to gather mugwort
in the mountains before dawn
on the second day.
I'm sure you'll depart at night.
What if you encounter a bear
or a robber? It'll be dangerous.
Most importantly,
it's a long journey.
You need a second driver somehow.
(The prescriptions and remedies
used in this drama)
(are referenced from relevant
traditional Chinese medicine books)
(Do not use without medical advice)
(End of Episode 9)