It's really hard for those of us
who are trying to pass on the knowledge.
The Taoist preaches
that a master seeks out his disciple.
I agreed to give a lecture
not for you
but for myself.
I think
that if I give more lectures,
I will eventually get a student
who is willing to pass on all this
without changing the teacher's way.
If that's the case,
then I
will be able to answer
to my own master.
As long as there's a desire to do so,
it'll work.
Well said.
You can eat beef, right?
Yes.
I'm coming!
You're so slow.
What? Didn't we say to meet at 7pm?
-Look at the time now.
-I took the time to get changed.
-We're here!
-You're so slow.
-Tian Zhen!
-Coming.
-What's more?
-You haven't placed an order yet?
-We haven't.
-Let me do it.
We're here.
Tian Zhen,
you're so slow.
Very slow.
-I'm not the one who's slow.
-You're late.
-I need to...
-There is seafood.
I had to wait for Meng Meng
to get changed.
Seriously.
Fine then.
What would you like to eat?
Their crayfish are good.
Miss,
well,
we want crayfish.
You have a lot of seafood.
Yes.
Our seafood is very fresh.
Give me more seafood then.
-Okay. Alright?
-Sure.
Just prepare according to
the number of people we have.
What else do you want?
That's why we came early.
The point is that you
haven't ordered any food.
I was waiting for you.
Because you're late.
The seafood here is not bad.
-So many, so fresh.
-Tou Tou.
I went to a lot of trouble
to find this spot.
What took you so long?
If it wasn't for Little Green,
I wouldn't have been able to make it.
What's the matter? The battery is dead?
-Hello.
-Hi, Xing Xing.
-Sit down.
-You can catch up here.
Do you want sliced buns?
Yes.
Miss,
two skewers of sliced buns.
Make it three!
I want one.
-Do you want some?
-I want one too.
-Meng Meng wants it too.
-Four, five. Five skewers!
Five.
Why is someone in here?
Tou Tou.
I can't hold back any longer.
It will probably take a while.
Wait for a while.
No, this...
Zhao Li Quan,
can you hurry up?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm on my fifth trip here.
Tou Tou,
it's all your fault.
If it wasn't for you, would I have
gone to the toilet so many times?
No, what do you mean by...
How could you blame me for this?
Why didn't you thank me
when you were eating so happily?
Listen,
you asked for it.
I didn't force you to come!
Open the door now!
Alright.
I asked for it.
I couldn't care less.
I need to poop in the field.
Field?
Quick.
I can't hold back any longer.
I know.
Tou Tou is calling me at this late hour.
Isn't she downstairs?
The kids aren't back yet.
-Hello.
-(Hello, Niece-in-law.)
Come over now.
We're all dead.
No, I can't take it anymore.
I'm dying.
I can't take it. I'm dying.
How are you doing? Any better?
I can't take it.
You won't die.
Something is definitely wrong
with the seafood today.
I didn't have such severe diarrhoea
when I took gutter oil before.
Something must be wrong
with it.
Did someone force you to eat it?
You've all got food poisoning.
You should all drink
your herbal medicine later.
Ms Song,
we have a bacterial infection.
Let's not resist it.
We'll be well tomorrow
if we get the antibiotics.
If we take the herbal medicine,
how many days
will it take to get better?
You can leave it out.
You can treat it with Western medicine.
I have something to say.
You're already in
such a state, what else
do you want to say?
You can say it tomorrow.
I can't wait till tomorrow.
I saw the skeleton patient
at the barbecue stall today.
That
skinny guy
who came in
with you guys today.
Since we have such severe diarrhoea,
he ordered a table full of seafood
and judging by his malnourished look,
I'm sure his condition
is even worse now.
Niece-in-law, Nephew, do you
think you should call and ask?
And Xing Xing.
Xing Xing
needs the medicine too.
What medicine is this? I
don't know. She needs it too.
Here you go.
What smell is this?
Drink it while it's hot.
No, it's too bitter.
It's too bitter.
Good medicine tastes bitter.
You have got yourself sick
by indulging
in seafood outside.
I have to stay up to cook you medicine
but you're complaining it's bitter.
Don't drink it then.
Put up with the pain then.
Ms Song,
We know we were wrong.
Thank you. I'm sorry.
Alright, finish it quickly.
Get some rest after you've finished it.
I was so scared.
I thought we were doomed this time.
I never thought that
Mr Ren would not scold us.
Guys,
don't mess with your body.
If you can't take it,
just don't take it.
Shi Yan,
keep it.
Every day in class,
the teacher talks about
not seeing the world
just from your own point of view
and not being stuck in a rut.
How come you can't figure it out
when you're sick?
Unlike TCM,
Western medicine's greatest
contribution to human longevity
is antibiotics.
The invention of this medicine
has increased human life
expectancy by an average of 20 years.
We have a bacterial infection.
We'll get well
after taking this.
Let's not fight science.
I'm not saying
Chinese medicine is bad,
it just takes time.
Do you want it or not?
Do you want it?
Give me one.
Give me one too.
Tian Zhen.
We may be able to take it as we're men.
Meng Meng is a weak girl.
If something does happen
to her in a few days,
what will you tell her parents?
Meng Meng,
are you still feeling unwell?
Take it.
I think you're quite weak.
Take both of these medicines,
there is always one that works.
Just take it.
Tou Tou, this is for you.
No, I will drink Chinese medicine.
Why are you acting like
you're really in it?
Do you really think
you're the successor?
Alright.
Even if you are the successor,
don't mess with your life.
No, what's wrong with you guys?
My nephew took our pulse
and prescribed the medicine,
and my niece-in-law
brewed the medicine herself.
Aren't you ashamed
of wasting their efforts?
Are you not ashamed?
But I am.
No one has ever been
this nice to me in my whole life.
Listen,
I'll drink this medicine
even if it doesn't work.
I admire you.
There is really someone who wants
to risk her life to repay a favour.
Alright, I won't persuade you anymore.
I can help you with something else.
If you're dead...
Won't it be too late to
take antibiotics then?
That's not what I meant.
I have a friend at the crematorium,
I can help you jump the queue
-and get burnt first.
-I'll burn...
I'll burn you first.
Jump the queue for what?
Look here, everyone.
For my nephew and niece-in-law,
I'll finish it.
What a pleasure!
Tou,
you're amazing.
I feel sick to my stomach
at the smell of oil now.
The wild species
is really different from us.
Attacked by Schrodinger's diarrhoea,
Tou is still the toughest.
No, what is Schrodinger's diarrhoea?
Something you can't verify.
You don't know whether it's Chinese
or Western medicine
that works faster.
The samples differ.
You reap what you sow.
If you were to drink the medicine with
me, you would have been well by now.
Tou,
let me put it to you seriously.
You must not spread the word
that you have cured your
diarrhoea by taking Chinese medicine
to avoid killing people.
Many people don't understand,
so they take small probabilities
as facts.
Tou has such a strong body.
She heals herself
without Chinese medicine.
You don't even know
that Tou has a steel mill
in her belly, right?
She can turn wire
into steel flakes in her belly.
What did your father
call us here for today?
I guess it's about Ms Dong's
technique class.
Technique class?
Let's go.
Are you all right?
Who else still has diarrhoea?
Mr Ren,
we're all much better
You're all much better?
Alright.
So let's get this straight.
Whose idea was it?
Tian Zhen.
Dad,
everyone just got diarrhoea.
It wasn't that bad.
It wasn't that bad?
You, as a doctor,
violate discipline
with your patients.
Can you be responsible
if anything happens to her?
I am liable
if any of you
have a problem.
I have worked so hard
to pass on my knowledge,
how could I raise such
ungrateful students?
God is watching us.
You guys
are the hope of Chinese medicine.
How are you worthy of
the word hope?
If all students
were as free
as you are,
Chinese civilization
would have been extinguished
like other ancient civilizations.
How many times have I told you
what your routine should be,
what you should do
and what you shouldn't do?
Are you less intelligent
than primary school students?
Why Chinese culture
is about the unity of
knowledge and action?
You know it but you don't do it.
You have learned it
and then ignored it.
All the students
in the apprentice class
appear to be sick now.
How can you
convince others
that Chinese medicine is the
knowledge of health and wellness?
Report. I can.
I didn't join them last night.
I'm not talking about you.
I have always
believed that
the passing on of Chinese medicine
is a common goal for us all.
But today, it seems
to be just my wishful thinking.
If you really don't want to do it,
if you really don't want to learn it,
then I will stop running
this apprentice class.
You have freed me.
I don't have to
worry about the location
of the classroom
for the apprentice class anymore.
Let's free ourselves from each other.
Mr Ren,
it's not fair to me.
If they don't fit,
they can leave.
But I have followed
your instructions exactly
from the beginning.
I think I'm a
very qualified and good student.
If the class is discontinued,
you should allow me
to continue my studies with you.
On the first day of class,
I told you
that all the students in the class
were mirrors and rulers
to each other.
You saw them doing something wrong.
If I judge you
from their point of view,
you are in the wrong too.
I advised them,
but none of them listened to me.
Now that something has gone wrong,
is it fair to me who is the only person
who hasn't made a mistake
to share the blame with them?
Do you think you are right?
So how come they don't listen
to anything you say to them?
You did a PhD, right?
You're a barrister.
Then why don't all your classmates
have any faith in you?
If so, how do you have the
ability to pass on knowledge?
I am not here to learn
about passing on knowledge,
I am here to learn how to save lives.
Sweep the snow from your own doorstep,
don't worry about the frost
on your neighbour's roof.
Master.
Well...
Yesterday,
I was...
I was the one who
asked everyone to join me.
Because
I craved skewers.
So I asked them
to join me.
And I was the one who ordered the food.
So I think
maybe the food I ordered
was just not clean or something.
You want to take
responsibility for this?
Are you up to it?
Mr Ren,
it was me who gathered everyone there.
It's not Tou's fault alone.
I'm the Class Leader.
I didn't take good care of
my fellow classmates.
It's my responsibility.
Mr Ren,
we all went of our own free will.
I am responsible for that too.
I am willing to be punished together.
Yes.
We all went of our own free will.
A law is violated by a lot of people
and is thus left unenforced instead.
If you want to expel anyone,
you'd better expel all of us.
Master!
It's really me.
It's really my responsibility alone.
Master,
don't disband the apprentice class.
They can really pass it on
after studying Chinese medicine.
It's the cravings that got me.
I know I've let you down again
by not being good enough.
Why don't you punish me?
Okay, Master?
You want to be a heroin?
You want to take the blame
for this, right?
Alright.
I guess my little pond
can't keep a big shark like you anymore.
From now on,
you are no longer a student
of the apprentice class.
You can leave now.
I can't teach you.
And I don't know how to teach you!
Mum.
Stop following me.
You're still at work.
Where are you going?
I'm going to look for a job.
I can get one at any time.
So where are you going to live?
You can't go back to
Tian Zhen's home anymore.
How about this?
You can move back in with Xing Xing.
I'll move my stuff out,
I can't take up your space.
Zhao Li Quan, are you a fool?
You've finally got a place
to settle down.
Just live there in peace.
I have a place to live.
You're not fooling me?
Why should I fool you?
I really have a place to live
and it's a single room.
Listen here.
You are the hope of your whole village
and the talent of the community.
You will be needed
in many ways in the future.
You are going to be a great doctor.
Don't stay in
those messy places.
Just live in peace
with Xing Xing.
Don't worry about anything else.
I was
never one of you.
So now I'm off
to wander the world with Little Green.
Bye.
Go back.
I think, in life,
we deserve to be forgiven
as long as we don't harm
someone on purpose.
Just like me.
Even if I did break someone's bones,
I stood up for what was right.
So you can't include that
in my dark history.
We need to look at
the bright side of life.
Stop blaming yourself.
If I may suggest,
learn medicine from me.
Learn TCM.
I really think
you have a talent for studying TCM.
In TCM,
if you can accurately
identify the illness,
confront it,
defeat it,
and cure the patient's condition,
the sense of accomplishment
is much stronger than catching a doll.
You're really mad?
Here you go.
What's with me?
Why do I have such a student?
It's your disciple.
This is the disciple
God sent you.
Being grateful to God, respecting
teachers and remembering elders.
Your master, who is also my father,
gave you such a tough task
and you accepted it,
didn't you?
You can't blame anyone else, can you?
Don't let yourself
get into trouble
when you haven't nurtured a disciple.
It's good that she's left.
I've tried my best.
It's not that I don't want
to nurture her,
she won't let me.
She's hopeless.
Enough, I know you well.
Don't take advantage of the issue.
Listen,
today's incident
has really made me
change my view of Tou Tou.
This kid
can be nurtured.
I mean it.
Look, she stepped forward
to admit her mistake today.
I observed the other kids
closely.
In fact, they all looked ashamed.
So she may not be
the one who started it.
Princess Taiping made a mistake,
right?
But she admitted it.
Didn't Wu Zetian also lament
that it was a pity she wasn't a man?
Are you comparing her to a princess?
She's a stubborn monkey.
Since she's a stubborn monkey,
why are you so angry?
You've taken it to heart.
Look,
she had such severe diarrhoea,
she still thought of
those irrelevant people
around her.
What does it mean?
It means she is observant and caring.
Of all the students who were there,
how come none of them
noticed that?
What do you mean by this gesture?
You've complimented her twice
for being observant and caring.
If you want to keep her,
call her
and get her back.
No.
If she doesn't come back,
this is the end of
our apprenticeship.
Is there a rebellion going on?
There are so many people in the world
who want to be my disciple.
Do I have to beg her?
Is she my grandma?
Yes.
If she doesn't come back, let her be.
Since she's left,
let's stop running this class.
So you can take some money home.
I can't
take money home.
If I could have done that,
you wouldn't have married me.
We have a very clear division of duties.
You are at home dealing
with mundane tasks
while I am out doing good deeds.
Can you tell me what kind of
good deeds you have done?
I teach
and nurture my students.
Treating patients is also a good deed
but there are so many
people in the world.
Even if I were capable,
I wouldn't be able to care so much.
I've thought about it.
Once
I've nurtured a great doctor,
I'll have an extra hand.
If I've nurtured 3,000 great doctors,
well...
I haven't seen you
nurture much renowned students
in all these years.
It takes ten years to plant a tree,
but a hundred years to nurture a person.
I haven't lived long enough.
Enough.
My father was absolutely right.
Do you know what God
is asking you to fix?
Pride.
The reason you can't even
let go of your pride today
is because
we have all lost face for you.
When you took all the family's savings
to support
the poor community,
as a married daughter,
I took my son
back to my parents' house for food,
didn't I embarrass myself?
You've said it twice.
Alright.
Okay, I will stop talking about this.
Let's talk about
your resignation.
You're ashamed to
return to the university,
so you asked me to
go and pack your stuff for you.
Did I feel ashamed?
No.
Look,
You let me
do everything you find hard to deal with
for you.
What does it mean?
It means that
God really wants to
smack your pride
on the ground
and rub it off,
just like that.
If you can do it,
you'll break through.
If you
don't want to beg
your disciple to come back,
fine.
You may
ask Liu
to find another classroom for you.
Isn't he just
trying to do something
in your name?
Nowadays, there are
so many people
who do things
in the name of others.
What is this?
Everyone has their own tricks
and ways of dealing with things.
If you don't want to do it,
you can find him
someone who does.
You've got a point here.
He's not really
using my name,
but TCM.
That makes sense.
Looks like God is helping me.
Is God helping you
or is your wife helping you?
God's way of helping me
was to let me marry you.
You have said it for the fifth time.
(End of heat)
(means the heat is leaving.)
(It reminds people that
the summer heat is fading)
(and the weather is gradually
transitioning to cooler.)
(End of Heat)
Professor Ren,
you're really treating me
to a feast today.
I didn't expect this.
Are you here alone?
Where are those investors?
I'm not sure what you're up to
after being fooled by you so many times.
I am here today
to find out your intentions.
Mr Liu, I've actually
been wondering
if you really
want to invest in TCM?
I don't know anything about it.
So I would like to use your reputation.
But you disagreed.
You want to use my reputation.
I've got two legs.
What if I run away
and your efforts are wasted?
Where are you running to?
Who doesn't know you
as a highly respected TCM practitioner?
Cut the crap.
Besides,
I also have a passion
for the promotion
of Chinese medicine
and culture.
I'm not kidding.
Really?
Alright.
I'm relieved now.
To be honest,
I invited you here today
to introduce you
to a highly qualified person
in the industry of TCM.
Who is it?
You will know it
when he is here.
Sorry for being late,
I was stuck in traffic.
Let me introduce.
This is the principal of
University of TCM,
-Wu Shan Dao.
-Mr Wu.
I'm just an acting principal.
An acting principal.
This is Mr Liu, the owner
of the TCM industrial park.
Mr Liu.
I've heard a lot about you.
You two can talk alone
over a meal later.
Okay.
-I am pleased to meet you.
-I hope we can work well together.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
Come on.
-Your delivery is here.
-Alright.
Well,
I've flown you
matsutake
from Yunnan.
Come in.
Can you tell me the collection...
Collection...
Look.
Collection code.
765558.
There is an extra number, right?
Are my eyes bad
or yours?
Three fives and an eight.
Okay, I'll leave it here for you.
Tou Tou is working a part-time job.
Do you know it, Senior?
Waiter!
Come in.
Well,
you
haven't been in touch
with Tou Tou lately?
No.
How can you be so cold-hearted?
You don't even know
what she's doing?
That's your grandmaster,
your classmate.
She's your senior aunt too,
and also your student.
If you're not cold-hearted,
why ask me?
Right,
you're the one who drove her away.
Since you drove her away,
she is no longer my classmate
or your student.
Isn't it a bit unnecessary for us
to be concerned about her now?
You are going to be a doctor one day.
After all these years of
being nurtured by the family,
you fail at being observant
and caring,
far worse than Tou Tou.
Dad,
if you have something to say,
can you just be straight with me?
Go ahead with your calligraphy.
(Grandson, I have a lot of deliveries
to make today and I will be late.)
(By the way, remember to
bring my skateboard with you).
Roger.
Do you need supper?
You're such a filial grandson.
(You're such a filial grandson.)
Uncle Tao,
why are you still lying in my place?
-Let me stay in your room for a while.
-I've told you many times.
Help me with massage.
You need to go to the doctor
to check your back.
You can't keep lying on your stomach.
It's okay.
I have to take time off work to go
to hospital and it's a waste of time.
You have great massage skills.
Don't you have social insurance?
You wish!
Our company filed our social
insurance in other regions.
(Uncle Tao)
So we can't use it for
medical treatment in Jiangzhou.
But you can't put it off.
I told you I studied medicine.
From my experience,
you're bound to get sick
if you keep putting it off.
Cut the crap.
Stop bragging.
Here are your brush, ink and paper.
Remember to bring them along.
Why should I?
Do you think I'll still be practising
calligraphy when I'm gone?
You can't leave anything
you've used with me either.
If you want to throw them away,
do it yourself.
What are you writing?
Look at your calligraphic writing.
Those who know
will know that you wrote it,
those who don't
will think it's a turtle's footprint.
When others write calligraphy,
they...
What are you doing?
I'm talking to you.
Uncle Tao, if you have nothing to
do here, you should go back to bed.
I'm doing homework.
This is your homework?
This is the homework my master gave me.
My master told me
to practise like this
for ten years.
After ten years,
I will be thirty-two years old
and when I write my prescriptions,
my patients will have confidence in me
when I start writing.
Get it?
Stop fooling me.
I don't believe you when you say
you'll be a delivery rider for ten years,
let alone ten years from now
when you'll be treating patients.
Silly girl,
listen here.
Anyone who promises you
something ten years from now
is a liar.
Remember this.
You're pretty serious.
I think
you are an over-ambitious
small potato.
Just accept your fate.
Even if you've been practising
calligraphy for ten years,
you're still a delivery rider.
What's wrong with still being
a delivery rider in ten years?
That will make a difference.
I used to be
a fidgety rider,
and I couldn't keep my mind calm,
but now I'm delivering
in a calm and peaceful manner.
What does it mean?
When you have a change of mind,
you will be happy,
and you will be happy
in everything you do.
Got it?
I got it.
That's a good point.
Everyone
should have a dream.
Silly girl,
listen here.
Be careful
when you are carrying large items
in the future.
If you were like me now,
you wouldn't even be able to
make deliveries for ten years.
Uncle Tao.
It's here, isn't it?
No.
It's not here.
-Lower.
-It's not here.
Back. Here it is.
Do you know where the back is?
-Here?
-No.
-How dare you say you studied medicine?
-Here it is.
What's wrong?
-It's here, isn't it?
-What's wrong?
-Well...
-No... Nothing.
Don't make a fuss about it.
Is it here?
You seem to have made it worse.
Tou Tou,
stop massaging him.
It's expensive to go to hospital.
-He has to see a doctor still.
-No, he's got an old injury.
So he needs to get
his old injury treated.
I'm just worried that his back
will get worse with massage.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
What are you doing here?
Well,
I have a friend
who has a back pain.
Can you check on him?
Go and register.
Can you check on him first?
Because
I don't have money.
He doesn't have money either.
But I'll pay it back
for him later.
Do you know how much it costs
for my medical treatment?
Your one month's salary.
So expensive?
Didn't you say
that a great healer
must be at peace with his mind
and free from desire? The first
thing to do is to show compassion.
Since I've told you
that we don't have money.
Can't you give me a discount?
If so, it means you can't walk the talk.
It seems that the daily
morning reading really works.
You even quoted the classic text
when you dissed me.
I know he doesn't have money
but I know you do.
I don't have money.
How could you not have money?
You don't have money,
so why do you take everything on you?
This small amount of money
means nothing to you.
Master, I was wrong.
I didn't behave properly,
took everyone out to have fun
and led my classmates
astray.
You're still talking tough?
You want to take responsibility
for this to the end, don't you?
Alright.
After you pay for the fee,
bring your friend in
and let me check on him.
Can you treat him first
and I'll pay later?
Can I pay in installments?
What kind of place do you think this is?
Aren't you eloquent?
Tell me.
(Qibo Medical Centre)
Amazing.
It's so amazing.
Try to move
and see if it still hurts.
Look,
I'm fine now.
Ms Dong. Thank you. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Ms Dong.
Can you teach me that technique?
Because a lot of my workmates
have back problems.
After you teach me, I'll go back
and give them all a massage.
-Yeah.
-I can't teach you now.
(The prescriptions and remedies
used in this drama)
(are referenced from relevant
traditional Chinese medicine books)
(Do not use without medical advice)
(End of Episode 13)