It's over there. I think he went over there.
You think you're something, don't you?
Did you grab that concept because you wanted to kill someone?
You're just a psychopathic serial killer, you bastard.
Don't hide and come out!
Come out, you bastard!
Mr. A, who was sentenced to five years in prison
for assaulting a rapist while trying to rescue his stepdaughter,
was found murdered shortly after he was released.
Mr. A was sentenced to 5 years in prison for assault back in 2016.
A while ago, an anonymous video arrived at our press office.
There can be some shocking scenes,
but a more shocking truth will be revealed to the world.
Please save me.
I did it. I killed them all.
I was the one who killed all the women from Suseong.
The women who disappeared from Suseong Middle School.
There is a big rock on the mountain behind the school.
I buried them all there.
The items from the dead women are all buried there.
Since I confessed like this,
please save me.
Please save me!
Ajussi!
Ah, no. No!
Don't die. Don't die!
Ajussi, your innocence has been proven. Why are you trying to die?
Bong Yi.
Bong Yi, what's the matter? Huh?
You think you're something, don't you?
Did you grab that concept because you wanted to kill someone?
You are just a psychopathic serial killer, you bastard.
I'm a killer.
I killed a person.
I...
I'm not what you think I am.
Oppa.
The shape is the same one that came out of the victim's body from the Suseong serial killer case.
"Eye for an eye."
"Tooth for a tooth."
What happened?
I had a question that I missed from the last interview,
so I went to see him today after I heard he was getting released.
Oh? PD, what are you doing here?
Ah, I coincidentally saw you leaving while I was covering another inmate.
- You must've been released?
- Yes.
Ah, where are you going?
I was doing an interview nearby...
Ah, Suseong. I'm going to stop by my mother's grave.
He suddenly asked me to take him to his mother's grave.
I have to go there for work anyway. Get in. I can take you there.
Ah, yes. Thank you.
I had to do an interview, so I had no choice but accept his request.
That's where the 10th victim of the Suseong serial killer was found.
-  It's not in this direction.
- Ah, is that so?
I must've gone the wrong way. Is it okay if we take a little more time?
Sure, why not. All I have is time.
Ah, you must be hungry? There's a plastic bag down there. You can take it out and eat it.
Ah, yes. Thank you.
Why? Are you reminded of that time?
What are you...
It was you, you bastard.
How can you go by yourself?
How did you know?
I wanted to live nice.
Why do you keep messing with me?
Live nicely?
You can't kick that habit.
What?
This bitch.
Did you see him?
I couldn't see anything.
At that time, I was unconscious with a gag in my mouth.
Oh, Officer Jung. Lee Jae Sik is going to be released today.
They say the release time is delayed due to internal circumstances.
I have to get an interview. Can you tell me Dong Gu's number?
Ah, yes, I will send it to you right now.
If PD Choi is in danger,
I need to speed things up.
In the video, Mr. A's confession turned out to be true.
At the mountain behind Suseong Girls' Middle School, the police found the victims' belongings.
The video from the killer who murdered Mr. A cleared
Kim Bong Cheol's name, who was unfairly accused this whole time.
The murder of the true suspect of the Suseong serial killer case,
referred as Judgement Man or Dark Hero, has gained an enthusiastic response from the people. So the Blue House...
The President said that personal revenge is an unforgivable serious crime
that has been disrupting our Constitutional state lately.
During the investigation, the President has ordered that all efforts should be devoted to arresting the criminal.
I don't feel good.
Why am I so depressed?
Last time, it felt refreshing.
You're just a psychopathic serial killer, you bastard.
I... I'm not what you think I am.
He's like that because of me.
He's doing this because of me.
Did you like Mu Chi Ajusshi?
I confessed to him, saying we should date.
But, I was rejected within a second.
It wasn't good timing.
It was right after Detective Go decided to kill Han Seo Joon.
He didn't want to make me unhappy, so he pushed me away.
Oppa feels the same way. Just like Ajusshi.
Get out.
This is the neighborhood I lived in when I was young.
Come over here.
What is all of this?
As a Christmas present,
you said you wanted to have a hideout?
Huh?
Your father had prepared this as a surprise Christmas gift.
The day you woke up at dawn. That day was Christmas, right?
You said your father’s whole body was soaked with rain and sweat.
And there was mud and grass on his pants.
The reason was because of this. Your father.
This... He was making this?
I didn't even realize.
What am I going to do?
I feel so bad.
What do I do about my dad?
- It's okay.
- What do I do? My poor dad.
Next is the Groom's entrance.
Please give a warm round of applause.
The Groom is now entering!
Wow!
Are you feeling good?
Next, the star of today, the Bride will enter.
Detective Shin Sang pursued her for five years!
Today, he's finally marrying her! Bride, now enter!
I'm sorry, Dad.
Oh... Why?
How did he get out? Didn't he need a formal trial?
He received a special leave.
If it wasn't for that person, he wouldn't be standing there right now.
Ajusshi, your innocence has been proven! Why are you trying to die?
Damn it!
Wait! Wait!
Look! Look at this, Ahjussi!
Over here!
He saved him. He saved them both.
That man.
Auntie!
Just because I haven't come by for a couple of days, how could you make such a mess of the place?
What would you do without me?
You're not angry at me anymore?
You didn't tell Hoon Seok off too much, did you?
Your uncle got transferred to the US branch. We've decided to go together.
Really? That's great. When?
He needs to go right away for the handover process.
There are so many things to get done, but my heart is the one feeling anxious.
We have to put the house on the market and pack, too.
Anyway, I feel bad for you, Ba Reum.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
Oh, it's this late already?
I need to get going.
I left Hoon Seok with the neighbor.
Auntie.
By chance...
that kitten, couldn't Hoon Seok take it and raise it?
He really liked it last time.
Let's do that then. He'll be lonely in a foreign country, too.
It'll be nice for him to have a friend.
Yes.
The call cannot be completed, and you will be forwarded to voicemail.
He didn't want to make me unhappy, so he pushed me away.
If he pushes me away, I'll just pull him back to me.
Oh, hello?
Oppa, I'm in Unnam-dong to gather material for a report, but the best burrito place is here.
Should I bring you some?
Do you want to have lunch together?
I'm busy. I'm working out of town on assignment.
I see. When are you coming back?
It's okay. I have time to wait.
Don't wait for me. I'll be late.
I'm really okay. I can wait.
What do you mean you're okay?
Okay then, Oppa.
I'll go home then.
But Oppa...
Whether you're the Oppa I know
or you're not the one I know, it doesn't matter to me.
Whoever you are or what kind of person you are,
I just like you.
I only wanted to tell you that.
I wanted to tell you in person.
I ended up saying it over the phone.
I'll hang up.
Did you two fight?
What's the matter? You liked her so much that it was annoying.
She'll be unhappy if she's with me.
She can't afford to be unhappy anymore.
Why are you thinking that way?
Why would Bong Yi become unhappy with you?
She's waiting to see you right now.
Hey, I don't know why you're having those types of thoughts,
but there was a time I thought that way.
Had I accepted that confession, what would have happened to me?
Would my life have turned out differently?
Have a family, kids, and planning out my retirement...
Dreaming about a job...
Would I be living that way?
Do you regret it?
Regret?
Regret...
I can't stop now. I have to just keep going.
There's nowhere for me to return to either.
Don't do something you'll regret, punk.
That's right. My life might change.
If I'm with Bong Yi,
I might be able to return to the Jung Ba Reum I used to be.
Oppa?
Tomorrow,
do you want to have dinner together?
You're not busy?
I'm not busy from now on.
The burrito place you wanted to go to, let's go together.
Hurry home so you don't catch a cold.
I'll overcome it for certain.
Bong Yi, give me the strength.
Please protect me.
Bong Yi, marry me when you're of age.
Thank you! I'll work hard!
Best of luck.
Oh, Oppa, you're here?
There's traffic, so I think it'll take another 10 minutes.
Okay, call me when you get here.
I knew it when you came to work all dressed up.
Oh, it must be a nice time for you.
Yes?
Oh, a report?
It's that little kid. That annoying kid.
Annoying?
That detective kid?
Make it quick and hang up.
Well, the thing is, that doesn't really suit our program.
Try contacting Animal Farm instead.
What? Do you know what time it is right now?
Go home quickly! Your mom will be worried!
Seriously...
He's in the lobby.
He must've come to complain after blocking the bulletin board.
He's a nourished kid.
Detective Go Nam?
My wrong choice...
Am I doing the right thing by using him this way?
Yeah, it's right to end it this way.
So, you want to relieve the grandmother's resentment because of your classmate, right?
You're so cool?
Like a detective.
On that note,
I will tell you the reason why I came.
What is it?
I figured it out. The cat murder.
Oh, really?
Wow, you're like a detective. Who is it?
Hey, it's important how I knew rather than who it is.
It's the mentality of Go Nam.
That's right. How did you–
How did you know?
I found the evidence.
Clear evidence! I have it.
Evidence?
But, from now it's serious.
The truth is more shocking than the cat murder.
There is only one truth.
Bong Yi!
Oppa!
Say hello. This person is Detective Go Nam.
Nice to meet you.
Date?
Then I can't get in the way, Writer Noona.
Later...
Kid.
You have to take your bag.
Go Nam, get back safely!
Who is that?
He came to give a tip.
Ah, there must be a rumor that his classmate's grandma is killing cats.
So that classmate became an outcast.
But he said that he found the suspect.
He found evidence, too.
Wait a moment.
Yes?
Ah, I have a dinner appointment right now.
It's important. Come right now.
What... Hello?
Why? Is it the office? Is it important?
Yeah.
Ah, then let's eat dinner next time.
I ate cake a while ago, so I'm not that hungry.
I think I'm a little indigested too.
I starved myself all day to eat dinner with Oppa, so I almost died from hunger.
It's time for 'Amazing Saturday' rebroadcast.
Why does Ahjusshi Shin Dong Yeop always hear wrong? His ears shouldn't be useless.
Writer Noona, I have something to say.  Is it possible to meet up tomorrow?
So cute.
I hope you come alone.
Alone?
- Oppa.
- Is your indigestion better?
Yes.
I'm fine.  The indigestion is all better.
That's a relief.
I'm sorry about today.  Let's eat something delicious tomorrow instead.
Even if your digestion is bad, eat something before you go to sleep.  Okay.
A date?  Then I shouldn't interfere, Writer Noona.
What are you thinking so hard about?
What did you call me about?
The next prey.  You can think of him as the biggest predator.
I've been thinking... There's a supporter, isn't there?
Did that supporter give you this person's DNA and ask to have them killed?
I heard that you were adopted in England when you were young, and you grew up there.
And now, you're officially dead.
There's no way you could have acquired the equipment and materials required for all this on your own.
Who is the person helping you?
You don't need to know.
You're a very mysterious person.
Why is a world class genetics professor
hiding in a place like this?
Why are you living in hiding, pretending to be dead?
You're being chased by someone... aren't you?
When it's the right time,  you'll get to know everything.  Just wait.
The right time...
I don't know when that time will be, but I'll wait.
Don't give these things to me anymore.
I'll decide... who I'll dispose of.
Of course I know him.  Go Nam is the problem solver at this school.
He even caught the guy who was stealing my shoes.
But class isn't over yet.
It's over.
Hello, Hyung!
Oh, you're here?  Just a moment.
Why are you working here every day?  You should take it easy.
Work hard!
Aigoo, Grandma!  Hey, get out!
Grandma!
Gosh, what's with that granny?
Aigoo, Grandma!
Oh! Sheesh, Writer Noona.
I told her to come alone.
Is he already done with class?
Why isn't he answering his phone?
By chance, do you know Myung Go Nam?
I saw him in the hallway on my way out.
Ah, you did?  Thank you.
Oh, Go Nam.  Where are you?
Noona, sorry... Sorry...
Did our paths get crossed?
Get out of the way!
Four cats.  Four cats.
My Go Nam!
I can't live if something happens to my Go Nam.
I'm going to die if anything happens to him!
Today we will be talking about the unfortunate accident regarding a kid detective,
who was on an investigation in order to clear a classmate's Grandma of false charges.
The kid detective, as the cabinet in the cafeteria shook,
the undiluted cleaning solution that was on top fell down.
And he sustained burns on his entire body.
The school did not lock the doors to the cafeteria.
If they wanted to, anyone could have gone in.
However, the school is still avoiding responsibility.
That's strange.
- Excuse me?
- That doesn't seem like a simple accident.
- They said the container that was on top spilled when this cabinet fell over, right?
- Yes.
If that was really the case, due to the momentum of the cabinet the cleaning solution would have spread a lot further.
- But take a look at this.
- The bleached area is quite small.
Then it was directly over his head.
They poured it on the child in order to kill him.
What kind of jerk would do that kind of horrible thing to a child?
We should catch him. To see what kind of psycho bastard he is.
Grandma!
Hey, Grandma!  Hey!
Oh, Bong Yi. About that footage of the cafeteria that was broadcast, when was it shot?
Okay, the morning after Go Nam's accident?
Okay, I got it.
- I'm going to check the CCTV.
- Okay.
By chance, did someone straighten up or clean up after the accident?
No. The cafeteria was shut down right away and the cops told us not to touch anything.
- Nobody touched anything.
- Oh, is that right?
Just a moment please.
They came after PD Choi filmed.
Why did they come back and touch the items on the shelf?
It's mine.
- That's evidence.  Give it to me.  Elder.
- It's mine.
Elder, which way is home?
Oh, Officer Jung!
Hey, it's been a long time.
Don't you remember me?  We worked together at the Gudong Station.
Officer Kim?
You remember me!
I heard that you couldn't remember since you had surgery.
No, almost all my memories have returned except for my childhood.
That's a relief.
Grandma, did you go to school with a packed lunch again?
Ah, she says that her granddaughter didn't take her lunch,
so she takes an empty container to her every day.
The kids all eat the cafeteria food at school.
Well, I don't know where she lives.
Let's go, Grandma.  I'll take you home.
Let's go.  This way.
Let's go.
Sheesh, what is this?  It's a fake camera.
Why was this put up when it doesn't even work?
The Grandma's condition looks very bad.
A while ago, she was carrying a dead stray cat
and went all around the neighborhood.
So everyone whispered behind her back that the senile Grandma fed cats pesticides and killed them.
Ah, it's that Grandma.  The one Go Nam was talking about.
You heard about it?  But, like Go Nam said, I don't think that the Grandma would do that.
Do you remember?  In Gudong, for a time, there was that bastard who went around killing cats.
He would kill them and pull out their teeth.
Ah!
I think he came to this neighborhood.
The cat that the Grandma was carrying around, it didn't have any teeth because they were all pulled out.
The teeth were gone?
Attempted murder?
Here, look at this.
How is this a stain from something that fell and spilled? It was poured from above on purpose. Wasn't it?
- You investigated this half-heartedly, didn't you?
- Half-heartedly?
Ah, seriously! Who are you to tell us what to do when it's not your case?
You're the one who didn't look at the traces on the floor properly! How dare you give me that attitude?
I understand, so we'll go check.
This is an attempted murder case, so turn in the evidence immediately.  Understand?
Ah, seriously!
But back then, that Grandma said they saw them in the cafeteria.  The person running away.
How can you believe the words of an old person with dementia?  Even if we investigate, it can't be used as evidence.
But still, when she was talking to us, she was clear headed.  And her statement was very detailed.
Don't do a thing. Why are you making a big deal out of this?
How could someone do that to the child?
He's a wonderful young man.
Four cats.
The items were all skewed to the right side.
Officer Kim.  Who put up these flyers?
Oh, those? A street-kitten dad from our neighborhood.
A street-kitten dad?
- Welcome.
- Excuse me.
I'm a police officer.
I wanted to ask you about the terrorist attacks at Nari Elementary School.
Well, I already made a statement to the police.
I wanted to hear some more about it.  Please tell me about the situation at the time.
My store supplies the school with meat for meals.
On that day, as usual, I was unloading the meat from the truck.
I was so surprised that I went running right away.
- Go Nam.
- Don't! You'll get hurt!
In case that woman might get injured,
I pushed her aside, covered him with my clothes then lifted him and ran right out.
The owner of the butcher shop at the three-way intersection.  The one who ran with Go Nam on his back...
Move aside!
Welcome! What can I get you?
I want to have a meat party with my friends.  What would be good?
A meat party is nice.  Take your time choosing from here.
What is this meat over here?
Ah, the chuck meat?  When you put chuck meat in your mouth, it melts.
But since the part it comes from is small, it's a bit expensive.
If the number of friend is large, you should go with pork.
To me, pork is more delicious.
Hemispatial neglect?
What is that?
If you sustain an abnormality in your right parietal lobe,
then you may not be able to respond to visual, tactile, or auditory stimuli on the other side of your brain.
In serious cases, among the food in a dish,
they would only eat the food on the right side.
They would only put makeup on the right side and shave only the right side.
Ma'am!
- Oh my.
- Hello.
What brings you here? Aren't you on duty?
I was in the area for an investigation, so I stopped by to see how Chi Kook is doing.
Sorry. I haven't been able to come lately, right?
It's okay. You're busy anyway.
Chi Kook, Ba Reum is here.
I got this CD back from the detention center, along with Dong Koo.
Chi Kook's father used to like this music.
Oh, that's right.
I guess you remember those things.
It seems like you're healthy.
Chi Kook will wake up soon too.
Wait a minute.
Oh my, my little puppy,
I need to pack his lunch.
I heard you saw me running away.
Why did you do that?
I always pack the leftover fat for you.
How ungrateful of you to snitch on me.
Meat... She likes meat.
It doesn't matter. Who would listen to a grandma that has dementia?
I'll pack you some.
Huh?
This was here all along.
Do you know how much I looked for this?
The nurse let me borrow this.
Chi Kook, do you remember this song?
My memories from high school are coming back.
We listened to this song so many times when we went camping.
Yesterday, Dong Koo came and said that Chi Kook came in his dream.
Dong Koo? For what?
One day, Chi Kook brought his girlfriend over.
Yes.
Pesticide?
Everyone said that the old Grandma killed the cats with pesticides.
It's the cleaning solution from the cafeteria.
These keys. Did he steal them from the granny?
He rummaged through the shelves. That means he was looking for something.
Could it be these keys? What are they?
The cat that the Grandma was carrying around didn't have any teeth because they were all pulled out.
He said that he found the suspect. He found evidence, too.
The cat's teeth. Go Nam knew that these were cat's teeth.
That's how he knew the cat killer was Kim Byeong Tae.
Knowing that Kim Byeong Tae tried to kill the child?
Just because of the cat, he went as far as to kill a child?
Ah, what is this key for?
It was the key to the music box.
What's this?
What were they burning?
Hwang Min Ji, 6 year old child, dead from burns all over her body.
The victim's friend, a mentally disabled child,
pointed towards part-timers who worked at the gas station.
However, the mentally disabled child's statement was deemed unreliable. He was eliminated from the list of suspects.
Min Ji testified that the criminal was wearing red-colored clothes before dying.
Due to inconclusive evidence or motive to find Han Soo Cheol guilty,
he was excluded from the suspect list. The case ended up as an unresolved case.
She was being adopted but after that case,
she kept being called to the station for testifying due to which her adoption got canceled.
The reason for the dismissal was that she kept saying unnecessary things which annoyed people around her.
She has been living here since then.
As I was investigating, I read that she has a mental disability.
Oh no, Angela has a hearing disability.
That's why her pronunciation isn't great but intelligence wise she has no problems at all.
However, seeing that communication is impossible for her, the police seem to have decided it's an intellectual disability.
Angela!
No. Oppa isn't coming. He won't keep his promise.
He will come.
- Oppa isn't coming.
- Don't worry. Okay?
It's just that he's taking some time.
What's the matter?
- I think Michaela has been hurt.
- No.
- Oppa isn't coming.
- Last year, her Oppa visited her twice.
On his second visit, he must've promised that he'd take her from here the next time he came.
But that guy... Gosh, that guy...
"That guy?"
Never mind that.
Do you remember what you told the policemen a long time ago?
Can you tell him that?
The police? No matter how much I tell them, they never trust what I have to say.
You can trust me.
Can you put your trust in me and tell me?
When I was young...
- I'm sorry.
- You are doing this on purpose, aren't you?
- No.
- Don't you know numbers?
- I know numbers.
Hey, just go and do your job.
Oh.
Customer! I'm sorry.
My employee keeps making mistakes in calculations. Now that I've seen your face well,
when you come here next time, I'll give you an automatic car wash for free. Sorry. Here.
- Two people?
- What kind of bastard messes with young children?
Crimes against children are all done by psychopaths. Child murder, child sexual assault, child abuse. All of these.
Bastards who have given up on being human.
Two days ago, in an elementary school cafeteria in Mujin,
"A" suffered severe burns from a cleaning solution spill.
Go Nam!
If only that wench hadn't shown up, that little kid would have been dead now.
He will wake up. Don't you worry about it.
Will our boy be fine?
Both of them are predators.
Son of a bitch.
- This–
- He suffered serious burns.
He couldn't have screamed if it's this serious, right?
Of course, he couldn't have. With his respiratory tract in that state.
I heard a kid screaming his lungs out in the cafeteria.
This freaking scumbag.
Who the hell are you?
Untie me right now. What are you doing?
You want to have all the fun to yourself?
- I want to have some fun too.
- Damn it.
Save me! Save me!
As Go Nam went around trying to clear his classmate's grandmother from her unfair false accusation,
he saw this.
And he realized it was cat teeth at once.
He went to the police station and told them, but no one would listen to a child.
So he went to the broadcasting station.
Oh! Sheesh, I told her to come alone.
The granny was quite clear-minded when she saw you. Even when she gave her testimony to the police.
If only the police would have listened to her and checked at least once.
- You would have been arrested right away.
- Spare me! Please spare me! Please!
But there is one thing I don't understand.
Why would you try to kill that child just because he found out that you kill cats?
Where did that little kid hide it?
The secret behind this key.
That music box. The Pandora's box.
In 1999, near the school where you and Han Soo Cheol used to go,
there was a case of animal abuse where a dog was burned to death.
In the end, the culprit wasn't caught.
The police didn't investigate it seriously either because it was just an animal, not a human.
After that, you started becoming bolder.
Killing animals wasn't as fun for you anymore, so this time it would be a person.
Min Ji is my friend.
A young child at that.
Min Ji.
And you took this photo.
To reminisce about your murders.
But Go Nam took the keyring and saw this picture.
So you had to kill Go Nam.
Before he could tell the broadcasting station and the police.
That was only a drop. But the pain was unbearable, wasn't it?
Then what do you think those kids went through?
You can't even imagine the pain their parents must have felt losing their young kids, can you?
Because psychopaths like you can't feel emotions.
You can't even imagine the pain others feel.
That's why you need to go through the same thing.
Because it's an eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
Kim Byeong Tae.
Huh?
Kim Byeong Tae was murdered.
It's that bastard's doing.
He couldn't have gotten that far. Search through all of the nearby alleyways. Hurry up!
Detective Kim go that way. Detective Park, you go that way.
- Yes, sir.
You were the detective in charge of the May 1999 gasoline terror case, right?
I've just sent you a photo.
Could you check it for me? Quick.
- It's the suspect, right?
- Yes, that's right.
What about the guy next to him?
A friend that used to work with him at the gas station.
Han Soo Cheol is also in danger.
Check if Han Soo Cheol is alive right now.
Right away! Hurry up!
Wait a minute.
Just listen to what I have to say! Wait.
I don't know anything about it. I really don't!
Why would I kill somebody?
Hey! It wasn't me!
Hello?
Yes, who is this?
What? Who are you?
Soo Cheol, is that you?
Kim Byeong Tae?
How come you called me? You know my new number?
I did?
I didn't call you.
It's the truth!
That's just how we ended up talking to each other over the phone. We decided on meeting sometime later.
And that was the end of the call.
So were you on a phone call with a ghost or something?
Ah, this is driving me nuts!
Oh, right. I have an alibi for last night.
- Who is it?
- The employee at my gas station.
You can go and check.
Excuse me.
Yes?
He's right.
That employee told me he was with you.
That means I'm completely cleared of these false charges, right?
Take these off then. Hurry up.
Too bad for you, though.
That employee has a mental disability.
You know, right? That his testimony wouldn't work.
A long time ago, you were set free because of the same loophole. It's quite ironic.
You can't escape this time.
I didn't do it.
It's not me!
It's his doing. Lee Jae Sik, the guy who killed Kang Duk Su.
No way. But all of the evidence is pointing to that guy.
What kind of a fool would kill a person and leave all of the evidence in their office?
The real killer planned all of this.
Is that so?
But there's one thing I don't understand.
Why didn't he kill him too?
That's right.
Kill him. Kill him.
He burned someone's precious daughter to death and feels no remorse. Are you just going to let him be?
There must be a way to make him pay for his crimes without having to kill him.
Seong Yo Han is disappearing from my head.
I'm going back to myself,
back to being Jung Ba Reum.
If someone had killed Han Seo Joon the same way
he had killed his victims, what would I have felt?
Would I have been happier than I am now?
It's Hyung's birthday today.
Oppa!
There you are.
What was it you wanted to say?
Bong Yi.
Yeah?
I'm...
a little sick.
Where? Does it hurt a lot?
But you know what, somehow I feel like I might get better.
Today, I saw such hope.
So will you wait for me until I fully recover?
I'll wait.
I can wait.
It might take a very long time.
I don't care about that.
I'm going to wait for you until I'm a gray-haired grandmother.
So you can't dump me later on just because I'm old.
♫  Tonight I regret letting you go  ♫
Should we go down to the countryside to live together when I get better?
I'll be an officer in the countryside.
Sounds nice.
♫  What I want most now is you in my heart  ♫
♫  Heart  ♫
You didn't have to come up here. You're a busy man after all.
I'll be seeing you only two years from now. Of course, I had to see you off.
Hoon Seok, did you name the cat?
Yeah, Toto!
It's the name of the puppy
in the Wizard of Oz. Toto.
Toto?
Wow! You've chosen such a cool name!
Hoon Seok, if there's something you're unsure of as you raise Toto, you can go to Kitty Cafe.
You say it too.
- "Kitty Cafe?"
- Yeah.
You can ask at the Kitty Cafe. You'll find a lot of information there.
But wouldn't Toto's mommy be sad? She won't be with Toto anymore.
She'll be fine because she trusts that you will raise Toto well.
We have to get on the bus. Let's go Hoon Seok.
- Take care.
- Yes.
Mom, who's that man?
Nobody. Let's go.
Say bye to Hyung.
Breaking news.
Child A, who was recently
found with cleaning solution spilled all over him,
suffered severe burns all over his body. Battling  death,
he miraculously overcame the crisis and is in recovery.
Meanwhile A...
Ta-da!
Are you having a birthday party?
With mom and dad?
Leaving me out?
Let's not see each other again.
Let's not see each other for the rest of our lives.
To be honest, I hate you more than that bastard Han Seo Joon.
I'm sorry, Hyung.
I'm really sorry.
I miss you, Hyung.
Mom.
Dad.
I miss you.
Bong Yi. I made a reservation at a great place for tomorrow night.
Alright. See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
What brings you by, Detective?
Let's have a drink.
Detective, is something up?
It's my brother's birthday.
I was just craving alcohol, and then as I was drinking Soju,
I thought it was really pitiful.
And then you came to my mind.
That's why I came.
I'm glad you did.
I've heard you treated my brother really well.
What did I do? The Priest took care of me very well.
The Priest talked about you so much.
Always worried about you.
Do you know why I hated my Hyung and did not see him?
Isn't it because he forgave Han Seo Joon?
No.
That was just an excuse. Han Seo Joon.
Because I was uncomfortable.
He became like that because of me.
He lured Han Seo Joon to save me.
When I saw his uncomfortable body, I felt like going crazy.
Because of my guilt.
I'd rather not see him at all.
To be comfortable. For my heart to be relaxed.
The Priest knew as well.
It's not because you hated him, but because you were sorry.
Should I show you a picture of him when he was young?
Oh, the Priest's necklace.
Ah, that's right. I told you before that my brother had the same thing.
Yes.
He was always wearing this.
My mom must've made two of them.
But he didn't have this.
It's small and hard to see but look.
- It's my Hyung.
- Wow.
It's pretty, isn't it?
Yes.
He was smart since he was a kid.
He studied well too.
The two of you look the same since you guys were young.
Oh, is that so?
Ah, you must have a lot of memories.
I don't have any siblings, so it's a shame.
Hey, Officer Jung.
Yes?
Do you want to be my younger brother?
Younger brother?
Yeah. I want to be a Hyung like my Hyung was to you.
You are by yourself.
Yes.
Please do so, Hyung.
I like it.
My dongsaeng, Jung Ba Reum.
Hey, let's cheer to becoming brothers.
Today, let's drink. Here, cheers.
Cheers!
Let's drink and go!
Hey, where's the restroom?
Restroom.
That's weird.
Hyung's necklace is gone.
Oh, the Priest's necklace. He was always wearing this.
Did it get mixed up with other evidence?
Was this knife always like this?
Isn't this blood?
He left something precious.
I compared the blood on the knife with Oh Bong Yi's blood sample and Seong Yo Han's blood sample,
but they don't match.
Then who's blood is it?
Just in case, please return it to the system and see if there's a match.
But when did I get this scar?
Good morning.
Ah, I want to confirm the evidence.
You gave it to the Evidence Storage Team? Okay.
- Ah, Bong Yi.
- Yes?
Will you go meet Team Leader Park Doo Suk from the Evidence Storage Team?
I have something to confirm for the evidence from Kim Byeong Tae's case.
Yes. I understand.
Did the results come out?
It's weird. That blood is Kang Duk Su.
What? Kang Duk Su's blood?
Why did Kang Duk Su's blood show up
on that knife?
Hyung.
Mu Chi Hyung.
Oppa!
Bong Yi.
This?
Ah, this. Do you remember this? Right before your accident, you gave–
Were you wearing this necklace the day you met Go Nam?
Only one truth.
That...
This? It's pretty, isn't it?
The Oppa that I really like made this for me.
Oppa?
- He's coming.
- Oh.
Bong Yi.
That kid found out
that these are cat's teeth.
But this cat looks like it was done by that guy, right?
It has no teeth.
Show your friends and tell them to report it if there are any witnesses.
Oppa, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Oppa. Oppa!
This...
Why is this in my house?
From tomorrow, everything breaks.
Now, goodbye forever.
No. No, you can't.
No.
Move.
I said move!
I said move.
No. Don't open it.
I'm telling you to not open it, please.
No. No.
It was me.
It wasn't Seong Yo Han.
But it was me.
Ba Reum, Chi Kook woke up!
He regained consciousness.
What?
Chi Kook is awake. Let's go in.
How do I look?
I asked to not make me a monster.
I begged.
But you completely turned away from my prayers.
Then what kind of god are you?
From now on, I'm a god.
The people who believe your bullshit and follow you, I'll judge them.