I almost died.
But you didn't.
You bitch! You keep hitting me!
-[screaming]
-Oh my God!
-Let her go.
-[sobbing]
[Mallory] Kimmie…
welcome to the family.
Horace wants us to meet our new boss.
-Looks to me like you the problem.
-[grunting]
So you gonna piss on me
when I'm dead, huh?
[spluttering] You nasty fuck.
You gonna show us where that safe at.
Catch his ass! Catch his ass!
-[Charles grunting]
-Yeah.
-[gun firing]
-[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
Fuck. [panting]
Fuck!
[breathing heavily]
[tense music playing]
Fuck.
[accelerating]
[tires screeching]
[cell phone ringing]
Fuck you.
[sighs]
[panting]
[line ringing]
-[phone buzzing]
-Stop calling. Stop that.
[sniffles, sighs]
[line ringing]
-[Felicia chuckles]
-Where you at?
[Felicia on phone] I stay at this motel.
Where's that at?
It's called the You Can Stay Here motel.
You know where that's at?
Uh, fuck no. [scoffs]
[Felicia chuckles]
Well, I can come to you.
Well, I got a meeting right now,
so I can, um…
I can come to you after, okay?
You know, baby, after last night,
I'm ready to do whatever you want.
Well you better, bitch.
[Felicia giggles] I will, Daddy.
[call waiting beeping]
This nigga. Goddamn.
[sirens wailing]
What's all that noise?
-[sirens wailing]
-It's police outside or somethin'.
It's always like that around here.
So you're living dangerous, huh?
[Felicia] Shit,
ain't everywhere dangerous?
Not when you with me.
[Felicia] I know, Daddy.
'Cause you can protect a bitch, huh?
-Mm-hmm. You better know it.
-[call waiting beeping]
-[sighs] Hold on one second.
-A'ight.
[Roy] Stay on the line.
What, nigga?
[breathing heavily]
I need you to come to my house.
I can't do that right now,
'cause I gotta go to this meeting
to meet this stupid-ass bitch.
Look, Roy, I need you to come to my house.
[Roy] And what did I just say?
Roy, I got robbed.
Nigga, we all getting robbed.
-Roy…
-She robbing the whole damn company.
[panting]
You not listening to me.
[Roy] Yes, I am listening to you, brother.
She's stealing every damn share we got.
Listen to me! All right?
You know what's really crazy, brother?
It's Father's gonna be messing
with the same girl I was messing with.
It's bad.
Charles, you keep saying
the same damn thing. You know what?
I ain't got time for you
and your bullshit. You know that?
[weeping] Goddamn it, Roy.
[Roy] Hey, I got one word
of advice for you.
You better make sure
you in that damn office,
because I'm about to make sparks fly.
-Roy, I need you--
-Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
[breathing heavily]
[phone clatters]
[whispering] Yeah.
Yeah.
You still there?
[Felicia chuckles]
Good, good, good. Look, um, I'mma call you
after my meeting, all right?
A'ight.
[Roy] And you better answer it
on first ring.
-I will.
-Good.
[Felicia] Thank you, Daddy.
Thank you, little bitch. [chuckles]
[sighs]
[exhales]
[sirens wailing]
[chuckles] I told you.
[chuckling] Got his ass like that?
Mm-hmm. Only from one night too.
-Mm-mm-mm.
-[chuckles]
Damn.
Shit, I got you like that, nigga.
You ain't got shit like that.
What the hell you talking about?
[chuckles] He called me and left me
three messages when I was asleep.
Damn, do that nigga ever sleep?
[chuckling] Not with
all that coke he be doing.
[phone buzzing]
-Shit, who that calling my phone?
-What?
[groans]
Hold on. Shh.
[tense music playing]
Carmine.
[Carmine] What up?
The hell going on out there?
[Carmine] Double homicide.
[police radio chatter]
Here?
[Carmine] Two doors down from you.
What?
[Carmine] Yeah.
[siren wailing outside]
-Oh, shit.
-[dogs barking]
All right, all right.
I, uh… I'll be out there.
[Trackson sighs]
What happened?
Shit. Dead niggas.
[tsks] Man,
that ain't nothin' around here.
I guess.
I'll be back. Let me get dressed.
No, don't leave, Daddy. I want that dick.
And I want that pussy.
Give me a minute.
Let me handle this business.
[groans]
Ah, shit.
[phone buzzing]
Yeah.
[Horace] Angel. It's Horace.
Yeah, I can barely hear you.
You… You there?
Yeah, I'm… I'm on a plane.
[Angel] The plane?
[scoffs] You can talk
on a plane like this?
[Horace] Yeah.
What airline is that?
It's a private plane.
[Angel chuckling] Damn!
Send me a picture of the plane.
[Horace] So, uh…
you don't care how I'm doing?
Yeah, uh… How… How you doin'?
[Horace] You don't give a shit.
[sighs] Why… Why are you
playing these games?
Oh, I'm playing games?
[Angel] Yeah, I mean, you know
I don't know you that well. Like…
I want you to be all right, all right?
But I don't really know you.
[Horace] I appreciate your honesty.
I thought you would.
Look, um, I'm trying
to get ahold of Kimmie.
She's not answering.
Oh, she--
She probably didn't answer 'cause
you're calling from an unknown number.
-Ah. Tell her to answer the phone.
-Okay, will do.
Listen, uh, James,
uh, he has a credit card for you.
James?
[Horace] Yeah, the butler.
Ah. Butler nigga.
[Horace] You can get
what you need. Okay? Um…
Tell Kimmie to answer her phone.
Okay, I'll go tell her right now.
-Great.
-All right.
[chuckling excitedly]
[whispering] Let's fucking go! Oh my God.
[knocking on door]
Yeah?
Horace is calling
from an unknown number. Answer it.
Okay.
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[Horace] You ready?
[Kimmie] Well, I'm about
to get dressed now.
Don't be early. Make them wait.
Oh. Okay.
[Horace] One thing
they can't stand is waiting.
[scoffs] All right.
Especially that damn Roy.
It's going to agitate the shit out of him.
Got it.
[Horace] You know, Olivia and Norman,
they'll be sitting there,
like snakes in the dark.
You seem to really be enjoying this.
[Horace] I am.
'Cause they have no idea who the bitch is
that's about to walk in the door.
I'm glad you got all this confidence.
[Horace] I have all the confidence
and the power.
[coughing]
You good?
That don't sound like power to me.
[coughs]
[sighs]
[inhales deeply]
Let me tell you something.
If I die tomorrow,
it'll be with a smile on my face.
All the shit.
I get to fuck up their lives.
They really must've done something to you.
[Horace] Ah, you have no idea.
Well, um… I will be ready.
I want books, chapters, and verses.
[Kimmie] I will give you all the tea.
[chuckling] Okay?
[Horace] You don't know this yet,
but when I get to the facility,
I'm gonna tap into the cameras
so I can see their faces.
I wish I could be there in person.
Well, that's the next best thing.
You don't seem excited.
I'm feeling it out.
[Horace] Own that room, Kimmie.
Own that shit.
I'm trying.
Don't try.
That fucking Jules?
Remember what he did to you?
[spluttering] Shit,
now… now you getting me there.
[Horace] He trafficked you.
And my brother Norman?
That's his business partner.
They were making money off of you like
you were from some third world country.
And they were licking their lips
to make even more off of little Sylvie.
All right, you a little too good at that.
-Am I?
-Yeah.
The way Roy humiliated me…
That's my girl.
You want the real Kimmie to walk in there?
[Horace] You damn right.
Go get them motherfuckers.
All right.
[breathing shakily]
[dramatic music playing]
-[siren wailing]
-[music fades]
[personnel chattering]
[tense music playing]
What we got?
One of ours.
Who?
Shake Shake.
And Daga.
[Jules] Where's the new little young girl?
[Trackson] Nowhere to be found.
-[Jules] You think she did this?
-Nah, nah, man. She's just a kid.
Ain't doing nothing like this.
Yeah. Yeah, you're right.
You ask me, man,
this looks professional for sure.
Yeah, somebody got that bitch.
Guess she pumped the wrong one.
Well, you know,
Rain was at the club last night.
What?
Yeah. I left you some messages.
[keypad clacking]
What was she doing there?
She was just hanging out.
But I definitely saw her
talk to the young chick.
[dramatic sting]
So she did this?
Nah, man, Rain ain't no professional.
She couldn't do this.
Yeah, but she messing with a nigga who is.
-Who?
-Our boss.
[exhales] Damn… Damn, you right.
Who was she with?
Alex was driving her.
Officer Alex?
Yeah.
So this is his work.
Hey, no, Alex a little bitch.
Come on, Jules. You know
Alex ain't doing no shit like this.
You sure?
Yes.
You got your thumb on him?
That's my dawg. Alex ain't capable
of doing no shit like this.
No way. Mm-mm.
[Jules sighs]
You find that young girl,
and you bring her to me.
I'm all over it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Roy was there last night too?
-Yep. Mm-hmm.
What happened?
You know Roy, man, VIP. [chuckling]
Fucking with them hood bitches, huh?
Yeah, man.
He, uh, ended up connecting with Felicia,
and now he got her number and shit.
Ah, shit.
She told me that he promised her
that she was gonna work for him
or somethin'. Like, what?
-There he goes on that bullshit.
-Yeah, yeah.
Listen, I gotta get back to the office.
I need you to stay on this.
Sure, I got you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[sighs]
[line rings]
-[phone rings]
-[horse neighs]
Yo.
[Trackson] Man, Jules is asking
all kind of crazy shit about you.
Like what?
[Trackson] You know
that Shake Shake and Daga are dead, right?
What?
[Trackson] Yeah.
Okay, so, what's that gotta do with me?
Because you was at the club with Rain.
You was with her.
-Yeah, doing my job.
-[Trackson] Yeah.
The shit that hit them
looks professional though.
Wait, he thinks I did it?
[Trackson] No, I… I told him no
because you… you with me.
I really don't like him asking about you,
though, man. It's making me nervous.
[Alex] Yeah, me either.
Make sure you tell him
where my loyalty is.
Yeah, I know where your loyalty lies,
but, you know,
Jules may be having all kind of crazy shit
going on in his head.
[chuckles] Man, he crazy.
He sure does.
Just… Just tell me what I gotta do.
[Trackson] Just lay low, man.
I'll keep an eye on it.
-I'll let you know.
-Yeah, yeah, do that.
You… You bringing Kimmie
to the office, right?
[Alex] Yeah.
All right, all right.
I'll see you when you get there.
All right, talk to you later.
Shit.
[horse neighs]
-That's what's up.
-How long do we have to wait for her?
[Rain] I know.
[Sylvie scoffs]
[Angel] Damn. Okay, look at you.
-Right?
-[chuckles]
Shit, she look like
she know what she doin'.
-She do.
-I'm glad y'all feel like that.
Girl, you better fake it.
They don't know no different.
I'mma try my best. [chuckles]
[scoffs] If Roy's stupid-ass can make it
at that company, you know damn well--
Girl, that don't make me feel no better.
[chuckles] Okay, you right.
You look strong, big sis.
Thank you, Sylvie.
You sure you don't want me
to come with you?
Nah, I'm good. I gotta do this by myself.
-Okay.
-Shit, well, you look good.
Where you get that wardrobe from?
The boutique.
We went shopping. [chuckling]
Shit, I'm about to do the same ting.
With what money?
Butler nigga said he got
a credit card for me.
Angel, you must got that angel--
[Angel] Nah, nah,
don't even start that shit.
-I'm just saying--
-Rain--
All right, all right, I'm about to get
out of here. I will see y'all later.
Okay. You call me
as soon as that meeting's over.
I will.
-All right. Go get 'em, girl. [chucking]
-Bye, y'all. [chuckling]
-Come on, I'll walk you out.
-Bye.
Oh, wait, Sylvie. Um…
When I get back, we need to talk.
-Yeah?
-Okay.
[Kimmie exhales sharply]
Go get 'em, bitch. [chuckling]
-[Alex] Wow.
-What?
You look amazing.
I know.
Open the door.
-[car door opens]
-Thank you.
Go get 'em, bitch!
-Wait, that nigga drives her?
-Yeah.
-Okay, well, I don't trust that nigga.
-[engine starts]
Yeah, but he been trying to prove himself.
Okay, well, he knocked the shit out of me.
You probably deserved it.
[Angel] What?
[Rain] Angel, I don't have time
for this right now. I had a long night.
-I'm going to bed.
-Okay, well, don't trust him.
Where you goin'?
I wanna see the horses.
Sylvie, you know Kimmie
do not want you wandering around here.
Well, she's not here, so she can relax.
But how can I relax and go to sleep
if you wandering around?
I'm just going to the barn
behind the house.
-Sylvie.
-I'll keep an eye on her.
You better.
[Angel] I got it.
[door opens]
You walking too fast.
[sighs]
[tense music playing]
-Hey.
I can't believe this.
What?
That he got us with this shit.
[chuckles]
No, he got you.
[chuckling] Oh, now you got to admit
this son of a bitch is smart.
Shit.
He ain't that damn smart.
He married a whore.
It worked.
He don't love her.
I know that.
He just did this shit to fuck us up.
And it worked.
[sighs] Look, did you come here
to try to depress me?
Or did you come here for a meeting?
I came here to listen
to what this dumb bitch has to say,
and hear how stupid she is,
and come up with a plan.
-[scoffs]
-That is exactly why I'm here.
And to see how this nigga
gonna be trying to tie our hands.
No, he's tied yo hands.
You know, I always got
three or four trains running,
but in your case,
you had three or four trains
being run on you.
[chuckles sarcastically]
Are you done
with your stupid-ass comments?
[laughing]
See, never let your enemy
know what you're doing next.
You damn right.
[chuckling]
But you know what?
Shit, it don't even really matter.
'Cause them cancer patients,
they gonna make
all the difference in the world.
They will take the company down.
Are you in on that?
I swear, Norman,
you and your damn conspiracies.
How in the hell would I be in on it?
I don't know. I don't know.
I can't give nobody cancer.
'Cause if I could,
all you motherfuckers would be dead.
Twice.
[chuckles] You are in on it, aren't you?
[scowls]
No, see, you always have
your nasty little hands into everything.
And what you got yo nasty little hands on?
[exhales] I don't know.
I'm just trying to figure this shit out.
See, on one hand, he marries this bitch.
On another hand, he's…
He's talking about this little Latin kid.
Yeah, well,
he always did like Latin women.
No. [chuckling]
No, I… See, I always thought that too.
But this…
But this is a man.
What?
He been talking about
the boy stole his watch or somethin'.
I'm not buying that.
I… I… I… I don't get it.
Uh, look, it don't matter anyway,
'cause he killed
the little motherfucker this morning.
-What? You shitting me?
-Nah, nah.
You see… see, I think he's just trying
to cover up that Kimmie shit,
or… or… or… or maybe that car stuff.
But then…
I think the young man pissed him off.
You see what I'm sayin'?
[Sylvie] Can you believe
Black people live like this?
-No.
-[horses neighing]
What?
All this shit ain't fair.
What do you mean?
The way that we struggle
and he gets to have shit like this?
-[Sylvie] You mad.
-You damn right I'm mad. I want it.
[Sylvie scoffs] Well, it's not yours.
I know that,
but that doesn't mean I can't want it.
You know, you're strange.
What?
I mean, this man has given us all of this,
and you're mad?
-He ain't given us shit.
-What?
You have to have sex with him.
-Who told you that?
-Kimmie, she told me everything.
Well, she should have told you
that I don't have sex with him.
I just danced for him a couple times.
[scoffs] Okay, well,
must've been a hell of a dance
for you to be here with us.
Look, you got somethin' to say?
No, I just wanna see the horses.
Oh, then look at the horses.
-You got a bad attitude.
-Yeah, whatever.
[pensive music playing]
[chuckles] Hey. I saw you earlier, right?
-[Sylvie] Hi.
-Sylvie, right?
[chuckles]
-Oh, the horse is so beautiful. Can I…
-Yeah.
Uh, his name is Duck.
[chuckling] A horse named Duck?
[chuckling] He's, uh,
Mr. Bellarie's favorite.
Although he doesn't ride anymore.
-Oh, yeah, I guess that's hard.
-Yeah.
Do you ride?
No. I always wanted to.
Well, uh, I take care of the horses.
I could show you.
Who are you?
[chuckles] Uh, sorry.
Uh, my name is Glen.
Sylvie.
-I like that name.
-Thanks.
So you work here?
Uh, in the summers and on the weekends.
I'm in college at Berkeley.
Oh, okay, I see. [chuckles]
Uh, Jules is my dad.
-Jules?
-He's the head of security.
-Oh yeah. Yeah, I met the head guy here.
-Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, no, that's… [chuckles] That's Whitman.
Uh, he runs this place.
My dad runs the company.
Oh. Okay. Nice.
Well, uh… I will gladly show you
how to ride if you want.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Sir.
[Roy] Jules. [exhales]
So… I heard you were
at the club last night.
Yeah, I was. [chuckles]
I thought we talked
about you staying away.
[clicks tongue]
You know, I don't really give a shit.
You know, because I thoroughly enjoyed it.
It was fun.
And, Jules, let me remind you,
I'm still in this business.
The laundering business.
-Stay out the club.
-Hey.
Jules, I'm going to go
as much as I want to.
-You understand?
-Roy…
Speaking of, I need to, uh…
I need to talk to you.
So sit down, please.
[clears throat] Since we gonna
talk about the club…
[sighs] Well?
So is, uh…
Kimmie really coming to work here?
She's on her way in now.
Hm. That's some shit, ain't it? [chuckles]
Okay, since they, uh…
They all wanna play games,
bring people in that's new, I want you
to bring someone else in for me.
Okay.
Like I said, I was at the club, right?
-Officer Trackson told me this morning.
-Yeah.
There's this bitch
that, uh, works at the club,
and I want her here.
[scoffs, tsks]
[sighs]
Okay.
I want her here as my assistant.
Roy, you know this girl can't even count.
Well, she… She can count 12 inches.
Because she had 12 inches
down her throat last night.
[chuckles]
Are you talking about you, sir?
Who the fuck else
would I be talking about?
I'm just saying, you probably
wasn't just the only one in the club--
Nigga, I don't give a shit, okay?
Like I said, I want her here.
You cannot bring her in here.
And why not?
Let me hook you up
with a nice Philly jawn.
I don't…
I don't give a fuck
about no Philly jawn, okay?
I want what I want,
and I told you who I want.
-Make it happen. Look.
-You're not listening.
Look, look, look, let me…
let me… let me break it down to you.
My father's about to die,
and I want what I want, okay?
Now, Jules, I've known you
for a long time now. A long time.
I like you. I really do.
But please…
please don't forget who you work for.
And when I tell you to go get somebody,
fucking do it, okay?
So go get Felicia,
and get her here as my assistant.
Copy?
She can't come in here.
Yes, she can.
Don't do it.
Make it happen.
[Jules sighs]
[groans]
I'm about to have her in here
doing some crazy shit. [chuckling]
[snorting] Ah.
Yeah, that's good.
Real good. Ah.
Shit.
[dreamy music playing]
[horses neighing]
What the fuck?
[dreamy music continues]
[chuckling] Yo.
Damn.
-Yeah, this is Mr. Bellarie's collection--
-Yo, is this a Lambo?
Yes, it is.
Mr. Bellarie said you can drive
any one of these, except--
Can I drive this one?
Yes, you can.
-Shit, well, where are the keys?
-They're in them.
[chuckling] Shit.
So Mr. Bellarie
must be pretty fond of you, huh?
Why you say that?
Well, he won't let his sons
touch these cars, let alone drive them.
I just helped him out with a situation.
Oh yeah?
Yeah, he was getting robbed,
and… and I stepped in.
Is that right?
Who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm Whitman.
I'm his head of security.
Oh. Okay.
I didn't know anything
about him getting robbed.
Then you must be shitty
if you're head of security.
Well, I'm head of security
here at the house.
I work directly underneath Jules.
Oh, that nigga?
Is there a problem?
You tell me.
Nah, there's no problem.
You're a guest of Mr. Bellarie's.
I'm just happy you were there
to help him out.
Hm. [clicks tongue]
Yeah. Well, uh, I wanna take this one.
All right, well, we'll have it dropped off
at the front door.
Just like that, huh?
That's how Mr. Bellarie does it.
Hm. Do what you do for him.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I might wanna drive three or four
of these things, man. [chuckles]
Yo, look at this convertible.
[chuckling] Shit.
Damn.
Hey, get the keys for this too.
Hey!
Hurry up, security nigga!
[cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[Horace] Are you there?
Hey. Uh, no, not yet.
We're about to pull up soon, though.
[Horace] You ready?
[sighs] Um…
Yeah.
I wanna give you
a little more insight on Mallory.
She came to see me after you left.
What happened?
[Kimmie] She said she wanted
to welcome me to the family.
She brought flowers.
[Horace] That's nice.
[Kimmie] If you say so.
[Horace] You don't trust her?
Hell no.
[Horace] You're smart.
She plays all sides to get what she wants.
-My type of chick.
-She's not just a pretty face.
She's ruthless.
-She don't think I know how bad she is.
-I thought so.
How are you?
[Horace sighs] I'm breathin'.
Did you make it yet?
Be there in a… Landing in about an hour.
[Kimmie] Okay.
Call me as soon as you get done.
I will. [sighs]
[Horace] Okay. Bye.
Bye.
[dogs barking]
[birds chirping]
Yo, butler nigga!
[happy music playing]
[sighs]
Sir, I'd prefer if you called me James.
I'm sorry, Nigga James.
Um, Horace said
you had a credit card for me?
Yes, sir. I'm told you're going shopping.
Shall I call ahead?
[chuckling] Shit.
Okay, well, where's it at?
Let me see.
-This in my name?
-Yes, sir.
[spluttering] Wait, wait, wait.
Who… Who gonna take the bill?
It's on Mr. Bellarie's account.
You don't have to worry about the bill.
For real?
Yes, sir.
What's the limit?
I don't believe Mr. Bellarie set one.
Are you shitting me?
No, sir, I'm not.
-And I can shop like I want?
-Yes, sir.
[chuckling]
How long on this damn car, man?
They're dusting it off right now.
It'll be up.
Oh! Let's do this shit, James!
Yes. Yes, sir.
My nigga.
[whispering] Motherfucker.
This shit is crazy.
Hey, you got some champagne, Nigga James?
Pour it!
[horses nickering]
[claps] Hoo-hoo-hoo!
This shit look good on me, boy, I tell ya.
[chuckles]
Appreciate it, Mr. Butler Nigga.
Blue interior.
[engine starts]
["What I Do" by Wendell 'UTK' Nelson
playing on speakers]
[engine revving]
[chuckling]
♪ And I make it look easy
Got nothing to prove ♪
♪ And I'm stepping on you
Wrecking it… ♪
[tires screeching]
Open the gate, niggas!
[music continues]
Appreciate it!
[engine revving]
[tense music playing]
[Mallory] Jules.
Yes, ma'am.
[ambient office noise]
Where's Gillian?
Roy had me remove her.
Mm. And you did so without asking me?
Just trying to keep the peace.
Where's Calvin?
-Same situation, ma'am.
-Mm.
So I have some idiot driving me that
doesn't know where the hell he's going.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Jules, it smells like
he washes his body in ass juice.
And you have him driving me?
I can get you a new driver.
[chuckles] This how
we gonna do this, Jules?
That's what you gonna do?
You gonna have these old-ass niggas
driving me around?
Ma'am, this man is highly trained.
Highly trained in what?
Smelling like a fucking trash can?
Is that his talent?
It's good to see you.
And why are you here already anyway?
I'm here to greet the new COO.
Oh, you're here to greet
the new COO, aren't you?
Then why don't you greet the new COO
downstairs curbside?
Mallory…
What, you too good to do that?
-No, I'm not.
-Bitch, I'm the boss here.
So why don't you go greet the whore
that you gave Roy,
that's now both our bosses, curbside?
Yes, ma'am.
Coming up here hiding.
Think I'm fucking stupid?
I run this bitch.
I wasn't hiding.
You were hiding.
[music ends]
[pensive music playing]
Attorney Varney.
Well, hello. [chuckles]
Where is she?
She's not here yet.
Oh, she's not here, huh?
-Not yet.
-So she's late.
You know how much I love that.
Well, I'm sure she'll be here soon.
Soon will be late.
[Varney chuckles]
[sighs] And on her first day.
And on her first day, she's already
annoying the shit out of me.
So have you decided on
how you gonna handle this?
Absolutely.
I'm gonna be the sweet, amazing Mallory,
as I vomit in my mouth
every time I look at her ass.…
[chuckles] That sounds
like a perfect plan.
Do you know that she went shopping?
-Hm. Didn't know.
-Lau called me from the boutique.
She spent $124,000.
That sounds like somebody else I know.
-On five suits.
-Right.
Well, at least you would've gotten six.
You think I'm in the mood for these jokes?
[chuckles] I'm sorry, forgive me.
Dumb bitch,
she even bought all the wrong things.
She gonna be coming up here
looking all stupid.
This is really testing
everything I know about myself.
Mallory, I'm sure you'll be fine.
I will be fine.
Not that it matters, because she's late…
but is everyone in place?
Yeah. Everyone's gathered in the lobby
to meet her as she comes off the elevator.
-Gathered in the lobby?
-Yeah.
-What's this special shit?
-[chuckles]
I didn't get this shit when I came here.
-Who the hell told them to do that?
-Your father-in-law sent an email.
-My father-in-law?
-Yes.
He did what?
-Sent an email.
-Uh-huh.
Telling us all to gather in the lobby,
when she comes
off the elevator, to greet her.
Oh, so my father-in-law
sent a new email for his new wife.
-[chuckles]
-Look at that, his new wife.
He's all excited, huh?
-This special shit. Yeah.
-[chuckling]
Is Roy here?
[Varney inhales deeply]
[sighs] I heard he's here.
Mm. You trying to avoid him?
I can't do that.
Is he still messing with you?
That'll never stop.
Varney, let me tell you something.
The only way it'll stop is if you stop it.
I don't know how to do that,
'cause I work for the family.
There are ways, Varney.
Okay, well, I'm a student.
I'll remember that.
Is Charles here?
I don't know.
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-No, I don't.
-It sounds like you do know,
with the way you said it.
I told him he needed
to be here this morning.
Oh. So you nudged him, or you texted him?
-Mallory…
-I'm just say--
Well, just calm down. Geez, just relax.
Well, shall we go out in the lobby
to greet your new mother-in-law?
Hm. I'm gonna show you how
to deal with trash in the most polite way.
Mallory… [hesitates]
What?
You sure you wanna do this?
This is my shit.
If this bitch wants to come in here
and play with the big dogs,
then she needs to bring her best.
Now go while I sit here and make her wait.
[chuckling] Okay.
[chuckling]
[horses neighing]
[James sighs]
-Um, James.
-Yes, ma'am.
Have you seen Angel and Sylvie?
Well, Angel is out shopping.
And where is Sylvie?
Sylvie's in the stables.
By herself?
No, no. Mr. Glen…
Who the hell is Glen?
He's a stable boy. She's in good hands.
Oh. [sighs]
[door opens, closes]
[scoffs] Damn, these people are crazy.
[employees chattering excitedly]
Where is she?
She's on her way in.
I thought you were supposed
to pick her up.
I got pulled away.
[Norman] Yeah, figures.
Where's Mallory?
Who gives a shit?
[Olivia sighs]
The tension in this room
is as thick as it comes.
Yeah.
I totally feel it.
Keep your head on a swivel. Be careful.
I got you.
You ready for this?
Look, I know you don't know me that well…
[sweeping orchestral music playing]
Thank you.
[chuckling]
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
Thank you. I appreciate it. Thank you.
Welcome.
Don't you look beautiful?
Thank you.
We're all so glad
that you could join us.
Join you?
Yes.
I came to lead you.
Of course.
The bitch has got teeth.
[scoffs] Yeah.
Everyone, this is Kimmie.
She is our new COO.
Thank you. Uh, my name is Kimmie,
but you all will refer to me
as Mrs. Bellarie.
All the shareholders are present,
and the boardroom is all set up.
[Mallory] Great.
Right this way.
No. I wanna see my office first.
[inhales deeply]
Right this way.
No, no.
I want him to show me.
Okay.
Roy?
Gladly. [scoffs]
Right this way.
[Roy sighs]
Everyone back to work, please.
[employees chattering]
Jules, what the fuck is this?
Wow.
You met Kimmie.
Hm.
She's a little stronger than I thought.
Good thing you know how to handle strong.
[scoffs] Breaking bitches is my pleasure.
[dramatic sting]
[horses neighing]
[Sylvie moaning]
[moaning continues]
What the fuck? Get off of her!
[grunting]
-Wait, wait.
-[Sylvie] No.
[breathing heavily]
[Sylvie] What? No!
Oh my God! Stop!
-No!
-Wait!
[Sylvie screaming] Oh my God!
[Glen screaming]
[shuddering] Oh my God. Oh my God.
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ Yeah, huh ♪
♪ Whoa, one ♪
♪ Two-steppin' in my Lou-Vs ♪
♪ Let my jewelry make you blind ♪
♪ My nigga keep a toolie ♪
♪ Step up to me
You might die ♪
♪ Pop up in the mix ♪
♪ Internet hos are sliding ♪
♪ My bitches love to rage ♪
♪ Like we back in '99 ♪
♪ Who da fuck in this bitch ♪
♪ Talkin' all this, talkin' all that ♪
♪ If you fuckin' up the vibe ♪
♪ Flick of the wrist, backhand smack ♪
♪ Who want smoke, who want smoke ♪
♪ I'm the coach, I'm the warden ♪
♪ How am I so fire? ♪
♪ But I'm putting down that water, water ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Keep it live ♪
♪ Keep it, yuh, yuh, yuh ♪
♪ Get on your knees, I'm blessed ♪
♪ Why don't I take this dress off ♪
♪ We just might need confession ♪
♪ Why don't I wrap this whip up tight ♪
♪ Matte pink Tii Tii Tesla ♪
♪ Ain't no man or bitch I need
To make Tii Tii successful ♪
♪ Fuck a highway, it's my way ♪
♪ Grew up by the mob way ♪
♪ Trenches bitch to godly ♪
♪ From the BX onto Broadway ♪
♪ Ay, extra cheese
XOXO, besos please ♪
♪ All my hos got double-Ds ♪
♪ All my niggas got SMGs
Bang, bang ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live
Like it's 30 Rock ♪
♪ Bow bow to the heir ♪
♪ I'm the pretty god ♪
♪ Every night keep it live ♪
♪ Keep it live, keep it ♪
[chuckles]
♪ Bow bow to the pretty god ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[music fades]