[English subtitles are available]
[Sweet On]
♫Oh love should be♫
♫Like songbirds soaring to the sun♫
♫My dear♫
♫When you walk with me♫
♫I feel the troubles in me fade away♫
♫And if I want you, you want me♫
♫Who cares what others may think?♫
♫I hear church bells ring♫
♫I have you, you have me♫
♫Roses will bloom in our dreams♫
♫I'd kiss you now♫
[Love the Way You Are]
[Episode 16]
Don't drink cold drinks. It's bad for your stomach.
Here.
Aunt Lan.
Have some warm milk.
Thank you, Aunt Lan.
Yibo,
is something bothering you?
No.
Your dad can't tell.
Aunt Lan can tell.
Are you stressed about taking the postgraduate entrance exam?
Actually,
don't put too much pressure on yourself.
It's best if you can pass.
But it doesn't matter if you fail.
Young people nowadays
can always live on themselves.
Most importantly,
you have to
follow your heart.
What do you want?
What do you need?
Got it?
Aunt Lan.
That day,
I was impulsive.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's normal for you kids
to quarrel.
I know you
are sensible children.
You'll reconcile in a few days.
Aunt Lan,
don't be angry.
I won't.
All right, don't think too much.
Rest early.
Don't stay up late.
Okay.
Don't eat cold food.
Thank you, Aunt Lan.
Yibo.
Urgent need for the Double Seventh Festival Special.
How about an emergency training tomorrow morning?
You'd better be serious.
Or I'll take revenge
with you who revealed my secret.
[Product selection for live stream]
Product selection for live stream.
Ke, time for breakfast.
Coming, Aunt Lan.
Hurry.
Come here.
Aunt Lan
bought you
your favorite meat buns.
Come, sit down and eat.
Did you sleep late last night?
Look at the dark circles.
They can't even be covered.
My company is in a rush.
I'll be fine after this period.
Hurry up and eat.
Where's dad?
Your dad went out
to exercise early in the morning.
He couldn't sleep well these days.
He must be worried about you.
Where is Yibo?
He's still asleep?
He went out
with many books early.
I guess he went to
study in the library.
Aunt Lan, I should go now.
Well,
tell dad
I have a live stream tonight.
I won't come back for dinner.
Will it be late?
Do you need your dad to pick you up?
No, no.
I can handle it myself.
I'm leaving.
Ke.
Here, bring some meat buns.
I think
you should find time
to tell your dad
about you breaking up with Zelin.
After all, it's a big deal.
We can't hide it from him.
I know, Aunt Lan.
Take your time. I'm leaving.
Bye.
That's all for your condition while you're on live.
Let's talk about
the product introduction.
If you just introduce
the parameter of a product,
it is meaningless.
You need to create a kind of...
How should I put it?
The atmosphere
or a sense of empathy.
Question.
Yes, please.
What is the sense of empathy?
Good question.
Xia Xiaomian, give me your hand.
Imagine me
the man you love the most.
Let's take
this perfume in vacation and coastal style for example.
Imagine we are
on the beach.
The afterglow of sunset.
He's your Mr. Right.
Right?
If... Of course,
if a boy buys it...
Guangxi
Imagine
I'm your beloved goddess.
You are telling me your love to me tonight.
If you have enough money,
you will choose a seaside restaurant
and a candlelight dinner.
Right?
Imagine the waves rhythmically
lap on the reef,
with the sound of
the candle in the room.
And the top note of this perfume is
elegant and gentle.
This night must be...
dangerous
and a little subtle.
Do you understand?
Are you sure you want to hold my hand?
Don't you know
who my goddess is?
Xia Xiaomian, got it?
Understand?
Of course.
Let's summarize it.
Yibo,
you look so handsome
while selling things.
So charming.
Xia Xiaomian, actually,
it's not hard for you
to think from another perspective.
You're indeed Dan from Xiafei Road.
After listening to you,
I want to place an order.
Shut up, Xu Guangxi.
This is a female fragrance.
Don't push your luck.
Okay.
But let me make it clear.
You must keep
to my sister about tonight.
But according to her tension,
she'll be watching the first live stream.
Do your best.
If you have any questions,
send a message in the group chat.
I'll find another way
to distract her.
No.
Why not?
The bet is not valid yet.
I'm your sister's boyfriend.
What bet?
Can I bet?
-Go away.
Xu Guangxi.
Just this time.
If you seduce my sister
while I'm not around,
well, I...
There must be a sequence.
Can we talk about it after the live stream?
Go on with your teaching.
So, Xia Xiaomian,
do you understand?
The things of empathy I just told you.
I've checked them all.
You did a good job.
Don't worry, Yike.
Tonight, according to this order,
there will be no problem.
Okay.
After today,
the mid-term data will come out.
Tonight is very important.
So we must work hard.
OK.
OK. Come on.
Yike.
We'll get ready.
Come on.
Let's get ready.
OK.
Where is Xia Xiaomian?
Where is she?
I'm late.
Sorry.
I'm here.
Where have you been?
Have you finished memorizing the script?
Yes.
Yike.
Just leave it to us.
Tomorrow, I'll show you
what a sales miracle is.
Rest assured.
What are you talking about?
Today is so important.
How can I not be here?
You're not leaving?
That's not right.
Yike, think about it.
You are the leader.
It's such an important occasion.
If you're here,
the employees will be nervous, right?
Just go back to nurture your health,
apply a mask,
and wait for our good news.
Right?
You're so afraid that Yike will be here.
Are you trying to slack off?
I...
I know.
Are you afraid if you fail
you will be hammered by Yike?
Am I right?
I'll hammer you.
You...
Enough.
Stop messing around.
The live stream
is in an hour.
Yike,
let's check
the list of our live stream today.
Let's go.
Go.
Hurry up and get ready.
Come to us when you are ready.
Your sister is still here.
Don't come up.
But I'm going to start.
What should I do?
If my sister finds out,
Dan from Xiafei Road will be beaten
to be Hornet's Nest from Xiafei Road.
In the middle,
we can't let the popularity fall.
Otherwise,
-the data will be bad
-Yike.
It's coffee time.
Just to show my concern.
For us?
Thank you, Guangxi.
Everyone,
Guangxi brought us coffee.
Thank you.
Thank you, Guangxi.
Good luck on the live stream.
-Good luck.
Why do you want to show your concern?
That's true.
But I still need you to
do me a favor.
It's urgent.
It's about to start.
What's wrong?
Let's talk on the way.
Just ten minutes.
You...
What are you doing?
Xia Xiaomian.
What are you doing? Have some coffee.
Coming.
Are you done? What are you looking at?
Thank you.
Why do I feel Guangxi is
more and more handsome?
What do you want me to do?
I have a very important mission.
What is it?
I'm stuck in a plot.
I need your advice.
Okay.
I'll give you ten minutes at most.
About my live stream today,
you know,
it's really important.
Yike.
What shampoo did you use today?
Why does it smell so good?
What are you doing, Xu Guangxi?
Yibo, you're finally here.
Xiaomian, it's about to start.
Coming.
This is...
Special assistant.
My sales elixir.
Let's go to the live room.
Give me the live stream schedule.
These are all prepared today.
These are the special gifts for Double Seventh Festival.
This is the product introduction.
Xu Guangxi.
You're a little weird today.
Are you hiding something from me?
I
learned a new
technique of latte art.
I was going to surprise you.
So being stuck in the plot
is just a cover.
Okay, I promise you.
I'll come to you
after the live stream.
See you later.
100 pieces for the main product.
Your sister is back again.
Wait.
Xiaomian, your special guest
leaves suddenly?
He has something to do.
Brother, what should we do?
It's about to start.
Xia xiaomian, don't panic.
I'll command you live stream in distance.
Xiaomian.
Are you ready?
I'll be your assistant today.
I am ready.
Brother, I'm a little nervous.
Brother?
Let me try the sound.
Brother.
Xia Xiaomian,
ask the assistant to send
the account and password of
the link monitoring backstage data.
And then send it to me.
Shen Xin.
Send me
password of
the backstage data monitoring account.
Just send it to me.
Okay, I got it.
I've sent you
all the product introduction.
Just do as I said.
Say them out naturally,
casually and happily.
OK?
-How is it?
-It's about to start.
Ready for live streaming.
Three, two, one.
Start.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to the live room.
I'm your
lovely live streamer, Little Xiaomian.
Today
is our...
When doing product introduction,
the first thing is the characteristics of the product.
The standard fragrance to attract men.
Next is
our first perfume.
The standard fragrance to attract men.
Next, let's smell
its fragrance.
Describe the smell.
Just tell
a romantic love story
on a street with sycamore trees in summer
with a fresh feeling.
Let's describe this perfume
with sycamore trees in summer.
Just like riding bike romantically
on the boulevard with sycamore trees
in summer.
Say out your love with it.
You will succeed.
Buy it on Double Seventh Festival.
The price is only 288.
Input Little Xiaomian,
you can also get
a small gift for Double Seventh Festival.
Let's order now.
Please take the link number four.
It' s only 288 yuan.
It's a special gift for Double Seventh Festival.
Don't miss it.
Everyone, just buy it.
The link is in three seconds.
Three, two, one.
Next, let's come to
our second product.
Our special orange fragrance.
Xiaomian's pace is good today.
She's different today.
She's totally different from usual.
The data is good too.
Why are they all male fans?
Xia Xiaomian,
let's change
the order of live streaming.
Draw the prize first.
And then put forward the link for Double Seventh Festival.
Let's increase the popularity.
OK.
Next, please
take the link of No. 17 first.
Let's move on to
the happy lucky draw.
Let's invite our assistant.
Why didn't she follow the order?
She seems to have her own procedure.
She don't need my remind at all.
A mysterious assistant just came.
But he left
soon.
Did Xiaomian ask
from a master?
Well,
Shen Xin, help me.
Coming.
Well,
adjust this height for me.
Xiaomian,
extend the drawing part
for three minutes.
When the popularity
increase a little in the live room,
let's continue, okay?
Because the backstage shows
there are still more male fans
than female fans.
Because this perfume
is mainly designed for women.
If you want
female fans to buy it,
you should...
Yibo.
Put on a few female products.
For example...
A mysterious assistant just came.
But he left
soon.
Product No. 22
and
Product No.6.
How about this?
Tell them
a romantic love story
about women.
You are good at making up stories.
You are brave enough to make it up.
Xiaomian.
Say something!
Hello, Xia Xiaomian.
Listen to me.
Can you hear me?
Where is Yike?
Well...
Hello?
Next,
we...
Well...
Well,
this product...
Xia Xiaomian, what are you doing?
Yike.
Why are you here?
Did you see Yin Yibo today?
Why did you mention him suddenly?
I heard
Yibo's voice
from Xia Xiaomian's headphone.
No.
How is that possible?
Xiaomian, say something!
Xiaomian.
The live stream
has half an hour to go.
We still have a long way to go.
Work harder.
OK? Xiaomian, come on!
OK.
Next,
we...
Well...
Well,
this perfume is our...
What are you doing?
Well...
Calm down. Don't be nervous.
We...
Yibo.
Don't panic.
Get ready for the next product introduction.
I'll use my account
to call you
and help you get more popularity.
Hurry up.
Hello, everyone.
This is Dan from Xiafei Road.
Today,
we will have an extra show temporarily
because of
our close friends,
the live streamer of SC Fragrance.
Xia Xiaomian.
Let's
connect with her, OK?
Hello, Xiaomian.
Long time no see.
Hello.
Here's the thing.
Xiaomian is a friend
I've known for years.
She's always passionate about
her own research of
fragrance and smell.
In some working occasions
or social occasions,
if I have to pick a perfume,
I'll ask her in advance.
Xiaomian, I want to know
what will you choose for
a normal journey?
What kind of perfume
will you choose?
Dan from Xiafei Road?
Search him online
and you'll know how good your brother is.
This is why
you sent me away today.
It's not right
to be a live streamer without telling you,
but he must have
his reason.
I suggest
to see his performance first.
He put a lot of effort into it.
OK.
Xiaomian just gave
an introduction to this product.
It reminds me of a story.
When you were young, have you ever
had a kind of ice cream?
-It only costs 50 cents per stick.
-Ice cream?
Yes, you've had it before, right?
There are many flavors,
like Sprite and orange flavor.
There are various flavors.
When you
put it in your mouth,
at that moment,
it was really cold.
At this time,
if the girl you like
or the boy you like.
First love?
You may say that.
He or she suddenly appeared next to the basketball court.
At that moment...
All the handsome and beauties in the live room,
please place orders now.
Link No. 1.
There are 98 groups left.
90 groups.
80.
The last 39 groups.
Guys, place your order.
Yike.
The trading volume
reached
8.53 million yuan.
Yike.
Haven't you heard of him?
He's Dan from Xiafei Road.
He's a famous trendy influencer
and has millions of fans.
I bought a lot of things
in his live stream.
He's using
his popularity
to help Xiaomian's live stream.
We don't have to worry about
today's KPI.
He is my brother.
Ten million, Yike.
Ten million.
Not only did we reach
the KPI,
we also
exceed it.
Our Live Stream Department is safe.
I'll leave you alone.
See you next time.
Okay, thank you.
Bye.
Yibo.
It's really good to have you.
Thank you for helping the live stream.
Wait.
Sister.
Dan from Xiafei Road, right?
How come I don't know it?
You are really good.
Yike.
Yibo
works very hard.
He's really good at live streaming.
He taught me all my work.
He helped us
such a big favor.
Please don't blame him.
Sister, I'm doing live stream.
Are you angry?
Do you care if I'm angry or not?
Of course I do.
Then why did you come to help me
without telling me earlier?
We got
such a good result today.
I should thank you.
Thank me?
Well.
Sister, will you
allow me to do live stream?
This is a different matter.
About your live stream,
talk to dad when you are home.
Tell dad, I...
He's very capable.
He even made a bet with me
because of the live stream today.
It makes me
in a dilemma.
A bet?
What bet?
Yeah.
Why didn't I know?
When did it happen?
Yike.
We've reached our target.
Congratulations.
The live stream today
is a success.
Hurry up and pack up.
Let's go home earlier.
I'll send red packets in the group chat later.
Red packets!
Thank you, everyone.
Sister, just tell me.
Do you support me to do live stream?
I need to think about it.
After all, you hid it from me.
I'm a little sad.
Didn't you hide
your own things?
We are talking about you now.
Don't get me involved.
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
Sister,
I think the live stream...
I think...
What do you want?
When you helped Xiaomian,
you were a fluent talker.
Why are you
so hesitant now?
I really want to take live stream
as a career.
I won't give up
casually.
So I hope you can...
You can support me.
I didn't expect
besides asking for living expenses
you would also
say words like "support me".
Don't interrupt me.
Just tell me.
Will you help me or not?
Anyway,
I helped you so much.
You can't cheat your brother.
Don't worry.
I know you really like it.
I am on your side.
Really?
You agreed so easily?
Even if I say no,
you won't give up.
But...
But?
But you have to keep the secret for me
about Guangxi and me.
Are you really going to
have a relationship with him?
Let me ask you.
Did Guangxi
ask you for help?
Yes.
He kept begging me,
so I came to help.
Look.
He's like this.
He never says anything,
but he does a lot for me.
Sister, I think
you've changed.
What? I look prettier?
I think
a little rebellious.
Rebellious?
I think
I've become more good at cherishing myself.
In the past,
I always thought I am
the daughter of Yin Chenggong,
Yin Yibo's sister,
Yike from the bomb disposal team,
and Li Zelin's girlfriend.
Yin Yike.
If you walk out of this room,
it's impossible for us.
Whatever I do,
I always consider your feelings first.
Sometimes, I even think
your feelings are what matter.
I'm not important.
Over time,
I forgot
what my happiness is.
But ever since I met Guangxi,
I realized that
I am worth to be cherished.
The reason for this relationship is that
Guangxi makes me feel I am good.
I want to cherish myself better.
This is what love
should be.
But
if dad finds out,
he'll go to hospital because of anger.
Do you acknowledge me?
I...
Good boy.
After all the rounds,
you still want me to acknowledge you.
Are you really going to date
with Xu Guangxi?
In the past,
I thought I live my life
following others'choices.
But this time,
I want to be myself.
I want to make my own choice
and live my own life.
Xu Guangxi
will become my brother-in-law.
How can I defend him
when playing basketball?
How should I call him?
He'll be my elder.
Shouldn't he give me red packets
on New Year?
Then I...
What are you thinking
in your mind?
That's it.
I believe in your choice.
You believe in mine.
Deal?
It's a deal.
But let me make it clear.
I still need to
inspect Xu Guangxi.
And it will be a long time.
Fine.
You are my family.
Take your time.
So...
Sister, you
support me to do live stream?
There's something
I have to tell you.
I think
you did a great job
in the live stream industry.
I am a greenhand.
I still need to learn from you in this industry.
Of course, Dan from Xiafei Road
is not for nothing.
Yin Yibo said
he has to carefully inspect
Xu Guangxi.
And there will be no due date.
Thank you, Yin Yike.
Double Seventh Festival is coming.
Get ready to receive the surprise.
This is the mid-term data of this month.
These special events
were a success.
Although they met
Frank's expectation,
the transformation rate
still needs to be improved.
We didn't get the client
of the huge live stream platform.
It's all my fault.
I didn't expect
Kong Xianzhe would play dirty tricks
right in front of people.
He came for me.
It was my mistake to let you go.
Luckily, you're fine.
Ms. Zheng, don't say that.
There are too many things
that are not friendly to women in the workplace.
No one could expect that.
Even you work with me,
you've still suffered a lot.
When you saved me
and asked me to join the Live Stream Department,
I decided
to make some achievements
in the Live Stream Department.
These are just small difficulties
that can be overcome.
Actually, I've been thinking
we can't just do promotion.
We need to have our
most competitive products.
Yes.
When the new product is launched,
Mr. Kong will definitely
compete with us.
Actually, I've finished
the promotion scheme.
But to be different
from them,
so that we can launch first online,
we need a gimmick.
A gimmick?
Wait,
there's a mobile game company
called Flower World.
They seem to be famous
in the game circle.
But they have too many categories
and the competition is too fierce.
So,
they want to find a new promotion method
and want to cooperate with us.
I know the Flower World.
It's amazing.
Are they working with us?
If we can work out a collaboration with them
and launch it online,
it will be great.
Cool.
Well,
I want you to follow up.
Look, many of our current competitors
are doing promotions.
We must surpass them
on the data.
I'll discuss the plan
with the team.
Thank you, Ms. Zheng.
Mr. Ma.
This is our cooperation plan.
Please take a look.
Although our live stream
started not long ago,
the data growth
has been very stable
and very optimistic.
I believe
the fragrance collaboration series
will definitely succeed
in the market.
This is Wu Yurou.
Our new live streamer.
She has been on the trending news list
several times.
She's very popular.
Mr. Ma.
As we know,
the newly launched mobile game
is very popular.
We can share our product design
on this basis.
On one hand, turn our perfume
into a flat image and
insert it into the game
to increase gaming income.
On the other hand,
in our live room,
we could promote actual derivative products.
Working both online and offline
will be a win-win situation for both of us.
I didn't expect
your live streamer
knows so much about
our products.
It's not an easy thing.
After all, we sincerely want to cooperate with you.
We should do our homework well.
I think your ideas are great.
This is better than directly selling products
in the live stream.
Thank you, Mr. Ma.
Well,
can we sign the contract today?
Today?
Don't get me wrong.
Our Flower World
takes efficiency as the first prioriy.
Because summer vacation is coming,
it happens to be the peak season
of our mobile game.
I don't know
how long does it takes on your side.
But I'm sure
it takes time from design to sample
for new packaging.
I mentioned it to Ms. Zheng last time.
That's why I'm here today.
Mr. Xu
particularly asked me
to bring the official seal.
Miss Yin.
Mr. Ma.
Do we have to
sign it in a rush today?
Is there a problem?
Actually, several companies
are inviting us to work on a collaboration.
Ask Shen Xin
to prepare the contract.
I'll ask Ms. Zheng
to approve it,
and ask the Legal Department to hurry up, okay?
Please wait here.
I'll be right back.
Be careful. Gosh.
Be careful, kid.
Don't broke this.
This is expensive.
Stop it.
What's going on?
This kid from nowhere
insists on covering
all the perfume facilities.
He covered them them once I took the covers away,
and kept calling for mom.
I don't know what to do.
Young man, what are you doing?
Mom.
Don't call me that.
Who are you?
I'm Yu.
If you're not my mom,
why did you call me man?
Let me tell you.
I'm 28 years old.
I don't want to be a mother.
Where are your parents?
Didn't anyone tell you
not to touch other people's things?
I used this at home. It stinks.
So I helped you
cover them all.
Don't talk about this.
Let me ask you.
Which floor is your family on?
I don't remember
which floor he is on.
Well, I have no choice.
I see.
No matter how old girls are,
they want to be called sister.
As a little kid,
you know a lot.
Do you remember which company
your family is in?
I'll send you to him.
My dad is a big boss.
He's in this building.
But I don't remember
which floor he is on.
I'll wait at the door.
Okay.
Just wait here.
Be good.
Don't touch anything.
Mr. Xie was very satisfied
after watching our demo.
The second installment is ready.
With the money,
our company will be successful.
After that,
I'm going to
make it big and popular and make it a listed company.
Wait.
Why do I feel the tone
is the same
when you are
making pie in the sky?
It's not pie in the sky to be listed.
It's a kind of...
Dad.
Since you're so curious about him.
-You have to save me.
-Let me introduce for you.
Dad.
What a cute kid.
He's so pretty.
Is he your son?
You're still young.
But you already have a kid at such an age.
You're amazing.
Look at this. So cute.
He looks exactly
the same
as you.
He's really pretty.
Xu Guangxi.
This is...
This is your son?
Yiran.
This is...
This...
Here's the thing.
Well,
your son is here to see you.
I'll give you a half day off.
Take your son to have fun,
OK?
Have fun with your dad.
Come on. Come on.
Thank you, boss.
You're welcome.
Well,
I'll take my son to have ice cream.
Hurry up.
Young people have babies so early nowadays.
I have a meeting.
I went the wrong way.
In a few days,
the summer events
in our game will start.
You'd better send your eGift Cards
to us earlier
so that the technical department
can launch them in the game as soon as possible.
Okay, I'll arrange it right away.
Mr. Ma.
This is our fragrance set.
Please keep it as a souvenir.
Wish us a pleasant cooperation.
Thank you.
Happy cooperation.
Happy cooperation, Mr. Ma.
I look forward to your product.
That's all for today.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
See you next time.
Okay, see you.
Take care.
This is the first time I've achieved a cooperation
in such a short time.
I can see your efforts.
In such a short time,
you have learned a lot.
This is good. I'll remember it.
I was right about you.
Hello, Xiaomian.
Yike.
I need to talk to you. Come to the rooftop.
What is it?
Stop asking. Come up now.
Okay.
Tell me.
What's wrong?
What makes you must let me
come up and talk?
Hold on.
I have to think about how to say it.
Later,
I have with Ms. Zheng.
If you don't tell me,
I'll go down first.
Guangxi has a child.
What?
It's true.
I saw it with my own eyes.
He has a child.
What child?
Just now,
in the lobby,
I saw the baby.
He called Guangxi dad.
Thank you, dad.
Actually, Dad Chen...
He
has his reasons.
I know. I'm five years old.
I'm not a kid anymore.
It's not what you think.
Your dad takes care of you alone.
It's hard and lonely.
So he...
So he's asking
that fierce aunt
to be my mom.
No, she's not fierce.
She just looks
a bit rude.
I know.
That anut is good.
You know that aunt
quite well.
I'm Chen's son.
We like
the same kind of aunt.
Didn't you just call her sister
in the lobby just now?
You really don't know
girls' secret.
Chen is really
worrying.
So every time Dad Chen ran away
to take you home?
And do laundry, cook,
teach me how to do homework, and
find my socks and underwear.
I don't want to know
about the details.
Eat more.
Uncle,
if Chen
goes on a date with aunt,
you'll be my godfather and take care me.
I don't deserve it.
But I'm capable
to keep you full.
Then it's a deal.
OK.
Deal.
Just now,
in the lobby,
I saw the baby.
He called Guangxi dad.
He's already this tall.
He's six years old.
Guangxi responded
and bought him ice cream.
Thank you, Yin Yike.
Double Seventh Festival is coming.
Get ready to receive the surprise.
Surprise?
Will it be a scare?
♫Travels to the end♫
♫Of the whole universe♫
♫Together, we will♫
♫Guard the whole one world♫
♫Look at me♫
♫I have a meteor♫
♫The world pauses for you♫
♫Baby, you are the one♫
♫I secretively in my heart♫
♫Wrote I'm willing to♫
♫Don't know why. I suddenly♫
♫Hate to calculate the distance between you♫
♫I fear I cannot see you in the next second♫
♫My heart is protesting♫
♫I just feel it too♫
♫It's like the coffee with full caramel milk foam♫
♫The air has the fragrance of missing you♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
[Love the Way You Are]