[English subtitles are available]
[Sweet On]
♫Oh love should be♫
♫Like songbirds soaring to the sun♫
♫My dear♫
♫When you walk with me♫
♫I feel the troubles in me fade away♫
♫And if I want you, you want me♫
♫Who cares what others may think?♫
♫I hear church bells ring♫
♫I have you, you have me♫
♫Roses will bloom in our dreams♫
♫I'd kiss you now♫
[Love the Way You Are]
[Episode 14]
Aunt Lan,
we're waiting for you.
Coming.
Try it.
Ke ordered this soup
specifically by herself.
I went to the market
and picked
a nice fork leg.
I stewed it with soy beans for the whole afternoon.
There must be plenty of collagen in it.
-Help yourself.
-Thank you, Anut Lan.
Have some more.
When did my sister
need collagen?
Well...
Aunt Lan. Dad.
My company
will go on an outing this week.
I'll go to a camping base
and spend two days and one night there.
I'll be back on Sunday.
What kind of company
would have an outing on weekend,
even overnight?
We agreed to buy clothes
with Aunt Lan this weekend.
Can you take a leave?
Yeah.
Sister, you don't look like someone
who would accept this kind of pick-up artist
on employees.
You're right.
What's wrong with you?
Do it yourself.
Whenever our daughter talks about hanging out,
you're like stepping on landmines.
She's tired from work.
It's a rare opportunity for her to take a break.
Look.
There are dark circles under Yike's eyes.
Have some more.
Yes, dad.
Sister, show me some respect please.
Why do you need respect?
Give it to your sister.
Okay.
I'll give the bigger piece to my sister like Kong Rong.
It's good for your health.
This...
Are you really going to spend the night outside?
There must be men and women
in your company, right?
We are all female colleagues.
Well,
the only male colleague is on leave.
See?
You can also take a leave.
You stubborn old man,
are you done?
Okay, fine.
Remember.
Come back early for dinner on Sunday.
Okay, dad.
Have a drink with me.
Come on.
Dad, my sister is an adult.
Stop nagging.
Come on.
Fill the cup up for my girl.
Girls shouldn't drink too much.
Here.
Have more soup.
There you go.
You too. Have some more.
Thank you, Aunt Lan.
Don't you want some respect?
I have a daughter at home, I have everything in the world.
Cheers.
Here you go.
Take it slow.
Dad, take it slow.
What about having a boy at home, dad?
Hurry up
and pass your postgraduate entrance exam.
What are you thinking?
Cheers.
Remember.
Come back early on Sunday.
Sister,
I put the milk on the table.
Okay.
Is this the lace?
When did my sister change her style?
No.
Isn't she going on an outing?
Hello, Xia Xiaomian.
I want to ask you something.
Are you going on an outing this weekend?
Outing?
What outing?
I'm too busy
to have time
to memorize the product instructions.
I don't have time for an outing.
Then whom is my sister going to meet?
An important client?
A client?
I don't think so.
She specifically said
she won't work overtime this weekend.
It's weird.
What happened?
No.
Nothing.
Enjoy your live stream.
I'm gonna hang up.
I'm too full for dinner.
Let's play basketball together.
Listen.
I have to go home early today.
I have something to do.
Wait.
You're a little weird.
Are you going to confess to me?
Are you insane, Xu Guangxi?
If you don't confess, I'm leaving.
Have a seat.
I have something to tell you.
Do you think
my sister is a little strange recently?
No way.
Did he find out?
Xu Guangxi.
Are you listening to me?
No, I don't think so.
We meet everyday at work.
Sometimes we even
go back home together for dinner.
Isn't everything good?
You're so insensitive.
What I mean is
it seems my sister is having an affair.
No, that's impossible.
How could someone
like Yin Yike cheat?
Why are you panicking?
My sister is not in a relationship with you.
Why are you nervous?
I...
Am I panicking?
I was just wondering
if you have too much time.
Where did you get
these weird thoughts?
No.
Listen.
My sister has been acting strange lately.
She stays in the dressing room
for one hour every night.
She even uses two masks.
She goes out every morning
with her eyebrows in a nice shape.
She shapes them so carefully
that you can clearly see them separately.
Do you think she's cheating?
Someone like Yin Yike
wouldn't cheat.
How can you be so sure?
I saw your sister
quarreling with Li Zelin
outside the building of her company.
They quarreled?
No wonder.
I asked her about her relationship with my brother-in-law.
She didn't answer me
directly either.
They're not married.
Why are you calling him your brother-in-law?
Xu Guangxi,
it's not the point.
Well,
what's the point?
What's wrong
with a girl
who suddenly wants to dress up?
I'm telling you. I have evidence.
Evidence?
My sister told me
she's going on an outing with her colleagues this weekend.
I asked Xia Xiaomian.
Xia Xiaomian said
there's no such thing at all.
And you know what the point is?
Before I went out tonight,
I found my sister
packing up her sexy pajamas.
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Why are you blushing?
I'm fine. It's too hot.
I'm sweating.
Seriously.
I'm telling you
something important.
Tell me.
What should I do?
Yibo,
if your sister
makes an unexpected decision,
will you object?
Of course not.
I will always
be on my sister's side
and support her unconditionally.
What if she breaks up?
If she breaks up,
it must be
Li Zelin's fault.
That's it.
But
if they really break up,
I have to keep an eye out
for her admirers.
I'm afraid they'll lie to my sister.
What are you going to do?
I've decided.
I'll sacrifice my weekend for a break
to go camping with my sister together.
I need to see
what kind of person he is.
No.
You can't go.
Why?
Think about it.
Your sister is trying so hard
to hide it from everyone around her
including you.
She must have some reasons
to hide it from her family.
That makes sense.
She must have her reasons
to hide it from her family.
If my dad knows
she broke up with Li Zelin,
our family will be in chaos.
Right?
At this point of time,
as her brother,
instead of covering for her at home,
isn't it inappropriate for you
to be a third-wheel?
You're right.
I shouldn't do that.
Anyway,
if that man
sees me,
he must feel a bit inferior, right?
Yes, he must be very inferior.
So I think
why don't you help your sister
cover it up?
You're right.
All these years,
I've been worried about my sister.
I'd better
protect her secretly
and protect
these weak sparks.
Yibo,
I really think
you're a great brother.
Really, Guangxi?
I also think you're very considerate.
So are you going to
cover it up with me?
Well,
it's only suitable for one person
to cover it up.
It'll be too obvious for two people to do this.
I won't get involved.
You're right.
I should go back now
to protect my sister.
The "Protect My Sister" plan
starts right now.
I can do it!
You can do it!
What can this piece cover?
Forget it.
Just wear this.
How's everything going?
I'm done. See you tomorrow.
Baba.
Dad Chen.
We're here.
We're coming!
Coming.
Come over.
Put it here.
This coach.
Take a look.
I spent a lot
on this rented luxury coach for you.
A two-day trip.
Are you happy about it?
Yes.
Are you excited?
This coach is so cool.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
Didn't you say you would take girls?
Where are they?
Are they here?
This...
Dad Chen.
We can't take girls
with us easily.
Right?
Yeah.
Look over there.
Those singles also on their own.
Morning.
Baba.
Just the two of you?
You should have told me earlier.
I spent so much money
on renting such a big coach
because you had told me
you would take girls with you.
Otherwise,I wouldn't have rented such a big coach
if it's just for you guys.
I'll deduct the cost from your salary.
Don't.
It's not a waste, Baba.
This coach is useful.
What if we can
bring back some girls?
I asked the fortune teller
before I went out this morning.
I'm lucky in romance.
You're too confident.
Well, Baba.
Actually,
I'm taking someone with me.
I knew you're the best.
Who is it?
Guangxi. Who is it?
Sorry, I'm late.
His sister!
Xu Guangxi, you broke the rules.
We agreed to bring a girl.
Why did you bring your sister here?
I don't have
many female friends.
So...
Really?
Guangxi said
every one of you
would take your girlfriend with you,
so I came here
to help him.
Where are your girlfriends?
Hello, mom.
I take the key with me.
Don't worry.
I've prepared everything.
Fortunately,
I've also invited another girl friend of mine.
Otherwise,
there would be too many men.
Who is it?
Who is it, Yike?
Is the wine bad,
or is the clubbing bad?
Why would I agree to go camping with you
in the early morning?
I'm really...
Perfume Queen.
What do you mean?
You don't welcome me?
Welcome to join us!
All right.
It's okay.
As the saying goes,
well,
since you're here...
Let's go.
I bought the one-day ticket.
The morning is almost over.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Get on the coach.
Don't waste money.
Take your belongings.
It's been a long time since I went hunting.
Guys,
let's indulge ourselves.
Sunshine!
Forest!
Beer!
Girls!
We're coming!
Get off and get your luggage.
I haven't worked out for half a year.
I'm so tired.
I shouldn't have given up
the part-time job.
I'll earn a few hundred less.
What a tragedy.
I'm really a bad cheese, aren't I?
I see you three
everyday in the office.
Now that we're here, it's still you three.
There's not even a girl.
Boring.
No.
When something is zero,
it has endless possibilities.
I think we are much better
than Xu Guangxi and Dad Chen.
One takes his sister,
the other takes a Manta
that can explode anytime.
At least they're girls.
It's better to go alone than take one's sister.
Let's go.
Guangxi.
Look, the view is beautiful here.
Yes.
Chen Musen now must think
I'm boring.
He didn't expect
that you're actually very happy now, aren't you?
Of course.
Super happy.
I guess Dad Chen
is also happy now.
Yin Yike,
tell me.
Did you do it on purpose?
Why did you get involved in this kind of trouble?
How am I supposed to assign?
We two can't
group together.
Ms. Qin.
I know you're very unhappy.
Will you please
live with it for now?
For the sake of me
trying so hard to row the boat.
Listen.
Stop bragging.
I'm an independent woman.
I never rely on men.
Ms. Qin, you're so strong.
Their characteristics
are too obvious.
Let me tell you.
Qin Yiran rides a motorcycle.
What do you think?
Let's give it a go.
We could possibly win.
Come on.
Go for it.
I can't row anymore.
Go ahead.
Your boat is spinning.
I'm exhausted.
Have we come too early?
Girls often
take beauty sleep.
What kind of logic is yours?
There are no girls here.
Guys, don't be so sad,
okay?
Always keep
a cheerful
sportsman image.
Maybe girls
will appear in a while.
Mom, I want to go home.
Let's take a photo here.
Here.
This bridge looks good.
Huiben.
Look.
Girls.
Hey girls.
Are you hanging out together?
Do you need labor?
Come on! Come on!
Go!
Hurry up.
We're waiting for you here.
Bye.
See you later.
Be careful.
Let me help you.
No, thank you.
Are you tired?
I'm fine.
It's quite fun.
Do you want some water?
Go away.
Let me open it for you.
Thank you.
Guys,
although my sunglasses are black,
they are transparent.
I can see it clearly, okay?
So what?
Your joke is so cold.
Here, have some warm water.
Do you think I'm cold now?
I think it's quite cold.
Listen, Chen Ye.
I'll take it today
since we're sharing the same boat.
Stay away from me.
Don't cross this line.
Do you hear me?
The 38th Parallel.
How old are you?
Did you reveal your age?
What era are you from?
Shut up and no talk.
No talk?
How many sun icons do you have
for your QQ Yellow Diamond Membership?
What do you mean?
I need some water to warm myself up.
Here comes the food.
Take some more.
Beer. Beer.
Beer.
I'm jealous of young people.
No matter what you do,
you are so energetic.
Don't make others proud
and sell yourself short.
What's there to envy about being young?
They have pimples
and oily skin.
You can't even find my pores
after I finish
my non-invasive facial laser procedure.
But there's always something
that can't be hidden.
What?
Take a guess.
The wrinkles?
You'll lose
that innocence
after you've gained some experience.
That cute boy is coming.
Hey.
Is there anything
we can help you with?
Right.
That's right.
Just tell us.
Do you need help?
That's enough. Stop being emotional here.
Go and save
your loyal puppy.
I'm not going.
What is this for?
Are you tired?
Can you help us carry this?
OK.
Huiben, come and help.
Let me do it.
Take a break. We'll do it.
Let's go have some fun together.
It's good for you to hang out with young people.
Go ahead.
You're still young.
Go.
Let's go.
I won't
go along for the ride.
Here, have some of this.
Let me help you with the barbecue.
We're going over there for the barbecue.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're back.
Do you want coke?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey man,
is this lady
your girlfriend?
How is that possible?
They're siblings.
No wonder.
Only good-looking people
are a family.
Miss.
How old are you?
It's rude to ask about a girl's age
when you meet her for the first time.
It's okay.
It's better for them to ask directly
rather than to be "YYGQ".
Miss.
What did you just say?
What's "YY"?
What does it mean?
Don't you know?
We never heard of it.
I might have learned
too much
about young people.
It just means being sarcastic.
How did you know?
I searched online.
You'll find it in a second.
Miss,
you haven't told us
your age.
I'll turn to 35 in three years.
Almost 35?
You don't look your age at all.
How do you take care of yourself?
Yeah.
Your skin is so good.
What skincare products are you using?
I have pimples.
Your skin is so good.
It's bright and tender.
Here, the barbecue is ready.
Here, try it.
The barbecue is ready.
I told you that you are young.
You are young.
You're welcome.
Here.
Grilled chicken wings.
Try it.
Is it salty? Is it spicy?
Eating more chili can make you younger.
Why?
It's rare to come to the wild.
Why are you
sitting and sleeping here alone?
None of your business.
I just want to be alone
for a while, can't I？
I just think
you're too quiet.
You know?
Look how lively there is.
I'm gonna get you some work.
Here, put them on the skewers.
Me?
Didn't you say you don't rely on men?
If these skewers
are all done
by men,
will you eat or not?
Fine, I'll do it.
I'll do it.
I don't want to listen to your nagging.
You know what?
Sister and brother are a good match.
Do you know about their relationship?
Do you think I'm blind?
Listen,
Yike has her own difficulties.
Don't gossip
or let the whole company know.
I'm can keep secrets.
Don't worry.
From now on,
this is our common secret.
Here.
Give me five.
Can you reach it here?
Thank you.
What do you want to eat?
-Let me get it for you.
- It's okay.
Miss.
I heard that both of you are working for a big company.
You are also the manager.
I really envy you.
I still can't find a job.
I don't even know
whether I can pass the postgraduate entrance exam.
Don't be afraid even if you can't.
Even students who graduated from universities of Project 985 or Project 211
can't find a job.
People who graduated from Tsinghua University or Peking University work overtime as well.
We all get suppressed
at work.
But take my advice.
Study may not
lead you to a good job,
but you can never find a good job
if you don't study.
So you still have to study hard.
That's good enough.
After graduation,
I worked part-time while looking for a job.
Now, I'm no longer
a graduating student.
Look at me.
I've changed four jobs.
I can't wait to resign now.
I'm asked to make tea everyday
in the current company.
Ladies,
I finally made it
to get into this company.
I'm not here to make tea for them.
Besides, I'm not their secretary.
They won't let me attend
important meetings either.
I've experienced
all the things you said before.
Really?
I just thought
no matter what
you ask me to do,
I have to do it better.
Even if it's making tea,
I'll make it different from others'.
They'll acknowledge
my capability someday.
Got it.
My mom said
if I fail the postgraduate entrance exam,
she'll arrange a blind date for me
and ask me to get married.
Do you still want to get married now?
Of course not.
You have to work hard
if you don't want to.
Miss,
however, we may not get to where you are
when we are at your age.
We'll be old by then.
It'll also be hard to get married.
You think
our work is going well.
Actually to me,
I always think
I'm a failure.
How come you feel like a failure?
It's just pressure
from work and life,
but I never thought about
getting married
can reduce the pressure.
I think
the biggest failure in life
is not about
whether you've become a manager or not,
but you're living a life
you don't want.
Well said.
You must
understand this anti motivational quote.
Dad Chen, you have a good taste.
Getting married and having children...
You too.
Is not necessarily bad.
But it's definitely not
a safe shelter.
Right?
It's the same as entering a workplace.
You might fail.
Anyway,
no matter which path you choose,
don't be afraid.
Youth is the capital.
Yeah.
After hearing what you said,
I feel like I've gained the courage.
I'm not afraid anymore.
Right?
This anti motivational quote
is really encouraging.
Mindset.
Mindset is very important, girls.
Come on.
Have some kebabs.
Try it, Baba.
These are the kebabs
cooked with secret recipe.
Great!
Awesome!
Kebabs and alcohol are the best match.
Help yourself.
Fill it up.
Let's
raise our glasses.
Come on.
To youth. To time.
Cheers.
Don't drink too much,
or I'll tell everyone
about your crazy behaviors after drinking.
How dare you!
Drink, young people.
-Come on.
-Cheers.
Anyone wants to give a performance?
Come on.
I'll do it.
Chen Musen.
Awesome!
Dad Chen! Dad Chen!
There you go.
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
♫Look at me♫
♫I have a meteor♫
♫The world pauses for you♫
♫Baby, you are the one♫
♫I secretively in my heart♫
♫Wrote I'm willing to♫
You danced well.
Aren't you afraid that others will see this?
The more nervous you are,
the easier you'll be discovered.
Be natural.
I find that
you really enjoy excitements.
You're wrong.
I only enjoy
excitements with you.
There you go.
Have some water.
Tell me.
Are you stupid?
I've done this to you.
You're still not angry?
Have you forgotten
what my job is？
I'm a supplier.
I can't be a supplier
if I don't have a good temper.
Our biggest competitive advantage
is we can tolerate any obstacles by others.
And I was wrong
for what happened between us,
so it's understandable for you to mess with me.
See? You've already done it.
Right?
After drinking this bottle of water,
let's move on
and make up.
You want to make up with me with just a bottle of water?
It's not that easy.
What else do you want?
It depends on
whether you can
make me happy or not.
Of course I can.
It's easy to make you happy.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the next part
is the "Taking Song Requests" session.
It's a song requested
by me, Chen Ye,
to Ms. Qin Yiran.
I wish her a whole happy night.
-Music.
- What's he doing?
He's probably gonna make his ultimate move.
His ultimate move?
He must be drunk.
He can't even stand straight.
They look like
a perfect couple.
Let them have fun.
Come with me to a place.
Let's go.
Here we are.
Is this the motorhome you rented secretly?
Do you like it,
or is it a bit old-fashioned?
I like it.
Let's get inside and take a look.
You've brought my suitcase here?
Have a seat.
Are you thirsty?
Have some water.
Thank you.
I'm a little hot.
So...
Yes, it's a little hot.
What should we do now?
Shall we watch TV first?
Okay.
We're going to spend the night
sitting here and watching TV?
You could take a shower first.
I mean
you've sweated a lot today.
It must be uncomfortable.
Here's the bathroom.
Let me help you.
I'm done.
The bed is ready.
It's your turn.
I'm gonna get in and take a shower.
Guangxi.
You look like a zombie.
What are you doing?
I'm doing some abs workout.
I'm doing some workouts.
Guangxi.
Xu Guangxi.
Who is it? It's late at night.
You're annoying!
Get back in!
Come here!
You...
Honey.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Psycho.
What are you doing in the middle of the night?
She bullied me.
She didn't bully you.
What kind of woman is she?
How come she even has a husband?
Don't say that.
Why?
Why did she leave with another man
after drinking my alcohol?
Who?
Who did this?
Just one of those girls,
Yuanyuan.
Stop it.
She could still be here.
Let's talk in the room.
I won't die.
Come on.
Drink with me.
You didn't have enough?
Well...
Come on.
Cheers, bro.
Cheers!
Friends go together forever.
We'll be single together.
Don't curse me.
Who wants to be
single with you?
Thank you for your kind words.
After I wake up tomorrow,
I'll find a girlfriend.
Take a sip.
She always left her phone number,
but never let me take her home.
You...
Why do you always
sing such an old song?
Can you sing something
more trendy?
You don't understand.
This is nostalgia for the classics.
Okay.
It's nostalgia for the classics.
The classics, right?
A toast to you.
To the classics.
Cheers!
Qin Yiran.
You're home.
I...
I'm gonna go.
Chen Ye.
Do you like me?
Why are you talking so loudly?
Do you?
Yes.
Listen.
I'm a
shaky boat.
It may run aground anytime.
Are you sure you want to get on board?
It's okay.
I'm a man
who's determined to be the King of Sailing.
I'll give you a chance.
I won't guarantee the time.
Stop.
Stop. Stop.
[Yu]
Damn it.
What happened?
I have to go now.
I'm gonna go.
I have something urgent.
Well,
I'll make it up to you next time.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
I'm getting off now.
I'm sorry.
Chen Ye.
♫Travels through the air♫
♫And arrives at any part of the universe♫
♫Together, we will♫
♫Guard the whole one world♫
Ms. Qin.
Can I sit here?
Suit yourself.
Just don't disturb my sleep.
Did you drink?
You're reeking of alcohol.
No.
I don't even mind
your smell of an old man.
Don't talk to me.
Are you crazy?
Give it to me.
Why does your company have
such a product?
Chen Ye, are you crazy?
Sir, open the window.
♫Look at me♫
♫I have a meteor♫
♫The world pauses for you♫
♫Baby, you are the one♫
♫I secretively in my heart♫
♫Wrote I'm willing to♫
♫Don't know why. I suddenly♫
♫Hate to calculate the distance between you♫
♫I fear I cannot see you in the next second♫
♫My heart is protesting♫
♫I just feel it too♫
♫It's like the coffee with full caramel milk foam♫
♫The air has the fragrance of missing you♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫