[English subtitles are available]
[Sweet On]
♫Oh love should be♫
♫Like songbirds soaring to the sun♫
♫My dear♫
♫When you walk with me♫
♫I feel the troubles in me fade away♫
♫And if I want you, you want me♫
♫Who cares what others may think?♫
♫I hear church bells ring♫
♫I have you, you have me♫
♫Roses will bloom in our dreams♫
♫I'd kiss you now♫
[Love the Way You Are]
[Episode 12]
Here, Mr. Xu.
Cheers.
Here.
Bro, cheers!
Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Cheers. Cheers.
Make yourself at home.
Here.
Mr. Xu.
Yike
had worked in the Marketing Department for many years.
She has been transferred
to a new department, Live Stream Department.
She has to depend on you in the future.
No problem.
Cheers, Mr. Xu.
-Cheers. -Your advice is appreciated.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Mr. Kong.
I think your subordinates
are really awesome.
Miss Yin is very straightforward.
She drank a glass of baijiu without hesitation.
Miss Yin.
You're beautiful.
You have a good face shape,
and your eyes are prettier.
I think she can
be a live streamer.
I can help her
hit
the headlines.
No problem.
Mr. Xu.
Stop joking.
I won't take over
my colleagues' jobs.
But my department signed
some talented live streamers.
If you can help them
hit the headlines,
we will double our KPI.
Is she bargaining with me?
Miss Yin.
The party has just started.
Besides,
Mr. Xu is sophisticated.
If he says you can do it,
maybe you're really suitable for it.
She's definitely suitable for that job.
We can talk about work later,
right?
Mr. Xu, cheers.
Cheers.
-Nice to meet you. -So beautiful.
Miss Yin.
I think you shouldn't refuse immediately.
To be honest,
from your face,
I can see you'll be famous.
I know how to read palms too.
Can I have a try?
Here.
Let me read your palms.
This hand is really soft.
This hand...
I'm sorry.
Don't you know how to be a waiter?
My new suit.
Are you okay?
It was splashed.
Have you ever been trained?
Leave here.
You didn't even wipe the chair for me.
Forget it.
I won't sit here.
Don't be upset.
Here.
I'm sorry for my treat.
Cheers.
Here.
Good.
-I'm sorry for my treat. -Miss Yin.
I haven't finished yet.
Let me tell you.
Here's what I think.
I heard Miss Yin
is in charge of a new department alone.
So,
she must have a new atmosphere.
I suggest...
Don't... Relax.
Don't put it down.
I suggest...
This one.
We brothers
finish our drinks if we love each other.
If Miss Yin
drink this,
I'll accept
all the conditions of her new department.
Here.
What do you think, brothers?
Great.
No problem.
Here.
I'll drink with you.
OK, Mr. Xu.
This pot.
Cheers.
Yike, what are you doing?
Yin Yike.
Yin Yike, stop!
Are you crazy?
Do you know why you can still
stay in the Marketing Department?
You're also known as a person
who never offends anyone.
You nearly hit him.
Mr. Kong.
Didn't you see
what Mr. Xu did?
Where did he put his hand?
Why did he let me
drink the wine in that pot?
You know his intention, right?
Just because of a drink?
Didn't Mr. Xu say that
with your appearance,
you could be a live streamer?
Right?
Because of a drink,
you want to give up the
platform resources?
Does the company achieve KPI
by sacrificing
its female employees?
-Let me tell you. -Mr. Kong.
I don't need you to educate me.
I'll handle it myself.
Who are you looking for?
I'm looking for you.
What? Were you cosplaying?
No. He is my younger brother.
Your younger brother?
Introduce your younger brother to me.
Mr. Xu can't satisfy you?
You even want my brother.
Your brother is quite manly.
He got me out of trouble.
So what was the ending?
I didn't see it.
It was exciting.
Unfortunately, there's no replay for you to watch.
I know you can handle it.
But I'm still
a little worried.
Because you gave me
a little bit of courage.
Now you're the Yin Yike
who knows how to
protect herself.
Why did you come here?
Did the proposal end early?
I...
I also scolded my client.
Between standing and kneeling,
I still choose to stand.
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
I'm crazy because of someone.
So,
I went crazy and lost a big resource
because of you too.
Staying true to yourself
is a happy thing,
isn't it?
In this case,
let's do something big.
Something big?
You brought me here to ride a bike?
It's healthy and environmentally friendly.
It can also keep you entertained.
Aren't you happy?
I'm happy.
I always thought
you couldn't ride a bike.
When you were abroad,
I learned a lot.
Slow down.
There's a downward slope ahead.
With you behind me,
I'll charge forward fearlessly.
OK.
I'll always be behind you.
What's wrong?
Why can you peel shrimp so fast?
You're faster than my speed of eating.
Did you major in
peeling shrimp in college?
How do you know?
When I was abroad,
I was a credit to our country.
I always ranked first in shrimp peeling competitions.
You're like a defeated cock.
Won't you educate me today?
I don't have to listen to reason?
Your project failed?
You offended Party A?
I knew it.
People who like to educate others
will certainly be given a slap in the face.
People have to pay the price if they overestimate themselves.
Qin Yiran.
Let me tell you.
In this world, there are people
who go back
after they hit a wall and bleed.
But there are some people
who wouldn't turn back even if they bled.
I'm that kind of person.
What's wrong with you?
Why were you talking nonsense?
Give me your hand.
This
is my pay for this trip.
What is it?
Little Guangxi and Little Yike.
Look.
What about your pay?
I also have pay?
I'll pay you.
What is it?
The last can of iced cola in the store.
Here you are.
Drinking iced cola
is comfortable on this hot day.
These days,
I feel like I'm dreaming.
Then don't wake up.
The dream is beautiful,
but how
can I not wake up?
If you turn your dream into reality,
you don't need to wake up.
What if it's hard?
Then learn to give up.
Give up?
I'm just kidding.
I regretted it.
What did you regret?
I regretted that I didn't
confess my love to you earlier.
I should be the one
who held your hands first.
How can you be so small?
You're right in my arms.
Maybe it's because
I'm like
those two small shells.
I want to take a sip too.
♫One more time♫
♫Still with me one more time♫
♫The darkest night♫
♫Has sparked in your eyes♫
♫Oh baby♫
♫If I can turn back the time♫
♫When bad dreams and sadness♫
♫Hang in the sky♫
♫Then we'll never♫
♫Say goodbye♫
Mr. Xu sent
a cancellation letter this morning.
Do you have
any explanations?
To be honest,
Frank,
I think
my team
is hard to control.
I really can't control it.
Originally,
I wanted
to help Miss Yin with negotiations.
But she
didn't appreciate it
and made me rile both sides.
It seems
that Miss Yin
only listens to Ms. Zheng.
She doesn't take me as her leader.
Mr. Kong.
This matter has nothing to do
with Ms. Zheng.
Really?
I just think
this partner
might have problems in the future.
What problems can Mr. Xu have?
Mr. Xu
is a prestigious person.
What problems can he have?
Frank,
I think the climate
in our company
is really bad.
Mr. Xu just wanted
to have a drink with you.
Why are you making such a fuss?
You should know
what kind of person Mr. Xu is.
How many obscene deals has he got involved in?
His company is also investigating it.
I really think our company
doesn't have to work
with him.
In business,
it's inevitable to have a grey area.
Business
is not like charity.
Right?
Miss Yin.
I suggest you
figure it out first.
How could you care about others
without figuring it out?
Frank,
I've found a substitute for the plan.
I've contacted
the boss of Waku.
He can help us
with promotion on the Internet.
I don't think we need
to take the risk of public sentiment.
I didn't expect Manager Yin
to have another plan.
No wonder you're so indifferent.
Miss Yin, do you think
their resources
are comparable
to Mr. Xu's resources?
I don't care about processes.
I only care about results.
I understand.
Oh no.
Everyone, listen to me.
Don't panic.
Our promotion on the homepage
has been canceled.
Then we can only rely on ourselves.
I told you.
It was cool to educate Mr. Kong,
but it also costed a lot.
Look.
Everyone in the Marketing Department
are waiting to laugh at us.
Stop complaining.
It's not a complaint.
It's the truth.
I can only expect
luck can suddenly come.
Do you think
it's late to pray for good luck now?
Try it.
It's not late.
The little fairy
you're looking forward to
comes.
I'm here to help you attract more followers.
One million fans.
I will complete the mission.
Applause!
-OK. -Come on.
Hello, everyone.
I'm here to register.
Welcome.
Well.
Welcome to the Live Stream Department.
Welcome.
Let's cut to the chase.
Let's get ready.
Give this to Mr. Chen for me.
-Okay, Yiran. -Thank you.
You're welcome.
Guangxi.
You have time to come to our company?
I'm here
to give something to my sister.
Where is my sister?
She should be on the rooftop
to relax.
Did her boss give her a hard time
because of the client?
You're well-informed.
My company is just two floors above.
Right.
Why don't you
send the warmth yourself?
I have something to deal with.
Please help me
give it to her.
No problem.
I'm leaving.
Can you withstand the storm
in your company?
I'm fine.
The thunder is loud, but it's a light rain.
I can handle it.
Let's go home together after work.
You're the strongest person in SC indeed.
Come on.
But Miss Yin,
since you're so confident,
show me your results.
The live stream data of the first month.
Everyone in the Marketing Department
will be watching you.
You scared me.
You've heard many unpleasant words.
I'm helping you forget them.
You deal with your boss
like this?
Of course.
I won't spoil them.
I find
you've changed recently.
Why am I different?
I still work a 996 schedule.
You weren't so tough before.
Why are you so tough today?
That day,
I didn't know where my courage
came from.
But after that,
I had to pay the price.
In the future, the difficulty of my work
has been increased.
Got it.
Don't worry.
I'm here when bad things happen.
Just go ahead boldly.
Don't have any worries.
By the way,
this...
Little Guangxi brought it.
He said Aunt Lan gave it to you.
He came to work?
Yes.
I met him at the door of the company.
I don't know if he was shy
or had other reasons.
He ran away in a panic.
So I have to give it
to you personally.
Every child will be shy
when they see Miss Qin.
Enough.
The food
your aunt cooked
is quite interesting.
What's wrong? You want to eat it?
I can divide it in half.
It's not appropriate.
Eat.
Go on with your rest.
I'll leave you alone.
See you later.
I made it
with my pay.
I hope you
can be in vacation mode every day.
Fuses are not blown.
Is there a power outage?
I must finish and save it before my computer
is powered off.
Don't disturb me.
Has our company
reduced to this situation?
There's no water left.
We can't stay in the company anymore.
We should take the initiative.
-We should take the initiative. -It's not that serious.
The failure is because of
the consciousness of Party B.
Besides, we also
got the chance
to scold Party A like his grandfathers.
That's the highlight of our career.
We have a highlight,
but we have no salary.
Haven't we got paid?
I'd better
write a resignation letter.
Did Baba run away with our money?
But we don't have money.
Would he run away without money?
-You're right. -How should we live this month?
Mr. Xie is not here.
Miss, look.
You are
beautiful and kind, right?
Please make a call
and ask it for me.
Just one question, okay?
Please.
I've already
told you.
Mr. Xie is really not here.
Even if you come here,
you can't see him.
I know.
Just make a call.
Just one call, okay?
It's not difficult.
It won't waste your time.
No.
Don't refuse immediately.
Look.
Please don't make this hard for me.
I told you again and again.
Mr. Xie is not here.
Even if you come here,
you can't see him.
I know.
Just a call.
Buy something.
Hello, Mr. Xie.
Mr. Xie.
Hello. Hello.
You're not busy today?
You sent warmth to our receptionist?
No.
I want to see you.
You are busy.
So I have to find a way.
OK. Go on with your work.
No. Mr. Xie.
Yesterday, I really…
Well...
I lost my mind.
My attitude was very bad.
I apologize to you.
Eagles don't catch flies.
Please forgive me.
You checked your account
and found you couldn't support your company?
I'm waiting for you
to help me.
You spoiled
those kids.
I can't serve them.
No.
They're good kids.
Well...
But artists are actually
willful.
They have ability, dreams,
and enthusiasm.
This is very rare.
Enthusiasm is No.1 productive force.
Am I right?
Here's the thing.
As long as you promise
our team can take charge,
I won't care about the profit sharing.
It doesn't matter how much money I can earn.
I just want to realize their dreams.
Dreams.
Mr. Xie.
I'm begging you.
Please take a look.
Take a look.
No wonder they call you Dad Chen.
You deserve this title.
Tell me.
Is it worth begging me like this
for your stupid team?
Yes, it is.
As long as you like it,
I can do anything.
I'm good at it.
Here.
Take a look.
Mr. Chen.
You're not sincere.
You're not bowing in a standard way.
You're right.
There's room for improvement.
Here, take it.
Lower.
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Mr. Xie.
Please give me one more week.
I'll perfect all the characters
and worldviews
in Fengqi Shendu.
I'll submit my proposal to you then.
You can also
take this opportunity to see
whether we are capable or not.
I know you.
You're the returnee.
You were enlightened?
After all, we put much effort into this project.
Well, Mr. Xie.
You can decide
whether we can cooperate again
after you see our proposal
and know our strength.
OK.
I can agree.
But
if you fail,
I won't pay.
It's a deal.
That's it.
Take care.
What a rainy season!
It rains frequently.
Not long ago,
there was a small problem
in the company.
I was afraid you would run away.
So I told
a white lie.
I knew it.
Guangxi.
But the modeling,
the design of characters,
the worldviews,
the scripts,
the preliminaries
and including the 3D models.
If we add these things
together,
the cost is...
I can give up my share.
Really?
But you have to pay them.
Don't worry.
I'm capable of
collecting money.
There's more than one way to skin a cat.
Just go ahead.
You have me behind you.
Of course.
Leave the creation
to me.
I rest assured.
You're my baby.
-Yu, I'm back. -Chen, you're finally back.
I can't breathe.
Oh my god, what did you do?
Dad.
I feel like I'm in a dustbin
because of the limited edition perfume you brought back.
Oh my god.
Why did you touch my stuff?
Where is the perfume?
I don't know where I put it.
Don't touch my stuff.
Oh my god.
It stinks.
Don't touch it.
Chen,
why do you care so much
about this stinky perfume?
Maybe it's because
I haven't received gifts for a long time.
Didn't I just give you a present on Father's Day?
Your gift is different.
Did the miss on the 20th floor
become angry
because I called you that night?
No.
You're the most important.
No matter when you call me,
I'll come back as soon as possible.
How did you know?
Did you eavesdrop on my phone conversations again?
Last time,
you fell asleep
on the sofa with your phone.
Are you going to have a girlfriend?
No.
I already have you.
Why should I have a girlfriend?
Yu,
I have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
The lucky money
you received every year.
Can you
lend it to me?
Chen, are you going to treat
the brothers in your company to dinner?
Yes.
They don't have money to eat.
I have to buy them food.
But I promise you,
as long as my project succeeds,
I'll pay you back and double the amount.
I also want a drumstick.
No problem. It's a deal.
It's a deal.
One more thing.
I want to ride a horse.
It's nothing.
Here, a windmill.
Go.
Fly.
Now I know
That's a big
animation movie company
with big signs and dreams.
But it has a small wallet.
You have to work with money
instead of working with love now?
I promised Dad Chen
a free demo.
I can't get the salary this month.
We plan to send a proposal
to Mars Animation after a week.
I might be poor
for a while.
That's great.
I'll treat you to meals.
Okay.
Guangxi.
You are the kindest artist
I've ever seen.
How should I put it?
When I saw Dad Chen
bow to others today,
I suddenly thought of you.
Why?
Both of you
looked vulnerable,
but you tried your best to protect others.
So you
stepped out?
It seems that I influenced you a little
in your life.
It's not just a little.
It's very effective.
Just like now.
I really need to recharge.
This one,
at most 20%.
In this case,
50%.
How about this?
Let me feel it.
It's almost
74%.
74%?
You ask too much.
How can it be
100%?
In this way,
♫I like you♫
I can be fully charged.
♫Your cold expression♫
♫Pretending not to care♫
♫Melting in my hands♫
♫I like♫
♫The differences between you and me♫
♫Collide to create a wonderful melody♫
♫I like♫
♫Sofa hug movies♫
♫Coke and ice cream♫
♫Your breath♫
♫Is the most delicious aroma♫
♫Exclusively for me♫
♫The distance between two hearts beating♫
♫I just can't wait to be close to you♫
The water is off.
And the salary hasn't been paid.
We can't be paid.
Should we still work here?
How can I live
without the salary this month?
Run away.
The company is going to close down.
Why do we need a salary?
You are really...
What are you doing?
Jogging.
What time is it? Jogging?
Jogging?
You traitors.
I haven't paid you
salaries for just one day.
How could you treat me like this?
I raised you for nothing.
You ungrateful people!
Baba.
You don't have to pretend to be strong.
It's just an electricity bill.
We can chip in.
Come on.
Give your money.
This is mine.
I'll pay the electricity bill.
Water bill.
Little money is still money.
Baba.
This is all we can give.
You used to take care of us.
Now the company is in danger.
Let us do our best
to help you.
Take it.
Baba.
Take it, Baba.
Take it.
You're welcome.
The power came back on.
The water came back on.
Is it because of love?
Nonsense!
I just paid the money.
Didn't the company run out of money?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I've saved much money.
Will I be defeated
by such a small problem?
The problem of finance is solved,
but money can't be earned if we do nothing.
Of course.
Previously,
we were trapped in a question.
Which one came first,
chicken or eggs?
When the investors didn't invest,
we didn't push ahead.
When we didn't push ahead,
the investors didn't want to invest.
So now,
we only have one last way
to go.
In a week,
we adjust all the original characters
and the worldviews.
Submit our proposal to Mars Animation again.
Xu Guangxi, you were enlightened?
Let's work hard together.
It's time
to prove yourself.
Here.
For Shendu!
Let's get to work.
This...
Save some for me.
You've collected it.
Get to work.
It's good to have dreams.
What a pity.
What time is it?
Why haven't they
come back?
Ke is working overtime today.
She won't come back to eat.
Yibo said he went to his friend's home
to study.
So tonight,
just two of us eat here.
Why did they only tell you
they wouldn't go home?
Do they still know
I'm their father?
Look at you.
Your face is always solemn.
Who dares to talk to you?
Enough.
You spoiled him.
I'm not blaming you, stubborn old man.
You like to control everything.
Your daughter has grown up.
She will get married one day.
Your son will also grow up
and leave home.
Who will accompany you in the end?
Me.
In the end,
only we will stay here
and eat together.
This situation will last long.
So, they are adults.
Stop rambling.
You don't like to listen?
Let me get you some soup.
Well...
Fine.
I'm bored.
I'm going out for a walk.
You finished eating?
Yes.
Stubborn old man.
Don't forget
to take a coat with you. Don't catch a cold.
Mr. Chen.
Your company went bankrupt
and you became a delivery guy?
I won't argue with you today.
I'll lose my luck if I argue with women.
I'm a big boss.
I can attack and defend.
I'm flexible.
Are you out of your mind?
Forget it. I don't want to argue with you.
I don't want to argue with you.
Let me tell you.
A miracle will come tomorrow.
Wait and see. Bye.
Madman.
If you want him to carry two swords,
you should pay attention
to the curvature of his elbows.
It must be over 45 degrees.
Look.
Right?
I've added colors
to the first character.
Let me see.
I like the colors.
Guys.
I've finished my paperwork on the worldviews.
Good.
I've revised the graphics
in our proposal.
But
the printer...
Dad Chen has repaired it this morning.
Use it now.
Okay.
Baba really tried his best
for the deposit.
Babes.
Here.
I prepared supper for you.
Hurry up and eat.
Thank you, Baba.
Hurry up. Baba.
Chicken wings.
Baba.
You don't have to meet clients tonight?
The clients are asleep at this time.
Hurry up and eat.
Get back to work
after eating.
It's delicious.
I'm waiting for you at the parking garage.
I've booked a nice restaurant.
I'm waiting
to take in a poor guy who works overtime for free.
I'm sorry.
I just finished the proposal
we're going to submit to Mr. Xie.
You're starving?
Since you worked so hard,
I forgive you.
Let's eat something delicious.
Hello, dad.
Where are you?
I told Aunt Lan this afternoon
I had to work overtime.
I won't go back for dinner.
Why is there no one in your company?
♫Travels to the end♫
♫Of the whole universe♫
♫Together, we will♫
♫Guard the whole one world♫
I give up.
I feel dizzy.
You feel dizzy?
Let's take a break.
You
lost
a big platform this time.
Does it affect you?
I've done a lot of work.
I even have images
of my target clients.
My two live streamers
have different styles.
Yurou
used to be a saleswoman.
She's good at introducing the functions of products
and their attractive points.
Xiaomian
already
has many fans.
This is her advantage.
I believe you can succeed.
Let me help you recharge now.
I'm fully charged.
Really?
Yes.
Let me try whether it will
help you recharge faster.
♫Look at me♫
♫I have a meteor♫
♫The world pauses for you♫
♫Baby, you are the one♫
♫I secretively in my heart♫
♫Wrote I'm willing to♫
♫Don't know why. I suddenly♫
♫Hate to calculate the distance between you♫
♫I fear I cannot see you in the next second♫
♫My heart is protesting♫
♫I just feel it too♫
♫It's like the coffee with full caramel milk foam♫
♫The air has the fragrance of missing you♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫