[English subtitles are available]
[Sweet On]
♫Oh love should be♫
♫Like songbirds soaring to the sun♫
♫My dear♫
♫When you walk with me♫
♫I feel the troubles in me fade away♫
♫And if I want you, you want me♫
♫Who cares what others may think?♫
♫I hear church bells ring♫
♫I have you, you have me♫
♫Roses will bloom in our dreams♫
♫I'd kiss you now♫
[Love the Way You Are]
[Episode 24]
What a coincidence.
Are you busy?
Yes, I am.
Are you animators well acquainted
with people in the gaming circle?
That's a good question.
Let me tell you.
Although these two things
seem different,
they are actually one thing.
There is an internationally
famous game company
that seems to make games.
So are you acquainted with them?
Not really, but I can ask.
Forget it.
No. I can ask.
Who are you looking for?
How are you going back?
Let me give you a ride.
No need.
Well, I happened to...
It's raining.
It's raining heavily.
I can drive you back home
on my way home.
The taxi has arrived.
No.
Take care.
Text me when you get home.
Goodbye. Have a good rest.
Mr. Chen.
-Are you working overtime? -Mr. Chen.
Yes.
Tomorrow, Yike is going to
the Original Animation Exhibition to see Xu Yuan.
So we need to prepare a plan for it.
Original Animation Exhibition?
Mr. Chen,
we need to make a plan now.
We have to go.
Okay.
Go on with your work.
-Okay. -Bye.
Go for it! Do your best!
Go for it!
Original Animation Exhibition. To see Xu Yuan.
Original Animation Exhibition.
Ms. Xu.
I sincerely ask for
a cooperation with you.
During the live stream,
if we can make
the sales volume of your company's game skins
reach the number you feel satisfied with,
will you consider withdrawing
the previous tort compensation
or having
a long-term cooperation with us?
The sales volume of game skins?
We've done a data research.
Currently, the sales bottleneck of your company
is the game skins.
Give me a chance.
I'll accept the Valuation Adjustment.
Valuation Adjustment?
I have confidence
in the company's business capacity.
But now in the company,
there's no product that is worthy of collaboration.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
Ms. Xu.
I think
you should be interested
in this painting.
So Yin Yike
has a backup plan.
Not bad.
But what makes you think
I'll pay?
Please hold this for me.
This is the current game skin
of your company.
Give me two minutes.
Ms. Xu.
I'm sorry.
The style is different.
But I don't know
what the overall dynamic effects
will be like
after the modeling.
For the dynamic effects of clothes
in the real world,
I'll simulate them well while adjusting
the details later.
Don't worry about this.
Besides,
I know your company
wants to develop Chinese style,
but
you can't find a suitable key animator.
So I made this plan.
What's your name?
My name's Xu Guangxi.
Have you signed a contract?
I'm the director of
an animation company.
What a pity.
If the intellectual property between the cooperator
and us is not clear,
it'll be very dangerous.
Then what do you think
of exchanging authorization for authorization?
Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
I'm his boss.
Let me introduce myself.
My name is Chen Ye.
This is my business card.
[Chen Ye]
[Shanghai That's A Big Animation Movie Company]
I can sign an agreement with you
for a waiver of
the intellectual property of this part.
In this way, it's between our two companies.
Look.
You won't have any worries.
Right?
Are you from SC?
This is not important.
What matters is that
you've got such a good animator
without any effort, right?
If you like him,
you can come to our company.
We can still continue the cooperation.
We still need to see whether
this animator I've got without any effort
is really useful.
Dad Chen.
Why are you here?
Can you really hide
the dark tricks in your heart
from me?
It's okay.
Fighting for love and dreams
is also the romance of men.
I understand.
I'll thank you on behalf of Yike.
In terms of the relationship between us,
you don't have to thank me.
It's okay. Don't take it to heart.
Let's go to SC together
and face it together.
Face it together?
What's wrong?
Our company
is so cohesive
because
as a boss,
I have to meddle in everything.
This is such a good tradition.
We can't lose it.
Then...
It's such a bother for you.
Thank you so much.
It's not a bother.
Not at all.
When are you going?
[Ms. Xu (Flower World)]
Hello, Ms. Xu.
Miss Yin.
I can give you
another half an hour.
See you in the company's meeting room.
Okay, Ms. Xu. Thank you.
Miss Yin, this way, please.
Ms. Xu.
Miss Yin is here.
Sit down and talk.
Ms. Xu.
This is our cooperation plan.
You can take a look.
With the current amount offline,
it's impossible to complete this Valuation Adjustment.
Frank,
I think
you were right about Miss Yin.
Miss Yin can
bring back such a
valuable contract.
It's not easy.
This Valuation Adjustment on the business performance
is not a casual promise.
What happened between SC
and the Flower World last time
caused such a groundswell of public opinion.
In fact, reversely,
it's beneficial
for our publicity.
We also did market research.
The consumers are looking forward
to this cooperation.
So,
we are quite confident in the Valuation Adjustment
on business performance.
You are very confident, Miss Yin.
You impressed me.
Now,
I sincerely hope
your Live Stream Department can do a good job.
If you can do a good job,
it's like sharing the burden for me.
However,
Frank,
after Ms. Zheng resigned,
the position of marketing director
has been vacant.
Without the director,
the morale of staff may be unstable.
Mr. Kong.
Don't worry about this.
Our Live Stream Department
won't be affected by this.
In the end,
it'll depend on the business performance.
We should encourage
the morale of the Marketing Department.
How about this?
The whole team of the Live Stream Department
will move back to their original workplace.
Then...
Miss Yin, keep up the good work.
Let the Live Stream Department
set an example for everyone.
It's rare.
It's rare that Frank
should trust you so much.
It depends on yourself
whether it can succeed or not.
Thank you, Mr. Kong.
Do your best.
Stop watching.
She has been there for so long. It must have failed.
Don't be such a doomsayer.
Can you stop making
yourself panic first?
Calm down.
I've thought about it.
If I get fired,
I'll open a cafe at my hometown.
You still have that much money?
No.
You've already thought about a way out?
What should we do then?
Yike.
Are we fired?
It's okay.
No matter what happens,
we can accept it.
And we'll always follow you.
That's right.
Say something.
Frank asked us to pack up.
I was right.
I quit.
The nail polish I've just bought
will be mailed to our company's address.
Pack up.
He asked us to move back to the 20th floor.
The Marketing Department.
We finally made it.
We can go back.
We made it.
Where is the Marketing Department?
Just come with us.
Yike,
are we going to
have new products?
I've just received a notice from Ms. Xu.
There will be some slight adjustment
for the co-branded skins this time.
We will choose a popular style
and a hidden style among them.
Will the Flower World
send an animator here?
Well...
Just wait and see.
Yibo,
try this.
Have some water.
No, thanks.
Stop reading.
-Xia Xiaomian. -You've been reading for so long. Take a break.
I'm memorizing the words.
I can't memorize them if you're like this.
Just tell me what you want.
If there's nothing special,
just go home.
You don't have to stay here with me.
But...
You study so hard.
If you don't like this,
why do you force yourself?
You don't understand.
I understand.
Anyway,
your dad is fine now.
Besides,
you promised me
to help me improve my live stream knowledge
and collaborate with me in the live stream.
Don't forget.
As for the live stream,
just forget it.
I won't do it again.
Why?
I'm lucky this time.
I can't make my dad angry again.
And I've figured it out.
I should listen to him,
and focus on the postgraduate entrance exam.
I won't do the live stream anymore.
No.
Look.
Your dad has even agreed on
the love relationship between
Guangxi and Yike.
He will agree on
your work on live stream.
Then what?
Make him angry so he has to live in hospital again?
But Yibo,
you are a famous live streamer.
You have so many videos.
You've accumulated these videos and fans
one by one for so many years to get today's results.
They all represent your hard work
and your achievements.
You just give up like this?
What's the use of being a famous live streamer?
My dad doesn't accept it.
We accept it.
During the live stream,
your eyes were sparkling.
I think
you really like this job.
Doesn't your dad know that?
Actually at the beginning,
I wanted to take the advantage of
the good trend of live stream
to earn some extra money.
From a nobody
to a live streamer who had more and more fans,
I don't deny that
I did feel proud.
When the number of my fans was
getting bigger and bigger later,
I got more and more
proficient in the live stream.
And you know what?
Many foreign brands
didn't plan to
enter the market of
our country at first.
I tried so hard
to get their products
and gave them to my fans
as gifts.
This way, they could
increase the popularity and open the market in our country,
so they were willing to enter the market.
And when we first cooperated,
it was really...
It was very tiring.
Many of them were in foreign countries.
There was time difference.
I stayed up late to contact them every day.
During that time, I really...
Yes, yes, yes.
I had to study for the postgraduate entrance exam
and do this at the same time, you know?
Yibo,
when you mentioned this,
you looked very serious.
Very handsome.
So I think your dad
will approve of you.
As the saying goes,
it's like...
Every profession produces
its own topmost "pasta".
Topmost "pasta"?
It's topmost master.
Whatever it is,
anyway,
there is always food
in every profession.
But Xiaomian...
You asked me to have
a heart-to-heart talk with my dad.
Thank you for that.
At first, I thought
you were
a reckless
and careless girl.
Later, I found
you are more insightful than me
on many things.
So I've figured it out.
Don't put a bet on family,
and cherish them.
Yibo.
Stop calling my name.
I'm going back to recite the words.
Besides,
you should go home early.
Be careful.
Thank you, Xia Xiaomian.
This is Dan from Xiafei Road.
Well,
it's been a long time since my last live streaming.
In this live streaming,
I want to tell you something.
Well,
I'm going to quit the live stream.
Farewell?
Where are you going?
No way.
It was not easy for me to find
a live streamer I like.
I know you've been with me
during the whole time.
I'm very grateful.
But as
something happened in my family,
I have to focus
a lot of my energy
and time
on that thing.
So I might have to be away
from this for some time.
Don't give me gifts.
So enthusiastic.
In that case,
I promise you.
After I finish handling
the affairs of my family,
I'll be back, okay?
Of course,
in the last live streaming,
I still remember
you guys, my dear fans.
I'll recommend you...
The latest version of shoes.
Why do I recommend these shoes?
Because first of all, look,
the design of the soles
is very stylish.
And more importantly,
the shoes are of neutral style.
Both men and women can wear them.
Boys wearing them
won't look like a sissy,
while girls wearing them
will look sporty.
And this pair of shoes...
Live stream is really fun.
Look.
He's not usually like this at home.
He's so eloquent.
Yes.
He's quite handsome, too.
Of course.
It feels like stepping on cotton candy, so...
Mr. Yin, look.
There are so many people.
They are all
Yibo's fans.
Yibo is
a big star in the live stream room.
Really?
How many people are watching his show?
Look, here is the number of audience.
It means
there are over 300,000 people
-watching Yibo's live stream. -Over 300,000 people are watching it?
This kid
is really amazing.
Well...
This...
What is this yacht
used for?
It represents a gift.
This is a like.
So if you place an order now...
I'll give my son a gift.
Very suitable.
Thank you, Yin...
It costs you money.
How much?
Over 1,000 yuan.
Over 1,000 yuan?
Yin Chenggong.
Yin Yibo, come out!
I have to hang up.
Dad.
Come out!
You...
Why did you give me a yacht?
I…
Xia Xiaomian.
Why are you here?
I'm teaching your dad to watch live stream.
This...
Give the money back to me.
It cost me half a month's
salary.
A yacht costs over 1,000 yuan.
Listen, you can't accept gifts
during your live stream in the future.
If someone gives you a gift,
return it.
Understand?
Wait, Dad.
You mean my live stream in the future?
Money
doesn't grow on trees.
It's just a small thing, and it costs over 1,000 yuan.
Don't accept this gift. Got it?
Got it.
You mean
I can continue to do
the live streaming?
I didn't say that.
As long as you can pass the postgraduate entrance exam,
with the door of your room closed,
you can do whatever you want.
I'll pretend I see nothing.
Dad, I love you.
Give the money back to me.
I won't love you for now.
Go away!
Remember to transfer the money back to me.
I'll help you
get your money back.
They look good together.
A yacht costs over 1,000 yuan.
It's so easy to earn money through live stream.
It's much more profitable than driving.
I'll do a live stream tomorrow.
It's okay! It's okay!
Why are you
at our home?
What did you tell my dad?
Why did he watch my live stream?
Nothing.
I taught your dad to watch the live stream.
He supported
your live stream.
How did you
enter our house?
Xiaomian.
Come on.
Have some watermelon.
Thank you, Mrs. Yin.
Come on. It's sweet.
Come on. Pick a big one.
Aunt Lan.
How did she enter our house?
What did she say to my dad?
Why did my dad
watch the live stream and give me the gift of yacht?
This colleague of Yike's
is too bold.
She just knocked on the door and came in.
As soon as she came in,
she coaxed your father
cleverly.
Your dad was very happy.
You know
your dad is stubborn.
He doesn't admit defeat.
Yibo.
Is she
your little girlfriend?
Aunt Lan.
Pure friendship.
Trust me.
Trust me. Pure friendship.
Xia Xiaomian.
It's late.
Go back.
Go, go, go.
I haven't finished yet.
-Eat on the way. -Bye, Mrs. Yin.
Be careful.
This kid.
Hello?
You're still working?
Yes.
I have to work overtime tonight.
What about you?
What a coincidence.
I have to work overtime, too.
It seems that
we're in the same boat.
Are you working overtime at home
or in the company today?
Hello, Miss Yin.
Your overtime working partner Xu
is online.
Thank you, Director Xu.
It's late,
and you have to come to my company.
So you finally moved back here.
After we received the Valuation Adjustment Mechanism,
we moved back here.
You're partly credited with this.
Come on.
This is an overtime working small corner
I've prepared for you specially.
So sweet.
I have
a personal reward for you.
Wait for me.
This is
the exclusive coffee for Xu Guangxi.
Do you like it?
This is the best coffee
I've ever had.
The best!
Can I have it every day?
It depends on your performance.
When will we
start working?
I know Ms. Xu has high standard.
I even asked for someone else's help.
What a coincidence.
I've also hired a helper
to assist us.
This is the original flavor.
Thank you.
This
is the cherry blossom flavor.
What else?
Are you here to help
or to eat?
You bought so many snacks.
Of course I'll help.
You'll be hungry during the meeting.
I did the logistics service.
No, I was kind enough
to buy you so much food.
You bought too much.
What are these?
So many snacks and junk food.
Well, you don't eat,
but there are still two other people.
Why are you giving it to me if I don't eat?
Well,
I bought pizza.
I'm sorry.
I'm hungry.
Thank you.
Learn from her.
Let's start the meeting.
Sit down.
Start the meeting.
Let's start.
I think
we are working with
an Otome Game.
But we also need to make
a sweet perfume.
Smell of popular co-branded
perfumes in games
all features
strong impulsiveness
and easiness to remember.
The users...
Chen Ye.
I'm sorry.
If it's extreme,
can we use
the concept of restless hormone?
Use...
Dad Chen.
Chen Ye.
What are you doing here?
I don't understand your talk.
What do you want me to do?
I'm a little bored.
I really don't know much about perfume.
Dad, pick up the phone.
I'm sorry.
Yu.
Go to sleep.
I'll get home late.
I might put it on the front page.
Like a video.
The details here.
Excuse me.
Yu said he was going to bed.
Could you please
tell him one or two stories?
-Look at these clothes. -Hello.
Mom! Mom!
Yu.
Don't call me mom.
I'll be off work soon.
Tell you a story?
No problem.
How many stories do you want to hear today?
Three?
You have to promise me
to go to bed first.
Xia Xiaomian.
How did you deal with my father?
That's easy.
I told him you showed up
at a "clitical" moment
and saved
our entire Live Stream Department.
What do you mean?
At a "clitical" moment?
Xia Xiaomian, it's "at a critical moment".
Can you improve your literacy skills?
It's the same anyway.
Now your dad supports you.
Thank you.
What?
Thank me?
Shouldn't you do something?
Don't be so insatiable.
You're lucky this time.
If you sneaks in again
and my dad discovers you,
both of us will be doomed.
Your father
isn't angry this time, right?
Besides, he even supports your live stream.
This is a good thing.
What do you mean?
Yibo,
true love can only be discoverd
after going through wind and rain.
Look at us.
You saved me from cyber violence.
I helped you solve the primary problem.
Can we consider it as
going though a typhoon together?
Tornado.
Extra large typhoon.
Extra large...
I don't understand.
Speak in human language.
Agree to
my one small request.
I see.
You want me to treat you to dinner, right?
No problem.
After you finish the collaborated live stream,
I can treat you to dinner.
Just dinner?
What else?
I'm busy with the postgraduate entrance exam during daytime,
and with the live streaming at night.
I don't have time.
But...
No buts.
This is the best condition.
Besides,
have you finished memorizing the script for your live stream?
You're always thinking about other things.
The script?
I haven't memorized the script yet.
How did you ride your motorcycle?
It scared me.
Are you hurt?
What's wrong?
I...
I think I've sprained my ankle.
Well...
Let me carry you.
I'll carry you.
What are you waiting for? Come up.
Hurry up.
Let's go.
Are you out of your mind?
What are you thinking about every day?
Watch out while you're walking.
Understand?
Yibo,
I've made up my mind.
After I finish memorizing the script,
I'll "calibrate".
I said you're not smart.
It's "celebrate", not "calibrate".
I want to "calibrate".
What are you talking about?
By the way,
I've promised you to help you with the lessons.
I'll see you online.
Don't forget to keep your promise.
Is he asleep?
Yes.
Sit down. Let me clean up.
My house is a bit messy.
It's okay.
This is...
I bought it for you.
Thank you for your hard work these days.
I didn't know
you know a lot about this.
I know little about it.
I just searched it online.
You can use it.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
What do you want to drink?
I'll get you some water.
It's okay. Don't bother.
Come on. Have some water.
Do they represent you and Yu?
Custom-made?
No.
I made it myself.
You made it yourself? So brilliant.
No, no.
Come on. Have a seat.
I didn't know
you can do this.
I was forced by the school.
It's the handmade class in their school.
Kids
don't know how to make these things.
They're all made by parents.
In other kids' family,
mothers and fathers made them together.
I did it alone.
I signed up for a class
and learned a few lessons
before I made them successfully.
I made that little wooden man, too.
It's not easy
to be a single father.
It's nothing.
At first, when I had to
look after him by myself,
I was not used to it.
But gradually,
I just learned it.
However, I really think
women are more gifted
for looking after kids than men.
Take myself as an example. I'll play with him,
cook for him,
and make these
little sculptures for him. I can do these things.
But for putting a child to sleep,
you're better than me.
Look. After you came,
he fell asleep so soon.
As for me... Look at these.
I have to tell him so many stories
before he goes to bed every night
so as to make him fall asleep.
It's like my story-telling session.
Enough.
Stop flattering me.
Chen Ye.
You're a boss after all.
You have a house and a car. You have good conditions.
It isn't difficult for you
to find a gentle and considerate
stepmother for Yu, right?
Why do you always
insist on
asking me for help?
As you know,
it doesn't work with me.
As I have
a car and a house,
and my conditions are good,
I still
have these
fantasies.
I'm imagining that,
apart from finding a mother for Yu,
I can also find
someone I like, and live with her
for the rest of my life.
What's wrong?
It suddenly occurred to me
I have something to discuss with you.
Do you think
Qin Yiran and Dad Chen
can be together?
What did you say?
I mean,
although she usually
seems to be carefree,
and always hangs out,
that's because
she hasn't met someone
she really likes.
She's afraid of getting hurt.
Don't worry.
Dad Chen won't let Yiran down.
But you...
Why do you sound like that
you're going to bring your bestie into the pit of love?
Let me tell you a story.
Someone feels guilty like a thief in the middle of the night.
What?
I...
I just want to chat with you.
Four feet.
No.
Two feet.
Two feet. Two feet.
My eyesight has dropped again.
I think I need to get a new pair of glasses.
Xu Guangxi has four feet.
It's you who have four feet.
Your proposal is good.
But there's a pity.
Why didn't Xu Guangxi
come to explain his work to me?
Because it's the cooperation between SC
and the Flower World.
According to the routine, I have to
come to report to you.
Guangxi has something to do at his company today,
but he also asked me to say hello to you.
What if I don't like
his work?
What will you do?
He said you would like it.
He studied me?
But it's useless if I'm the only one who likes it.
Only when the users like it can it be a success.
You are the leading figure
in the Flower World.
The work you like
must be the one
that the core users like.
Yin Yike.
No need to say those flattering words.
It doesn't work with me.
I'm not flattering you.
It's my extremely good comment
on the creator.
Your negotiation skills are really good.
Okay.
Let's work on
the following content quickly.
Okay.
Thank you, Ms. Xu.
Hello.
How was it? Did it pass?
What?
You have no confidence in yourself?
How is that possible?
Thanks to you,
I don't need to modify anything.
Look.
I told you Xu Yuan would like it.
I didn't expect
you to be so likable to female bosses.
Tell me honestly
how long you spent on
studying her.
I didn't.
I've worked for other clients for so many times.
I have insight into what clients like.
These are basic skills.
Xu Yuan really thinks highly of you.
She kept praising you, saying
you are both handsome and talented.
How she wishes
she could make you work in her company now.
Well,
I have to hang up.
I've worked for you for a few days,
and the progress of Fengqi Shendu
has slowed down.
I think I have to work overtime tonight.
You have to go home alone.
But Guangxi, I...
I have to hang up.
I really have to hang up.
They asked me to work.
Be careful
on your way home tonight.
Bye.
What's going on?
Ms. Xu.
Your Blue Mountain coffee.
Help me replace it
with the Geisha beans today.
Didn't you say that Geisha is too refreshing,
and not strong enough?
It's good to change
the flavor occasionally.
Okay. I'll change it right away.
Xu Guangxi.
♫Travels to the end♫
♫Of the whole universe♫
♫Together, we will♫
♫Guard the whole one world♫
♫Look at me♫
♫I have a meteor♫
♫The world pauses for you♫
♫Baby, you are the one♫
♫I secretively in my heart♫
♫Wrote I'm willing to♫
♫Don't know why. I suddenly♫
♫Hate to calculate the distance between you and me♫
♫I fear I cannot see you in the next second♫
♫My heart is protesting♫
♫I just feel it too♫
♫It's like the coffee with full caramel milk foam♫
♫The air has the fragrance of missing you♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
♫Baby, from now on, come to me♫
♫Come to me♫
♫I want to be an umbrella for you♫
♫To shield you from rain and wind♫
♫You are my luck♫
♫I'm like an ice-cream beneath the sun♫
♫Melt my heart into love♫
[Love the Way You Are]