♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how resolute the past was♪
♪It was all a fictional plot♪
♪The vow named forever turned into a lie♪
♪Changed long ago with Time♪
♪Gradually disintegrated♪
♪When late night flips through memories♪
♪It feels like I still have everything♪
♪But when I come to my senses♪
♪The story has already ended sloppily♪
♪Flickering on and off♪
=Chasing Love=
=Episode 24=
(Hongcheng Church)
Governor, the bride has arrived.
(Ouyang Yue,)
(in this life)
(you can only be my woman.)
Let go of me. Don't do this.
Let her go.
Qin Jifeng,
you came after all.
Let her go.
The person you want to kill is me.
Brother.
Do you love her very much?
Do you love her more than I do?
If you die, she can live.
No.
Qin Jifeng, no.
Goodbye.
No.
I won.
I love her more.
Jiahao.
Jiahao!
♪Turning back, I'm lost and unable to return♪
I prepared this for you a long time ago.
I always wanted to put it on you.
♪No time to weigh gains and losses♪
Yue.
I love you.
Jiahao.
No matter what you've done,
I love you just as I did when we were kids.
Jiahao, let's play the piano together.
♪Life is too cold, the embrace too warm♪
♪How can fragile petals
withstand the harsh snow♪
♪The dancing light takes away the brilliance♪
Today,
Moonlight Hotel reopens.
You're the only guest.
Yue,
happy birthday.
This will be our home from now on.
I can do business
or work as a laborer.
I can give you the life you want.
Yue.
I've finally got to be with you.
Never...
Never changed.
Jiahao.
Jiahao, wake up.
Someone help me!
♪No time to weigh gains and losses♪
Jiahao.
Jiahao, wake up.
♪Happy times are too short♪
Jiahao.
♪We met too late♪
♪When feelings grow, we often have to part♪
♪Life is too cold♪
(Fifteen Years Later)
Down with Japanese Imperialism!
National resistance is everyone's duty!
Miss Ouyang.
Down with Japanese Imperialism!
This is the last truck of supplies.
They can be shipped out tonight.
Okay.
Send a message to the Commander.
Fortune Trading Company will fully cooperate
with the strategic material transfer.
We guarantee to complete the task
within a month.
Yes, Miss Ouyang.
Miss Ouyang.
A letter from the Boss.
Down with Japanese Imperialism!
National resistance is everyone's duty!
Alright.
♪The streetlight's glow falls on the ground♪
♪Your silhouette blurs and fades away♪
♪I'm stranded in place♪
♪Love and hate linger on my lips♪
♪Time pushes away♪
♪The distance between us♪
♪Is enlarged♪
♪Until I can't see you♪
♪Until you forget♪
♪ How many years must pass ♪
♪Before this love fades away♪
♪So that when we meet again,
it won't be noticed♪
♪If I weren't afraid♪
♪And didn't retreat♪
♪On the day you left,
I moved forward without hesitation♪
♪Would you have stayed
by my side a little longer♪
♪Forget me a little slower♪
♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how intense the past was♪
♪It was all a fictional story♪
♪The vow of forever turned into a lie♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)