♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how resolute the past♪
♪It was all a fictional plot♪
♪The vow named 'forever' turned into a lie♪
♪Changed long ago with time♪
♪Gradually disintegrated♪
♪When memories are revisited in the deep night♪
♪It feels like we still have everything♪
♪But upon realization♪
♪The story has ended hastily♪
♪Flickering on and off♪
=Chasing Love=
=Episode 12=
Open the door.
Master, what happened?
Who is this?
Qin Jifeng.
No, now he should be called Liang Jifeng.
- Find a day to change your surname
- Liang Jifeng.
and return to the clan.
My son should not take his mother's surname.
Understood, Father.
Master, where is Jiahao?
Where did Jiahao go, Master?
Don't mention your useless son.
He pointed a gun at his head to threaten me.
I don't have such a rebellious son.
He wouldn't lose to an illegitimate son,
Master?
Listen to me carefully.
Jifeng is my son.
If I hear you say that again,
don't blame me for being rude.
Jiahao.
Jiahao, where did you go?
(Hongcheng Hotel)
- Yue
- Water.
- Yue, you must hold on.
Water.
No.
The fever is severe.
I need to get some medicine.
♪Lingering and gazing♪
Go, go, go.
Hurry, move aside.
(Xingrui Medical Clinic)
No money to pay for the medicine?
Do you think this is a charity hall?
Ladies and gentlemen, don't miss out.
Don't push.
Everyone will get some. Here. Here.
One at a time.
Today is our pharmacy's anniversary.
Free clinic and free medicine.
Free medical consultations.
Free medicine.
Whether you have a fever, a cold,
or a headache.
Genuine medicine at fair prices.
Alright, here, take it.
We guarantee genuine medicine at fair prices.
The event ends today.
Don't miss out. It won't happen again.
Come, take a look.
♪No time to weigh gains and losses♪
Doctor, how is she?
Follow the prescription I gave you.
Three times a day.
She'll get better soon.
Thank you, sir.
♪We met too late♪
Take care.
♪When feelings grow, we often have to part♪
♪Life is too cold ♪
Yue, you're awake.
♪How can fragile petals
withstand the harsh snow♪
♪The dancing light takes away the brilliance♪
Why did you save me?
Your dad
killed my dad.
♪Only regret remains♪
I'm sorry.
My father wronged you.
Your dad killed my dad.
Do you know how much I hate him,
how much I want revenge
and how much I want to kill him
with my own hands?
I know. I know it all.
Let's leave this place, okay?
Go far away.
Forget the Governor's Mansion
and the Fortune Trading Company.
Those burdens shouldn't be ours to bear.
I just want to be with you.
And live a peaceful life.
Where can we go?
I can do business
or work as a laborer.
I can give you the life you want.
♪Happy times are too short♪
Trust me.
♪When feelings grow, we often have to part♪
Your hand is wounded.
Let me bandage it for you first.
♪How can fragile petals♪
Yue.
I've finally got to be with you.
♪The dancing light takes away the brilliance♪
(Where can we go?)
(This vast net of Hongcheng)
(has already deeply entangled us.)
Don't worry. It's nothing serious.
Don't tell anyone about what happened today.
Boss, the boat is ready.
Yue is meticulous.
Don't let her find out it was me.
Alright.
Jifeng, these are what we usually eat.
I don't know if you can get used to it.
If you can't get used to it,
I'll prepare something else for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Chen.
This is already good enough.
Jifeng,
we're all family. No need to be so formal.
And you just came back.
If there's anything you're not used to,
just tell her,
and let her arrange it for you.
Thank you, Father.
Let's eat.
Alright.
By the way, Jifeng,
there's something I need you to do today.
Father, just give the order.
Go to the Newspaper Office
and publish a front-page article.
Fortune Trading Company is caught
smuggling arms.
Starting today,
seal the banks and detain all ships.
Yes, I will handle it right away.
Sit down.
Finish your meal first.
before you go handle the matter.
Yes, Father.
Silly child.
This silly child.
(Fortune Trading Company caught smuggling arms)
(Its owner Ouyang Zhongtian suspected
to be involved)
(To Governor Liang)
Mr. Jifeng,
Master asked me to give you the intelligence
we received this morning.
It shows the hotel where Miss Ouyang
and Mr. Jiahao are hiding.
Master wants you to personally lead a team
and capture Miss Ouyang.
Understood.
Master wants you to go now.
Are you teaching me how to do things?
I wouldn't dare.
Lieutenant Li,
you used to follow Jiahao,
and had to listen to him for everything.
But now that I'm back,
you should know what you can do
and what you cannot.
Got it?
Yes, Mr. Jifeng.
Let's go.
I got two tickets from my classmate.
Let's head south.
You said you like the sea.
Find a warm place to stay by the seaside.
I'll find some work.
You can raise some flowers at home.
When there's nothing to do,
we can take a walk on the beach.
Jiahao.
Yes?
Nothing.
I just thought we might not come back.
It makes me sad.
Everything will start anew.
Jiahao,
I just remembered
I haven't picked up a photo of Father and me
at the photo studio.
I need to get it back.
I'll get it for you.
Wait for me.
Jiahao.
What's wrong?
Be careful on the road.
Rickshaw.
Madam,
take a look.
Freshly baked cakes.
(Yue is acting a bit strange today.)
Take a look.
Yue.
Yue!
♪The streetlight's glow falls on the ground♪
♪Your silhouette blurs and fades away♪
♪I'm stranded in place♪
♪Love and hate linger on my lips♪
♪Time pushes away♪
♪The distance between us♪
♪Is enlarged♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)