♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how resolute the past♪
♪It was all a fictional plot♪
♪The vow named 'forever' turned into a lie♪
♪Changed long ago with time♪
♪Gradually disintegrated♪
♪When memories are revisited in the deep night♪
♪It feels like we still have everything♪
♪But upon realization♪
♪The story has ended hastily♪
♪Flickering on and off♪
=Chasing Love=
=Episode 13=
Yue!
Yue.
Back off, back off!
Mr. Jifeng, what should we do now?
Take her back first.
Quickly call the doctor over.
Yes.
Qin Jifeng.
What did you do to Yue?
- Let her go.
- There's nothing to see.
Liang Jiahao.
She just jumped out of the window.
Stop the fuss!
Take Mr. Jiahao back to the mansion.
Yes.
Let's go, Mr. Jiahao.
(Governor's Mansion)
What exactly happened?
When I arrived,
she jumped out of the window,
hit her head,
and passed out.
Did she jump off herself?
Yes, she jumped as soon as I arrived
Qin Jifeng.
What do you want to do?
Haven't you caused enough trouble?
Yue.
You're awake.
Jiahao.
I...
How are you?
Mr. Liang.
Mrs. Liang.
Why are you all here?
Who...
Who are you?
Yue, are you feeling unwell somewhere?
I...
I seem to...
I seem to have forgotten a lot of things.
What do you
still remember?
I remember
I received the news of my father's death.
Then I bought the earliest ticket back.
And then...
And then I can't remember anymore.
Where's my dad?
Did something really happen to my dad?
- Yue.
- I need to find him.
If you can't remember, don't think about it.
It's okay. I'm here.
- This...
- Don't think about it.
This is amnesia.
What should we do now?
Miss Ouyang indeed seems to have amnesia.
It might be due to severe mental trauma
and also a brain injury.
Didn't you like roses?
When did you start planting daisies?
Roses have thorns.
Not everyone can grow them.
Unlike daisies,
which are innocent and elegant.
Suitable for home and family.
Don't you agree, brother?
What did you call me?
You are my fiancé's brother.
I should call you brother.
You really don't remember anything?
What should I remember?
What should you remember?
You should remember who killed Master Ouyang.
And now you're going to marry his son.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Yue,
you remember everything,
right?
I am your brother's fiancée.
Manners, please, brother.
Master,
do you suspect that Miss Ouyang
is pretending to have amnesia?
Listen,
help me arrange a meeting with an old friend.
Yes.
I'll do it.
- Yue.
You just recovered.
Drink more soup.
Thank you.
Jiahao,
there's a bit of dirt here.
Yue,
from now on,
you have to help me take care of Jiahao more.
He's been spoiled by me.
He never grows up.
Ma'am, you're too kind.
Jiahao and I will soon be married.
I will take good care of him.
By the way, Yue,
your uncle's plaque
hasn't been placed in your family's
ancestral hall.
Now you're the only one left in the family.
It's up to you if his plaque should
be placed in the ancestral hall.
Jiahao has told me everything about my uncle.
After all, he is my uncle.
Bring him back to the ancestral hall someday.
Yue is really magnanimous.
You have a kind heart.
Once you become a family,
no one will bully you anymore.
Our Jiahao
will not let you suffer any grievances.
You two brothers
help me handle some matters
at the company this afternoon.
Yes, Father.
Yue can stay at home.
I have an appointment with an acquaintance.
His family is also in the shipping business.
If you want to revive the company,
you can use some connections.
Thank you for your efforts, Mr. Liang.
Let's eat.
Mr. Liang said that your family
is also in the shipping business.
He asked me to seek your advice.
Miss Ouyang,
long time no see.
Why?
Miss Ouyang,
are you very afraid of me?
You must be joking, sir.
It's our first meeting.
How could I be afraid?
The first time?
I couldn't forget you, Miss Ouyang.
Your body is so soft and smooth.
Your hair carries a fragrance.
I already told you I don't know you.
This is the Governor's Mansion.
Please show some respect, sir.
Don't know me?
Then let's relive it.
Maybe you'll remember me.
Let go of me.
I already told you I don't know you.
Let go of me!
Liang Jiahao.
Jiahao, save me! Jiahao, save me.
Today, I was able to come here.
You should know what that means.
- Come on.
- Jiahao.
Let her go.
It's you again.
I'll kill you!
You can't kill me. I...
I not only remember you,
but also want to kill you.
Yue!
Mr. Liang.
♪Streetlight falls on the ground♪
♪Your silhouette blurs and fades away♪
♪I am stranded in place♪
♪Love and hate linger on my lips♪
♪Time pushes away♪
♪The distance between us♪
♪Pushes further to the other side♪
♪Until I can no longer see♪
♪Until you can forget♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)