♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how resolute the past♪
♪It was all a fictional plot♪
♪The vow named 'forever' turned into a lie♪
♪Changed long ago with time♪
♪Gradually disintegrated♪
♪When memories are revisited in the deep night♪
♪It feels like we still have everything♪
♪But upon realization♪
♪The story has ended hastily♪
♪Flickering on and off♪
=Chasing Love=
=Episode 22=
Tomorrow is the wedding day.
I will arrange for the Ouyang Mansion
to be renovated.
Whenever you want,
you can come back for a short stay.
Look,
isn't this great?
Just like when we were kids.
It's time to go,
Mr. Jifeng.
Are you really going to marry him?
Why did you come back?
You should leave.
Do you know?
Your acting is not good at all.
♪The streetlight's glow falls on the ground♪
You are his big brother.
We can't do this.
♪I'm stranded in place♪
♪Love and hate linger on my lips♪
♪Time pushes away♪
♪The distance between us♪
♪Is enlarged♪
♪Until I can't see you♪
♪Until you forget♪
♪How many years must pass♪
♪Before this love fades away♪
♪So that when we meet again,
it won't be noticed♪
♪If I weren't afraid♪
♪And didn't retreat♪
♪On the day you left,
I moved forward without hesitation♪
♪Would you have stayed
by my side a little longer♪
♪Forget me a little slower♪
♪But no matter how passionate we were♪
♪No matter how intense the past was♪
♪It was all a fictional story♪
♪The vow of forever turned into a lie♪
♪It changed long ago with time♪
♪Gradually disintegrating♪
♪When the night brings back memories♪
♪It feels like I still have everything♪
♪But when I come to my senses, I realize♪
♪The story ended long after you left♪
All I want is you, my sister-in-law.
Qin Jifeng.
You're still alive.
Liang Jiahao.
Sorry to disappoint you.
It's time to go,
Mr. Jifeng.
Put it down, all of you.
Put it down.
Luckily, I followed you all the way here.
Boss, should we proceed as planned?
Chen Qi,
I'll leave the arsenal to you.
I still have other matters to attend to.
Alright.
After the plan is completed,
leave Hongcheng with the brothers.
Don't come back.
Jiahao.
It's all my fault.
I deceived you.
I beg you.
- I beg you to let him go.
- Yue.
Don't beg him.
Today, I'll make sure you die here.
Mr. Jifeng, there's trouble at the warehouse.
The Governor has taken the men there.
Go to the warehouse.
Take him away for me.
I'll go with him.
Alright.
Take both of them away.
- Yes.
Go.
Get them out!
Move quickly.
As many as you can.
Don't come in.
It's going to explode inside.
Come here.
Marshal, the fire is too big.
We can only save this much.
No matter how big the fire is,
you go in.
Or I'll shoot you dead.
Marshal,
this place is full of ammunition.
It could explode at any time.
We should leave first.
You get in there now!
Anyone who retreats
will be shot.
Yes.
Quick.
When I find out who set the fire,
I'll skin him alive.
Dad,
it's okay. I brought the man here.
Qin Jifeng was investigating the arsenal
and tried to destroy it
and you too.
Didn't you come back to me
for wealth and honor?
Wealth and honor?
Obtained at the expense of innocent lives?
Don't you find it laughable?
But you are my son!
I never considered you my father.
I have no father.
Liang Zongyue,
You killed my mom with your own hands,
smuggled arms,
incited riots and harmed civilians.
Do you think I would collude with you?
Even if your blood runs through my veins,
I am not like you.
Fine.
- Very well.
- Liang Zongyue!
You never lost your memory.
You killed my father.
I can never forgive you.
You should have behaved
and handed over the company to me.
Even if you faked the amnesia,
for the sake of your relationship with Jiahao,
I could have spared you.
But you are just like your father,
headstrong.
Dad.
Take him away.
- Dad, Dad!
- Let's go, Mr. Jiahao.
Don't kill Yue.
- It was you all...
- Dad.
who forced me.
Boss, run quickly.
Hurry.
Brothers, cover the Boss.
Dad, it's going to explode. Let's go
Take Jiahao away.
Quickly.
Yes.
- Dad!
- Mr. Jiahao.
- Go.
Dad!
Quick, let's go.
♪The streetlight's glow falls on the ground♪
♪Your silhouette blurs and fades away♪
♪I'm stranded in place♪
♪Love and hate linger on my lips♪
♪Time pushes away♪
(The exclusive information network
dissemination rights of this work)
(belong to Shenzhen
Tencent Computer Systems Co., Ltd.)