♪My favor for you♪
♪Is an exception♪
♪I willingly love you♪
=Fervent Kiss=
=Episode 11=
Why is it raining?
It's fine, Mr. Kang,
let's go inside and keep drinking.
I can see you are so happy today,
I'll make sure you have enough fun.
Let me tell you,
today,
you'll all have to
get drunk
and stay here.
I'll make arrangements.
Alright, alright.
Come on.
He Can, come.
(Egret Restaurant)
Good morning.
You performed well last night.
You taught me well.
Thank you.
So can you tell me where He Chen is?
The resort project is only halfway done,
it's not finished yet,
why the rush?
Well then,
help me out, my ally.
What do you need?
This Dr. Huang
was the attending doctor for you
after the car accident.
I've noticed something strange about him.
After you and He Chen had the accident,
he mysteriously resigned. Then he suddenly
(Investigation Report: Huang Ren)
disappeared.
I've recently received news that he's back
in the country.
I want you to help me
find him.
I suspect he knows something.
Send it to me, I'll try.
Hmm.
Thanks.
Hanxing.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Good morning, Uncle.
He Can,
I've been meaning to ask you something.
What is it, Uncle?
Have you ever wanted
to become the real He Chen?
My dream has always been violin and Vienna,
you know that, Uncle.
Sometimes, I just want to be myself,
not anyone else.
To remember who you are,
that's great.
You go ahead.
- Hello.
- Mr. Zhong.
How have you been?
It's me.
Huang Ren from St. Cross Hospital
in Los Angeles.
You promised me if I came back,
you'd give me money.
Why aren't you keeping your word?
You wanna deny it?
Then let me give you a little surprise.
The moment he is gone,
the will takes effect.
And you know,
the will clearly states everything is left
to He Chen.
(The school has been exposed.)
(Zhong Sihuai must be prepared.)
(For now,)
(finding the doctor might be easier.)
(Why am I thinking of him?)
(Where is the necklace?)
I'll help you put it on.
Hmm.
♪Please stay with me♪
♪I think I'm falling for you♪
♪You make me want to approach you♪
♪When I approach you♪
♪Even my breath becomes erratic♪
Thank you.
♪I've lost my mind♪
Do you miss me, baby?
Get lost.
Bother me again and I'll teach you a lesson.
I'm not He Can, Shen Weixi.
I'm He Chen.
I heard my boyfriend, He Can,
has become the heir to the Heshi Group.
As his girlfriend, of course,
I'll accompany him through thick and thin.
You've arrived.
Uncle.
Uncle,
you came at the right time.
Help me settle this,
we were in a good relationship in the U.S.,
now that I'm here to reconcile,
he turned his back on me.
Let's go talk in my place.
The accident was arranged by me.
Now, the old man could...
Once he leaves...
Where did you
get this video?
How about your boyfriend?
Correction:
ex-boyfriend, okay?
Why?
Didn't you tell me he was born in a
super wealthy family?
Just drop it.
I found him as poor as a church mouse.
Okay, fine.
It's a gift from God.
Speak up,
what do you want?
I've said it,
I just want to get back with He Can
and marry him.
Alright, I can help you with that.
Wow,
that is easier than I thought.
But,
are you sure you want to marry him
just like that?
Shouldn't you develop feelings first?
Hmm,
you're right, Uncle.
So, what about this video?
As long as I marry He Can,
I'll destroy the video.
Before that,
I won't show it to anyone else,
including He Can.
Don't worry,
my lifelong happiness depends on you.
How could I go back on my word?
May we cooperate well.
(If I use this dumb fool who came to me,)
(the issue about Hanxing and He Can)
(might be resolved smoothly.)
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪Oh, it's you♪
♪Now it's time I realized♪
♪I have to hide the feelings for my love♪
♪Getting rid of the mask chained onto my soul♪
♪But the real me derail what I pretend to be♪
♪Take your cost away, I will come to you♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪I need you♪
♪Sorry for push you away♪
♪Getting your broken side♪
♪Sorry for set you free♪
♪'Cause I had the only way♪
♪Sorry for...♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)