♪My favor for you♪
♪Is an exception♪
♪I willingly love you♪
=Fervent Kiss=
=Episode 8=
Hanxing,
what are you doing in my room?
I...
Did you check my phone?
What do you want to do?
What do you want to know?
Tell me!
I just want to know you better.
We've been together for so long,
and even though you're so gentle with me,
I always feel like I can't see through you.
You said you'd give me a sense of security,
but I feel like I have none at all.
I feel like you're not honest with me.
I haven't been honest with you?
I'll be honest with you now!
I'll give you everything now.
I asked you before
what it means when you come at night.
I won't ask you again.
What happened?
Sorry to interrupt you..
Zhaozhao is a mischievous cat.
He scratched me and ran off.
He even knocked over...
Be careful next time.
Cats are animals, they have
their wild instincts.
Got it,
I won't bother him again.
Go back and get some rest.
(Security Service Contract)
(Party A: Zhong Sihuai)
(Zhong Sihuai rented this place.)
(Medical Employment Agreement)
(And he hired security and medical staff.)
(Lease Contract: Huaihe Vocational Information
Technology School)
(This place is abandoned.)
Who is he hiding?
Could it be...
(He Chen?)
Someone went upstairs.
Quick, go, go, go!
Hey!
He's upstairs, catch him!
Shh.
I hear something.
You two, come with me.
Okay.
Stop! Don't run!
- Don't run!
- Stop right there!
You two go check over there.
Alright, let's go.
Hey,
what are you doing here?
(Sihuai)
(Zhong Sihuai)
Hanxing, are you home?
He's back.
Ms. Zhang.
Yeah, Mr. Zhong.
Is Hanxing at home?
He hasn't returned yet.
- What about He Chen?
- Mr. He is at home.
I think he is in his room.
You snuck out after going home?
How will you get in later?
What, are you worried about me?
I'm not an ungrateful person.
Boss,
two suspicious people came just now.
Did you recognize them?
I sent the surveillance footage to you.
The footage is unclear though.
(This person looks like...)
Hanxing,
where did you go just now?
Why didn't you answer my call?
I went for a spa.
I was so tired I fell asleep.
Next time, please...
I'm too tired.
I can't keep my eyes open now.
I'll go rest now, Sihuai.
Alright, get some rest.
Hmm.
Why don't you check the top floor?
Mr. He likes to take a bath there.
I'll take off my clothes.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I was just worried about you.
What could happen to me?
Do you need help?
No,
I'm just lame.
I can still move.
It's too stuffy here.
Don't stay there for long.
Okay.
You still haven't told me,
why were you there?
Were you following me?
I found out that school might have
Zhong Sihuai's secret.
I need something on him,
just in case.
It's rare that you trust me.
Not exactly,
it's just that you've saved me so many times.
That proves
you and Zhong Sihuai are not the same type
of person.
Although I don't know what your struggles are,
from now on,
you and I
are no longer enemies.
Does this count as
an alliance?
Yes.
Then thank you, ally.
♪Please stay with me♪
♪I think I'm falling for you♪
I...
I'll head back now.
♪When I approach you♪
(Hanxing,)
(I know you want to find me.)
(But I don't want you to fall into danger.)
(But since I can't stop you,)
(I can only stay by your side)
(and protect you.)
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪Oh, it's you♪
♪Now it's time I realized♪
♪I have to hide the feelings for my love♪
♪Getting rid of the mask chained onto my soul♪
♪But the real me derail what I pretend to be♪
♪Take your cost away, I will come to you♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪I need you♪
♪Sorry for push you away♪
♪Getting your broken side♪
♪Sorry for set you free♪
♪'Cause I had the only way♪
♪Sorry for...♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)