♪My favor for you♪
♪Is an exception♪
♪I willingly love you♪
=Fervent Kiss=
=Episode 2=
Try it!
Why should I listen to a mad dog?
What did you say?
What did you just say to me?
Look at me!
Get your hands off me!
He Can, tell them to let go of me!
What are you doing?
This is the He family,
not a place where you can run wild.
Your stepson, He Can, is in the hospital
receiving post-surgery treatment.
If you want to see him,
wait until he wakes up.
You can't do this to me!
He Can! He Can!
Sorry, everyone.
I'll handle this.
Please continue.
You lied to me!
Mr. Charles,
he really is He Can.
There's no violin mark on him.
But he didn't try to unlock the phone.
Where are you now?
It's all your fault.
It looks like you are really behind
what happened tonight.
Yes.
So what?
How come I never knew
you dance so well?
There are a lot of things
you don't know
about me.
Has Uncle seen you like this?
What?
Jealous?
If he knew you were so distracted
while holding him just now,
do you think he'd go crazy?
Sihuai is very gentle,
the one going crazy
seems to be someone else.
When did you find out
someone was going to test your identity?
From the moment you took my hair.
Now it's my turn to ask.
Why did you suspect
I'm not He Chen?
(DNA Identity Test Report)
(DNA match rate is 100%)
So what?
Is there a problem with the DNA match?
Of course, there's a problem.
Because the hair I sent for comparison
was mine.
Your assistant is too stupid.
He just swapped the documents
without knowing anything.
If you hadn't been afraid,
would you have done this?
When did you start suspecting I'm not He Chen?
The moment He Chen told me we were breaking up.
(Santa Barbara, America)
He Chen!
What happened?
Why are you in a wheelchair?
An accident happened,
and it ended up like this.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
You'll get better.
I'll always be with you.
If you want to go to Paris for treatment,
I'll go with you.
Let's break up.
What?
I don't love you anymore.
I don't believe it.
He Chen!
You didn't believe
I'd be so cold to tell you we're breaking up?
You don't want to give up?
No, I don't.
I met Charles at the hospital,
he said you're He Can.
He's mistaken.
Then where's He Chen's red bracelet?
He's never taken it off.
You suspect me
just for an bracelet?
He Can,
where is He Chen?
Right in front of you.
Who says I'm not He Chen?
Charles,
or your baseless DNA report?
Or,
is it the scar from appendectomy
you've been trying to see
in my room?
It's just a scar.
It's easy to fake.
The key is, are you satisfied with the result?
Do you want it to be there,
or not?
Get lost!
I'll do everything I can
to destroy your disguise.
Hanxing,
I've ordered a custom wedding dress in Paris.
Next week we can fly over and try it on,
then pick a good day
to get married.
Sihuai,
you know Xinglan was left to me by my mother,
it's very important to me.
So I want to wait...
Are you still unable to forget him?
No, I…
It's fine,
I can wait.
It was He Chen who dumped me.
From the moment he did that,
this relationship was over.
Now,
we must look forward,
and continue living.
Okay.
You are right.
First, we'll solve the issue with Xinglan.
Hey,
I want a lot of flowers at the wedding.
Anything you say.
How is He Can now?
Wasn't he in the accident with He Chen?
He's
still unconscious,
recovering abroad.
Oh.
Which hospital?
Should we go visit him?
I haven't met him yet.
He Can's father never liked him
before he fell ill.
Given the current situation, it's not
appropriate for us to visit him.
Let's do it later.
Hey,
what happened with that
troublemaking foreigner?
How did you settle it?
Thank you for taking care of He Can
all these years.
You,
you know I've been taking care of him.
I know exactly how you've taken care of him.
Leave!
I won't leave.
He is my son, He Can.
Please believe me.
You've all been fooled by him.
If one more person knows this secret,
I'll send someone
to take care of you,
just like you've taken care of He Can.
Leave this country!
I gave him some money to send him away.
I see.
(Charles didn't expose He Can,)
(and Zhong Sihuai refuses to disclose
the hospital address.)
(He Chen,)
(how should I find you?)
Are you the relative the we called just now?
Yes, I am.
We need you to identify them
and do the registration.
Who is the right one?
The moment he is gone,
the will takes effect.
You're Heshi Group's lawyer, so you know,
the will clearly states everything is left
to He Chen.
Then what chance do I have?
I have to think of something soon.
You don't need to worry about the rest.
I'll arrange it.
What are you planning?
Let He Chen go back safely.
How is that possible?
He's seriously injured,
won't wake up in a short time.
And I don't understand,
whether he wakes up or not,
whether he goes back or not,
the will will still take effect.
How can that work?
If the real He Chen goes back, of course
it won't work.
What about a fake one?
You mean
He Can?
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪Oh, it's you♪
♪Now it's time I realized♪
♪I have to hide the feelings for my love♪
♪Getting rid of the mask chained onto my soul♪
♪But the real me derail what I pretend to be♪
♪Take your cost away, I will come to you♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪When your eyes on me, red burst the rim♪
♪I know that you're my destiny♪
♪My fervent kiss to my fervent love♪
♪Going through the mist, I believe
I've seen that love from you♪
♪I need you♪
♪Sorry for push you away♪
♪Getting your broken side♪
♪Sorry for set you free♪
♪'Cause I had the only way♪
♪Sorry for...♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)