Hello, guys!
It's our first day and
here are the cleaners.
Hello!
Say hello to the camera!
See, you guys are
great at cleaning.
Oh, Felice!
What’s going on?
My pouch is missing
and my money’s in there.
Oh, no!
Maybe it was stolen by…
What's wrong with you?
It's not funny.
What’s her problem?
They're cleaning right now.
[students screaming]
Wah!
Bet you were scared.
Come on.
What?
I'm vlogging and-
- You're crazy, Santiago.
- So what?
- You all are losers.
-There.
And there.
And then...
[students screaming]
I’m not used to Moma not
being the first one I hear
waking me up on the first day of
my last year as a high school student.
Oh no! I think I fell
asleep in my uniform.
I think I really need
to clean my room.
Mom?
Moma?
Ah...
Mom must have left at dawn
to sell her yema and rice cakes.
I've had so many first days
in junior high already.
But I don't know,
I still get nervous.
MOANA "THIEF"
This is so annoying,
they still won't leave me alone.
Oh!
I thought you were brave!
You're such a jerk.
- Let's go.
- Should we go back to the classroom?
Oh, look, it’s Felice.
She’s probably coming from early morning
practice again with the school band.
She’s so beautiful.
Being a majorette
really suits Felice.
I would also like to
join our school band.
Not as a majorette, though.
Since I’m not as beautiful
or as sexy as Felice.
What I really want
is to be a lyrist.
But Moma is against it
she says it’s just
a waste of money.
What’s happening to her?
Should I go over there?
Felice.
- Did you do your homework?
- Are you done with yours?
- No we didn't.
- Not yet but we'll do it later.
I'm sorry guys but im done with mine,
you should finish yours too.
Oh, it's just the wind.
Felice!
Let’s sit together.
Felice, come here!
Are we having an acitivity?
I don’t know.
Good morning, class.
Good morning, Sir Win.
I'm sorry, class.
There was an accident.
On the way here
someone got hit.
Did the person die, Sir Win?
I think so.
Sadly, she was on her phone
when the accident happened.
So, everyone, please,
when crossing the road
This is just a reminder, okay?
But it’s super effective always.
When crossing the road,
look to your left…
Look to your right.
Very nice, good.
You know what, class
Science tells us that the very last sense
that stops functioning before we die
is the sense of hearing.
Whoever it is that
she was talking to
I hope it was someone she loves.
And the last word she heard,
I hope they were kind.
Right.
Alright, um…
Later we'll have an activity.
This is just a review from
last year's lessons.
Alright?
[knocking]
Hello, everyone.
I am Cadet Officer Dylan Gallego.
And I just want
to remind you guys
that we have an anti-bullying seminar
happening in 10 minutes.
Attendance is a must.
Okay, you may go.
Sir, can I be excused?
I already attended
the same seminar
as part of our training
for the school band.
Maybe I can use the time
to rest for the meantime.
Alright.
You can rest here, Felice.
Thank you.
Hey, Naomi.
What are you doing?
No wonder things are
going missing around here.
You’re a thief!
Where have you been?
How snobbish.
What is happening?
It's our first day and
here are the cleaners.
It was just here.
Where is it?
Hi cleaners! Go ahead and clean.
Oh, Felice!
What’s going on?
My pouch is missing
and my money’s in there.
Felice! It was Naomi!
Naomi stole your pouch!
Oh my!
Maybe it was stolen by…
What's wrong with you?
That's not funny.
There you go,
we're tidying up  first–
What’s her problem?
I think she's upset.
Such an attention seeker.
[students screaming]
- Waah!
- Felice, it was Naomi!
Are you mad?
Did I do something wrong?
Felice, why aren’t
you listening to me?
Felice!
[screaming continues]
Why are they mean to me?
Who’s that?
Are you okay?
I've been trying to talk to you,
but you were ignoring me.
And now you suddenly
want to talk?
Oh, it's just the wind.
Felice!
Let’s sit together.
You’re a thief.
Where have you been?
No!
No.
This isn’t real.
Moma, you totally startled me!
Hey, you're the one
who startled me!
Why did you wake up so early?
Of course, we now have
a beauty routine, Moma.
You know, my pretty classmates
at school use that.
Look at my skin, Moma.
- It’s glowing now.
- Let me look.
Oh, wow. You’re right!
Why is my daughter suddenly
so motivated to look pretty?
Well, that's just how it is.
I’m all grown up now.
I guess this means
you won't want to come
with me to our spot
at the market anymore.
So what’s going to happen
to our yema and rice cakes?
That's not going to happen.
That’s exactly why
I use White Rose Papaya.
So even if I’m out in the sun or sweating,
my skin still stays glowing.
You're definitely the prettiest
girl in your school.
You take after me, after all.
This isn’t real.
Moana.
Was that you I felt earlier?
Yes.
Yes, Felice.
That was me.
I’m here, Felice.
I really hope it was you.
Because I really need a friend now.
- Bye, you guys take care.
- Bye, Moana.
Bye!
What a day!
Are we going to commute?
So dramatic.
Oh, I’m sorry!
Give me your hand.
Sit down.
This is what my mom does to me
whenever I get panic attacks.
Are you feeling better now?
I’m okay now.
You must be really tired.
You just came from practice,
didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Sir Jonas is merciless.
Did you know?
My arms are like Jello from
twirling that baton all day.
I’m so tired, friend.
What’s that?
Yema candy.
It’s for you.
To give you an energy boost.
Here.
Don’t worry.
My mom used healthy sugar,
so it’s not fattening.
That exists?
Just believe me.
Alright, if you say so.
It’s good, right?
You know,
Moma’s hands look
like Christmas lights now
with all the wrapping
she does with those yemas.
You’re so crazy.
It’s true.
The color from the cellophane
has already stained her fingers.
But that doesn’t mean
Moma doesn’t wash her hands.
- For sure.
- Her yema is clean.
It’s just the color from the wrappers
that got on her hands.
Yeah, for sure.
Your mom really loves you,
doesn’t she?
She really does.
We’re a team.
We’re Moma and Momay.
Oh, Moma.
Monica Marie.
That’s her name.
Momay is short for Moana Marie.
That’s why I call
her Moma—it just fits.
You know, I love her so much,
even if she is a total killjoy.
Killjoy?
Yeah.
She doesn’t want me
to join the marching band.
She says it’s just
a waste of money
So you want to
be a majorette too?
Then we’d both have aching arms.
Crazy.
I want to be a lyrist.
I’m not as pretty as you.
You’re pretty, too.
Thank you.
So, yeah.
You can call me Momay ‘cause
Moana Marie’s too long.
Or you can call me
Moana thief.
Crazy!
Because that’s what
our classmates call me.
They’re calling me a klepto.
And apparently,
I’m being blamed for all
the recent thefts in our class.
I don’t believe that.
- Why?
- I just know.
Also, this is just between us,
Even if we don’t
talk all the time,
I feel so at ease with you.
I just know, deep down,
that you're someone I can count on.
So there’s no need to overthink.
Not everyone believes in rumors.
Oh, wow.
You’re being so dramatic.
Come on, let’s go home.
Moana.
Moana!
I’m so sorry, Momay.
Don't worry,
I’ll always visit your mom
in the hospital.
Hospital?
What happened to Moma?
I’m so so sorry.
Felice.
Are you avoiding me?
Of course not!
Why are you being so dramatic?
What’s your problem?
Seriously?
Why are you avoiding me, Felice?
Dylan, stop it.
You’re hurting me.
Hey, don't you dare touch Felice!
Sorry.
Come in.
I am so sorry.
I think I interrupted your practice.
Don’t worry,
I wasn’t practicing.
I’m not part of the marching band.
Sit down.
But you’re actually really good.
I know.
You see,
I can see and hear
every single note.
I guess that’s why playing any
instrument comes so easily to me.
Oh, so you’re a musician?
Actually, no.
I’m a cadet.
I’m here because
I’m waiting for my girlfriend.
She’s a majorette.
She’s very lucky, then.
I know.
It’s also my dream to be part of
the marching band as a lyrist.
But Moma is against it.
She says it’s just
a waste of money.
You know what,
you shouldn’t listen to your mom.
Because for me,
it’s just a waste of time.
Everything that they say or do
is just a reflection of their insecurities.
I don’t think it’s like that.
Trust me, that's how it is.
Is your mom against you
focusing on music, too?
To be honest,
I wouldn’t know.
Because I was young
when she left us.
Oh...
I’m sorry to hear that.
That’s why I didn’t pursue music.
It was because of her.
Is that why you just want
to join the military instead?
Exactly.
Do you want me to teach you?
Really?
Yes, I will teach you. Here.
Right now?
Of course, right now.
When else would it be?
This is just simple.
Here.
But it's already late.
Maybe we can
just do it next time?
You know what,
time is gold.
There might not be a next time.
Or maybe…
You'll be the one
who's gone by then.
I really can't.
Moma will get really mad at me.
Didn't I tell you?
Stop listening to your mother.
Because she doesn't want you
to achieve what she never could.
Moma is not like that.
You listen to me.
So, you’re going
to listen to me now?
Sit down.
Help me!
Don't make this difficult!
I’m begging you...
please don't.
Please, don’t.
I’m begging you...
please don't.
Goddammit!
I’m done with this world.
I’m sorry for everything.
Please stay calm, Felice.
Don’t worry, I won't let
anything happen to you.
Felice.
Felice, he’s gone.
I’m in Felice’s body.
Mom.
I’m sorry, mom.
I’m sorry.
This is not your fault, Moma.
Because I know now.
I know I didn’t kill myself.
I could never do that to you.
Because more than anything,
I can't bear to hurt you.
I can't leave you alone.
Don't let go. Just hold on, Moma.
I won't stop until
I get justice for myself.
I’m getting my revenge.
I will get justice for you, Moma.
I will find justice for myself.
I’m going to do exactly
what he did to me.
I’ll kill him in the very spot
where he killed me.
That’s a promise.
I just want you to live, Mom.
Happy.
Without carrying heavy burdens.
[phone chimes]
Where are you?
Let’s talk.
You know how an AI video
can ruin someone’s reputation.
Meet me,
or I’ll start spreading it.
Meet me at school.
Wait for me.
Does this sound familiar to you, Gallego?
Felice, about a while ago.
I’m sorry.
Did you feel even a
shred of pity for your victim?
Dammit, Felice!
What the hell are you talking about?
You’ve been acting
like this all day.
I know you did it, you monster!
You did all of this on purpose.
You faked that suicide note.
You even made sure
I was the one who came here,
so that I’d be the one
to discover her body.
You planned every single bit of it.
Now tell me,
did you ever feel sorry for me?
Do you want to know the truth?
No.
I don't feel any pity.
You want to know who I pity?
I pity myself, Felice.
Because I’m going
to end up behind bars.
Look at me—
I’m Dylan fucking Gallego.
And I’m going to jail
because of one little problem.
One mistake.
I am the future General
of the Philippines.
And if I wanted to be,
the future President.
And I’m supposed
to just go to jail?
So much potential wasted in this world
because of one stupid mistake.
I won't let my life be destroyed.
I will not let one mistake derail my life.
That wasn't just
a simple mistake.
You killed...
You killed her.
- I accidentally killed her.
- You killed her.
Okay, fine. I killed her.
But let me ask you this
Do you even remember her name?
Did you even consider her a friend?
Exactly my point.
She’s a nobody, Felice.
She will be easily forgotten.
An invisible girl.
Thank you for understanding, babe.
I knew you’d understand me.
I know whatever happens,
you’ll support me.
Momay.
Huh?
My name is Moana Marie.
What?
No, Momay!
Momay, don’t do it.
I heard you earlier.
You mentioned killing
the person who killed you.
In the same place you were killed.
Here.
I know it was you who spoke to me
when I wanted to let go
You told me to keep fighting.
That’s why I knew
I had to wake up and live.
But he has to pay, Moma.
He stole my life and dreams for us.
But you don’t have to do
to him what he did to you.
I know you’re a good person.
Because you’re my daughter.
I raised you.
And in the end,
what’s important
is how you lived,
not how you died.
I’m sorry, Moma.
I should be the one
apologizing to you, Momay.
Because I believed you were
capable of hurting yourself.
You didn’t do anything wrong, Mom.
I love you so much, Momay.
My only wish as your mom
is for you to rest in peace.
I love you too, Mom.
I’m happy, Mom, that in this life,
your voice is the first
and last I’ll ever hear.
Hi, Felice.
Everything’s a blur about
what happened that night.
But I was left with evidence.
You killed her.
Okay, fine. I killed her.
Proof of what truly happened.
Don’t worry, Momay.
I’ll take care of your mom.
I won’t abandon her.
Finally.
I can say my heart is at peace.
Everything's going to be alright.
Thanks to Felice,
my name was cleared
about the stealing allegations.
Naomi was given a sanction.
Now everyone knows I didn't commit suicide.
I'm a victim.
The true monster is Dylan Gallego.
Even if I didn't kill him,
he still ended up in prison
and will be held accountable by the law.
And now I know that
even when I’m gone,
there will still be someone to
love the people I left behind.
That is enough for me to say
that I am ready to let go.