♪Hi, waiting a thousand years away♪
♪Taking the star as you♪
♪I told it many of my secrets♪
♪Hi, can't wait to confess♪
♪Now we see each other again♪
♪How about we stick together longer♪
♪Hey, how are you doing lately♪
♪Feels like the world is insane♪
♪I'm thinking if you'd think of me♪
♪I'm not so sure and it stresses me♪
♪Hey, no more waiting♪
♪Cuz I miss you crazily♪
♪On a time machine,
I'll travel through stars♪
♪The trip may be risky but I don't care♪
♪Hi, can't wait to confess♪
♪Now we see each other again♪
♪How about we stick together longer♪
=Fall in Love Stockade=
=Episode 2=
Looks like she's all right.
Glad to hear that.
Who are you?
What's the password?
I'm the Chief of Yunlu Abode.
But unfortunately,
I was kidnapped here.
Fine, fine.
Anything you want,
I'm ready.
I don't have time for your silly words.
You trespassed on my place.
For this alone,
you may be imprisoned or detained
for up to three years.
You better tell me the password.
What?
Say it again.
Hey, let me do it.
Hello, ma'am.
We're with Shashi Law Firm.
We deal with bad guys for people.
I have something to ask you
and hope you can answer honestly.
Deal with bad guys
for people?
Defendant,
you trespassed on someone else's place.
You may be imprisoned or detained
for up to three years.
You better confess.
All right, I'll confess.
(Defendant, Plaintiff)
Who are you playing, Old Chief?
I'm personifying justice.
To deal with bad guys for people.
Just like a local lawyer.
Oh, I get it!
You're a lawyer.
You should have told me.
(What's she doing?)
(Playing dumb.)
You!
In broad daylight,
how dare you strip me?
I'll fight you!
We didn't.
Hey, calm down, ma'am.
What are you doing? Stop!
Watch out!
Freeze, everybody!
(Just now...)
I'm the Chief of Yunlu Abode.
(She called herself Chief.)
Chief,
I have something to tell you.
Don't be dramatic!
Oh, OK.
Chief, my female disciple
changed your clothes.
I'm a great doctor here,
descendant of Hua Tuo.
[*Great doctor in ancient China]
All right.
I always respect doctors.
Greetings.
Thank you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
Sorry for being rude.
I'm sorry, too.
Sorry for that.
It's OK.
And those two guys...
I have something to tell them.
Chief, you stay for some rest.
All right.
Go.
Oh, it's extendable.
She's suffering from
short-term memory loss.
What do we do?
Take her where she lost her memories
to stimulate her cerebral nerves.
It may work.
(Outpatient)
Are you really a lawyer?
And the other man...
Is he a lawyer, too?
Didn't the doctor just confirm that?
(Oh, my God.)
(It's exactly like what Old Chief described.)
Get in the car.
What?
Why are you pulling me?
Let me go!
Old Chief,
what are you drawing?
It's a car.
Just like our carriages,
it's a kind of vehicle.
Car?
That car looks bigger
than yours.
It looks more rugged, too.
So, you can't be very rich.
Mm.
(I'll hold my anger.)
(So, this is the other world
Old Chief talked about.)
Buckle up.
This is ridiculous.
I don't think I can't sit tight.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Lin Wanwan, what are you doing?
What's wrong?
Don't throw up in my car.
I won't throw up.
Don't throw up in my car!
I won't...
♪Time was a scale but later measured♪
♪Waiting seemed out of place♪
♪I couldn't say how much I missed you♪
♪Old memories would tell that though♪
♪I meant to ask if you♪
♪remembered the alarm code♪
♪I wished to see you as the door opened♪
♪So, I didn't♪
♪change any furnishings♪
♪Were you back, you'd be more adaptable♪
♪There must be some way to find you♪
♪Risky trips wouldn't scare me though♪
♪Through a time warp and black hole♪
♪I saw you ring my doorbell, tinkle♪
♪I reached out♪
♪to fiddle with timelines♪
♪Such signals were just for us♪
♪Years later, we met again♪
♪at the corner as the rain was over♪
♪Finally, we saw the tender rainbow♪
♪Through loneliness and relaxation♪
♪Like the wind up in the sky♪
♪I'd protect you♪
♪where I wasn't there♪
♪I reached out♪
♪to fiddle with timelines♪
♪Such signals were just for us♪
♪Years later, we met again♪
♪at the corner as the rain was over♪
♪Lucky for us to see the tender rainbow♪
(The right of network communication)
(exclusively belongs to Tencent)