Wen
Zhan'er
My war son
war
brother
How can you bear to leave us?
You are the invincible big brother
Didn't you and I, brothers, have an agreement?
So many big things at home are undecided
We agreed to work together to revive the Lu family
After you leave
You let your brother live in this world
What should I do from now on?
The sky has no eyes
Father
So far
Sorry
You and your brother should have worked together.
advance and retreat together
But what about you?
Why did you let your brother go to suppress the bandits alone?
Don't think I don't know
You were deliberately provoking me before
Otherwise Zhan'er
How could he go there in person with his identity?
I was going to be with my brother
Dao went to hunt down the evil thief
But brother doesn’t trust me
Not only did it hurt my arm
And they forced me to stay in the house
Father
I am also your biological son
from now on
You only have one son: me.
finally arrived
Let's go first tonight
An inn run by bad guys
have a night's rest
I listen to you
Lao Bai
This life is too short
Can't you adjust what people drink?
drank it
Your life will no longer be miserable
Don't drink
This girl feeds me wine for fun
You grown man feed me medicine
It's life-saving
Just drink it
I don’t feel at ease if you hold it
This thing is really not for people to drink.
I know there's something
Better than this medicine
Just one sip will make me feel good all over
I have plenty of wine
But you have to drink the medicine first
I'll do it myself
It's getting cold
It's time to put on more clothes
I'll ask the shopkeeper here
I went to buy you some new clothes.
Will be able to put it on soon
No need to waste it
perhaps
I can't survive the next winter either
Don't talk nonsense
I'd better do it
What about warming wine?
I'm better at
You used to warm the wine for me
I'll do it later
It's New Year's Eve soon
It's a day of reunion
yes
before leaving
I promised Medicine Jar and Ronger
I want to take you back for reunion
Laozi
This time we are in a life and death situation
Are you still thinking about going back?
Is it true that you risk your life to join the game?
but hope
Not false either
I have promised Ronger
It must be done
Although I can't go back
But you must live well
Juan Huifan Hanling
sensitive
Ze
Qikai
Ning Junjiebo