Wen
Jianghu
Ume Musume's life
There are some things I dare not say to you
Now she is gone
I want to ask a question for her
you to her
Have you ever been tempted for a moment?
Don't dare to have
People in Jianghu
Can't help myself
Life is like duckweed
Not worth trusting
Then do you know
she has been
Ji Niang is the most important relative in my life
I swear an oath here
Even if the body is broken into pieces
It is necessary to kill the real force behind Lingui Pavilion
Fight to the death
Lin ghost haunts
Not a blade of grass grows
The person who wants to kill
Cutting off the roots
I have only been in seclusion for seven days
They actually
So easily eradicated
What a joke
Who is the strongest Deadpool?
Simply vulnerable
your vision
Really
Every year is worse than every year
Pavilion Master
A secret message came from the capital
Ask about the current situation in Dongdu
Do you want to report truthfully?
Verbatim
Report truthfully
But
Lingui Pavilion is now destroyed
Are you afraid of his anger?
Even the remaining subordinates cannot escape punishment.
yes
This is too ugly
That old man
Will be very angry
But what to do
I just want to make him even more angry
I just want to see him get even more angry
Not as good as
Even the remaining
Let’s cut the grass and root it out too.
Jianghu
I'm in Yunzhou
Wait for you
It's time for you to go
Ten days passed in the blink of an eye
Lao Bai
You are finally willing to speak
The medicine jar is already being explored
The real master of Lingui Pavilion
Once there is news
I will set off
kill
I can't miss this excitement
Very dangerous
Not easy to deal with either
Heaven and earth, knife mountain and sea of ​​fire
As long as Lao Bai's heart desires
I, Ayu, sacrifice my life to accompany you
always wanted to ask you
Why are you always playing music?
Want to learn
I'll teach you
Not interested in learning
I just suddenly want to listen to a song
My mother is the daughter of a musician
Extremely talented
Just because I am a lowly person
Experienced too many ups and downs and misfortunes
So I learn music
Not for the sake of being arty
but to remind
I want to remember my mother’s appearance
good wine
good scene
Best to talk about killing
I don’t know the future
Is there any chance to come back here again?
Enjoy this beautiful scenery
Don't talk nonsense
i know very well
My own death is coming
Don’t talk about death
I'm not afraid of death
but before death
I must let the people from Lingui Pavilion
pay the price
Who are you taking revenge for?
For Ji Niang
Still the Ronger family
Or
yourself
is it important
Jianghu
If one day you know
It was I who killed your witness Han Yang
You lost everything
you
Will you hate me?
Uncle Medicine Jar is back
night rain
Take a look
These
But it’s all Jiang Shuai who gave me enough money.
Let me buy it
Didn't you say that before?
Does he owe you a nice meal?
Today we are all alive
A lot of delicious food
Ronger is getting ready for dinner
good
Walk
Just remember
Juan Huifan
Liu Li Cao Zhang Sun
Taoning's army draws waves
Ling Chen Shunwei