Henghu
Didn't say that
You and I join hands
two masters
so exciting
There are bugs in his body
let me
are you okay
fine
Uncle Jiang and Brother Yeyu
Why haven't they come back yet?
Uncle Gong
Brother Ye Yu
Ronger
Uncle Jiang, you are finally back
Uncle Jiang
What’s wrong with you
Advanced room
Uncle Jiang, are you okay?
Come
I just lost my parents
I can't lose you again
brother brother
Uncle Jiang, is he okay?
How can I help?
Ronger
Go and get the medicine box for me
Brother, Uncle Jiang, is he okay?
Ronger, please go out first
Uncle Jiang will be fine
All right
What have you been through these years?
drive drive drive
drive
Who is pretending to be a ghost?
Get out of here
Jianghu
You're not dead
Linyuan four years
General Hu was framed for rebellion
Behead everyone
After you betrayed him
collude with foreign enemies
Attack the border city
Three days of massacre
The city is almost deserted
Every family hangs funeral bells
you can plead guilty
Ridiculous
So what if I don't plead guilty?
kill me
Kill kill kill
I heard you just came back from outside the customs
Were you going to meet someone?
Is to kill
The last person to betray General Hu
My wish is fulfilled
I also ask Mr. Lu to allow me to resign.
Resign
do you still remember
You were implicated in General Hu's case
It’s me who is taking care of things up and down in the court hall.
Only to save your life
What I value
It's your invincible martial arts
hope one day
You can be in my hands
The sharpest knife
I also said this when I surrendered to Mr. Lu
As long as Mr. Lu can be preserved
My remaining delinquent brothers
The world is at the mercy of Mr. Lu
If one day I decide to quit
The Lu Mansion will never force him to stay.
I understand the rules of the Lu family
Please also invite Mr. Lu
reward me and leave
According to the rules of Lu Mansion
People who left Lu Mansion
Three yuan Gu insects must be planted
Whenever the energy of alchemy circulates in the body,
Poison will definitely damage the internal organs
Lose his life
Jianghu is willing to accept this three-dimensional Gu insect
Have you thought clearly?
Once the poison is taken
You will never lose your inner strength
You are really willing
The best martial arts in the world
Farewell to Jianghu
Meng Cong Ning Jiaqi Min Duan
Dongyuyuweilupu
Yuhao Weidong Yupu
Weiyu Yuhaodong
Sun Xiaohuai, Ning Junjie, Yu Wei Taobo
Xiaowen written by Ling Chenshunwei
Gao Lugou Xing Zhao Gao Feng Ling Chen Shun Wei Xiao V
Hong Sihui Ao Chen Jiu Yao Jiao Xiang Ni Zhen
Xu Zhang, Guo Sunchen, Li Xuejiao, Hong Nisi, Hui Ao Jiuxiang
Xu Zhang Li Xuejiao Si light Xiang