English subtitles are available
Peacock in Wonderland
Episode 23
Qian.
You're still busy at this hour?
Ni.
Why are you here?
I brought you light refreshments made by Uncle Li.
Come. Have a taste.
-Thank you.
-Have a taste.
Qian.
I heard Yu sent someone to deliver Master's Decree today,
but you didn't accept it.
I didn't.
You like her so much.
Why didn't you accept it?
Yu doesn't like me.
It's just my wishful thinking.
She issued Master's Decree.
It means she's willing to marry you.
Besides,
I think
she likes you.
She just hasn't realized it.
You are so nice.
It won't be a problem that your love grows over time.
We've known each other for so many years.
We were together every day.
Love growing over time
is the most useless.
You spent every day together
as friends.
How do you know it won't work this time?
I know
Yu feels guilty towards me.
She doesn't have romantic feelings for me.
That edict
was just to fulfill
her dead mother's last wish.
But I think...
Ni.
If Muyang doesn't have feelings for you,
will you marry him
just because of an edict?
Of course I won't.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have tried to persuade you.
I was being too subjective.
I didn't care about your feelings.
It's okay.
In love,
people should follow their own hearts.
But don't try to persuade me again.
I've made up my mind.
Yu.
What do you think?
The clothes made by you
are all beautiful.
Since childhood,
you've always been the one making clothes for me.
Now,
you even made a wedding dress for me.
Moqian,
I like it very much.
Master,
what brings you here?
This belongs to you.
Why didn't you accept it?
Do you really want to marry me?
I know you have a lot of resentment in your heart.
But you've fulfilled my mother's last wish
by making a wedding dress for me.
How can I ignore her wish?
Moqian.
Du Moqian!
I'm here
to deliver the edict as the master.
I summon Du Moqian, the boss of Yanxia Shop,
to the palace today.
The relevant department should pick an auspicious day for the wedding.
Yes,
Master.
Why did you ask me here?
Kneel.
No.
You broke the rules
by changing the procedures at the ceremony without permission.
You don't admit your mistake?
Master Rong didn't say anything.
Who are you to criticize me?
The rules have remained unchanged
for a century.
You took the belongings of the deceased
to the ceremony.
It was really ominous.
Ominous?
It's called inheritance.
Understand?
So you mean
the late master is ominous?
Are you despising the late master
or the current master who accepted the inheritance?
You...
What do you want?
Stop.
I have something to tell you.
I tolerated you
for the sake of Master Rong.
Now,
I don't want to tolerate you anymore.
I'm going to be frank with you.
If you don't like me,
just confront me directly.
Don't play tricks
behind my back.
Childish.
Think about it.
Hua Ni!
How dare you!
She has Master Rong's support.
Of course she's arrogant.
It was such a good opportunity in Lisha Town.
But she managed to escape.
If we had succeeded,
she wouldn't have had the chance to argue with me here.
I was thoughtless.
I didn't expect
Li Muyang to save her again.
Didn't you say you're not feeling well?
Why are you still here standing in the wind?
The moon is very beautiful tonight.
I don't want to miss the moonlight.
Although the moon is cold and bright,
it's something in the sky.
We can only look at it from afar
and put our admiration for it in our hearts.
The moonlight is cold.
It has nothing on the warm candlelight in the room.
In the past,
there was moonlight in my heart.
But now it has dimmed.
Moqian,
since I've chosen you,
I will never let you down.
Come with me.
I, Rong Yu,
came with my husband, Moqian,
to visit my late parents today.
In front of your memorial tablets, I swear
in this life,
I will share weal and woe with Moqian
and be with him forever.
I will never let him down in this life.
I'll only accompany him
for the rest of my life.
Ancestors,
I, unfilial Moqian,
married Rong Yu today.
She's the only one I love.
I'll never betray her.
From now on,
I'm your only wife.
You are my only husband.
There will never be anyone else
between you and me.
I trust you.
Li Muyang, Assistant Minister of Rites, you addressed the drought.
So I promote you
to the position of Minister of Rites.
I hope you can encourage yourself more in the future
and serve the city-state well.
Thank you, Master.
Chen Mo, Minister of Revenue, you are talented,
upright, and straightforward.
You've achieved remarkable feats many times.
You're indeed a trustworthy minister of Peacock City-State.
Now I promote you
to the position of Glorious Grand Master.
I hope you can assist me meticulously
and devote your wisdom and loyalty to me in the future.
I will do my best
to assist you loyally.
Also,
Hua Ni, Holy Envoy of Peacock City-State,
you always care about the people
and have prayed for blessings for them.
So you are rewarded with nine pieces of silk fabrics
and a pair of phoenix hairpins.
Thank you, Master.
-Master, you're wise.
Master, you're wise.
Guanbuzhu
Muyang.
-You've been an official for years.
-Come and eat.
You've been doing your best for the city-state and the people.
Your promotion today
is a great honor to our family.
It's so lively.
Cool Guy.
How have you been?
You've solved Moon Pavilion's problem?
Li's Mansion is indeed magnificent.
Holy Envoy, thank you for your concern.
It was not a big problem.
It was solved long ago.
Maybe someone thinks I'm an eyesore.
So he made things difficult for me for a few days.
But it doesn't matter.
Greetings, Uncle.
Who is he?
He's gone too far.
Jing.
Lord Li, I heard that you got a promotion.
So I came to congratulate you.
I wish you a smooth career
and great success.
Cool Guy, impressive.
You're so generous.
It's real.
Mr. Qing Jian, impressive.
You're really generous.
But I'm an official.
I dare not accept it.
Thank you.
I didn't know you would come here.
I only prepared humble fare.
So I'm not going to ask you to stay for the meal.
I don't think
I said I wanted to stay.
Lord Li, you think too much.
Except congratulating you,
I have another very important thing.
Holy Envoy.
Are you free tomorrow?
I'd like to ask you out.
Ask me out?
You have forgotten?
This makes me sad.
That day in Lisha Town, you promised me
you would buy me a drink.
I still remember it.
But it doesn't matter.
I have a bottle of fine Autumn Dew.
Why don't you come to my Moon Pavilion tomorrow to have a drink?
Sure.
In that case,
I won't disturb you any further.
Holy Envoy.
See you tomorrow.
I'll wait for you.
See you.
Bye.
Moon Pavilion
I don't think I invited Lord Li.
I learned to be an uninvited guest
from Mr. Qing Jian.
He insisted on coming.
I couldn't stop him.
Forget it.
It's livelier with more people around.
Have a seat.
Moon Pavilion
I think
drinking like this
is too boring.
How about... playing a game?
Okay.
As you wish.
The game
is called Truth or Dare.
We take turns to spin the chopstick.
The person who the chopstick points at
should answer a question
asked by the person who spins the chopstick.
This is called Truth.
If that person can't answer it,
drink.
This is called Dare.
What do you think?
Interesting.
What do you think, Lord Li?
Who spins the chopstick first?
Me.
Me?
Fine. Go ahead.
Do you have someone you like?
Cool Guy,
it's your first time playing this game. You're so good at asking questions.
Yes.
Who is he?
Sorry.
This is another question.
Continue. Who's next?
I...
You're quite active.
Me again?
Who do you like?
I... I choose Dare.
Don't compete with me this time.
I'll spin it.
This is weird.
Cool Guy.
Come on, answer my question.
Cool Guy, do you have someone you like?
I like you.
We're out of wine.
W-Where is your wine? I'm going to get it.
Upstairs. Don't take the wrong way.