[English subtitles are available]
[Peacock in Wonderland]
[Episode 10]
What if you have a friend who is a member of Flowers Kill?
Friend?
As the young master of Peacock City-State,
I won't show mercy to any of my enemies.
Even if my friend is a member of Flowers Kill,
I will kill them
and tear their body into pieces.
Oh no.
If they know
I'm also a member of Flowers Kill,
they will definitely kill me.
[Li's Mansion]
Son.
Is there anything bothering you?
No.
Oh, you've grown up.
Now you won't tell me what your trouble is.
Are you really not going to tell me about it?
Come on.
Dr. Sun, who treated you last time,
told me about your trouble
when he came to buy flowers at Guanbuzhu.
What did he tell you?
As the poem goes, "The youth yearns day and night.
For the maiden so fair.
His yearning grows so strong.
He cannot fall asleep.
But tosses all night long.
So deep in love, so deep!"
Is that girl the Holy Envoy?
No.
Then who is it?
Muyang.
You should never
hurt Holy Envoy's feelings.
Father.
Stop talking nonsense, okay?
Then...
Who was the girl in your dreams?
I don't care
who the girl was in your dreams.
Just forget the girl in your dreams.
No wonder the Holy Envoy hasn't come to our home lately.
Turns out, you've fallen in love with another girl.
Forget her?
How?
It's easy.
Well...
The best way to forget a girl
is to stay far away from her.
As far as possible.
As time goes by,
no matter how many lovers you have,
you'll forget them all.
I can try this method.
Lord Li.
Lord Li. Lord Li.
Li.
Li Muyang.
Hello, Holy Envoy.
We're in public. What are you doing?
Lord Li.
I want to quit.
I want to quit Flowers Kill.
Look.
I didn't join it voluntarily.
Just let me quit.
If you do, I won't embarrass you anymore.
I'll listen to you, okay?
Look.
Actually, I think...
Holy Envoy.
It's improper for a man and a woman to be too close.
I'm on an errand.
See you.
Wait, Lord Li.
I...
Li Muyang
is such a jerk.
Let's wait and see.
[Guanbuzhu]
Father, is everything alright?
Why did you ask me to come back all of a sudden?
Because there's an emergency.
What emergency?
My coming is your emergency.
I know you are very busy.
But you still have some time
to talk to Holy Envoy.
Father.
I have work to do in the Ministry of Rites.
I need to go there right now.
Bye.
Stop!
How dare you!
You think you can disobey me now?
I don't care whether you have to go or not.
Just stay here for 15 minutes.
Have a nice talk with Holy Envoy.
Go, go, go.
Bye.
Lord Li, you're forgetful.
I've said it to you many times.
I want to quit Flowers Kill.
I'm
just an ordinary person.
I really can't take two jobs.
You can rest assured
that as long as you allow me to quit,
I won't tell your secrets to others.
What happened yesterday?
I don't remember any of it.
Gosh.
If you don't trust me,
I can give you a written guarantee.
Please allow me to quit Flowers Kill.
If you don't,
I won’t let you go.
Lord Li, come on.
I'm a good-for-nothing.
It's useless for you to keep me in your organization.
Let's go.
Listen.
It's improper for a man and woman to be too close.
I've said it to you so many times.
If you touch me
in public again,
I'll kill you.
Understand?
Since you want to avoid Holy Envoy,
why not just let her quit?
If you don't,
you'll still see each other all the time.
There are many ways to let her keep your secrets.
You don't have to force her to stay in Flowers Kill.
Besides,
she can't even do manual labor.
She's really a good-for-nothing to us.
If I hope to make the dreams stop bothering me,
I should let her go first.
Yes. If you can't see her, you won't be bothered.
[Guanbuzhu]
Please.
Give me a chance to live.
I'm a good-for-nothing to you.
I'll only hinder
the development of Flowers Kill.
If you want to succeed,
you have to get rid of me.
If you don't agree,
I'll kill myself here.
Are you threatening me?
I'll die sooner or later.
I'd like to die here right now.
Then do it.
I'm really going to kill myself.
I'm waiting for you to do it.
I'm going to break my neck.
It hurts.
You really want to quit Flowers Kill so much?
Okay, now I allow you to quit.
Really? You won't go back on your word?
I never go back on my word.
Okay.
Let's sign an agreement.
What Flowers Kill did and will do has nothing to do with Hua Ni.
From now on,
Flowers Kill and Hua Ni have nothing to do with each other.
The two will go
their separate ways.
I hereby make the statements.
Your turn.
Good.
I'll leave if there's nothing else.
Did you forget something?
Yes.
The Flower Poison.
From now on,
I have nothing to do with Flowers Kill.
Help me get rid of the Flower Poison.
It’s easy to remove the Flower Poison.
Go to the mountain
and find the white jade root.
White jade root?
It's white and chubby.
Just like a radish.
You'll recognize it when you see it.
Soak the white jade root
in water for a week.
And keep drinking the water for a few days.
Then the poison will be removed.
Alright.
Thank you for telling me this.
White jade root.
[Yanxia Shop]
I haven't come to Yanxia Shop for a long time.
I feel everything is still the same.
It's getting cold this autumn.
Let me make a warm coat for you.
Moqian.
Do you have something to tell me?
I...
Well...
Make the coat in my old size.
No need to measure me.
Okay.
Yu, are you worried because of what Flowers Kill did?
Flowers Kill has been causing trouble here for years.
It's not easy to completely destroy them.
Last time, you found where their base was.
Have you got any new information?
That night,
someone from Flowers Kill sneaked into my house
and tried to assassinate me.
I led my men to chase him
and found that base of Flower Kill's.
But since then,
I haven't found any of Flowers Kill.
I think
I alerted them.
It's okay.
There will be chances for you to catch them in the future.
Yu.
I remember
your father gave you this jade pendant.
Yes.
My father wanted me
to give it to the man I love.
I should have given it to him long ago.
But I have been too busy recently.
So I haven't got a chance to do it.
If it's not the right time to for you to do it now,
just keep waiting.
You have plenty of time.
You don't have to do it now.
But I've waited many years.
As long as I find the white jade root,
I'll be able to remove the Flower Poison from my body.
Then I'll be free again.
But Mount Yunyin is so big.
How can we find it?
Wait.
The mountain roads are not rough.
Let's split up.
Let's meet at the foot of the mountain in an hour.
Okay.
White jade root.
Where can I find it?
Who is it?
Stop there!
What did you see?
I saw nothing.
You...
Did you see everything?
I...
If you dare to tell anyone that you saw me here,
I'll have your tongue cut off.
I won't tell anyone about it.
The white jade root is white and chubby just like a radish.
Does that kind of thing really exist?
White jade root.
White?
Is this the white jade root?
It's not difficult to find.
I found it so...
Who was so naughty
to cover the hole with leaves?
Where am I?
It didn't rain in Peacock City for a year.
How come it's raining now?
Lai.
Lai, where are you?
Who can come to rescue me?
Lord Li.
Lord Li, rescue me.
It's me!
Why should I rescue you?
We're good friends.
Friends?
I remember
we signed an agreement yesterday.
It says
we'll go our separate ways.
I'm not a kind person.
I can't think of any reason to save you.
Seriously, Li Muyang?
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
Look at me.
You just want to take this opportunity
to force me to go back to Flowers Kill, right?
Did you forget something?
Go to the mountain
and find the white jade root.
Soak it in water
for a week.
and keep drinking the water for a few day.
And the Flower Poison will be removed from your body.
I see.
Li Muyang, no way!
I, Hua Ni, would rather
die here than go back with you.
I'd rather starve to death, freeze to death, and not sleep
than beg you for your help.
Leave.
I don't need your help.
Good for you, Holy Envoy.
You're not afraid of death at all.
I admire you.
Bye.
Are you really leaving?
Li Muyang, help me.
I won't do it again.
I will always be a member of Flowers Kill
and never quit.
Please save me.
Flowers Kill is not where
you can come and go as you wish.
Holy Envoy, you'd better think carefully
before you make the decision.
I've thought it through.
Really.
Come down now.
There is snake trying to bite me.