[English subtitles are available]
[Peacock in Wonderland]
[Episode 21]
I thought about it many times.
Could it be Peacock Sect?
We don't know that yet.
Let's just wait for the result to come out.
Peacock Sect
might not have the guts.
Greetings, Young Master.
Why did you summon me here?
Young Master, what does this mean?
Ruan Jiushu.
Is Peacock Sect
behind Flowers Kill?
Young Master.
Flowers Kill has been preventing my sect from doing the right things
and worshiping the true God.
My sect considers it
as a pain in the ass.
I want to eliminate it very much.
What a good explanation!
Let me ask you.
When the child went missing,
why was there Flowers Kill's mark at the scene?
Do you suspect Flowers Kill has colluded with my sect?
How do you explain this?
Nonsense.
No need to explain.
You just lost your mother.
You're heartbroken.
I also understand how you feel.
But Young Master, think carefully.
It's a century-old tradition to offer a sacrifice and worship the God.
There has never been a flower mark before.
Why would we make an unnecessary move this time?
My sect disdains to work with Flowers Kill,
let alone framing it.
Young Master,
for a century, Peacock City and Peacock Sect
have balanced
and protected each other.
They are in the same boat
and share the same fate.
Now that Master Rong passed away,
you should ascend the throne as soon as possible
to appease the people.
Young Master, you will rule the city-state.
Peacock Sect will help you.
You care about the people.
I'm sure you don't want to spoil the harmony between us.
Young Master,
if there's nothing else,
I'll take my leave.
Young Master,
don't believe her.
Look.
This is the evidence of He Huan's plot against me.
He Huan and I haven't got along well.
But he was released not long ago.
I don't think he has the guts to cause any trouble.
Ruan Jiushu must have instigated him.
Peacock Sect has committed many crimes.
You should be wary of them.
I'm afraid the master's death
also has something to do with them.
Young Master.
I know you were wronged.
But now,
it's not the time to seek justice.
My mother just passed away.
The public sentiment is unstable.
I need the help of Peacock Sect
to become the new master.
Right now,
the most important thing is to appease the people.
Hua Ni,
I will seek justice for you in the future.
But...
Young Master is right.
The priority now
is to have a new master
to take charge of the overall situation.
The Ministry of Rites
and Peacock Sect
should hold the succession ceremony together.
Yes.
[Taining Hall]
The things left by Master Rong are all here.
You may leave.
Yes.
Yu.
When I was little, I heard
people who died
will be reincarnated with burdens.
If he carries too many tears from the mortal world,
he will walk too slowly
and can't find the way to reincarnation.
If Master Rong sees you crying so sadly,
she wouldn't rest in peace.
This teardrop hasn't fallen.
It doesn't count.
Thank you.
Moqian.
Now
is not the time to be sad.
When I was little, my mother told me
no matter what happens,
we should shoulder the responsibility.
[Edict]
Young Master.
I've asked Sanqing Tower to practice divination.
It'll be an auspicious day in seven days.
It's perfect for holding the succession ceremony.
Young Master?
You decide.
Young Master.
I'm here to tell you
that you don't have to take Master Rong's last wish seriously.
Last wish? What last wish?
I found it
from my mother's belongings last night.
I think
my mother wrote it when she was alive.
But before she had time to announce it,
she...
What?
Master Rong bestowed a marriage to Moqian and Young Master Rong?
Mother has never mentioned this to me.
Young Master, you don't need to force yourself.
To me,
whether it's true or not,
it's not as important as your own feelings.
What should we do?
Li, what should we do?
Give me some more time.
Let me think about it.
Muyang.
Come.
Drink with me.
Drinking too much wine is bad for health.
Come.
Just one more cup.
Muyang, let me ask you.
Do you want me to marry Moqian?
Why are you asking me?
You should ask your own heart.
My heart?
Don't you know
my feelings?
Muyang,
we are childhood sweethearts.
We grew up together.
There is no secret between us.
All these years,
liking you has become a habit of mine.
But within just a few days,
my mother left me.
Even we
will have nothing to do with each other in the future.
Why does fate treat me like this?
As your friend and subordinate,
in the future,
I will still be by your side
and do my best to assist you.
But that's all I can do.
Muyang.
For yourself
and the people,
you should look ahead.
Don't be troubled by the past.
You're not even willing to tell me a lie.
You should be in charge
of Young Master's succession ceremony.
You have to do your best.
Don't make any mistake.
Do you understand?
I can do that.
But I...
I know you don't know the etiquette.
So I asked He Huan
to teach you the rules about the ceremony.
Can you ask someone else to teach me, Chief?
I cultivated He Huan myself.
He knows all kinds of rules the best.
He's the most suitable person to teach you.
Chief,
I will complete the task.
You?
Teach me?
What's wrong? Of course I'll teach you.
Since you are the Holy Envoy of our sect,
you should
keep personal grudges separate from this important matter.
Also,
there are many grudges between He Huan and you.
You should take this opportunity to clear up the misunderstandings
and improve the relationship between you.
In the future, you two should
work together
to handle the sect's affairs.
-Yes.
Is this what you want to teach me?
Of course.
The succession ceremony will attract much public attention.
You're always careless
and ill-mannered.
If you lose your manners at the ceremony,
it will be a disgrace to Peacock Sect.
If you don't want to listen to me,
you can report it to Chief.
You...
Stand still for four hours.
Don't move.
I won't stand still with a bowl on my head
for four hours.
You don't want to teach me.
Someone is willing to teach me.
-Where is Lord Li?
-Your Excellency.
Lord Li is over there.
Shouldn't you be learning
the etiquette in Peacock Sect?
What?
Are you slacking off again?
Who is slacking off?
I want to learn earnestly.
But he doesn't want to teach me.
You know what?
Ruan Jiushu asked He Huan to teach me.
What can He Huan teach me?
He just asked me to balance a bowl on my head.
He didn't teach me anything.
He just doesn't want to teach me.
So,
you want me to teach you?
Lord Li,
you are so smart.
You can tell what I'm thinking immediately.
Lord Li, you are knowledgeable.
Can you teach me?
It's not difficult to teach you.
But
you should teach me something in return.
Holy Envoy, why don't you
think about what you can teach me?
Then I will solve your problem.
That's easy.
You've been calculating the items
for the ceremony these days,
right?
You must be deeply troubled.
I have a good idea
that can easily help you calculate
the amount of items needed.
Take this as an example.
If you want to know how many long and short tables
are needed for the officials,
one equation is enough to solve the problem.
We already know
there will be 224 officials.
We need to customize 50 tables in total.
A long table can accommodate six people, and a short table can accommodate four people.
So let's make the number of long tables
A
and the number of short tables B.
So A plus B equals 50.
50 minus A equals B.
So 6A plus 4B
equals 224.
Then let's do reverse deduction.
We can find out that A is 12
and B is 38.
So we know
12 long tables
and 38 short tables are needed.