[English subtitles are available]
[Peacock in Wonderland]
[Episode 39]
Welcome, Chief.
Chief.
Are we really leaving Peacock City?
That announcement has been made.
The reputation of Peacock Sect will be all ruined.
How can Peacock Sect continue to exist in the world?
The Peacock Sect has existed for over a century.
We have never suffered such humiliation.
So many bad things have happened to us.
Our reputation has also been seriously damaged.
That's why I had to make that announcement.
Chief, please lead the disciples
to regain our reputation.
We'll regain our reputation!
Since the founding of the Peacock Sect,
the Peacock Sect and Peacock City-State have been interconnected.
The Peacock Sect is blessed by gods.
Without the Peacock Sect,
Peacock City-State wouldn't have existed.
[Guanbuzhu]
Today is the Lantern Festival.
It's a good day
to bid farewell to the old and welcome the new.
From today,
let bygones be bygones.
Everything will be fine.
Our life will be happy and harmonious.
Cheers.
Okay.
Let's eat.
Let's see who will be lucky
to get the lucky dumplings.
Thank you, my son.
Lai.
You are so lucky.
Make a wish.
I hope Her Ladyship and Lord Li can be a happy couple forever.
I hope everyone here
can be happy and healthy.
Why didn't you make a wish for yourself?
You also got a lucky dumpling.
What wish will you make?
Have son next year!
Do you want to have a son next year?
Take it.
Why?
It's you who are lucky to get it.
Make a wish.
My wish is
that I hope your wish will come true.
I hope...
I hope stability in Peacock City-State
can be restored.
The lives of people here can return to normal.
And
I hope to be with you forever.
Cheers!
Yeah.
Let's drink.
Cheers.
Today is the Lantern Festival.
It is so lively in the city.
What's going on?
Run!
Mother.
Are you abandoning me?
Qiang, guard Li's Mansion.
Okay.
I need to go to Master's Mansion.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Shu Ya?
Qing Jian.
How is it?
Do you like
what I prepared for you?
You killed my mother.
You framed Moqian.
Of course it was me.
You didn't know until now?
You're a fool.
I'll kill you!
If you had chosen to be my puppet forever,
I might keep you alive.
Unfortunately,
you made me have to kill you.
Dream on!
Are you okay, Yu?
Brother.
Why do you always stop me?
Did you cause the explosions in the city?
This is the annual Lantern Festival.
I just set off some firecrackers for the people
to celebrate the festival.
What's wrong with that?
Have you forgotten
that we used to set fireworks together when we were kids?
Today's explosions
are not as splendid as the fireworks we saw back then.
Are you crazy?
They are all living people.
Holy Envoy, you're here too.
Without your formula
for making gunpowder to make bombs to dig wells,
I wouldn't have been able to make explosions in the city.
It's all thanks to you.
This is the gunpowder I've been testing these days.
Can you help me make more gunpowder
according to formula?
Thank you.
Sure.
I'll help you do it.
This is a blessing
Holy Envoy brought for people in the Peacock City-State.
They must accept it.
It's so much gunpowder.
How did you transport it into the city?
Good question.
It's because Peacock Sect helped me a lot.
The Peacock Sect who claims to work for the country and the people
helped me transport the gunpowder.
Chief, bad news!
What happened?
Bombs were exploding all around the city.
Those from Moon Pavilion invaded Master's Mansion.
Got it. You may leave.
To collaborate with me
is the last chance
for Peacock Sect to rise.
The Peacock won't commit such a sin.
Chief, you must be joking.
You want to do good deeds,
but no one appreciates what you did.
Are you really going to
watch Rong Yu
destroy Peacock Sect bit by bit
and do nothing about it?
Chief.
Without Peacock Sect,
Peacock City-State shouldn't continue to exist.
Isn't that ridiculous?
Li Zhiyun.
How could you collude with Peacock Sect?
They took your enemies as your friends.
You have no right to criticize me.
What do you want?
Nothing.
I feel bored.
I just want to be the master of Peacock City-State.
-You...
-Are you
willing to step down and let me the master?
You wish.
My wish will come true even if you don't want it to happen.
Open your eyes and look carefully.
Look.
Listen to their cries.
-I’ll kill you!
-Rong Yu, calm down.
It's finally my turn.
Qing Jian.
Yu, Yu.
Yu.
-We can't stay here any longer!
-Let go of me!
As the master of Peacock City-State，
even if I die here,
I can't let him harm the people!
Yu.
Take her away.
Let's go.
It's an earthquake!
What's going on?
I don't know. Let's go.
Run! Hurry!
Hurry!
Run!
Watch out!
Get out first.
Hurry up. Be careful.
Hurry up!
What a jerk.
How dare you lie to me!
I've imagined this
countless times.
Finally, it's happening.
You said I lied to you.
I just said
without Peacock Sect, Peacock City-State shouldn't continue to exist.
I never said
Peacock Sect should continue to exist.
The Peacock Sect and Moon Pavilion are not enemies.
Why are you doing this?
Shut up!
We are not enemies?
Twenty years ago,
at the Lisha Town...
Lisha Town?
You jerks!
No!
You were a child who escaped from Lisha Town?
You didn't die?
Maybe it was because the Peacock Gods didn't like me.
I used to like a bug in a peacock's mouth
and the peacock could kill me easily.
But now the bug is biting off
the peacock's neck bit by bit.
Isn't it interesting?
Let me ask you.
Now you end up like this.
Do you regret what you did to me?
Do you regret it?
Peacock Gods are my gods.
Their spirit will never disappear.
I uphold truths for them.
I'll never regret it.
Fine.
Then die!
I was born as a servant for Peacock Gods.
After I die, my soul will guard them.
I do my best,
work tirelessly,
and sacrifice everything for my gods.
I devote my whole life to my gods.
I'll never betray my gods.
Never!
Yu.
Kill him!
-Kill him!
-Yu.
Yu.
It's okay.
It's me!
Yu.
Why did you take me away?
I'd rather die
than see my people suffer.
He has become the new ruler of the city...
This not your fault.
Yu, Yu.
-Let go of me!
-Yu.
I know you're anxious.
But Qing Jian has controlled the Peacock City.
You'll only get yourself killed if you go confront him.
Mother once taught me
the master of the Peacock City-State
must protect the people.
As the master of Peacock City-State,
how can I run away like a deserter?
But he has gunpowder.
If you provoke him,
he may bomb the city again and injure more people.
Have you thought about it?
Gunpowder?
You taught him how to make gunpowder.
If you hadn't,
the people of Peacock City wouldn't have suffered.
Step aside!
Rong Yu.
Hua Nie made gunpowder to dig the well to get water
to save the people.
You know that better than anyone.
Qing Jian is the one who bombed the city.
Even without gunpowder,
he would have thousands of other ways to hurt people.
We saved you.
It doesn't mean we would let you abandon the people.
We cannot let you
die for the city easily.
It's easy to die.
Anyone can do it.
But you're not a nobody.
You are the master of Peacock City-State.
Your life is not only yours.
but all the people's.
Only if you live
can the people in the city will have hope.
can we have chances to fight back.
Do you understand?
Fight back?
This is the gunpowder I've been testing these days.
Can you help me make more gunpowder
according to formula?
Thank you.
Sure. I'll help you do it.
Without your formula
for making gunpowder to make bombs to dig wells,
I wouldn't have been able to cause explosions in Peacock City.
You taught him how to make gunpowder.
If you hadn't,
the people of Peacock City wouldn't have suffered.
What are you thinking?
Muyang.
Why did Qing Jian
succeed in becoming the master?
Is it that no matter what we do,
we still won't be able to change what will happen in the end?
You're still with me.
This is a change.
But
nothing else has changed
except this.
Qingqing.
Do you trust me?
I trust you.
But...
If you trust me,
don't be too worried.
Just stay with me, okay?