English subtitles are available
Peacock in Wonderland
Episode 24
A handsome guy said he likes me.
No.
No, no.
Did I hear it wrong?
I definitely heard it wrong.
But...
I'm so distressed.
Holy Envoy, have you found the wine?
Cool Guy, why are you here?
I was worried you couldn't find the way.
I've found the wine.
Let's go downstairs.
Holy Envoy.
I'm sorry that I offended you at the table just now.
My apologies.
But I want you to know
what I said just now
is sincere.
You may not know this.
Since we first met in Moon Pavilion,
I've felt we hit it off.
As I get to know you better,
I'm more attracted to you.
You're knowledgeable,
smart, and cute.
You also care about the world and the people.
I know I don't deserve you.
But I still want a chance.
If I can win your heart,
I promise
I will cherish you.
Cool Guy,
are you drunk?
Do you know what you're talking about?
I know.
I'm begging you.
I'm begging for your love.
I'm drunk. Holy Envoy, take me home.
Let go. You're hurting me.
What are you doing?
If you want to drink wine, go home.
We have plenty of wine at home.
Who are you to me?
Why do you even care
where I drink?
I'm your...
What?
I'm your friend.
I have the responsibility to give you advice.
Friend?
Just friend, right?
Fine.
You are my friend.
Cool Guy is also my friend.
Why can't I drink with him?
Besides, he likes me.
He's not like you.
You're so stubborn.
Leave me alone.
Didn't you say
you don't like him?
Why are you defending him
and siding with him?
I didn't like him. It doesn't mean I don't like him now.
It doesn't mean I won't like him in the future either.
Love grows over time, understand?
Friends can become lovers too.
Right.
He even confessed his love to me.
How do you know I won't say yes?
Lord Li,
don't hinder me from finding my true love.
Li Muyang, what are you doing?
You bastard!
You bastard.
Li's Mansion
My Lord.
It's been two hours.
Why have you remained motionless?
What on earth happened?
My Lord,
where did you go just now?
I forcibly kissed...
You forcibly kissed?
If a woman forcibly kissed me...
Holy Envoy forcibly kissed you?
I didn't say it was her.
I didn't expect Holy Envoy to be so frivolous.
How dare she do that to you!
I'm going to her now.
Sit down.
My Lord,
she must have coveted your beauty
and developed lustful desire.
Then she took advantage of you while she was drunk.
How could you tolerate it?
She didn't drink.
She didn't do it under the influence of alcohol either.
Then she... likes you.
But no matter how much she likes you,
she can't force...
My Lord,
considering your martial arts skills,
I don't think you could possibly be forced.
Alright.
You may leave.
My Lord,
could it be you...
Muyang.
I like it very much.
It's flying so high.
What is this?
This is a love bell.
I tied this love bell for you personally.
It represents my love for you when it rings.
I've liked you for a long time.
I like you too.
Li Muyang
ran away after kissing me yesterday.
Today, he asked me out.
Why did you ask me here?
It's a sunny day.
I asked you here to fly a kite.
Since you're already here,
just fly it for a while.
Holy Envoy.
Lord Li.
It's you. I'm really sorry.
The weather is nice today.
I wanted to shoot a wild goose.
I didn't expect to shoot your kite.
We truly are destined to meet.
Mr. Qing Jian, you really are good at archery.
Autumn Dew we drank yesterday
tastes sweet
and has a strong delayed effect.
When I woke up this morning,
I forgot everything that happened yesterday.
Holy Envoy, I wonder if I talked nonsense
and made a fool of myself in front of you after drinking.
No, no.
You were drunk. It doesn't matter if you don't remember.
Nonsense after drinking?
I think you overstepped the mark after drinking.
I think someone else overstepped the mark.
Anyway, it's my fault.
I'll shoot a wild goose for you
as an apology. What do you think?
Really?
Shooting a wild goose is much more interesting than flying a kite, right?
Interesting.
If you are interested,
why don't you come with me?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Why don't we shoot a wild goose together?
Okay.
I'm not interested.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Your Excellency.
Can we... meet at Mount Yunyin tomorrow?
I have something to do tomorrow. I don't have time.
But I have something important to tell you.
Something important?
What's so mysterious?
Tell me now.
Hua Ni.
I...
Anyway...
I have something important to tell you.
I'll see you at Mount Yunyin tomorrow.
See you there.
What's wrong with him again?
He didn't tell me anything.
The flower tree is like you, and the jade pendant is like me.
From now on,
let's go our separate ways and take care.
Why is there dew on your clothes?
Where did you go just now?
I took a walk around.
It's late.
Go to bed early.
Yu.
We're a couple.
Yes.
We're already a couple.
♫The moon is hazy when the wind passes the court♫
♫How can I dream about the past when it's gone?♫
♫When we parted, I understood♫
♫The deep love hidden in your eyes♫
Why does he have to talk about it in a place like this?
It's weird.
Li Muyang, where are you?
I'll leave if you still don't show up.
I play my zither
to show my feelings.
I hope I can be a good match for you,
so that we can be together hand in hand.
You... prepared this for me?
This song is called "A Phoenix Seeks His Mate".
I'll only play it for you.
What's going on?
Which one is played by Li Muyang?
Li Muyang,
you're fooling me again.
I would become a dog if I talk to you again.
Why does he know how to play the Song of Yarn?
The Song of Yarn was composed by my mother.
Why does he know how to play it?
Brother.
What's wrong?
Hang in there.
We'll be home after crossing that mountain.
But I can't take another step.
I'm so hungry.
You eat first.
My flower.
This...
Father,
please think hard again.
Are you sure
there was no other kid nearby when you found me?
When I found you,
you had wounds all over your body.
That place was surrounded by mountains and forests.
There was no one else as lucky as you.
What a pity.