=Lost You, Found You=
=Episode 15=
These are
all dishes I used to love.
I don't know if the taste has changed.
I'll serve you some rice.
Yuan.
What's wrong, Fei?
Feifei.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You must be hungry.
You didn't eat much last night either.
You eat too.
(She didn't remember.)
It seems
you're not too fond of these dishes.
It's my first time cooking.
Do me a favor.
You eat too.
(I'm sorry.)
The poison of the Carefree Needle is incurable.
Her memory damage is irreversible.
Even if you remove all the needles
from her body,
she may not remember you.
I've never respected gods or feared ghosts,
but this time,
I hope the Buddha blesses me
to achieve my wish.
If my beloved Yuan cannot remember the past,
it might not be such a bad thing.
If that's the case,
I'm willing to use
the remaining days of my life
to ensure she has a life without worries.
Sir, do you ask for fate?
I want to ensure one person's safety.
(Fate)
(Yuan)
(No.)
♪A fleeting moment♪
(From now on,)
(you are just Yun Feifei.)
(No longer burdened by the past.)
(You'll have a bright future.)
♪You see the prosperity in the mortal world♪
♪The wind and rain blur the truth♪
(Yun Feifei)
♪You roam the world during wartime♪
♪The affection in the brows stained with sand♪
♪The most infatuated♪
(Fate, Yun Feifei)
Be gentle with me.
Chu Xin?
Feifei.
He ambushed me on the way here,
so I captured him
to do the chores with you.
Feifei, don't be afraid.
I'll protect you.
We'll defeat this villain together
and escape.
So,
the villain really didn't do anything to you?
Tell me the things
you know about me and him
in details.
At that time,
you were our only head constable
brave enough
to confront the Qian Kun Sect directly.
To uncover Gu Linyuan's true identity,
you took a risk
and set a trap at the Zhulou Music.
A trap?
Is that so?
Feifei, let me tell you.
You were very impressive.
They surrounded us with dozens of people,
but when you unsheathed your sword,
they were scared out of their wits.
Really?
I was very brave back then too.
Seeing my stern expression,
they gave up without even fighting.
When you took out the fire stick,
he didn't expect you
to go all out with him.
He instantly gave up.
What's wrong?
Are you having a headache?
Do you want to go rest over there?
I'll help you close the door.
♪Let longing grow thorns♪
♪Pierce every word♪
♪If my heart isn't here, I'll know♪
♪Never respond to the peach blossoms♪
♪Because of the tangled hair♪
♪Let scars cool the past♪
♪Flowers without love are like duckweed♪
♪To exchange for a word from you♪
♪That's my name♪
♪Your name is my destiny♪
♪No one knows the path of dreams♪
♪The bronze mirror is flawless♪
♪Ink-stained green clothes knot♪
♪Hard to decide♪
♪The wind dances with the snow♪
♪We can only meet♪
♪One last time♪