=Lost You, Found You=
=Episode 2=
(Longfeng Bridal Shop)
Which wedding dress do you think looks best?
Any one will do.
This dress is nice.
I'll take it.
How dare you take my dress?
I'll kill you.
Xiaoyu,
go try on your dress.
- Leave this to me.
- Give it to me.
Alright.
What are you doing here?
Trying on wedding dresses.
Is that a problem?
Linyuan, come in.
Coming.
What do you want?
- Linyuan.
- I'm next door.
Okay.
What are you doing?
My groom has a similar build to you.
Try on the dress for me.
Are you crazy?
Afraid she will hear us?
- What are you doing?
- This is a fitting room.
What's wrong with me trying on a dress?
Shameless.
You like this, don't you?
Before the wedding,
I'm happy to play this game
of old love rekindled.
Linyuan.
What's all that noise?
Did you fall?
Linyuan?
I didn't.
You're not like this
with Du Xiaoyu.
Are you really going to marry her?
Marrying Lady Xiaoyu gives me power and status.
Why not?
Then why are you still wearing
the item I gave you?
You're marrying her
to kill someone,
right?
Leave Heyang City quickly,
or
I don't know what I'll do.
Xiaoyu,
are you done?
This wedding dress is beautiful.
Stop sulking.
You'll have your target
on the wedding day.
Today was supposed to be happy,
but I met a wretch.
Xiaoyu, it's late.
Let's go back.
Why are you wearing a dress like my groom's?
Take it off.
What if I refuse?
Then you'll die.
(Liushan Agency)
You're Yun Feifei?
Yes.
I heard Qian Kun Sect plans
to execute someone on their wedding day.
Well.
I need to investigate it.
Fine.
You won't live to see the results.
Guards.
Surround this shop.
She must die today.
Gu Linyuan, what are you doing?
She's just a small constable.
You don't need to do it yourself.
Hyah!
We're even now. You'll be my enemy next time.
(Trying to trick me into leaving again.)
I won't go. I won't go.
We can never meet again.
I won't.
Go. Go.
Go!
Change your name.
Start over.
I won't.
Take the imperial exam.
Become a female official.
You'll have a bright future.
I won't. I won't.
Go!
Ms. Yun,
I'm ordered to send you to sail away.
It'll be years before you can return.
Qian Kun Sect will never catch you again.
Tell me.
Who is Qian Kun Sect planning
to execute at the wedding?
(Liushan Agency)
Gu Linyuan,
our head constable Yun Feifei is missing.
The Grand Constable wants to question you.
(Chu Xin, Liushan Agency)
Bringing so many people,
are you openly defying us?
Why? You summoned me.
Don't you dare let me in?
(Martyrs List of Honor)
(Grand Constable Yue Tianxing)
(Yue Tianxing,
Liushan Agency's Grand Constable)
Help!
(Martyrs List of Honor,
Grand Constable Yue Tianxing)
How dare you!
♪Let longing grow thorns♪
♪Pierce every word♪
♪If my heart isn't here, I'll know♪
♪Never respond to the peach blossoms♪
♪Because of the tangled hair♪
♪Let scars cool the past♪
♪Flowers without love are like duckweed♪
♪To exchange for a word from you♪
♪That's my name♪
♪Your name is my destiny♪
♪No one knows the path of dreams♪
♪The bronze mirror is flawless♪
♪Ink-stained green clothes knot♪
♪Hard to decide♪
♪The wind dances with the snow♪
♪We can only meet♪
♪One last time♪