(Koi) Huh? What is this?
(Takuya) Here.
(Yosuke) Huh? This guy...
(Kataru) Eh, was that the person Chiharu met at the hotel?
(Yosuke) Chiharu-chan is the one who said she was in sales, right?
(Ko) “Currently working part-time at a bookstore→
It says, "Mr. Sasaki continues to write novels every day."
(Takuya) I also read the same part about 100 times.
But no matter how many times I read it →
It only says that I work part-time at a bookstore.
It doesn't say that I work for some company.
(Yosuke) Haha.
(Yosuke) To be honest, I was in the 1%.
(Takuya) 1%?
(Yosuke) It's the probability that Chiharu-chan is having an affair.
That's what I thought at first.
>>It was surprisingly low.
(Yosuke) I just thought it would be interesting to have an affair→
I didn't think I was actually doing it.
Because he's the one Takuya chose.
But I think I'm doing 99% now.
And when you think about it actually happening, it's not even that interesting.
Even I feel bad.
Ah... the man who had many affairs →
I wonder what you're talking about →
I know this because I have had many affairs!
Adultery is...
No one will be happy except me.
♪～
(Male) Thank you for your hard work. (Chiharu) Thank you for your hard work.
(Female) Thank you for your hard work. (Chiharu) Thank you for your hard work.
(Sasaki) Thank you for just entrusting me with your order.
(Customer) Thank you.
☏(ringtone)
Yes, ABC Shibuya store.
It's me though.
♪～
(Takuya) Um...
(Sudo) Yes.
(Takuya) Is Mr. Sasaki here?
>> Ah, I left early.
(Yosuke) Were you able to escape? (Takuya) No, did he run away?→
I don't know, but apparently he went home because he felt unwell.
>>I mean, I definitely knew Taku-chan was coming.
(Takuya) Yeah, but how?
(Yosuke) Lend me your shoes.
(Takuya) What? (Yosuke) It's okay, just lend it to me.
(Koi) Why shoes?
(Yosuke) My ex-wife once gave me shoes as a gift.
They were pretty nice shoes like this →
I loved it and wore it almost every day.
(Takuya) Is that it? (Yosuke) But from that day→
For some reason, you've started to guess my actions.
(Takuya) Why?
(Yosuke) It was a shoe with a GPS installed in it.
>> Oh no. (Takuya) Scary.
(Yosuke) So this is definitely it. >> Seriously? Seriously?
(Yosuke) Let's go. >> Yeah.
(Yosuke) Huh? This way or this way.
(Yosuke) No.
So, this one or this one?
(Takuya) Oh, stop it! Stop it...
Hey, really, really, please stop.
I bought these for myself because I want nice shoes →
I bought it myself with a bonus.
It's not like I got it from Chiharu.
(Yosuke) What is it? >> Please get me the shoes.
(Takuya) Eh, stop making it seem like it's my fault.
>> But then, how did you know?
(Takuya) Delicious. (Chiharu) Hmm, good.
(Takuya) Today. (Chiharu) Yeah.
(Takuya) I went to the bookstore.
(Chiharu) Hey.
(Takuya) In terms of work, I also study civil law →
I thought I'd study it.
(Chiharu) Hey, that's great.
Which bookstore did you go to?
(Takuya) At Shibuya Station...｡
(Chiharu) Oh, maybe ABC?
(Takuya) Eh, how did you know?
(Chiharu) It's a business location.
Manager Sudo and I were having a meeting at the hotel the other day.
Wasn't Sasaki-kun there?
(Takuya) The store manager was there, but →
I don't understand Sasaki.
(Chiharu) Hmm, I see. Sasaki-kun is a part-time worker.→
I'm good at my job and the store manager has a lot of trust in me.
Just because you are busy, do it for us →
I heard that Sasaki-kun is also responsible for our sales partners.
(Takuya) Seriously, sales... What do you think...｡
Which...
(Takuya) I'm going to the gym again today because I want to feel refreshed.
(Chiharu) I understand.
yeah? (Takuya) Oh no.
Well then, I'll go.
(Chiharu) Welcome.
>> Well then, thank you for your hard work. (Takuya)...
(Yosuke) Good work. (Takuya) Nice to meet you.
(Yosuke) Come to think of it, I didn't ask, but what should we do?
If the affair is confirmed, will we break up? Will you forgive me?
(Takuya) Chiharu told me this before.
"What would you do if I had an affair?"
But me →
I thought Chiharu would never do something like that →
I said something nice, so I guess I'll forgive you.
But I don't know if this actually happens.
I don't even know what to do.
(Yosuke) Well, indecisiveness is your true charm.
(Takuya) What? that.
(Yosuke) It means that no matter what answer you give, I will be on your side.
(Takuya) Yosuke.
(Yosuke) Just go ahead.
(Takuya) Yeah.
♪～
(Sasaki's voice) I'll be waiting forever tomorrow.
(elevator arrival sound)
♪～
(Takuya) Ah... I'm sorry! I'm getting off...
(Takuya) That's right, that's right, damn it!
☏(Ring tone)
(Takuya) Ah, sorry, I forgot that key→
I left the room, but could you please open it for me?
☏(Staff) May I have your room number?
(Takuya) Ah, I don't know which room that is.
☏(Staff) We are very sorry.
☏ We are unable to provide you with your room number.
(Takuya) I made a reservation with either Yoshioka or Sasaki.
☏(Staff) I'm sorry, but I can't tell you this...
(Takuya) Yes, that's right!
♪～
>> It's scary that your whereabouts are being monitored.
(Chiharu) That's right.
>> Well, thanks to that, I can meet you with peace of mind →
I can't say anything.
(Chiharu) But he might be monitoring Sasaki-kun too.
>> That's what I think. (Chiharu) Yeah.
>> I'm Chiharu-san's husband →
Even if my current husband were in my position →
Chiharu-san has no interest in my whereabouts, right?
(Chiharu) Why do you think so?
>> Intuition of a future popular novelist →
Just jealousy.
♪～
(Koi) Taku-chan, are you okay?
Taku-chan, are you okay?
(Yosuke) Huh? >> Taku-chan.
(Yosuke) Huh? >> I wonder if it's okay.
(Yosuke) Ah, it's going to be like that.
>> I guess so.
(Yosuke) I had no idea they were monitoring my whereabouts with this.
>> Is the ability to search for lost items convenient or scary?
(whistle)
(room chime)
(Takuya) I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
(sound of door closing)
(Takuya) It's no longer possible.
♪～
(fire alarm sound)
(Chiharu) Huh? >> What? A fire?
(Chiharu) Hey, clothes, clothes. (Sound of fire alarm)
(fire alarm sound)
(Chiharu) Ah!
♪～
>> Was it you who pressed the alarm? Just check around.
(Female staff) Yes.
(Male staff) Does it look okay? (Female staff) Yes, it looks okay.
Let's go together for a while.
(Takuya) Ah, ah…｡
Ah~! (Female staff) Hey.
(Takuya) Ah!
(Male staff) Security guard Security guard!
(screams)
[I was transferred to the Family Registration Division]
(Chiharu) [Family Registration Division? ]
(Takuya) [What is necessary for a person from birth to death→
A place that handles all kinds of certificates]
(Chiharu) [Wow, that's amazing]
(Takuya) [Even within the city hall, we interact directly with residents →
That's why it's called the face of government.]
[That's why it's often a little difficult.]
But I submitted my own request for transfer]
(Chiharu) [Takuya? Why? ]
(Takuya) [I want to be with Chiharu forever from now on]
(Chiharu) [Huh? ]
(Takuya) [Chiharu gives me stimulation and things like that→
I'm so normal that I can't give you anything.]
[So change yourself even a little →
I wanted to try my best.]
(Takuya) [I want Chiharu to like me more]
[I was able to transfer, so the first thing I did was this→
I was thinking that I would like to accept it.]
(Takuya) 《In times of despair like this→
Why do I remember my happiest times?
[Please marry me]
(Takuya) 《Oh no》
《This is not a happy memory》
[Chiharu? ]
《At that moment, Chiharu stopped for a moment》
``I always thought that was a surprise.''
《Surprise at the sudden proposal》
(Chiharu) [Yes]
(Takuya) 《But I'm sure that was just hesitation》
《Hesitation about marrying me》
[Let's be happy]
(Chiharu) [Yeah]
(Takuya) Will tomorrow morning be the same as usual?
(Chiharu) Huh?
(Takuya) Coffee and bread→
Isn't it okay to have the same fruit and yogurt as usual?
(Chiharu) Takuya? (Takuya) I prefer the same as usual.
Chiharu is good too, right?
(Chiharu) Takuya.
(Takuya) Isn't it okay?
Let's do the same as usual.
(Chiharu) I'm sorry.
(Takuya) Is it no good?
(Takuya) Isn't it okay for Chiharu to stay the same as always?
(Takuya) Hey, wasn't that bad!?
Is it because I’m boring?
Is it more interesting to be with him? Is it fun?
I'm an ordinary person, but I'm warm and calm.
That's why my life with Chiharu is so happy. It's important.
Because I got it myself →
I thought it was something that Chiharu and I made together.
But...
Why would Chiharu take that away?
(Chiharu) I'm sorry. (Takuya) Ah...｡
I don't want you to apologize, I just want to know why.
(Takuya) Is it because he has talent? Because I'm normal →
Did you have an affair with him? (Chiharu) No.
(Takuya) Then why?
(Chiharu) In place of myself who couldn't become an editor →
I certainly wanted to support his dream.
If it wasn't my dream to become a novelist →
I might not have chosen him.
But I've never compared him to Takuya.
(Takuya) Do you think I'll be happy if you say something like that?
(Chiharu) For me, Takuya is the best!
You may not believe it, but it's Takuya.
I also really...
♪～
(Chiharu) What to do depends on Takuya.
(Takuya) Can I ask you one thing?
(Chiharu) What?
(Takuya) When I proposed→
Why did Chiharu hesitate?
♪～
(Koi) Hey, what should we do with this?
(Yosuke) No, I guess I'll have to keep it for a while.
>>My friend said that happiness is faster than a cheetah.
(Yosuke) That's right.
It might run away soon.
(Takuya) [I want Chiharu to like me more]
(Chiharu) 《Takuya smells like the sun》
(Chiharu) 《That's why I hesitated to get married》
《I definitely depend on that sun→
Because I'll break it someday
《So I...》
♪～