(Takuya) Looks like things will go your way.
(Rino) Huh?
(Takuya) Congratulations.
>> But...
(Chiharu) [I want to be able to love only Takuya]
>> [I don't need to be loved, I want to be by your side]
(Chiharu) [Sorry, Rino]
[Say selfish until the end]
♪～
(Chiharu) This is...
(Suzuki) Yube It arrived at my address from an unknown sender.
If this is spread out, you're out.
(Endo) [If you could buy it for me at a higher price than my mother→
I will not tell my mother about these three people.]
(Chiharu) [I don't care if my mother finds out]
[Please go home] >> [No, no... even if you're good →
Everyone else will be in trouble, especially Mr. Sasaki]
[He just won an award, so he's probably a hot stock right now.]
[I think it will be interesting]
(Chiharu) [Do you think that only you can spread the word in this day and age?]
[If I spread your dirty tricks too →
We are no longer open for business, please go home.]
>> [Do you think this is just a threat? ]
(Chiharu) [You're really persistent, please go home now]
>> [Sound of door closing]
♪～
(Yosuke) Why didn't you consult us?
(Takuya) I don't want to cause any more trouble.
(Wataru) Rino Oda was the one who came to the exhibition the other day, right?
(Yosuke) Well, I thought it was weird →
I never expected it to be with Chiharu-chan.
Hmm... (Takuya) Wataru.
(Yosuke) Hey hey hey... hey!
>> I'm drinking for Taku-chan today!
(Yosuke) Why are you drinking? >> Taku-chan→
Your alcohol isn't that strong, so I'll take your place.
(Yosuke) You're not that strong either. (Kataru) No, you're right.
But... Taku-chan.
Oh...! (Yosuke) Oh...!
what up? (Takuya) I can go today.
(Yosuke) Don't go! You stop! I'm going to die!
📱(vibration sound)
(Yosuke's voice) Takuya says he's staying at Kou's house today.
Sakurai.
It's been a while since I slept with a small fry.
(Kou) It was fun, like going back in time.
(Takuya) Hey.
(Yosuke) You're human, if you keep moving forward, you'll get tired →
Sometimes I need to go back in time and be healed.
So you can say it anytime.
I'll go back to any age with you.
(Takuya) Yes, thank you.
Thank you for your patience. We have accepted your request.
Customers waiting at number 13.
(Takuya) Chiharu.
this….
(Chiharu) Takuya wrote about it before, right?
(Chiharu) I…｡
Stay with Takuya →
For the first time, I had high expectations for myself.
(Takuya) Huh?
(Chiharu) If I'm with Takuya, I can change.
Even though I am like this, I can definitely change.
(Takuya) Did Chiharu want to change?
(Chiharu) I wanted to change so much that I died.
(Chiharu) Changed...｡
I wanted to love myself.
(Chiharu) I'm really sorry.
>> Why didn't you stop me?
(Takuya) Please complete the acceptance procedure.
>>Are you serious?
(Chiharu) I got divorced from Takuya.
(Kyoko) Then come back now.
(Chiharu) There's something I've always wanted to ask you.
>> Huh?
(Chiharu) Mother →
do you really like me?
>> What do you want to say?
(Chiharu) Takuya told me this.
The most important thing to me is myself.
That's why I don't want to get hurt →
I'm running away from many things.
>> That person says some really bossy things.
(Chiharu) But I was relieved.
I thought that was right.
(Chiharu) I didn't want to be like my mother.
I never wanted to see myself like that.
Even though it's just that...
She had an affair saying it was for Takuya.
Your mother is the same, right?
>>Together...｡
(Chiharu) The most important thing for your mother is not me.
It's the mother herself.
That's why he became so excited about my affair.
Because I felt like I was being hurt.
I'm not my mother's alter ego.
Mom and I too →
As a proper human being →
I have to face the people who are important to me.
(Chiharu) So please release me already.
(cry)
📱(vibration sound)
(Takuya) Yes.
📱(Mina) That's Matsuda, but what about Chiharu-chan?
Thank you.
(Chiharu) Please delete the data now.
>> For this amount?
(Chiharu) It's impossible to go beyond that.
>> But your husband will be working at City Hall until he retires, right?
So, don't you feel like this amount is still not enough?
Or will my husband quit his job too?
(An) Chiharu-san, did you quit your job as well?
(Takuya) Yeah, I called the company and they said they had submitted their resignation letter.
(Yosuke) Where did you go? (Takuya) I don't know.
(Mina) I can't connect to my cell phone either →
My SNS account also disappeared.
But why did he even leave the company?
(Takuya) Chiharu's boss said that he had received an anonymous email.
That Chiharu is having an affair.
>> Don't you remember being anonymous?
(Takuya) Maybe your mother-in-law →
I think he's the detective who commissioned the investigation into Chiharu's affair.
(Yosuke) Is that what you asked for? (Takuya) Yes, that one →
I think he threatened Chiharu.
(Yosuke) Ha, I heard that there is a detective who blackmails you.→
I had no idea it was really there.
Anyway, I have to delete the photo data that he has.
>>Let's all ask them to please delete it.
Well, there's no point in saying anything to these guys.
Take my smartphone and destroy it?
That’s it!
Ah, let's remove the SIM card as well. >> Yeah, that's right.
(Takuya) But not all the data is on your smartphone.
(Yosuke) So first, check where the data is saved.
(Takuya) How?
(Yosuke) On the app.
(An) Why is it so hot here?
(Koi) This is the most confidential area.
(Yosuke) Okay? (Navigation) Okay, yes.
(Yosuke) Of course it tracks location information →
Camera and recording functions can be activated remotely →
There are apps that can monitor your smartphone.
>> What? That's scarier than an app that shifts location information.
(Yosuke) It's scary. Well, originally →
Developed for parents to keep an eye on their children's smartphones →
It's a proper app, but recently →
It's used to monitor partners and investigate cheating.
>> But what are you going to do about it?
(Yosuke) In other words, use this app to infiltrate that person's smartphone.
Then you can delete the photo from your phone.
You can also find the storage location.
(Takuya) Does that mean I should just delete all the data on that photo?
(Yosuke) Yeah. (Mina) Then use that app →
Wouldn't it be nice if I could secretly download it to someone else's smartphone?
(Takuya) Okay, I'll try it.
(Endo) Sorry for keeping you waiting.
So, how much alimony did you plan on getting?
(Takuya) Not so →
When I asked you to stop doing that →
Will you please stop?
>>No way.
But it's fine if you buy it.
(Takuya) After all, that's how you threatened Chiharu?
>> I mean, it's worse to have an affair in the first place.
(Takuya) Ah, I'll buy it.
Please show me all the photos.
>> Please do this from the beginning.
But you can't see either.
Marry such a frivolous woman.
(Mina) No, An-chan already.
Ah!
(Endo) Wow! >> Oh, sorry.
It's tough. I need to remove the coffee stain quickly.
(Endo) Okay, just wipe it, wipe it... just wipe it!
it's okay! it's okay….
(Yosuke) [Is it necessary to go this far for Chiharu-chan? ]
[You were cheated on]
(Takuya) [Well, honestly→
There is also a feeling of wanting to look at Chiharu.]
[Because you'll betray me]
[Well, but even as I think about it, the only thing that comes to mind is →
All I had was fun]
(Takuya) [It's already a mess, isn't it?]
[So if Chiharu is punished →
I guess the punishment is mine →
I think I'm the only one who should give it.]
(Endo) Let go! Let go! (Koi) Not yet. Not yet.
(Endo) Don't pull! Don't pull me, you!
(Kou) Wait, wait. (Endo) Enough, that's enough.
Don't come! Don't follow me! I want it.
Are you really planning to buy it?
(Takuya) Yes, I will contact you again.
>> Hurry up.
Will you pay for this? Because I already asked for it.
(Takuya) Ah, yes.
>> Well then!
What, you couldn't download it? (Takuya) Sorry, I couldn't make it in time.
(Yosuke) Hey, what is that?
>> It can't be helped in such a short time.
That's right, let's think of another method.
No, there is no better way than this.
📱(vibration sound)
(Endo's voice) I waited two days.
Haven't decided to buy it yet?
Please delete all data now.
It's not enough to erase everything.
(Takuya) If so, how much is enough?
>> You... Hey.
Parent-child co-starring in-laws hahaha.
(Takuya) By the way. >> Huh?
(Takuya) How much is this?
♪～
(Takuya) [Puts my earphones in his bag]
>> [Eh, maybe earphones...]
(Takuya) [Yes, one that can share location information]
(Yosuke) [Why would you do that?] (Takuya) [That guy is definitely →
Other clients must have been extorted as well.
[So I took a photo of the scene →
I thought it would be a good idea to just hand it over to the police.]
You can also take this to the police.
(Yosuke) By the way, the exchanges the other day and today's exchanges are →
I'm definitely filming it on video.
>> Ah, you are from now on.
(Takuya) Mr. Endo.
This is a serious crime of intimidation.
>> No way, those earphones with many fates →
I can't believe it will be useful again. (Yosuke) Yeah.
>> I wonder what Chiharu is doing?
(Takuya) There may be someone you want to be with.
>> There's no place for that kid to go anymore.
(Takuya) Huh?
>>That's what he told me, ``I broke up with everyone.''
I can't save that child anymore.
It's frustrating though →
Takuya-san, only you can do it.
♪～
(Yosuke) [Is it really okay? ]
[Chiharu-chan may have done it wrong →
I'm sure that I like you
(Takuya) Sorry!
(Takuya) Oh, hello, I'm Takuya Yoshioka.
(Takuya) Oh hello, are you Tsutsumi-san? Sorry, it's late at night.
Ah, it's okay, uh...
Have you heard of Chiharu Yoshioka?
Ah, isn't it?
♪～
(Takuya) Chiharu.
(Takuya) Why are you here?
(Takuya) No, it's normal. It's a place where the two of us have fond memories. →
I was wondering if you were somewhere like that.
(Chiharu) Sorry. (Takuya) Oh, no.
But why?
There's something about meeting in an ordinary place like this →
On the other hand, I think we may have a connection...
Just something →
I'm starting to wonder if I can start over.
(Chiharu) But you'll regret it tomorrow.
(Takuya) Yes, I will.
I'll probably regret it.
(Chiharu) Yes.
(Takuya) But what happens tomorrow →
This time, I'm glad this happened →
You might think so.
I'm sure I'll do something, no matter what choice I make →
Sometimes I regret it, sometimes I think it was a good thing.
I think it's always been like that.
But →
I still feel like I can do it.
(Takuya) About Chiharu →
I think it will be accepted.
(Takuya) Please tell me the real Chiharu.
What kind of person are you, what are you worried about, and what are you afraid of?
(Takuya) Tell me everything.
(Chiharu) Can I talk to you?
Is it really good?
(Takuya) Let's start from that next time.
(Chiharu) I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
(Chiharu) Thank you.
♪～
(Rino) Mr. Yoshioka, are you planning to remarry?
(Takuya) Ah, that...
>> I can't do that. (Takuya) Eh.
>> Because Mr. Yoshioka's divorce notification has not been accepted.
(Takuya) What do you mean?
>> I spilled my coffee by mistake →
I was thinking of having it rewritten.
(Takuya) Mr. Oda...｡
>> It's just for my wife.
♪～
(Takuya) I think it will take time.
Do it properly this time→
Let's become a family.
(Chiharu) Yes.
(Takuya) Ah! (Chiharu) What?
(Takuya) Wait, wait. (Chiharu) What?
(Takuya) I'll go.
(Chiharu) Yes.
(Takuya) Yes.
Ha ha ha ha...
Ah! (Chiharu) Wow, that's amazing...!
(Takuya) Hahaha...!
Yay!
♪～