♫ Suddenly entering and leaving the red dust of
the rivers and lakes with a thought ♫
♫ Looking around everywhere are lonely smiles ♫
♫ Looking for the path of fallen flowers and remnant snow ♫
♫ Greed and betrayal, deliberate or unintentional ♫
♫ After many years, things are different ♫
One side of the martial arts world is like a dream,
a group of heroes fighting for power ♫
♫ A piece of the world, walking with horses,
talking about life with a smile ♫
♫ Ruling the world, with lonely brothers
turning against each other ♫
♫ Both honored and disgraced, tasting the warmth and cold,
making it hard finding a place to return ♫
♫ Ruling the world, with lonely brothers
turning against each other ♫
♫ Both honored and disgraced, tasting the warmth and cold,
making it hard finding a place to return ♫
[The Demi-Gods and Semi-Devils]
[Episode 26]
Her death is on you, too.
She lied to me, not the other way round.
I only beat her in her own game.
You're so cruel.
You murdered your husband.
You killed your lovers.
Now, you want to kill the man who refuses to take a look at your face.
I'm such a beauty.
Why don't you want to look at me?
Let me ask you one last thing.
Who was the leader that wrote to Chief Wang?
Qiao Feng. Look at both of us.
Which one of us is pleading now?
Everyone who knew his name has died.
Now there is only me and him.
It's not that difficult for you to find out his name.
You only have
to give me a hug,
and take a good look at me.
Then, I'll reveal his name.
Tell me.
At that time, why didn't you look at me directly?
Do you hate me?
If you don't hate me,
give me a kiss.
Stop fooling around.
If you don't want to kiss me,
why are you still hugging me?
Qiao Feng! Why are you so shameless?
My sister died because of you, and now you're kissing my father's lover.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
You too, hideous woman. You're still alive?
Do you really think men will still be interested in you?
What did you say?
You called me a hideous woman.
You should take a look at the mirror yourself.
You want a mirror?
Sure.
Enough.
Why are you so uptight?
Do you really like her?
Her death is nothing worth fussing about.
What do you know?
What I was asking her
was a question she alone in this world could answer.
If you didn't interrupt us,
she would've already given me the answer.
Well, I am sorry to have ruined your plan!
You should've stayed with your father.
My father's men are always glaring at me.
I told my dad to execute them, but he refused to do so.
So why would I want to go back?
Then, you should return to your master's side.
I stole a scripture from my master.
If I go back to him, he will surely kill me.
I'll go back when I'm done with my training.
Up to you. You do you.
I would've already taken my revenge if it wasn't for you.
Because of me?
I know.
You must be angry at me because I caused Madam Ma to be so angry she died.
I didn't expect the famous Qiao Feng would be affected by what I did.
It's so much fun.
What? Do you want to kill me?
You have already killed my sister anyway.
It won't matter if you kill me as well.
Where are you going?
I promised your sister that I would head north beyond the Yanmen Pass.
North beyond the Yanmen Pass?
After all, I can't stay in the Central Plains anymore.
You'll pass by the Yanmen Pass on your way, right?
I'm going to meet my mother. So, we'll take the same route.
You'll be on your own. Don't follow me.
Why?
A young girl and a man.
It'll be inconvenient for us to find accommodation.
What a joke. I don't think it will cause any inconvenience.
Why would you think so?
Moreover, didn't you and my sister go through the same thing?
She was engaged to me.
It was different for us.
I always thought my sister was a demure lady.
I didn't expect you to repeat what our parents did.
You hadn't gone through the ceremony to become husband and wife, yet you acted like a couple.
Shut up!
All you ever talk about is this nonsense.
Your sister remained chaste until the day she died.
I had not done anything immoral to her.
I always respected her.
Who are you trying to scare? You killed my sister nonetheless.
Young Master, it's bad.
Madam Wang's boat is headed here. Straight to us.
Aunt?
She has always hated the Murong family.
Why is she here all of a sudden?
I've no idea.
I think... I think she's here for Miss Wang.
In order to leave the Mandarava Villa, we upset Madam Wang's subordinates.
Young Master, what should we do now?
A'Bi, don't panic.
Since Aunt is coming, we can only welcome her.
I'll bring along my men to the dock to welcome her.
Please inform Cousin and tell her to come, too.
Yes.
Which busybody told him about my arrival?
Aunt.
This way.
People at the manor saw your boat and notified me about your arrival.
We are honored by your visit, and I apologize for the inadequate hospitality.
Please have some rest, and I'll serve you some tea.
The Mandarava Villa has everything.
I'm not here for the tea.
Where is Yuyan?
I'm going to take her home.
- Mother.
- How dare you show yourself?
You are a young unmarried lady.
How can you stay with a man all day long?
Don't you worry about being the center of gossip?
Come home with me. Stop bringing shame to the Wang family.
Aunt, Cousin and I grew up together.
She is family. It's been a long time since she last visited me.
Why not let her stay for a few more days?
Murong Fu, Yuyan grew up at the Mandarava Villa.
She doesn't know how wicked others can be.
Of course, she thinks you're a good person.
But I think differently.
I know exactly what you're scheming.
Indeed.
You claimed that the Murong Villa has a vast collection of treasured books.
But if you are to compare it,
the Huanshi Library's collection is nothing
compared to that of the Langhuan Jade Cave.
It's also rare to see you acting so diligently and eager to please me.
It's such a shame that my daughter has taken a fancy to you.
However, I don't like you.
With your limited intelligence and talents,
don't you ever think about visiting the Langhuan Jade Cave for the books.
Mother, how can you talk to Cousin like that?
Why?
Did I say anything wrong?
Since you were little, have you seen anything from the Murong family that is better than that from our Wang family?
He is a young man, yet he's so arrogant.
He got a few compliments from the men of the martial arts world,
and he thinks he is a famous man.
And all of you, too.
It has been so many years since the fall of the Yan nation.
Why do you still stand by the descendant of the fallen dynasty
as he continues to dream of being an emperor?
It's just wishful thinking.
Aunt, you are the older generaton.
Of course, you can reprimand me.
But no one can smear the name the Murong family spent hundreds of years building.
Whether we can successfully reestablish Yan or not,
we don't need any opinions from outsiders.
Aunt, do know your place and refrain from making impertinent remarks.
Come home with me.
Aunt, Cousin is all grown up now. She can think for herself.
Why don't we listen to what she has to say?
I'm teaching my own daughter, and I don't need your opinion.
Get out of my way.
Aunt, Cousin ran away from home because of me.
I hope that you won't blame her before you understand the entire incident.
Mother, Cousin is your biological nephew.
Why do you hate him so much?
How dare you take the side of this man?
A girl is born to leave her family. Sure enough.
So have you made up your mind to not come with me?
Mother, I don't want to stay at the Mandarava Villa forever.
I don't want to spend my whole life reading books and looking at the flowers.
I don't even have friends.
I only want to stay by the side of the man I like.
I want to see the world through my own eyes.
Even if it may be dangerous, I want to live life the way I want.
So this is the daughter I brought up.
She is doing all of this...
because of a man.
All right.
Don't ever come back to the Mandarava Villa.
I will wait and see what happens to you.
Let's go.
Mother. Mother!
- Let's go.
- Mother!
Brothers, do you think it was inappropriate for me to upset my aunt in public?
Yes.
Miss Wang is a young girl who longs for romance.
We can understand why she refuses to go home.
But Young Master is a man of foresight,
how can you be as willful as her?
You made Madam Wang look bad in front of others.
Brothers, how has my aunt been
to our Murong family all this while?
She hasn't been very friendly to us.
That's not entirely accurate.
She is more than just unfriendly.
She loathes us.
Exactly.
When my mother was still around,
I thought the town wasn't big enough for two of them.
They are both strong-headed women.
Hence, they didn't get along well.
After my mother passed away,
I have always treated her with respect.
Swallow's Nest has helped the Mandarava Villa a lot.
But what I got in return is her being so hostile against me.
Although Cousin has taken a liking to me,
Aunt refuses to let me into the Mandarava Villa.
Exactly.
It can only get worse.
So if one wants to acquire the treasured books of Langhuan Jade Cave,
a gesture of conciliation is not enough.
Instead of persuading Aunt, we should start with Miss Yuyan.
Although Aunt is stubborn, she is old too.
Sooner or later, the Wang family will belong to our Murong family.
So this was what you had in mind, Young Master.
We have misunderstood you.
I knew it.
Young Master is not one who gets distracted by romance.
There is a reason behind everything he does.
The Wang family doesn't have many descendants.
Whoever marries Miss Wang will definitely get the Langhuan Jade Cave, too.
Besides, Miss Wang has a vast knowledge of martial arts.
She will definitely be of big help to Young Master in the future.
Young Master puts the Yan Kingdom before everything else.
You have my utmost respect.
Unfortunately, we haven't gotten any reply from Liao.
We thought the Prince of Chu was a hero.
After we helped him, he would be tempted to join us.
Unexpectedly, he despaired because of the battle at Yanmen Pass.
He refused to show up.
We tried probing, but there was absolutely no response from him.
If that's the case, we should let this matter go.
Although I intend to reestablish Yan,
I don't need an alliance that is reluctant to fight along my side.
In the martial arts world of the Central Plains,
there are the prestigious Shaolin and the Beggars' Sect.
We are the outsiders,  it'll be difficult for us to achieve anything.
There's no hope for us to work with the Liao Kingdom.
In the Dali Kingdom, there's the Duan family.
It's even less likely for us to work with them.
If we want an alliance, we can only approach the Xixia Kingdom and the Tibetan Empire.
But I don't have anything to offer them.
It won't be easy to convince them.
As far as we know, both these kingdoms have princesses of marriageable age who have yet to be betrothed.
Have you ever thought about forming an alliance through marriage, Young Master?
[Cangbei Guesthouse]
Your dishes are here.
Beef.
Chicken.
Wine.
Enjoy your food.
This way, please!
Miss, can I take your order?
Waiter, what's your specialty?
Of course, we have a specialty dish.
But price-wise, it's not that cheap.
Is this enough?
Yes. This is surely enough.
Our store's specialties are sweet and sour carp, braised pork, and braised beef.
All right. I'll have three servings of each.
Miss, do you want to sample all the dishes?
Just serve it. Don't ask so much.
- Hurry up!
- Yes. Right away.
Three servings of sweet and sour carp.
Three servings of braised beef.
Three servings of braised pork knuckles.
Miss, your food is here.
- Here.
- Nice. Put this one here.
As for this one, give it to that man over there.
And, this one, leave it on this table.
Set up the table, and serve a bottle of good wine, too.
Is there anyone else coming?
Why do you talk so much?
Do you want me to cut off your tongue?
You want to cut off my tongue?
I'm afraid that you don't have the capability to do so.
Sir, the young lady ordered this for you.
What is this? This is so unpalatable.
I wonder who will actually eat this.
Is this for pigs?
There are wine and meat. Why aren't you eating?
You prepared this for me?
Thanks, Junior.
Thanks. Please come again.
Waiter.
- Come here.
- How can I help you?
Send this bowl of wine to that man over there.
What's wrong?
Hurry up. He's waiting for you.
Miss, but for what you have done to the wine, how can anyone drink it?
Are you saying that my hands are dirty?
No. I don't mean it.
What about this? You take a sip of this wine,
and I'll give you this silver ingot.
One sip of this wine for one silver ingot?
This is too good to be true.
I'll drink it even after you washed your feet in it, let alone your hands.
- What's going on?
- Get up.
Get up. What's going on?
Send help. Bring him to the physician.
Help. Hurry up.
Help me carry him!
Carry him out.
Hurry up!
Didn't you say that I wasn't capable enough to cut off your tongue?
Look at yourself.
Am I capable enough?
He was only joking.
And now, you turned him into a mute for the rest of his life.
You're too vicious.
What has that got to do with you?
Why? Didn't you say that you didn't want to care about me?
Why are you interfering with what I do?
Second Martial Brother,
let me serve you a bowl of wine as a gesture of respect.
Why don't you say anything?
Are you afraid that the wine is poisoned?
You're so impressive, Second Martial Brother.
You easily relieved the effects of the poison.
Let's go.
See you around.
What do you mean?
Our master is furious. He wants you to come back with me.
Just because our master is furious, you're forcing me to go back with you?
Are you trying to kill me?
Since you refuse to come with me, pass me the thing.
I'll bring it to our master.
At least, I won't go back empty-handed.
What is that "thing"? I don't understand what you're saying.
Junior, I'm not attacking you because we come from the same sect.
Don't overstep your bounds.
I'm very cautious with my bounds.
But, Second Martial Brother,
I have promised this brother here that I would go to Jiangnan with him.
We'll bring souvenirs for Master when we get back.
Who is this brat?
How can you speak like that?
Don't be rude.
He is my brother-in-law.
We are very close to each other.
You took our master's... You little brat!
Do you really want me to attack you?
Brother-in-law, he's going to kill me. Help me!
You brat!
Brother-in-Law!
Second Martial Brother, why did you poison yourself?
It's so much fun.
Come back. Don't go yet.
Brother-in-Law, you're so amazing.
Were you worried about me just then?
Second Martial Brother has been gone for so long and he's not back yet.
Yes.
Were we given the wrong information?
Did he let A'Zi that brat slip away again?
Even if he didn't manage to get hold of Junior,
it's almost time for him to come back, too.
Eldest Martial Brother, could she have plotted something
and lured Second Martial Brother into her trap?
- Third Junior.
- Yes, Martial Brother.
Bring your men there.
A'Zi has always been a scheming and intelligent girl.
If we let her slip away again, it'll be even more difficult to track her down in the future.
Yes, Senior.
I'll send my men to capture her.
Eldest Martial Brother, you really have good foresight.
You must be the reincarnation of Zhuge.
(TN: Zhuge Liang, an amazing strategist in Chinese history)
Eldest Martial Brother is both brave and astute.
A'Zi, that prat, is bound to lose to us.
Yes. That's right.
Eldest Martial Brother is really a composed man.
A'Zhu,
I should have listened to you.
I'm sorry.
I'll leave Yanmen Pass and head to the north now
to fulfill my promise to you.
A'Zhu...
Brother-in-Law, I finally caught up with you.
Wait for me.
You fought off Second Martial Brother for me.
I'm here to express my gratitude.
You don't have to thank me.
He started it first.
I wasn't trying to help you.
Brother-in-Law, slow down.
Wait for me.
Brother-in-Law!
Brother-in-Law, you promised my sister you would take care of me!
So many of them are bullying me now.
I'm only a young girl. What should I do when I'm all alone? You don't care about me at all!
I'm in a foul mood.
Stop following me.
You're in a foul mood?
I can stay with you and cheer you up. Then, you'll definitely feel better.
If you keep following me and creating troubles like what you did just now, I'll have to take care of you.
Isn't it even better if you can take care of me and guide me when I do something wrong?
My parents left me when I was little.
I know nothing, and no one cares about me.
Now, even my sister has left me.
Do you really want to come along?
Let's make things clear beforehand.
If you hurt another person for no reason,
I won't forgive you.
What if the person attacks me first?
Besides, I only kill bad guys.
You don't have to decide who's good and who's bad.
When you're with me, no one can hurt you.
So you are not allowed to harm anyone from now on. Do you understand?
Sure. I won't hurt anyone. You'll protect me from all harm.
Brother-in-Law, you're only my brother-in-law and you are already so controlling.
If A'Zhu were still alive and married to you,
wouldn't you have been even more... controlling?
Brother-in-Law, do you want me to sing for you?
No.
Then, do you want me to tell you a joke?
- Why don't you tell me a joke?
- No.
- I'll give you a riddle, then?
Then, do you want me not to play the flute?
No.
Look at you. You say no to everything. It's really hard to get along with you.
You insist on me playing the flute for you.
Then, I'll give you what you want.
She's there!
The girl is too arrogant.
She hurt our Second Martial Brother, and now she is heedlessly playing her flute to lure us into her trap.
I think she is plotting something against us.
We have nothing to fear. There are so many of us here.
Juniors, please be careful.
Don't fall into her trap.
I will never let her slip away this time.
- After her!
- Yes.
Did you play the flute to cue your comrades to ambush me?
Third Martial Brother, Fourth Martial Brother, Seventh Martial Brother, and Eighth Martial Brother.
Nice to see you again.
What a coincidence. You're gathering here, too.
Junior, we didn't expect to bump into you here.
I heard that you injured Second Martial Brother.
Is Second Martial Brother injured?
Is it bad?  Who hurt him?
Why are you still pretending?
He said that you told someone to hurt him.
What are you talking about, Eighth Martial Brother?
You were the one who sent your man to hurt Second Martial Brother.
How can you be so vicious?
Aren't you afraid that our master will find out about this?
You hurt him, not me.
Wait.
You said you hurt him, not me.
Martial Brothers, did you hear that? He admitted that he killed Second Martial Brother.
Did you use the San Yin Centipede Claw?
Who told you that Second Martial Brother is dead?
He's still alive.
His injury was not caused by San Yin Centipede Claw.
Wasn't he injured by the San Yin Centipede Claw?
Then, I'm sure he was hurt by the Marrow Sucking Palm.
That's your expertise.
You're really impressive.
You even dared scheme against Second Martial Brother.
You...
Third Martial Brother, bring the brat back with us so that our master can decide what to do with her.
How dare you speak such nonsense.
Let's not get into a fight.
Junior has always been an obedient girl.
Why don't you come with us?
Third Martial Brother, I've always obeyed you.
I'll do what you say.
That's great. Let's go.
Let's go. Please go ahead.
Go ahead.
Go ahead? Why should we go ahead?
You should come with us too.
You go first. I'll be right there.
No. You can't do that.
We should go together.
It's a good idea to go with you.
But my brother-in-law doesn't want to let me go.
Brother-in-Law?
Suit yourselves.
Can't you see that my brother-in-law is just right there?
Oh, right. You're too tall. He can't see you either.
Stop right there!
Brat, come with us.
You look so calm.
Could it be that you activated the Holyword's Pot?
What is a Holyword's Pot?
Hand it over!
Hand over what?
The Holy... Are you crazy?
You know what I mean!
I've already gifted it to my brother-in-law.
Brother-in-Law!
Brother-in-Law! You are so amazing.
Eighth Martial Brother, if you can pull out your weapon,
I'll go back with you.
Your martial arts skills are impressive.
We truly respect your skills.
That... The pot is our sect's treasure.
It won't be useful in someone else's hand.
Please return the pot to us.
We'll be very thankful for your kindness.
It's not with me.
Hold on!
Leave the Holyword's Pot with us, or you will be in huge trouble!
You've spent a long time arguing, and I still have no idea what a Holyword's Pot is.
Show me.
Brother-in-Law, didn't I pass it to you just now?
It's all up to you now.
You passed so many things to me just now. How would I know which one you're talking about?
It's a delicate small pot.
It's one of our sect's three treasures.
We use that to practice the Great Energy Dissolving Skill.
Eighth Junior, you talked too much!
The Great Energy Dissolving Skill?
- Give it to me.
- Brother-in-Law, didn't I already give it to you?
It's a tiny silver pot.
Forget it.
If you have no intention to change your attitude, there's no need for me to cover up for you.
The pot is useless to me. I won't keep it with myself.
It's up to you whether you believe it or not. I've got to go now.
Brother-in-Law, wait!
Brother-in-Law!
Where are you going?
Surrender the Holyword's Pot.
Sir, your meal is served.
Thanks.
Enjoy your meal.
We caught A'Zi!
Second Martial Brother,
Eldest Martial Brother sent me here to tell you that we have already captured A'Zi, the brat.
That brat.
I'll make you pay for what you did.
Let's go!
Junior, you got caught, after all.
I'm back.
Eldest Martial Brother has superior power.
It was an eye-opener for us.
Junior, you are quite something.
So many of us were running up and down just for you.
We even came all the way from the Xingxiu Sea to the Central Plains.
Even Eldest Martial Brother is here.
It seems like I really am something.
But if you count my protector in,
you really are no match for us.
You have a protector?
I wonder who he is.
My brother-in-law. You'll be shocked if you find out who he is.
People call them Murong of the South and Qiao Feng of the North.
My brother-in-law is the chief of the Beggars' Sect.
Qiao Feng of the North, the man whose name sounds across the entire Central Plains!
Now I know why.
I won't mind losing to him.
We'll be in huge trouble if the Beggars' Sect gets hold of the Holyword's Pot.
Eldest Martial Brother,
Qiao Feng is no longer the chief of the Beggars' Sect.
You just came from the West, and may not know what's going on.
Something big happened in the martial arts world of the Central Plains.
Qiao Feng was long expelled from the sect.
Was he really expelled from the sect? Really?
It must be true.
This is what all the martial artists said.
They said that he isn't a Han, but a Khitan.
All of the heroes of the martial arts world of the Central Plains want to kill him.
I heard that he killed his father, his mother, his friends, and many others.
He perpetrates every conceivable evil and is more wicked than me!
Why did your sister marry someone like him?
Are there no other men left in this world?
Why she married him... I've no idea.
But he killed my sister.
Then, it seems like you aren't on good terms, either.
The Beggars' Sect can easily outnumber us.
It won't be easy for us to fight them.
However, since Qiao Feng has been expelled from the sect,
what else is there for us to be afraid of?
Yes. That's right!
Junior, you stole our master's pot and handed it to an outsider.
How should we punish you?
Yes. I violated the rules.
But, Eldest Martial Brother, don't you want to retrieve the pot?
It's one of our sect's three treasures.
Of course, we have to retrieve it.
But my brother-in-law
is an extremely stubborn man.
I was the one who handed the pot to him.
If I am the one who asks for it from him,
he'll definitely return it to me just like how I gave it to him.
It will be different if someone else approaches him.
Eldest Martial Brother, although you are good in martial arts, the most you can do is kill him.
But it would be extremely difficult
if you want to retrieve the pot.
So, according to what you said, what should we do?
Release me.
I'll go to the Yanmen Pass alone.
Then, he will return the pot to me.
I'm only trying to atone for my sin.
You have to promise to spare me from the punishment after this.
What you said makes sense.
However, Junior, you
are humiliating Eldest Martial Brother.
When I let you go, you will flee
with your brother-in-law.
Then, where can I find you?
About the pot, we will definitely get it back.
As long as we don't leak any news,
I am sure that Qiao Feng won't leave so soon.
Junior, show me what you've got.
If you can beat me, you will be the Eldest Martial Sister of the Xingxiu Sect.
I'll obey you and accept whatever punishment you impose on me.
Martial Brother, are you kidding me?
I am all tied up. How am I going to attack you?
Why? Are you plotting against me?
Am I right?
All right.
I'll let you go.
Eldest Martial Brother's power is phenomenal.
We are really impressed.
This is something we haven't seen before and haven't heard of before.
In this world, save our master,
Eldest Martial Brother is unrivaled.
What Qiao Feng of the North and Murong of the South?
They don't even deserve to carry
- our eldest brother's shoes!
- Yes. That's right.
Junior, now you know how powerful we are.
Unfortunately, it's too late for you to regret now.
You are quite calm.
Junior, take this!
Don't fret. I'll help you.
Brother-in-Law!
Use the power of the palm strike and fight back.
Eighth Junior!
You!
You haven't exhausted your power.
You have been fooling with me.
Did Master teach you the best skills of the sect?
Zhai Xingzi.
Eldest Martial Brother.
Why are you on your knees? You finally admitted your defeat?
Zhai Xingzi, you have lost the match. Hurry up and apologize to Junior.
How dare a mediocre person like you try to show off your skills?
You have embarrassed the Xingxiu Sect! You useless thing!
Junior spared your life, and you were still trying to be a hero. Why don't you talk?
Zhai Xingzi, 10 years ago, I knew you were a pathetic failure of the Xingxiu Sect!
Today, Junior eliminated the useless guy of the sect.
It's a great contribution to the Xingxiu Sect.
Yes. That's right.
Eldest Martial Brother, why don't you talk?
Could it be that you still refuse to admit your defeat?
I admit defeat.
I'm not your eldest martial brother.
You are our eldest martial sister.
Amazing!
Eldest Martial Sister has incredible skills in martial arts.
From now on, the Xingxiu Sect will have a new heir!
We will be known by the whole world!
Yes.
You should defeat Qiao Feng of the North and Murong of the South!
Then, the Xingxiu Sect will be peerless in the Central Plains!
Yes. Our eldest martial sister will be peerless! Eldest Martial Sister, all the best!
- Quiet.
- Eldest Martial Sister is peerless!
Quit the nonsense.
According to the sect's rules, after we have a new heir,
what do we do to the former one?
Eldest Martial Sister! Please!
I want to show you some mercy.
But I can't disobey the sect's rules.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ⚔️Martial Arts Team ⚔️@Viki.com
♫ In this life, no matter who is laughing at me ♫
♫ I will not go mad or be unreasonable ♫
♫ I have crossed seas and mountains of hardships ♫
♫ Everything has it's earnings ♫
♫ All the things that happened in the past are as clear as ink ♫
♫ I wait for it to run dry and then start to tint ♫
♫ All worldly desires are like mountains and valleys ♫
♫ Borrowing rain's tears as the water rushes out  ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
who cares if it's life or death in the end ♫
♫ I might as well become a river ♫
♫ As the sword laughs, many of your dreams are shattered ♫
♫ It's just a small story in the martial arts world ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful ♫
♫ If you make it past, come back to find the cause ♫
♫ How will fate deal with me? ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful ♫
♫ As the sword laughs, many of your dreams are shattered ♫
♫ It's just a small story in the martial arts world ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful ♫
♫ If you make it past, come back to find the cause ♫
♫ How will fate deal with me? ♫
I am Xiao Feng, around 31 years old. And you are?
I am Yelv Hongji. I am 13 years older than you.
- Then you are my older brother.
- We are brothers, let's bow to the heavens to seal it.
- Okay.
- Great.
Brother.
Big Brother!