♫ Suddenly entering and leaving the red dust of
the rivers and lakes with a thought ♫
♫ Looking around everywhere are lonely smiles ♫
♫ Looking for the path of fallen flowers and remnant snow ♫
♫ Greed and betrayal, deliberate or unintentional ♫
♫ After many years, things are different ♫
♫ One side of the martial arts world is like a dream,
a group of heroes fighting for power ♫
♫ A piece of the world, walking with horses,
talking about life with a smile ♫
♫ Ruling the world, with lonely brothers
turning against each other ♫
♫ Both honored and disgraced, tasting the warmth and cold,
making it hard finding a place to return ♫
♫ Ruling the world, with lonely brothers
turning against each other ♫
[The Demi-Gods and Semi-Devils]
♫ Both honored and disgraced, tasting the warmth and cold,
making it hard finding a place to return ♫
[Episode 21]
- Brother Bai.
- What do you need, Brother Qiao?
We've been best friends for so many years.
I've never thought that we'd be enemies after this.
Actually, I've long heard about your family background.
But I refused to believe it.
But it turned out to be true.
If this was not a matter of our kingdom's enemies,
I would rather die than become your enemy.
After we turn into enemies, a fight is sure to come.
I have another favor to ask from you.
If it won't affect the country,
please go ahead and tell me.
If all of you think that I've done the Beggars' Sect good in the past,
please take good care of this young lady.
Keep her safe.
Don't worry, Brother Qiao.
I will beg Divine Physician Xue to treat her.
If anything happens to this lady, I'll kill myself.
If that's the case, thank you very much.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ⚔️Martial Arts Team ⚔️@Viki.com
Take care.
- Take care, Chief.
- Take care, Chief!
Take care, Chief.
[Value righteousness over material gain]
[Heroes' Gathering Manor]
Who else?
Me!
Qiao, let me drink with you.
You ran away when we fought with the Liao Army.
What qualifications do you have to drink with me?
This parting wine today
marks the ending of my friendship with all the heroes here.
What friendship do we have?
No need to be so troublesome.
Come at me together!
This jar of wine is my parting wine with all of you today.
Who will fight me first?
I'll go first then.
Calm down! Spread out!
- Father!
- Hurry up and go! This isn't some place you can stay!
Hurry up and hide!
Father.
Xiao Juan, it's my fault for not being able to protect you on time. Do not blame me.
That person killed his father, his mother, and his teacher.
He should die. Let's attack him together!
Yes! Let's attack him together!
Reverend.
I said something rude just now.
I hope that you won't blame me for it.
What did you say?
Just now, I said that Qiao Feng entered Shaolin alone and left.
Not only did he not suffer any injuries after murdering Reverend Xuan Ku,
he even kidnapped a monk from Shaolin.
What's your point?
Qiao Feng is a master of martial arts.
He's a rare talent.
Now, I realized that he could come and go as he pleased because it was impossible to stop him.
Divine Physician Xue, do you want to have a taste of Shaolin's martial arts?
- Brother.
Fine. If we don't attack, others will think that Shaolin Sect has no one left.
Amitabha.
Qiao Feng, you are too sinful.
Just blame me for everything!
So what?!
- Young Master.
- It's you.
Young Master!
Brother Qiao took the risk to come here to save me.
You have to help him.
Murong Fu.
What's your relationship with this lady?
This lady is my maid.
But I don't know why she's with Qiao Feng.
And I'm here today for the same reason as all of you.
I'm here to defeat this evil, Qiao Feng.
As for the other issues, we'll discuss them later.
Young Master.
Brother, we live and die together with our shield.
Today, we've been greatly humiliated.
We've lost our dignity to continue living in this world.
Qiao Feng!
We'll seek revenge from you in the next life for this humiliation!
Father! Father.
Amitabha.
Father.
Master You!
Father!
Qiao Feng! I'll kill you!
Let me ask you. Am I a Khitan or a Song?
I ask you! Am I a Khitan or a Song?
You are a Khitan.
The cold-blooded Khitan!
Be careful!
Son!
Kill that lady!
[Heroes' Gathering Manor]
A'Zhu!
Who are you?
Why did you bring me here?
Why did you save me?
You still want to send yourself to your death?
Such a disappointment.
Your martial arts training has made you invincible.
But you almost got yourself killed for a woman.
I owe it to that woman.
She is innocent.
I have to save her.
How is she related to you?
She is neither kith nor kin.
You are not in debt to her.
And she's no stunning beauty.
But you are willing to sacrifice yourself for her.
What a foolish man!
I went berserk.
That's why I didn't think about the consequences.
So, you went berserk.
There is half-a-month's worth of food here.
Focus on recuperating here.
No one will be able to find you!
Qiao Feng!
We'll seek revenge from you in the next life for this humiliation!
Divine Physician Xue, say no more.
I know your rules.
How about this. I promise to teach you the seven moves of Silk Thief Technique.
If I do that, will you be willing to treat this lady?
Of course.
The Silk Thief Technique is your personal ultimate technique.
One for one.
Of course, I will save her.
I'm almost fully recovered now.
But the most important thing now is to find out my real identity.
Then I have to go to Yanmen Pass to look at the writings on the cliff.
I wonder how Miss A'Zhu is right now.
I hope that Elder Bai can take good care of her
for the sake of our past friendship.
Seems like my benefactor doesn't want to see me.
I don't know who he is.
If I have a chance,
I'll definitely repay him for his kindness.
- Divine Physician Xue.
I'm here to check on Miss Ruan's recovery.
Miss Ruan. Miss Ruan.
How do you feel?
Divine Physician Xue.
Divine Physician Xue, I feel a bit stuffy in my chest.
And I feel weak.
You were too seriously injured.
You have not recovered your strength yet.
Although I've given you medication and acupuncture treatment
to treat the injuries that your internal organs suffered,
but the human body is not a machine.
Even if you cure your illness, it doesn't mean you will come out the exact same as you were before.
You need to be patient with your recovery.
I understand.
But I can't breathe very well.
I don't know. No...
You...
If you don't want to die, keep quiet.
Divine Physician Xue.
Miss Ruan was suffering from a sudden illness just now.
But I managed to keep her condition stable.
Pass down this message to everyone.
Don't disturb her for the next two days.
Let her rest in peace.
If you need to ask her any questions,
you can do that after she has recovered.
- Okay.
- Go on now.
Young Miss, I am not staying here!
Come in.
A'Zhu, what are you...
Young Master, I'm here today to bid my farewell.
Are you blaming me for not saving you that day?
I don't blame you.
I have been an orphan since young.
It was all thanks to your father who kindly took me in.
I won't be able to repay your family
even if I'm crushed to death.
It's not that I didn't want to save you.
But back then, I couldn't let others think that I was colluding with Qiao Feng because of you.
And I couldn't go against the whole pugilist world because of you.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize to me.
I know that you have a great cause.
You can't sacrifice so much for me.
I can't ask that from you.
And I don't want you to do that.
But Brother Qiao risked his life for me.
I have to repay him for his kindness.
Young Master, when your father was still alive,
he said that if one day,
A'Bi and I met someone we loved,
he'd marry us off as if we were his daughters.
Now....
Now, I've found someone I love.
I don't care what he feels about me,
as long as I can accompany him and make him laugh every now and then,
it'll be enough for me.
Are you talking about Qiao Feng?
After this, I won't be able to accompany you anymore.
I know that you have the great ambition to revive the country
and the outstanding skills to do that.
But if you want to conquer people's hearts,
you'll have to give them yours too.
That is the right way.
The path of reviving the country is full of obstacles.
Besides having manpower,
more importantly, you need luck.
If you feel that it's hard for you,
you don't have to force yourself.
This is your father's ambition.
If you are willing, you can let it go and live the life you want.
I will now...
bid my farewell to you.
Young Master, I'm leaving.
Please allow me to repay the Murong Clan
in the future for raising me.
I come from the south today.
If the writings on the cliff state that I'm indeed a Khitan,
then, after leaving Yanmen Pass,
I'll forever become the people from the North of the Wall.
And I will not come back.
Even the wild geese have more freedom than me to travel
from south to north every year.
But the writings on the cliff have been destroyed.
If Reverend Zhi Guang was telling the truth,
then this is where my father jumped off from the cliff.
I traveled all the way here
to find out about my family background.
But I got nothing out of it.
Why? Why?
Reverend Zhi Guang and Zhao Qiansun
said that there are writings on the cliff.
But who destroyed the writings?
I have to find them and ask them.
What was engraved on the cliff?
- Brother Qiao.
- A'Zhu.
I finally found you!
A'Zhu!
Brother Qiao, I've been waiting here for a long time.
I was worried that you couldn't make it here.
Thank the heavens that you are here now in one piece.
Why are you here?
I...
I thought that you would definitely come to Yanmen Pass
to look at the writings on the cliff.
So, I came here to wait for you as soon as I recovered.
You've recovered?
Divine Physician Xue healed you?
Luckily, Elder Bai was willing to exchange his martial arts technique with him.
Or else, that Divine Physician Xue wouldn't have saved me.
Brother Qiao, who was that man in black?
I don't know either.
You don't know either?
Why would he risk himself to save you from danger then?
Now, who should I seek revenge on and who should I repay?
Am I a Hu or a Han?
Am I doing the right thing or the wrong thing now?
I don't even know anymore.
Brother Qiao, I think there's no need to think too much about it.
The truth will eventually come to light.
As long as we have a clear conscience and can face the heavens and those on Earth with no qualms, it'll be enough.
I'm upset because I don't have a clear conscience.
That day in Xingzi Forest,
I vowed not to kill any Hans.
- But...
- Those people from Heroes' Gathering Manor
indiscriminately surrounded and attacked you.
You were just defending yourself.
You couldn't possibly let them cut you into pieces without reason, right?
That's absurd, right?
Let's go.
By the way, how did you escape?
Did Elder Bai save you?
Brother Qiao, do you still remember the time I dressed up as a monk in Shaolin Temple?
Even their own seniors and juniors couldn't recognize me.
Not even you.
Your naughty trick.
Who did you dress up as this time?
Divine Physician Xue.
Him?
He treated me every day.
We talked the most.
I can mimic his expressions and figure the best.
I attacked his pressure points
and tied up his hands and legs.
Then, I wore his clothes
and put wrinkles on my face like his.
I looked almost 70% like him.
But Divine Physician Xue has a black and white beard.
It's not easy to make that.
If it's not easy to make, use the real one.
Use the real one?
Yes.
Really?
I took a penknife from his trunk
and cut off his beard.
Then, I glued them onto my face strand by strand.
He must be so furious.
But what can I do?
He didn't save me out of kindness.
So, I didn't repay his kindness with hate, did I?
Moreover, after I shaved off his beard,
he looked at least 10 years younger.
He looked more handsome than before.
Don't tell me that you had dressed up as me before.
Brother Qiao, I did dress up as you
to save your friends in Beggars' Sect from the First Class Hall of Xixia.
You dressed up as me to save my friends?
Why did you do that?
You saved A'Bi and me.
We were very grateful to you.
But I heard how they treated you.
So, I thought that if I dressed up like you to send the cure to them,
they might feel compassionate towards you.
I never knew that not only were they ungrateful,
they even attacked you in the Heroes' Gathering Manor that day.
So, you also dressed up as me to kill my parents,
infiltrate Shaolin Temple, and kill my master.
Brother Qiao, wh-what are you talking about?
I didn't kill your master.
I didn't kill your parents either.
- I...
- My master was gravely injured.
And I was accused of being the culprit right away.
In this world, who else can mimic me as well as you do, except for you?
No. I didn't kill your master. And I wouldn't kill your...
Who are you working for? Tell me now!
Brother Qiao! Think about it carefully.
Your master was so powerful. How would I be able to kill him?
Moreover, even if I were powerful enough,
why didn't I kill those villains for you
when we were in the Heroes' Gathering Manor that day?
That's true.
You are not the one who killed my master.
I'm sorry. I've been restless and confused in the past few days.
Please forgive me.
Brother Qiao, there's no need to apologize to me.
You saved my life.
No matter what, I won't blame you.
Don't take this to heart.
Who did you learn this Art of Disguise from?
Does your master have any other disciples?
You don't need a master for this Art of Disguise.
I liked to disguise myself as others since young.
The more I do it, the better I get.
That's strange.
There's another person in this world who looks exactly like me.
Even my master mistook him for me.
Brother Qiao, although it's not easy to find that person,
at least we have some clues to guide us.
I believe that you'll be able to find that person.
I have to find Reverend Zhi Guang.
I want to ask him what was engraved on this cliff.
With Reverend Zhi Guang's personality,
I don't think he'll tell you.
Zhao Qiansun would rather die than give in.
But I have a way to make him talk.
Go! Hurry up!
Speed up!
If Commander finds out that we arrested
the people of Khitan without his order...
The Khitan killed my family.
If I don't avenge them, can I call myself a man?
They always capture our citizens, too.
It's not too much for an eye for an eye.
If they can burn, kill and pillage us, why can't we do the same?
If Commander finds out about it, I'm sure he won't blame us.
I can't believe those soldiers of the Song Dynasty.
How can they bully those innocent people?
Who is it?
Run.
Wait for me.
Get up.
Look. Our benefactor is a Khitan, too.
He's a Khitan, too.
Yes.
Let's go home.
I want to go home.
Brother Qiao!
Brother Qiao, there are good people in Han.
And there are good people in Khitan.
You are the one who saved my life.
No matter if you are a Han or a Khitan,
it has no difference to me.
I wasn't planning to save you.
I was just feeling competitive at the time.
So, you don't owe me anymore.
You can leave.
I have been an orphan since young.
I was left on the street.
The late master of the Murong Clan saved me.
He brought me back to Swallow's Nest.
From then on, I became the maid of the Murong Clan.
Although I am Young Master Murong's maid, he doesn't own me.
Young Master Murong has never treated us as maids either.
He even bought some maids to serve us.
Master Murong and his wife
once said that if we are to leave Swallow's Nest one day,
the Murong Clan will send us off in joy.
Brother Qiao, I've already bid farewell to Young Master Murong.
From now on, I'll follow you and be your maid.
I am a man from Khitan.
I don't deserve you.
You are used to the comfortable lifestyle in Jiangnan.
What good will it do for you to wander around and suffer with me?
Brother Qiao, are you rejecting me because I'm a lowly servant?
If you don't allow me to go with you, I'll jump down from here.
I'll do it.
General Han who guards the Yanmen Pass is strict and impartial.
By right, his soldiers
won't be allowed to treat the citizens of Khitan like that.
Those soldiers must be seeking personal revenge.
I coincidently saved those people of Khitan today.
The wolf head tattoo on their bodies proved that I am a Khitan.
From now onward, I will not be ashamed of being a Khitan.
And I will not be proud of being a Song.
I will fight only for the people in need.
And my only mission is to avenge my parents.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by ⚔️Martial Arts Team ⚔️@Viki.com
♫ In this life, no matter who is laughing at me ♫
♫ I will not go mad or be unreasonable ♫
♫ I have crossed seas and mountains of hardships ♫
♫ Everything has it's earnings ♫
♫ All the things that happened in the past are as clear as ink ♫
♫ I wait for it to run dry and then start to tint ♫
♫ All worldly desires are like mountains and valleys ♫
♫ Borrowing rain's tears as the water rushes out  ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
who cares if it's life or death in the end ♫
♫ I might as well become a river ♫
♫ As the sword laughs, many of your dreams are shattered ♫
♫ It's just a small story in the martial arts world ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful  ♫
♫ If you make it past, come back to find the cause ♫
♫ How will fate deal with me? ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful  ♫
♫ As the sword laughs, many of your dreams are shattered ♫
♫ It's just a small story in the martial arts world ♫
♫ If you come across me in this life,
so what if I abandon all my riches ♫
♫ Where do I go to ask the rights and the wrongs,
the benefits and the losses, the empty and the colorful  ♫
♫ If you make it past, come back to find the cause ♫
♫ How will fate deal with me? ♫
Who is it?
A licentious and immoral man.
A wanton and shameless woman...
is cheating on her husband and meeting up with her lover.
You are Qiao Feng?