(The World of the Married)
I love you.
You know that, right?
Yes.
Of course I know.
My son.
My house.
My life.
I won't let anything of
mine being taken away.
Lee Taeoh is the only thing
I want out of my life.
Your house is on collateral.
And your bank accounts are
under your husband's company.
You're asking for a lot.
I must take it all back...
...by any means necessary.
If he already siphoned it off
to someone else's account,
you may not get anything back.
All right.
This is the important part.
Divorce is all about confidentiality.
Please control your emotions
so your husband doesn't find out.
You have to deceive him properly.
If you're not up for that,
you'll have to forgive and move on.
It must be hard for Joonyoung.
He did like his grandmother.
And it's his first time losing
someone close to him.
Don't worry about Joonyoung.
I'll take care of him.
You should pull yourself together.
Take it easy at work.
I'm worried about your health.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I kept accusing you...
...of seeing another woman.
I think I did it because
I love you too much.
It's just something that women do.
Sometimes I want to check
if you still love me.
Hold on a second.
I'm sorry.
A patient is calling.
I'm slowly befriending her.
We spend a lot of time
at each other's houses.
I heard you're very close with Mr. Yeo.
So I came to you.
(Episode 4)
We found gonorrhea
from your PCR STD test.
You'll be fine as long as
you take antibiotic.
At my age?
This is so embarrassing.
Don't be.
It's a common disease among adults.
Right?
So it's not necessarily...
...transferred by doing it, right?
You mean intercourse?
You can get it when your immune system
is weakened by exhaustion and stress,
or at a sauna or a spa.
Right, doctor?
Are you sure I can trust that doctor?
You saw her asking me
to help her husband.
She's a quick-witted person.
She'll handle it discreetly.
Don't worry.
What?
It is very unlikely that it was caused...
...by anything other than intercourse.
99 percent of the times...
...it's passed on through sexual contact.
I'm sure it's going well.
Look.
(Specialist Ji Sunwoo)
Did the doctor explain...
Honey.
Thank you for your consultation.
Honey...
Honey. Honey!
Honey!
Honey...
I'm a doctor.
I have a responsibility
to inform the patient...
...about the cause and
treatment of her illness.
I don't know why you thought
I'd cover up your friend's affair.
If you're done here,
I wish you a nice day.
All right.
I guess I was wrong about you.
Say what?
It's Mr. Yeo, Dakyung's father.
He's with Sunwoo right now.
It looks like they're having
a serious conversation.
I'm not sure what they're
talking about though.
You have principles as a doctor.
I'm sorry if that hurt your pride,
but you're a married woman yourself.
I'm just saying,
it could've been much better
to keep her in the dark.
I'm not sure.
I personally think that couples
shouldn't keep secrets from each other.
Does that mean you know everything
that your husband does?
Yes.
I know everything about my husband.
He doesn't know how to keep secrets.
Looks like he's on a short leash.
By the way,
your daughter...
...is dating someone.
Oh dear.
I ended up revealing
your daughter's secret.
I thought it was a serious relationship.
I figured your family already knew.
I'm sure she would've told us
if that was the case.
My Dakyung...
She may be pampered and naive,
but she is smart.
Not as smart as you, of course.
-Have a nice day.
-Thank you.
-Mr. Yeo.
-Yeah.
How do you do?
How was the funeral cortege?
It went well.
-Cheer up.
-Thank you.
Thank you for the talk.
Goodbye, sir.
-What brings you here?
-Oh... I was just passing by.
What did you talk about with Mr. Yeo?
Why won't you answer me?
Who is he?
Bring him home some time.
-We want to meet him.
-Forget it.
We're just dating.
Someone saw you.
They said you two looked intimate.
Who saw us?
Let's drop this.
Just break up with him
if it's not that serious.
I'll find a decent man for you.
Wait until we fix a blind date.
No.
What's wrong with you!
I convinced your dad
when you insisted to move out.
And now your love life is
on everyone's lips.
Don't embarrass me like that.
You know how scary your dad is
when he gets angry.
I'm an adult.
Can you respect my privacy, Dad?
Dad.
Move back in with us
if you don't want a blind date.
It's not good for a girl to live alone.
By the way,
you look like you gained some weight.
Work on your diet.
Hey Mom.
-Are you tired?
-I'm fine.
-Mom!
-Hey.
Hey!
-Dad!
Noeul!
Do you need...
...a ride home?
Thank you.
Isn't it hard...
...raising a child by yourself?
What else can I do?
We just have to accept things
the way they are.
Does she get uneasy about...
...living apart from her dad?
I think she's used to it now.
She doesn't ask about him anymore.
Thank you for giving us a ride.
Miyeon?
Yes?
That night...
...when I visited the office.
You know why I did that, right?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not sure...
what you're talking about.
I see.
It seems like I've wasted your time.
I'll get going now.
-Why did you do that?
-Are you serious?
That's not what I meant.
I don't want to talk about it. Get out!
I said, get out!
I saw your husband leaving.
It seems like they had a fight.
I'll find out more.
Is something wrong?
No.
I just feel like drinking.
What were you thinking?
I'm not upset because
the donation's been cut off.
You should've looked the other way
for the patient's sake!
The patient wanted to know.
-She was my patient.
-Exactly!
Didn't you know that her husband
is our biggest sponsor?
You know,
bringing up your doctor's conscience
as an excuse was overkill.
Be honest. You let empathy get in the way.
A woman with a cheating husband.
It looked a little risky.
You're the one playing a risky game.
What?
You're a double spy.
When will you stop?
I know you're not that kind of person,
but a hospital is a crowded place.
I came here just to be sure.
You know Gosan is a small place.
Please make sure...
...that our family affair
doesn't leak out.
All patient information will
remain confidential. Don't worry.
Do you...
...blame me?
Would you have been better off...
...not knowing?
I'm not getting a divorce.
Ignorant people might ask...
...if I'm tolerating his affair
because of his money.
But why do you think I spent
all those years with him...
...if money was the only
thing that mattered?
Is the time you've spent
with him enough...
...to forgive him and move on?
He was just...
...fooling around with a woman.
What is there to forgive?
To men,
sex is like excretion.
I made him the man he is today.
His background, wealth,
and even his personality.
If I divorce him,
I'd be wasting everything I've
done for him over the years.
I don't want that.
Please answer my call.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes.
Something came up at work.
It seems like the staffs can't handle it.
At this hour?
I'm sorry.
Don't wait up for me.
Enjoy your drink.
Thank you.
He just left. Can you check on him?
I'm sorry, but I need to go home early.
-Okay.
-Sorry.
(Start Recording)
Hyunseo.
A car...
...and a flat.
I must say, you're good.
Did you get yourself a sugardaddy?
What's wrong with you?
-We've broken up.
-Is that what you thought?
I beg to differ.
-I'm not done with you.
-Beat it.
Hyunseo.
That crazy lady is
a hospital director after all.
It's her, isn't it?
What's up with you two?
Are you dating her?
She's just a doctor who treated me.
My life has nothing to do with her.
Stay out of it.
Get out of my life.
Are you crazy?
This number cannot be reached...
Did something go wrong?
Why won't you answer your phone?
(Recent Calls)
(Lee Taeoh)
Hello?
Oh, hey.
You're still awake?
You rushed out in a hurry,
so I got worried.
How did it go?
I've taken care of the urgent matter,
but I need more time to finish it up.
Will you be working overnight?
I think so.
You must be exhausted.
Make sure you get some rest.
All right.
Thank you.
I love you.
Me too.
(Did something go wrong?
Why won't you answer your phone?)
Sunwoo!
Sunwoo.
You didn't hear me?
What were you thinking?
Just some trivial thoughts.
I guess you just finished work.
Is something troubling you?
No.
I came out for some exercise.
I saw what you saw.
At the parking lot.
I'm so busted.
Taeoh got busted all right.
Talk about bad timing.
What should I do?
How can I help you?
Is divorce the answer?
I don't know.
Maybe my family will be better off
if I sweep it under the rug.
Then how will I live
with all that pent up resentment?
I feel like every step I took
in my life was wrong.
I wonder...
...if I'm no longer attractive as a woman.
No way.
How silly of me.
I feel stupid telling you this.
Whenever you need me.
We can go somewhere near for a drink.
I'll take a raincheck on that offer.
Thank you, Jehyuk.
You're home late.
Yes, I'm tired.
How about dinner?
Of course I've eaten. Look at the time.
You did great.
Come back in two weeks.
Make sure you eat healthy until then.
-Okay, thank you.
-Sure.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
I'm looking for Dr. Ji Sunwoo,
the assistant...
There she is.
Should we go inside?
Or should we talk here?
Go inside.
Looking for this?
Where's Hyunseo?
Why are you looking for her?
This is what you should be worried about.
I have photos of your husband
going into that house...
...right here.
How about...
...a fair trade?
This is a hospital.
-What do you think you're doing?
-My point exactly.
Who would look bad if we raise
our voices in here?
What do you want?
20 million?
No?
Let's make it 30 million then.
I'm not giving money
to some punk like you.
You have until next week.
Or everyone will know that
you hired someone...
...to tail your husband.
Min Hyunseo...
Is she safe?
Why?
Do you think I locked her up or something?
Hyunseo...
...can't stand you.
She wants this to be the last payment.
You have until next week.
You've ensured us that you will
get the evidence.
What happened?
I don't think you're fit to lead this war.
You might as well forget
about the divorce.
It's better not to do it at all.
Dr. Ji?
What is it?
I think these are from your husband.
(You're still a wonderful woman)
Do you like the gift?
Why did you send me this?
Think of it as consolation from a friend.
You don't need to overthink it.
This is all part of client management.
Lee Taeoh is my client after all.
Thank you anyway.
One thing about me,
I try not to think much
when my head's in a mess.
I don't even think before I decide.
In life, nothing ever goes as planned,
and there is no answer.
Just going with the flow...
...isn't so bad.
Have you ever been betrayed...
...by someone close to you?
Do you trust that husband of yours?
Nothing was found from your
ECG and endocrine tests.
And they didn't find anything...
...from your allergy test.
I can't find the cause
even in this place.
It seems to be a psychiatric problem...
...rather than a medical problem.
I suggest you see a neuropsychiatrist...
I know my own symptoms.
I don't need psychotherapy.
Just give me the usual medicine.
Most people think that they
know their own problems.
You should seek...
...professional help instead.
How about you, doctor?
You have the same symptoms as me.
-Mr. Ha Dongshik...
-Instead of dealing with it alone,
you should seek professional help.
Raise your toes and look at the ceiling.
Make sure you stretch out...
...every part of your spine.
Keep engaging your core.
Now go back to your original position.
Keep your eyes to the front,
raise your knee slightly
and stretch your leg out all the way.
Stretch it out slowly.
Eyes to the front.
Less tension on your shoulders.
Keep your pelvis aligned.
Now, slowly stretch out your legs
without lowering your feet.
Stretch.
Less tension on your shoulders.
Keep your pelvis aligned.
Go back up.
Let's go again.
I have three older sisters.
So...
I only need to see a person's backside...
...to know if they're pregnant.
What's your point?
I thought it was strange
that you're quitting after this week.
What a surprise.
I'm not sure what you mean,
but if you don't like the
fact that I'm quitting,
you can ask for a refund.
I only put up with your shenanigans...
...because you're Taeoh's toy.
But now...
The situation's changed.
I can't keep my mouth shut anymore.
Tell her.
Go ahead. I wish you would.
I bet you can't.
All this time you covered up for us,
and now you want to be loyal?
That's hilarious.
When she finds out,
do you think she will back down?
She would rather see you
ruin your life over...
...raising Taeoh's bastard.
Maybe Sunwoo is only pretending
like she doesn't know anything.
Didn't that ever occur to you?
Taeoh is just leading you on, isn't he?
There is no cure for stupidity.
Do you want to eat out?
We need a diversion.
Let's go somewhere nice.
I'll send you the address.
See you there.
Okay.
What is it?
Are you going somewhere nice?
Have you heard anything
from the investors?
You're asking a lot of questions today.
I'm sorry.
That night...
......when I visited the office.
You know why I did that, right?
(Lee Taeoh: Pairing restaurant...)
Dakyung, get in.
What are you doing here?
You didn't even call me.
I'm here to see my daughter of course.
What else?
Well, you saw me.
Bye.
-I'm busy.
-Hey!
I can't just leave when
you have a long face.
Get in. Let's go shopping.
I need to buy some clothes.
Hurry up.
Come on!
Chop-chop.
How do I look?
Does it look good on me?
Are you really not going
to buy the one we saw earlier?
I'll buy it for you.
Forget it. I don't need it.
It'll look great on you
if you lose a little weight.
Will you cut it out?
Oh my, that one looks cute.
How adorable!
My goodness. Hello there.
-Oh hello.
-Hello.
So pretty!
Hey! Come here and pick something for me.
Why are you buying this?
Did someone get pregnant?
My friend's son is in college,
and he knocked up a girl.
She'll be a grandmother next month.
How can they be so immature?
They're pretty nerveless
for 20-year-old kids.
As if becoming a grandma wasn't enough,
she has to raise the baby too!
She's about to go insane!
Just get something so we can go.
Hey. I don't want to be
a grandma too early.
Don't let me down.
Excuse me.
Can you have this wrapped?
Yes, thank you.
This goes in the bottom?
Why didn't you go inside?
How is it?
Isn't it nice to dine out?
I'm sure you're happy, Joonyoung.
I'm glad I didn't have to cook dinner.
I bet you're excited
for some good food.
I'm not a kid. I don't get
excited over such things.
Then?
The three of us coming to
a place like this in a long time.
Anyway,
this place looks nice.
You have a good eye.
I booked the hottest place in town.
Let's go in.
Oh my.
Dr. Ji!
What a coincidence.
Did you just finish dinner?
We came without a reservation.
We were just leaving because
they don't have tables.
I see.
Enjoy your evening.
Then...
Why don't you join us?
We made a reservation.
Oh no.
I'd hate to bother you.
I was wondering how I should
thank you for attending the funeral.
As long as it's okay with you,
you can join us.
Should we?
We're in a bit of trouble and
my husband will arrive soon.
Are you okay with that?
Oh, yes.
Sure.
Honey, over here!
Over here.
How are things with your boyfriend?
What's the matter?
Here.
Dakyung is...
...a social butterfly.
A lot of people misjudge her
because she has so many friends.
But she's not seeing anyone.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Maybe I heard her wrong.
I have homework to do.
I'll go now.
Okay.
My apologies.
Please excuse us.
He loves his son dearly.
They always stick together
wherever they go.
A son means a lot to his dad.
Mr. Lee is so good-looking.
I bet a lot of actresses
tried to flirt with him.
Of course there were.
But Taeoh is so devoted to his family.
Even if that ever happens,
it's nothing more...
...than just excretion for men.
Right. All men make mistakes.
Even Mr. Choi's wife was generous
enough to forgive him.
She's getting a building from him.
Hello?
You should watch your mouth
as a doctor.
Whatever happened to
doctor-patient confidentiality?
You said he'll get a divorce in two months
and have the baby with you.
I figured you already introduced
him to your parents.
I'm sorry if I caused you trouble.
(Min Hyunseo)
Who is it?
It's me.
Hyunseo...
What happened to you?
I'm sorry.
Do you mind if I stay for a few minutes?
I have decided.
I'm going to get an abortion.
I don't have money,
and parents whom I can depend on.
And the baby's father
beats me up all the time.
I'm not fit to be a mother.
The baby...
...would only be miserable.
You don't have to give me that look.
I feel so relieved now
that I've made a decision.
My life is important to me.
I don't want to end up
with a baby at my age.
You're lucky.
You don't have to worry
about this kind of thing.
You have parents who support you.
And soon,
you'll get married.
What's the matter?
Is something wrong?
Actually...
He's married.
What am I going to do?
I'm about to go crazy.
You said he was getting a divorce.
He wants to divorce her right now.
He can't put up with her anymore.
That woman is the problem though.
She'll continue to stay with him
even if she finds out.
That's how shameless she is.
What's she like?
She belittles people thinking
that she's better than everyone.
She is such a snob.
I bet he hates living
with a woman like her.
Well...
He said he's not sexually attracted
to her anymore.
He said sleeping with her
is just a responsibility.
Why would he want to sleep with her?
She's old now.
It's late. Why don't you stop?
Aren't you sleepy?
I'm almost done.
I'll be upstairs.
(Min Hyunseo)
(Son Jehyuk)
Did you find the answer
you were looking for?
Not yet.
What about tomorrow?
Shall we go for a drink?
Where's your mom?
Eat some fruits.
Enough with the cookies.
Aren't your lips too red?
Does it look weird?
I'm just saying.
What do you think, honey?
I thought you're going to a conference.
It's a little too much if you ask me.
It's been a while since I went out,
so I tried a new look.
But the reaction isn't so great.
It's a little too much,
but it's not bad.
I made dinner.
You just have to heat it up.
All right.
Hey, apparently this guy is moving teams.
-Really?
-Yes.
-That's a shame.
-He was pretty good.
Awe, man.
-This sucks.
-Money is everything.
You're early.
You look wonderful today.
But then again,
that's how you always look.
Can you pour me a glass?
I never thought this would happen.
What?
Spending time with you like this,
just the two of us.
But?
It's not as bad as I thought.
That's it? "Not bad"?
I should step up my game.
Why do people cheat anyway?
There are two types of men in the world.
The cheating type,
and the type that gets caught cheating.
Our instinct always get the better of us.
Instinct...
...is not only wired to the male brain.
My new place is in the middle of a repair,
so I've been staying at a hotel.
Yes.
I'll see you at the hospital soon.
Yes sir.
No way.
You still don't believe me?
I swear it was pure jealousy.
Men always try to exert
dominance on each other.
They pretend like they don't know,
but I know position Taeoh is in...
...among his friends.
You decided to provoke Taeoh that day,
because you felt like your perceived
hierarchy was being challenged.
You only used me as an excuse.
Am I wrong?
Taeoh doesn't deserve...
...someone like you.
You knew, right?
That I like you.
I had a rough idea.
And yet, you're here.
It's not a bad way...
...to get back on Taeoh.
You can say no.
It's up to you.
(Bird's Hill Hotel Parking Lot)
What are you doing here?
You could've just called.
Let's break up.
I couldn't help it yesterday.
-Let's calm down...
-I got rid of the baby.
What?
You happy now?
There's no reason for us
to see each other.
Are you leaving already?
I was hoping we can do another round.
I should go to work.
At 4:00 AM?
I have a family.
You're ruining the moment.
About Yerim...
Do you want to tell her or should I?
What?
Should I tell Taeoh?
You're welcome to do it if you want to.
But,
you don't want to break up
with Yerim at all.
If you want revenge, take it out on Taeoh.
Women are capable of cheating too.
We just refrain from cheating...
...because we believe that the
wedding vows must be kept sacred.
That's why I suggest you stop
fooling around like this.
Statements of T.O Entertainment's
corporate funds...
...and details of Taeoh's
personal account.
Find everything and hand it over to me.
Wait...
Am I being blackmailed?
Yes.
Instead of dealing with it alone,
you should seek professional help.
I found this at the restaurant
on your husband's birthday.
I'm sure you will find this...
...helpful.
Use a fork.
-I don't have one.
-Oh, there's my dad.
Wait here. I have to take his pictures.
If you don't believe me,
I'll go to Mr. Yeo right now
and tell him about us.
Are you crazy?
My son.
My house.
My life.
I won't let anything of
mine being taken away.
Lee Taeoh is the only thing
I want out of my life.
(The World of the Married)
This is the new neuropsychiatrist.
I'm Kim Yoonki.
About Sunwoo...
Did you notice anything strange about her?
I thought you two made up
when you sent her the flower basket.
Taeoh doesn't know yet, does he?
Don't worry.
I haven't said anything yet.
You should break up with him.
Don't let him walk all over you.
I guess your parents don't
know about your pregnancy.
That's why you shouldn't covet
what belongs to others.
Were you always this low?
When you were fooling around
with another girl,
you should've known that you
may never see your son again.
I couldn't help it.
Falling in love is not a sin!