It's obvious. No matter how we try to control it, the gossip has already spread everywhere it could reach.
This issue could be used against us at the shareholders' meeting.
Omo! This means that even if we don't do anything, she could be chased out with nothing to her name.
How many times must I tell you that it's more beneficial right now if she's with us?
Even if the remaining shareholders combine their shares,
as long as the major shareholders back Seong Wun's wife, there won't be any issue, right?
Yes. We're pursuing their whereabouts, but one of them is in South America and can't really be reached.
We're also looking for the other one.
Keep trying to reach those two major shareholders,
and let's wait and see what happens until the shareholders' meeting.
But then ... Do you think that Sister-in-law's memory has returned?
Don't you feel that she's overreacting, just because she heard us
speaking English and French?
What difference does it make if her memory has returned or not?
This is all because you trained her badly.
With her temper, imagine how it will be if she gets the control of her company? Would she listen to us as before?
I think it's actually better if her memory returns. My endurance has its limits.
I want to kick her around now.
Still, let's wait until the shareholders' meeting is over.
Watching her earlier, it seems we could get our hair pulled out if we aren’t careful.
So why didn’t you speak more cautiously?
You weren’t especially nice to her either, Nuna.
She said it's something a subordinate could say.
You ... seem a bit excited.
The scene earlier felt slightly cathartic to me.
Are you taking her side right now, Oppa?
Is that important?
As it is, no matter whose side I take, it won't influence how Hanju flows.
I'm sorry about today.
Do you have a particularly Confucian way of thinking?
Are you here to bicker with me like a condescending elder?
Sure. I lost my temper a bit.
But that can happen! You heard it all too, earlier.
Also, after a shocking experience, one might let out emotions violently—
You ... Who are you?
- What?
- I asked, who are you?
What's your identity?
Where is the real Mi Na?
What do you mean, "the real Mi Na"? Are you saying I'm not the real Kang Mi Na?
You truly can't remember anything?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Her behavior after the accident was recorded very thoroughly.
It seems that it would be very difficult to feign memory impairment.
The issue is, does this woman know this or not?
Of course. If she doesn't know,
she's also a victim, in a way.
Who knows what Hanju will do if you make a big deal out of it?
They may use her because of her fortune. More than that—
They could find the real Mi Na and do something to her.
Of course. Since, according to succession laws, the entirety of Yumin Group could be handed over to us.
I wouldn't put it past these people to do that.
For now, let's just see how the situation progresses.
I'm sorry.
You're so different from the usual Mi Na, so I think I was confused for a second—
Look at this. Before, you spoke to me without honorifics, so why the sudden politeness now?
But the strange one is actually you.
I’m “quite different from the usual Mi Na”?
This isn't proper attitude for a cousin-in-law who has just returned from the US.
It's my turn to ask. What's your identity?
Did we have some kind of relationship?
Perhaps...
an affair?
I've caused you much trouble.
Wait, wait! Are you just going to leave like that?
Are you just going to say all you want, apologize and then leave?
What do you want me to do?
Did you bring your car?
Pardon?
[One the Woman]
How did you get there without a car?
Someone without a car or taxi fare is in no position to talk.
It's not that I don't have a taxi fare.
The fare is in my bag. My bag is in the car.
And the car? It left without me.
What are you going to do now?
What can I do?
Since they probably don't know I overheard them, I'll see how much they keep lying to me.
Wait until I get my inheritance. They’re done for.
Will you be able to get the inheritance?
What are you saying, out of the blue?
Management rights are not inherited. You have to be appointed by shareholders.
Everyone who was here earlier is either a member of Yumin Group's shareholders’ meeting or knows someone who is.
By now, they'll have told everybody what they saw.
That the Yumin Group's heiress is mentally unstable and—
You're saying something strange.
Are you saying that I have a mental problem?
You heard earlier. That family is the one with mental issues!
Even if everyone else thinks you are abnormal, if you are considered normal within your own circle, you are normal.
Wow ...
In any case, after hearing the rumor, the shareholders will call for an extraordinary shareholders' meeting.
They might entertain a dismissal resolution. Because they can't allow their property to be controlled by a lunatic.
Amazing. Are you saying I'll be dismissed immediately because I said something that was right?
I know you're angry,
but making Hanju your enemy won't do you any good.
They are the only ones who will protect you until the shareholders' meeting.
Can I believe what you're saying?
Do as you wish. Believe it or not.
Perhaps ... are you saying "do as you wish" to avoid responsibility later?
Is that your ploy?
What do you want me to say?
How bad is this situation for me to have become so distrustful?
Whatever people say, I can't tell whether it's false or true,
whether they're a friend or foe and if I should smile or glare at them.
Why are we getting off together? Why don't you take the taxi home?
Don’t you have money to pay for the ride?
I have enough to pay. I also have something to say.
What else is there?
I want to say I’m sorry
that I made a joke before about you losing your memory.
If someone doesn't remember, shouldn't they be able to start over without being bound to the past?
I've wondered about that occasionally.
That's why I treated it so lightly when you said you couldn't remember.
I got out of the taxi to apologize to you.
Go on in.
Where are you crawling in, after humiliating your family?
When hurting your head, you should have been thoroughly injured so you couldn't move.
Just go and jump onto a car again.
I'm sorry.
Is that all?
Because I’m trying to speak carefully, I really have nothing more to say.
Now I finally understand you. Why you say everything you want.
What did you just say?
And here I thought you had returned to your old self.
But Sister-in-law, you were a bit mean to Seon Wu earlier.
How could you do that to a child, in front of all those people?
Do you look down on him because I raised him by myself?
What will you do if my Seon Wu is traumatized because of that?
After all, as a woman alone,
how can I raise him well by myself?
There’s no suitable role model,
and I worry so much every day.
I see. Don't worry. Just look at Mother and raise him, Sister-in-law.
- What?
- "Just don't be like her"... That's enough of a role model.
I know, right? I don't have to worry.
Oh no, Mother. I'm not saying she's right.
Today, I went too far. I'll go to my room.
She should have lost all her gusto.
Why is she still in such high spirits?
Even so, she is still being submissive, right, Mother?
Was that “being submissive”?
She was playing "strike people with words" at an expert level.
I was too submissive.
As expected, submissiveness isn't for me.
I'm sorry that I made a joke before about you losing your memory.
What was that? I was over it all anyway.
Why do my legs hurt so much? I'm sore all over.
This is why it hurts.
They shouldn't be new. Why am I getting blisters?
They don't "quite" fit perfectly.
Whether it’s a curse or a blessing, they say she has amnesia.
Since she's forgotten how she was treated, you only need to treat her with common sense. Why are you all—
Then it means that I knew everything these people had done.
Only the memories before a certain point disappeared.
Her memories are gone but the emotions will be left.
In truth, there weren't even any emotions.
It felt I was a blank page with everyone.
You were monitored according to your schedule, 24 hours a day.
Even your clothes. You only wore what was chosen for you.
Right now, it's heaven. Everyone is being nice to you.
Then I wouldn't have hidden anything in a place like this.
Nice car! Look at this! Oh my...
Wow ...
This car is so good!
Awesome! Look at the reverse cornering on this one!
Was I a hell of a good driver as well?
My goodness ...
Of course, everyone in this century needs this to multitask.
What? Whose car is that?
I said I wasn't able to answer the phone today.
Regardless ... How could you come here? What if someone sees you?
Who? Your wife?
Ah, I see ... Now that her situation has changed, don't tell me you're scared of upsetting her?
You're right that her situation has changed, but you've changed as well.
We've been together for quite a while. Why do you nag this much lately?
For now, go home. I'll call you later. Hurry and leave. Go.
Oh, it is you!
- Look at this. We got caught. I knew this would happen!
- Wow, this car is really nice!
Ah, move away.
What are you doing in there instead of going in?
Long time no see...
I heard you had a lot of bad things happen, but you seem to have overcome them quickly.
Who...?
For now, let's go inside.
Are you pretending you don't know me, now?
It seems I've seen you somewhere ... You look quite familiar.
The news. You saw her on the news.
She's announcer Park So Yi from SBC's 9 p.m. news.
What are you trying to do right now?
Should I tell you who I am, specifically?
Your husband and I have been seeing each other since before you met—
- You don't need to bring that up.
- What?
Well, She is ... No, I mean ...
Well, it's not a good story to begin with.
I see ... So, you two are having an affair and I'm aware of it?
And she shamelessly comes in and out of here?
Yes.
I'm not just a good driver. I'm patient as well.
I couldn't stand you when you did nothing but watched us like a voyeur.
But I can't stand you either when you're being sarcastic like this.
Let's stop. If I start screaming, you'll be embarrassed.
Embarrassed?
Wow. In our country, since when has the wife had to be embarrassed when the husband is the one cheating?
For someone on the news, you are very disrespectful.
Disrespectful?
How many times do I have to tell you? I've never once been disrespectful toward you.
I've always made sure he sleeps at home.
That's why I'm so mad. All he does at home is sleep.
He's useless! This isn't some kind of hotel!
Stop already! Let's go inside, all right?
Ah, let go! This is the only time you touch me!
Huh?
I'll just stand in the middle.
Look here. What exactly are we competing for?
This very confused man who doesn't even know whose side to take?
I don't want to be part of this fight where I have nothing to gain.
So, you two can make love or break up all you want.
But don't ever step into this house again. Understand?
Is your wife on drugs? What's up with her?
I know. Her face is no longer expressionless.
But I have no idea what she might be thinking.
What?
I have to find out.
Leave, all right?
How could she come here?
Your room is out front. What? Do you have amnesia too?
I didn't ask her to come. She suddenly arrived by herself.
By the way she drove in here so smoothly,
it's obvious she's been here more than once.
You're worse than her for making a perfectly good woman
sneak into someone else's garage. You're the jerk.
Fine. If making me into a jerk makes you feel better, go ahead.
No way. You're blaming me for calling you a jerk
when you're the one doing all kinds of bad stuff.
You're very smart with things like this, aren't you?
Fine, fine, I got it.
Stop saying a hundred things when one thing someone said bothers you.
Nothing good will come from the shareholders' meeting if more people suspect you've changed.
Don't act as if you care about me.
I'm being sincere, here.
Sincere? Hey, there's even a movie about how the Joker has sincere feelings.
I don't care about your feelings.
I have to wake up at 4 a.m...
and grill deodeok* that your father is craving, so I have to go to bed.
(Codonopsis lanceolata root)
Can you leave?
- I'm leaving.
- Good night!
Good night.
Good night, my foot.
The unit across the hallway must be empty.
The interior took a while but now it's finally presentable.
The layout is different in each unit.
This is the largest one, the "royal size."
But are you sure it's enough?
What's wrong with this place?
I came back to Korea to invest in social businesses. To me, this is like a palace.
Hello.
Hyeong-nim*.
(lit: "elder brother". Also said by subordinates to gangster bosses)
The ones held at the prosecution office are small fry, so there's no need to worry.
The prosecutors will get nothing out of them.
And the girl?
It seems she only knows the leader of the World Cup gang.
The others don't know her. We're searching the downtown Seopyeong area right now.
What's her identity? How can she disappear without a trace?
- Where is she hiding that even you can't find her?
- I'm sorry.
Downtown Seopyeong is not that big! Is it?
How could she look just like her? It's unbelievable.
- What will you do now?
- First, I have to find the real Mi Na.
Please, check the emergency department at every hospital in the country.
Do you plan to look for her without informing the Hanju people?
We have to meet the real Mi Na first. You said it too.
That we don't know what Hanju will do if they find that the current Kang Mi Na is fake.
Regardless of what happens, we must find the real one first.
They said that as the chairman, he wants to be first to arrive at the company. What's taking him so long?
At this point, the security guard ajeossi will take over.
Have you heard there will be an extraordinary shareholders' meeting today?
No, Father. As you can see, I've been cooking all morning.
How can you be in the kitchen right now, without a care in the world?
If you had asked for simple toast
rather than a full-course breakfast, I wouldn't have to be in the kitchen "without a care in the world."
It's very unfortunate.
- What about the major shareholders? Still no response?
- Yes.
Seeing that an extraordinary meeting is being held so quickly, it's not going to be easy.
Don't embarrass the entire family by letting it be known that you've lost your mind. Just stay home.
Father!
Won't you have some deodeok before you leave?
I peeled and pounded it all by myself.
Pound some more!
Good for you. Go make some juice so we can drink after eating.
Mom, you should stop.
Why? Compared to how I usually treat her, I'm being an angel right now.
What about your food?
Hey, I'm letting you off easily by just telling you to make juice.
If I went all out, you would be making Sujeonggwa* instead.
(cinnamon punch made from dried persimmons and ginger)
- Mom, stop it!
- What's wrong with you too? Did you eat something bad?
I have something to say to Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law, it's about the day you got hit by a car.
I had told you to go pick up my shoes but you never went there.
Since you're not going to the shareholders' meeting, go pick up my shoes from the department store.
Before all of that,
I need some more soup.
Things have finally gone back to normal.
Letting me off? For what?
What did I do so wrong?
I'm their daughter-in-law, not their slave.
Why is everyone ordering me around?
Today, we have to wash the curtains. Please hurry up.
Oh, my. Curtains?
Director. You heard them earlier, right?
They heard about an emergency shareholders' meeting because of me and suddenly their attitude changes.
At the shareholders' meeting, if they decide not to give me management rights nor shares, and I become penniless,
I will suffer so much starting tomorrow.
Can't you go easy on me today, for just one day?
All right. I'll take care of the curtains.
What? She's not denying it. That makes it even scarier.
Am I really going to be ruined?
Wow, seriously. Oh, this is really good. Damn.
Hello.
She's on vacation. She's not back yet.
Yes, thank you.
Calls asking for Prosecutor Jo keep coming in.
I mean, fine, let's say she took yesterday off too. But shouldn't she be back today?
I know. She may be corrupt, but she works diligently.
That's right. Diligently taking bribes.
Good morning.
Hello.
Isn't Prosecutor Jo in yet?
Why? What's going on? Is something up?
She was supposed to return yesterday, and she didn't apply for an extra day's leave.
- What about her phone?
- It's off.
Wow, she must be somewhere nice.
- If you do get hold of her, tell her to call me, please.
- Yes, sir.
Good day.
Shouldn't we tell him that the Second Division took the Hanju Group bribery case?
It seemed as if they were going to send a summons right away.
And what if we told him, then Prosecutor Jo gets angry with us when she returns?
Where is she? What is she doing? Does she know this is an emergency situation?
The number you're trying to reach...
It's still off.
It's an emergency.
I can't think straight after waking up at 4 a.m. every day.
I think I'll die of sleep deprivation before any emergency.
Excuse me, Director.
Yes?
Do you know what "four at breakfast, two at lunch, and three at dinner" means?
It's the number of times I set the table for yesterday's meals in this house.
Four times for breakfast. Lunch was twice. And three times for dinner.
Why don't they all eat at the same time?
Sleep-deprived every day,
doing all the housework, and a husband who cheats on me.
I can't live like this anymore. I'm going to that shareholders' meeting!
Whatever it takes, I'll go to the meeting and prove I'm perfectly sane.
And I'm going to take my inheritance. I'll no longer obediently do as I am ordered!
I won't keep being their docile little puppet!
When you come back, bring Han Seong Mi's shoes.
Yes, ma'am!
Trang.
Knife skills should be in the muscle memory, but ...
So strange.
Honey.
I'm on your side.
You're on my side, Honey?
Then why don't you just eat with the others,
instead of making me set the table twice
because you were sleeping while the others were eating?
There's no reason for you to look down on me that much, is there?
Something else you've forgotten, Honey,
is that you and I are the same class.
You chose me because I'm an heir of this family.
What nonsense is this?
Just saying. Have a nice day.
What is this car?
Oh, I bought it yesterday.
My foundation began distributing coal to the needy.
Those neighborhood alleys are so narrow that my car won't fit.
I'll use this for volunteer work.
You're very picky.
But Agassi, are you going to work?
Yes, I should at least go in twice a week.
In this day and age,
what if someone has a problem with that?
Why? Do you think my slacking off will upset everyone else?
That's not my problem. I was born with everything, so I don't have any tenacity.
Good for you.
Of course it is.
Is she crazy?
That I have to come back to set the dinner table for such people is just ...
If the shareholders' meeting doesn't go well, I'll just jump into the Han River.
Do I know how to swim?
No matter what, I'll make this shareholders' meeting go well!
Did the prime minister eventually decide to stay at Yumin Hotel?
Yes, that's correct.
It's the same person doing the same work, but isn't it strange?
I made our department store, distribution center, and construction company all number one.
So why can't I get our hotel on top as well?
The hotel industry is very conservative.
Do you think I'm asking because I don't know?
I'm sorry.
Why did you sue the car driver for damages in the recent hotel accident?
When we ultimately receive criticism over things like this, it casts a poor light on us as a service provider.
Public Relations was busy covering up the fact that the youngest madam was the accident victim,
so they followed standard procedure and didn't consider the driver's circumstances.
And all criticism falls on me.
I'm the immoral executive demanding compensation from an epileptic
who had a seizure because he couldn't afford medication.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
What's scheduled next?
There is nothing in particular for today.
Isn't there a meeting about a duty-free shop today?
Well... Due to the investigation, we may not obtain the permit to open a duty-free shop.
What are you talking about? That was all settled.
Another summons came.
I received a call from the chairman's secretary to wait for now.
Then let's go directly to the hospital.
If the Epilepsy Association gives an interview saying that we stigmatize patients, what will happen?
Make an appropriate donation to the association, otherwise everyone might continue to gossip about the accident.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't give so little that we get cursed at,
like last time, when I passed out watching the news.
Yes, ma'am.
Don't you know Madam is particularly sensitive to things like this?
Put a sentence in the article stating that she values the low-income class
and societal concerns.
Ma'am! Welcome.
I heard that my sister-in-law asked for something.
Yes. Our store is very grateful for
Hanju Group's "noblesse oblige", seeing that you always come to pick things up personally.
So I was totally their shuttle.
Pardon? What...
It's nothing. Please bring the shoes.
Of course.
I see Her ladyship here is also quick to catch on. We understand each other.
I know, right? So, hey, share the tip with our Prosecutor Jo too.
Aigoo, Your Ladyship!
I can't believe I'm running into you here.
Wasn't that tip really great? Did you already make a killing with it?
- Do you know me?
- I almost didn't recognize you.
You look so prosperous now.
Who am I?
I made a mistake.
You look very similar to someone I know.
I mistook you for someone else. I'm sorry.
No, wait a minute! Wait a minute!
- No, who–
- Ma'am!
Yes.
Is that someone you know?
No, I think I made a mistake.
"Your ladyship"?
It's obvious he's a nouveau riche scammer.
How did I live my life as Hanju's daughter-in-law?
He wasn't taking his epilepsy medication.
I found out he was trying to save the medicine money.
It's been a while since we closed our store because the business didn't do well.
Seok Ho, how could you cause such a big accident while trying to save a little bit of money?
You even hit someone.
The victim wasn't seriously injured.
But of all things, the car went in her direction.
That's what I'm saying.
What can we do? The hotel is like that because of us ...
That's the reason I'm here.
You don't need to worry.
Because Mr. Jang Seok Ho is lying in a sickbed like this, and all responsibility will be shifted to his wife,
I don't think it is right for us to ask for compensation.
Then ...
Actually, it's hardest for you who has to nurse someone.
I know that very well, as my grandfather was sick for a long time.
Use this to hire a caregiver, so that you can get some rest.
And ...
take care of yourself.
Among the upper class, there are people like you! Thank you.
"Upper class"? Why would you say that?
Actually, we had to give up all the insurance too.
There's no source of money.
So I was worried about how to compensate the hotel for everything ...
I was thinking of just dying.
Thank you ... thank you.
Wet wipes.
Why are there still so many vicious comments?
Did I throw a glass of water in someone's face? Or did I assault someone after paying them for it?
Do you still not know?
If someone like me makes a mistake, the green light goes on for everyone to join in dragging me down.
Even my father is like them.
I am sorry.
How much longer do I have to take care of each and every little thing myself?
In these kinds of cases, you can't quickly recover your memory just because you want to.
Is that so?
After you went back home, did you remember anything else?
No, everything seemed foreign to me.
In your case, if I put it simply,
it's not your memory itself that got damaged, but the process of remembering that has an issue.
So you'll recover.
The problem is how long it will take.
When you live your daily life without memories,
it can be stressful even if you're not aware of it.
So why don't you try to relax here?
All right.
Does anything come into your mind?
If I do remember my past, am I going to say everything in front of you?
- No, I'm not hypnotizing you.
- Ah...
By any chance, are you close with my mother-in-law?
No, not at all.
Medical personnel are obligated to keep patient confidentiality.
So, don't worry about it and relax.
Let's try to remember your past memories.
How would you have been before waking up in the hospital?
"How would you have been"?
Grandma! Grandma!
Then why don't we try to think about earlier memories rather than recent ones?
Let's try to think about your father and mother when you were young.
"Let's try to think."
What do you see?
I think it's my father, but the memories don't come easily...
It's painful.
How do you feel right now?
What kind of emotion do you feel?
If it makes you uncomfortable, you don't have to try too hard to remember.
Your father was the chairman of a large company, so he might have been extra stern.
If trying to recover your memories makes you stress more,
it's better not to try too hard. Let's wait for them to come back naturally.
Yes.
You don't have any symptoms at present, but if you suddenly experience headaches,
nausea or vomiting, please come to the hospital right away.
It could be helpful for you to visit the accident site,
but considering your condition, it's better not to do it for a while.
"The accident site"?
First of all, on that date, no female patient
who looked similar to Kang Mi Na, went to the ER.
I investigated the possibility of Chairman Kang Jang Su
having another child out of wedlock.
But at the time Kang Mi Na was born, because his wife pestered him to do it,
he was not just "tied", he had it completely "ripped off."*
(irreversible vasectomy)
There is no recovering from it.
His entire past was carefully scrutinized back then,
so there is almost no chance he has another child
who was born out of wedlock.
Is that so?
So just think of her as a woman who bears an uncanny resemblance to Kang Mi Na.
Let's go to the accident site.
I'm not your personal secretary...
You mean, let's go together, right?
Seven, eighty-three.
Eighty-three.
Look, Hyeong-nim. We're already very busy doing business.
So let's stop taking care of Yeon Ju's messes after her.
So if and when she returns, let's tell her we can't do it anymore.
Hyeong-nim, gangsters with a strong history don't hastily move just because someone asks for help.
We don't have a strong history.
That's right.
Anyhow, she has to come back first for us to say anything!
I think the situation is serious.
- Why?
- The Prosecutor's Office said she'd be back to work by yesterday.
But I called today, and they said she's not in the office and is still on vacation.
It sounds like this could be serious.
I think it's time for us to take action.
What? She's on the same team as those clumsy guys?
The people at Seopyeong said she sometimes appears here.
Maybe they look like that but there's more to them than meets the eye?
As they say, "a rotten slender shad is still a slender shad"*. They might have been strong in their prime.
Anyway, if you see them take any action, call the kids.
Yes, sir.
It means the car traveled at 80 km/hr speed and hit here.
I'll stand right here. Can you drive the car straight to here?
I mean...
To hit here if you start driving from there,
you have to turn the steering wheel at least once when you're over there.
The epileptic driver passed out, the car drove straight ahead but he still turned the steering wheel?
It does sound strange. But what do you want to find out?
I think he might have hit her on purpose.
- Why?
- We have to figure that out now.
If that car was trying to hit Kang Mi Na or the other woman.
Since things turned out this way, the fake Kang Mi Na has to get the inheritance.
What?
If someone was trying to kill the real Mi Na, that's the way to protect her.
When she's more important, it's harder for anyone to attack her.
Didn't you say you have to see Kang Mi Na in person?
Then shouldn't you focus on finding her first?
I'm trying to do that at the same time.
You know, there are two ways to find someone in the dark.
One is casting light on that person,
and the other is cast the light to me for them to find me.
Excuse me.
Are you going to the Yumin shareholders' meeting?
Just as I thought, your foresight is incredible, Eonni.
I wondered why your portfolio had stocks in the in-laws' business.
Is there any company in this field that's not in-laws in one way or another?
If you're here for your hair, just get it done and don't bother me.
I just heard something at the sauna.
Today's extraordinary shareholders' meeting at Sister-in-law's company
was called all of a sudden because her aunt strongly pushed for it.
But I heard that it's all because of this somebody who took action last night.
Did you want to step on the younger sister-in-law because of her behavior?
Or did you want to keep her in check because you think she'd be too strong if you leave her be?
What are you talking about?
Stop pretending to be a nice person! You're the most despicable.
You took advantage of her the most by pretending to care.
Also, on the day of her accident, you intended to frame her if the slush funds became an issue,
so you sent her to the auction.
Why are you telling me this right now?
Don't misunderstand me, Eonni.
I'm a rude person, but I have no intention of being a bad guy to you.
If I can't beat you, I should be on the same side as you.
Side? Don't dare think we will be sharing Hanju.
Hanju is one slab of gold.
If anyone grabs it, then you have to cut that wrist and take it back.
[Under construction]
The memory of the time of the accident.
According to my official schedule on that day,
I, Kang Mi Na, came out of the hotel after the auction.
But why didn't I get into my car
instead of standing here and getting hit?
As they say, the criminal usually returns to the scene of the incident.
Doesn't she look weird?
- How?
- What's with her clothes? Is she still undercover?
Is it already time?
Why does time fly when I'm doing anything other than house chores?
That's right. I have to pass this shareholders' meeting no matter what,
and get more of these dreamy times for myself.
Hey!
What happened to you?
Do you know me?
What's going on? Are you kidding me?
Why do all people who say they know look so shady?
What, what's going on?
Look who is here.
It's been a long time, lady.
What is this now?
Why are you pretending not to know me?
Don't you remember flying around and hitting us with your flying kicks?
What's going on, Hyeong-nim?
Did we bring them on our tail?
I-I became farsighted with age.
Don't you have something more to talk about with us in private?
I'm in a hurry to go somewhere very important.
How dare you pull that cheap trick?
I mean, I'd like to talk to you after I return from there.
Are you kidding me!
Right then, I knew it with certainty.
I'm definitely not Kang Mi Na!
Go get her!
She's my niece,
but because there are many bad rumors about her, I hesitate to let her be the head of the group.
First, because of the car accident,
there are rumors that she badly injured her head,
has lost her mind and is acting strangely.
So we need to look into this issue.
Since she has a memory disorder, she can be considered similar to a dementia patient.
Are you sure you'll be comfortable leaving Yumin to someone like this?
From what I heard, she has a considerable problem with her memory.
How can we let a person like that take the reins of our Yumin Group?
I think that now she should focus on treatment rather than business management.
I had hoped to hear her explanation today, but she hasn't arrived yet.
So I think that this might be her answer.
Why are you doing this to me? Do you know me?
I don't know! How do I know you?
I asked why you're doing this to me! Why am I so good at fighting?
Why are you doing this? Do you know me?
Say something!
My father founded the Yumin Group,
and my older brother developed it for his entire life.
All of our Yumin families' futures
are in our hands right now.
With that in mind, I hope you can think about it carefully.
First, according to Article 4, Paragraph 1 of the General Shareholders' Bylaws,
we will start the vote to determine if Ms. Kang Mi Na succeeds to the leadership of the Group.
What?
One of the two major shareholders, who between them hold 32% of Yumin Group, is Alex Chang.
His Korean name is Han Seung Wuk.
The other is Alex Chang's stepfather.
He's the one who married Mr. Han Seung Wuk's mother.
Also, Han Seung Wuk is currently in Korea.
Then, are you saying he'll be attending the shareholders' meeting?
I'm trying to shine the light on me so they can find me.
If anyone knows anything about the real Kang Mi Na, they'll contact Yumin.
Not Hanju.
[Yumin Group's Emergency Shareholders' Meeting]
Sorry for being late. I'm Alex, the shareholder of the Prix fund.
The other shareholder is my stepfather.
But he's residing outside of the country right now, so he made me his proxy.
Nuna, you climbed to your position by yourself, not because it was handed to you.
Work hard ... As hard as you can.
We hold a total of 32% of the shares of Yumin Electronics, Yumin's holding company.
And if you include the 22% inherited by Ms. Kang Mi Na,
it's the majority.
I believe Miss Kang Mi Na is the legitimate heir of the Yumin Group and can lead the Group,
and I support ... her succession to the Group's leadership.
I think some of you might disagree with this.
You can't help it. Hating someone has no power.
Consider voting. You vote for the person you like, not the one you don't like, correct?
Are you okay?
What is it? Who am I?
Why do I fight so well?
You're the successor of the Nammun gang. Of course you fight well.
"The Nammun gang"?
What is this? Why am I naturally so good at fighting?
Am I really a gangster?
Nothing good will come from the shareholders' meeting if more people suspect you've changed.
That the Yumin Group's heiress is mentally unstable.
Don't embarrass the entire family by letting it be known that you've lost your mind.
Run!
Since he didn't come to Grandfather's funeral
and I heard that he got a job in the US,
I relaxed too much.
His stepfather, who married his mother, has been living abroad for a long time.
His mother passed away last month.
- In the US?
- Yes.
I guess she didn't suffer in her later years, at least.
But he came to the shareholders' meeting and took Seong Wun's wife's side?
I think we need to find out his purpose.
Call him and ask him to come over for dinner.
Also, about Seong Wun's wife,
ever since she went through that big incident ...
Is this her true character?
I'm thinking about that as well.
I don't think she will be our puppet anymore.
The board of directors won't let the resolution pass easily.
So if they attack her and push her into a corner,
let's make it look as if we are helping her.
Yes. Besides her aunt, the other directors are from the maternal side of her family.
So I don't think they'll relinquish power easily to her.
Even if she were lucky and got the board of directors' approval,
she would eventually need to bend down for me.
Who am I? Why do I fight so well?
You're the successor of the Nammun gang.
Of course you fight well!
I mean, it's already ridiculous that I'm not Kang Mi Na.
But what? A gangster?
Wait.
Am I a twin, like Jeon Ji Hyun in the movie Assassination?
Except that I grew up in a weird place, and Kang Mi Na grew up in a chaebol house?
So what am I going to do?
How can I reveal that when my parents are dead?
[Dude Who Survives By Himself]
- What?
- I told you that I'm on your side, right?
Don't you ever forget about this.
What nonsense are you talking about?
I heard you were approved at the shareholders' meeting.
But where are you? Why didn't you go to the meeting?
What?
Honey. Honey?
I'm not Kang Mi Na.
Why did they pass the resolution by themselves?
Wait, no. Then I was making all that fuss when I'm not even Kang Mi Na?
What? Understand it?
You put it nicely by saying "understand it," but it means I should shut up and stay quiet!
Be quiet!
Is this a shouting match?
This is not a gambling place. Why are you shouting all of a sudden? You surprised me!
Sister-in-law, acting like this toward your husband's family is disrespectful. It's like spitting on yourself, so stop it!
Forget about it! Ptew! Ptew! Ptew!
Well, I didn't say anything wrong.
It's not like I risk being found dead somewhere.
After that, what is there to be afraid of, when she's a child with no parents or siblings?
Would anyone care about what happens to her while she lives in our house?
They might really kill me.
My God, what am I going to do?
Right. For now, I have to pretend more than ever
to be the daughter-in-law of that family, both in mind and in body.
I was born a daughter of a chaebol family
and lived my entire life as a chaebol.
Behave modestly.
- You're home, Sister-in-law!
- Yes.
Didn't you hear your father-in-law say that you shouldn't go out today?
Now that you got lucky and are rich, you treat your in-laws' words like dog crap.
Mother!
Why? Can't I even say this?
I'm not a celebrity. Can't I say what I have to, just because I might get cursed at?
If you go out, you should say where you're going!
How dare you show your feelings?
No matter how your situation has changed, how dare you?
Let's not talk back.
Your family's company hasn't become yours yet, and even if it does, do you think I care?
But I can't stand it without talking back!
Let's just not listen to what she's saying.
Think about something else. Let's try subtracting seven starting at one hundred.
Ninety-three ... Eighty-six ...
Even the daughters of a better family than you live quietly in their in-laws' house—
Seventy-nine...
Seventy-two...
What's going on with your eyes?
You'll kill someone with those eyes!
Sixty-five... fifty-eight*...
(The last two syllables of 58 in Korean sound like a curse word.)
- What did you say to me, Mother?
- My goodness!
You're out of control!
Hey! Do you want to be kicked out of this family?
Do you know what happens when a chaebol daughter-in-law gets sued for divorce?
If it becomes a lawsuit, in the process of paying alimony or dividing the assets,
your son's source of funds will become an issue, since he doesn't have any disclosed salary as an executive at Hanju Department Store,
nor does he have shares in any affiliate.
Why am I talking about this?
I guess you were thinking about this the whole time!
That's why when you heard about divorce, that came out of your mouth instantly!
- That's not true, Mother!
- "Your son," what?
"The source of funds"? What? Oh, my God!
No, Mother, I didn't mean—!
Sister-in-law, did you have to say it that way?
What?
That's what Mother-in-law implied.
And it made you angry.
I totally understand you!
I—uh—!
Why do my eyes get intense,
while my mouth says weird things?
What's inside my head?
I'm home.
Stop acting,
and since you're home, get ready and come inside now.
That didn't work.
Director, I believe you heard already, but I'm not just a stay-at-home housewife anymore,
I became CEO of an actual, respectable group.
Therefore, how long do I have to clean the cockles like this?
Director, I said, how long do I have to clean these?
"I'll never again eat seasoned cockles in my life."
Wash them until you think that.
That didn't work.
By the way, we always make a lot of food, as if we had a feast every day.
But why are we making more today?
The son of your father-in-law's older brother is coming.
He is your cousin-in-law, Youngest Madam.
Oh, the one who came from the US?
Yes.
Why do we have to do this much for him?
I don't think I'd prepare this much food even for someone who saved my life!
I don't know the details, but it seems he did a huge favor for this family today.
"A favor"?
How much of a loser is this family to owe so much to that kind of person?
Hello?
It's your aunt.
Auntie!
What's going on, Auntie!
I have something to talk about with you and wanted to see you someday—
What's that? I should come right now?
Of course! If you're asking me to come out right now,
then dinner is not important.
What's going on with her?
Hey, hey! Listen to me!
Yes, yes! Come to our hotel. I'll leave right now and wait for you.
What? R-Right now?
No, no. Wait a second. Wait.
Take your time! Of course!
I have cockles to wash, but what can I do?
Yes, yes! Oh, yes.
You need inborn ability for those tricks.
Is it possible to develop the ability after hitting your head?
Unbelievable.
Wait, wait one second!
- Can you turn the car around?
- Yes, ma'am.
She really isn't in good condition.
Help me, please.
If you say one word,
it can be resolved, Uncle.
My maternal uncle and mother's side-family,
you can save all of them!
Is there a reason for me to rescue your family?
There's the harm that your father did to our company.
How can you guarantee that your mother's family won't do that again?
This is your grandfather's wish as well.
Just as you're kneeling right now to protect your family,
I also have to defend my own family.
Are you dressed up because you were invited to dinner? Isn't that too tacky?
Why are you here and not going in?
Where are you going? You didn't even come to the shareholders' meeting.
How did you know I wasn't at the meeting?
What?
Ah, that is—
Are you perhaps following me?
Now that I think about it, that makes sense.
It makes sense for you to come to your grandfather's memorial service,
but you were spying on the family's conversation.
And you know I wasn't at the shareholders' meeting.
Now that you know that this family's not protecting me, do you think I'm a joke?
It's not like that—
In case you're following me to get something out of me,
forget about it! I'm not such a naive person.
So, what kind of work exactly will you be doing in Korea?
I'm going to sponsor companies that will make the world a better place.
I've also created a few non-profit corporations.
I heard about today's shareholders' meeting.
Human beings do things only for their own sake.
If it seems as if someone is doing something for others,
it's because there will be some benefit to it.
What's your real reason for returning to Korea?
I guess you feel guilty about something.
What is your goal?
Now you have a sturdy backing,
are you going to take Seong Wun's wife
and take back my company?
If you're saying "take back,"
does that mean it was originally mine?
You became much more confident than before.
You were a kid who couldn't even come into the house and kneeled and begged for help in the garden.
There's no reason for me not to be confident.
At least, I am not as powerless as my mother and I were back then.
You're misunderstanding something.
The reason your mother left this place with her head down was not due to lack of power,
it was because she willingly decided to shoulder it herself.
Well, try and do whatever you want to do.
I'll watch what you do.
Yes. Watch what I do until the end.
Let's see if this rain is just a passing shower,
or if it's a hurricane that takes away everything.
[Epilogue]
I'm Alex, the shareholder of the Prix fund.
I believe Miss Kang Mi Na is the legitimate heir of the Yumin Group and can lead the Group,
so I support ... her succession to the Group's leadership.
You got to where you are on your own.
No one handed it to you.
Keep doing your best ... As long as you can.
This place has been fully disinfected, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Why did they hit a person at my hotel! Also, with that dirty car.
It wasn't the spot we agreed on for the accident,
but Youngest Madam Kang Mi Na showed up all of a sudden,
so he panicked.
They can't do the work right and don't even die.
Poor things are always stupid and live long.
Do I have to pay for that thing's hospital fee?
My sister-in-law is very lucky.
She didn't die, but she also doesn't remember anything.
Watch her carefully for a while.
Yes, ma'am.
[One the Woman]
What is this?
It's the official history of the person named Kang Mi Na.
Your mother "willingly decided to shoulder it herself." What do you think that means?
That woman is a weapon to us.
I'm saying let's keep her, so we can use her when we need to.
Who is close with Prosecutor Jo?
Tell him to go to her house right now!
What if I'm arrested for impersonating Kang Mi Na when I'm just a gangster?
My sanity comes and goes, and comes and goes like this!
Why did she climb all the way up there, just for me to drag her down with my hands?
I'll show you how scary a speck of dust can be
by trampling on you people and climbinb up.