Oh no, why are they coming this way?
I'm not finished.
Send them all to the police.
I won't talk long.
I will make the new Hanju that I've always dreamed of.
Why is Seung Wuk in there?
- There was no good reason to kick him out.
- What about the rest?
The two that were trespassing were sent to the police office,
but Jo Yeon Ju isn't a current offender,
and a prosecutor from Seopyeong Branch Office is here too so ...
Go ahead.
When did we start sending just the guilty people to jail?
Why don't you let it slide for today?
That prosecutor will be demoted soon anyway,
so all the things she's doing will end in just a few days.
"End in just a few days" ...
Is that woman, Jo Yeon Ju, going to disappear in a few days or something?
Why was the team leader getting out of the car?
He was planning with us from start to end. Why is he suddenly acting like that?
If that was his plan, wasn't he fooling us from the start?
I don't know.
- There must be some reason behind it.
- "Reason"?
What reason can there be in this situation?
All that remains is the Jeong Do Wu side of it, right?
No matter how much he's questioned,
he stubbornly keeps saying that it was all his doing.
Since your uncles are not around,
I'll go to Kang Mi Na's hospital. What about you?
Don't ask me, I can't trust anyone.
There might be a traitor among us.
She must've been quite shocked.
I guess so.
I am Director Kim Gyeon Sin. Do you know that?
Yes, Director.
Can I see ...
Manager Jeong Do Wu's résumé  from when he first joined the company?
Is there no possibility of recovery?
We're at a stage where it's too late to do anything.
By the way, there's something strange.
What is it?
The number you are calling is unavailable, you may leave a message—
The number you are calling is unavailable—
- Hello?
- Oh, incredible, he answered!
Stop calling me!
Do you think I can answer right away in a situation like this?
It's because I'm so frustrated! What's going on!?
Tell Seung Wuk
that I'm sorry.
Whatever! Let's meet up first.
No, wait ... How can I meet you if I don't trust you?
But I can't just not meet up ...
Something came up.
I'll tell you the details when we catch up.
Can I really just meet up with you?
You're not trying weird things again, right?
I'm not that much of a bad guy.
If I was really going to be a spy,
I wouldn't have been standing next to Han Seung Hye in the open.
Do we have to talk at such a noisy place?
Haven't you seen the movies?
If you whisper in a quiet place because it's something important, someone will eavesdrop for sure.
We need to talk casually at a noisy place like this,
so no one pays attention to us.
And even if we're bugged, it's hard to hear us in a place like this.
Also, why would I trust you and meet
in a secluded place, just the two of us?
What on earth ...
So what happened?
The truth is ...
when Seung Wuk's father passed away, I already knew about the account books.
If I had mentioned that to CEO Han,
he might not have gone to the factory.
Oh my ... How could
you hide that fact until now?
By nature,
it's hard for people to admit their wrongdoings.
Human beings are like that.
Even so, since you were so close to him, you should have been loyal.
Loyalty? Loyalty is great and all,
but will "loyalty" alone keep paying me one million won*  (≈$860)  every month?
My father has been in hospital for the last 20 years.
Loyalty is a luxury to someone like me.
Anyway, I guess there's no secret in this world. Han Seung Hye blackmailed me with that fact.
So I had no choice.
So now what are you going to do?
What do you want me to do?
Team Leader, even with your backstory, this isn't right.
Will you live as a chaebol's gofer* for the rest of your life?
(Errand boy)
I mean, you can just open an attorney's office.
That's easy to say.
I've never had a high position in the law, nor am I from a huge law firm.
it's not like I just spend a penny or two on my household.
You're still daydreaming.
What's wrong with being a chaebol's gofer?
I told you, if I'm shunned by this side,
I'll have to find a way to live on the other side.
Prosecutor Jo Yeon Ju, you know well about gangsters.
Even the lowest gang member
takes the head of the boss when betraying the gang.
How can I go to the other side with nothing in my hands?
What ...
Did you ...
put something in this?
Damn that team leader.
How much did he put in that drink?
I know, right?
I told him I have to kill you in front of my eyes, so he must've used just enough to keep you alive.
Look here, Director Han Seung Hye.
What I'm most confident with is
a private, undisturbed one-on-one interrogation.
Whether I had to make a deal, or lie, or yell,
if I decided to,
I always got the answer I wanted from the suspect.
So? Are you going to try and interrogate me in that state?
No. Today, I'll just ask for a favor.
Turn yourself in. The recording from when you killed CEO Han Gang Sik,
and hit my grandmother, I heard it all.
It was an accident, wasn't it?
You must still believe you are a prosecutor.
What if I turn myself in? The law is always on the side of the strongest.
What happened then slid away without anyone knowing.
At that time, if Prosecutor Ryu Seung Deok
hadn't turned a blind eye for his own benefit,
you wouldn't have turned out like this.
Turn yourself in, even if it's late.
Also the fact that you tried to kill the real Kang Mi Na in a car accident,
and the fact that you killed Lee Bong Sik, the man I staked my whole prosecutor career on,
and even the fact that you killed Jang Seok Ho and his wife at the reservoir...
just confess to them all ... and turn yourself in.
Why would I? Do you have any evidence?
All I did was give orders, so there's no evidence.
That's why you're begging me to turn myself in.
I dealt with them without getting a single drop of blood on my own hands.
You and the real Kang Mi Na ...
will both become the same soon.
How many
did you admit to murdering just now?
What?
In the case of requesting or plotting murder using power or rank,
the sentence is death, or five or more years in prison.
I told you, I always get the answer I want.
This whole time, did you think I was just a player in your game?
Do you know how to attack those chaebols?
Their weakness is this.
They're people who think they've got where they are on their own,
so they believe that they are always right.
You have to attack that part.
Are you telling me to be a traitor just like Han Seung Hye wants?
It's great! You fit the role perfectly!
I lived my life that way because I had to,
how could you treat me like Yeopo* who keeps changing teams?
(A character in the Chinese story, "Three Kingdoms")
Oh, come on! All right.
Team Leader, you are like
a  lotus flower that blooms in mud, very virtuous.
Is that good enough?
I mean, if you say you won't do it,
I can't force you.
I told you before,
you should use a pawn to catch a queen.
If you don't have power, no one keeps you in check,
so it's possible to change teams.
Then, will you do it?
If you were going to do it anyway, why did you make such a fuss?
Try being an office worker for 30 years.
You can't say "I'll do it" without protest.
Once Han Seung Hye gets the team leader on her side, it's my turn.
She'll think I'll be a bother, just as I was on the inauguration day.
She'll try to get rid of me at any cost.
Do you think she'll trust me 100%?
That's why we need some appetizing bait.
All the original evidence we have, take it to her.
And when she says she wants to kill me, make it so she can.
I'm against it. I can't gamble with your life.
Don't worry. As long as we make her join the gambling,
I can get her to confess for sure.
Even if you get the confession, how are you going to arrest her?
"If bugs get into the rice bag,"
"you have to leave it on a rooftop with lots of sunlight."
Then the bugs will crawl out of the dark, wet rice.
So you're saying that we need to publicly humiliate her in broad daylight,
and in a very luxurious way.
A public humiliation ...
Just as you said, our country's laws are mostly on the side of those with power,
but once in a while, the laws support the weak.
That is, when it is publicized.
Are you delirious from being close to death? What are you talking about?
That's why I give this advice to those in unfair situations.
"If you think you'll get beaten up by people with power,"
"then, make sure you get beaten up where there is CCTV."
If you get beaten up where no one can see you and you land a lucky punch,
then if the powerful sue you,
there will be no way to prove what happened.
Today, I did nothing.
You just ruined yourself by being reckless.
And the thing that makes bad people become reckless
is that divine providence from above.
Han Seung Hye, that lady acted like she's some really nice person,
but it turns out she's crap! Crap!
Ryu Seung Deok is the Chief District Prosecutor ...
Our channel, "The Man Who Teaches You Law,"
checked the statute of limitations right away,
and for Chief District Prosecutor Ryu Seung Deok, the statute of limitations has passed,
so legally bringing him to justice seems improbable,
do you think that makes sense?
- It's unbelievable!
- Isn't this insane?
Does this make sense?
The world is so dirty! Dirty!
Everything you just said, from beginning to end,
was broadcast live.
How much of that stuff did he put in my drink?
I said so, didn't I? That I won't be fooled twice.
Are you all right?
They're filming here, so let's get out.
♫  Reaches toward me   ♫
♫  and leads me to you all the pain is healed now.  ♫
♫  I will hug   ♫
♫  and wrap you.  ♫
♫  Like a warm  ♫
♫  breeze  ♫
Hey, Honey, it's me. I can't come home for a few days.
And also, our house might get searched,
so take everything that's worth anything and go somewhere else.
Your mother's house or your friend's house. You have many places!
Seonbae, if I'm inspected, all my accounts and phone calls will get revealed.
Then it's over for me. I'm dead.
Seonbae, I blocked everything for you last time
so this time, please save me.
Seonbae, Seonbae—... Hello?
Hello!
Prosecution!
South Korea!
What did they ever do for me!
I want to go back!
When a person is too angry,
they can say things that are not true.
That woman was spewing such nonsense, so ...
What are you all doing?
Are you going to leave me to splutter on?
Well, first of all, she filmed without your consent.
So if she tries to use it as legal evidence,
we can make it an issue.
In the worst case, we can says it's a deepfake*,
(A skillfully edited video)
and that it's fake news.
We stopped all the live videos,
and it wasn't on prime-time news or anything, so don't worry.
You have all of the evidence anyway, right?
Lee Bong Sik's list,
the bugging device I took,
and the USB from Kang Mi Na, I brought all of them. Everything!
This is so harsh!
I'm the oldest here, yet both of you are ordering me around.
You had me install that webcam or whatever on the ceiling of the basement,
and it took so much labor. Do you realize the effort?
I didn't just sit around either.
First of all, I'm the one who recruited all the live streamers,
- and I went to hospitals here and there—
- Right! And was I just sitting around?
You put so much of that drug in the water, my head still hurts!
- I know. You could've just pretended to add some.
- That's what I'm saying!
I mean, she told me to make it realistic!
I thought you might care about me too much,
and just give me plain water.
We didn't need to go so "method",* did we?
(Referring to "Method acting")
Wow, when I recall your evil laugh as you looked at me,
it still gives me the creeps ...
You said they would surely bug us,
so I had to act correctly!
You didn't have to talk about it so seriously either!
"Chaebol's gofer"?
Gofer?!
And calling me a hundred times?
And who raged at me as soon as I answered the phone?
I mean, at the inauguration,
did we decide that you'd get out of her car! No, we didn't!
When you got out so confidently, I was shocked!
How can I trust someone whose thoughts show so clearly on her face,
and let her act?
You had to be authentically shocked for Han Seung Hye to believe it!
I told you, he had a reason.
What "reason"!
In the worst case scenario, we have that criminal who confessed for the incident 14 years ago.
How about pinning all the crimes on him?
When we were told to take a break,
that was the signal.
Chairwoman Kang Mi Na, Lee Bong Sik, Jang Seok Ho,
the Director of Sun Star gallery ...
Do you admit to murdering these people,
and did Managing Director Han Seung Hye order the murders?
Yes.
That incident from 14 years ago,
was that also her doing?
Yes.
Why are you suddenly changing
all your previous testimony?
Your little sister
was hospitalized for a long time, wasn't she?
When she was little,
I heard she had surgery thanks to Han Seong Hye.
That's right.
If there had been an opportunity to fix her illness afterwards,
what would Han Seong Hye have done?
She would have made it possible by any means.
It's the résumé of Manager Jeong Do Wu who worked in Hanju security.
He only had his grandparents and a younger sister.
Apparently she underwent major surgery for acute kidney failure as soon as he was hired.
And Han Seong Hye helped with that.
Han Seong Hye did? Why?
She was given Hanju Fashion at a young age,
so perhaps she wanted to build a reputation of "noblesse oblige".*
(People of privilege acting honorably)
Apparently she went around looking for workers in such circumstances.
So all that money
has been going toward his younger sister until now?
There is something strange.
There were many chances for her acute kidney failure to heal.
She was named several times on the rotation list for kidney donation,
but the patient refused surgery.
Did Mr. Jeong Do Wu refuse the surgery?
Ah, Ms. Han Seong Hye takes the calls about this matter.
It was she who refused surgery.
That's why the patient's condition worsened.
She wanted to keep your weakness, so she could use you as her servant.
She's someone who held a person's life hostage.
I just asked why you're retracting your testimony.
Because ...
I feel betrayed.
Here's the script.
The news for your last day is quite extravagant.
I heard that Han Seong Hye used tabloid articles
to hurt you and her brother and kick you off the pedestal.
So you're bound to be fired.
So what. Did you come here to see how I'm doing?
No. Well, it did happen because of your own fault,
but you've worked hard to get to your position,
so I was hoping you'd be able to do a better job
as a journalist, and as an anchor.
All right, shall we begin?
Hold on!
Yes, I got it.
Let's leave out everything related to Hanju.
Apparently Hanju is threatening to remove all their ads.
Okay, let's begin!
Three, two, one!
This is your first piece of news.
Urgent news. This evening, Chairwoman Han Seong Hye's evil deeds
were sent out in a live broadcast, causing an uproar.
- What is she doing?
- She—
What's wrong with her?
Hey, you, you, you, have you gone mad?
Hey!
For those who missed the live broadcast,
our company, SBC, was planning to tell you the details.
But because Hanju Group threatened to pull all its ads
if one word this event gets out,
we are unable to mention it. For that,
and for being a news anchor who is unable to deliver the truth,
I apologize.
There must be reasons why Hanju is preventing reports.
Did she drink?
Next. Due to our recent stock market—
Eonni's gone mad, right?
No matter how much she wants the company ...
She's gone mad, completely mad.
- We know nothing.
- Mom ...
Right now, getting involved with Seong Hye
means we'll all fall together.
Do you want to sink with her?
Don't take her calls, even if she does ring.
What will you do about attending the Substantial Examination of Warrant Validity?
I'm not going.
Nowadays, if you don't appear,
it's seen as a sign for an arrest as a means of penance ...
Don't make me say it twice.
I'm not going.
Understood.
Yes, Congressman. It's me, Director Han Seong Hye.
Ah, I see.
Then when can I call you?
Yes.
Hello, Mr. Minister. I'm Director Han Seong Hye—
Han Seong Hye?
Yes, Director Han Seong Hye?
Chief Prosecutor?
About this incident—
It's good of you to call me. Save me.
You know all the strings you have? Congress, Senate, everywhere else?
You must have more strings than I do.
Why didn't you give their sons retirement congratulatory funds and stuff?
Last time, the Wu—
That's the real Han Seong Hye. Han Seong Hye.
- Oh, he's coming out!
- He's here!
You issued a warrant for almost the entire Hanju family that includes past crimes and bribes. Are you confident of seeing this to the end?
You put the Seopyeong gangs in jail because they were connected to Hanju.
Why have you announced a war against both the gangs and chaebols?
What do you mean?
So from now on, do you have another goal as a prosecutor?
I didn't prosecute them for my own benefit,
I just prosecuted them because they were criminals.
Isn't that the role of prosecutors?
- Prosecutor, Prosecutor!
- Did you get that?
One more word, please!
It doesn't matter what!
My position right now is just like this leaf.
Damn, are you crying?
Goodness, look at those dark circles!
You haven't slept at all, have you?
Who can't sleep? Who? I slept very well!
I heard that you expressed your intention to resign in a rush yesterday, but it wasn't processed due to the press running wild.
Everyone who is investigating me is my subordinate,
and I ... am the law!
I know it better than you guys!
It's scarier because you know it better!
Do you need to go this far?
Do you need to put me in jail?
I mean, did I kill someone or what?
I just ... I just closed my eyes for them once!
Among the professionals around me,
if we just talked to them, no one would admit their wrongdoing unless we took it this far.
You damn—... What kind of impossible normality is that?
Look at this! You're not admitting to it.
Jo Yeon Ju!
Do you think I won't be able to climb back up? Huh?
You are bound to see me sometime soon.
Yeah, all right, whatever.
I have no interest
in what evil people promise.
Good work!
Yes, what is it?
Kang Mi Na, woke up.
I managed to pass the bar exam and become a prosecutor,
thanks to my amazing memory and deduction skills,
and I was able to solve all the obstacles before me ...
How could I pretend to sleep like Kang Mi Na?
I guess Kang Mi Na even slept like a perfect lady.
Well ...
Did you say you're two years older than Kang Mi Na?
It unlocked. It's today's date.
It was your birthday.
Mi Na!
He will be all right.
Oppa is different than he looks.
I mean, why do I find my amazing memory and deduction skills to be a burden right now?
Why am I going through all kinds of scenarios of my own imagination?
Stop deducing, Jo Yeon Ju, you ajumma!
Damn it!
Let's hurry and go inside. She says she must meet you, Yeon Ju.
Oh, I see. But ...
how about you go in first?
Just me?
Why? How about you, Yeon Ju?
Well ...
You haven't seen her in a long time. I'm sure you have a lot to say to each other.
I'm sure she's not feeling settled.
People's feelings are usually pretty simple.
If you truly like someone, it's not that complicated.
Let's go in.
Right.
I'm happy to meet you, Ms. Jo Yeon Ju.
Let me introduce myself formally. I'm Kang Mi Na.
Oh, yes. Nice to meet you.
Long time no see, Oppa.
So, what happened?
I don't even know.
When I woke up, everything was back in its place.
But how could we look exactly the same?
I know. I checked with my father so many times.
But seeing how my father kept emphasizing that he'd want me to be a rich man's daughter,
I think my mom gave birth to me.
As for me, my aunt was in the labor room
and saw my mother giving birth to me right next to her.
She ran a paternity test as soon as I was born.
Geez, that aunt of yours.
But ... anyway ...
I'm sorry that I inadvertently pretended to be you for so long.
I think I'm the one who should apologize.
Han Seong Hye did that to you while trying to kill me.
I thought that she'd merely accuse me
of being a drug addict then send me to a psychiatric ward.
That was so naive of me.
You had no idea. So you couldn't help it.
Had you known there would be an airplane accident, you wouldn't have run away like that.
If I hadn't run away then,
right after the airplane accident,
I would've been killed without anyone's knowledge.
Thanks to the two of you, I'm alive today.
But why didn't you take your tablet with you?
At first, I was going to meet Oppa overseas
and give it to him somehow.
All I could do was to run away,
but I wanted to see someone destroy Hanju.
But right before I ran away,
I changed my mind.
Why?
When my life hit rock bottom,
I started considering other people's lives.
I thought that manipulating Oppa's life any further for my sake,
would be wrong.
More than anyone ...
I want to apologize to you, Oppa.
After I returned to Korea
and saw you living with my face,
I started wondering if I was too cowardly all this time.
That's why I decided to find
Han Seung Hye's weaknesses.
Most of my life was filled with pain until now.
But there were some nice gifts along the way.
I think you two were like that for me.
I feel sorry toward the two of you,
and I'm grateful.
So what other crimes were committed by Han Seung Hye that aren't revealed yet?
As for that, everyone at Hanju
is being punished by the law according to their own crimes,
except for my mother-in-law.
That's right.
Except for torturing her daughter-in-law, she hasn't broken the law herself.
As for those additional crimes,
I think that more than anything, they will be extremely painful for my mother-in-law.
So I'd like to tell her myself.
It's also my share
of revenge.
I thought you were in a coma.
You sure live a long life.
How dare you show up here?
Did you come to see what I'm doing in this big house all by myself?
You're still the same.
I almost died several times by your daughter's orders.
Don't you want to say any words of apology?
So? Did you die?
You didn't die.
You didn't die and you will get to live in wealth.
Stop being so arrogant. Do you think you gained the world?
In the end, you were afraid of us and wanted to hide behind your new face.
Just because I changed my face,
do I look like I'm hiding behind it?
And so? What are you trying to do now?
I'm here because I have something to tell you,
and I'll leave after I say what I have to say.
As you said, I have a tenacious lifeline,
so I managed to survive many times.
But why did your oldest son die in vain
at the same time Father tried to overlook Han Seong Hye
and promote your oldest son to the Vice Chairman position?
What are you saying?
I'm so tired ...
What are you feeding me?
Did Nuna tell you to do it?
I won't become a victim like Hyeong because of not being careful.
I won't become a victim.
I wont ...
Brother-in-law went to volunteer at the animal shelter with Sister-in-law
and died of an asthma attack.
Since then, you hated hearing of volunteering at animal shelters,
so I ended up going there alone.
As expected, the dog shampoo that Sister-in-law had donated to the shelter that day
contained an ingredient that could be lethal for asthma sufferers.
If only Brother-in-law's asthma inhaler, which he always carried, had been with him,
he could've survived.
But it disappeared that day.
As to where it was found,
why don't you ask your second son?
Because he was so afraid of his Nuna, he kept his mouth shut, even though he knew all along.
I just want to live quietly.
I don't want to end up like Hyeong.
I tried to get Director Han Seong Hye to confess to all she had done.
But under the circumstances, I didn't think it would mean much
to add one more crime to those she had committed.
So I'm only telling you, Mother.
Shut that mouth of yours. Get out of here right this minute!
You won't be going to jail for torturing me, Mother.
But instead, your beloved son was driven to his death by another child of yours,
and the other child kept quiet even though he knew.
Please keep thinking about this and, for the rest of your life,
live locked up in the prison that you built for yourself.
We will now reveal the results of voting on the agenda item
about the dismissal of the Hanju family.
Here. Am I too late?
We need 66.7% of attendees to vote "Yes."
Since the result did not meet the required number of votes, the agenda item has not passed.
Those who opposed their dismissal! Are you crazy?
How could we let owners like them run the company?
You don't have to be moral to run a company. That is a separate matter.
What the hell is he saying?
Excuse me.
I'm late. Can we vote again?
- What?
- Who's that?
Who are you?
Is Director Kim that powerful?
Hanju Group's "Director" title isn't to be taken lightly.
I'm sure Grandpa gave her the best stocks, and that she has quite an influence among the shareholders.
I guess late bloomers can be quite scary.
She always said she was neutral. Must she show her true colors going there so late?
At the end of a long, drawn-out re-voting at the Hanju Group's Shareholders' Meeting,
with 67.1% "Yes" votes and 32.9% "No" votes,
the dismissal of Chairman Han Yeong Sik's family has been decided.
With this, Chairman Han Yeong Sik's family has become the first leading family to be dismissed by shareholders.
And an arrest warrant for Director Han Seong Hye has been finally issued,
and she will be arrested soon.
The Deputy Chief Prosecutor at the Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office in charge of the warrants said
that suspicions are justified and that she may choose to flee, as he issued her warrant.
Early this early morning at a reservoir in Gyeonggido,
missing Managing Director Han Seong Hye was found dead. She was due to be arrested.
At the time of discovery, the corpse was extremely damaged.
But the clothes and rings she was wearing at the time
were on the body.
In other news, Hanju's executives held a meeting and brought in Han Seung Wuk to head the company.
He is the late Chairman Han Gang Sik's son.
Hanju Group memorialized the late Chairman Han Gang Sik as an honorary Chairman
as they expressed sorrow for the death of Managing Director Han Seong Hye.
They canceled the new Chairman's installation ceremony and other events.
You must be going to Vietnam.
Do you want me to tell you a Vietnamese proverb?
"Keep walking outdoors in the dark, and you will eventually encounter a ghost."
(In Vietnamese)
This is what it is in Korean.
"Misbehavior eventually catches up with you."
How did you ...
I know people like you too well.
The true cowards can't kill themselves. Do you know why?
Dying is so scary.
So I looked at the corpse very carefully.
The clothes and shoes,
and the watch and rings were all yours.
But the underwear!
It wasn't what I had hand-washed at your house at one point.
How dare you pretend to die with dignity by suicide?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Turn yourself in. Okay?
I was going to let her be elegant to the end.
But it can't be.
Strike!
Out!
I guess Han Seong Hye thought that everyone was afraid
to admit to their wrongdoings from their past and to apologize.
But that's only for people like her.
She must've thought that you'd be hiding everything from me.
It was tough for me to tell you, too.
But no one in this world is perfect.
You just have to know that and not repeat your mistakes.
I feel much better now that I've paid my debt from that time.
Hey, Seung Wuk!
Yes?
I've quit my job at the company, and I've repaid my debt now.
I'll just be an ajeossi to you now.
Let me live in peace.
Don't make me drive anymore.
I'm off. You have a friend, right?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I've just finished my sprint, but I feel like
I'm now running a marathon. That's how I feel.
Now I'm wondering where I should run,
and where my place is.
Your place?
You said this a long time ago.
Wherever you are and whatever you're doing,
if something happens,
you don't want to live a life
where you only wonder what happens to your company stocks.
So I've been thinking,
how should I live?
I'm not sure, though.
From long ago until now,
I've never lived without having a goal or revenge in mind.
Now that all that is over, I have no idea what I should do with my life.
Let me know when you find your answer.
I guess you've found what you need to do.
I'll be waiting for you.
Who sent that?
The owner?
The rumor has it that your sashimi is so fresh.
You even opened up your second branch.
Stop being mad.
Are you still mad about going to the police station?
Hey! ... Hey ...
Do you think we're angry about going to the police station?
It's because you didn't tell us that you were a fake.
Don't talk to me. Many people are asking us about opening our branch. I'm crazy busy.
- Oh-ho?
- Stop it already.
Come on now.
Right, Uncle Pil Gyu? As expected ...
- Where is my father?
- I won't tell you.
I'm mad at you!
- You came.
- Oh, yes.
With a second branch, you need to hand out flyers to attract customers.
These flowers won't do it.
How come
you're more clueless than me, who has been behind bars for over ten years?
Who's inspired by flyers these days?
Everyone gives out coupons through apps and promotes through SNS*.
(Social Network Service)
We have dinner reservations already booked.
Why open a store as soon as you were released? You should have taken a break.
Uncle Pil Gyu says your wrist will hurt if you use the knife too much. Take this.
You should've bought it after finding out what my role is at this sashimi place.
I never even used a knife when I was with a gang. Why would I use one now?
We have a chef.
Then I guess I'll take it back.
Aigoo, but still ...
How can you take it back?
I can hurt my joints while counting money.
Take it slow.
I can see that I don't need to worry about you anymore.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
All right.
- Yeon Ju ...
- Don't—
Don't say anything mushy.
Don't say anything.
Aigoo, give me a napkin. This got on my hand.
I'll go now.
Be careful.
Yes.
I'm really leaving.
Stress, stress.
They always tell me to resign.
I mean why? Over what?
Why do they pick on me whenever they hold a stockholders' meeting?
Did I ever sneak around with someone and steal the money?
What have I done that they keep telling me to bring in professional management?
It's because you keep uselessly putting together donation funds for the foundation.
That's why the shareholders
keep misunderstanding it as a fund laundering account.
I'd love to smash her over the head.
She's so quick.
How did she find out about fund laundering?
I finally got rid of the fake one and now the real one shows up.
But the real one isn't too easy.
Is she real for sure?
The good times are gone. Shit!
I just don't get it.
Isn't this a useless effort and only for show?
It's better for people like us to pay more taxes.
How many briquettes can we deliver as volunteers?
And Sister-in-law, I don't understand you even more.
Why did you come back and suffer voluntarily?
I went back to my family and no one welcomed me there either.
Never mind what else, I couldn't bear to see my Seon Wu walk on eggshells since he's the only grandson.
I just couldn't bear it.
Don't you think we know?
You thought Oppa Seung Wu would take over Hanju all by himself.
But they unexpectedly brought in professional management.
You figured, "Ah, my Seon Wu might get a chance, too."
That's why you're back.
If you know that so well,
why don't you work hard and stop fiddling around?
Father says an economic offense doesn't even count as an offense.
He says he'll return when he's released.
I heard he's gnashing his teeth in prison.
We should help him too!
Father is too much.
But how did Mother change so much?
She's got no energy.
Ninety-one.
Ninety-two.
Ninety-three.
Ninety-four.
Ninety-five.
Ninety-six.
Ninety-seven.
Ninety-eight.
Ninety-nine.
One hundred.
I won't go down like this.
I won't go down.
I will not go down.
How dare you do this to me.
How dare you!
How many times do I have to say it?
I have no interest in how wicked people end up.
I don't care if they do squats or make bodybuilding videos in prison.
Don't even tell me about stuff like that.
But I heard you opened up your own practice.
You spread the word throughout the industry.
For me to run the business, word of mouth is important.
Anyway, your father has been released and is settling down.
You must feel relieved.
Yes.
Actually, I'm here to say goodbye.
Are you finally leaving?
Yes.
I've been doing this and that while trying to find my place.
No matter where I am and what I'm doing, I think my place is next to my man.
Are you sure it's all right to rent this place to someone else?
Yes. That's what I'm saying.
Otherwise, why don't you move in here?
Gosh, you were talking about a demotion. Look at you moving onto the Central District Prosecutors' Office.
I'm very proud of you.
Anyway, because of you, I got to live very economically in Seoul with its expensive housing prices.
Thank you so much for not raising my rent.
Sure.
I've been so grateful, Nuna.
What's with you ...
I didn't do anything for you.
Either you always came home late because you forgot that I was waiting for you,
or you didn't come home.
In the midst of that, while waiting for you ...
I studied so hard.
That's why I got good grades from the Judicial Institute.
And ...
I was grateful that you didn't feel bad for me.
That's why I could face you as if I was fine.
I think this is truly goodbye for me.
♫  Please tell me now, please tell me now  ♫
♫  Please tell me the right answer  ♫
Right ... Someone said this ...
At times, there are people who are like gifts even in the midst of a tough life.
I think you were my gift, Yu Jun.
Take care.
Mr. Han, how do we know how far away a star is from us?
Since the Earth orbits the sun, the same star appears to be at different points depending on where we stand.
If you know the difference, you can calculate and measure the distance.
This is what we call "Annual Parallax."
Why are you smiling all of a sudden?
Oh, "Annual Parallax" is called "Yeonju Shicha" in my native language, Korean.
This word just makes me feel good.
Why?
My life has always consisted of dreaming about another place instead of where I was.
But now when I look back, I realize that what I truly missed were the past moments.
I wanted to be someone different from who I was.
But in the end, I was able to do everything because of being myself .
No matter what my face looked like, I didn't lose myself,
and that was why I could do anything.
You worked so hard and passed the bar exam.
And the first thing you wanted to do is ...
There's no jokkbaengi in the USA.
Let's just eat jokkbaengi and go back. All right?
The land is so vast in the US. So many people got on my nerves.
You're all dead. You just wait.
Gosh ...
Did you call him?
He's been asking me every day when we're coming back.
That's why he asked you.
♫  Remember the words spoken through dry lips  ♫
Attorney Jo! Attorney Jo!
Where do you think you're going?
Gosh, seriously. What is that?
Jokkbaengi.
You brought this smelly thing all the way here?
That's what I mean! I brought this smelly thing just in time for your plane to land.
Stop using me.
I don't know anyone else in Korea, Ajeossi.
Where did you get it?
Where do you think?
Thank you to our channel manager:
a_hauth_238
Thank you to our segmenters:
bepina (chief), kitty100, pilar_velasquez, nicefly09, hana_860
karenperez, chemellelott, miss_rochester, shastalime
Thank you to our translation editors:
irmar (CE), manganese (GE),
emilyazel, nimi_stepinac, choitrio (TE)
Thank you to our English subbers:
nomi637, leenlee91, kjk_916, ztarbrite,
taniacao12, tenshi2408, netty_123
Thank you to our English subbers:
chewbacacorg, katreed15_677, rlaxogjd, surrealspace, naticula
dainee, hollykimm11_716, jo_p66, cicimong, marieoh
Thank you to all the language moderators and their teams.
♫  Let’s mount a snail as a watermelon  ♫
♫  Let’s use an electric light as a quail  ♫
♫  Let’s step on the table as an ant, Let’s do it  ♫
♫  Let’s ride an awl as a balloon  ♫
♫  Let’s not ride it but let’s hug instead  ♫
♫  Let’s hug a wardrobe as a pine caterpillar  ♫
♫  Just the way you see, just the way you hear  ♫
♫  Just the way you imagine, cyber  ♫
Thank you for watching "One the Woman"!
We hope you enjoyed the show!
♫  Let’s play a motorcycle as a guitar  ♫
♫  Let's ride a guitar with a motorcycle  ♫
Four, three, two ...