SANPO KITCHEN SINKS, CLOSETS
CUSTOM-DESIGNED FURNITURE
SANPO SINKS
SANPO KITCHEN SINK, CLOSET
CUSTOM-DESIGNED FURNITURE
Sorry!
Hang on. This is our dad's truck.
Why did I say sorry? Jeez.
What the heck?
SANPO SINKS
We're home.
Hey.
Wash up quick and come eat, okay?
I'll pass today.
Why? Wash up and come eat, okay?
Did you eat while you were out?
Of course not.
Then why isn't he eating?
Just leave him.
Why do you keep bothering him?
Then what? Just let him starve
when he worked all day?
He must want to drink on an empty stomach.
We know he drinks every day.
You take care of him every day.
Do you think he loves that?
It's like you're saying,
"Pull yourself together already."
He probably feels pressured.
Who's pressuring him?
You are, Mom.
I don't know what to take photos of.
I saw a tricycle on my way here.
Why do you drink every day?
What else would I do?
Should I give you something to do?
Worship me.
I've never felt whole before.
One asshole after another…
Every guy I've ever dated was an asshole.
So worship me and make me feel whole.
It'll be winter soon.
Nothing survives when winter comes.
There will be nothing to see sitting there
and no work at the factory.
If you drink all day,
you'll only feel like crap.
It'll be like hell.
You have to do something.
I want to feel whole for once.
So worship me.
Love isn't enough.
Worship me.
Go home.
Go home and sleep.
You have nothing to do anyway.
Do you think I want to do anything?
Do you know my name?
Do you know anything about me?
Why do you think
I'm living quietly in this countryside…
without telling anyone my name?
I don't want anything to do…
with anyone.
Not a thing.
Why are you still here?
Are you not going home?
I don't want to go home.
You don't want to go home?
What's gotten into you?
I've never heard you
say you don't want to go home.
Where should we go? A bar?
It looks delicious.
So tell me, why don't you want to go home?
Just because.
There you go again.
You always dodge questions like that.
Before I beat you up to make you spill,
just tell us.
There's this guy
that eats at my house.
And it's uncomfortable.
He eats there? Who is he?
Is he good-looking?
What does he do? How old is he?
I don't know, either.
-What?
I really don't know.
I don't even know his name.
I don't even know his name,
yet I made a huge mistake.
So what kind of mistake?
Spill it already! Spill! Now!
You lent a guy money, didn't you?
Guys can be sly as a fox too.
He saw that you're the kind of woman
he could borrow money from, screw over,
and get away with it.
So stop avoiding it
and deal with the problem at hand.
Once that jerk's paid all the money back,
will my life be fine?
I think it will still be the same.
I'll still have never felt whole
in this crappy life
with these crappy people
acting like they're so great
and just talking away thoughtlessly.
How they talk…
Sorry.
I'm an asshole, too.
Oh, no! The last train!
What?
I really don't want to go home.
Hey.
Just miss the last train.
-Miss it!
Asshole.
Idiot.
All he ever does is drink every day.
Do you want to win by cheating
your friend like that, asshole?
Whatever.
-That's your problem.
-Hey.
Mom.
Please, let's turn
the air-conditioner on. Please?
Mother. I beg you.
Why has he turned
his back against the world?
The number you have dialed cannot be--
I MADE THIS MONTH'S PAYMENT. CALL ME.
THIS MESSAGE WAS DELETED
She asked if anything's up with you.
What's going on?
I got called to the Joy Support Center,
and I cried
because I didn't want to join a club.
Goodness.
Just join anything
and say you're too busy to attend.
That'll do it.
She's too straitlaced.
How about joining
the photography club with me?
No one drinks, and everyone's really nice.
It must be annoying
to keep being called in over such a thing.
I want to stop learning things.
When I learned to swim,
I couldn't swim freestyle.
But since there were a lot of us,
we moved on to the backstroke,
then the breaststroke…
School was the same.
I hadn't learnt the multiplication table,
but we still had to move on to fractions.
After that, I was just sitting there.
In a club, the same thing
will just happen again.
Besides, nothing's fun for me.
I shouldn't have told you
about Su-jin and the others
going on a trip.
You think I'd have fun on a trip?
Here you go.
Why are you asking
around for Se-yeong's number?
I've been paying
your money back consistently.
I've even worked part-time
to pay it back every month.
It's just this one month I couldn't pay.
I'm racking my brain now for a solution.
But if you call Se-yeong,
you can forget about the money.
For God's sake.
Crazy bastard.
DESIGN TEAM 3, CHOI JUN-HO
Were you…
talking to me?
No.
I was reading my text…
I guess he knows he's a bastard. If you're
going to a cafe, let's go together.
No. I'm going to do it at home.
See you tomorrow.
Okay, see you.
SOMETHING GOOD WILL HAPPEN TO YOU TODAY.
IMMEDIATELY HE SPOKE TO THEM AND SAID,
“TAKE COURAGE! IT IS I. DON’T BE AFRAID.”
(MARK 6:50)
I hate this season.
Where the air you breathe in
and breathe out
are the same temperature.
Can we get coffee here?
Well, you can,
but it doesn't taste all that good.
Should we just go?
Our coffee beans are old.
I'm sorry.
Has anyone come
to take a look at your cafe?
What do you think?
Can't you turn on the air-conditioner?
Is she crazy? Why would she come
to my friend's wedding?
If she broke up with me,
she should be done with my friends too.
How could she think
of coming there all dolled up?
And what? "Let's stay friends."
She hurt me so badly.
After saying I'm "unbearably
and disgustingly old-fashioned,"
she wants us to be friends.
Is she insane?
Does she think I'm an idiot?
Sorry.
She said she and that guy weren't a thing,
and they picked up
two more people right after.
What does that have to do with me?
Why did she even tell me that?
If it's over, just let it be over.
That's normal.
But her being friendly…
End things beautifully?
Don't make me laugh. There's
no such thing as a beautiful breakup.
Then she took it out on me
saying I embarrassed her
-in front of others.
-Asshole.
Can't they just get married
without other people?
In the past, people went to weddings
to eat food since they were poor.
But they all eat well now.
Hey, I'm hungry.
So you live in Uijeongbu?
Yes.
Then this is a meeting between
North Gyeonggi-do and South Gyeonggi-do.
We have penetrated the egg yolk to meet.
Oh. That's what my brother says.
That Gyeonggi-do is like the egg white
wrapped around Seoul,
which is the egg yolk.
So we've both come into the yolk to meet.
That's funny.
Does it take you about an hour and a half
to get to Seoul from there, too?
Yes.
Right, me too.
A round trip of three hours
for both of us.
We might as well go on a trip.
Isn't the commute pretty bad?
It's the worst.
Are you managing?
Not really.
I feel like my batteries are
going to run out soon.
Same here.
So I should decide soon
whether to change jobs or move to Seoul.
I'd decide to move to Seoul.
You haven't let go of that dream yet?
Have you let go?
It's still too early to give up just yet,
so hold on a little longer.
You were saved
in Jeong-su's phone as "Pick-up Girl."
What does that mean?
Oh, that?
"A girl who always picks up the phone"?
I asked him, but he said it wasn't that
and told me to ask you directly.
What does it mean?
This again.
I'm tearing up, just thinking about it.
Once, with my friends,
we were talking about
"What's the noblest romance there is?"
And I was reminded of something I saw
in a history book at school,
about a woman who ran to pick up the
severed head of her husband in her skirt.
When I was young,
it was too gruesome for me,
but now that I'm older, I think,
"Yes, I would pick it up,
no, I'd have to pick it up."
"I can't let it fall to the ground.
I should run and catch it in my skirt."
Yes.
Don't you think so?
Isn't that only right?
And one summer, ages ago,
I spent a short time at Bible Camp.
I heard the story
of how Jesus was nailed to the cross,
but weirdly, it was Mary
that my heart went out to.
It took about six hours for Jesus to die
after getting whipped
and nailed to the cross.
For those six hours,
Mary followed the entire way
and took Jesus's body down.
She's amazing.
I should stay by my partner's side, too.
Why would you talk about that?
They'd be too scared about
being beheaded to fall for you.
You need to watch what you say.
Why would you say that
to someone you just met?
Well, he asked.
So what?
Would you tell him how your poop was
this morning if he asked?
Yes, I'd tell him everything.
Just live alone.
Why are you trying so hard
to love just anyone?
Don't do it. No one will love you.
No man would fall in love with a woman
who says she'd pick up
their lover's severed head.
I just mean, if such a thing happens.
Hypothetically.
Exactly, why are you
imagining that situation?
We don't want to be beheaded.
We don't want to imagine that.
Why did you have to
give him such a gruesome example?
That's the noblest romance?
We're not living in that era.
She's not looking for a boyfriend,
she's looking for a comrade-in-arms.
You must feel so much regret
that you were born in such peaceful times.
You must want to charge at enemies
and risk your life to save the country.
So sitting and eating dinner with a guy
must be terribly dull
and unsatisfying for you, right?
All right, then.
One. Women who run away.
Two. Women who faint.
Three. Women who pick it up.
Which woman do you want?
Which one would you prefer
out of the three?
Hey, which woman are you?
I'd pick it up too if it came to that.
She's a pick-up girl.
Girls who flirt and act all feminine
like Lee Ye-rin would never pick it up.
Those kinds of girls would run away.
Is that love?
So you're saying
that your man should be beheaded.
Hey, Du-hwan.
We need to start a war.
Gi-jeong's man
absolutely must be beheaded.
As long as it's not me.
Oh Du-hwan.
Your name could start a war. Oh Du-hwan.
Yeom Chang-hee. Your name's just as bad.
Mi-jeong, go buy some more alcohol.
No.
No?
Then go borrow some from Gu.
Just go borrow some already.
You bring him food every day.
I'm sure he'll give us some.
Hurry. You and Mr. Gu are close.
As if.
Let's just call it a night.
We're short by just one drink.
Hurry up and go.
There's no alcohol at Mr. Gu's place.
So enough.
Why wouldn't there be when he's a drunk?
Alcoholics never have alcohol stored away.
They just keep two to three bottles.
At first, he thinks,
"Just two bottles today."
"I'll just drink two bottles."
And he only buys two bottles.
Once he finishes them, he just wants more.
So he goes all the way
to the train station to buy more.
It would have been better
if he had started off with four bottles.
But it's always two.
That's how hard it is to be an alcoholic.
You two must be close.
We're next-door neighbors.
Have you guys even talked?
Once.
So, while drinking,
he always goes in
and brings out a new glass.
He always has two or three
shot glasses on the table.
So I asked him why,
and he said he changes glasses
when he gets bored.
What a poor, lonely guy.
I thought he was really cool.
Right.
See, during the day,
he drinks one glass
looking at the window on this side.
When the sun sets, he drinks one glass
looking at the porch over there.
At night,
he drinks one glass
looking at the other window.
He only changes the direction
staying still like this.
It's as if he's standing guard.
Like a neighborhood watch.
Hey, he's not out there today, though.
Come on. It's too hot and humid.
There's no breeze, either.
He's probably inside with the AC on.
Let's call it a night.
Bring those with you.
Should I go over?
This wall is perfect
for catching mosquitoes.
You can see everything. It's so clean.
If a mosquito gets into my room,
I can never find it.
The wallpaper's a mess,
everything's a mess.
How many bottles have you had?
I have the feeling that's the second.
I came because I thought it might
be more fun to have a drinking buddy
than change glasses.
Can I join you?
Where's a glass?
HANJO BANK
Do I look pathetic to you, too?
No way.
YSTAT RESEARCH
Everything else is almost done,
but we don't have enough
single men in their 40s from Gangwon-do.
We won't make it up
with cold calling by 6 p.m.
We should widen the limit.
Let's try for a bit longer.
There's still time.
But it's a long shot. We haven't
gotten anyone in the past two hours.
Let's just widen the limit.
Then…
how about until eight?
Let's try until eight o'clock.
Working overtime again today?
He's making us every day.
That's why he gives out
those lottery tickets so often.
By the way, how did your blind date go?
You know…
We agreed to meet again next time.
Doesn't "next time" usually mean "never"?
I was wondering,
did you get your chompers done?
It's just that they look so straight.
Don't you usually use
the word "chompers" with animals?
For people, we say "teeth."
You can use the word chompers
on people too.
You can say chompers, teeth,
or gnashers. Right?
We can use any of them. What's with her?
Hey. Are you on your way home?
Yes.
Good job today.
You too, Mr. Park.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
How many of those lottery tickets
have you given out to women?
I'm sure it's quite a lot.
And not just to women.
Do you know
you've never once given one to me?
No way.
Not even once.
Hold on, wait.
Well…
I'm sorry, that shocked me quite a bit.
I should have been more subtle.
I'm embarrassed.
-I'm so sorry.
-No.
You know,
I've decided to love someone this winter.
Just anyone.
Don't be nervous.
I've been so impatient lately,
I just want to die already.
After 14 years, my job is the same,
the meetings are the same,
and the people are the same,
I curse and get mad the same way.
It's all the same endless repetition.
"Will it be this way until I die?"
"Let's not live like this anymore.
Let's just love anyone."
"Even a relationship
I force myself into could turn into love."
"I'll love him passionately.
I'll make him my whole world."
But…
no one comes near me.
Everyone skips over me, like you.
Well, that was…
A subconscious decision?
I want to know
why it was that you did that.
Why does everybody skip over me?
I'm willing to hear
whatever you have to say
even if it shatters my pride.
Why do you think that is?
Well…
First of all, from my perspective,
the type of woman
a man likes never changes.
Whenever my friends introduce me
to their new girlfriends,
I find that they date people
who are just like their exes.
Men's tastes don't change.
In general, comedians marry comedians,
and actors marry actors, right?
-Well, that's who they see the most.
-No.
That's not the reason.
It's because
they're attracted to those types.
It's whether you prefer
someone who makes you laugh
or someone who makes your heart flutter.
I prefer the latter.
I prefer the latter too.
People who have a lot of dating experience
know what they want.
But those who don't,
don't know what they want
or what type of person they are.
They just want passionate romance
because that's what they hear people want.
But when they finally have it,
many find it
too embarrassing and can't stand it.
It can be embarrassing, but I like it.
When you're embarrassed about something,
it means you find it uncomfortable.
So…
You might be very natural and charming
in a different genre, Ms. Yeom.
Melodrama isn't the only genre
of relationships, right?
There's comedy, surrealism,
thriller… Yes, that's a good one.
What else, slice-of-life? Suspense?
There are so many.
In which genre among those
do you think you'd be most effective?
What are your strengths?
I'm like a Jindo dog.
I stand by my man and never betray him.
I protect him.
And my man must be a real man.
But I don't mean
he has to be all big and burly.
Yes, I have my own idea of masculinity.
A man, yes.
Slice-of-life it is. Yes.
It almost veered toward thriller,
but you're the slice-of-life type.
Many are not really interested
in surprise events or grand gestures.
The most important thing to them
is their attitude toward life.
They look at a person's core.
The core.
Attitude.
Anyway, if you keep that in mind,
you'll usually make the right choice.
And rather than being recklessly
determined to love just anyone,
deciding to go for it
when you meet someone you like
will be far more constructive.
You really are an expert.
Okay.
If I meet a man I like,
I'm going to try to make the first move.
Not just the first move,
but the first confession.
That's so embarrassing though.
My mom always says,
"A house and spouse will come
to you when the time is right."
You'll find one when the time is right.
-Will he?
-He will.
Okay.
I feel like I need to give you
a fortune-teller's fee or something.
No.
If I go this way, I can get home faster.
Get home safe.
You must really not be
interested in me at all.
You can't wait to go home.
No, I'm just kidding.
-Let's go together.
-No, go ahead.
-It's fine. Go ahead.
-All right.
-See you tomorrow.
-Go on, off you go. Go ahead. Go.
See you tomorrow.
SOMETHING GOOD WILL HAPPEN TO YOU TODAY
Something good, my foot.
I'm going to go.
Hey, use the restroom before you go.
I'm fine.
Do as I say.
It's a long way back to Seoul.
I just wanted to try coming here once.
I came here for a change!
To your neighborhood, Dangmi Station!
It's nothing special.
Even if you need to pee, hold it.
This is the last train.
Hold it until you get to Seoul.
I'm home.
Mom and Dad aren't here.
Where are they?
At a funeral.
Who passed away?
Mom's uncle.
Why are you acting like you got dumped
when it was you who dumped her?
What do you mean?
Lee Ye-rin. You're the one who dumped her.
Watching the movie
and going to the restaurant alone
when you promised to go together.
Who wouldn't break up after that?
He always does something
that'll get him dumped.
He totally deserves it.
Do you have another girl?
Did you want to break up with her
because you met someone else you liked?
-Do you think I'd do that?
-Then why did you do it?
Lee Ye-rin went home after crying
for a while at Dangmi Station.
I guess she knows she messed up.
You're the one who messed up.
She started it!
I saw that look in her eyes.
The look in her eyes that says,
"This guy's nothing special."
The look I've seen
in their eyes many times.
"This guy's nothing special.
How shall I break up with him?"
"What excuse should I come up with?"
At first, I do as they say and play along.
"Yes, I know I'm nothing special."
"But I'm fun to be around.
At least I'm not a bore."
But if that doesn't work,
what am I supposed to do?
What else can I do
when they want to end it?
From that point on,
I start fighting them constantly.
And that's when the reason we broke up
becomes that I watched a movie alone,
or that she texted some guy late at night.
And it can never be because
she found out what a pathetic loser I am.
I know it, too.
That I'm not the best she can have.
I know that she thinks she can
find someone better.
He always asked, "Aren't you
curious about my neighborhood?"
"Aren't you curious about Dangmi Station?
Tell him I know now.
DANGMI
Now every time I pass near here,
I'm sure I'll think of Yeom Chang-hee.
YEOM CHANG-HEE
Where are you going this late?
I'm sorry
for the other day.
I was drunk and crossed the line.
I'm not that rude usually.
We should drink together sometime
and get to know each other.
What should I call you?
I only know your last name.
I was born in 1985…
I'll just call you Gu.
Did everyone just arrive?
I worked overtime. I didn't drink.
You're home.
If you think about it,
all the assholes in my life
started with that same look in their eyes.
Eyes that seemed to say,
"You're not good enough."
It makes you feel so small.
Like you're insignificant.
It was that look
that made us sick and exhausted.
Repetitive relationships you jump into
to find something to love about yourself,
only to come out of them even more sure
of how unattractive you truly are.
Where should we look for the answer?
What about you?
Have you ever made anyone feel whole?
SANPO KITCHEN SINK, CLOSET
CUSTOM-DESIGNED FURNITURE
It's too hot.
I want to eat something cold.
Hey.
Does that guy still eat
at your house these days?
Are you still uncomfortable around him?
Stop already. Forget what I said.
-Hey, the omelet's pretty good.
-Really?
-Today's my lucky day.
-Is it?
I'd like to discuss the details
of a new club with you.
So could you come
by the Center sometime today?
These guys are seriously pissing me off.
Should we just report it
to the commission?
Are you going to go?
Let's just make one ourselves. Anything.
It seems they're going to
keep calling us until we join a club.
We can just tell them we'll form one,
and not do anything.
But they'll probably be suspicious.
What if they ask what we're doing?
A book club?
There's already a book club.
What don't they have yet?
Hiking's probably taken.
Definitely.
We have to choose carefully.
If it's something they already have,
they'll make us join that.
Calligraphy?
Can't we get a list
of all the workplace clubs?
If we can, it'll be easy.
I think it's on the website.
Here, there's a list.
Right, let's see.
How about we actually do it?
"The Liberation Club."
I…
want liberation.
I want to be liberated.
I don't know where I'm trapped,
but I feel trapped.
There's nothing in my life
that relaxes me.
I feel cramped and stifled.
I want to break free.
Liberation?
I like it.
The three of you?
Yes.
What does "liberation" entail?
The Republic of Korea
was liberated in 1945,
but we have yet to find liberation.
What?
That's it?
Well, so…
what are the three of you going to do?
Liberation.
That's what we'll do.
JOY SUPPORT CENTER
My gosh.
What are we actually
trying to liberate ourselves from?
What do we have to do?
Then let's first think about what we're
trying to liberate ourselves from.
Oh, my.
Cover it up.
Do you
want me to worship you?
It seems you've never felt whole too.
Let me know if you want me to.
I'm heading out.
Let's at least say hi from now on.
The bus is coming. You better run.
I said, run.
You've found someone, right?
We're really going to do it.
You cheer them on.
Yeom Gi-jeong.
Wait, are you Yeom Gi-jeong?
Have you lost it?
He's Gyeong-seon's little brother.
He's a single father.
I wonder how he managed
to get that nasty old man to pay.
I doubt he beat it out of him.
Why are you so moody?
To each one's own.
-What is it?
-Where is Mr. Gu going?
Do you know someone around here?
You would've been in trouble
if you had kept going.
Get inside now! I said, get inside!
Subtitle translation by: Elodie Lieberman