(A project funded by Zhejiang Cultural Art Development Foundation)
(Directed by Liu Xue Song)
(Episode 21)
You're at a crossroads in life...
and you have two choices before you.
One of them is a flat road...
while another is a bumpy road.
In the end, death is the direction they take.
You hesitated for a long time at the junction,
not knowing what to do.
That's why you are seeking help from me.
I'm telling you.
If this was back in the day...
I would choose the smooth road.
I really enjoy living a carefree life every day.
I'm relaxed and happy.
There's no pressure...
- and I don't have to think much. - I know.
But...
recently,
I have a new sentiment about my life.
I think...
people should live a more fruitful life.
We have to go through more ups and downs.
We should encounter different things.
We should let different colors fill up our lives.
We should enrich our lives with different flavors.
That way, our lives...
will be more meaningful.
But your life will surely be a lot more tiring that way.
Everything you do is tiring.
But every day, on this rough and rugged road,
you'll meet different people...
and different things.
You'll be fooled by a lot of different things...
and get beat up.
But these things will all turn into your scales...
and your armor.
They will enrich your life...
and allow yourself...
to grow stronger in the future.
These experiences will make your life...
very interesting.
People especially like those who are interesting.
Do you want to be liked?
No.
That's because when I'm tired,
all I want to do is eat and sleep.
I don't want to do anything or think about anything.
How relaxing is that?
But...
I think if I were to really live a life like that,
then I may end up envying...
those who are busy, always running around,
and have a lot to do.
People are always so indecisive, aren't they?
Yes. People are like that.
You want to take a vacation when you go to school.
When you're on vacation, you want to go to school.
When you're working every day, you want to rest.
But you want to start working as soon as you take a break.
Everyone is like that.
I understand.
So you're saying...
people should live a more fruitful, exciting,
and meaningful life, right?
Torture yourself.
I think your presence...
is already torturing enough.
It's also fruitful and exciting enough.
Let's sleep.
Sleep.
- Are we not talking anymore? - No.
I was just getting fired up.
I hope my nagging today...
brought a bit of help...
to your path of life.
I'm going.
Good night.
Thank you.
Sleep tight.
Mr. Sheng, are you looking for Mr. Hou...
Go and open the door for me.
Mr. Sheng, are you all right?
Is it swollen?
No.
- What about my hairstyle? - It's fine.
Go and open the door.
- Mr. Sheng, please wait. - Shut up.
Mr. Sheng.
This...
What brings you here?
From the look of it,
it seems like you're here to interrogate me.
Did I do something wrong that upsets you?
Stop talking about useless things.
We've worked together for so many years.
We've had arguments and got angry at each other.
But luckily, we both have straightforward personalities.
We're fine after we talk things out and put things behind us.
That's why our relationship has lasted until today.
Am I right?
That's right, Mr. Sheng.
You're suddenly saying all these things. It's making me...
What's going on?
Did someone upset you or something?
Honestly, this matter is quite humiliating.
Originally, our kids...
should be handling matters by themselves.
Am I right?
But my kid is a girl.
So...
So I'm taking advantage of this to complain a little.
My dear friend,
you have been helping me all these years.
How are you taking advantage of me?
Did Hou Jue...
make Chen Chen angry?
Is that right, my friend?
Initially, our plan was...
if they can be together,
then the two of us...
can take our business relationship a step further.
We'll become relatives.
Am I right?
You're absolutely right.
This is a good thing.
- Yes. - That's right.
If they're not meant to be,
we can just let this go...
and can keep doing our business.
After all, this is just our wishful thinking.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
If he doesn't like Chen Chen,
that's okay.
I had her at an old age.
My child has always been spoiled,
so she has a lot of bad habits.
But even so,
there are several handsome and successful young men...
lining up to pursue her.
- Do you believe that? - I do.
Mr. Sheng, honestly, I even think...
Chen Chen is a bit out of Hou Jue's league.
That's how I truly feel.
But I don't understand.
I didn't hear Hou Jue mention...
how he angered Chen Chen either.
How?
If I tell you,
you'll feel humiliated too.
Tell me.
Your son sure is something.
Not only did he not protect Chen Chen,
but he even sided with that female bodyguard instead.
He even scolded Chen Chen...
in front of so many people.
I can't accept this.
That jerk!
I'm so mad.
How could he do such a thing?
Even I'm mad just hearing about it, let alone you.
I'm serious.
Mr. Sheng.
Calm down first.
On behalf of Hou Jue,
I apologize to you and Chen Chen.
I sincerely apologize.
It's Hou Jue's problem.
I'll definitely teach him a lesson later.
Regarding your apology,
I'll reluctantly accept it.
But for my daughter,
I can't let go of this.
You're right.
I know.
Chen Chen is your precious daughter.
Never mind you, even I can't stand it...
after hearing this.
Whoever upsets Chen Chen...
is going against you.
How about this, Mr. Sheng?
Please calm down first.
Later on, come to my clubhouse.
I'll arrange it.
Bring Chen Chen over.
I'll bring that punk...
and make him apologize to Chen Chen...
in front of both of you.
You can do whatever you want with him then.
Does that sound good?
What about that female bodyguard?
That's easy.
It's a small matter.
I'll just let her go.
What do you say, old friend?
Brew me some tea.
Okay, I'll brew some tea.
The interior design of your company...
really doesn't make sense.
Hello.
Okay, I got it.
Mr. Hou wants to see me. I'm going over there.
It must be about that stupid matter with Chen Chen.
I don't know.
- I'll go with you. - It's okay.
He told me to go alone. He didn't ask for you.
It's okay.
I'll be your bodyguard today. Come on.
Mr. Hou Junior, Mr. Hou...
- Wait for me at the door. - Come in.
Mr. Hou, did you ask for me?
Have a seat.
Shi Yi.
You've been with the company...
for almost two months now, right?
Although there were ups and downs...
and you experienced several obstacles,
no matter what happens,
you've always fulfilled your duty...
and done your job well.
As your client, I'm very satisfied with that.
Thank you, Mr. Hou.
Back then, I recruited a female bodyguard for Hou Jue...
because I like how they're composed and meticulous.
Not only do you have to keep him safe,
at the same time, you must also restrain his behavior...
and not let him stir up trouble.
However, it seems like...
I was too simpleminded.
Having a single man and woman...
spend 24 hours a day together...
is bound to trigger some chemistry.
Actually, I can understand that.
Even if you're raising a pet,
feelings will grow as time goes by,
let alone two people.
Our company has a very specific rule about that.
We can't date our employers.
I'll strictly abide by it. Don't worry.
I don't care if you date or not.
You're free to date whoever you want.
But when it comes to marriage,
Hou Jue definitely cannot make his own decision.
That's Hou Jue's destiny.
Hou Jue's marriage isn't just about him.
It's also an important matter to the company.
Shi Yi.
I'll be honest with you.
The current market environment...
isn't as good as before.
The bigger a company is,
the more enemies you'll have.
Only if strong companies form an alliance...
can we withstand the risk in the market together.
A marriage alliance is the best way to do that.
I hope you can understand this.
Although Hou Jue doesn't understand my thoughts right now,
people eventually grow up, right?
Mr. Hou Junior.
Can you hear them like that?
Someday,
he'll understand that I'm doing this for his own good.
Also, Shi Yi,
I don't care if Fang Lu doesn't like you.
But if Chen Chen is bothered by you,
I have to take it seriously.
That's because you need to be clear about one thing.
Chen Chen is the future wife...
that I've chosen for Hou Jue.
Then what do you want me to do, Mr. Hou?
I want you to leave.
Mr. Hou.
What does this have to do with Shi Yi?
Why are you making her go?
It's none of your business. Leave.
Can't you see that I'm talking to Shi Yi right now?
She is my bodyguard.
Why can't I listen to a conversation related to her?
Shi Yi, go out first.
Let me talk to Hou Jue for a bit.
Okay.
Go ahead and talk.
Why are you asking Shi Yi to leave?
I'm clearing the obstacles for you.
What obstacles do I have?
I'm clearing the obstacles between you and Chen Chen.
Can't you see that?
As long as Wu Shi Yi is around,
all girls will misunderstand.
I didn't think about this...
when I asked Shi Yi to be your bodyguard back then.
The obstacle between me and Chen Chen...
has nothing to do with Shi Yi.
The obstacle between us is Chen Chen herself.
Okay?
In other words, she's too much of a drama queen.
She's too much for me.
How are you going to fix that?
That's not for me to fix.
Time will do the job.
Once you get married...
and have a couple of kids in a few years,
by then, you'll have grown older...
and be more mature.
Everything will be fine then, right?
Being of equal social status is the most important.
Do you understand?
It is important, but what does that have to do with Shi Yi?
Why are you making her leave?
It's not my request.
It's Chen Chen's request.
Chen Chen's request?
Who is she to make any demands?
What rights does she have to make requests?
If it weren't for her,
would things have ended up like that yesterday?
She doesn't respect other people's jobs.
She embarrassed herself.
Whose fault is it?
Some people might like a girl like Chen Chen,
but that's definitely not me.
It's impossible between us.
Hou Jue.
I'll be having Mr. Sheng and Chen Chen over...
at the clubhouse tomorrow.
If you've made up your mind not to dismiss Shi Yi,
but at the same time, you also don't want to be with Chen Chen,
figure it out yourself.
Think of a way...
that can ease your relationship with Chen Chen.
Do you understand?
This isn't only what Chen Chen wants.
Mr. Sheng's company is very important to us.
I'm sure I don't have to tell you this.
You should know this very well.
It's unnecessary for things to turn out like this.
Sure.
Arrange a dinner then.
It'll give you the chance to see Chen Chen's disgusting behavior.
I'll pack up and leave right away.
I won't trouble you.
You wish.
Do you want to leave after causing me trouble?
Don't even think about it.
Just be good and stay here, okay?
I need to see you. Now.
(Delete)
I'll be back.
Tian Min.
What's so urgent that requires you to tell me now?
What did you do again?
I didn't do anything.
Someone transferred out 20 million from our account.
You...
You've been hacked.
How are you still in the mood to joke around?
What's going on?
What exactly happened?
Let me tell you.
I'm afraid it won't be safe to keep the money here,
so I transferred the money to a friend who's abroad.
I asked him to help us buy a house.
Didn't you say you want to leave?
I have to arrange things for us.
Just relax.
Didn't we agree on this back then?
We're just giving Hou Zhi Rong a scare.
When Hou Jue leaves,
- we'll return the money. - Yes.
You used the money to buy a house.
How are we going to pay Hou Zhi Rong back?
Ma Yong, hurry up and transfer the money back.
Let's hurry and pay the company back.
All right. Don't worry.
Just stay out of this.
Ma Yong.
I hacked the neighborhood's property management company...
and the Zhirong website...
to take revenge for you.
Hou Jue didn't bring any actual losses...
to the neighborhood and Zhirong Construction.
But...
But you've gone too far.
What if the police find out? What will we do?
I'll just go to jail then.
Tian Min.
You know this.
I started working here as soon as I graduated from college.
I ran errands and served as Hou Zhi Rong's assistant.
I had to endure it for so many years to get to where I am now.
I eluded so much risk...
and created so much value for him.
I acted like a fool to show my loyalty.
I even refused a higher salary.
Did he ever give me an extra penny?
No.
All he does is suck me dry.
So what if I took 20 million from him?
Hou Zhi Rong owes me this money!
I know.
You're saying that Hou Zhi Rong has been using you.
He didn't keep his promise.
But since you don't trust him,
we can leave.
Why should I leave?
He promised to make me the company's successor.
You know that.
He told the whole company...
that I'm closer to him than his own son.
The company needs me.
I was an idiot. I believed it. I believed everything he said.
That's why I always put the company's interests...
and his interests first.
That day,
in front of the hospital room,
I heard him tell Hou Jue,
"Ma Yong works conscientiously and diligently."
"But he's an outsider."
"Outsiders have other intentions."
"Outsiders have other intentions,"
"so we have to be careful of them."
I worked hard for 13 years.
But these honest words are what I get.
His so-called affection...
is just for using people.
You're going to regret this.
You're committing a crime. We can't escape.
I just want you...
to be happy...
and safe every day.
I don't want you to go to jail.
Ms. Zhang.
Where did you go on the weekend?
The photos you posted are so beautiful.
It was a resort.
My future son-in-law runs it.
Your son-in-law is very capable.
The hotel is beautiful and it's by the ocean.
It's okay.
It just opened.
If you want to go,
I have a VIP card.
You can get a discount.
Your son-in-law...
is so thoughtful and capable.
That's hard to come by.
You're jealous, right?
I'm so jealous.
- Hurry and read the documents. - All right.
Do you think she'll like this purse?
I think so.
It's so expensive.
Isn't he that guy?
It's your old acquaintance.
Lan Qi.
Shi Yi.
Mr. Hou Junior.
Mr. Lan, are you shopping with your girlfriend?
- Where is she? - Lan Qi, look at my outfit.
- Lan Qi. - Mom?
This is such a nice outfit.
Dad.
Shi Yi.
What's going on?
Well, it's your mom's birthday this Saturday, right?
I told them I would buy them new outfits to cheer them up.
Is it your birthday?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Ma'am, which outfit do you want? I'll buy it for you.
You like the one you're wearing, right?
What other stores are there nearby?
Let's go and take a look. Let's go, ma'am.
- No, you really don't have to. - That's enough.
I already said I don't want to celebrate it.
But Lan Qi said he has a gift card...
and that it will expire if he doesn't use it.
Yes, it would be a shame not to use it.
Don't bother using a gift card.
You don't need to feel bad for my wallet.
- Let's go, ma'am. Come on. - There's really no need.
What are you guys doing?
- He came to buy... - I just took Shi Yi shopping.
We just bought a purse.
Something urgent came up.
I'll get going now, ma'am and Mr. Wu.
- All right. - Let's go.
- I'm leaving then. - Shi Yi.
- Thank you. - No problem.
I'm leaving.
You...
The conversation was going well. Why did you keep trying to explain?
Why do you always ruin things for me?
What did I do?
You didn't even let me talk.
You're the one to talk.
What nonsense were you saying just now?
Anyhow, you're not allowed to explain to them.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
What do you mean?
Who does he think he is?
He's trying to get in with your parents...
while I'm not looking.
I hate people like that. He's so cunning.
You need to stay away from this kind of person.
He already knew my parents very well over 10 years ago.
So what? Can he do this just because he knows them well?
He pretends not to do anything, but he's secretly making moves.
What kind of behavior is that?
How can he do that?
Say something.
Why are you looking at me?
What kind of behavior is that?
What's wrong, Ms. Zhang and Mr. Wu?
If you think...
I'm bothered by Mr. Hou giving Shi Yi a gift,
then you're overthinking it.
That purse is really expensive.
From what I know about Shi Yi,
she would never accept it.
- That's right. - That's for sure.
Besides, we're different.
When I met Shi Yi,
she was still in elementary school, right?
Yes.
She has always had many pursuers ever since she was young.
I'm used to it now.
That's right.
But Shi Yi is very faithful.
Mr. Wu and Ms. Zhang.
My parents passed away early.
So...
deep down,
I've always thought of you two...
as my parents.
Shi Yi is busy.
I'll take care of you on her behalf.
Lan Qi.
Hearing you say that, I feel...
You're a good kid.
All right, let's go eat.
Okay.
Lan Qi said that purse is quite expensive.
If Shi Yi doesn't accept it, it'll be such a waste.
She can give it to me.
It could sell for a lot of money on secondhand shopping websites.
How cheap.
Look at you.
I was just kidding, but you took it seriously.
You're so old now,
yet you still have no sense of humor.
Whatever.
I'm just wondering...
what stage he and Shi Yi are at now.
Why don't you send her a message and ask?
There's no point in asking.
She'll definitely say they're just working together.
But I saw Hou Jue's eyes.
He can't fool me.
If Shi Yi has really fallen in love with Hou Jue,
what should we do then?
What about Lan Qi?
That would be a good thing.
Both of them can pursue her at the same time.
If there's a rival,
they'll both care about Shi Yi even more.
Moreover, Shi Yi will understand her own value even better.
That's right.
In terms of competitive mechanisms,
you're an expert.
Back then, I also had to fight my way through a rain of bullets...
and a bloodbath.
Why did I marry you?
Why did you follow me here?
Aren't you going to take me home?
Who said I would do that?
Your place is so close. Walk home by yourself.
I have a date.
Isn't this a competitive mechanism?
Give me your parents' phone numbers.
Why?
You're with me every day, right?
You risk your life for me, right?
If anything happens to you,
as your boss,
I have to tell your parents right away.
It's okay.
If anything happens to me, you can notify our company.
They'll notify my parents.
A notification from your company is one thing.
Right? It's completely different if it comes from me.
I have to tell your parents directly.
That shows sincerity.
- People... - That's enough.
Stop thinking about these useless things.
Hurry and think about how to apologize to Chen Chen...
when you get to the restaurant later.
Why should I apologize? I'm not apologizing.
I'm asking for phone numbers right now.
I'll develop a good relationship with your parents first.
That way,
this can slowly develop as normal...
You're not getting their numbers.
Has that Little Qi of yours...
not contacted you yet?
No.
He hasn't done anything at all.
This guy is strange.
Is he that calm?
He's deep.
That's true.
Anyone is deeper than you.
All right.
I'll wait for you here.
Go in.
Remember.
Be patient.
Think about the bigger picture.
I hope Ms. Chen...
can bring her best today.
Open my dad's eyes...
and let him witness her evilness.
I'm going.
Good luck.
Dad.
Mr. Chen.
Why are you so late?
Look at the time.
What time did I tell you to come?
Hurry up and apologize to Chen Chen.
An apology isn't enough.
I went to buy a purse.
Ms. Chen, please accept it. Here.
Look at this.
He's a smart one.
Accept it. See if it's nice.
If you don't like it,
I'll ask my son to buy you a new one.
I'll go right away.
It's all right.
Okay, come on.
Son, pick up your glass.
- Here, Mr. Sheng. - Okay.
On behalf of my son,
I apologize to you and Chen Chen.
It's nothing.
My son doesn't know any better.
Please forgive him.
What did I do wrong?
You upset her.
It's a man's crime.
Do you understand?
Then I've committed a deadly crime.
I apologize.
- Come on. - I'll apologize to you too.
Thank you.
That's right.
Zhi Rong.
Thank you so much.
You had to personally take care...
of a trivial matter like this for our kids.
Mr. Sheng, you're treating me as an outsider by saying that.
Kids are still young and reckless.
It's understandable that they have bad tempers.
In fact, having quarrels will bring them closer together.
Don't you remember the times when we were young?
Didn't we also bicker and argue?
That's right.
Chen Chen.
Back then, when Zhi Rong and I worked together,
we didn't trust each other at all.
We really had a lot of arguments.
Yes, I'm telling you.
When your grandpa stepped down and I joined the company,
I was still young.
I didn't know anything.
It was Mr. Sheng who helped me out a lot...
at the most important stage of my life.
We often slammed tables and threw wine glasses...
because of business conflicts.
We've done everything.
- Isn't that right, Mr. Sheng? - Yes.
But look at us now.
We're fine.
If fate brings two people together,
you should treasure this relationship.
Mr. Sheng and I both have faith in you two.
All right.
Hou Jue, did your female lackey resign from her post yet?
No.
Little brat.
That's enough. It's in the past now.
There's no need to set yourself against a little girl.
That's right.
Dad, I'm not setting myself against her.
She's just a little lackey. She's not worth my time.
I just want her to leave.
This...
Chen Chen.
Listen to me.
That girl really can't leave.
I especially hired that girl from a security company...
to protect my son.
She used to be an athlete.
She had won championships and medals.
Her working ability is definitely top-notch.
With her by my son's side...
Mr. Sheng, you also know this.
I only have one son.
I'll feel a lot more at ease.
That's true.
Right?
No wonder she's so fierce.
That's more the reason she has to leave.
All right.
But she didn't do anything wrong.
Why does she have to leave?
How was she not wrong?
She bullied me. I hate her! Is that not good enough of a reason?
Chen Chen. That is good enough.
How about this?
I'll make sure you're happy today.
Let's do this.
Ask Shi Yi to come in here.
She should apologize to Chen Chen.
What do you think, Mr. Sheng?
That's a good idea.
Just call her here.
Once they meet and talk things out,
everything will be resolved, right?
- Okay. - Go on.
I can't go.
Are you going or not?
As long as you're all happy.
Why did you come out?
Well...
You need to go in and apologize to Chen Chen.
I'm doing this out of respect for my dad.
Chen Chen just won't let it go no matter what we say.
Let's just apologize.
There's no need to say more.
Okay.
What should I say then?
Just say...
Just say, "I'm sorry."
That's it.
Okay?
Let's go.
Has he still not contacted you yet?
Who?
Little Qi.
No.
Did he not believe it?
Have I met my match?
Are you going in or not?
Let's go.
Thank you. Come on.
Dad. Mr. Chen.
Hou Jue. Shi Yi.
Mr. Sheng, this is Shi Yi.
Chen Chen, Shi Yi is here now.
You two have a good talk.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Ms. Chen.
Heroine, we meet again.
If I did anything wrong before...
and make you angry,
please forgive me.
I'm sorry.
She apologized.
I've waited for this moment for an eternity.
All right. Tell me. What did you do wrong?
Brat, that's enough.
No.
Whatever it is you think I did wrong,
then that's what it is.
I want to ask you.
That day,
did you purposely embarrass me?
I didn't.
Yes, you did.
Is this the right attitude to apologize?
Chen Chen.
She already apologized.
Why are you still getting hung up on the details?
Sit down.
Forget it.
Since Hou Jue gave me a gift,
I won't ask about that.
How about this?
Drink this up.
Then we can be good friends.
Ms. Chen.
Thank you for your kindness,
but I can't drink alcohol.
That's our rule.
I decide what your rule is.
- I told you to drink it. - She really can't drink.
There's a policy in their industry.
They can't drink when they're on duty.
If you're really angry,
then how about this?
You can't be friends anyway.
I'll drink it for you.
No.
What are you doing?
Who is she to you? Who are you to drink for her?
Your apology...
isn't sincere at all.
I've finished the drink.
Stop dragging this out now.
Fine.
I won't drag this out.
All right.
Drink this up.
I'll let this pass if you drink this.
I really can't drink.
Chen Chen.
This is the rule of her profession.
It's their policy, right?
We should at least respect her occupation.
What do you mean?
Is her career more important or am I more important?
Who do you think you are?
I'm telling you. I can make you lose your job anytime.
You're just a lackey.
You're just a human shield.
You're just a guard dog!
Don't insult my profession.
That's exactly what I'm doing!
Chen Chen, what are you doing?
Get lost!
That's enough.
Apologize for what you said.
I won't apologize.
Apologize.
I won't.
Zhi Rong.
Shi Yi, that's enough.
Dad, you saw it too.
This is the situation.
We've already come to apologize.
The rest is none of our business.
Let's go.
Hou Jue.
Come back here.
Hou Jue!
I told you to come back here!
Die!
Chen Chen!