=General Order=
=Episode 18=
So that's how it is!
It turns out that you
married her.
Exactly!
Father.
Leave it alone.
Who the hell did it, trapping you here?
Since I entered the Palace,
the Emperor had confined me here.
The Emperor?
Is it Sun Duo?
What happened between you and Sun Duo?
As you saw,
The time we time traveled
was different.
(16 years ago)
Your Majesty, the person arrived.
You go ahead.
Got it.
Cao Jian.
Take your seat!
I know you've come here already.
Liu.
Why have you become so old?
I know it's your first instinct.
I was the first to be time travelled.
I've been here for 20 years.
20 years?
What have you been through?
I...
He
runs a grocery store.
- For novel items.
- Is that true?
He's well-off now.
If I didn't enter his stall by accident,
I thought I'd never see him.
Liu, amazing!
Sun Duo.
What happened to you?
Why have you been an emperor?
Well, I...
It has a long story.
When I first time traveled here,
I fell to the Eastern Palace,
meeting the Crown Prince.
The former emperor was seriously ill.
The Prince was about to take the throne.
He asked me to help him with plans.
After I helped him kill his opponents,
he dared to
kill me, either.
All is about tactics, plots,
we were intrigued all day long.
Forget it.
Let it go off.
By the way,
after many years of separation,
I want to give you a gift.
What's this?
It's the design of a musket.
The court is dangerous.
You'd use it to keep you safe.
Liu!
You didn't even give me any muskets!
Liu,
thank you!
No more formalities. We're friends.
Cao Jian, what will you give me?
Leave me alone.
I don't even have enough military funds.
I have nothing.
Say something about yourself.
I'm so miserable.
When I woke up,
I was fighting
at the border.
I was almost killed.
Thanks to Dai, he saved me.
Then, I followed General Dai.
After that, he was seriously injured.
He feared foes would invade out of this.
So,
I was ordered to pretend to be him.
It had lasted
for ten years.
So I'm always masked when I go out.
How tough!
Yu,
although I'm your adoptive father,
I always see you as my real child.
You've lived a hard life
for the past few years.
You're wrong.
I'm incapable of making you suffer losses.
Although I'm your real child,
I always see you as my real father.
Father,
for the past few years,
what's going on with those killed girls?
The third girl was killed this month.
I've seen her in Sun Duo's place.
For those girls,
they resembled Su Ke.
Is the real killer Sun Duo?
I heard he sent a pic to the Ministry,
setting off a massive search.
If nothing unexpected happens,
those three died because of him.
Negative.
I have to examine myself.
Ask him to give us an explanation.
You can't come to him.
He's been lured by power.
If we just come to him,
I'm so worried...
How could that be?
Even if he killed those girls,
I believe in him, who couldn't
hurt us, his old friends.
Please, listen to me.
We'd better leave here right now!
You wait here for me.
I'd come to him alone.
You!
What should I do?
Sun Duo.
So many girls have been killed.
Did you do that?
Cao.
We've known for a long time.
Don't you believe in me?
You sent the pic to the Ministry.
Then, those girls were killed.
Those all resembled Su Ke.
Was that a coincidence?
Look, we three have all been put here.
Su Ke must be here, too.
Am I right?
I took the pic to the Ministry,
because it was to find Su Ke.
Isn't this also something we
have always been concerned about?
But why did you kill them?
Cao.
I don't want to tip it off.
I did so,
because I wanted to make Su Ke safe.
Sacrifice, to some extent,
is a must.
Sun Duo.
You killed the innocent as you wish.
I can't watch on the sideline!
Guards!
Sun Duo!
Sorry, Cao.
I tried hard to take the throne.
How can I let you ruin my thing?
You're wearing a mask to pretend,
you'll never be allowed to put it down!
(Although Sun Duo did it,)
(I can't let Yu know at the moment!)
I
don't know who did it.
Why did Sun Duo keep you here?
Sun Duo has
been lured by power.
You mustn't confront him!
Plus,
Liu once said
If there's one of us
leaving here,
all of the rest
will leave together.
So,
you must come to find Liu.
Only he knows how to time travel back.
Cao.
Liu
has died.
How could that be?
Father!
Cao.
Liu died before me.
I saw it myself.
After you've been trapped,
Liu set up the Luli Manor.
This time,
we're right about to go there, seeing
if there are any clues left for us.
Then there's no time to lose.
You need to go now.
But,
before that,
you have to find another one.
Who?
Liu once said
the site of our internship
was the Tomb of General Xinwu.
So,
you must find that person!
The person is General Xinwu.
And find his General Token,
which is the key
to the time travel.
Father.
I'm General Xinwu.
♪The world is fuzzy and ruthless♪
♪There's no way of avoiding farewells♪
♪You robe yourself in moonlight♪
♪Staring at your mottled silhouette♪
♪How to remember when fate began♪
♪Face to face, drinking in the wind♪
♪Love and hate are still unsettled♪
♪Where to meet and part♪
♪I can't have my final say♪
♪Hoping to reunite♪
♪But cannot wait for when you return♪
♪I don't know when the dream will end♪
♪Looking at your silhouette from afar♪
♪Ties are tough. Tears fall like rain♪
♪This life is only for you♪
♪No matter if swords pierce bones♪
♪Let the millennia change♪
♪Let the flowers fall as expected♪
♪Let go of everything to be with you♪
♪This life is only for you♪
♪I have only you deep in my heart♪
♪A song of lovesickness♪
♪A letter of farewell♪
♪All gone with the wind♪
(The exclusive network
distribution rights of this work belong)
(to Shenzhen Tencent
Computer System Co., Ltd.)