The announcement is next month.
Chef Tango. We're tough, you know.
So are we.
This is getting interesting.
Why'd we have to come all the way here?
The incident three years ago
with the peanut oil...
I know it was Shohei's mistake.
So that's what this is?
That's why he went to work for you.
-I didn't threaten him.
-I know that.
He couldn't work at my restaurant while
hiding the truth from Kyono and Aizawa.
That's why he came to you.
Shohei chose me, not you.
What's your plan?
I can't work at that restaurant
while I'm hiding the truth.
Shohei, if you're
going to quit French cuisine...
I'm not quitting.
I want to work at the restaurant
where I can make the best food I can.
In the restaurant judging,
the disciple that you raised
could become my secret weapon.
I don't know if he'll be of that much use,
but, to be honest,
I'm kind of looking forward
to see what kind of food
you guys can come up with.
-He's here.
-Sorry I'm late.
What did Tango say?
Nothing much.
He said he's excited
for the Tokyo Olympics.
No he didn't.
Why did Shohei go to Gaku?
It was his own decision.
What? After all that work we did together?
What a traitor.
He's been close to Tango
since they were in Paris.
That's right. He got worked hard by Obana,
so Tango often listened to his complaints.
I see.
Either way, he isn't quitting
French cuisine after all.
That's right.
Shohei Hirako will be back at it.
-Alright, let's go.
-Okay.
-Take the cart back.
ONE MONTH UNTIL TOP RESTAURANTS 50 RANKING
This year's Top Restaurants 50.
The award ceremony will be held in Tokyo,
which has attention from the Olympics.
The controversial Grand Maison Tokyo,
run by Natsuki Obana
has been selected as a candidate, right?
It was chosen by gourmets around the world
and members of the food
and beverage industry.
You'll have to ask them.
The Top Restaurants 50 competition
could be called a preliminary round
for Michelin reviews.
One of the most prestigious
awards in the world.
Does that mean we might be grouped in
with restaurants like El Bulli,
Noma and Francescana?
I don't know about that,
but it's a big deal.
Does this mean that
after all the fuss about Mr. Obana
we have a chance at a comeback?
It's not a chance.
If we make the ranking,
gourmets from around the world
and industry members
will come to eat here.
With that, Grand Maison Tokyo
will become a world-famous restaurant
overnight.
Shohei improved the lamb. Give it a try.
It's not just smoked.
I wrapped it in kombu
before grilling it to make it soft.
I smoked it with straw for fragrance,
and added bamboo shoots
and a flower kimchi.
I think the umami of the kombu
could be more present,
but this is a good start.
How is it, Mr. Eto?
Yeah. Not bad.
You've improved.
I'm glad I called you here.
-Thank you.
-Got it, guys?
Top Restaurant officials
will be visiting us in the coming month.
Our food and our service
can still be improved.
Let's aim to be the first Tokyo
restaurant to break the top 20!
Oui, chef!
Don't tell me you're not interested
in the Top Restaurants 50?
I don't like having my dishes criticized
by pompous foodies
who think they're critics.
This again?
-Are you a child?
-He is.
We don't have time
to think like that, Obana.
These are orders from the head chef.
With all our might,
we will fight for the Top Restaurants 50.
-Then we change the menu.
-Huh? Again?
But we only have a month.
One dish with seasonal ingredients.
Seasonal? What will you change?
Why do you want to change the fish menu?
We both liked the uni gratin, right?
That's true, but Japan has
the best fish in the world, right?
We want the world
to know our restaurant, right?
That is true.
No other country puts in as much effort
into eating every kind
of raw fish like Japan.
But then we'll have to make a dish
that fully shows off
the deliciousness of fresh fish.
That's exactly it.
I like your style, Chef Grandma!
-Watch your mouth, Gramps sous-chef.
-Welcome!
-Hello!
-What do you recommend today?
We've got some great mackerel
from Miyagi Prefecture.
-How big are they?
-At least four kilograms.
-Can I take a look?
-Sure. One mackerel!
Mackerel?
That's mackerel, right?
It's written as "spring fish."
Is it in season in spring?
In winter, before the spawning season,
the females become fatty and delicious.
-You know everything.
-You know nothing at all.
Here you are. What do you think?
-It's huge.
-This one is 4.9 kilograms. The best.
This looks great. We'll take two.
They're 10,000 yen a piece.
-Lowest price?
-You can take 'em for 13,000.
Alright! Get these in the truck!
So you'll be renewing
the seafood menu next?
Since most of the voting members
are foreigners,
fish dishes will be the key to winning.
Chef Tango.
I poached the grouper
in a pumpkin seed broth,
and added a walnut, beech herb
and malted barley sauce.
The style is too similar
to what you can get in any other country.
I see.
How about you, Shohei?
Give it a try.
This is monkfish papillote
wrapped in fig leaves
and steamed in mushroom and seaweed broth.
A mix of flavors
from the kombu and monkfish.
It has impact.
Let's work on this.
Thank you.
Chef Tango.
I'll contact a food researcher
and gather ideas for a fish dish.
Thank you.
This is grilled tripe.
On top, we have a mixture
of dill and chervil. Enjoy.
-Obana, is the kitchen okay?
-What?
We've been getting more customers lately.
We need more hall staff.
I'll leave it to you.
-Mr. Kyono, table four.
-Right.
-How's the cold soup, Moe?
-Almost ready.
Why do I have to help
with things other than desserts?
I'll take over, Moe. Thanks.
Thank you Mr. Aizawa, I'm saved.
I wish Chef Hirako were here.
Don't worry Moe,
I'll evolve into a super sub...
Don't touch that, Serita.
You're not ready yet
to touch the customers' food.
Chef, please acknowledge me.
Look at this perfect cutting.
It's better than Shohei's.
Serita, bring me a soup plate.
Okay.
FOR CUTTING PRACTICE
FROM ETO
CAN YOU COME TO GAKU TONIGHT?
Grand Maison Tokyo
is making a fish dish, too?
Perfect. Get me the recipe for that dish.
You're going to copy it?
Recipes don't have copyrights.
The recipe for an omelette
cooked in butter
has been copied worldwide countless times.
When you put it that way...
The biggest difference between
Gaku and Grand Maison Tokyo
is financial strength.
Even if we make the same food
with the same recipe,
we'll win with our finer ingredients.
We'll let you work here
if you continue the good work.
Starting your career
at a high-class restaurant
is the quickest path to success.
So? Let's hear it.
Come on now.
Oh? What are you doing here?
Nothing.
-Wait.
-Let go of me.
You really are a hard worker.
You've been doing 5 mm dicing.
None of your business.
What are you doing here yourself?
Everyone's talking about you.
I'm sick of it.
25 DAYS UNTIL TOP RESTAURANTS 50
Ms. Kanna? You mean the
food writer Ms. Kanna Kuzumi?
That's right.
She has a lot of knowledge about food,
so I think she might be a good addition.
We've been getting more customers too.
-Let's ask her.
-I'll contact her right away.
-Good morning.
-Morning.
You're here too, Kyono?
Yeah, talking about hall staff.
I think we found a good person.
Would you like some, Mr. Kyono?
I'm alright. I already ate.
-Okay.
-Thanks for the food.
Let's eat.
Oh, about the mackerel,
smoking or aging it might work well.
Maybe unlike a carpaccio or something,
it might be better slightly cooked.
I thought maybe we could
cook it as a meunière...
-No, not meunière.
-Don't be so negative.
We won't know until we try.
That will make it lose its freshness.
Those things can be adjusted.
Don't worry about it.
The cooking process can?
-Yes.
-Look at you.
I'm telling you it'll work out.
Well then, we'll have to compare
our cooking and see whose is better.
-Fine.
-What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
You want some food after all?
Yeah, maybe I'll have something after all.
I'll make one more for you.
-What is it?
-It's nothing.
I was just thinking that looks good.
-Want it?
-No.
-Mine is...
-I haven't touched it.
-Hurry up.
-Mine's over there.
No, I want to drink this first anyway.
I'll eat the one she's making.
This is Kanna.
She's been reporting on our restaurant.
She'll be working here as hall staff.
She speaks English and French
and knows a lot about food.
She's also a certified sommelier.
-She's just what we need.
-That's great.
I still have a lot to learn
and will need your help,
but I promise to do my best
to smile and stay positive.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Welcome to the team.
Oh, also, here's my resume.
Thanks for bringing this.
Could I have a look at the kitchen?
It's an honor to work with you, Mr. Obana.
Actually, ever since Escofille,
I've been a big fan of your cooking.
Thank you for your patronage.
Watch your back. He's quick with a knife
and even quicker with women.
-Move your hands, not your mouth.
-Sorry.
He doesn't look that way.
He minds his manners when he's cooking.
Let me know if you need anything.
We don't want to lose
a valuable talent like yours.
-You're kind. Thank you very much.
-Not at all.
-What if she's better than you?
-Whatever, I'm older.
-You can't even make a staff meal.
-Yes I can.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
I'm glad she's here.
Indeed.
Is something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
Sojiro Kuzumi?
It's you that holds the grudge, no?
Okay, let's choose
who'll make the staff meal today.
-Draw one, please.
-Pardon me!
Let me make the staff meal today.
I wanna eat something good.
Don't worry.
I've been working here too all this time.
-Okay, you're up.
-Really?
-Alright!
-Good luck.
-Seaweed salt.
-Oh, right.
EGG
RICE
CARROT, ONION, ZUCCHINI,
RED PEPPER, SALT, PEPPER
The meal is ready!
Five-millimeter veggie fried rice.
-Dig in.
-That's a lot.
-Pardon me.
-Thank you.
-Looks good.
-Thanks for the food.
Thank you.
This is awful.
If you use a freshly sharpened knife,
the metal taste gets in the food.
Oh, I see.
Using our bodies as much as we do,
do you really think we
only want veggies and rice?
But the rice is nice and crisp, no?
Clean up.
-I'll make something.
-Moe, none for me, please.
-I have to get Amelie.
-That time already?
-Be careful.
-Thanks. I'll be back soon.
Alright, see you soon.
-Be safe.
-Sure.
Let's see...
Wow, this is great.
What's wrong? Drink as much as you like.
Why'd you invite me here?
Me? It's just...
I thought you might be feeling down.
No, I'm fine.
-What?
-Nothing.
Shohei was just like that at first, too.
Shohei this, Shohei that.
Why don't you just hire him?
Sorry, I'm not trying to compare you.
It just happens. Forgive me.
Thank you.
It doesn't matter. I'm no good anyway.
I'm not skilled or talented
like everyone else.
Talent takes time to be understood.
In cooking, you see,
everyone has to start
not knowing if they're good or not.
But with effort and practice,
by building your skills,
you become aware of your own talents.
So what should I do?
Rinko and Obana won't say it,
but they're watching you.
Maybe it's that.
They don't want you to be someone
that just follows orders.
Maybe that's what they think.
Those two, you know,
put in more effort
and hard work than anyone.
-Roasting it is best.
-Definitely.
We made plenty of failures, too.
But now we know that roasting is best,
so I'd say it was worth it.
This is the best one.
We can confidently recommend
it to our guests.
The fish might benefit from a simple sauce
to bring out the flavor.
Let's ask Mr. Aizawa
what he thinks will work.
Sure.
But the problem...
...is the heat.
MAIN TITLE
20 DAYS UNTIL TOP RESTAURANTS 50
Thanks.
Alright.
Sorry.
See you later.
-You're not coming?
-I...
-I've got an errand.
-An errand?
It's nothing important.
-Be safe.
-See you later.
Alright.
Excuse me.
What is it? Forget something?
No. Um...
-Can I work here with you?
-What?
I want to learn how to fillet a mackerel.
Please!
What a pain.
-You'll start by cleaning.
-Okay!
-I'll make a thin one.
-Okay.
You have to put your hips
into it at a fish market.
-Here's the thin one.
-Okay.
-And the thick one.
-Great.
Ready?
Okay.
Too much heat.
The skin doesn't look
crunchy enough, either.
Should we keep it in the pan longer?
Let's add ten seconds.
Mackerel has a lot
of moisture to begin with,
so it's probably better to use
more salt at first.
-Let's try again.
-Okay.
When filleting into three pieces,
you follow the bones.
Don't overdo it.
Let the knife do the work. Got it?
-Yes.
-Look!
Check this out.
About two minutes.
-It's been about two minutes.
-Okay.
Should we set it to one minute?
This oven is a bit finicky.
-How's this?
-Good.
Almost there.
Go along the bones.
Carefully now. Good.
You're getting good.
Fennel, celery and Italian parsley.
Dill and capers. And what's this?
-Pomelo?
Crystal pomelo.
I made a light sauce
to preserve the delicate flavor
of the rare mackerel.
Well done, Mr. Aizawa.
And for sides?
It'll depend on how it's done each day,
but I'm thinking of
using a pan-seared tardivo.
-Shall we try?
-I hope it's a good match.
Serita, clean this up.
-Got it.
-I'll try roasting it again.
Sounds good.
Yum.
Crystal... pomelo...
Give it a try.
Even the throwaway parts are good.
-It's so good!
-Right? The whole fish is good.
FIFTEEN DAYS UNTIL TOP RESTAURANTS 50
Okay.
Everyone, come here please.
-Over here.
-Okay.
Wow.
Roasted mackerel with pomelo sauce.
We let the fatty female mackerel
sit out for one day to distribute the fat
and concentrate its umami.
The skin is crunchy,
and the center is cooked rare.
Wow! It's amazing.
It's roasted but almost raw in the middle.
Your pomelo sauce was perfect, Mr. Aizawa.
I wanted to try a girolle mushroom
and white wine sauce, too.
-How is it?
-It's out of this world.
Kyono?
I think we can serve it
to our guests with confidence.
-Great.
-Thank you.
Ouch!
Chef Rinko, see if we have
a wine to pair with this.
-Okay.
-Obana too. Get to it.
It's so good.
-I can help, Mr. Aizawa
-It's fine, I got it.
-I know how to do it.
-Get out of his way.
Moe, do we have more salt somewhere?
We do.
Alright.
At least carry one.
-Hey, Serita.
-What are you doing?
It's perfect, right?
-Oh no.
-Look.
It looks like Mr. Aizawa's cuts, right?
I think I did pretty good.
You fool. It's totally wrong.
-It's the same.
-We can't serve this.
It's the same. Why can't you...
I'm doing my best here!
What knife did you use?
You're not ready for this restaurant yet.
Fine. I'm done.
Cutting veggies here is a waste of time.
Then I quit myself!
Carry on.
-Mr. Aizawa.
-It's okay.
We have more.
Here. Like I promised.
Study notes?
I wrote that so no one would find out.
Don't worry about it.
You can skip that part.
It's in the back.
I just quit that damn restaurant.
Just like you said.
The only way to get good
is to work at a good restaurant.
It's my pleasure to work with you.
Understood. I'll put the word out.
You're really going to hire that punk kid?
Of course not.
It's up to you now.
Hey.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd pay your severance.
But we're struggling
with cash flow right now.
I don't need it.
Instead of that,
I'll get you a good meal.
MONKFISH, BUTTER
LEMON THYME, KARATACHI, KOMBU
MISO
Plating it.
This is it.
Yes.
Alright!
-We'll have Mr. Eto try it tomorrow.
-Okay.
10 DAYS UNTIL TOP RESTAURANTS 50
This is a bone-on poached monkfish
with lemon thyme, butter and liver.
Monkfish and liver on the same plate?
Please try it with the miso sauce.
Simple and refined,
with complex tastes and flavors.
It's incredible.
Shall we add it to the menu?
-Not yet.
-Why?
With the idea I got
from a food researcher,
I've ordered Kakitani
to make a fish dish as well.
I'd like to compare the two first.
Thanks for waiting.
Fatty mackerel with only the sides cooked?
A roast?
The outside is fragrant,
but the center is rare.
It's complimented with a pomelo sauce.
It looks simple,
but I think this wonderful dish
will become a unique Gaku staple.
Go ahead.
Give it a try.
This is...
Here's your amuse.
Please eat directly with your hand.
Take your time. Enjoy.
-Welcome.
I'll show you to your seat.
Right this way.
Thank you.
Chef Tango!
-Welcome.
Thank you for coming.
I have voting rights, you know.
Of course I'm here.
Please enjoy your meal.
This is a goat's milk bavarois.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's great.
Somehow, even more delicious than usual.
I sample all of our dishes myself, too,
our food is different
than other restaurants.
In each of the dishes we serve,
the cooks have added a part of their soul.
That's why good food
is made even better
when it's for the customer.
Sorry, I'm talking too much.
Please take your time.
-Let's make the fish.
-Oui, chef.
-Let's make the new fish dish!
-Oui, chef!
Make Linda's dishes perfect.
Roast mackerel with pomelo sauce.
It's superb.
-Thank you.
-Great work.
You must be so busy.
We're doing very well.
He's been helping us as well.
I'm Gaku's new sous-chef, Shohei Hirako.
Have we met before?
I used to work
at a place called Escofille.
That's right.
Perhaps it's thanks to you
the food reminded me
of Escofille's heyday.
Sorry, that's rude of me.
The fish was absolutely unique
and wonderful.
Thank you.
Thank you for the meal.
Serita.
Thanks for coming today.
Of course. I'll pay.
We won't accept your money.
We served you food
that we can't serve our guests.
The roast mackerel.
Compared to the test product,
I felt like it had a smell.
So you noticed?
We used your fillet.
If you fillet with a knife you used
to cut pungent vegetables,
that residue will transfer to the fish
and degrade its flavor.
Remember that.
That's why you said mine was different?
I know you asked the fishmonger
to teach you how to cut a fillet.
But that's just basic knowledge.
The place you work
is trying to get three stars.
Don't take food lightly.
-Forgive me!
-Hey.
I betrayed you all.
I sold your recipe to Mr. Eto at Gaku.
I was being paid to spy.
I can't believe it.
I'm sorry.
Listen.
Don't you know what will happen
if you give that recipe away?
They said they would use better mackerel.
That's why
if they got the recipe,
Grand Maison Tokyo would lose.
I've made a mess of all your effort.
I'm sorry.
You're so naive.
They can't copy the dishes
we put so much thought into.
When you're at this level,
a recipe doesn't guarantee results.
The best chefs
don't worry about their
recipes getting out.
Because they know they can
make it better than anyone.
Go ahead.
-This is...
-It's no good.
The umami from the fat isn't there.
It hasn't been aged right.
The heat is all wrong.
This is nothing but a fried fish!
But I followed the recipe perfectly.
What should we do, Mr. Eto?
We'll serve the monkfish.
It's superb.
Based on the condition of the fish,
the recipe has to be adaptable.
The drying time,
the temperature of the oven.
Even the temperature
and humidity outdoors.
If you think you can copy it, just try!
It's not just for the mackerel roast.
The pressed eggplant
and the roast venison too,
none of our dishes can be copied.
We don't mess around here.
There are plenty who try to copy us.
But if you want three stars,
you have to make the real thing yourself.
So which are you, Serita?
What kind of chef do you want to be?
You've got to decide for yourself.
Um...
Can I try making the staff meal again?
Please.
Alright.
Even the throwaway parts are good.
-It's so good!
-Right?
The whole fish is good.
EGG
RICE, SESAME OIL, SALT, PEPPER, SOY SAUCE,
CARROTS, ONIONS, ZUCCHINI, MACKEREL
-Here you are.
-Thanks for the meal.
Yum. This is great.
It's great.
The flavor of the mackerel comes through.
-Thank you.
-The flavor could use work.
The heating was uneven.
It might not need zucchini.
It could use more color.
Even so, I can tell that you used
all of your skill and experience
to create a dish that would make us happy.
-Thank you.
-Thanks for the meal.
Cut the mackerel after you clean up.
-What?
-It's fine right?
Of course.
-Check on him, Mr. Aizawa.
-Are you sure?
Can I really stay?
You're the prep cook, right?
That was tasty.
Thank you.
I've been reminded,
since cooking with you again.
You really are a genius, Mr. Tango.
Since the Top Restaurant survey started,
I've been scared every day.
I wake up, look in the mirror,
and somehow muster up
the strength to come here.
If I really were a genius,
I should be having more fun.
Everyone gets nervous.
Obana doesn't.
He always enjoyed himself.
I'm kind of looking forward
to see what kind of food
you guys can come up with.
Even when being judged
by the world's strictest gourmet critics
he just laughed.
Shohei, I know
that you'd rather work for Obana.
You probably came to Gaku
because you thought you could
make great dishes as a way
to pay Obana back.
-Mr. Tango.
-It's fine.
From when we were training at L'Ambroisie,
Obana had the power to fire people up.
But I've worked so hard for this.
I can't lose to a brand new restaurant.
To a man who spent three years on the run,
I refuse to lose.
-What should we do for sides tomorrow?
-Good question.
-How about chicory? I saw it for sale.
-Nope.
There you go again. Then what?
How about wasabi leaves? That'd be fun.
-Wasabi leaves?
-Obana's having fun.
Thanks to Ms. Rinko.
It's because she's the chef.
Obana is free to do his thing.
Could it be?
Obana at his best right now?
If he can keep it up.
DAY OF TOP RESTAURANTS 50
TOP RESTAURANTS 50
So you're working at Grand Maison Tokyo?
-I am.
-What's your plan?
It depends on what happens
to the restaurant.
Obana and the Escofille crew
getting their groove back
at Grand Maison Tokyo...
I simply won't allow it.
We will now begin the award ceremony
for 2019's Top Restaurants 50.
Welcome to the Top Restaurants 50, 2019.
It's time now to start the award ceremony.
It's showtime!
We will get three stars!
I'm here to take Amelie with me.
I won't give her up.
Do you think a chef has time
to raise a child?
You can't beat mom's cooking.
I'm going to make a new dish.
It's overwhelming work.
It's impossible.
Welcome.
A special lunch for a princess.
Have faith.
You'll get your family back.
Acknowledge that chefs aren't foolish!
We will now announce the top ten.
This time, we can do it.
Dad!
Good luck.
Subtitle translation by: