SEVEN DAYS UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
An open kitchen, huh?
I want diners to enjoy
a vibrant view of cooking.
What about the menu?
Just the chef's recommended course.
Including appetizers, there are a total
of ten dishes, and no à la carte options.
How presumptuous
to not let the customers choose.
Aren't there any floor staff?
I'll handle the floor by myself.
The kitchen staff will also be serving.
The best dishes will be served
directly by the chefs.
Is she really such a gourmet?
Restaurants praised by Linda have
their reservations booked for a year.
But also, many famous places
closed after poor reviews.
That's no joke.
So Mr. Obana, who dated
such an amazing person...
He's just a chef who likes women.
I see.
You're doing the pre-opening, right?
You'll be inviting people
who supported you and Chef Rinko, right?
-Yes.
-Could you invite me as well?
Pardon?
I'll feature it in Marie Claire Dining.
I'll write it.
How about it? Head chef Rinko Hayami.
It'll be crowded on opening day
so I'll invite you on another day.
Kyono, can you save a spot for me?
Of course.
-Then, I'll invite you.
-Mr. Obana!
I'm glad. I'm looking forward to it.
What'll we do? Suddenly,
our pre-opening has become a fateful day.
It's exciting and good.
If we receive a poor review,
our restaurant might close.
Why did you invite her?
I don't trust critics
who brag about their knowledge of food.
They often collude with restaurants
and distort evaluations for money.
Then it's even worse.
But Linda is different.
She's a true gourmet
who genuinely loves cooking.
If we provide good food and service,
she'll give a good review.
You seem to hold her in high regard.
If the head chef keeps running away
like this, we won't get three stars.
I'm not running away!
But geez...
Because of you, we have to do this!
But there's a problem.
The dessert.
What? Isn't it already complete?
Linda places a lot of
importance on dessert.
Let's try to improve it in a week.
There's no time for that.
We're already short-staffed...
NEW STAFF (CHEF DE PARTIE)
HIKARU KAKITANI
If we work overnight, we'll manage.
If you keep doing things your way,
no one will follow.
Kakitani, you don't have to do it.
It's true that we can't run a restaurant
with just us.
We'll get more chefs
before the pre-opening.
Then, there's someone I want to bring in.
-Sorry for coming repeatedly.
-What do you want?
Mr. Obana says
there's someone he wants to recruit.
-Really?
-Looks like you're needed.
Moe Matsui, right?
Oh! You were here before.
We're opening
a three-star French restaurant.
Would you like to be the pastry chef?
Huh?
If it's this one, you'll do it.
Which one is it?
Huh?
-Thank you.
-Good job.
Félicitations, Tango, congratulations.
Linda.
I came from Paris just to see you.
The real reason you came to Japan
is because of Obana, right?
You've been a huge fan
of Obana since long ago.
Is that so? I was the first
to recognize your skills.
Did you come to help his restaurant?
As if.
The repercussions of that lunch
didn't only hurt Escofille.
I recommended that restaurant
to the government.
When allergenic ingredients were used,
my reputation was also ruined.
Did you come for revenge?
You're not the type to let personal
feelings affect your evaluations.
I'm Moe Matsui.
I'm here today for a visit.
I'm thinking of having her
be the pastry chef.
SIX DAYS UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
I'm completely in favor!
It's not decided yet.
We need to hear Ms. Moe's opinion too.
Who are you, lady?
I'm the head chef!
Totally unexpected!
What kind of dishes does this place make?
We use Japanese ingredients
to bring out the natural flavors.
Here's our menu.
For dessert, there's meringue ice cream
and Mont Blanc.
I'm confident in the meringue,
but I plan to improve the Mont Blanc.
I'd like to taste it.
This is the Mont Blanc.
It's really delicious!
Can you match this level?
Honestly, the appearance is lacking.
It's not something
you'd want to take photos of.
-It's lacking in finesse.
-That's harsh.
Finesse? Less experienced people
often say that.
Here.
Confectionery Competition Rookie Award.
World Pastry Design Award.
-You won the Loir Award at 25?
-Unbelievable.
-Yes.
-What is that?
Pâtisserie Herbe,
the famous shop in Daikanyama?
I got bored and quit after six months.
Boulangerie Node, Chef Motoki,
Anterose Aoyama.
They're all famous places.
So why are you working
at that buffet place?
Well, I wanted to make
various things at once.
-That's impressive!
-Experience doesn't matter.
You need to be able
to make delicious food.
So, can you make a dessert
better than this?
Do you have chestnuts?
You'll make it now?
Not right now, but I can manage
in about five hours.
It took us over a month to make this.
Honestly, time doesn't matter.
No matter how hard they try,
people without talent will never succeed.
Talented chefs can create
delicious food right away.
It doesn't matter how hard you try
if you can make something delicious.
That's true.
But since that's hard to achieve
for most people,
chefs around the world
struggle with all their might.
But I can do it.
I can make a dessert
with more finesse than anyone here.
-I see.
-Yes.
They're hiring a young woman
from a hotel to be their pastry chef.
How do you know so much about them?
This industry is small.
Stop being so underhanded.
Aren't we allies?
Once again...
Let's join hands
and win that three-star rating!
Got it?
It's done. Here's the Mont Blanc!
What are you doing?
I upload photos of desserts I make
to see how people react.
It'll get a lot of likes.
The thinly stretched
sugar decoration is unique.
It's delicious.
-You made it quickly.
-Thank you.
-But...
-This is no good.
Huh?
You've let me down.
Wait a minute, what's wrong with this
perfect Mont Blanc?
We're not a pâtisserie specializing
in desserts or a hotel buffet.
In French cuisine, desserts play
a crucial role in finishing the course.
This doesn't fulfill that role.
But it's prettier and more refined
than the other one.
If you want to brag,
then do it at your own shop.
I see, you don't want to admit defeat.
I admit, the appearance is excellent.
But the liqueur flavor is too strong,
and despite using chestnuts,
the flavor and fragrance
of those chestnuts are missing.
That's a fatal flaw.
That's...
The concept of Grand Maison Tokyo
is to bring out the taste
and aroma of Japanese ingredients.
That doesn't belong on our menu.
Then I'll make it again.
We don't have time to keep testing you.
We'll improve it ourselves.
What should we do?
-Then I'll make it too.
-What?
If my dessert tastes better,
put it on the menu.
-I decline.
-You can leave now.
You called me, didn't you?
I already told you, you let me down!
So try my dessert again!
Now, now. If she wants to,
let her make it again.
I want to try it too,
so bring it before the pre-opening.
Okay.
What do you think?
She has the skills
to back up her arrogance.
The innovative design
is something Obana lacks.
There was a distinct feminine cuteness.
The look of desserts
can make a place popular.
So we might need her design sense.
But if the head chef and sous-chef
both say no, then it's no good.
She didn't clean up anything
before she left.
But what if she makes a better dessert?
It might be tough with her current skills.
You never know what might happen
with a good mentor.
No way.
Even if we make something better,
Mr. Obana won't admit defeat.
I don't think that's true.
I've never been acknowledged by Mr. Obana.
He only acknowledges his own cooking.
THREE YEARS AGO, ESCOFILLE
The consommé is too strong
and overpowers the lobster.
Try harder.
But Shohei, weren't you surprised
when you returned to Tokyo?
You were only just a trainee under Obana,
but when you joined the hotel,
you were better than the other chefs.
In the three years and six months
at Escofille, you grew the most.
You're now the head chef
responsible for the hotel restaurant.
How about it?
Don't you want to see?
How well the current you will fare
against Natsuki Obana?
This is our menu.
What kind of dish would you add
to the end of this course?
Nice! This'll get so many likes.
-Is that a new dessert?
-Huh?
No, it's just something I'm working on...
Wait a minute.
You think you'll beat Mr. Obana with this?
Huh?
You're a skilled chef, but...
Don't take cooking lightly.
Chef Hirako, what are you saying?
Desserts in a French restaurant
are part of the course.
They play an important role
in finishing the meal.
Have you looked at this menu?
It's not just Mr. Obana.
Multiple professional chefs
got together with their ideas
and spent time failing repeatedly
until they finally decided on that menu.
After these incredible dishes,
you can't just serve
this Mont Blanc drowned in liqueur.
You really are his apprentice.
You sound just like him.
I'm not his apprentice.
If we're doing this, we have to win.
What?
You can't win alone, so I'll help.
Who are you to decide that?
This is my competition.
This is our competition.
Answer me.
Oui, Chef...
We'll go to one more place.
FOUR DAYS UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
To buy more?
Where did you park?
Go right!
Here it is.
There are so many types.
What are you going to buy?
-I'm picking yours.
-What?
You'll need your own knife soon.
What?! Are you finally acknowledging me?
I'm glad I worked hard.
I'll take this one.
Choose a petty knife.
Didn't you see me looking at them?
Those are the petty knives?
Then I'll take this one.
Try holding it.
When cutting, your fingers
shouldn't touch the blade.
Omiya and Namiki will handle
the hall and ingredients.
We're counting on you.
The table numbers
are one, two, three, four.
The large table is five.
Four mains for table five.
Oui, Chef.
-Be careful, it's dangerous.
-That's too narrow.
The flow between tables
six and seven is crowded.
-Should we widen it?
-Would that be better?
A personal knife is really different.
Treat your kitchen tools with care.
-And take good care of them.
-Don't worry, I'm doing that.
Because I was acknowledged by Mr. Obana.
-Hey!
-You startled me!
Don't just throw it away.
We could still use it.
Sorry.
It reminds me of when you taught Shohei.
If this was back then, I'd be kicking him.
I remember after being told off by Obana,
he made a dish with discarded vegetables.
Shohei's cheap dish.
Yes, that's it.
If you add fruit or vinegar,
the flavor of chestnuts disappears.
But without other ingredients,
it's just chestnuts.
There must be a way
to bring out the chestnut flavor.
Theoretically, dairy products
should be perfect for chestnuts.
This is it.
Not the shell. It's inedible.
We might be able to extract
the aroma and flavor. Let's try.
I'LL BE WORKING LATE, GO TO BED FIRST
I want to bring out a bit more
of the chestnut aroma.
TWO DAYS UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
Can we make people taste
a different side of chestnuts?
How about using chestnut shell?
Interesting. The astringency could
enhance the sweetness of the chestnuts.
Let's try it.
Obana.
Look. Ms. Moe posted
a new chestnut dessert.
They're using chestnut shell
to bring out the aroma.
How did she come up with such an idea?
Ah! Maybe...
The only one who makes cheap dishes
with discarded ingredients is him.
A hotel buffet chef
sure has a lot of time.
Is it the guy named Shohei helping her?
Damn it...
The astringency of the shell is there,
but can we bring out the chestnut more?
Did we overuse the sugar
to capture the tannins?
No, the astringency is balanced,
but I want to enhance the aroma.
-Let's roast the chestnut shell.
-Roast it?
Then it might give off a nutty aroma.
ONE DAY UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
-This is it!
-Chestnuts!
It's completely different.
It's delicious.
Good.
This is amazing!
Like my mouth is filled with chestnuts!
I'll leave the plating to you.
Is the recipe ready?
Huh?
It's your dish.
Yes, with this, I'm sure I can beat him.
Then go now.
At this late hour?
If it's those people,
they'll still be preparing.
18 HOURS UNTIL THE PRE-OPENING
It seems almost done, but what's missing?
It's done.
It's a Mont Blanc. Please try it.
You took out the caramel.
You used roasted chestnut shell?
Yes, but why?
You managed to use
the aroma of roasted chestnuts.
It was created in an instant
with intuition and inspiration...
How is it?
Can you make 24 servings
for tomorrow's dinner?
I want to add this to our menu.
Can you do it?
That'll be easy.
Then let's do it.
What about the consommé?
We should add more red currant.
Moe, good job.
-Please do well tomorrow.
-Okay.
Also, pass this along.
Where did you put it?
Isn't it there?
It's delicious.
Serita.
Mr. Kakitani, what are you doing?
I'm heading home.
Did you just finish work?
Yes.
I'm a chef now but they had me
cleaning the exhaust fan until this late.
Tomorrow is the pre-opening.
I wonder how it will turn out.
I'm looking forward to it.
PRE-OPENING DAY
Good morning.
You look pretty good.
Right?
It's gold?
Silver...
Damn Kyono... He used different colors.
You really hate losing?
Did you sleep well?
Yeah.
Well...
Shall we start?
Oui, Chef.
We have 24 guests today.
Mr. Sugita at table five
cannot eat celery,
and Mr. Kano at table ten
cannot drink alcohol.
The table flowers are dianthus flowers.
Their meaning is "boldness"
as a tribute to Ms. Rinko, who risked
everything to open this restaurant.
Ms. Rinko, please.
Somehow, we've reached this day.
It's thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
We haven't done anything yet.
That's right.
Ms. Linda will come today and...
If she gives a harsh review,
this place might close down.
But let's serve the dishes
we've prepared just as we've planned.
For the guests...
Let's make sure
they enjoy our masterpiece.
And one more thing,
I'll set the rules for Grand Maison Tokyo.
Whenever someone greets a guest
in the dining area,
let's all greet them together.
The same for when a guest is leaving.
It's an open kitchen, so
you'll be in the same space as the guests.
Let's serve with heartfelt hospitality!
Oui, Chef!
Let's serve the best dishes
and the best service,
just like always!
Let's do this!
Moe, relax!
Just focus on the dessert.
It'll be easy.
PRE-OPENING
-Thank you for waiting.
-Welcome.
Welcome.
-Thank you.
-Be careful, it's steep.
I heard my pastry chef
is making the dessert.
Thank you for coming. Please, go ahead.
Welcome. I'll take care of your bag.
Thank you for coming.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll take your coat over here.
Welcome!
All the guests have arrived.
Orders coming in.
Today's course is for 24 people.
Oui, Chef!
This is complimentary champagne.
FIRST DISH ~AMUSE~
GIROLLE MUSHROOMS AND HIMO PEPPER SABLE
Thank you.
-Tables two and seven.
-Okay.
Serita, please do the dishes.
Understood.
-I'll put the bavarois here.
-Thank you.
-Table two.
-Okay.
This is a goat milk bavarois.
SECOND DISH ~ENTRÉE~
GOAT MILK BAVAROIS
The salt and olive oil should stand out.
Delicious.
Table five has finished.
Kakitani, is the crispy eggplant ready?
-Ready.
-I'll do the plating.
Oui, Chef.
Excuse me.
Eggplant and white liver pressé.
THIRD DISH ~ENTRÉE~
EGGPLANT AND WHITE LIVER PRESSÉ
MUSSELS, MOROCCAN BEANS,
WHITE CELERY, LEMONGRASS
CLAM BROTH, SUDACHI PEEL,
SUDACHI JUICE, GARLIC
FOURTH DISH ~ENTRÉE~
MONT SAINT-MICHEL MUSSEL COLD SOUP
This is Mont Saint-Michel mussel
cold soup.
NORTHERN CLAMS, WILD MUSHROOMS, OLIVE OIL,
BUTTER, GARLIC, ONION, PARSLEY
This is mushroom and
northern clam vol-au-vent.
FIFTH DISH ~ENTRÉE~
MUSHROOM AND NORTHERN CLAM VOL-AU-VENT
This is grilled beef tripe.
SIXTH DISH ~ENTRÉE~
GRILLED BEEF TRIPE
-For table 15.
-Yes.
Here.
Now, prepare the fish dish
before the main course.
Kakitani, bring out the sea urchin.
-Serita, call him.
-Yes.
Ms. Rinko!
Mr. Kakitani is missing!
Mr. Aizawa, please bring the sea urchin.
Got it.
Ooh la la!
It hasn't been prepared at all.
But Mr. Kakitani said he did it...
How could this happen?!
He's not answering his phone.
What about the guests?
Waiting more than 15 minutes
is unacceptable. What should we do?
We'll have to apologize
to the guests and remove this dish.
We can make it possible!
I won't remove one dish.
Everyone, help out.
-I'll help too.
-Don't touch it.
-Remove the innards.
-Okay.
Would you like more wine?
It's been handled.
Good job.
They won't be able to serve the fish.
Now Ms. Linda's harsh criticism
is coming for sure.
-Aizawa, fill this once you've washed it.
-Oui.
When will the next dish come out?
It'll be out soon.
Did something happen?
The fish dish is late.
There's a problem.
Preparing the sea urchin is taking time.
Are you preparing it now?
Won't you help?
What?
If you help, we can make it.
Don't be ridiculous.
Please!
Mr. Obana doesn't need me.
Then show that you're needed.
Obana is just too stubborn to admit it.
I know that he wants you here the most.
I'm helping so we can get to the dessert.
Where's the disinfectant?
It's over here.
-Serita.
-Yes?
Take this over there.
Shohei?
I'll put it here.
Don't remove the roe from the shell.
You don't need to tell me.
Amazing...
Serita, the tray and tweezers.
Yes, understood.
-Serita, take this.
-Yes.
Shohei hated doing menial tasks
and wanted to be promoted quickly.
So he practiced preparation
more than anyone else.
Ms. Moe, focus on your task.
Yes.
-Chef.
-It's ready.
-The seasoning is done.
-I'll plate it.
Oui, Chef.
Thank you for waiting.
Here is the sea urchin gratin.
SEVENTH DISH ~POÍSSON~
SEA URCHIN GRATIN
Excuse me.
The sea urchin gratin is served.
Thank you.
Shohei.
Roasted Honshu venison loin
with blood consommé.
EIGHTH DISH ~VÍANDE~
ROASTED HONSHU VENISON LOIN WITH CONSOMMÉ
It's not gamey at all.
-Let's start from table five.
-Yes.
Excuse me.
Meringue ice cream.
NINTH DISH ~DESSERT~
MERINGUE ICE CREAM
Mont Blanc à ma façon.
-May I take a photo?
-Take as many as you like.
Please take this to table six.
Here is the Mont Blanc à ma façon.
TENTH DISH ~DESSERT~
MONT BLANC À MA FAÇON
THE SEA URCHIN GRATIN WAS DELICIOUS!
#GRANDMAISONTOKYO
The sea urchin dish came out!
Thank you.
Thank you for visiting us today.
The fish dish was a bit delayed,
but the first day is always hectic.
Good work today.
Um, how did you like the dessert?
We worked hard to improve it for you.
For me?
Could you share your thoughts with
the person in charge of the dessert?
Sure.
Go.
The first dish that came out
was the meringue ice cream.
It was misted with a strong brine.
The taste changed each time I ate it.
The appearance was simple, but it was fun
and interesting till the end.
But the Mont Blanc à ma façon...
It was magnificent.
It was even better.
Did you use chestnut shell?
The roasted richness and astringency
were a great idea to enhance
the chestnut flavor and taste.
The aftertaste was refreshing,
making it a perfect finish.
Most of all,
the presentation was beautiful.
It was a great meal.
Thank you.
I'll be right back.
Your cooking has changed.
You, the selfish chef
who ruined the summit
and disappeared without a word to me...
Has there been a change of heart?
I think you might be mistaken.
That isn't my cooking.
It's Chef Rinko Hayami's food.
You hold her in quite high regard.
I hope you visit again.
Do you think I'll keep this place open?
If I know Linda Machiko Richard,
she never lies about taste.
Take care.
It seems that
Ms. Moe's Mont Blanc was better.
Seems that way.
Mr. Obana acknowledged it.
I'm sorry!
Saying it was easy was a lie.
Actually, that Mont Blanc...
was a recipe created
with all of Chef Hirako's efforts.
Really? I see.
How hard you two worked was evident
the moment it touched my lips.
No.
I only made the shape.
I committed a big sin against all of you
who worked so hard for today.
I'm truly sorry.
But that Mont Blanc
was delicious and beautiful.
That's why Chef Rinko served it.
But diners don't care
about how much effort we put in.
The Mont Blanc made diners happy.
That's all that matters.
I said I could do this and that
with intuition...
I'm sorry.
I...
want to study more.
I want to work harder.
So...
Please let me work here.
Please.
What will you do?
Our place will be quite tough.
-Thank you.
-Let's do our best.
It's identical to our recipe.
Shohei really is your apprentice.
What do you mean?
We use hazelnuts so ours is much better.
That's a matter of taste.
The presentation was enjoyable too.
Ms. Rinko made the right call.
Aren't you going to hire Shohei?
Your interest in Moe
was because of Shohei, wasn't it?
That's something he has to decide.
Thank you! You really saved us.
I finally understand
why Mr. Obana didn't acknowledge me.
I was just simply...
unable to make delicious dishes.
Try harder.
Obana said
that the quiche is a lot better.
What?
The quiche you improved.
He said the almonds were a great idea.
I see.
THANKS TO CHEF HIRAKO
WE MADE THE BEST DESSERT!
Yo.
Mr. Kakitani, why did you
suddenly disappear?
I have someone to introduce to you.
Huh?
Good evening.
Here is my card.
-Mr. Eto, you're the one bothering us...
-This contains 100,000 yen.
I'll pay you monthly if you give me
your new recipes and information.
You're frustrated because
of your tiny pay and late hours.
And you can't even
touch the ingredients, right?
Don't touch it.
Forget about the hard work.
Use this to blow off some steam.
Here, take it.
I'm telling you to take it.
"Japan's rich..."
"Using Japan's rich ingredients,
the innovative French food
at Grand Maison Tokyo..."
"May shape new gastronomic..."
How do we translate this?
"Trends"?
"May shape new..."
"...gastronomic trends."
It's high praise.
The article about
Grand Maison Tokyo is creating a stir.
The retweets have already
exceeded 30,000.
I see.
Linda evaluated us properly.
You should read to the end.
What?
At the end, it mentions that Obana,
who caused
the allergy incident three years ago
in Paris, took the position of sous-chef.
Why include something like that?
Perhaps the perpetrator who
introduced allergens three years ago...
VIOLENT CHEF
...may strike again.
You've been following them.
What do you think?
I think I've figured it out.
Who is it?
The person who envies
Natsuki Obana the most.
-Are you Mr. Natsuki Obana?
-Geez...
I'd like to discuss the incident
in Paris three years ago.
Who are you?
I absolutely cannot
let that restaurant fail.
-We'll sell curry.
-Curry?!
Grand Maison Tokyo
is getting flamed online.
I'm quitting the hotel and French cuisine.
You're helping me.
If customers won't come to us,
how about we take it outside to sell?
Wildly Delicious B-Grade Three-Star Curry!
Grand Maison Tokyo isn't going anywhere.
Sell, sell. Sell as much as possible.
This is getting interesting.
-Rinko!
-Call an ambulance!