My heart is burning
Towards the distance
The past is like a dagger
It's broken my wings
I still have to fly
Following the light
I'll forget you
I'll break through the stubbornness
I'll use the light in the dark night
To return to the long yearning in the dark night
I'll climb the river of life and never forget the madness
The Long Ballad
Zixin, the water is ready
Doctor Su and Nuer went to the front to scout the road
They've already found the person who will replace us
Follow the team to continue to the outskirts
Then go back to the prairie
But according to our current schedule
We should be able to get there in half a month
Half a month
Half a month is too long
We have to hurry
Yes
That is
Why is there a corpse there?
Why is it this guy?
Deqin, what's wrong with you?
Ya Luo
Go find a place to rest
Yes
Deqin, let me carry it
No need
When did Deqin like to be so nosy?
It's like a treasure
Search carefully
We need to find the person alive
We need to find the corpse
Yes
Deqin
Wei Shuyu
Congratulations
You took Li Changge's life
And shot him in the head
You did a great job to defeat the rebels
I have to report to His Highness
And tell him about your plan
Hao Du, you are too vicious
You don't know whether Changge is guilty or not
It doesn't matter what I think
I am a father
I will do as my father says
But I have to tell you
There is no such thing as beauty in this world
If you want to help the Wei family
Just do it
Deqin
This is the place where the rebels usually rest
No one should come
Go get the wine and medicine
And get a suit of clothes
Yes
Go
Shameless
Why are you hitting me?
What are you doing?
You said what I am doing
What did you see?
You are a man
What's there to see?
Then why are your eyes blind?
I don't like to see the snow stars
I am not interested in your wounds
I want to see you
Do you think I am a fool?
Yes
Then I don't want to see your eyes
I want to see your eyes
If you want to see my eyes
Then I will do it
I'm sorry.
Since you're so capable,
do it yourself.
I didn't ask you to help me.
Listen to me.
Aliqi.
What do you mean?
The elite pourquoi of the western region.
I'm much better. Thank you.
Are you crazy?
Hold on.
It's a man. Give him the medicine.
Don't touch me!
Don't yell like a mother.
You can't wait until now.
Leave him alone.
Let's go.
I'll go.
Father, you're...
Prince Qin came just now.
He was scolded by me.
I believe he'll send someone to
punish me.
Father, I'll go prepare the horse.
You go back to your hometown to raise the goods.
I'll go find Mr. Du.
Shuyu, I'm not a coward.
It's just
I've got Waner involved.
Father, I'm useless.
I can't catch A'ye
and defend Wei.
Get up.
I did what I did.
How does it concern you?
Prince Qin came today.
He's really a brave man.
If I want to follow Prince Qin in the future,
I won't stop you.
A'ye, I don't know if
I made the right choice.
Mr. Wei, this is what the Crown Prince asked me to give you.
A'ye, I can't.
I'll beg the Crown Prince. I'll beg Mr. Du.
Shuyu.
A'ye.
Take it.
Mr. Wei, take your time.
I'll go find Mr. Du.
Take your time.
A'ye.
A'ye, I can't.
I'll beg the Crown Prince. I'll beg Mr. Du.
You're young.
How did I teach you?
Let go.
Cucin.
The palace often says that Mr. Wei is a cuckold.
The Crown Princess and the Crown Prince are in the palace.
They are all in good health.
Today, they are in bad health.
Mr. Wei is a cuckold.
A'ye.
A'ye, I can't.
I'm being petty.
But the King of Qin is capable of taking advantage of the situation.
Although we are in different camps,
I won't say it out loud, but I know
that the King of Qin is kind and kind.
But he also has his own ways of killing.
This change cannot be stopped.
If I can defend myself for the sake of Zhong Zhen,
but the land we have is still the land of Tang.
The people of Yun Yun are still the people of Tang.
Isn't my life's wish
to protect Tang?
A'ye, I understand.
Zhong Yisheng has never captured many people.
This Cucin
makes me feel so blessed.
I'm so happy.
Come, drink some water.
It was my misunderstanding to previous time.
If you can give me life, I will definitely...
No need.
Let's not be Ov Wohnung I'm not against you.
Can you give me another drink?
Sure.
But I never do business with you.
How about we exchange drinks? I'll give you a drink.
You answer my question.
How about it?
We come and go.
Let's play a game. Do you dare?
I don't dare to play a game.
Let's ask each other a question.
Whoever doesn't answer the question,
will be punished with a large amount of wine.
Okay.
You ask.
Where did you get the sword wound?
From the Imperial Army.
You're so honest.
Since we exchanged drinks, I can't lie.
It's my turn.
How should I call you?
My surname is Qin.
One word is correct.
You can call me A'Zhuang.
A'Zhuang.
What about you?
My surname is Li.
I'm ranked 14th.
You can call me the 14th.
Why do you insist on my sword wound?
I just want to see you look ugly.
I know you're a bad person.
A'Zhuang, where are you from?
I'm from Central Plains.
I was born in Sai Wan.
Then you're from...
That's another question.
Next,
where is the 14th Wolf going?
To avenge.
Where are you going?
To avenge the north.
What are you doing in the north?
I'm doing a big business.
Since you're back, why do you still want to drink?
Because you'll ask me
what business I'm doing.
I can't answer.
I'm afraid I'll get drunk if I keep drinking.
Then I'll ask you one last question.
Is A'Zhun really A'Zhun?
Is the 14th Wolf really the 14th Wolf?
Come on.
What is Te Qin talking to that guy?
I haven't heard him laugh like this in a long time.
Te Qin has been in charge of Eagle Division for so many years.
But he has been suspected by Da Ke Han.
And there's that dead man everywhere.
In that environment,
you're the one who's going to be punished.
You know that.
That's true.
But it's okay not to mention it.
So as not to spoil the mood.
But I haven't seen anyone
who Te Qin is so concerned about.
Your Highness.
The spread of the rumors
has nothing to do with Princess Yong Ning.
I'm afraid someone else did it.
As for Princess Yong Ning,
I'm incompetent.
I let her escape.
Fine.
For many days,
the heavy troops in the capital have been sleeping in.
Even if she has actions,
she never loves.
You should be more careful.
Yes.
Ke Ming.
What else do you want?
The two things Chang Ge took away
are the important weapons of the court.
No matter what,
can't it be taken away by someone else?
I understand.
Wei Zheng is right.
I'm the most ruthless person in the world.
Princess.
Mr. Du.
His Highness is inside.
Go in.
Go.
He Qi.
Let's get up.
Where's the boy?
Went.
Went?
Why didn't you tell him and he left?
Su Yishe.
Send food and fire back to Eagle Division.
Tell them to prepare these.
Wait for me outside Youzhou.
And
give this to Great Khan.
Don't worry, Tuxi.
Go.
Tuxi.
What should we do after we go to Youzhou?
I've already asked Su Yishe
to prepare the food and fire.
Okay.
Greetings, Father.
It's rare to see you come to see me.
What's up?
Nothing.
I just want to visit you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
If there's nothing else,
you should go back to rest.
I have a lot of things to do.
I actually want to
ask Changge...
I beg you not to hurt him.
He's just a little bit more aggressive.
But he...
Yan'er.
Forget about this world.
There's still Changge.
It's good for you and him.
Father.
Your Highness.
Someone is here.
They're here to see Her Highness.
His Majesty heard that Her Highness
was very kind and willing to marry into the grassland.
He asked me to send him a gift
and a letter of edict.
Please listen to it.
The daughter of the Crown Prince
is pregnant and has a wife.
Tang Mudog has permission
to send Princess Yong'an
3,000 houses to her.
The leader of them will eat her while she's still asleep.
Princess Yong'an.
intercept the edict quickly.
Prince Yong'an.
I hereby thank Heaven for your kindness.
Let's go.
Yin.
Essence,
do whatever you want
to do v NASA.
Let's go!
No, no, no.
Let's also go to the preventive zone first!
You have to
and Plum Village
good
my police dad
Ting Zeng is sad
Is that because his highness is still so obsessed with Li Changge
Li Changge
If she's still alive,
she must be in trouble.
I don't understand.
Why would Li Changge
let the Crown Prince,
Princess,
and the Wei family
care about her?
The Crown Prince loves her
with all his heart.
The Princess loves her
with all her heart.
As for Young Master Wei...
If Li Changge is still alive,
she'll go to Wei Shuyu
and tell her
to find Crown Prince
and get rid of her.
Understood.
Hao Du.
Remember.
Don't be afraid of the Young Mistress
when you do something big.
Don't be bound by
your love.
Yes.
(*Li Changge's tomb*)
This is the place
where Li Bei died in Chang'an.
I didn't expect
I'd end up here.
It hurts!
A'Dou.
Master, what's wrong?
Nothing.
Why are you here?
I didn't ask you...
I've been waiting here for a day.
I knew you were going to the north.
I'm sure
you'll pass the Chang'an barrier.
How is it, Master?
I've been following you for days.
I'm a little nervous.
But if you don't show up,
I'll be suspicious
if I'm wrong.
A'Dou.
I don't know
where the future is.
You still have a bright future to go.
Although you can't stay in the品香氈,
you still have other choices.
Why are you following me?
Master, you're my future.
I'll follow you for life and death.
A'Dou said
he wouldn't look away.
You're a hero.
No hero has a general to help him.
I'm your general.
Master, A'Dou is serious.
A'Dou.
Master,
let me follow you.
Ketou.
Since you're going to worship a master,
you should have a proper gift.
Master, please accept my bow.
Thank you.
From now on,
you're my disciple.
We'll be like a family.
Okay.
Master, where are we going?
To Youzhou.
My father's old horse is there.
The governor of Youzhou, Li Yuan,
used my father as a friend.
And
if I can persuade him to send troops to help,
I'll have hope.
Then
I'll be a general soon.
Soon.
But
I won't give up.
Kevin Han
It depends in hongmen.
I can't afford to be a
common visitor.
I'm here to apologize to you.
You're right.
I scolded you.
What did you say?
This is the gift for the
wedding.
You're a good father.
When Ni Xinmei died,
did you think about it?
I'm sorry to bother you.
I have a few mothers and sons in my family.
It's enough to support my children.
It turns out that people like Mr. Wei
will also care about their children.
It turns out that people like Mr. Wei will also care about their children.
What do you want to say?
I just said it casually.
I have a son.
I can't help worrying.
I have read a lot of holy books.
I don't know
how to seduce them
as the head of the family.
I'm also a father.
I also heard
that Princess Yongan is getting married.
If you
want to do this,
I have an idea.
Please say it first.
What?
I have a strange disease?
Yes, you remember.
The strange disease you have is not going to get better.
You have to go to Luoyang to treat it.
Go to Luoyang?
Yes. I have arranged everything for you.
You can leave now.
The sooner the better.
Go.
You're crying because you can't say a few words.
How can you be like a princess?
You should think more about Changge.
Yan'er.
Because you have this strange disease,
you can't get married for a long time.
You can't get married for a long time.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You should rest in Luoyang.
When you recover,
I will send someone to pick you up.
I know you and that young man Wei have always been close.
I have ordered him
to escort you to Luoyang.
He will take care of you.
You can rest assured.
Yes.
Brother Shouye.
I will send you to Luoyang.
Thank you, Brother Shouye.
You will understand me in the future.
Come here.
Okay. Next.
Be careful.
Next.
Go there.
Okay. Go there.
Next.
Go there.
What's in your car?
It's food.
Food?
You, you, go there and search.
Yes.
Sir, don't search. It's food.
It's not up to you.
Is there any problem?
No.
Thank you, sir.
Go.
Wait.
Sir.
Why are you in a panic?
No, sir.
What's in your car?
It's food.
Sir.
Check it.
Yes.
Don't...
General, what's this?
We didn't find anything.
You didn't see anything.
General,
what's this?
we didn't find anything.
You didn't see anything.
Remember?
Yes.
Don't forget, sir.
Hurry.
Sir, don't forget.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Sir,
you're so smart.
Without the carriage,
we can't get to Youzhou so fast.
I'm afraid we'll get soaked.
It's called a lesson.
Learn it.
The food is really good.
Be careful.
What are we doing?
Let's go to the front.
We'll live here.
Please.
Coming.
Sir,
what room do you want?
Is there the cheapest room?
The cheapest room?
This way.
Sir, please.
Sir,
have a look.
Although the room is small,
it's not a problem to give you two a room.
Sir, are you satisfied?
Yes.
Okay, take a rest.
I'll get you some hot water.
I'll check around the capital.
Stay here.
Yes.
Sir,
please be patient.
It's good that
the manager can sleep in the woodshed.
I'll clean it up.
I'll give you a comfortable place to sleep.
Don't be too tired.
I won't be particular about going out.
Sir, I'm not tired.
Please have a rest.
I'll go out and check.
Sir, I'll go with you.
You're still going out with me.
Have a rest.
I'll bring you some food.
This is the last stop.
We can arrive at Luoyang Xinggong tomorrow.
Brother Shuyu,
are you leaving tomorrow?
The scenery of Luoyang Xinggong is beautiful.
All the workers will accompany you.
The days when we played together
were like a dream.
We used to be so happy.
I'm glad that
we three used to be so happy.
I don't know why
we are now going to the end of the world
to be separated.
There is no one in the world
who can accompany us forever.
Brother Shuyu, I understand.
The dream should be awake.
We have grown up.
Brother Shuyu,
can you
write me a letter
when you are free?
Whenever you have news of Changge,
you must tell me.
I promise you
I'll find her.
It's getting late.
Go back and have a rest.
Go.
I didn't expect you to be so fast.
We'll arrive at Luoyang soon.
Wei Shuyu, listen.
The crown prince has ordered
Wei Shuyu to be the special envoy of Chang'an.
No need to go back to Chang'an.
Go to the capital with Hao Du
and go to Youzhou.
Summon Lord Lu Jiang and Li Yuan
to the capital.
Qingrong wants to know
if you have news of her.
Do you hope so
or not?
Whether it's true or not,
you can go to the capital with me.
Besides,
Wei Shuyu only needs to be responsible for the incident.
As for the rest,
I won't bother you.
Someone saw
Princess Yongning and a young man
go to Youzhou on the way to the capital.
Listen,
keep an eye on Wei Shuyu.
If they meet in private,
they'll kill Yongning.
If Wei Shuyu is not allowed to go,
do it in the same way.
Yes.
Go.
Master, which iron flag is better?
Heart gradually responds,
gradually awakens,
gradually swims towards you.
Before saying goodbye,
I look forward to it.
I'll remember your life
and lock it into my dream of longing.
Before dawn,
through the years,
my longing flows.
There's always a moment
which burns down the wastelands in my heart.
There's always a longing
which unites us.
In different worlds,
in different worlds,
I'll remember your life
and lock it into my dream of longing.
It'll become the eternal
and the cocoon of time.
There's always a moment
which burns down the wastelands in my heart.
There's always a longing
which unites us.
In different worlds,
in different worlds,
I'll remember your life
and lock it into my dream of longing.
It'll become the eternal
and the cocoon of time.
It'll never end.