I am the one who has been through the hardships
I will be the light in the dark night
I will be the hope in the dark night
The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Keep an eye on them. Report to me if you have any questions.
Yes.
Who are you?
Who are those people?
How dare you!
You are not allowed to enter the Purple Palace.
Aren't they the ones?
You are looking for death.
Tell me who you are.
Why are you acting like a guard in the Purple Palace?
Luo Yao actually has so many personal matters.
Since you are not afraid of death,
who are you trying to seduce?
Since you dare to take the poison,
it means that you know that
if you fall into our hands,
you will definitely die.
It's better to think it through
and explain it to me.
The fire has been put out.
It seems that we are no longer needed here.
Take this guy away first.
As for your old friend,
it's not appropriate to go to him now.
Go.
Madam, something bad has happened.
Something bad has happened.
Madam.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Madam, something bad has happened.
I just heard from Xia Er
that something bad has happened in the Purple Palace.
I heard that someone saw the owner of the house.
What happened in the Purple Palace?
I heard that it was a sudden fire.
Madam, I'm leaving.
Princess, Father,
I found traces of the fire oil
outside the Purple Palace.
I'm afraid someone is trying to set fire.
Who is trying to harm my father?
Who is the last person
who has seen the Crown Prince?
You just have to be honest.
The last person you see
when you see the Crown Prince
is the one who can explain it clearly
and make the whole thing clear.
Princess, Minister,
although I haven't seen the Crown Prince,
I saw a group of people dressed as refugees
break into the Palace of the Crown Prince's bedchamber.
There are assassins who broke into the Purple Palace.
Can you see their faces clearly?
Minister,
there was a lot of smoke all over the place.
I stood far away
and didn't see them clearly.
Minister,
I saw a woman dressed as a nun
who ran out of the Crown Prince's bedchamber.
I saw her and remembered her.
Could it be the accomplice of the assassins?
What does that woman look like?
Can you see her clearly?
She looks like a nun
with a mole on her eye.
Could it be her?
I really saw a ghost.
Minister.
Minister, listen to me.
Yifu.
What are you waiting for?
Get the car to the Cloud Temple.
Yes.
I haven't found my brother yet.
Brother Chang, please be safe.
I'll inform Changge.
No.
If Hao Du is found,
you...
Brother Shuyu,
I didn't mean that.
I mean
if Hao Du and Duorou Hui are found,
I can still hold them back.
You stay here.
If there is a conflict between Changge and the Cloud Temple,
you can still get rid of the suspicion
and continue to take over.
Okay.
I'll prepare the silver and the token.
Be careful.
Okay.
Help!
Anli!
Please help!
Help!
Be careful.
Take Minister Du inside.
Zhezhen Sun is inside.
Okay.
Get them back.
Yes.
Go.
Sirs.
If you're here to see a doctor,
you must have gone to the wrong place.
I've heard that the Cloud Temple is good for the people.
It's good for traveling.
I'm here today.
I have to walk around.
I can also show my respect to you later.
Thank you.
But we
are just kind-hearted people.
These little things
are nothing.
What?
You're not only kind-hearted,
but also want to walk around.
Do you want to
compete with me?
I have something important to do.
Please make yourself at home.
I have to make myself at home.
It's convenient for me to be with someone.
It's convenient for me to be with you.
It's late at night.
I don't want to fight with you.
Please step aside.
I've given way.
Whether I can make it or not
depends on whether you have the ability.
What?
You don't want to walk around?
What are you going to do?
You're blocking me.
I have to be more honest.
Do you think
I'm going to enter the Cloud Temple
or you're going to control me?
Where did I get this little disciple?
Someone is looking for me in the martial arts world.
People from the court are also watching.
You're amazing.
Your Highness.
Why are you here alone?
I'm worried about the safety of Duke Du.
So I came to visit you.
But I don't know what happened.
I'm lost.
How is Duke Du now?
Take me to see.
Did you see
anyone suspicious?
No.
I'm alone.
Hao Du.
It's so late now.
I'm still a little scared.
How about we go back first?
Okay.
I'll send you back to the Cloud Temple first.
Your Highness, please.
Your Highness.
Yi Feng.
Duke Du.
Don't disturb.
Go.
You two
go around and search for it.
If there's anyone suspicious.
Changge.
Leng Yan.
Why are you here?
Changge.
I found you appeared in Ziwei Palace.
I suspect you're involved in this.
But he's suddenly ill
and sent to the Cloud Temple.
I'm afraid you'll meet him and come to you.
You should go now.
If I go now,
I can't wash it clean.
Where's the Crown Prince?
I still don't know where he is.
But you can't get in trouble again.
Changge.
Keep the Green Mountain.
I'm not afraid that I can't wash it clean in the future.
It's a misunderstanding.
Someone is chasing you.
It's Hao Du.
I'll help you hold him.
You should go now.
What about you?
Minister Du doesn't dare to take me.
You believe me?
Then you be careful.
Go.
Yes.
Tu'er.
I've helped you
with many troubles.
But they're from the court.
I don't want to bother them.
So I can only stay here.
But except for the Cloud Temple,
I have no reason to stop them.
Thanks.
Who are you?
Why did you...
Did Du Ruhui leave?
I think so.
But I heard
that the young man was caught by you
and he was angry and vomited three times.
He was so anxious.
He almost didn't marry you.
Tu'er.
What if those officers and soldiers
come again?
No.
They won't expect that I dare to come back.
Tu'er is interesting.
You've been working hard.
I'm not as hard as you.
Watch your step.
Be careful.
Come on, sit down.
Did you explain to him?
I did.
He's a guard.
He was washing himself
while he was cleaning the house
and mixing with the water.
He was a good man.
He was washing himself
and mixing with the water.
Who sent them
to kidnap the Crown Prince?
He's a concubine.
He doesn't even know
who he is.
But he must have something to do
with the concubines.
The concubines?
You mean
the people of Dingxiang?
Madam.
Dingxiang.
Madam is Madam.
I admire you.
Where is Zi Yuan?
Take me to see him.
Mr. Qin.
My wife's factory
is not good.
You've been working all night.
Why don't you have breakfast together?
All right.
Father.
Sun Chen said
this medicine should be taken on time.
Father.
Are you still thinking about Li Changge?
Li Changge is still alive.
I saw her with my own eyes.
I don't know if it's a good thing or a bad thing.
She's still in Liuyun Temple.
If the temple owner
and Sun Zhenren
are determined to repay her,
we can't rely on them.
I just don't know
if the Crown Prince
is in Li Changge's hands.
What if...
In my opinion,
if the Crown Prince is really in Li Changge's hands,
the Crown Prince's safety will not be a problem.
Even after going through so many things,
Li Changge and Princess Li have a deep relationship.
She will not really be kind to the Crown Prince.
Let the Princess experience the same pain as her.
That's right.
But we can't let Li Changge
use our first army as a means.
The news of the Crown Prince's disappearance
can't be kept for too long.
We must catch Li Changge as soon as possible
and get the Crown Prince back.
Li Changge is a tough one
to catch in Luoyang Fishing Village.
What's more...
What's more,
Princess Yong'an will be the bait
and cover up for her.
Right?
Princess Yong'an.
Princess.
Now that the Crown Prince is missing,
Luoyang Fishing Village will be in chaos soon.
Please don't let your uncle
make any mistakes
in case you have to go back to the same day.
Don't worry.
Now that my brother is missing,
I won't cause you any trouble.
Now the rumors are all false.
No one knows what will happen next.
I'm going to dispatch troops now.
I can't keep an eye on the Princess.
Please don't cause yourself any trouble.
Didn't all the servants send out to patrol?
Why do you still need to dispatch troops?
Are you searching for someone
or are you going to catch someone?
Hao Du.
The most important thing now is to find my brother.
As for catching someone,
I think we can let him go.
How do you know that the Crown Prince is missing
has nothing to do with others?
Now the Luoyang Fishing Village
must be done by someone.
Whoever makes the biggest profit
must be the one who wants to disturb the people's hearts.
Okay.
Then let's open the window and talk.
What are you suspecting?
Li Changge is in Luoyang.
Yes.
Princess Xie didn't lie to me.
I saw her with my own eyes.
But I can testify for Changge.
This matter has nothing to do with her.
Because I...
I don't care what she said
or did in front of you.
This may be part of her plan.
So please
stay in the mansion.
Don't mess up.
Yes.
Mr. Xiang,
what are you thinking about?
I've been lost for a long time.
It's your turn.
I thought you got news from the maid
and wanted to take me to investigate the fire in Ziwei Palace.
What are you thinking about?
I don't even know where you came from.
How can I take you to investigate serious things?
Then why do you still take me
to play chess in such a place?
What's wrong with this place?
It's too hot.
The game of chess
is about calmness and calmness.
You have to be fully focused.
Only in a lively place
can you get your mind straight.
I have something to do.
Goodbye.
You've been back home with me.
You just left like that.
It's not appropriate.
Besides,
you followed me
just to know
what the nobles in Ziwei Palace
have to do with me.
Don't you still need to find your old friend?
Come back.
Next time,
Gu Renyu
is like a man who is used to playing chess.
After you and I play chess,
I can get a good feel for you.
Maybe then
I can take you to do serious things.
I don't know how to play chess.
The old tricks in your hands
are not something
you can get from fighting for years.
It's like using troops to play chess.
I've told you the rules.
Since you know how to fight,
you must know how to play chess.
Come on.
That's not enough.
Let's start over.
All right.
Your Highness,
I'm still scared.
Don't be scared.
Just do as I said.
They won't do anything.
If they break in,
you can teach them a lesson.
Just say,
this person is too worried
and caught a cold.
He's sweating.
He's only wearing a formal dress.
They won't do anything.
But you must remember
to cover your face.
Just wait until I come back.
Do you understand?
Your Highness.
Quan Niang.
Sorry.
Liuyuan Temple closed recently.
I don't have any guests.
Quan Niang.
Your Highness.
Zhao...
Where's A'Li?
Why did you
call A'Li?
I have something to do with her.
Where's A'Li now?
A'Li...
She's not in the temple now.
Quan Niang.
If A'Li comes back,
please give her this letter.
Tell her
I'll wait for her until she's back.
Remember.
Okay.
Any news?
Father's prediction was right.
Princess Yongan
is in the trap.
Don't look at me.
Go find the Crown Prince.
Yes.
The Crown Prince's Manor
You're using the army.
Among the leaders I've seen,
there's only one who is so well-equipped.
Governor of Shuozhou, Gongsun Heng.
It's a pity.
I heard Gongsun Heng
risked his life
to save the people.
I'm willing to ask.
It's a real man's festival.
But I heard that
Gongsun Heng has a capable man
named Qin in his hometown.
Is Mr. Qin his friend?
What are you going to do
in this mud of Luoyang?
You've been using Gongsun Heng's
army formation to deal with me.
But you never show
your familiar way of using the army.
So you've already gotten used to it.
You're not going to
join the army as soon as possible.
I just want to see
how well you can use
Gongsun Heng's army.
If you use your own way of using the army,
I may not be your opponent.
It's a pity that you're not honest enough.
I'm Mr. Qin's nephew
in the military.
In fact...
We're partners.
There are two ways to the outside world.
But you're afraid to show
your own way of using the army
because you're afraid of being attacked.
It's easy to be seen.
Actually, you want to be here.
But this is the way of the grassland people.
No.
I'm from the Central Plains.
Interesting.
Li,
Her Highness is here.
I told her you weren't here.
She left this.
Thank you for thinking for me.
Quanniang,
I have to see Her Highness.
Don't worry. I'll be careful.
I'll go with you.
Go.
It doesn't matter who I am.
I came to Luoyang
just to find my old friend.
Then can you tell me now
if your old friend is also related to the nobility in the palace?
No.
It doesn't matter.
I'm looking for him.
It has nothing to do with his identity.
Li seems to be
actually considering Her Highness as a side person.
He's very close to her.
If Her Highness is gone,
I'm sure Li will find her even if he steps on the mountain river.
Am I right?
I thought you were a man.
I didn't expect you to be a woman.
I like this.
Okay.
I'm willing to help you find someone you like.
Someone I like?
Isn't it?
I guess she must be a beautiful and handsome woman.
Yes.
See? I'm right.
Do you care about her
and care about her
and don't want to leave her at any moment?
I don't care.
You don't care about her
and don't want to leave her at any moment?
You don't care about other women.
If you insist on staying with someone
every moment,
and never leave her,
until you're old enough,
do you want her to be her?
Even if there are many beautiful and gentle women
who look up to you,
you still want to choose this bad-tempered
and arrogant little girl.
Not a little girl.
Is she a father?
Qin Xun's hobby is really admirable.
She's a woman who's always on top.
No matter who she is,
anyway,
she's the one I like.
I'm done.
The door of the garrison in my stomach
is about to be blown up by you.
I'm done.
Brother Li,
you're going to be a bad-tempered woman?
What bad-tempered woman?
You're talking so badly.
It's her.
Mr. Qin,
you're a man
who's not innocent.
You're a man
Qin Xun,
with your unidentified identity,
I think you should mind your own business.
It's still early.
Come on, sit down.
Let's play another round.
Come on.
Brother Li,
I have something urgent.
I'll visit you another day.
I'm on the way.
Just go.
Brother Shuyu,
have you got the things?
They're all in the bag.
But Leyan,
it's so strange.
How could things go so smoothly?
With Hao Du's behavior,
he must have noticed.
How about this?
Take the things to the gate and wait.
I'll wait for Changge
to inform her to meet you in the dark.
But,
I'm not going to wait.
I'm going to wait for you.
I'll wait for you.
But...
Mr. Wei,
you're too mean to me.
Hao Du,
why are you here?
Now the Crown Prince is missing.
Luoyang City is being robbed.
You take the Princess out of here.
If anything happens to her...
How do you know I'm here?
If you don't even know this,
how can you protect the Princess?
You...
Where did you get the token?
And who did you give it to?
I took the token.
Are you going to catch me?
I'm going to catch you.
Go.
Oh, no.
Go after her.
Let her go.
I told you to let her go.
Changge.
That person is...
That person...
That person saved Changge in Youzhou.
He is Changge's friend.
He saved Changge?
Yes.
He kidnapped me
and saved Changge from Hao Du.
No matter who he is,
he can save Changge in time.
He is trustworthy.
Before saying goodbye,
I'm looking forward to...
Changge.
There is an ambush there.
Your friend is kidnapped.
I'm going to catch you here.
I didn't expect you to be here.
What about Leyan?
They are all people in the court.
Don't worry. He must be safe.
Leave here first.
You don't hate me anymore?
There is always a sense of longing
between you and me.
I hate you for leaving without saying goodbye.
In different worlds.
I miss you forever.
I promise to stay by your side.
This way.
Don't be a shadow.
What is this place?
The most famous bar in Guiyang.
They must not expect
we are hiding in the most crowded place.
Come on.
Why are you so familiar here?
I played chess with someone here before.
You played chess here?
Changge.
I'm looking for you.
It's so hard.
You are looking for me from the grassland to here?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't blame you.
I owe you too much.
Then don't leave anymore.
Take your time.
I saved your life just now.
Don't you want to give me a drink?
I'm grateful for your kindness.
I didn't say I would marry you.
Who will suffer the loss?
Not sure.
Tang...Tang.
I heard your voice just now.
I can't believe it.
It's really you.
Go away.
Shut up.
Why are you here?
Do you know that it's a mess because of you?
Tang.
You are alive.
Congratulations.
You haven't answered my question for a long time.
I...
I slipped out.
The people below said that this bar was very fun.
There was a western dance that was close to the eyes and a piglet dance.
I just want to...
want to...
So you sneaked out.
Not tied up.
Kid.
Think it over first.
Have you been staying here all the time?
Do you know that Ziwei Palace is on fire?
I...
I heard about it.
You heard about it and you still didn't go out?
I...
When it was on fire, I was already asleep.
I only heard about it later.
If I go back now,
Du Shao Shu will scold me to death.
You little brat.
Li Chang Ge.
I am the crown prince now.
You are annoying.
Besides, I will beat you.
Li Chang Ge.
If you dare to touch me again, I will cut your fingers.
Sister Tao.
I am your brother.
Just say what you want to say.
I will beat you.
Li Cheng Qian.
You are getting older.
The older you get, the more you are not getting better.
It is so ridiculous to be the crown prince.
I feel ashamed for Li Shi Ming.
How can he raise a son like you?
You didn't even learn a little from your father and you want to be the crown prince?
Why are you scolding me like this?
Everyone says that I don't deserve to be the son of my father.
I thought...
I did such a thing to your family.
At least you think I deserve to be the son of my father.
At least I have the ability to take advantage of others.
But you...
Are you really going to take away the crown prince?
How dare you!
I must tell Minister Du to tell you.
How dare you come back to Luoyang?
Since you found out,
I won't let you go.
Sister Tao.
We are all relatives.
We can't talk about it.
You have to turn around.
You can't be a bad friend.
Li Cheng Ge.
Don't be rude.
Don't you like to play?
Then I'll let you play once.
Go.
Masters.
Please let my brother have a good time.
Make sure he is as handsome as a turtle.
Okay.
If there is any harm,
I won't forgive you.
I'm the crown prince.
You dare to offend me.
You don't want to live anymore.
My brother had a fever when he was a kid.
He has a bad brain.
You must not believe what he said.
Sister.
I'm sorry.
Please let me go.
We are all relatives.
We can talk about it.
You know I'm your sister.
Okay.
Since you call me sister,
I'll teach you a good lesson for your father.
Masters.
Thank you for your help.
Don't break it.
Otherwise, I can't tell my mother.
Don't worry.
I've taught many kids.
I know.
Have fun.
Don't go.
Sister.
I've never lost since I was a kid.
You're so cheap.
Are you happy now?
Yes.
Then go back with me.
Where?
18th and Qin Lao are in Luoyang.
They are all looking for you.
18th and Qin Lao.
What about Yuan Niang?
She is also here.
What about Xu Feng?
They are all here.
Yan Xingmen?
It's the picture of Qin Lao and his friends.
I really miss them.
What's wrong?
I don't know how to face them when I go back.
Don't think too much.
You'll know when you go back.
Let's go.
Princess.
Your memories gradually come back to me.
Before we say goodbye,
I hope...
I hope your life
can be locked into my tender dream.
Before dawn,
the yearning flows through my fingers.
There's always a moment
that burns down the wastelands in my heart.
There's always a longing
that's between you and me.
It's all in front of me.
In different worlds,
in different worlds,
I'm missing you.
The deep night
has become eternity.
The cocoon of time.
There's always a moment
that burns down the wastelands in my heart.
There's always a longing
that's between you and me.
It's all in front of me.
In different worlds,
in different worlds,
I'm missing you.
The deep night
has become eternity.
The cocoon of time.