♪Love grows wildly in my soul♪
♪Longing weaves its net♪
♪I dare not meet your gaze♪
♪Yet I crave the light in your eyes♪
♪Memories are left behind as time flies♪
♪After splendor comes desolation♪
♪When I've braved the world's storms♪
♪I'll kiss your face♪
=Lock Her=
=Episode 22=
=How about a Goodbye Kiss?=
Shiyue.
What are you doing here?
Grandma said you got a new mosquito net.
I don't have one.
Mosquitoes are everywhere in my room.
That's why I came.
You want the mosquito net?
Then where am I supposed to sleep?
I have no idea.
You can go
wherever you want.
Looks like Grandma spoiled you.
♪Stirring the nebulae♪
Did she bring up having kids again?
Nope.
Grandma said
a baby born on the wedding day
would be smarter.
♪Our love has gone mad♪
So, who's in a rush,
you or Grandma?
♪First night, my sunset♪
♪In the whole world, there are just us♪
♪The city stays awake,
rising and falling♪
♪Breathing softly in the dead of night♪
Guess it's you who's in a rush.
I'm not.
What are you doing?
♪Lovers are burning each other♪
♪Inside and out♪
♪In every late night♪
♪Someone plays a tune♪
How could I be so careless
and let all the maids see me so early?
Now, it'll surely reach Grandma's ears.
What will Grandma think of this?
Will she make me kneel
in the ancestral hall?
Miss.
You look just like a bride-to-be.
Your cheeks are glowing.
No.
It's just the red lantern.
No, no.
Since moving
to the Young Marshal's room,
you've had this special glow.
Little rascal.
How dare you tease me?
Adjutant Wen.
Young Marshal.
Something happened.
What's wrong?
Liu Yong's nephew was killed.
Someone's at the front hall
on behalf of Liu Yong
to negotiate with you.
Morning, dear.
Don't call me that.
We're not married yet.
I have to go to the front hall.
Do you want...?
Stop it.
People are watching.
Just go already.
Who's even here?
♪Spring comes late after the snow♪
Alright, I'm going.
♪Stories untold on the busy street♪
♪Lost you as I turned♪
Dear.
♪Through a haze of dust♪
Wait for me for breakfast.
♪Reunion masked by moonlight♪
Alright.
♪Crowds push us apart♪
By order of Marshal Liu,
I'm here to ask
about the investigation
into Liu De's death
by your soldiers.
How can you be sure it was my soldier?
Every army marks its weapons
to prevent losing them.
Take a good look at this gun.
Is it from your army?
On the battlefield,
it's normal for guns to be lost.
One gun alone isn't solid proof.
Besides, I just reached an agreement
with Marshal Liu for peace talks.
There's no need to attack
an innocent man.
That may be true,
but it's already happened.
You owe me an answer today.
The Marshal said
that if there's no answer,
then the peace talks
will be called off.
Please tell Marshal Liu for me:
On this matter,
I will dig to the bottom.
I'll catch the culprit
and deliver them myself.
In three days.
Make it five.
Let's go.
Hold on.
You're just a lowly adjutant.
How can you bargain
with the Young Marshal?
Do you know the rules?
Uncle.
I was just about to look for you.
Wait for me in the office.
I'm not going anywhere.
I want to hear
what exactly Liu Yong wants.
Did you kill him yourselves
and try to frame us for it?
What nonsense are you saying?
I'm saying
it's a setup.
Don't you get it?
Calm down.
I just told you
I'd find the killer.
Put the gun down.
I'll let you walk away today.
Sorry.
The gun went off by accident.
Do you know what you're doing?
I'm helping you make up your mind.
Shiyao.
Stop being so softhearted, will you?
Go do something big.
With your skills, you fear nothing.
Get out of Nancheng.
Sheng is on his way
to take out Liu Yong.
There's an inside tip
that Liu Yong's heading
to Shenyang today.
He'll show up at the station
at the You hour.
Speaking of timing,
your brother's sharper than you.
You can still catch up.
But
the city must be on high alert now.
They're just waiting to trap him.
Who's this today?
Such a grand setup.
They're clearing the whole station.
I heard it's the Marshal.
He's always like this when traveling.
Watch out. I'm stepping out for a smoke.
Why so fussy all the time?
You can go later.
Hurry up.
Protect the Marshal!
Shiyao.
Shiyao, why are you here?
I'm your brother.
How could I not come?
Shiyao.
Young Marshal.
Guard our home.
Shiyao.
♪Rain flows through fleeting years♪
♪Like a lone boat, tossed and adrift♪
Sorry, Shiyao. I shouldn't have come.
Shiyao.
Sorry, Shiyao.
♪Shattered clouds cast fleeting shadows♪
♪Beneath the moon, who wrote the line♪
Shiyao.
♪For hearts to find♪
♪You ask me when the wind will rise♪
♪When the rain will fall,
and when the moon will meet the shadow♪
♪I'll send a long letter♪
♪Drifting through the fleeting world♪
♪Wait till blooms fade away♪
♪Petals drift by;
seasons change through the years♪
♪I still recall that bright moon then♪
♪Hanging high in the sky♪
♪You ask me when the wind will rise♪
♪When the rain will fall,
and when the moon will meet the shadow♪
♪I'll send a long letter♪
♪Drifting through the fleeting world♪
♪Wait till blooms fade away♪
♪Petals drift by, etched in my heart♪
♪Hand in hand under the bright moon♪
♪Never once did it change♪
♪Trapped by fate's decree♪
♪Love and hate remain uncrossed♪
♪The wind sends tears astray♪
♪Moistening the distant sky♪
♪Where can the longing be sent♪
♪Where can the heart rest♪
♪Watching your back fade away♪
♪I'll wait a lifetime for you♪
♪You ask me when the wind will rise♪
♪When the rain will fall,
and when the moon will meet the shadow♪
♪I'll send a long letter♪
♪Drifting through the fleeting world♪
♪Wait till blooms fade away♪
♪Petals drift by;
seasons change through the years♪
♪I still recall that bright moon then♪
♪Hanging high♪