力量之間絲漸落地成分
könnte дорог尋 stability within the pl Fe》
..
Lee Cho
I only only
Go
together
You only
Wait
and wait
Not
Mind
Hyped
Boy
You
are not
you
select
go
Jan
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 16
Everyone calls me a devil who kills people.
But I never knew
I was a child who couldn't even hold a sword.
Dad, this sword is too heavy.
I don't want to practice.
No, Li'er.
The most important thing for a martial artist is to hold on to it.
Father gave me martial arts.
But he didn't tell me how people in the martial arts world are.
Your father is going to travel to the Yuan Gate.
He won't be back for a long time.
I heard that he died under the sword of a friend.
Mother took me to hide and fight.
Mother, why don't you let me practice?
We are far from the martial arts world.
But the martial arts world doesn't dare to let us go.
In order to take away the family's school of medicine,
they killed my mother.
That was the first time I smelled blood.
That was the last smell of my family.
Now I only feel happy when I hold the sword.
Because this is my only family.
It's the Master of the Great Buddha. Run!
Master!
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
So I'm the thief of the Great Demon.
First, he let me go on purpose.
Then he took me to make a fishing rod.
He looks young.
But he is so cunning.
He will be bald in the future.
My hair.
Thank you for your concern.
You're welcome.
Well,
Your Highness,
are you here to thank me for catching Nan Chun Meng?
How can you come here in person?
I have something to do.
I'll go first.
Okay.
You want to do the same move again?
It's useless.
But people are useful.
Look,
if I didn't do it,
how could you catch Nan Chun Meng?
But you've used up all your power.
You useless person.
Kill you.
Again.
I told you.
It's really dirty.
Who are you?
Why do you know Nan Chun Meng is in Ningxiang?
If you're not Chu Meng Die,
why do you have his three-color bracelet?
If I tell this devil,
I read it from the script.
He will think I'm fooling him.
I don't know what to do.
I...
I am...
Little bitch.
What are you looking at? Tell me.
I really don't know Chu Meng Die.
I've said it for eight hundred times.
I'm the most beautiful little princess, Li Song.
My father gave me this bracelet.
It's Nan Chun Meng.
Your Highness.
Some men
just like to go to some feng yue places.
Your Highness.
I'm telling the truth.
I'm not lying.
Little liar.
Liar.
Shut up.
Little sister.
So you two know each other?
No.
Then why did you call me little sister?
All the beautiful women in the world are my little sister.
I know my appearance is the best in the world.
Indeed.
I walk on the street.
I also have many...
No.
Nan Chun Meng.
Tell the devil.
We have nothing to do with each other.
Little sister.
How do you know my name is Nan Chun Meng?
But five days later.
I'm going to marry Chu Meng Die, the daughter of the head of Jing Yun Villa.
Devil.
Did you hear that?
He's going to marry Chu Meng Die.
I'm not Chu Meng Die.
After you said that.
I don't think I've ever seen a girl from the Chu family.
Are you...
Right?
Buried. Buried.
Let me die.
Continue to interrogate Nan Chun Meng.
Take her away.
Put her in the dungeon.
Keep an eye on her.
Help.
I want to go home.
I suddenly want to get drunk in Meng City.
I don't know.
My favorite book.
The queen ran away again.
Where is the pen?
Lv Xiang.
Are you reading this book too?
It doesn't matter.
I also love reading love novels.
I think this is the most relaxing time.
But back to the point.
I also know the author of this book.
When I go back.
I'll invite her to my mansion.
Tell me what the next plot is.
You can come too.
Really?
Okay.
I'm not going.
You be honest with me.
The queen ran away again.
I think.
It's related to the maid who came after that.
Which maid?
The one that the prince picked up on the road?
Yes.
It's her.
Then do you know.
Why did the queen run away again?
Of course.
Because the prince's men are too stupid.
I can't keep an eye on him.
The princess.
The
princess.
The dreamy man's bag.
All of them are here.
He was sent to the Western Regions.
He was in his prime.
For twenty years.
But he's a man of character.
He has eight hands on his left.
He likes to drink tea.
Now the leader of Feng Yu Valley, Bai Wu Xie.
He's unique.
And Nan Chui Meng hasn't returned yet.
He must be suspicious.
I've prepared the clothes for Nan Chui Meng.
I'll show you.
Have a rest and practice martial arts.
We'll be there soon.
Send a letter to Feng Yu Valley immediately.
Tell them that the Japanese attack is a big battle.
Nan Chui Meng is in big trouble.
In a few days,
he'll arrive at Feng Yu Valley.
What about Li Song?
Chu Meng Die is in a bad shape now.
Leave Li Song
to him.
It'll be useful.
Princess.
Nothing.
The cold poison in your body
has been activated again.
If it wasn't for Li Song
who touched me to heal your bones,
you must...
It doesn't matter.
The poison
has been with me for so many years.
I'm used to it.
Tomorrow morning,
we'll leave Feng Yu Valley immediately.
Yes.
Han Yan.
Move.
Where are you going?
The princess sent me out to do something.
Move.
You're blocking my way
and delaying my time.
Can you afford it?
No.
Han Yan.
What?
How dare you ask about the princess?
Han Yan.
But...
But what?
Shut up.
But...
This is a forbidden area.
It's full of gas.
Why is there so much smoke here?
It's dangerous.
Help.
Your Highness.
The poison in the body is spreading faster.
It may be triggered once every three months.
I'll seal your bones,
triceps, and intercostal blood
to ease your pain.
Your Highness.
Please forgive me.
Li Song'er...
He ran away.
Li Song'er.
Mother.
You don't even know
how much I've eaten here.
Looks like this idiot has absorbed the poison of the organ.
If we don't take him away,
I'll be in trouble.
So,
I know you're hungry.
I brought you your favorite
gongfuli bun.
Look.
What?
Gongfuli bun.
Why does it smell like strawberries?
It's going to change color.
Hello.
I was just angry.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have done that.
And...
It's obvious that...
You're taking advantage of me.
If I'm being magnanimous,
I can ignore you.
But the premise is
you have to let me leave.
I'm talking to you.
We did have many grudges before.
But this time,
we can make up for it.
The Demon King is sleeping.
I should take the opportunity to sneak out.
I'm really beautiful.
But I don't think I'll fall in love with you
after biting him.
Don't go.
I'm sorry.
It's hot.
Are you sick?
Who's the one who's been forgiven by Heaven?
I didn't expect you to be a demon today.
I just want to leave you here alone.
Your enemy has found you.
Kill him.
What should I do?
There are many people here.
If you don't know the way,
you can't leave.
As long as you find me some herbs,
I'll let you go.
Water.
Water?
I'm thirsty.
I won't save you.
I'm crazy.
I even helped the demon pick herbs.
I'd better run.
Oh, no.
I'm so stupid.
I'll wait for the beauty to come out
after saving her life.
I knew it.
Even the herbs are so...
Blood.
It's blood.
I must be dead.
I'm dead.
I want to see elixir,
and it's gone police.
Listen,
do you want to see elixir?
Yes.
What? Are you scared?
Mom, why are you so stupid?
You haven't found me yet.
Mom!
Mom, don't leave me!
I'm very obedient!
I don't want to go to the capital anymore!
Give my mom back!
From today on,
there will be no more Sun Moon Palace!
Mom!
Mom?
Did you have a fever and burn your head?
Look carefully. Am I your mom?
No, no.
Why aren't you speaking?
Are you
moved by my beautiful judgement and cryingestly?
It's unlike you!
The devil's eyes
The tears of a monkey
look like they're going to kill a peach blossom.
What?
You're so beautiful.
In the Dream City,
you're still single?
Nonsense.
I have so many.
I can't pick them out.
Really?
I thought they were all poisoned by your fish.
Is...
The fish I baked...
So delicious.
Have a bite.
What?
You think I poisoned it, don't you?
Take this.
I understand you're a patient.
So I want to roast a fish to give you some nutrition.
You didn't even have a bite.
You're a lowly woman who is trying to get a beauty's love.
Okay.
If you're honest,
it's okay to have a bite first.
I shouldn't be so nice to you.
Roast it yourself.
This whole piece is mine.
It hurts.
You even want to fight a fish with me?
I've never been unlucky since I came here.
It's so bad to eat a fish with a bone.
You can go now.
Turn right after you leave the cave.
You'll see a small path.
I'll go.
Are you serious?
I'll keep my word.
You help me find the herb.
I'll let you go.
You're kind.
If you have no other choice,
you can go to the Wind and Rain Valley to find me.
By then,
don't call me devil again.
What should I call you?
I don't care.
I'm leaving then.
See you in the Abyss.
I'm so ugly.
How did you walk?
What a place!
Although I've got rid of the devil,
how can I find my way home?
I'm so tired.
The devil is so generous to me.
Miss.
Don't touch me.
No.
I think the heroine is in a mess.
She wants you to go to our bathhouse to soak the grass.
Where is my princess?
It's all because of the devil.
He's been buying my princess' hair every day.
I've been buying her hair since then.
Go to the bathhouse to wash her hair.
Wait.
Art Hanging
Why are you fishing in bath house?
The water is hot.
Where did the fish come from?
There are fish in your heart.
You can catch them wherever they are.
You have no fish in your heart.
Of course you can't see them.
Don't look for them.
Your fish is not here.
It will appear at the right time.
You must be hungry after a long time of hard work.
May I ask what kind of fish you want to eat?
Sweet and sour.
It must be sweet and sour.
Childe, I see you are not happy.
This is the sign of a great disaster and a great joy.
I'm not a childe.
I'm a girl.
Princess.
You are so beautiful.
This is the sign of a great joy.
You must be blessed with happiness.
No.
You are the old man who drew me that day.
That's why I'm here.
Tell me.
How can I go back to the original world?
You are a boy.
But you want to be a girl.
I'm not.
You still don't say damn.
You must care about my happiness.
What is happiness?
What's wrong?
Why does my voice become like this?
Did you suffer some teachers' punishment today?
Just get rid of it.
everything will be back to normal.
You will
be blessed
and return to the Holy Land.
Is this a dream?
My face, my voice.
How did it become like this?
The illusion of the five senses.
It must be that hand.
Gu Yuan, you're a bad guy.
When I wake up in the morning,
I will find the person who wrote the script
and write you into the worst and worst ending.
I will make you be killed by birds.
No.
I will make you a woman
and then be killed by birds.
What did that old man say just now?
Wash the medicine and use it to wash the worms.
Could it be that I will make the devil
a sweet and sour fish?
As long as it is removed,
everything will be back to normal.
You will be blessed
and return to the Holy Land.
Isn't this the devil Gu Yuan?
Gu Yuan,
you better hope that
what this weird old man said is false.
Otherwise, I will kill you.
You don't need to write the script to help me.
Just cut your own hand.
When I wander to such a place,
I only have beauty and wisdom left.
Even if I have to see you again,
I have to take good care of myself.
If you have no way out,
you can go to the Wind and Rain Valley to find me.
No wonder he said that.
It turns out that he had a plan.
Now, I can only go to the Sun and Moon Palace to make a living.
Why don't I go to the Wind and Rain Valley to wait for him?
I will wait for him.
Sir,
how do I get to the Wind and Rain Valley?
Thats why, there must be no tablet for him.
Is this brush used to peel off holes in paper?
Why don't you call the TC fired from the exists Hijali?
I'll see if it works.
Beggar Han of the Others
Your Highness, Xiangyang?
Xiangluoyang?
Nanchui Meng said
she would marry Chu Mengdie at the mouth of the valley
and then dance with her.
Feng Yu Valley had to obey the promise
and let her learn the art of dancing in the valley.
When we received Chu Mengdie,
it would be easy to get the secret scroll back.
You are really good at planning.
You are not just a soldier
but also a master.
This plan...
Liu Yunying.
Yes, Your Highness.
A man is like a jade,
a man is like a frost.
In the future, please call me
Childe Nan.
Come.
I'll stay with you in the future,
never looking back,
I'll stay here for the rest of my life.
I look back, but I still need to go back.
Perhaps I'm lost and I don't know where I am.
The deep love I feel for you makes me afraid to take a step back.
The winter flowers are in full bloom,
the spring comes, and I miss you.
I want to tell you all my feelings.
Why don't we start over again?
I'll count down for you and run for the next life.
Why don't we never meet again?
I'll never give up on my dream.
Why don't we meet again?
We'll be together forever.
We'll meet again when we meet again.