My fingers are like the dust on the ground.
I'm not willing to leave this world.
I'm not willing to die.
I only love you.
You're the only one I can wait for.
I'm not willing to die.
I regret this life.
I'm willing to sacrifice my life for you.
I'm willing to witness it.
The Taoism Grandmaster
Episode 18
It seems we're still a step behind.
Is this the craftsman you're looking for?
There's a lock on the hand.
And the mark of being burned.
It seems the craftsman is right.
I was to move outside on purpose,
to find the owner of this thing.
It beastly!
I don't care about that!
Let's go here.
Did you see that?
and the Fengyi Valley.
My sister-in-law,
don't get me wrong.
These days,
she's been looking for the clue to the old abode.
Now, she's outside the city.
What's she doing there?
Of course, she's looking for the secret.
Don't worry.
I'll give you the ticket.
As long as my senior finds the clue,
the young valley master will be in a good position.
It's definitely her.
Fine.
It's rare for her to have that sense of duty.
Then I'll wait for the good news.
Let's see what she can do.
It's so hidden.
It can't be fake.
There's no one here.
Let's take her away.
No.
If she comes back and sees our footprints,
she'll be shocked.
Are you going to carry her down?
Demon.
Demon Regard
Once she sees this Quails,
all her spirit will be lost.
Forget it.
Just keep practicing.
I'll guard her well today.
Han xiang
Sir,
please go and take a rest.
When the hero is not around,
ThrowingSecret Madness.
YourESS is going to be very tired.
You came back.
Stop.
I'm so tired.
Bai Li Xingchen,
you're good.
When I was sleeping, you practiced martial arts,
and when I was practicing martial arts, you slept.
When I was looking for you, you were sweeping the floor.
You were busy all day.
Why are you hiding from me?
You're afraid of the situation today.
What do you mean?
Lin,
I'm grateful for your care.
Focus.
Don't come over.
You...
Stand there.
Say it.
Lin,
I'm sorry.
I only like women in my life.
Just like Song Bai in the snow.
Even if the snow is heavy,
I'd rather not be afraid.
Even if we're brothers,
I won't give up.
Bai Zi,
do you still think I'm a man?
No.
Why aren't you wearing clothes?
What's the matter, Lin?
What should I wear?
worse
Miss,
I'll beacasf you.
I...
He won't allow it anymore.
You can't get a guy like him.
Get away.
He's not good.
Yes.
I need to practice martial arts these days.
So I don't have time to accompany you.
I can accompany you.
What's your plan if you stay?
I'm hungry.
Where are you going?
I'm going to give you...
I'm going to find something to eat.
You practice martial arts first.
I won't bother you.
Even if I'm a woman,
you don't have to look at me for so long.
Lin Xiu.
You...
You're really a woman.
Like a fake bag,
we're not related.
Lin.
Hello.
I'm sorry.
Now Gu Nian hates people who hide their anger.
You're dressed as a man.
If you're found out,
you'll be expelled from the martial arts and expelled from the valley.
This short sword is as sharp as a nail.
Take it to defend yourself.
Run down the mountain.
White Star.
This sword
is for you.
Yes.
My fish fork is too
I think I'm missing something too.
The duasar beámangjia,
it's quite giant.
Do you know that
number ofaliae in this world
is not halfway to the eight weather.
Number ofaliae low.
But they are always lower.
This photo is a little bit over Yoda.
The older brother of Yoda
I want to make it
Thank you.
Buns.
Newly-made buns.
Hot and tasty.
Buns.
Okay.
Miss.
How much?
Three taels.
Okay.
He looks like a man with a beautiful face.
He's a man with a beautiful face.
Sir.
I didn't see him.
Little Jiujiu.
Who is he looking for?
Sorry.
Sir.
Your buns.
I want to ask you something.
Have you seen a man with about 70 cm high,
with eyes wide open,
and with eyebrows straight?
No.
No?
They also found out something.
The devil has to rest after training.
I'll go and have a look.
Ladies.
Have you seen a man with about 70 cm high,
with eyebrows straight?
Miss.
What are you doing?
I'm doing business.
Your Highness.
This secret technique
is very violent.
I know
you want to take revenge.
But you're so trained.
It hurts your body.
Why don't we take it slow?
You have the business paper.
I've waited for more than 20 years.
How can I return it now?
If you have something to say,
go and see Li Song'er.
Just now,
she went out.
She said she would buy you breakfast.
It's noon.
I don't know why she hasn't come back yet.
Brother Zhou?
Brother Zhou.
She was killed.
Chu Mengdian.
Put down your weapon.
Heng.
Heng, what's wrong with you?
You...
You killed my beloved disciple.
It's a misunderstanding.
When I came here,
she was already like this.
Today, even if I die,
I want to avenge my senior brother.
I just passed by.
Heng.
Be careful.
She has a big move.
I caught Chu Mengdian.
No, Master.
She has no internal force in her body.
You're not Chu Mengdian.
Who said I'm not?
Chu Mengdian was a three-year-old martial artist.
She participated in the Chichen City Youth Martial Arts Competition at the age of six.
She defeated 150 contestants.
At the age of twelve,
Chu Wuya sent her out of the mountain villa to practice.
She challenged the leaders of all major sects.
She was defeated by none.
She was called the first female hero in the martial arts world.
How could she be
a scoundrel like you?
Take her back
and interrogate her.
Yes.
Take her away.
Go.
Let me go.
It's fine.
Yuxi.
This is Jinxi.
You can go on.
Yes.
You...
certainly know...
these strips.
APPLAUSE
Save me!
My dear husband,
Her blood
is pure.
Master,
this woman disguised herself as Chu Mengdie
to be the spy of the Devil's Palace.
My Senior Brother died so tragically.
I don't know how much he suffered in his life.
I think she is the one
who secretly colluded with the Sun Moon Palace
to cooperate with the Devil's Palace
and stole my treasure,
the Man of the Demon.
Your Majesty.
I have the Three-Colored Handcuffs of the Manor.
My bracelet
also opened the mechanism of the hidden demon.
Why do you say I'm not?
The Three-Colored Handcuffs are in your hands.
That only shows
that Chu Mengdie has been killed.
Since you don't know martial arts,
that means
Chu Mengdie was killed by that devil Gu Yuan.
Then you were given the handcuffs
and you sneaked into the Wind and Rain Valley.
After you and Chu Mengdie get married,
you can take the treasure.
You should cooperate with the outside world
to help Gu Yuan steal the secret weapons.
After you succeed,
you can continue to stay in the valley
and be his spy, right?
Yes.
But you didn't expect
my smart and powerful Senior Brother
to know your true identity.
In order to avoid your plan from being destroyed,
you
brutally killed my Senior Brother.
Tell me.
Where is the Devil's Palace hidden?
Good guy.
I'm going to believe it myself.
I...
That's right.
I really didn't expect
that the lady I love
is a liar.
She wanted to steal the Peony Pavilion behind my back.
Tell me.
In the Wind and Rain Valley,
do you deserve to respect your beloved disciple?
You were so affectionate with me last second.
Why is this second not natural?
Did she deliberately act
to show the Peony Pavilion to someone?
You're so hard to fool.
I really misjudged you.
I didn't expect you to be such a person.
I misjudged you.
Who are you?
Who is the one who instructed you?
You're so confused.
You hired me.
Who are you acting to now?
You...
Nan Xian Zhi is a bunch of nonsense.
Master, she's a liar.
She and I
have never had anything to do with each other.
Master,
why would my nephew have the heart to steal books?
Please give me a clear explanation.
I haven't mentioned the people in the Wind and Rain Valley.
You kept talking about not teaching me martial arts.
I think
you stole this book
and made a fake devil yourself.
You!
You're making a big deal out of it.
I'll take the justice for you today.
I'm the one who ordered her
to fake my identity.
Who are you?
I'm Chu Meng Die.
Nonsense.
Aren't you Lin Shu?
It really seems to be Lin Shu.
Yes, it is.
With this weapon,
no one will be suspicious anymore.
I've made a statement as the Young Master of Jingyun Villa.
He has nothing to do with
the Young Master of South.
He's Chu Meng Die's best friend.
I was assassinated on the way to the marriage.
I had no choice
but to ask my friend to fake my identity.
I
sneaked into the Wind and Rain Valley
as Lin Shu
to find out the truth.
Are you really Chu Meng Die?
Then why did you do that?
I have to ask
those people who
did something evil in the dark.
That's right.
I think
you're just a dog and a dog.
That's why Brother Zhou Heng died in the alley.
I, Li Song'er,
am a straightforward person.
I don't know how to do
these sinister and vicious things.
Unlike someone,
I can do whatever I want.
Shut up!
Zhou Heng, drag her down!
Song'er is my best friend.
She's standing behind Jingyun Villa.
If you dare to disagree again,
don't blame me for being rude.
Sister Lin is fine now.
Chu Meng Die has taken her back to the grass house.
My identity is not changing now.
It's good that there are people
guarding her in Jingyun Villa.
But she is used to living there.
I don't know if she is used to living there.
Princess,
Chu Meng Die has really appeared.
We are now
on her side,
or maybe the Demon Lord has abandoned us.
Let's stay in the Fengyu Valley
and wait for their next action.
Heroine Chu.
Thanks.
Heroine Chu, you are married.
I also wonder why you have to get so noisy today.
Young Master Nan, don't you forget
that I supposed to be the one who should be married to you.
So now, I'm not the guest here,
but the master here.
Don't blame me to misbehave.
There's no one here.
You can say whatever you want.
Song'er is young and kind.
Even if someone
betrays him a thousand times,
if you give him a little bit of credit,
he'll be deceived by the same person
a thousand times.
I heard it right today.
Song'er, at a critical moment,
you just care about yourself
and sell him.
What you said to me before
is the same as today.
Whatever plan you have,
Shangji and Li Song'er
are enemies of Jingyun Villa.
This should be my residence.
Mr. Nan,
I won't see you off.
Please, Miss Chu.
You might fail in the name of você.
And you're Master Beimian.
Who didn't understand that?
Didn't aid me.
Littleassemble.
Has Wu Yan cleaned up this place?
She has.
Why are you so serious?
Shen Lushu is really a perverted person.
Your Highness.
We can talk about the most dreamy thing.
Say something, Baili.
I feel you're even more stupid
after you come here.
What are you looking at?
Don't touch it.
You're finally alive.
Is there anything to eat?
I'm starving.
Get me something to eat.
Go ahead.
I made this specially
for Lin Xiong.
Is this what you made for Mengdie?
Yes.
I made half of it.
Why does Mengdie live such a miserable life?
No.
You're so worried about Mengdie.
Do you like Mengdie?
What are you talking about?
How can I like you?
I'm Li Song'er.
Mengdie is the Chu Heroine.
She's the Lin Shu who lives with you.
Everyone knows it now.
I don't have to pretend anymore.
You mean
Lin Xiong is Chu Mengdie?
Yes.
You haven't told me
how you got here.
Then...
Lin Xiong is...
Yes.
She's your wife.
Then she won't be with my master.
Idiot.
What are you talking about?
Is your master that kind of person?
Of course not.
That's good.
So you have to trust your master.
Whatever he does,
there's a reason for it.
All right.
You can go out and watch.
You went out and watched.
You went back to the valley
to find Lin Xiong
to make a big mistake.
Yes.
Chu Mengdie is in the valley now.
It's not a good time to get married.
When you're done,
we'll think about it.
You've seen what happened today.
Now the country is in a crisis.
It's not easy to stay here.
We have to get the scroll
to get the whole secret.
But this time,
I'm sorry for Zong'er.
Your poison is spreading.
If you add more to the palace,
it will be more dangerous.
People are in the world.
Even if there's a mountain of knives and a sea of fire,
I have to get to the bottom of it.
But, Your Highness...
All right.
I've made up my mind.
WOW
Since I came to theachi boat,
I've reclaimed isolation from the bandits every day.
I've had enough ofï¿½ï¿½
to recieve the good news now.
.
It's ì†¡ åŸƒ.
You are awesome.
You even know how
to make scrambled eggs.
Do you know if
you will be02z plays
in the next day?
Let's eat.
I can't eat it anymore.
You care about your senior so much.
You can go down and cook for him.
You dare to talk back?
Listen.
I don't touch you
because I'm afraid of
Jingyu Villa.
But I'm not afraid.
Come with me.
Let's teach this witch a lesson today.
Let her go down and cook egg cakes for you.
Where are you going?
Chase her.
I didn't expect
you're my teacher.
We've been in the same bed for so many days.
I didn't expect
you'd be my teacher.
Maybe no one in the world
knows
how passionate Zheng Yunchang and his dagger were
and how bright the roses were.
But today,
I'm going to bury you all.
Today is your anniversary.
Let's bury it like this.
Our memories.
Our lost youth.
Let's bury it like this.
You loved me.
We'll never go back.
Brother.
Are you also
burying your secret?
Yes.
Who can hide a secret?
Brother.
They're trying to kill normal people.
Come on.
Don't come near me.
Where do you want to run to?
It seems that I'm sleeping while hibernating.
You can also call it fencing.
Cry out.
Take your life.
Brother Nan,
think it over.
He's not Chu Mengdi.
Why do you still want to help him?
Even if he's not Chu Mengdi,
he was once my woman.
Your woman?
You've...
Brother Nan,
you're like a poisonous snake.
It's fine if you don't want him.
How about this?
Give him to me.
I'll go to Ningxiang House
and find you a hundred of men like him.
Since he was once my woman,
I need to help him one last time.
If you don't leave,
don't blame me for not keeping my love.
I'm leaving.
Go, go, go.
Go, go.
Hurry.
Wait for me.
I knew you'd take care of me.
The words you said to me in the hall last time
were all on purpose.
Just to save me later?
Get lost.
Don't you understand what I said?
From now on,
you have nothing to do with me.
I understand.
Oh, my.
How could you do this to me?
What is he looking at?
Then tell me.
This boy
hasn't paid for it.
Why has he stopped giving?
changes the defeat andðŸ™
Tuç•œ palm
What's wrong with Xiao seed Market Pumpkin
I don't know where I am.
I don't know when I will be back.
Maybe you are looking at me.
I don't dare to make up my mind.
The winter is so beautiful.
The spring is so fragrant.
I want to ask you if you are still in love.
I'd rather dance for you.
I can run for the next life.
I don't want to leave you.
I won't let you down.
I'd rather be a man of my word.
I'll be a man of my word.