Emil!
KARAOKE
Give me a smile.
There.
Eiko, can't you give me a smile today?
Only a few of them are left
and they always look sad.
Remember when we used
to have a lot of customers,
when I was swamped taking orders?
The tsunami changed everything.
As of now, it's still raging.
It changed a lot.
Otsuchi…
doesn't look like Otsuchi anymore.
You see, people have left this place.
We're the only ones here.
And then here I am,
crying over my Haruto.
It's a good thing he went first
and didn't witness the tragedy.
Have you talked to them?
He's still missing, Mayumi.
And I'm not ready to say goodbye.
Hannah.
We both know Emil is gone, right?
Also…
It's been too long since…
Wait…
How long has it been?
Sometimes I can't remember.
I get confused.
Hannah.
You should move on.
Go back to the Philippines.
Visit your parents, your family.
I'm sure they really miss you.
- And if I am your mother--
- Mayumi.
How do I return?
If I do…
I want it to be when I've found Emil.
So even that at least
I can give to our families.
I have to return to school now.
I still have things to do.
Come home early tonight.
I'll cook humba.
I'll make you humba tonight,
your favorite.
Mayumi. Come here.
- Come here.
- Why?
Look under Kaito's seat.
Take care of it.
Okay, take care.
Kaito, are you okay?
My sister's name is Midori Agawa.
She was at the school
when the tsunami hit.
I just want to know if you've found her.
We have her DNA on record.
You will be notified immediately
if we have news.
Thank you so much.
Please help me.
Excuse me.
My fiancé…
I saw him get swept by the tsunami.
Please find him.
Sir.
Don't worry. Please calm down.
WIND PHONE
Excuse me?
What are they doing?
Looking for bodies.
Remember the tsunami?
It happened here.
On the north coast.
I read about it.
Things are swept away from here to the US,
Canada.
One time they saw a fiberglass boat.
Sturdy, right?
It floated for eight years.
That's how it is here in Japan.
There are still bodies
and debris being swept ashore.
I'm Ren.
Hannah.
I'm a hardware design engineer in Kobe.
Fujitsu Ten.
I teach English here.
There's something here!
Wait.
It's just a glove.
Are you okay?
Sorry, I have to go.
Hannah, right?
I saw this on a documentary.
That's a wind phone, right?
I just tried it.
It could be a viral video.
Viral?
Are viral videos not popular here?
It's not connected to anything.
You're not talking to anyone but the wind.
The owner of this garden,
he set up that phone.
When his cousin died,
he used to call him using that phone.
Calling through that phone
helped the survivors.
Illogical, but…
the thought that somehow
the wind carries your message
to your loved one…
It's comforting.
Who did you call?
How about you? Who will you call?
You can go to Namiita Fudo Falls.
There are shrines nearby.
Okay.
I'm looking for my mom.
The last Dad heard, she was here.
But that's a long time ago.
I asked around but I didn't get any info.
You haven't seen her in a long time?
I didn't grow up with her.
Where did you search?
That's my specialty, humba.
Eat well.
Thank you.
Hey.
You grew up without your mom?
It's just you and your dad?
Am I the only one freezing?
My parents weren't married.
When I was two years old,
my mom went to Japan.
She said she was going to work here.
She never came back.
Didn't call my dad anymore.
But you're still looking for her?
My dad is something else.
She left him but he still hasn't learned.
Even before he died a few months ago,
he was still waiting for Mom's return.
He'll tell anyone who went to Japan
to ask around for my mother
wherever they went.
Your dad really loves her deeply.
Crazy.
That's what he is.
But I love him.
That's why I'm here.
Because he told me
to find Mom and give her a letter.
It's something when guys fall in love
with beautiful ones like us.
Head over heels.
That's how my Haruto was.
That's why…
even if Otsuchi changed a lot,
with many buildings constructed,
I never let them touch this restaurant.
My Haruto and I built this.
No one can evict us from here
no matter how hard they try.
Hannah, you can relate
to Ren's dad, right?
Did the tsunami take
someone away from you?
Yes, her boyfriend.
As of now he's missing,
and she's still searching.
Is he also a teacher here?
He used to work in Singapore.
He just visited me here.
Hannah?
If your dad told you
your mom is in Otsuchi,
do you think she was here
during the tsunami?
Because you can go to the police station.
They have a list…
of people who died during the tsunami
and those who are still missing.
Hey, handsome Ren!
Eat. The humba will get cold.
Go ahead.
You didn't eat your food.
It looked good, but I don't know.
Maybe I'm just tired.
You and Mayumi live here?
We sleep downstairs.
When I arrived in Otsuchi,
Mayumi and I immediately became close.
Two Filipinas in a place where
there aren't many Filipinos.
It's automatic you'll become friends.
After the tsunami,
Mayumi opened her house
and restaurant to the survivors.
We stayed there.
We became each other's support group.
There used to be a lot of us.
But now it's only Mayumi and I.
Plus two others.
Good thing you and Mayumi
are there for each other.
I hope you find her.
Thank you.
It's hard to ask around here
since only a few people speak English.
My search would be easier
if you're with me.
You might be busy.
Sorry, I get bold when I'm tired.
Are you okay?
He's asking if you're okay.
Get in.
Go ahead.
There are only a few taxis here.
Get in.
Why is he rushing me?
Thank you.
Fuck!
Why does this keep happening?
Here it is again.
What'll I do?
It's hard to fix.
- Mayumi. Are you okay?
- It keeps happening.
Look, it won't get fixed.
I'm okay.
I'm a rich lady here,
I fix my own toilet and not others'.
If Haruto were here,
this would have been fixed.
If Kenji or Kai was here,
and everyone who left us.
There are still days when I think of them,
what has changed, and my Haruto.
I still want to break down.
- Hannah.
- Mayumi.
It's not just you.
- How are we going to fix this?
- Plunge deeper.
This is so hard.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
Dad.
I'm here.
I'm doing what you told me.
You're passing on your job to me.
All right, Dad.
I'll keep you updated.
You look so surprised.
I'm sorry.
What's written in this notebook?
Let me see.
Good for him.
You?
Have you asked?
I went to the police station.
Good thing we understood each other.
I gave them my mom's name,
but she's not on the list.
I'm think Dad got the wrong info.
Maybe she's not here in Otsuchi.
That's why I called him.
I complained.
I said his instructions
were based on "fake news."
Fake news? That's cute.
I'll use that on Mayumi.
You don't know fake news?
No.
You really should visit back home.
But you know,
even if you complain,
you still won't stop searching, right?
You love your "crazy" dad.
I don't want him to haunt me in my dreams.
What year did your mom get here?
Maybe she stayed here for a while,
but moved at some point.
How can we be sure of that?
I know someone who can help us.
I'll bring you to him.
Wait, you don't have a class?
It's done.
This early?
Yes.
Okay.
I'll just put this back.
Of all places, you went to Otsuchi.
I've been to a lot of places in Japan.
My first job wasn't teaching English.
I worked at a hotel,
and became a fruit picker.
I'm not kidding.
I paid for my siblings' education.
When the tsunami hit,
our youngest had just graduated.
I love my family so much.
It was a relief when my responsibility
to them was over.
I can finally focus on myself
and all my plans in life.
But…
the tsunami washed it all away.
Yamato.
He's Yamato.
Yamato, this is Ren.
A new friend from home.
Welcome to Otsuchi, our new friend.
Did I say something wrong?
It seems you two are getting along.
Noella Basbas?
You know,
if Yamato wasn't here,
I don't know how I would've survived.
He became my refuge and solace.
Yamato.
Are you talking about me?
Wella.
Rikuzentakata.
Rikuzentakata is only
one hour away from Otsuchi.
You can get there easily.
Hannah, are you okay?
Hannah?
You know,
Emil and I talked
that we' meet after my class.
But there was an earthquake
so we escorted the kids out.
Then came the tsunami alert.
I left immediately
to go to Emil.
I saw him.
He was so close.
But I also saw the waves
crashing onto him.
After that,
the next thing I remember,
I was already underwater.
Until I reached the surface.
I searched for him
in all the evacuation centers.
But I didn't find him.
As of now, he's still missing.
Hannah, it's not your fault
that you lived.
What's your plan now?
I'll go to Rikuzentakata.
Come with me?
Come with you?
But it's in Rikuzentakata.
You told me it's just an hour away.
I can pick you up before I head there.
Why do you want me to join you?
Because…
you're now part of my search.
See…
I learned about Rikuzentakata
because of you.
It seems like you're my good luck charm.
I don't know.
I still have a lot to do for my class.
I'll come back here next week,
but if you're not ready then, it's okay.
How are you and Ren?
I already helped him.
Maybe that's enough.
You know I can't be away from Otsuchi.
No one would get mad if
you paused in your search for Emil.
Why are you scared?
Scared?
Me?
Why would I be scared?
I'm the one asking you.
I know what you're thinking, Mayumi.
Nothing's wrong.
You're single, he's single.
Mayumi.
Okay, I'll shut up.
What's holding you back?
Why?
He's handsome.
I thought you were going to shut up.
I can't keep quiet
because I don't want to.
I don't want to.
Because you're still young.
I don't want you to waste your life.
What you and Emil had
will forever be special,
but it's okay to have another
special someone in your life.
Right?
You don't understand, Mayumi.
What is it I'm not getting? Tell me.
There's nothing new in our lives.
Ren is new.
Embrace it!
If the embrace leads to a kiss
then that's great.
You told me you'd keep quiet.
I don't want to.
Mayumi, it's dripping.
- There's so much to fix in this house.
- Take care of it.
Do you know where Eiko is?
Can you help me?
The toilet needs fixing again.
Sorry, I don't understand English.
Sorry.
I've been looking for this restaurant,
but I couldn't find it.
I circled a few times.
Really?
It's the only restaurant here.
I think…
you should really come
because I might get lost.
I rented a car
so you'll be comfortable when you join me.
I contacted some Filipinos in Japan
on Facebook.
They know where my mom is.
You've found her?
If the address they gave is correct.
That's great.
What are you waiting for?
Go there already.
So you'll come with me?
Okay.
Your dad must be happy,
wherever he is now.
Are you excited?
Ren?
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
I said your dad must be really happy now
because finally
his letter will reach the woman
he waited for until his last breath.
You dad is so romantic.
Are you also a romantic like him?
Is there a woman you'll wait for
until your last breath?
No one.
I mean, no woman
has ever made me feel so deeply.
Not even one?
My second girlfriend…
It started great
but quickly fell apart.
My fourth lasted two years.
My third…
It lasted three years
but still had the same ending.
You lasted for three years,
but you never thought of her as a woman
you'd wait for in your deathbed?
Mayumi's restaurant is amazing.
Is it made of magic wood?
Come to think of it,
the tsunami wiped everything out,
but her restaurant stood firm.
A miracle, right?
Yes, a miracle.
We're almost there.
TAKATA MATSUBARA MEMORIAL PARK
FOR THE TSUNAMI DISASTER
What are we doing here?
It's my first time here.
Really?
I just want to take a look.
It's on the way anyway.
We could've visited this
after we met your mom.
Have you been here before the tsunami?
There were 70,000 pine trees here?
This used to be a pine grove.
I remember before,
Mayumi and I couldn't stop
taking pictures here.
Seventy thousand,
but only this one remained.
I recall, this also died,
survived for a while,
but also perished.
The locals just preserved it.
Sorry, I speak like a tour guide,
when you're the one who lives here.
This is the first time
I've seen this, too.
Really?
I was caught in the water.
It was a miracle
that I was able to reach the surface.
I searched for something
I could grab onto.
Then I saw a clothes drawer
floating towards me and I climbed onto it.
I survived
but I saw people
being swept away around me.
I still see them every night.
Are you okay?
I should be the one apologizing.
This is just a museum to me,
but you went through it all.
Let's go.
Did they give you the address?
I think this is it.
I'll stay here.
I'll wait for you here.
What happened?
No one's answering.
No, maybe she just went out.
Come on, let's go.
What?
Let's wait for her.
Let's go.
Hey.
Ren!
You know, we were already there.
You didn't even wait.
It's your chance to see your mom,
and instead of hurrying,
you went on a stopover.
When you arrived,
not five minutes had gone by,
and you already left.
I don't understand.
This is not what I wanted to wear
for our reunion video.
It might go viral online,
I don't want that.
Are you serious?
You can still crack jokes?
Stop the car.
What?
Do you want to know?
While we were on our way,
my chest kept getting tighter and tighter.
When no one answered,
that's when I calmed down.
Because I can't.
I don't want to.
Ren, do you know why I'm helping you?
Because I don't want you
to experience what I did.
Yours can still have an ending,
you can still find her.
If I'd been given a chance
to have closure like yours,
I wouldn't waste that.
Ren, you are lucky.
Don't you see that?
You call that luck?
I have to face the person who left us.
All the questions I kept
my whole life
are making noise in my mind again.
That's why you won't face her
like you did before?
Because you don't want to be like your dad
who waited and did everything for nothing?
Ren, until when?
Until when will you try to escape it?
Don't talk like you know me,
you don't know me.
You're right.
I also don't know what I'm doing here.
What are we going to do?
What's happening?
It happened suddenly.
I don't know what's happening.
I don't know why it's like that.
What's even worse,
Eiko left and never came back.
That's why only Kaito and I
are fixing this.
I don't know if Kaito can fix it.
Wait.
Mayumi,
I went to Rikuzentakata.
They built a museum there
to commemorate the tsunami.
Then there's a lone tree that survived,
which they preserved
to be a reminder of what happened.
How come I didn't know that, Mayumi?
Why did I see and hear about it just now?
Before,
it was like I was in a different world.
It seemed like a lot happened
and I didn't know everything.
It's like everyone has moved on,
and I'm still stuck.
Kaito.
Be careful!
Can you fix it?
Let's check the toilet later, okay?
I'm sorry about what I said.
I shouldn't have said that.
We just met.
Hannah, you're right
about everything you said.
My last relationship
went on for three years.
It came to a point where
she was expecting a wedding.
When I felt that, I broke up with her.
I told her we couldn't get married
because we were too different.
We always fought.
But after what you said,
I realized you're right.
I was scared of settling down because…
I might have the same fate as my dad.
It sounds immature
compared to what you and Emil had.
I hope you find your mom.
Hannah.
Sorry, did I say something wrong?
Ren, can you please stop?
Don't say I'm mature
or paint me as a saint.
You're also telling me not to feel guilty
that Emil died and I lived?
That's far from what really happened.
When I had to help my siblings
finish their studies,
Emil accepted that.
He waited for me.
In 2011,
when my sibling graduated,
I was ready to get married.
That's why he came here.
He surprised me.
I've waited so long,
to have you all to myself.
We can be together now, Hannah.
We can start a family now.
But, Emil, how about my job here?
Your youngest sibling graduated.
I'll take care of us in Singapore.
Just think about our future children.
That was really the plan.
But when I heard from Emil
what his plans for us were,
I realized I couldn't do it.
All my life,
I'd been responsible for my siblings,
for my family, for everyone.
I hadn't truly lived for myself.
For once, that's what I wanted.
I fell in love with teaching in Japan.
That's why I needed more time,
for him to wait.
He wanted me to say yes right away.
Emil!
But I couldn't do it.
On the day of the tsunami,
Emil and I met
Because I wanted him to understand
that even though I said no to marriage,
I didn't want him out of my life.
I still wanted him to be a part of my life
because he was my best friend.
He was supposed to leave then,
but I asked him to stay.
I begged him not to leave.
Emil!
It's my fault.
Because of me, Emil died.
He died angry and hurt
because of my selfishness.
That's why I must not
stop searching for him,
because I don't have the right.
Okay.
How do you say,
"Thank you for accompanying me."
Thank you for accompanying me.
I give up, teacher.
You know,
you should join my English class.
My students get embarrassed
when they make mistakes.
But I tell them that's normal
when learning a new language.
You should smile more.
It suits you.
Thank you.
You know…
I'm scared of opening up
to people about what happened
to Emil and I.
I don't want them to blame me
like how I blame myself.
But now that I was able to tell you,
I feel relieved.
I haven't felt this way in a long time.
Why thank me when I haven't done anything?
Because you're here…
listening.
It means a lot.
Ren, my life still needs a lot of fixing.
I understand.
I shouldn't have done that.
We can still be friends, right?
Hello, Emil?
Sorry I'm only just now calling.
I was shattered.
I was a coward.
The last time we met,
you were so mad,
you told me
you didn't want to see me anymore.
I looked for you, Emil.
So even that I would have done for you.
That maybe when I find you,
you'll be able to forgive me.
Emil, it feels like I've been carrying
a huge weight for so long.
I think I'm finally ready to let it go.
I want to live again,
and I'm ready for possibilities.
But can I do that?
Can I embrace that?
Or will it make it harder for you
to forgive me?
Ren. Son.
Have some tea.
Before Dad died,
he asked me to give this to you.
That's why I searched for you.
He waited for you until the end.
I didn't ask him that.
But still, that's what he did.
I'll go ahead.
I tried contacting you
but my life became complicated.
I never planned on looking for you
because I thought
I didn't want to see you.
Or…
because I wouldn't believe
anything you would say.
But I was wrong.
Because the truth is,
I don't want to face you
because I'll be reminded
of how much we're alike.
Dad…
poured his heart out to you.
He didn't care even when he was hurting.
But you ran away.
Those are the two kinds of people
in a relationship.
Dad and I are different,
so I'm more like you.
I can't wait and love
the way Dad did for you.
But I don't see it that way now.
Maybe I'm wrong.
It's funny I realized all this
because I was looking for you.
You're right.
No explanation will be enough
for you to understand what I did.
It's good you found me.
I searched for you first in Otsuchi.
A Filipina helped me.
A teacher.
We also know someone from there.
She died during the tsunami.
She was my daughter's teacher.
Hannah.
Hannah Sarmiento.
You might be mistaken.
No.
I can't be wrong.
- Look.
- You're wrong.
No, my son. Look at this.
She and her fiancé are tsunami victims.
The guy survived, but she didn't.
It was sad.
She and another Filipina died.
The other one
is a restaurant owner in Otsuchi.
Fuck, I don't know what I'm gonna do here!
Hannah!
Mayumi!
Look!
What should I do?
Look! Call Kaito!
Hurry!
Kaito?
Kaito, will you help us in the bathroom?
Mayumi!
Let's go!
Mayumi.
It's Emil.
Maybe he's the reason
why all this is happening.
I finally called him.
I told him I'm ready to move on.
But maybe Mayumi doesn't want me to.
That's not true.
Emil can't do that to you.
You know that.
Ren!
Ren.
Last night,
I called Emil on the wind phone.
What happened?
It happened so fast.
Water was coming out of the bathroom.
It was like water from the tsunami.
The walls and floors were cracked.
Don't you believe me?
Mayumi was there.
She saw everything.
Ren, I feel like I'm close
to finding Emil,
here where I last talked to him.
Hannah, how did you get out of the water?
I don't know.
You said you were washed away.
You said you remember being underwater
until you were able to breathe.
But how did you get out of the water?
I said I can't remember.
Why?
I don't know.
I already told you,
I remember being underwater,
then I searched for Emil
at the evacuation center.
Hannah.
Please…
Please stop.
Can't you just believe me?
Hannah, Emil didn't die.
I was able to talk to him.
Like you, he was washed away,
but he was able to hold onto something,
survived, and was brought to the hospital.
He tried looking for you.
Why wouldn't he find me?
I'm here.
I did what you told me.
I went to my mom.
That's where I learned the truth.
Thanks again.
Get in.
Ghost.
Ghost!
There's no one there.
Hannah, you're dead.
That's not true.
I told you earlier
that I was able to get out of the water.
and I looked for Emil
at the evacuation center.
What are you talking about?
He tried to save you,
but he didn't find you.
Hannah?
SUPPLIES RECEIVED TODAY: RICE, WATER,
BLANKETS PEOPLE HERE:
As of now you're on the missing list.
Mayumi is also gone.
I saw her grave.
She was buried here.
The restaurant is still there, right?
You saw that.
You saw the restaurant.
You went inside it, Ren!
Aren't you wondering?
I can only see the restaurant
when we're together,
because nothing is left there, Hannah.
There's nothing.
Also…
when you go to work,
when you teach,
do you really remember doing that?
Your watch…
is stuck at 3:20.
That's the time the tsunami hit.
But, but why are we here?
Why can you talk to me?
Why can you see me?
I have no idea.
Because you're wrong.
I'm not dead.
I'm still alive!
MAYUMI TAKAMOTO
DIED: MARCH 11, 2011
Mayumi.
Are you okay?
You'll be fine.
It's been a long time now.
Can you really hear me,
Hannah?
They said yes.
Ren called me.
He said you're looking for me.
On that day,
while in the water,
I tried grabbing your hand.
I tried to save you.
I hope you know
that later I searched for you.
Hannah?
Hannah!
It took long time before I gave up,
Hannah.
But I hope you understand
that months and years have passed.
I have a family now…
that I love so much.
But there are also days
when I still think of you.
Wherever you are,
I hope you're happy.
You'll always be in my heart.
Goodbye, Hannah.
I went to Yamato.
You know, he should be haunted.
He said you weren't ready for the truth.
You know, it's amazing
how we only see the things we want to see.
Those who were with us
learned about the truth early on.
I didn't want to believe then.
That's why I only saw
what I wanted to believe in.
Emil.
You know, he called me
on the wind phone.
I heard him.
It's really working.
Tell everyone about it.
Can you tell Emil
I'm happy he has a family now?
That his dream came true.
That's what I want for him.
I'll do that.
Ren, do you regret meeting me?
According to Yamato,
I met you because you needed me,
and I needed you.
I went to your school.
I met your co-teachers.
I saw your picture there.
You were always smiling, Hannah.
You should have no regrets
because I know you were happy.
Join them now.
I'm sure
I'll be happy wherever you go.
Thank you, Ren.
Because of you, I felt like I was alive.
Thank you, too.
Because you made me understand
that real love
is setting someone free.
Rest now.
Ren, I hope you learn from my story.
Live and love.
Someday, the right person will come,
because I know you have
so much love in your heart.
How are you?
Well, I…
When I came to Manila,
Mom called and asked me to move to Japan.
That's why I'm here again.
I know it's peaceful wherever you are.
I shouldn't be calling you,
I might just disturb you.
I just miss you.
There's something I failed to tell you.
You asked me about the person
I'd wait for until my last breath.
I told you no one.
But the truth is it's you, Hannah.
If we will be given a chance,
I know that it's you.
I wish the wind
carries all my love for you.
If only it's possible
for you to call me, too, right?