Poor Wu Yi.
Martial Jiao Jiao, you vicious woman.
I'm back
You're back.
I'm going to cook now.
You still know to come back?
Do you think
This world is fascinating.
What are you talking about?
Martial and charming.
I think you have completely forgotten
The existence of a child
Is your skin itchy again?
When you and Dongfang Yu were in love,
Do you know what Wu Yi is doing?
I
He has done so much for this family.
Look for yourself.
Why did you send me a photo of Wu Yi?
You see that?
You must be ashamed.
You still think you raised Wu Yi?
The most suitable candidate?
Why are you so greedy?
From now on,
I won't let you go.
Martial and charming.
I officially inform you that
I'm taking Wu Yi home tomorrow.
From now on, everything about Wu Yi,
I'll be in charge.
If you want money, come to me.
What are you doing?
Come on.
You hit me?
You can't kill me.
I'll take Wu Yi home tomorrow.
I'll tell you again.
No one will take Wu Yi.
Hello, Miss Li.
Miss Wu Yi.
Are you not very supportive?
Wu Yi's extracurricular activities
No.
I support him very much.
Alright.
Come and see me when you pick up Wu Yi.
I'm going now.
Mr. Li, I'll go too.
Why am I not Wu Yi's parent?
Alright.
Don't take it.
Everyone, be careful.
It's Wu Yi's father and mother.
We came together.
Seems to be supportive.
Our activities
Stop it, Miss Li.
This lady and I
Has nothing to do with it.
Miss Li.
What's wrong with Wu Yi?
Are you in trouble? Tell me.
Miss Li.
I'm the guardian of Wu Yi's future.
So what do you want to tell me?
Here's the thing, Mother Wu Yi.
Wu Yi, this afternoon,
I didn't hand in my homework.
Da Li went home crying.
Wu Yi didn't hand in her homework this afternoon.
Yes, Mother Wu Yi.
We know that parents
I love you dearly.
So we use
Rotating field practice
Yes, I know.
I've talked to Dali's mother.
Waste utilization
The activity of turning waste into treasure.
We've done a lot of sessions.
Wu Yi, what are you doing?
This time, Wu Yi and
Darley is a group.
But Wu Yi didn't come this afternoon.
Darley cried for a long time.
Just got coaxed home by his mother.
I saw
Wu Yi picked up the bottle.
I also want to know
Why didn't he bring the bottle to school?
Wu Yi, don't pick up garbage anymore.
Do you know
Second Junior Brother,
There's no buts.
That's me.
I know.
You have done so much for this family.
I'll take care of you from now on.
Why are you so greedy?
From now on,
I won't let you go.
Come on.
You can't kill me.
I'll take Wu Yi home tomorrow.
Miss Li.
WuYi
You really picked up the bottle.
only
Was taken away by a beggar.
I threw out some garbage.
But you asked Wu Yi to go to school alone.
It's not right.
The road condition is so complicated now.
He's so young.
What if there's any danger?
Look for yourself.
We didn't leave until we saw you.
Who knew you would throw the bottle away?
And then made wild guesses about others.
Hum
It's too hasty.