Actually,
If you throw us out now,
And pay us back.
How inappropriate.
But if you let us stay,
Can you collect rent?
I bought the house.
Do you think I care about the rent?
Yes
big shot
I'm shallow.
Look.
You and I are Wu Yi's closest relatives.
You have too much money to care about the rent.
that
Why don't you let us
And love each other.
Think about this picture.
How wonderful it is.
I bought this place.
To take care of Wu Yi.
But after I met you today,
I found Wu Yi's living environment
Is much worse than I thought.
I don't trust you with Wu Yi.
You can either
Give up the custody of Wu Yi now.
The house is yours.
or
Move out of this house now.
WuYi
We'll move out now.
custody
Don't even think about it.
Mom
Why are you moving?
Are we getting kicked out by a bad landlord?
Yes
Bad landlord.
Second Brother, we have a deal.
To protect the martial arts together.
Do something.
You can't bear
Let Wu Yi sleep with you?
WuYi
We'll pack up now.
Just like our spring outing.
Our adventure is about to begin.
Well
WuYi
Do you like it here?
This is my home.
Of course I like it.
Then you and Second Junior Brother
Live here together, okay?
Second Junior Brother.
I really, really like you.
But I have to protect my mother.
She will be bullied by the bad guys.
As you wish.
We'll move out now.
to wait a moment
Protect our homes and defend our country
Keep fit and healthy.
That's all for today.
Bye. Be careful on the way.
Goodbye, teacher.
Where are you going, Wu Yi?
Let's train after class.
Hurry up.
YanKai
To find the best room here.
Put my clothes down.
Okay, boss.
Eldest Brother.
Look what I brought you.
Piggy Bag.
Do you like it
Come on.
It's so pretty.
It's so beautiful.
Why are you here?
Moving?
Come on.
This Qi Mo
How could you be so kind as to let me stay?
There must be a conspiracy.
No way
I have to get rid of him.
high five
Yeah
Why are you moving?
The beautiful scenery
To practice martial arts.
Practice