Hello, Xiaorou.
Why does your brother want to live in my house suddenly?
Oh dear
My home is inconvenient.
What's wrong with your home?
I'm in a relationship.
Why did you take off your order so quickly?
I don't care.
Just take care of my brother for a few days.
Please take care of my brother.
Hang up, right?
You can do it with my help.
Dongyu
Do you think this is a hotel or a restaurant?
Come and go as you wish.
I just go home often.
That's enough.
Yes, I'm fine.
You can go back now.
Who stay here.
It's probably not me.
I'm afraid you haven't figured it out yet.
I'm the landlord here.
What are you talking about?
Ah
Nothing?
Dongfang Yu said he was tired.
I want to go back and rest.
I'm not leaving. He's not going.
I disagree.
Why don't you agree?
I'm the landlord. I have the final say.
I'm a tenant here.
I have the final say.
Old rules
Rock and paper scissors.
It's up to the winner.
I won.
Dongfang Yu, you can leave now.
Wu Yi is still in the room.
When you wash him,
Hurry up.
I know.
I've been
A business travel
I just came back.
therefore
I have more time to take care of you and Wu Yi.
Oh
Are you here to see Wu Yi?
I'm here to see you.
Brother Yu, eat fruit.
Xiao Yu, it's getting late.
Wu Yi is still in the shower.
I'll check on him first.
good
Xiao Yu came to see me.
Are you here to see Wu Yi?
I'm here to see you.
You're a child yourself.
How can I take a child?
What am I thinking?
Why would I...
Compare the two of them.