It's okay. Do your own thing.
hey
This chair is mine.
You can't sit there.
If you say that,
I still insist on
Brother Yu, why are you here?
This is a game of musical chairs.
I played it in kindergarten.
Mom, can I play with you?
Brother Yu, why are you here?
I thought you were on a business trip.
He came to see me.
I'll be back soon.
You two know each other?
I have some business contacts.
Not really.
I just came back from a business trip.
So I came to see you and Xiao Bao.
What about the side dishes?
Xiaorou made it.
We don't eat these dishes, right, Jiao?
Why do you always call me Jiao Jiao?
It's weird.
She's so affectionate.
After all, we are a family.
Besides,
Who says I don't eat side dishes?
You don't even know.
Xiaorou can cook these dishes.
Wu Yi and I won't eat it.
Second Brother, don't say it too early.
You won't know until you eat it.
Wu Yi knows it best.
Wu Yi, let me ask you something.
Choose between me and the side dish.
Who are you going to choose?
Of course, you're more important than the side dishes.
Well
But you don't have any side dishes.
Mom, I'm going to paint.
I have to finish my homework after drawing.
Go. The teacher told me.
WuYi
As the heir of the Qi family,
How can you say these dishes are delicious?
I heard that
The landlord has been looking for trouble.
Xiaorou just told me
It's nothing.
Has been solved.
that
If there's something to hide,
You can tell me directly.
I really don't.
Don't get me wrong.
How about this?
You and Wu Yi should move to my house.
The room is still empty.
Xiaorou can be your company.
I don't want to leave here.
If my sister comes back,
I'm afraid she can't find me and Wu Yi.
It took me a long time to persuade him.
Qi Mo asked us to stay here.
therefore
Qi Mo
Is the landlord here.
Qi Mo didn't bully you, right?
How about this?
We can buy this house.
Dongyu
I'm really sorry.
The price of my house
You can't afford it.
I won't let anyone bully Jiao Jiao.
Mom, I've finished drawing.
I'll play outside for a while.
Go.
Please be safe.
Well
Brother Xiao Yu.
How about we go out for a walk?
There are outsiders.
It's inconvenient to talk.
go
Who wants to go out?
He was here just now.
Where are you going?
Second Junior Brother.
Wu Yi, what are you doing?
This damn Wu Jiao Jiao
How could you let such a young child
To do this.
Wu Jiao Jiao, you're finished.
Give it to me.
WuYi
Don't do this anymore, you know?
Second Junior Brother,
There's no buts.
That's what I used
I know.
You have done so much for this family.
I'll take care of you from now on.