Nice!
Ah... I’m sleepy
I think it was too much to wake up at 5AM
You look good in your uniform
I know, right?
Don't be so nervous
Your classmates are nice
Okay
Shall we go in?
Silence, class
We have a new student here today
Would you briefly introduce yourself for us?
Okay
Hello
I’m here as a new student from today and my name is
Se-
-Heon
Yoon
You guys are making the new student very nervous
Seheon?
Yes?
Oh...
Oh, I'm Seheon Yoon!
Seheon is majoring in classical piano,
He's been doing the homeschooling for a long time,
so it is the first time for him to attend the arts high school
You guys can support him well to adjust in school, right?
Yes
Doyoon Suh!
Yes?
Seheon, you can sit next to him
Okay
Please remove the backpack for him
Hello?
Hey
My name is Doyoon
Nice to meet you
Is that a drum?
Yes
You’re right
It’s a snare drum
Can you show him around the school after class, Doyoon?
Okay, I will
Well, then, what were we studying about?
Today's lesson is...
The development of music in the Renaissance period
Music in the Renaissance period was very religious
And it was very focusing on combining the artistic beauty with it
Especially, it developed in the form of the church,
including chant and...
Hey
What the heck? You scared me
What are you doing here?
Playing house?
I was just doing my homework
But why?
What's that?
Come on
It’s so embarrassing
Are you going to give it to Taeyi?
Hey
Damn it
What you just saw is the nurse’s office
The cafeteria is all the way through the hallway
And the convenience store is at the back of the school
The gym, you have to walk 300 meters towards the northeast side
And you know the faculty room, right?
Do I need to let you know even the security office?
Oh yes, here it is
Hey, what are you doing over there?
What is this room for...?
As you can see it's a piano room
The room that I went yesterday didn’t look like this
Where is it?
It's a bit messy... With the old piano...
Oh you went to that haunted piano room?
Haunted?
Yes, that an old piano room
There is a rumor to shut it down,
and it must not be managed well too
But the piano was fine
Is that so?
But there’s a rumor that the room is haunted
So nobody visit that place
As you know,
the appearance of the room is a bit...
No way, there is no ghost
Did you just say, “no way”?
I’m not sure whether I should tell you this
Students who passing by often hear some strange sound over there
A strange sound?
Is anybody out there?
Oh, hold on
What’s wrong?
Then that piano sound was...
I... I think I heard it
Huh?
You freaked me out!
I swear, when I stood in front of the door, the music has stopped
For real?
Obviously
Well, it’s an arts high school,
So there's a lot of kids practicing piano all over the place
You must have heard the wrong thing
Is it?
But that piano room,
It's not like we're banned to use it, right?
Well, it’s not technically banned
And it’s unmanged, right?
I told you
Nobody use that room
Taeyi!
Where have you been?
Are you friend with him?
Why?
Huh?
Just because
He is my boyfriend
Your boyfriend?
What are you thinking?
If your friend is a boy, then he is your boyfriend
Normally we just call them as friends
You are cute
His name is Taeyi Han
I’m kind of close to him
Does he play the piano too?
A little?
His major is a trumpet
A trumpet?
That punk plays the trumpet?
Did you fall in love with him?
Huh?
What?
You are staring at him
I asked, did you fell in love with him or not
What are you talking about? You are giving me goosebumps
What do you feel about?
About what?
About the piano
Are you good at playing the piano?
I don't think I'm that good...
What do you like other than classical music?
I like jazz music
A jazz music?
Yes
Like...
Like this kind of thing?
Yes
That can be considered as jazz too
That's unique
While I was thinking about the piano, I was totally forgot about something
The thing is, I don’t have any friend
Why?
What?
Are you care about the new student?
No I’m not
Poor guy, should we ask him to eat together?
He kept staring at you today
I heard that he likes jazz...
Did anyone ask you?
Not really
Why are you being so mean?
What are you so angry about?
Why is he looking at me like that?
Did he recognize that I snuck out the piano room this morning...?
Wait, teacher
Yes?
The piano room is full, so...
Is there any empty piano room?
Did you make a reservation?
A reservation?
If you want to use it for other than practice purpose,
you have to make a reservation
If I make a reservation now, when will I get to use it?
Maybe in a month?
Huh? That long?
There are so many students using the piano room,
so we are always running out of room
You will have to practice at home for a while
You don’t have a piano at home?
Yes, I have it
But the thing is...
Thank you, anyways
Sure, take care
Alright, school is over guys
Thank you
Aren't you going home?
I will
Seheon
Huh?
See you tomorrow
Yeah, bye
Why are you being so nice to him?
Are you jealous?
Ouch
I get it, let go of me!
Hey, isn’t that Juhee?
Hey
You go first
But why?
Just make up any words
And about the birthday present, let’s call it even
Call it even?
Geez
Doyoon!
Oh, hey
Where is Taeyi?
Hmm... Oh, Taeyi
He left first
Oh really?
But why didn't I see him...
Why?
Nothing
See you
Alright
Oh, I’m heading this way
Bye
Goodbye
No one goes there
because there is a rumor that it’s haunted
Hello?
I'm not afraid of ghosts
I'm more afraid of that I won’t be able to play the piano
He will never come back around this time
What should I play then?
I have already warned you
That I'll kill you if you play the piano here again
You don’t really listen to me, right?
Don’t you think it’s wrong?
What?
I heard that no one uses this room
You are so stubborn
I even use it after school
You were here in the morning too, right?
Like a rat
Don't you think you're being too harsh?
Just get the hell out of here no matter it’s a morning or a night
Then at least give me a good reason why I shouldn't be here!
If I smash the piano, will you never come back?
Are you mad?
Listen,
whatever as you understand,
there’s only a single choice
Get the hell out
Understood?
No
What?
I said I don’t understand
You really bother me
Get off me, it hurts!
It won’t just hurt
It’s not a thing that breaking your wrists
What the hell is wrong with you? Just tell me the reason
Shut up
Then just break it
I could even die to play the piano
Yes, I like it
That I could die for this
Get off me
I'm sorry...
But why did you...
Hey, don't act like this
What are you guys doing out there?
I came in to practice because there were no room
But he just started to grab me and push
Grab and push you?
Yes
And then we went like this...
And this...
And I climbed up on him
Climbed him up?
Yes?
Well...
Then he just jumped on top of me
Just shut up
Jumped on the top of you
Well I didn’t lie
I’m leaving
Well, well
The conversation is not over yet
And then what happened?
Well... It’s not as the weird thing you think
But the situation was...
Well, it’s interesting
What is your name?
Seheon Yoon
Oh, Seheon Yoon?
Okay, you’re free to go
Pardon?
I said you can leave
I have something to talk with him
Oh, okay
I've been looking for you
You ignored Juhee so I was wondering where you are heading
And, look at you...
Well, it’s so interesting
That’s enough
My sister was up all night to make something for you
She must be sad if she find this out
I’m leaving
Do not act up, Taeyi
Put your hands away
Hey, Taeyi
If...
If my sister starts to cry, mentioning your name
I can’t stand then anymore
You get what I mean?
And Seheon?
Well, he is cute
I was bored since I came back to school
Thanks to him, I'll have fun
Do whatever you want
Give me your hands
What are you doing? Why your hands look like this?
As a pianist, you should consider your hands as your life
I just bumped into something
How’s school?
It’s good
I also have friends there
It's not like what you think!
I’m popular in school
Don’t be too excited
Of course
If you hang out with your friends,
that means you'll have less time to practice
Friends..
To earn something,
you have to give up something else
I know it too
I've heard that for a long time
It’s done, how do you feel?
Good enough
Don't practice today, just take a rest
Okay
It was the first day of school,
and things went out of control
But what is the reason...
Don’t act like this
That he overreacts in this way?
Is everything going to be alright?
Taeyi Han
Why do I feel sympathy on him?
He is such a jerk
I’m so annoyed
Take it slow
That’s it
Hey, Juha!
Hello
Can I join?
Sure
It's been such a long time
Doyoon Suh!
Why aren’t you defend well?
Okay, i will
You’re so annoying
Hey, take it slow
It's a foul, right?
Give him a free throw for him
Hey
Hey, Taeyi!
I need to talk to you
Why?
Just to be clear,
I'm still going to play the piano there
You're not going to tell me the reason anyway
Whatever you want
What?
If you’re done, I’m leaving
Hey wait a second!
At least you should tell me the reason what bothered you!
Must I tell you the reason for you?
Of course! You’re being ridiculous
You threatened me all of a sudden, telling me not to play the piano,
and now you want me to do whatever I want?
I don’t want to listen
Huh?
I don’t like your piano performance
What do you think you know?
Did you even listened to it closely?
Are you confident?
Of course I am, who do you think -
Then play it
What?
I said, play it
I will listen to it closely
It’s not what I expected
What happened suddenly..
If you stare me like that
How am I supposed to play..
Hey, you’re not going to play it?
It.. seems like you don’t like jazz
Do you want to request a song, or,
have a favorite song?
Whatever you feel confident
Then.. Shall I begin...?
How do you think?
Huh? How did you listen?
As I expected…
I don’t like it
Say that again?
It’s not good
Hey, hold on!
Is that all?
Do as you like
Now it doesn’t matter
whether you are going to play the piano here or not
Hey!
They definitely look similar
Is that possible..?
Or I’m just out of my mind
How do you think?
I don’t like it
Do whatever you want
because now it doesn’t matter anymore
I lied
To be honest,
I wanted to listen to it for more
Everyone, sociocultural phenomena
are caused by the complex interaction of society and culture
And they have a variety of characteristics
The five main characteristics of sociocultural phenomena are
first complexity,
second diversity, third variability,
fourth, interrelatedness, and fifth, social meaning
Now, there are divided meanings of complexity,
such as the interactions of members of a society
And when I say members of society,
it could be you or...
You’re not eating?
I don’t feel like it
Do I have to feed you?
Come on
My husband,
Open your mouth
Stop it
The weather is already low pressure, why are you even low?
Why isn't Seheon coming to school?
Stop talking about him, I’m not interested in
Well, you are
You've been staring at his empty seat this whole morning
Did I?
Yes, I saw you
Take your time, I’m leaving right now
He is weird today
Seheon Yoon
Why do I
care about him
Should I stop playing?
You’re cute, Seheon
Hey, what are you going?
Just stay still
It hurts..
Please…