[PERSON]
Have you ever heard of the saying that the kanji for "person" represents two people supporting each other?
But please take a good look at this.
Clearly, only the person on the right is putting in all the effort.
Meanwhile, the other one is putting his entire weight on him.
Um, Sir.
What kind of class is this?
Up till recently,
I thought I had to be the person on the right, for the person I liked to reciprocate my feelings.
No, really. If only you'd be my "wife".
I'd love to!
That invitation was a once in a lifetime opportunity for me.
With me as your "wife", I won't let there be
a single speck of dust.
With me as your "wife", having an unbalanced diet will be unthinkable.
However,
it seems like I was working hard in the wrong way.
- I meant to support her,
- What are you doing?
I'm shaving the bonito fish.
- but it only gave her pressure.
- It's okay. I'm doing it because I want to.
Because I'm the "wife".
Why do you have to work so hard just because you're the "wife"?
Even though there's nothing I can offer in return.
Just as I thought all hope was lost,
she was the one who reached out to me.
Which is why, I'd like to at least pay for things if we're going to live together.
In other words, I'll be the pillar of the family.
- That was how Hayami and I
- As an inexperienced "wife",
As an inexperienced pillar of the house,
- I look forward to working with you.
And so, we're officially living together
as a "wife" and the pillar of the family that support each other.
Any questions at this point?
- Sir, question.
- Yes, Akamine?
Doesn't that mean
both of you are merely housemates living together for mutual benefit, especially in her case?
How do you plan on going beyond such a relationship?
Well...
Hayami.
Yes?
Even if you think it's okay, I'm not sure if I'll be able to remain a "wife" till tomorrow morning.
Um...what do you mean by that?
What do you think?
[Yamamoto Chihiro & Hayami Honoka, Sales Department]
Could it be the rescue squad?
- Obviously not.
- Right.
Judging from the doorbell's beat...
It's my brother! My eldest brother.
What? Your brother?
Hey, Chihiro!
[Yamamoto Masami, Chihiro's Eldest Brother]
Oh? Sounds like he came in.
What? The door wasn't locked?
I think it was left like that?
How can you be so careless!
Chihiro?
You're not done unpacking?
Sorry, excuse me!
No, don't! My brother is--
Chihiro!
Chihiro! Are you inside? I'm coming to save you!
Chihiro! Hang on!
Chihiro!
Chihiro?!
No, this isn't what it looks like--
Um, nice to meet you. I'm--
Get away from him!
What?
Get away from my precious brother, you homewrecker!
[SALES DEPARTMENT - HAYAMI HONOKA]
I didn't know you're his senior at work, sorry for my atrocious behaviour earlier.
I apologize for my disgraceful actions too.
Chihiro, you didn't tell me anything about sharing an apartment with a woman.
Sorry.
You said you wanted to move somewhere closer to your workplace to focus on your job.
That was why we tearfully,
and extremely reluctantly, agreed for you to live by yourself.
I wasn't lying about that.
But to hide such an important detail from us, are you...
Um, it's not Yamamoto's fault.
You should blame it all on me.
I was the one who said that I wished he could be my "wife".
Your "wife"?
Did you propose to Chihiro?
When you haven't even greeted his family in person?
Well, uh, it's not really a pro--
Unbelievable.
You're a homewrecker!
I-I-I'm sorry!
Stop it! It's the second time today.
I'm really sorry!
I've been looking after him since young, in place of our busy mother.
That's why, when it comes to him, I can't help but...
It's fine, please get up.
So, in summary,
you invited Chihiro to stay with you
purely as a housemate
because you were charmed by his housekeeping abilities. Is that right?
It's just as you said.
"Wife" is just a figure of speech.
The terms "wife" and "housemate" may be used interchangeably.
In other words, you're saying that you don't harbour any feelings for him,
not even a single ounce of romantic feelings for him?
That's right. Not the slightest bit.
I see.
Aright then, I'll go home for today.
- Let me send you downstairs.
- There's no need.
I'll have Hayami send me instead.
Thanks for making the trip here.
The room where you two were locked in a grapple earlier,
was it yours?
Locked in a grapple...?
Yes, that's my room.
Hayami,
it pains me to say this, but I have to,
since I'm responsible for protecting Chihiro as the family's representative.
Okay.
Honestly,
you're not a suitable candidate for cohabiting with Chihiro.
As his brother,
or essentially,
as his "mother", I disapprove of your cohabitation!
[MR. BRIDE, EPISODE 3]
Wow, I didn't know that the recipe for chiffon cake was initially kept secret for twenty years.
How did things end up like this?
Take a look at this, right here!
[TEA PARTY INVITATION]
A tea party invitation?
[Takahashi Kimiko, Honoka's friend]
- What's this about?
- This isn't a simple tea party.
It is a meeting to determine if I'm a suitable candidate for their precious youngest son to be "married" off to.
In other words, it's a "husband" appraisal.
Come again?
His brother passed this to me the other day.
If you really want to live with Chihiro,
please prove yourself to be a worthy housemate at this tea party.
But...how do I go about doing that?
Our whole family loves sweet food. We love eating them,
and also
making them.
I'm sure he was trying to say, "You'd better make a cake or two for us, you homewrecker"
behind his uncanny smile.
But aren't you the pillar of the family?
In that case, shouldn't you prove your worth in that area?
Kimi, you're too naive!
Indeed, in the olden days, the pillar of the family only has to work hard to earn money.
But right now, we're in the Reiwa* era!
[*1 May 2019 to present]
Even if I'm the pillar of the house, I need to be competent at home as well.
That's why I need to be someone who can at least bake fluffy chiffon cakes in a breeze,
to be a pillar of the family in the Reiwa era. I have no choice!
I'll definitely overcome this tea party, or rather, this "husband" assessment,
and have Yamamoto's brother-cum-mother approve of this cohabitation.
His brother-cum-mother...
Aside from that, you seem extremely unwilling to let go of Yamamoto.
That goes without saying. I can no longer imagine living without Yamamoto.
Do you really...only see him as a housemate?
What?
Oh, nothing.
By the way, are you free tonight?
- I'd love to come over to your place to practise--
- Absolutely not.
- No way.
- What's with that immediate reply?
Every time you step into a kitchen, it'll end up as dirty as hell.
I absolutely refuse.
If I can't get Kimi to help me out...
Yes, got it.
Okay.
Thanks for the help. Yes, thank you.
But it doesn't seem right to ask for Yamamoto's help.
- This is for you!
- Thank you!
- Kasuga, here's one for you too.
- Wow!
You really made sugar cookies for us.
Yup! I've been thinking of trying to bake some.
[Hanazuma Ran & Kasuga Ryou, Sales Department]
Woah, they're really well done for a first try. You're amazing!
You're too kind.
Oh, yeah! Hanazuma!
Yamamoto, how do you do?
[Akamine Reina - Raccoon Electronics, Human Resources]
You almost gave me a heart attack.
Could you please explain how exactly did this happen?
[CHANGE OF RESIDENTIAL ADDRESS]
Akamine, please help to follow up with these two requests for change in address.
What? Are they c-cohabiting?!
Stop it! Let's talk elsewhere.
- But why? What's wrong?
- Shh. Come here.
We're trying to keep the fact that we're living together a secret.
Even though we're just sharing an apartment, a man and woman living together will definitely invite gossip.
What kind of gossip?
You know,
speculations of how Hayami and I
may be seeing each other or something.
In the worst-case scenario, even if that's what people think, I'm not really opposed to it.
I wonder how the other party feels, though...
- Huh?
- Wait, what did you say?
Hayami, you're sharing an apartment with a guy?
Yeah.
But don't misunderstand, we're not seeing each other. He's just...a friend?
Or more like, an acquaintance?
- I see that quite often! Two people without romantic feelings...
- In the first place,
that person has never even seen you as a man, am I right?
I'm glad young people nowadays get straight to the point!
In my university...
Hayami, today...?
I'm still busy with work, you can go back first.
You don't have to cook for me either.
Got it.
Hayami, I'm back.
Sorry for the trouble.
Look at this.
- I went all out.
- Wow! Where did you...
Your eyes seem to be saying, "Look at me instead!"
[Koga Iori, Sales Department]
Koga.
Who wouldn't be hurt after hearing that?
I suppose. There was that incident too.
Yamamoto.
Sorry for interrupting, I...
came back to get something.
Hey--
That's why I suspected there was an unusual relationship between you two.
No, there's nothing going on between us at all.
It's one-sided, from my end.
Oh, really?
Sorry about that.
If anything, how should I even go about making our relationship into something special?
Why are you asking me?
I mean, you seem like someone
who has gone through countless extraordinary relationships.
Well, you're...
not wrong.
I knew it!
Actually, the main problem is that she doesn't see me as a man.
For example, when I pinned her down the other day,
she merely looked at me blankly.
Wait, what? You pinned her down?
I went overboard and I regret my actions.
I have no idea how to make her view me as a potential love interest!
Do you have your personal written guide?
No.
Like a spring in full bloom, pure and wholesome! It's Hanazuma Ran: Pâtissier Version!
Today, I'll teach you how to make delicious chiffon cakes.
[CHIFFON CAKE]
You even went through the trouble of making this?
Sorry for requesting this out of nowhere, preparing all these must've been a lot of trouble.
Not at all.
In fact, I got way too excited because I was so happy that you were willing to rely on me.
Hanazuma...!
No, right now, I should be calling you "chef".
In that case, I think what you need is
tactics, probably.
Tactics?
You need to constantly watch the other party and...advance,
or back off.
She looked over!
But that's not good enough.
You have to wait till she's completely wrapped around your finger,
making an expression that shows she wants you so bad
that she can't stand it anymore, then it's time to...
dive right in.
Something like that, I guess.
Anyway, if making advances all this time has been futile,
why not try backing off a little?
That's an unexpectedly straightforward advice.
Alright...whip it to this consistency and it should be good.
Now, just pour it into the mold and bake. Simple, right?
Simple...? I'm not sure about that.
It must be hard on you,
having to bake a cake for your housemate's family when you're just sharing an apartment.
I know, right?
Our whole family loves sweet food.
We love eating them, and also
making them.
My housemate is dearly doted on by his brother.
He's like a very sheltered boy.
But what happens if one of you gets a boyfriend or girlfriend?
Huh?
It happens all the time!
Two friends share an apartment,
then one of them gets attached and the housing arrangement falls apart.
Something like that.
You need come to a consensus and lay out the ground rules.
You're right.
I'm home.
Two friends share an apartment, then one of them gets attached and the housing arrangement falls apart.
Something like that.
No way. Yamamoto doesn't even have anyone he likes.
But there's a chance he does?
I'm home!
Welcome back.
Did you go drinking with someone?
Yeah, actually--
I-
I can drink with whoever I want.
Yeah, you can.
Oh, by the way,
there's something I think we should discuss--
I'm exhausted.
Okay.
Is this what it means to back off?
Ugh...I don't know if I'm doing it right, Koga!
Good morning.
[I'LL GO FIRST.]
It's time to back off, it's time to back off, it's time to back off...
It's time to--
How do you do, Yamamoto.
Why can't you just say, "Good morning"?
Come over here for a bit.
Huh? Wha--
Did I mess up again...?
Come on, out with it.
How can I possibly tell you?
I want to know how you truly feel.
What should we do, moving forward?
Well...
Hayami?
I-I'm sorry. I didn't mean to watch.
- She's my--
- I'm Akamine Reina.
I'm from HR.
Yamamoto and I joined the company at the same time.
I see.
Hayami, just now--
Oh, no! I just remembered, I have out-of-office business this morning.
And so, um, I'll get going. If you'll excuse me.
Yamamoto.
We'll continue where we left off, later tonight. Will you tell me all about it?
What?
Hey.
Come on, out with it.
How do you feel about me?
I love you.
I guess that's
what I saw this morning.
[YAMAMOTO: I'LL BE GOING DRINKING WITH AKAMINE TONIGHT.]
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Did you make the reservation?
Yes, I did. But don't just send me the URL for it next time.
Oh? I thought sending you the link was already a pain.
You could've done it yourself.
Do you know of any good restaurants, then?
Of course not.
Knock, knock.
Are we doing it today as well? Baking practice?
Wow! You did it!
But...you helped me out for half the steps.
But with this, your housemate's family will approve of you!
Did something happen?
You know, when we talked about having a lover the other time?
Actually, I think my housemate might be in love.
Then what about the apartment sharing?
Right now, it's just my guess.
You can't confirm it?
I tried, but he seems to be avoiding me.
That's mean.
Either way, we can't share an apartment if I don't get through this tea party.
All I can do now is work hard on this.
This reminds me, how much was it?
How much?
How much did all the ingredients and stuff cost?
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
Let's see...
[SPECIALTY SUGAR COOKIES STORE]
[SUGAR COOKIES SET A - 8,100 YEN]
[SUGAR COOKIES SET B - 8,400 YEN]
Sugar cookies?
I've been thinking of trying to bake some.
Woah, they're really well done for a first try.
I-It's not what you think!
I do enjoy baking.
But, that day, the ones I made didn't turn out cute at all.
I felt kind of emba--
I felt bad about it.
You shouldn't let that bother you.
But...
I'd hate for people to think that's all I can do.
Hanazuma.
I get it.
Actually, in the first year I joined,
a senior asked me to make one of my specialties and bring it to the flower viewing.
I could've turned them down, but I decided to be stubborn for some reason.
In the end, I just repacked a few side dishes I bought from the deli of a department store.
From then on, I was seen as the "perfect bride", and here we are today.
I didn't know about that.
I'm also the type who will give my all in order to not disappoint the people around me.
So I completely understand how you feel.
You know,
seeming like that's all you can do is important too.
Or perhaps I should say,
letting others see your failures is important.
If you can reveal your weaknesses to even just one person,
it'll make life a lot easier.
I think, the always cheerful version of you aside,
showing your frustration has an edge to it too.
With that said...um, sorry for sounding like a know-it-all.
Alright, let's eat!
As I've said, hurry up and tell me what you think already.
As I've said, I can't possibly tell someone from HR what I really think about the company!
But my superior told me to collect responses of what our young employees truly think.
I promise this won't affect your performance appraisal.
As if I'd take your word for it.
Besides,
aren't there are tons of other young employees?
Does it even matter?
What's with you? Do you want to go home and see her so badly?
Not really, since I'm backing off right now.
Backing off? What do you mean?
Yamamoto, are you using love tactics?
Yes, that's what I'm doing!
But it's not working out anyway, is it?
That's not true.
With this, I'll make sure
she returns my feelings.
In that case, we can keep at this, right?
Excuse me!
We'll have two highballs.
Don't just order more!
"Sorry, I'm having a terrible hangover.
This will be all for breakfast."
Is this a gorilla's breakfast?
I had too many drinks!
[THANKS FOR BREAKFAST. HOPE YOU FEEL BETTER SOON.]
What's this?
My tactic is working?
Or is it not?
I don't know anymore!
- Um--
- Hayami!
Shall we...do this today too?
Oh, right.
Next is...
the meringue.
[YAMAMOTO: SORRY, I'LL BE HOME LATE AGAIN TODAY.]
Today too?
[GOT IT! I'VE GOT SOMETHING ON AS WELL SO IT'S OKAY!]
Welcome back. Did you go drinking with someone?
I can drink with whoever I want.
But what happens if one of you gets a boyfriend or girlfriend?
- She's my--
- I'm Akamine Reina.
Yamamoto and I joined the company at the same time.
You're not a suitable candidate for cohabiting with Chihiro.
I disapprove of your cohabitation!
I want to know how you truly feel.
What should we do, moving forward?
Well...
[MASAMI]
What's up?
I made the perfect sweet red bean paste this year too.
Huh? What are you talking about?
What? Hayami didn't tell you?
Again?
Seems like I'm hopeless.
Hayami!
Welcome home. You're back earlier than expected.
Um, this is...
Why did you hide it from me?
The fact that my brother invited you to a tea party, and more importantly, the fact that he's against our cohabitation!
Sorry.
I wanted to prove that I can at least bake a cake on my own without your help.
Is that why you've been staying behind with Hanazuma?
Gosh...
If that's the case, you should have said so!
My tactics were totally meaningless!
Tactics?
Um, anyway! You don't have to do all this, because I'll convince my brother somehow.
It's fine, you don't have to convince him.
What?
It's just...I agree with what your brother said.
I can't even bake a cake on my own, and yet I want to live together with you.
That's probably too presumptuous of me.
After all this time, what are you saying now?
- Who cares about th--
- Also,
Yamamoto.
There's someone you like, right?
What?
Recently, you've been distancing yourself and coming home late.
- That's because--
- If it gets inconvenient for you to continue being my "wife",
it's perfectly fine, you can just let me know.
I think it would be a good reason for dissolving this cohabitation arrangement.
Are you stupid?!
What?
I mean,
it's true that there's someone that I like.
- I knew it! Then all the more--
- But that's...
That's...
That's different from being a "wife".
In other words,
even though there's someone that I like, she's just someone that I like.
Since we're nowhere near having mutual feelings for each other, I can't afford to miss out on living as a "wife"
all because of that.
Anyway, I'm not about to
give up on being your "wife" so easily.
As the pillar of the house, please take a firm stance on this!
Okay.
That settles it.
Now, let's figure out what to do with these.
They aren't fluffy at all. I put in so much effort to make the meringue foamy too.
That's probably because the meringue is over-beaten.
Really?
Over whipping the meringue will dry it out instead, and the cake wouldn't be fluffy.
That's how it works?
Sorry for wasting food.
Don't worry, I won't let it go to waste.
In the first place,
there's absolutely no way you can win my brother over
with just a single cake.
After all, my second brother, Kaoru, is a pâtissier.
Oh, really?
Does that mean he tasked me with the impossible right from the start?
Sorry about that.
When it comes to me, my brother gets triggered and will suddenly turn into a toxic mother-in-law.
I see.
But it's okay.
Refusing to give up is your strong point, isn't it?
[YAMAMOTO]
Hayami, are you ready?
Yes.
Wow.
Look, Chihiro.
It's your favourite choux à la crème.
[Yamamoto Kaoru, Chihiro's Second Brother]
Say, "Ahh."
You mean a cream puff? I can eat it myself.
You've never met him before, right?
- He's my second br--
- Hello Honoka, I'm Kaoru.
Nice. To. Meet. You.
- Nice to meet you too.
- Please don't get too familiar with her.
He's totally in his mother-in-law mode.
Is that how he should act when he did all the cleaning himself?
So?
Hayami, what have you brought?
It's here.
I tried to bake a chiffon cake.
Oh, deary me.
I'm sorry.
This was the best I could do.
Is that so?
I regret to inform you, but I do not approve of your cohabitation.
Having to live with someone who can't even bake a cake satisfactorily
will only be a burden to Chihiro.
Please, hold on.
I wasn't able to bake a cake,
but I would like to prove that I'm a suitable candidate for cohabiting with him using another method.
- Another method?
- Yes.
[LIVING WITH YAMAMOTO CHIHIRO]
Now,
I will be presenting to you, what is the value of me living together with Yamamoto, from his viewpoint.
A presentation?
I see, so that's your plan.
Firstly,
you're assuming that there are no advantages for Yamamoto to live with someone who's bad at housework.
Rather than a give and take, he only "gives".
That's what you're worried about, isn't it?
- Exactly.
- With regards to that,
I'm paying for all the living expenses, so he "takes" in this aspect.
That's news to us. Isn't it, Masami?
But if we're talking about living expenses, he can just stay with us. It's the same thing.
As compared to staying with us, what are the advantages for him to stay with you?
That will be...
the fact that he will become a "God of Sales" from living with me.
[GOD OF SALES]
"God of Sales"?
People who can do everything themselves are unable to see through the eyes of someone who is bad at housework.
For example, the convenience of household appliances. As someone working in the sales department of its manufacturer,
wouldn't that be a critical weakness?
To resolve this issue, if he lives with someone who is hopeless at doing housework,
he'll be able to open his eyes to new perspectives.
Failures may give rise to other things as well.
For example, take a look at this.
What's this?
Yamamoto turned my failed chiffon cake into cake rusk.
Slice the failed chiffon cake thinly.
Sprinkle on granulated sugar, then place in the oven and bake.
It becomes cake rusk!
What I'm trying to say is,
my cohabitation with Yamamoto is a sharing of knowledge,
it brings about an effective synergy,
so ultimately, it's a win-win situation.
Knowledge, synergy, and win-win...
Fantastic!
Kaoru, don't be fooled by those English terms!
On top of that, these are delicious. Masami, try some too.
- I don't--
- Here, say "Ahh."
Well, it's delicious.
But will Chihiro really be okay without me?
That child tends to push himself too hard all the time. Without me there to watch over him--
- Don't worry, Mother.
- What?
- No, I mean, Masami.
- Yes?
I care for your brother as much as both of you do.
No matter what happens, I will protect him.
Hayami...
Alright, then. However...
Let me set this straight.
If you hurt my precious brother,
I will never forgive you.
Masami, what you saying?
You don't have to worry about that either.
Please, look at this.
[WRITTEN OATH]
- What's this?
- A written oath?
That's right.
During our cohabitation,
I solemnly swear to not lay a finger on your precious brother.
[I WILL NOT LAY A FINGER ON HIM.]
I see.
That's how far you're willing to go.
Hayami.
I leave Chihiro in your hands.
Thank you for trusting me.
Chihiro, isn't that great?
No...
It's not.
It's great,
but it's not.
I see how it is...
I'm glad we managed to pull it off.
Well...
I guess.
They even gave us sweets and stuff to bring back.
Your brothers may have strong personalities, but they're nice people.
Their strong personalities are the problem.
I'm being serious,
but the person who gets with you will be really blessed.
Why are you saying that?
I'm talking about...the person you like.
I'll give you my fullest support.
Which reminds me, I wanted to set some ground rules.
Previously, you mentioned that living as a "wife" is important to you.
But let's say,
one day, your feelings become mutual.
What shall we do with this cohabitation arrangement?
Mutual feelings, huh?
Making an agreement like this is important when sharing an apartment, you know?
Don't worry about it.
Right now, there's no chance of it happening at all.
What? No way, you give up too easily.
I'm sure the other party will fall in love with you if they knew of your strengths.
That's what you think.
I guess...
If a miracle happens
and our feelings become mutual,
I won't be able to continue being a "wife", as you'd expect.
Ah, you're right. Of course.
You'd want to be together with the person you truly like.
Wait.
What was that reaction?
Huh?
Could it be that
you'll feel lonely?
N-No, no! That's not...
the case, is it?
Sorry, I'm confused about my own feelings.
Hayami.
Can we hold hands?
Where did this come from?
You won't lose sight of-- I mean, I know my way back.
Besides, I promised your brother I wouldn't lay a finger on y--
That means you can't lay a finger on me, but it's fine if I'm the one initiating it.
Um...
I've decided
to stop backing off after all.
Um, Yamamoto?
Maybe we should try out to see how compatible we are.
Do you want to try it out?
Even if it's just a trial, I'm going all out.
Don't try to escape.