[OVERDO]
[Episode 5]
[Murong Residence]
Qingyu.
Rest assured, Qingyu.
When the aviation school opens,
whether my father shows up or not,
I will be there.
Thank you.
If it puts you in a bind...
"Bear family burdens without complaint;
transcend self-interest in the clan."
You taught me this since I was little.
Have you forgotten?
Ali.
What's the deal tonight?
It's so secretive.
We couldn't even drive in.
Young Master,
please head in
and see for yourself.
Interesting.
Even Boze is out of the loop.
Today's banquet
was arranged by Mulan.
She decorated the courtyard.
Then I'll be sure to take a good look.
Do you recognize him?
Your Young Master Huo.
My master's hosting this banquet
just to let you catch up with him.
I left the Huo household a long time ago.
I've been honestly looking for work
to make a living.
Why must your master do this...
You did so many dirty deeds for the Huos.
Do you think your hands are clean
just after 2 years as a lawful citizen?
Don't worry.
For your sins,
the victims will naturally come for you.
My master isn't that nosy.
He's just giving you a choice.
You're over 50 now, and still
running around looking for work.
It must be tough.
Later at the banquet, you just need to
identify the murderer for my master.
Then, for the rest of your life,
you'll be well provided for.
Didn't they say cars aren't allowed in?
Laiyi.
Young Master Qingyu.
Who is this?
You are...
Hello, Young Master Zongqi.
I'm Li Cai, the butler
of Yu Estate in Beicheng.
He's here.
What about the Huos?
He recognized Huo Zongqi at the door.
I haven't mentioned Miss Fang to him.
Okay.
Let's leave a surprise for the Huos.
If that butler really
recognizes Miss Fang,
the Huos will probably kill her.
Have you thought it through?
Help me tie my apron.
Coming.
♪ Fantasies reduced to ash ♪
Hold still.
♪ In a raging fire ♪
Keep staring,
♪ Those caught in the wake ♪
and I'll gouge your eyes out.
♪ Now tell only gray lies ♪
♪ Willingly ♪
♪ Surrendering the naive visage ♪
Butler Li is waiting outside.
♪ Of the past ♪
Still want to run?
♪ With no expectation of dawn ♪
Making such a big fuss
and returning with a new identity,
you must have an ulterior motive.
♪ Wandering beneath a pitch-black sky ♪
♪ I smell no sorrow ♪
Since you have a motive,
you must have helpers.
Do you think I'm that stupid
♪ Let the story start over ♪
to not have a backup plan?
♪ With a new beginning ♪
♪ When our paths cross again ♪
The banquet hasn't even started.
♪ I shift my gaze away ♪
How much have you had to drink?
You're already blabbering nonsense.
♪ Only then can I ♪
♪ Rid all hope ♪
♪ No longer able to break free ♪
Death is at your door,
yet you still won't own up.
♪ From the shackles of destiny ♪
♪ No more questioning ♪
♪ The cruel jests of fate ♪
♪ Now I know to appreciate ♪
Fine.
Since you won't own up,
♪ The calm as it shatters ♪
let the people from Yu Estate see
♪ No longer craving ♪
who really killed Huo Mingxi
back then!
♪ Absolution from the heavens ♪
♪ No innocent yesterdays ♪
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
♪ My intuition is my only faith ♪
♪ Pull out all the stops to deliver ♪
♪ A show-stopper ♪
Let go of me!
Let go!
Jinrui.
Boze, you're here!
Come, come.
Come over.
A new dress?
That's right.
Don't I look pretty?
Very pretty.
You look 10 years younger.
I thought you were a movie star.
Oh, please.
Naughty.
Come on. Let's go
take a look over there.
Sure.
I never imagined the Murong residence
to have an area that
exudes such Nanyang charm.
Your soon-to-be brother-in-law
really is hard to read.
I've never gotten involved
in business in Beicheng.
This Butler Li was
a servant
to my wrongfully deceased uncle.
He just looks familiar.
I don't understand
why Qingyi invited him.
Qingyu,
know anything about this?
Qingyi has always
been unpredictable.
But don't worry.
He knows where to draw the line.
He sure does know where to draw the line.
Qingyi said he wants
to give the Huos a surprise.
Could it be related to
that case from 3 years ago?
It's rare for us to gather
for Qingyu's happy occasion.
Heaven forbid things get ugly.
Don't worry.
I believe in Qingyi.
I have something to do.
Excuse me.
You're about to be exposed.
Are you excited?
Do you want to be taken away by the Huos
and die from their
unspeakable, disgusting methods...
or should I
mercifully
send you on your way?
Say something!
Since you think I must die,
I have a gift for you
in the drawer
in my room.
Stay right here.
Fang Mulan!
Come here!
That lady
looks familiar.
In the Huos' place in Beicheng...
That is a gift exclusively for you.
If I must die today,
I hope it will
always accompany you.
I hope it accounts for
those 3 years.
I have just one question for you:
Right now...
in this second,
you do like me...
don't you?
She clearly...
remembers everything.
Oh no!
Miss Fang fell into the water!
Somebody help!
Help!
Can anybody swim?
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Take away everything I have ♪
♪ Can you bear the weight of it all? ♪
♪ I offer you my whole life ♪
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
Miss Fang caught a cold
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
and has a slight fever.
She just slipped.
Don't worry. She's fine.
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
Nothing to see here.
♪ Let the tears fall,
let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
♪ Neither you nor I ♪
You can't escape this time,
♪ Can ever break free ♪
Ren Susu.
How are you?
Feeling better?
Need me to get a doctor?
No need.
I feel much better.
I'll be leaving then.
Get some rest.
It's an emergency.
Might be an internal injury.
Okay.
I'll come to you as soon as possible...
Trying to run after being exposed?
Contacting your accomplice, huh?
Go ahead.
He's a famous doctor in the concession,
specializing in orthopedic rehabilitation.
I was inviting him to
take a look at your hand.
It doesn't matter.
My hand can't hold a scalpel anymore,
but it's still very steady with a gun.
Who did it?
The Huos.
They think Huo Mingxi's death
was orchestrated by me.
So they hired someone to sever
my hand tendons in prison.
If the doctors in the concession
can't fix it,
I'll find one for you in Nanyang.
I don't need your concern.
I'm a surgeon.
You think I can't tell if my hand
can be fixed or not?
Qingyi.
Be it the past
or the present...
I've never thought of hurting you.
Cover up.
Why are you crying?
Didn't you tell me
you were only ever using me?
Even if I'm disabled,
what does it have to do with you?
Whether I cry or not,
Forget it.
If you truly feel guilty towards me,
then don't bring this up again.
You still have
that gentian flower.
You lost it,
and I found it.
I didn't.
On the train then...
You clearly remember everything.
You frown too much now.
You didn't before.
Anyone locked up in prison for 3 years
would forget their past self.
I'm sorry.
Ren Susu,
is a word of "sorry"
the only thing you owe me?
I detest your innocent act
when you're full of schemes.
If you really cared about me,
how could you bear to
fake your death in front of me
3 years ago?
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
If you want me to pay with my life,
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
you can do it now.
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
You're such a good actor.
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
You really think I won't do it?
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
♪ Let the tears fall,
let the blood spill ♪
You're always like this,
being soft-hearted at the critical moment.
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
That's why you always lose.
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
What do you plan to do about Butler Li?
Let me warn you, Ren Susu.
Behave and stay by my side.
No more tricks and crazy ideas.
It's your turn to experience
what it's like to be manipulated.
Otherwise,
Butler Li can
pay a visit to the Huos at any time.
[Huo Residence]
Butler Li?
Did you say Butler Li appeared
at the Murong residence?
Yes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You bet it's real.
What's Murong Qingyi up to again?
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You chose not to attend
the Murong banquet.
Now you blame me?
Butler Li's sudden appearance
at the Murong residence
must be related to my father's death.
You should've grabbed Murong Qingyi
and interrogated him thoroughly.
Such a pretty face...
but such a stupid brain.
Huo Minxian, keep in mind that
you're just a loser
from a collateral branch of the Huos.
You have no right to yell at me.
If you have the guts,
kill me.
You can go marry Murong Qingyi instead.
Do you still think your life
belongs to you?
Believe it or not,
I'll kill myself right in front of you.
Go on. Do it.
I'll make sure to
take good care of your mother.
Then at least tell me
where
Butler Li is.
[Taixing Hotel]
Gentlemen,
please help me out.
Young Master Qingyi
didn't need me last night.
I suppose I can't be of any help.
Could you relay a message to him for me?
Tell him I'm needed at home
and to let me go back to Feng'an.
Butler Li.
Young Miss Minxian?
Why are you in Nancheng?
Did you go back to the main house?
Miss Huo.
Stopping me?
I'm your master's fiancée.
Are you tired of living?
Did Murong Qingyi ask you
to come to Nancheng?
What did he ask you to do?
He told me to identify someone.
It seems to be related to
what happened 3 years ago.
Did you identify the person?
Last night at the banquet,
in the Murong residence,
I did find a woman
familiar.
Unfortunately,
I didn't see her whole face.
If you saw her again,
would you recognize her?
Come with me.
Miss Huo.
No one can take him away
without Young Master Qingyi's order.
I don't care.
Let's see who dares to stop me.
Notify Young Master Qingyi now.
He went out of town for ancestral rites.
[Spirit tablet of
the late respected father, Murong Feng]
Do you know how hard it is
for me to be
the pillar of the family alone
with you gone?
Fortunately, Qingyu is excellent.
The Murong family will
get stronger and stronger
in my and Qingyu's hands.
You can rest assured on the other side.
Just wait for me to join you.
Mother,
why isn't Boze here?
He was just promoted to inspector.
He's under close public scrutiny.
Letting a descendant of
Ying Army members
come to the Murong ancestral hall to
pay respects to Cheng Army members
would raise eyebrows.
Mother, you're really thoughtful
of your dear son.
Mother,
we should let Father know
about Mulan and me too.
It's no hurry.
Miss Fang,
I'm afraid you don't know
the background of our Murong family.
Jinrui,
as the eldest sister,
tell Miss Fang
about our origins.
Yes, Mother.
Enshrined here are
the spirit tablets
of the Murong family.
[Spirit tablet of
the late respected father, Murong Feng]
Our ancestors migrated to Songjiang
at the end of the Yuan dynasty.
With a history
spanning several centuries...
Miss Huo,
why are you here?
Qingyi asked me to come.
Go in and look carefully.
If you see anyone suspicious,
point them out loudly.
Young Miss, aren't you
making things difficult for me?
Everyone here, inside and out,
is from the Murong household.
Once you're sure,
go back to the main house
to report it.
Let the Old Master
punish the Murongs for their sins.
Yes.
Compared to some upstarts outside,
our "meritage" is naturally exceptional.
What an illiterate.
Mind you, it's "heritage."
Your brain must
only be good for
covering up for murderers.
Did you just make fun of me?
Miss Huo, you came uninvited.
What is this about?
Forgive me, Auntie.
I was baffled when I heard
that Qingyi is observing
the ancestral rites,
so I came to see the fun.
Since when is
a man who killed his father-in-law
qualified to
play the role of filial piety and loyalty?
Have you lost your mind?
Qingyi
brought my butler
from Feng'an to Nancheng
to identify someone.
Who was identified?
Don't you need to tell me?
What butler?
Why haven't I heard you mention it?
Mother is asking you a question!
-What are you doing behind our backs again?
-Murong Qingyi.
I now suspect that
you're shielding your accomplice
who killed my father.
If you know what's good for you,
hand the person over.
Where's your proof?
Miss Huo,
if you really can't bear
to part with your paramour,
just call off the engagement.
Oh, I forgot.
Your paramour hasn't contacted you
since the theater incident, has he?
I understand that you're upset,
but this is the Murong ancestral hall.
Isn't it ridiculous
for you to make a scene here?
Don't change the subject.
I do like him.
So what?
Who do you think you are?
They say you belong to two families,
but really,
you're just a loser
that neither family wants.
A dog unwanted by the Li family
scampered to the Murong family's door
to beg for food,
and now he's their second young master?
You killed my father,
yet you expect me to marry you?
On what grounds?
On the grounds that you're a shameless,
ignorant, and scheming
murderer
who was abandoned by his parents?
How dare you hit me?
Disrespecting
the ancestors and elders,
insulting your fiancé,
and spreading rumors—
are these the manners
your family taught you?
Who are you to chime in?
In terms of seniority,
I'm your elder sister-in-law.
In terms of status,
I'm the daughter
of the Fang family in Nanyang.
It's not a matter of
if I dare to hit you,
but if I want to.
Butler Li already recognized you.
Aren't you afraid?
With me here,
don't be afraid.
With you here,
I'm not afraid either.
Miss Huo,
regarding your father's matter,
our two families already
reached a settlement 3 years ago.
Qingyi has paid the price
for his immaturity, too.
Today,
you came to the Murong ancestral hall
and insulted members of my Murong family.
If the Huo patriarch sent you,
then I'll consider it
an act of hostility
towards my Murong family.
Otherwise,
you slandered my brother...
I have a witness!
Butler Li can prove who the murderer is!
You finally remembered him.
Where is he?
Murong Qingyi,
what did you do to Butler Li?
Butler Li?
Did any of you see Butler Li?
-No.
No.
You...
Are you all blind?
How can you allow this murderer
to publicly take a witness hostage?
When your father was alive,
at least several dozen,
if not a hundred, people
disappeared at his hands.
Miss Huo, have you forgotten?
So annoying.
How do you want to disappear?
I'll help you.
Qingyi.
Enough.
Get lost.
You unfilial son.
Kneel!
Qingyi.
You unfilial son.
I don't care about
what and how many shady things
you do outside.
But bringing those
filthy and sketchy things
into the ancestral hall?
Unfilial!
Your incompetence
giving others leverage is unwise!
Resorting to threats
to chase Huo Minxian away
invalidates your stance,
be it justified or not!
How did I give birth to
such a bastard?
Everyone walks alone in life.
Don't let others
drain your energy.
I don't deserve...
anything good, either.
Qingyu, you're noble and upright,
and Sister-in-Law, you're considerate,
unlike me,
who crawled out of the gutter.
A vicious woman like Huo Minxian
is my perfect match.
Even Huo Minxian knows that you
can't expect a son,
whom you birthed
but didn't raise,
to turn out perfect.
Get your head out of the clouds.
You...
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate ♪
♪ Till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down ♪
♪ Hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ Come what may, we will be ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate ♪
♪ Till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down ♪
♪ Hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ Come what may, we will be ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
♪ Take away everything I have ♪
♪ Can you bear the weight of it all? ♪
♪ I offer you my whole life ♪
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
♪ Let the tears fall ♪
♪ Let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ I can't break free ♪
♪ I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
♪ We remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
♪ Neither you nor I ♪
♪ Can ever break free ♪