[OVERDO]
[Episode 3]
[Three years ago, Nancheng]
Susu.
I've got news.
My senior heard about this
while performing
for the Huo family.
Lan is in a place called Yu Estate
in Beicheng.
That is the base camp
of the Huo family in Beicheng.
It's heavily guarded.
You must be careful on your journey.
You just need to find out
Lan's whereabouts.
Don't act rashly.
I'll join you shortly after.
[To Qing]
[Huo Family's Branch Residence, Yu Estate]
Thank you for treating my master.
I heard that Young Master Qingyu
has been promoted again.
My master
acquired a few century-old ginseng roots.
Please bring them to Young Master Qingyu
to express our gratitude.
Please keep this gift.
Brother asked me to come here.
I'm usually in Beicheng.
You should send these gifts
directly to my brother.
[Li Cai, butler of Yu Estate]
I'll prepare a car for you
and send you back to the clinic.
Hold on.
Okay.
If you jump from that height,
the probability of fracture
is about 70 percent.
If you fall,
you're most likely to fracture
the fibula and tibia of your two legs,
the ulna of the left arm,
and the finger bones
and hamate bones in the palm.
Mind your own business,
or you'll get in trouble.
Fine.
I'm leaving.
Whether you jump down or stay there
is up to you.
You're really a good doctor.
How did she know I was a doctor?
Could it be...
Slowly does it.
Are you okay?
♪ I forgot when it started ♪
♪ You're always behind me ♪
♪ Silently accompanying me ♪
Is...
♪ My heart belongs only to you ♪
Is that you?
♪ Am I out of my mind? ♪
♪ It's too late to turn back ♪
We
♪ I'll be lonely without you ♪
exchanged letters.
It's me.
Duhuo.
Do you remember me?
♪ Our hearts are close ♪
♪ But our distance is widening ♪
♪ While silently waiting for your reply ♪
♪ I've been answering my own questions ♪
I'm sorry.
Maybe I mistook you for someone else.
♪ I constantly confess ♪
♪ The bitterness in my heart ♪
Do you want to make a bet with me?
♪ As long as you live happily ♪
Guess
♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪
♪ I miss your hug ♪
which bone I broke.
♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪
♪ I miss the corners of your lips ♪
♪ I miss every second of you ♪
If you're right,
I'll write you a reply.
♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪
♪ I miss your hug ♪
♪ I miss the corners of your lips ♪
♪ I miss you, I miss you ♪
Since the beginning of winter,
♪ I miss every second of you ♪
Beicheng had experienced many snowfalls.
But to me,
♪ Our hearts are close ♪
♪ But our distance is widening ♪
this was the first snow of this year.
♪ While silently waiting for your reply ♪
♪ I frantically hide the fear
in my heart ♪
♪ I can't confess ♪
♪ The bitterness in my heart ♪
♪ As long as you live happily ♪
♪ I can't help falling ♪
♪ It's a sudden whirlpool ♪
♪ You don't know I've been here ♪
♪ Waiting ♪
Done.
Thank you.
You...
How did you recognize me?
Your mole is very special.
The chirping grasshoppers
spring about in lively leaps.
I've not seen you in a while.
It worries me so.
Since you wanted to see me too,
why didn't you reply?
And why are you
here in Beicheng?
I came to Beicheng
for an important task.
I had no time to seek you.
I can help you.
I want a ribbon.
Okay.
I understood it.
Since she didn't want to elaborate,
I did not ask further.
Thank you for helping me.
Let me treat you to dinner.
Just this?
Of course, we have to eat
roasted sweet potatoes in winter.
Try it.
It's very sweet.
Here.
Your house is quite similar to mine.
My family used to grow
many gentian flowers.
It would be great
if you could plant some in your yard.
When they bloom,
I'll treat you to the great view.
I plant the flowers,
and you treat me to the view?
How generous of you.
Gentian flowers only grow on the plateau.
My mother spent a lot of effort
growing them in Nancheng.
Isn't it enough
for me to teach you to grow them?
Fine.
It's very kind of you.
In your past letters,
you said you wanted to learn dancing.
In return,
you teach me how to grow flowers,
and I'll teach you to dance the tango.
After half a year of exchanging letters,
I finally met her in person today.
Truly, some remain strangers for life,
while others feel like
old friends at first sight.
[Two months later]
I have an operation tonight.
When I come back,
I'll change your dressing again.
I've recovered.
When the snow stops,
I'll be on my way.
But we still
have one dance left to do.
You're leaving already?
Thanks for treating my injury.
Treating you
is my duty as a doctor.
Whether you go or not
is your choice.
That was not what I really wanted to say.
But who was I
to ask her to stay?
Take care.
Have you heard?
The whole of Beicheng
is going to have a blackout tonight.
They said a fight broke out
at the Beicheng Power Supply Plant.
What a time of unrest and uncertainty.
Why is there a blackout?
All that's left is to stitch it up.
But we can't see anything clearly.
Go and have a look.
Dr. Murong.
We're here.
We heard you have surgery today.
We were afraid
the blackout would hinder things.
You often treated our illnesses.
Now's our time to repay you.
-We’re here to help you.
-How did you know I had surgery?
Miss Ren knocked on every door
and asked us to help you.
-Yes.
Miss Ren asked us to come.
We're all here.
Thank you.
I'll finish the surgery first.
Susu!
I'm sorry.
The power is back on.
The lights are back on.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
I left food heating on the stove.
Susu!
Did the surgery go well?
The surgery went very well today.
It's all thanks to you.
The people you sent all brought candles.
When the candlelight
lit up the operating table,
it felt like
you were telling me that
being a good doctor was worth it.
By the way,
here.
Gentian flower?
Yes.
I had a friend help me
search the highlands for a long time
before finally finding this one.
I wanted to give it to you during the day.
But this morning,
I was upset
that you were leaving.
I thought,
if you really left,
I wouldn't stop you.
I'd simply
throw this plant away.
If you don't want it,
I'll take it with me.
Susu!
We haven't known each other for long.
A person like me...
Doesn't deserve anything good anyway.
I also know that
there is nothing
we have to keep
in this world.
But this time,
I'd like to try.
I'm sorry.
I have something I must do.
So...
I know you have things you want to do.
If you don't want to tell me,
I won't ask.
But before that,
can you spare me
even a second of your time?
Just like me for a second.
Once the snow stops,
I should be on my way.
♪ Running toward you ♪
♪ From the day I thought ♪
♪ I succeeded in forgetting you ♪
♪ Facing the past ♪
♪ with you inside ♪
♪ My resolve crumbles ♪
♪ Immediately ♪
♪ I'm running ♪
♪ Running toward you ♪
♪ No matter how much gossip there is ♪
♪ I have the courage ♪
♪ I know you're not far away ♪
♪ Having loved you deeply ♪
♪ was the best decision I've made ♪
Murong Qingyi,
forgive me
for meeting you again in this way.
But there's something I must do.
No one can stop me.
Ren Susu.
Stop hiding.
I miss you so much.
I think of you day and night.
I want to skin you
and break your bones.
Let go of me!
Your favourite gentian flower.
Do you still remember it?
What gentian flower?
I've never seen it before.
It's been 3 years.
You came back from the dead
just to set your sights on my brother?
♪ This spark of wildfire
spreading across the plains ♪
♪ Stirs embers that refuse to fade ♪
♪ I seize fate by the hand ♪
♪ Accusing it of refusing to relent ♪
♪ Pain and joy blur before my eyes ♪
I remember that
♪ Fate keeps replaying its endless cycle ♪
our first kiss
♪ The love that refused to die ♪
tasted exactly like this.
♪ Has already consumed us both ♪
About what happened today,
I'll take it as your drunk mistake.
Do you think you can get away with it?
Ren Susu, listen.
I'll make you reveal your true identity
in front of everyone
and pay the price.
Young Master Qingyi.
Why are you visiting
the gentian flower field
in the middle of the night?
We'll take our time
investigating Miss Ren's matter.
You mustn't let your emotions
get the better of you.
Ren Susu.
Were you just using me back then?
Did you fake your death
just to get rid of me?
Exactly what happened
3 years ago?
Susu.
My family's friend, the Huo family,
is holding a banquet in Beicheng.
My brother asked me to attend it
in his stead.
Come with me.
Don't like such occasions?
Is Master Huo
their master?
Yes.
Does he usually
live here?
Yeah.
Yu Estate
is the base of the Huo Family
Chamber of Commerce in Beicheng.
It can be considered
Huo Mingxi's private estate.
Go ahead and do your thing.
I want to take a walk in the garden.
Okay.
I'll pick you up in the garden later.
We'll go home together.
Master Huo is dead! Help!
Huo Mingxi?
What happened?
Where is Susu?
You brought that woman
into the Yu Estate, didn't you?
Now she has disappeared,
and you were at the crime scene.
What else do you have to say?
I didn't kill him.
Then why did you run away?
Are you guilty?
I just want to find her.
Murong Qingyi.
I'll give you 3 days.
You have something to do
with that woman anyway.
If you can't find her,
you're doomed.
Susu!
[Closed Today]
[Pharmacy]
[You]
I've asked the Art Academy of Nancheng.
There has never been
a student named Ren Susu there.
We've searched
both the east and west districts.
No trace of Miss Ren.
Dr. Murong.
The Huo family has insisted that
Huo Mingxi's death is related to you.
You should...
Do I need you to teach me what to do?
Keep looking.
Find her
no matter what it takes.
-Yes.
[Jiujiekou Street, East District,
Beicheng]
[To: Mr. Duhuo, No. 27 Liuli Hutong]
Young Master Qingyi.
We have news about Miss Ren.
Susu!
I finally found you.
Susu.
Hurry!
Get out of here.
Susu.
On the day you left,
the flowers bloomed.
Didn't you tell me
you would treat me to the view?
Since we first met,
I've wanted to sneak into the Huo family.
Later, I knew you were close
with the Huo family,
so I took advantage of you.
Don't you get it?
Why?
Search every carriage carefully.
Only these carriages are left.
She must be in here.
Get lost!
Don't you understand?
I approached you
only to use you.
Did you think
I really liked you?
You lied to me.
Fine.
I told you,
I'd have helped you
with whatever you wanted to do.
I only have 1 question right now.
Right now,
in this second,
you do like me,
right?
Susu.
What are you doing?
Just pretend that
you've never known me.
I found her!
That woman is here!
Susu!
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
♪ The more icy ♪
♪ Our present clash ♪
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
Ren Susu.
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
Three years ago,
I saw you die with my own eyes.
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
But you came back.
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
Since you're not dead,
♪ Together, we fall ♪
I don't need to keep this anymore.
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
[This footage is a visual effect
and not a real shot]
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
Young Master,
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
this field of flowers took you
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
so much time, energy,
and efforts.
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
It's such a pity to have it
all burn away.
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
These flowers
♪ We ♪
were meant for the dead, anyway.
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Young Master.
My condolences.
That person
must be watching you from heaven.
♪ Let the tears fall,
let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
She won't be in heaven.
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
Someone like her
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
is either in hell,
♪ We ♪
or...
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
But it's fine.
Since she's back,
I will ask her
for an explanation myself.