=Dangerous Love=
=Episode 8=
That temper of yours
is just like mine when I was young.
Too quick to act.
We're father and son.
How could I not trust you?
But the cultural relics theft was odd,
and the Zhous' death
is even stranger.
It is hard not to suspect.
Here's the deal.
Keep digging for me.
And see
who's against me.
Got it.
(Xu Beisheng.)
(You destroyed my family.)
(This debt...)
(I'll make you pay in full.)
(You want to claim)
(the Governor's heir position, right?)
(I won't let you get your way.)
(The more you want something,)
(the harder I'll make it for you.)
Mr. Xu.
It's been a few days.
Feels like no one remembers me.
Menghuan.
I heard about
your family's situation.
You have to stay strong.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
Menghuan.
You must've been tiring.
Why not rest inside for a bit?
Mrs. Xu,
let me apologize first.
I acted rashly before.
Letting down the Xu and Zhou families.
But now I've figured it out.
I come back
just to marry Tianci.
Throw her out of here.
Who dares?
I'm the future Third Young Mistress.
Master.
You…
You… you actually hit me!
My dear,
we do have some misunderstandings.
But I'm still your future sister-in-law.
You're young,
so I should guide you more.
There's always
an order of respect.
If her behavior like this
spreads out,
it will harm
her reputation and the Xus'.
What do you think?
Menghuan.
I'm glad you've figured it out.
But
Tianci was set up by someone.
He's still in bed, can't get up.
What happened?
What's really going on?
Master, Madam.
Good news.
Third Young Master
is awake.
Master.
Thank you.
I'll go check on him.
How dare she!
Where is everyone?
Where did they all go?
Come here and attend to me.
Someone!
Tianci.
Are you alright?
Madam said you were hurt.
I was so worried about you.
Seeing you fine now,
I'm really relieved.
About that night,
you're not upset?
I am.
Of course I'm upset.
You've done it
without telling me first.
But,
I'm even mad at myself.
How did I not see
that you are
actually an artist.
You know not only how to
to appreciate beauty,
but how to create it.
Really?
Yes, really.
And
I really love the snake
you gave me.
Menghuan.
You're the only one who believes in me.
Thank you.
Stop, everyone's watching.
Master.
Look how sweet they are.
How about
we pick a date soon
and hold the wedding?
It'd be a great chance
to shake off the bad vibes.
Menghuan,
come with me to the study.
I've something to tell you.
Alright.
Get some rest.
Mr. Xu, what's going on?
Menghuan.
Didn't you say before
you wanted to marry Beisheng?
Why the sudden change of heart?
Did Beisheng do something
that upset you?
Don't worry,
as long as you tell me
I'll stand up for you.
In the past,
I was too headstrong,
and got drawn to
Young Master's cold, distant charm.
Now that the Zhou family is gone,
I can't keep being willful
and wasting time with him.
Well, at least you're honest.
But...
the main reason I suggested
this arranged marriage
is that I valued your family's status.
The Zhous are gone,
but the network remains.
Haven't you always wanted to break free
from being overshadowed by the Jiangs?
You need someone higher up.
And if
I become your daughter-in-law,
I will give everything I have
to connect you to the right people.
If that's the case,
then I'll be waiting to drink
your Bride's Tea.
(Smooth talker.)
(I don't believe Xu Beisheng's shady work)
(has nothing to do with you.)
(In this whole mansion,)
(you're all evil.)
(No one can be trusted.)
Then I'll follow your arrangements.
I'll take my leave.
Get up now.
Tianci is already awake.
Tianci.
Mom.
Listen up,
you got lucky this time.
Miaoyin found you
a trustworthy doctor.
Otherwise, it would've gone really bad.
Well...
Thank her.
Thanks, Miaoyin.
My pleasure, Madam.
Tianci.
I'm glad you're okay.
Since you care so much for me,
why not do me another favor?
What are you doing?
Lend me your hand as my canvas.
I plan to
tattoo
a toad.
I think this animal
suits you best,
always dreaming
of things you can't reach.
Don't you think?
Enough.
You brat, talking nonsense again.
I'm serious.
Alright, sit.
Sit down.
Madam, since nothing's wrong...
Well.
You've kneeled long enough.
Go rest.
Yes.
What's wrong?
Come on, have a seat.
(Li Manzhen.)
(You've really crossed the line.)
They've gone way too far.
Why are you crying?
It's just a scratch.
Lady Miaoyin,
leave with me.
I promise you,
I'll treat you well.
Don't be silly.
If I leave,
wouldn't that let them win?
Come to think of it,
I should thank Li Manzhen.
That beating today
has completely woken me up.
The humiliation today,
I'll make them repay double.
But I'm scared...
you won't beat them,
and end up risking your own life.
It's fine.
I still have you, don't I?
Lu Siyuan.
In this family,
you're the only one I need.
I'm tired.
You go back first.
Alright.
Lady Miaoyin,
if you
need anything, just let me know.
Xiaotao.
My lady,
you're finally back.
From now on, can you
not leave me all alone again?
Xiaotao.
From now on,
we're each other's only family.
I'll treat you
like my own little sister.
My lady, please don't be sad.
I'll get you something to eat.
Okay.
Dad.
Have some water.
You rascal.
When will you make me proud?
Stop following that woman around
all the time.
But at least you care about me.
Dad.
I remember
you once saved a Japanese.
Why do you want to know that?
Just curious.
So I asked.
Siyuan,
times are rough right now.
Let's stay out of this.
Or someone might label you
a traitor to the Chinese.
Butler Lu.
Madam wants to see you.
Alright, got it.
You go ahead first.
About that matter,
keep it to yourself
and tell no one.
Alright.
(Zhou Menghuan,)
(since you chose this path,)
(you must keep going
no matter how hard.)
Who?
Xu Beisheng.
You still dare come to me?
Guards!
♪A butterfly flies into the biting wind♪
♪Crashing into the pure white of winter♪
♪I want to fill your life
with rose vines♪
♪Striving to bloom♪
♪In the empty, deserted city♪
♪A stranded ship♪
♪In silent accord with storm and waves♪
♪Though we knew and chose to forget♪
♪That our courses were never the same♪
♪We rode the tides born of the moon♪
♪For just a fleeting embrace♪
♪After sunrise, no one will know you♪
♪Yet you're so heavy in my heart♪
♪If the mistake was meeting by chance
that windy day♪
♪I only wish for a gentle ending♪
♪Even if the sunset swayed that day♪
♪Even if our embrace was not sincere♪
♪We loved deeply,
falling like startled swans♪
♪Tears rushed forth as once they surged♪
♪She wove a crown of solitude
with her life♪
♪Silently stepping into
the crowded world♪