=Dangerous Love=
=Episode 22=
Xu Miaoyin.
How long are you planning
to use me and keep lying to me?
Because of you,
my father is already gone.
Isn't that enough for you?
So, you already knew.
Who are you?
Why are you so scared?
Relax.
We won't touch any of you for now.
Come on, let's have a chat.
Come on.
Let's just sit and talk, okay?
Don't touch me.
Stay away from me.
You nasty woman.
So you're a lunatic.
Stop!
If you touch her,
you won't get those relics.
Get out of here.
It's me.
Miaoling.
You're safe now.
Beisheng and I
will keep you safe.
No one will hurt you again.
It's okay now.
Commander,
just as you predicted,
the entire mansion
is under Lu Siyuan's control.
Our rifles
have been confiscated.
Lu Siyuan is nothing but a puppet.
The people from Japan backing him
are the real problem.
Those traitors to the nation.
I'll fight them head-on.
They're not going to
give up the cultural relics.
Keep this gun safe.
And remember,
no matter what happens,
you must protect Zhou Menghuan.
And keep yourself safe too.
Got it.
You're the representative?
That's me.
Lu Siyuan.
Are you serious?
Why side with the Japanese
and even be a traitor?
I learned all that from you.
To reach a goal,
using any means necessary,
even giving up dignity,
and selling one's soul.
Lu Siyuan,
if you hate me that much,
then end me right now.
Take it as paying Butler Lu's debt.
Want to die?
It's not that easy.
I'll use the cruelest ways
in this world
to break you
and humiliate you,
until living
feels worse than dying.
How's Miaoling doing?
Her mood's still unstable.
I just
gave her a bit of sleeping pills.
She's much better now.
Menghuan,
she's done so many things to hurt you.
Why are you helping her?
Because of you.
I know.
You came to the Xu family
out of revenge,
but you truly treat her like a sister.
By the way,
tomorrow is Lu Siyuan's
final deadline.
What's your plan?
I haven't decided yet.
But no matter what,
our national treasure
must never fall into foreign hands.
Beisheng.
Don't worry about me.
Just do what you need to do.
As long as
I can be with you.
Even if it means dying,
I'd still be happy.
Siyuan.
Starting today,
you'll be my servant.
Serve me well.
Alright.
Do whatever you want to get back at me.
But can you let the others go?
They've done nothing wrong to you.
Xu Miaoyin, when did you become
this nave?
You're in no place to bargain with me.
Siyuan.
- Siyuan.
- Quiet.
Get up now.
I've got things to take care of.
Young Master Xu.
My staff are just too slow.
They held me up a bit.
That's why I'm late.
Hope you can forgive me.
I wanted to ask you about
the cultural relics.
Have you made up your mind?
No problem.
I'll work with you.
Xu Beisheng.
What did you say?
However,
I have my own terms.
Alright.
Let's hear them.
First,
no harm can come to anyone
in my mansion.
Second,
once it's done,
I'd like you
to introduce me to Mr. Yamamoto
to make future cooperation easier.
Sure, no problem.
You're really straightforward.
Then, Mr. Lu,
three days from now,
we make the deal.
Pleasure doing business.
Xu Beisheng!
You traitor!
I'm going to end you!
- Take him out!
- Wait.
I'll do it myself.
What are you doing?
You've gone through life and death.
Xu Beisheng.
You... you...
Xu Beisheng,
I was wrong about you.
Xu Beisheng!
Mr. Lu.
He's been with me all these years.
Please send his body back in one piece.
Why are you so quiet?
I'm waiting for your explanation.
Why did you work with the Japanese?
Why...
did you kill Adjutant Yuan?
If I told you,
would you believe me?
Of course.
As long as you say it,
I'll believe it.
There's nothing to explain.
It's exactly what you saw.
I've worked so hard for years
to climb up to
the Governor's seat.
No one
and
nothing can stop me.
No way.
Did something happen?
Beisheng, tell me.
We can face it together.
Xu Beisheng.
Madam Zhou,
aren't you taking yourself too seriously?
You...
What did you call me?
I called you Madam Zhou,
Xu Qingshan's concubine.
You've passed your prime.
I was just after something new.
You didn't really think I cared,
did you?
You jerk.
I'll give you one chance.
If you don't want more humiliation,
get out right now.
Get out.
Out!
Jerk.
Keep your eyes on him.
Before the deal,
there can't be any mistakes.
Yes.
You and Xu Beisheng,
are you really siblings?
Why is it that when you act,
you're both so ruthless
and cold to your own family?
Xu Miaoyin,
stop pretending you're not here.
Or I'll go after your mother first.
Siyuan,
please,
please don't hurt my mom.
I'm begging you.
Then you'd better behave.
Aren't you the one
who's best at reading people?
Make sure you please me.
Who knows, maybe one day
if I'm in a good mood,
I might just let you go.
Do you deserve that?
♪A butterfly flies into the biting wind♪
♪Crashing into the pure white of winter♪
♪I want to fill your life
with rose vines♪
♪Striving to bloom♪
♪In the empty, deserted city♪
♪A stranded ship♪
♪In silent accord with storm and waves♪
♪Though we knew and chose to forget♪
♪That our courses were never the same♪
♪We rode the tides born of the moon♪
♪For just a fleeting embrace♪
♪After sunrise, no one will know you♪
♪Yet you're so heavy in my heart♪
♪If the mistake was meeting by chance
that windy day♪
♪I only wish for a gentle ending♪
♪Even if the sunset swayed that day♪
♪Even if our embrace was not sincere♪
♪We loved deeply,
falling like startled swans♪
♪Tears rushed forth as once they surged♪
♪She wove a crown of solitude
with her life♪
♪Silently stepping into
the crowded world♪