Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪From morning to night,
my heart flutters for you♪
♪You are my everyday joy♪
♪Even when you appear in my dream♪
♪When I open my eyes, I still miss you♪
♪You are the blue sky
in the early morning♪
♪I feel shy
as if I'm kissed by the sunset♪
♪I know you will wink at me in my dream♪
♪When I wake up, I still miss you♪
♪You are the sweet glass of water
in the early morning♪
♪I immerse myself in your freshness♪
♪You are in every scene
that I've ever imagined♪
♪I'm waiting for you to
appear at the next moment♪
♪LaLaLa...♪
♪I wake up and fall into
your arm without a care♪
Forever Love
Episode 21
Goodbye, Brother
Come on.
Do you want some more?
-Waiter, get us some more beers.
-Okay.
-Sir, your beer.
-Thank you.
Enjoy yourselves.
It's your first time to
work in a company, right?
Yeah.
How do you feel?
Tell me about it.
Well,
I think
the work itself is interesting,
but the fights in the workplace
are boring to me.
Let me tell you.
You should focus on
learning in the company.
Nothing else matters.
Those
childish fights
have nothing to do with you.
Come on.
Jiang Zheng Han.
Do you know that
whenever I look at you,
it seems like that
I look at myself back then.
Were you this handsome like me?
I was
the same as you.
I've got talent.
I've got dreams.
I've taken up responsibilities.
I thought I could do anything.
I wouldn't be restrained by any rules.
The whole world knelt at my feet.
Therefore,
we would easily get envied.
You have to be careful now.
Back me up
if I have some trouble with others
in the future
that I can't solve by myself.
You pick up the crooked things
quite fast.
What if I quit,
who can you count on to cover your back?
You have to learn to
deal with the problems yourself.
What do you mean by that?
It's just an example.
You're still so young.
You have a great future ahead of you.
Okay.
I
won't let you down.
It's not about letting me down.
You shouldn't let yourself down.
Cheers.
Come on.
My toast.
The Second Half of Freshman Year
I was grounded the whole vacation by my mom.
-That's too bad.
-Xiao Man!
Xiao Xi?
-Qiu Yan?
-Qiu Yan! What a coincidence!
What a coincidence.
Well, Qiu Yan,
you've become even more beautiful
after the vacation.
That's so sweet of you.
By the way, haven't Chen Yi Chuan
and Zhang Huai Wu come together with you?
They're helping Xiao Xi
with her stuff now.
Qiu Yan,
can you take my case to the dorm for me?
I have something else to do
and will go to the dorm later.
Are you going to the gathering then?
Yes, but later.
And,
don't tell Jiang Zheng Han
that I've come back.
I see, you want to surprise him.
Well, you know it.
Thank you two for helping me.
-I shall go now.
-Go ahead, Xiao Xi.
-Okay, see you in the evening.
-Bye-bye.
-Qiu Yan, you're getting more beautiful.
-Let's ride in my car.
Xiao Man.
I've been wanting to ask you
why Duan Ning didn't come to pick you up.
He? Why would he pick me up?
I didn't tell him.
You fought?
No.
I haven't really replied his WeChat messages
during the vacation.
So,
you haven't been with Duan Ning at all.
Am I right?
You only did it
to upset Chen Yi Chuan.
How could I upset him?
I went to Sanya with my parents
for the Spring Festival
just to avoid thinking about him.
Don't mention him.
I'm so angry whenever I hear his name
that I don't want to
live on this planet anymore!
Xiao Man.
Yeah?
If you still like him,
just admit this feeling.
If you are over him, just let him go then.
Don't make yourself sad
because of a man, okay?
How about
having something delicious together?
You've got a point.
Let's go have a nice meal.
Food is the only thing
that can make me happy in this world.
-Right after dropping the luggage.
-Okay.
-Xia Lin Xi!
-Coming!
The last pieces, right?
Yes, the last.
Thank you both.
What are you doing now?
You've literally moved
brother Zheng's home
from Jiangming to here.
What do you think she's doing?
She just wants to be closer to the company
where Jiang Zheng Han
has been doing internship.
Well, are you going to
live with Jiang Zheng Han?
That's nonsense.
Chen Yi Chuan,
don't you start any rumors.
I just moved back to the dorm.
I'm warning you,
if you tell others about this again,
I'm going to burn
all your Snoopy into ashes,
then put them in a little box,
and I'll hand-deliver them
to your dorm room.
That's enough, sis Xia.
If you keep on frightening Chuan,
he's going to pee his pants.
Cut the crap.
How can you threaten me?
I've helped you a lot, okay?
I won't help you next time.
My smart brain
isn't created to lie to my aunt
every time you need help.
-Next time…
-My mom wouldn't know
that I failed my exam if not for you.
I didn't shove you off the train
only because you're my brother.
That's enough. That's enough.
You two are fighting
every time you see each other.
Come on, let's move all these stuffs.
Let's go. Come on!
You two can go ahead
to the gathering after this.
Sis Xia, aren't you going?
Well,
I gotta unpack those stuffs first.
I'll go later.
Okay.
By the way,
don't
tell Jiang Zheng Han.
-Okay.
-Okay, I know.
Have a drink, brother Zheng.
Zhang, I want some ribs.
Ask Chen Yi Chuan! He's so close to you.
No, thank you.
It's too oily. I'm on a diet.
I...
I want salad instead.
-Xiao Man…
-Come on, everyone.
We haven't seen each other for so long.
Let me propose a toast to you.
-Long time no see.
-Come on! Come on!
Staying with you guys is so much fun.
-It's so boring staying home alone.
-Come on!
I've been waiting to
see you guys for so long.
Really, I've finished my drink!
Don't have so much.
Stop it.
Brother Zheng,
I heard that you abandoned sis Xia
and came back on the seventh day
of the Spring Festival.
Were there any problems at work?
What do you mean by "abandon"?
That was because of
an emergency of the company.
Okay.
But it will return to normal
after the semester begins.
Okay.
Well, absence
makes the heart grow fonder.
Then do you know
when Xiao Xi's going to come back?
She told me she'd arrive tomorrow.
Don't you know?
No.
As long as I know.
Jiang Zheng Han,
you care about Xia Lin Xi so much,
even I can't stand that.
It's disgusting.
Wait a minute!
What is disgusting?
What happened?
He performed action art
in my uncle's Moments!
-Really?
-So disgusting.
I didn't.
Brother Zheng, well done.
You've impressed her parents.
Chen Yi Chuan, you…
Come on, tell us
what kind of action art that was?
-Poems!
-No.
-Poems?
Extremely embarrassing.
Come on. Show us!
-Let me see.
-Come on! Show us.
Chen Yi Chuan!
I said I didn't.
Moments: Xia Bei Hai
-It's meant to be...
-I have to go to the restroom.
No, you must stay here.
You have to hear this.
I hope you don't throw up
after reading this.
-It's meant to be...
-Let me see.
I met Lin Xi.
It's my turn.
Our beauty is
in her prime.
I'm going to throw up.
I can't listen to it anymore.
I'm most fortunate
to meet uncle.
I won't regret to be a member of the Xias.
Period.
Wait!
Uncle Xia replied that
-"great poem, Jiang".
-Great poem.
-It's so awkward.
-Come on.
-So awkward.
-Just eat.
For the first time
in my life,
I sympathize with
Chen Yi Chuan.
What do you mean?
I said that because
he suffered so much
from watching
this "action art".
Cheers.
Jiang Zheng Han,
if you do this kind of action art
in the Moments again,
my uncle would be
the 17th person I blocked.
Can you stop?
Mr. Jiang,
I suggest
you start a lesson in our Chinese Dept,
called "Embarrassing Poems Writing".
It would be very popular.
Let me tell you.
-It would be embarrassing enough.
-Of course!
Though the form remains to be discussed,
Jiang's love to Xiao Xi is rather pure.
It seems that
-uncle Xia was happy, too.
-Yeah.
Amazing.
I really can't bear with you.
What's wrong with you?
He's old.
Talent Jiang.
-What?
-Since Xiao Xi is not here,
tell us
what are the advantages and disadvantages
of having such a perfect girlfriend?
Right. Tell us.
We swear that
we would never tell Xiao Xi.
Right.
Disadvantages?
There are too many disadvantages.
Too many?
Like stars in the sky.
Stars? That's really a lot.
-What about advantages?
-Stars? That's a lot.
-No.
-No?
Just one.
She's like the sun.
When the sun comes out,
you can't see any stars.
That's so cheesy!
Oh no.
I can't eat anymore.
Don't tell Xiao Xi about this.
-She's going to be cocky.
-We won't.
-That's hard to say.
-We have to think it through.
My god!
-Whose hands? How dare you touch them?
-Right!
Whose hands are you touching?
Do you know whose hands?
Not only dare I touch them,
I dare kiss them as well.
I need to stay away from you two.
Are you surprised?
-Do you miss me?
-No.
Didn't you say that
I had many disadvantages?
Didn't you?
Why did you tell me that
you would arrive tomorrow?
We haven't seen each other for so long,
have you missed me?
Have you?
Of course.
The internship must be very tiring.
It seems you've lost your weight.
You look toilworn.
Do you need to work overtime today?
Today...
I don't have to
work overtime today.
Really?
Let's have a walk.
Where do you want to go? Let's go.
Let's go together.
Well,
if you don't have to work,
let me take you to a place.
Where are we going?
I've prepared a surprise for you.
Let's go.
Come with me.
Come on.
We're getting in.
-Come here.
-Slowly, slowly.
Just stay there.
Let me hang the coats first.
Where are you?
Coming.
Okay.
Have a guess.
We're not
in a B&B for couples, are we?
No!
Then, where are we?
Well.
Okay, let me take it off.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Three.
Two.
One.
What do you think?
You know what,
these were all specially transported from Jiangming.
I did a great job restoring it, right?
And look,
it's only
five minutes' walk to XV.
And have a look at this street.
Turn right,
and you could
find a delicious breakfast diner.
And here's
a convenient store that
opens for 24 hours.
You don't know
how much trouble
I've gone through to get this closet here.
And this sofa.
I especially went to
the flea market to buy this
to match the style of this secret base.
Lin Xi.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Xia Lin Xi,
how lucky am I
to meet you?
Why are you suddenly saying these?
Lin Xi.
It's been a year.
How did you think of this surprise?
It's close to your office,
so, you don't have to
sleep in the company.
It's more convenient for your internship.
Then am I
benefiting from you if I live here?
I have the contract for
the ownership of you.
Behave yourself.
I owe you too much.
I can never repay them.
I can only give myself to you.
You've done so much for me.
Is there anything I can do for you?
Yeah.
You just…
Just make much money,
and
repay me.
In the end,
you can
buy the stars as a gift for me.
Stars?
I'll remember it.
Are you nervous?
Are you not ready
to give yourself to me?
You took a cold bath?
How could you tell?
Because there's no heat around your body.
This is my pay card.
Here you are.
If you need money
in the future,
use it first.
Take it.
You don't have to.
You've given me a computer.
Why can't I give you a card?
I can't repay all once,
then pay by installments.
Here.
Take it.
Okay.
How did you know
that I would continue
the internship at XV?
Because
I can read your mind.
The internship at XV is a golden chance.
You could improve the ability there.
Participate in more projects.
You love programming, after all.
You can even read my mind now.
It's settled.
I'm going to have my internship
at Lion Group.
-That company belongs to Qin Yue, right?
-Qiu Yan.
-Lin Xi, long time no see.
-Shi Ying.
When did you come back?
I just arrived yesterday.
Isn't this lesson
only for freshmen?
How come you are here, senior?
I spent the second semester of my freshmen year
in Britain for academic exchange.
Therefore, I missed this lesson.
So I
come back here to
gain the credits
before the internship starts.
I see.
Guess at which company
she is having her internship?
Why should I guess?
Oh, could it be
that...
Lion?
Yeah, Qin Yue's company.
Wow, congratulations.
-Thank you.
-Does Qin Yue know about this?
He does.
But I didn't tell him
about this in advance.
I just sent my resume.
Shi Ying, you're so amazing.
You don't need to
pull strings with the boss.
Hasn't the teacher arrived yet?
Zhuang Fei.
The teacher is here.
Hello, all.
I'm Ms. Wu,
the teacher for your practice lesson.
I'd like you to
form groups of four people.
Then you could discuss and study
your projects in your groups.
To save your time,
let's form the group
on the basis of roommates.
If there're less than four people in a dorm room,
you could come to me to make some changes.
In this way, it's more convenient for you
to have discussion after class.
If you're clear with what I said,
you could change your seats.
I'm going to
distribute the materials to every group.
While you're changing the seats, I would…
How about us four
starting a group together?
In this lesson, we will mainly focus on
simulating an investment bank.
In this lesson…
Xiao Xi, I don't mean to be narrow-minded,
but why is she always in your sight?
We still have to
live together in the future,
just ignore her now.
Let's go.
Zhuang Fei.
You heard what Ms. Wu said, right?
Then how about us four starting a team?
Try to improve your abilities
of collecting data
-Okay.
-and analyzing problems
by analyzing the project.
Come on.
Great.
The four of us are a team.
You're going to help me finish the project
and get me the credit, okay?
Okay, senior.
You're the team leader.
You're the boss.
Okay.
Xiao Xi.
Yes.
Are you really going to
move back to the dorm?
Then I would live more often
in the dorm, too,
in case you would get bullied.
-Really?
-Sure.
Thank you, Qiu Yan.
You're such a great friend.
Well,
you know I moved out of that apartment
for another one closer to
Jiang Zheng Han's company.
But that's too far from the university.
I can only spend the weekends there.
That's the surprise
for Talent Jiang you mentioned?
Yeah.
Does your mum know about this?
How could I let her know?
I'm just a freshman, and she already
arranged blind date for me.
She would punish me severely
if she knows that
I'm still with Jiang Zheng Han.
Blind date?
Xiao Xi,
you've had quite an exciting vacation.
Yeah.
With whom?
With your childhood sweetheart, Qin Yue,
right?
So smart of you.
-Really?
-Yes.
But I messed it up.
You don't know
how I felt when I came home
and saw the whole family of Qin Yue there.
I was almost crazy!
Tell me about it, god!
Nothing much.
I just pretended to be an alcoholic
and a shrew the whole time.
Qin Yue.
Hello, Shi Ying.
-You...
-Long time no see.
I heard that you're here for the credits?
Right.
By the way,
I didn't see you
when I reported at Lion that day.
Oh.
I've heard about it.
I wasn't at the company for a few days.
How about you tell me in advance
before you go to the company next time?
Sure.
How about
dining together?
Well, I…
I'm going to…
Hello, Qin Yue!
Long time no see!
Yes, long time no see.
Qin Yue,
why didn't you come to
the gathering of
the Student Union last time?
I…
I have an idea.
How about we all dine together today?
Qin Yue's treat, I will pay.
Senior Shi Ying is
always thinking for Qin Yue.
What a perfect match.
I'm very sorry,
but I already had plans today.
Therefore,
let me treat you all another day.
Sorry. Sorry for today.
-Sorry.
-What is going on?
-Senior.
-Xiao Xi.
Hi.
Xiao Xi.
-Brother Qin Yue.
-Hello, senior Qin Yue.
What is going on here?
Isn't Xia Lin Xi's boyfriend
Talent Jiang?
The girl really got something.
The two dreamy boys
of Jing Hua University.
Shi Ying,
isn't she your roommate?
What kind of person is she on earth?
Sorry,
I still got things to do, gotta go.
-Wait, Shi Ying. She's gone?
-Shi Ying!
I was having a lesson just now.
I didn't check my phone. Sorry.
Do you want to
dine together?
Well, I have already asked Qiu Yan
to dine with me.
Yeah, we'll dine together.
Then how about having me in?
I can use this chance
to know Qiu Yan better.
Okay.
What do you prefer then?
Seafood or Japanese cuisine?
Brother Qin Yue, you don't have to
take us to such expensive places.
Let's just go to the cafeteria.
Okay, sure.
Then let's go.
Okay.
Senior, are you okay?
I'm okay.
I'm just feeling a little uncomfortable.
I'm going back to rest.
Senior, do you know that
Qin Yue and Xia Lin Xi had a blind date?
Cafeteria
Let's sit here.
I'm going to get us trays.
Let me get it.
You two can have a talk.
Xiao Xi,
the credit of the program
is going to be recorded.
You can ask me anytime
if you have any questions.
Thank you.
I can do it myself.
You're already a senior.
You must be very busy.
Don't bother yourself to help me.
I think you may
have some misunderstandings about me
from the gathering last time.
-I was…
-It has already passed.
It's my mum's fault, too.
She tried to make a wrong match.
I acted very weirdly that day.
You parents must be
very unsatisfied with me.
But I don't want to apologize, either,
because I don't want
any other misunderstandings.
They've known you since you were little,
-your behavior that day wouldn't make them…
-Brother Qin Yue.
I believe I've made it
very clear to you last time.
Let's just have a meal.
Okay?
Okay.
Let's go get something to eat.
Let me do it. Wait a minute for me.
How did it go?
We've talked it out.
Hello, Xiao Xi.
I've just received my new clothes.
But it doesn't fit me.
Come to my dorm and try it on
when you're free.
I haven't gained weight!
I just bought the wrong size.
Yes, the class just finished.
I'm at the cafeteria now.
The cook is already off duty.
I almost missed dinner! I'm so hungry.
Okay then. Don't forget about it.
Love you!
Alas.
-Hello.
Xiao Man.
Slow down. It's all yours.
Why are you here?
Didn't I tell you
that I had lessons tonight,
and I would go straight back
to dorm after dinner?
You don't have to accompany me.
Just take care of your own business.
I'm glad to accompany you
as long as I can.
Don't eat this.
This!
Isn't this my favorite Dongpo Pork
from the restaurant outside the east gate?
A new branch in the university?
No, I especially
went there to buy you this.
Have it while it's still hot. Have a try.
How is it?
Nice.
Duan Ning, thank you.
You're welcome.
Chen Yi Chuan can never do this for me.
It's nothing.
Running errands for my fairy
is what I should do.
Wait.
Hello, there are still people here!
Why did she turn the light off?
I... I haven't finished my dinner yet…
Wow,
Prince Duan, you even prepared this?
It's quite amazing.
Wait.
When the flowers and sages
in the plain are decaying,
in the temple on the mountain
is the peach blossoming.
Smell it.
Does it smell good?
It smells like peach flowers.
Yes. Do you like it?
Come on, have your meal.
Is it the same taste as you remembered?
Duan Ning.
I think we should end it.
I mean, we should break up.
Sure.
Wait,
aren't you upset?
Come on,
why would I be upset?
I knew it from the beginning
that you agreed to be with me
because you wanted to
upset Chen Yi Chuan.
You've known it all the time?
Of course.
I brought it up
to go along with your plan
and teach him a lesson.
Well,
now that you don't want to
do this anymore,
of course, I could drop the act.
You should have told me earlier,
I was so nervous.
You have
always been so naughty.
Tell me how much it cost.
I'll transfer it to you.
You can
take the candle back
and attract some other girl with it.
Well,
no matter what you say,
this is a so-called break-up meal.
It sucks to talk about money.
And you
could keep the candle.
I bought it just for you.
Don't you like the scent of peach flowers?
Okay.
Thank you, Duan Ning.
You're welcome.
It's pretty late now.
You may go back first.
I can go back to the dorm myself.
Sure.
Okay.
Then I'll go. Have a great meal.
Enjoy yourself.
Okay.
Ma'am.
Yes.
Thank you.
Lin Xi.
I've made a plan
for our recent working arrangement.
Qiu Yan and Zhuang Fei
have already got their assignments,
have a look at your part.
Okay.
Senior,
the data on the report
is different from what I've found.
There might be some mistakes.
Maybe you need to
check the data more carefully?
I understand what you're talking about.
This is the next step in my plan.
It would be difficult for me
to finish the work within today
according to the form.
Really?
According to the form,
I've only asked you to organize the data.
Going by the current situation,
I have to redo loads of data comparison…
Lin Xi, everyone was assigned with
heavy work.
I hope you could think more for the team
instead of trying to
evade your responsibility.
Okay?
Jiang Zheng Han
I have to work overtime today.
You can go home first.
You could sleep first if you're tired.
Don't wait for me.
I would finish work late, too.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Xiao Xi, get in the car.
Wait, brother Qin Yue, what are you doing?
Let me go.
Lin Xi, I know that
you've clearly told me
that you see me as a brother.
You've told me clearly that
I can't overstep the boundary.
But is this the way
Jiang Zheng Han treats you?
You took bus all the way here
to wait for him at such late hours.
He just let you wait for him
in the rain here?
Could Jiang Zheng Han be responsible
if accidents happened?
What does it have to do with him?
Hands off me!
-Brother Qin Yue!
-Xiao Xi, get in the car!
Let me go!
Brother Qin Yue.
Let me go.
Qin Yue!
Xia Lin Xi is my girlfriend now.
You know it.
Yes, I know it.
But she's been suffering so much with you!
Sorry, I can't bear with it!
♪Start missing every movement of you♪
I respected
and admired you very much
when you were my leader.
But now, don't make me look down on you.
♪Recalling the sweet script again♪
It won't be a problem
for me if Xiao Xi could
live a good life with you.
I can totally let her go.
But now
I don't think you're able to
protect her at all!
Jiang Zheng Han,
if you're not comfortable with
me being here today,
please ask yourself first!
Have you done enough?
Both of you, stop!
♪I can no longer smell your existence♪
Brother Qin Yue,
this is my decision.
I hope you could respect me.
♪Still your sweet words
resounding in my ears♪
Let's go.
♪Sitting in my room in pain♪
♪With arms around your photo♪
♪In a world without you♪
♪I can't stop missing you♪
♪You took everything away from me♪
♪I can't help missing you♪
♪In a world without you♪
♪I suddenly start missing you♪
♪What you took away with you♪
♪It's a whole world to me♪
♪I rewind every day♪
♪Hoping we could go back
to the beginning of happiness♪
♪Like a kite straying off the string♪
♪I can no longer smell your existence♪
♪In the long corridor of youth♪
♪Stored so many secrets♪
♪The unmodified dreams and thoughts♪
♪Were all on our faces proudly♪
♪The direction that leads to wider sky♪
♪Was the place that
we promised to go together♪
♪Your warmth filled my luggage♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that
you'll always accompany me to look up♪
♪We occasionally got hurt on the way♪
♪Just to spend all my time with you♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that our love never changed♪