Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪From morning to night,
my heart flutters for you♪
♪You are my everyday joy♪
♪Even when you appear in my dream♪
♪When I open my eyes, I still miss you♪
♪You are the blue sky
in the early morning♪
♪I feel shy
as if I'm kissed by the sunset♪
♪I know you will wink at me in my dream♪
♪When I wake up, I still miss you♪
♪You are the sweet glass of water
in the early morning♪
♪I immerse myself in your freshness♪
♪You are in every scene
that I've ever imagined♪
♪I'm waiting for you to
appear at the next moment♪
♪LaLaLa...♪
♪I wake up and fall into
your arm without a care♪
Forever Love
Episode 11
The Damn First Kiss
What do you want to do?
I don't want you
to be taken away from me.
I know you have one just like this.
I just want to confirm
whether I still have an opportunity?
How do you know that?
Jiang Zheng Han, we promised we would
go to Jing Hua university together.
Don't you remember that?
Where are you now?
Jiang Zheng Han.
I didn't expect that you
even bought off Chu Qiu Yan.
When you left,
you told me not to be childish.
What do you mean by doing so today?
I am a slow starter.
And I am not sociable.
I was just worried about you.
Anyhow you haven't said yes
to Qin Yue, right?
I was afraid that he would take the lead.
-So I...
-So that's what you're thinking.
The thanks you said before,
the gratitude you expressed,
are all lies.
-Lin Xi...
-But it's not important any more.
It's up to me whether
I'll accept brother Qin Yue.
None of your business.
None of my business?
I want to know your answer to me.
What answer?
Talent of technology,
you hacked into the live screen
and made disturbances in my life.
You made it.
Now you feel happy?
What do you take me for?
A trophy of you two's battle?
No.
I just thought you might
accept Qin Yue's confession,
so I became thoughtless.
But I was very embarrassed
at that moment.
Sorry.
I succeeded at a great cost.
But I had really considered
confessing my love to you earlier.
However, I held it back.
I'll go back to our university.
Please
don't make me a topic
of others' gossip again
in such a way.
Lin Xi.
Lin Xi, let me send you back.
No. I can go back by myself.
You broke the rules to confess.
Aren't you definitely the winner?
Why are you running alone here?
It was you who broke the rules.
Now neither of us wins,
okay?
I know Xiao Xi well.
She won't like
such a way of love confession.
Yeah, you are right.
But next time,
I'll do it in a better way.
I've been accompanying Xiao Xi many years.
I know what she likes.
I know what kind of person she is.
But have you ever thought that
even you've stayed with her many years,
you still have no idea
what kind of a girl she is.
You don't know her for long.
What do you know?
I've protected her for so long.
I won't allow you to cut in.
She isn't a girl who needs protection.
Do you know?
She pursues freedom.
There are things that she likes.
Of course there are moments
when she can't be sensible.
This is why I like her.
If so,
let's make a new rule.
Let's compete again.
Well...
Hello, professor.
You've done a good job
in the analytic theory of number.
Thank you, professor.
Which department are you in?
And your name?
I'm Xia Lin Xi,
from the Dept of Economic&Management.
Xia Lin Xi?
Yes.
Oh, you are Xia Lin Xi?
Do you know me?
You may say so.
Well, go on with your work.
See you next time
if there's a chance.
Oh, okay.
See you.
Next time?
See me?
Hey.
What?
Chuan, you have a nice profile.
-I don't need you to tell me that.
-Hey there.
I saw that.
After you.
Use my pen.
No.
Is the seat taken?
It is.
Please tell your friend
that I'll take the seat.
Lin Xi, calm down.
I really have something important
to tell you this time.
Yesterday Professor Shi saw
your analysis of a math problem.
He felt you have a great gift for math.
So he wanted me to ask you
whether you want to
join the computer varsity.
What?
The varsity is recruiting?
Why didn't I know that?
Why can Xia Lin Xi join it while I can't?
Fill out an application form.
I need to discuss it with Professor Shi.
Then you must tell Professor Shi,
if I am not recruited,
it will be the biggest loss
for the varsity.
I'll apply for it later.
Brother Zheng.
How about you speak up for me?
I can try to help you
get into the qualification trials.
Your success relies on your own ability.
Okay.
It's already a big help for me.
-Thank you, brother Zheng.
-Why you again?
Wow!
Pretty,
you still remember me?
I read my fortune this morning.
It's said that I'd be lucky
in adventures with women.
See? I meet you here.
You know what? It's God's will.
Glib-tongued.
Mrs. Jiang.
I'm not like what she said.
Though it's the first time we meet,
I've heard a lot about you.
First time?
Why aren't you shortsighted?
My name is Duan Ning.
Others call me Prince Duan.
You know what?
Even if I look at you
at such a short distance,
you are still so beautiful!
Brother Zheng, good taste.
Cut it out.
-No, Duan Ning...
-Mrs. Jiang, you know what?
-Brother Zheng cares about you very much.
-Well, he always speaks in such a way.
Don't take it to heart.
I know you're still angry at me.
But I know that is also your interest.
Don't give up what you like
because of me.
Think it over.
Hey, Xiao Xi.
-You're leaving?
-I'll go to the front row.
I said nothing wrong.
Don't worry.
Xiao Xi will go for the interview
because it's her interest.
Trust me.
Here you are.
Listen,
I come because
Professor Shi wants to see me.
There's nothing to do with you.
No problem.
Anyhow you are here.
Have a seat. Sit.
Okay. Okay.
Lin Xi.
We lack a member good at math
in the varsity.
That day, I noticed that
you're really good at math.
So I hope you can join us.
Hmm, professor, maybe you don't know
I am a student of
the Dept of Economic&Management,
not the Math Dept.
So I may not be professional enough
to meet your standards.
That's exactly what I appreciate.
Although you're not from our department,
you're interested in math.
What's more, you have a clear mind
of solving problems.
You have great potential for competition.
Right?
Thank you, Professor Shi.
You don't need to thank me, but Jiang.
I am easy-going.
Don't get nervous.
Don't call me Professor Shi.
Just call me Shi.
Okay.
Professor Shi.
There is really nothing
between Jiang Zheng Han and me.
Oh, that's right.
We were just high school classmates.
Professor Shi, in the future,
if you find she's no more capable,
you can ask her to quit.
There is a term in math
as “one and only one”.
I think every member in our varsity
is irreplaceable.
Those qualified for staying
must be capable and mentally strong.
So I think...
Don't scare her.
I believe that
our team is a warm,
responsible and capable group.
Right.
Lin Xi.
Our team is a sweet
and harmonious big family.
Our professor is handsome.
Our team members are humorous and funny.
It is your best choice
among all the clubs on campus.
That's right.
And out varsity
is a very famous official team
in Jing Hua University.
The scores you gain in the team
will be counted as scores
of extracurricular practice.
Most importantly,
it's very helpful in getting a job
and postgraduate recommendation.
Exactly.
Senior, even if
you don't make the introduction,
I know Jing Hua University's
varsity is great.
However,
I don't know...
I don't know how to program.
I may be a drag on all of you.
Don't worry.
We still use mathematical thinking
when solving problems.
Even if you don't know how to program,
it's still okay as long as
you have mathematical thinking.
You have a big advantage on that.
Well...
If so, I'll have a try.
Thank you, professor.
Welcome to join our varsity.
Applause.
By the way,
there will be a qualification trial in two days.
So,
you can come here for preparation.
Jiang, you teach her.
Okay?
Er...
In my opinion,
seniors can teach better than me.
Ah?
No, thanks...
He and I used to be classmates.
Mr. Jiang.
No, Jiang Zheng Han.
Don't mind that I might not be so smart.
It doesn't matter.
Er, professor.
They come also for the interview.
-Hello, Professor Shi.
So many students want to join us?
We don't have enough vacancies.
Professor Shi,
you can ask me any questions.
I'll answer them very well.
Me too.
-Me too. Any questions.
-Okay.
Since they are here,
let them do the tests.
You are the supervisors.
Just tell me the results.
Okay. Okay.
Xia, let's go.
I'll show you our place.
Oh, okay, professor.
Professor Shi is kind.
Take it easy.
The varsity is more suitable for you,
compared with my Math Club.
Lin Xi.
Sis Shi Ying.
I heard you joined the varsity.
Yes.
I am also one of the varsity.
But,
have you learned programming?
No.
I don't know
why Professor Shi chose me.
He asked me to
take part in a contest next week
for training.
Training through a qualification trial?
You asked Jiang Zheng Han for help
or Qin Yue?
What do you mean, senior?
The literal meaning.
Lin Xi, I know you're clever.
But you can't regard others as fools
because you're clever.
Though it's Professor Shi
who decides in the varsity
and assigns members for contests,
it's a tradition that
contestants should be selected
through competing fair and square.
Such things ever happened,
although the contestant
was a varsity member,
since his result in the trial
was not good,
he was disqualified from
taking part in official contests.
No one has told me this.
Although I haven't learned programming,
-I believe...
-In the varsity,
except Jiang Zheng Han or Qin Yue,
no one else is willing to team up
with you for the contest.
Aren't you afraid that
you will drag your team down?
In fact, it was Professor Shi
who recommended me to join the team.
I don't know whether it is an excuse
that Jiang Zheng Han or Qin Yue told you
or it's just your own illusion.
But if you can stay in the varsity,
I'll congratulate you.
I took a look at that code.
I think
we'd better modify this one.
Well, Zheng.
I gotta go.
Send me messages if you need help.
Okay.
What's wrong?
Why so hard-working today?
I heard the qualification trial
is also a knockout one.
The ones who lose will be disqualified
from taking part in official contests.
Yes.
Don't worry.
You are in my team.
We won't lose.
Why am I with you?
Don't you want to be
in the same team with me?
That's not important.
No matter which team I am in,
I don't want to be
the one who drags all down.
Lin Xi.
Personally speaking,
I'm happy that
you can join the varsity.
But the reason
why I recommended you
is that I really find you suitable for it.
Because you enjoy it and do well in math,
and you are a good contestant.
I hope
you can keep on enjoying what you like
and working hard for it.
These are my real thoughts.
Xiao Xi.
I heard you become a substitute.
Congratulations.
Thank you, brother Qin Yue.
Maybe you don't know that
I was ever Jiang Zheng Han's referrer.
Yes.
Also the "Party A" to me.
Never thought that
you're on such good terms.
Before some coincidence appeared,
we were.
Am I here at an incorrect time?
We all come for training.
It doesn't matter.
Oh, Lin Xi.
Have you decided whom to team up with
in the qualification trial?
Xiao Xi.
Brother Qin Yue,
I've promised
to join Jiang Zheng Han's team.
Oh, that's right.
That's good.
Qin Yue, you can be with Shi Ying.
And we two a team.
Lin Xi was chosen by Professor Shi.
Leader Jiang,
you've got another capable team member.
I am still weak in programming.
I need to learn from you, senior.
Hmm...
Now that we're not in the same team,
we will be opponents
in the future competition.
It'll be a cruel contest.
Only two teams can be qualified.
So, if you want me to teach you something,
maybe after the contest.
This contest is only for
internal selection.
Its main goal is for
learning from each other.
Xiao Xi.
If you have any questions,
ask me at any time.
Xia Lin Xi is my team member.
I'll be responsible for her.
Let's go to the library.
Um, it seems that Leader Qin
is late again.
I've been in the lead for years,
so it's nothing if I'm late once.
Don't worry.
In this qualification trial,
we can beat Jiang Zheng Han's team.
In fact I don't care
whether we can win or not.
If I win,
Xiao Xi cannot join the varsity.
Let's start training.
Student Cafeteria Building A
All vegetables?
You can eat this.
No, no, no, this is for you.
You're too thin.
You should eat more meat.
You can get enough energy to study
when you are full.
-I just want to borrow a meal card.
-I'll eat this.
-Eat.
-Why so stingy?
Sis Xia, brother Zheng.
Zhang Huai Wu?
I've been trying to borrow a meal card.
I am lucky to meet you two.
I'm starving!
Why do you come to our school so often?
It's a long story.
I've put down roots in Jing Hua University.
I live in brother Zheng's dorm.
Put down roots?
Don't you have lessons?
Forget the lessons. I don't understand
what professors say anyhow.
They talk all nonsense in class.
I can't understand.
I'd rather learn from brother Zheng.
Am I right, brother Zheng?
Yes.
That makes sense.
Sis Xia.
Yes?
Your cafeteria
is much better than ours.
Look at the dishes.
The dishes look more delicious.
-I'll eat it. What?
-Zhang Huai Wu.
-It is for Xia Lin Xi.
-Sis Xia gave it to me.
-Sis Xia, right?
-Okay, okay, okay.
-Wait, I...
-Right?
-I can lend you my meal card.
-Right, right, right.
-Sis Xia just gave it to me.
-Here.
Enjoy your meal.
I'll buy another portion.
What are you looking at?
Brother Zheng,
should I call her Mrs. Jiang?
Eat your food.
Okay.
Library
What are you laughing at?
Don't you feel it's like
when we were in high school?
The period when I was your tutor.
What?
You mean I need to pay you?
For you, of course not.
Now, no matter what I do for you,
I do it willingly and for free.
Then, can you tell me
the potential security problems
of the singleton pattern
in a multi-threaded environment?
Alright, let me see.
Wait a minute.
Xia Lin Xi.
Can't you be attentive? Read it.
Look.
Xiao Xi.
Um?
Brother Qin Yue.
I was going to your dorm to see you.
I didn't expect to meet you here.
What's up?
Well...
Here is the thing.
I've made a summary of
all the tests of the varsity contests.
I think it may be helpful for you.
So,
I come to give it to you.
Thank you, brother Qin Yue.
But I won't accept it.
What Shi Ying said is reasonable.
We are in different teams.
If I use your team's learning materials,
it'll be unfair to other members.
But if I have any questions,
I'll ask you.
Just like when we were kids.
Okay.
Well...
I wasn't thoughtful enough.
I...
Brother Qin Yue.
Yes?
You've been taking care of me
all the time.
You're like a brother
who makes me feel easy
all the time.
Tomorrow is the date of the contest.
We should sleep earlier today.
See you tomorrow, brother Qin Yue.
Xiao Xi.
Um?
The contest tomorrow,
go for it.
I really wish you can
become a member of the varsity.
Thank you, brother Qin Yue.
Go back to rest early.
-Bye-bye.
Alas...
Jing Hua University,
ACP Qualifier
Jing Hua University
ACP ADOLESCENTS COMPUTER
PROGRAMMING CONTEST
Team member: Jiang Zheng Han
All the teams, enter please.
All the contestants, get ready please.
The contest will begin soon.
The points will be
recorded and accumulated.
One point for one problem solved.
The duration of the contest
is five hours.
We'll stop recording the points
in the last hour.
The first two teams gain the most points
can enter the next stage.
The teams can attack one another's
vulnerabilities by means of technology.
If succeeded, one point got.
Now, all the teams are ready.
The competition will begin.
Countdown begins.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
Go!
I am sure brother Zheng's team can win.
Don't worry.
Since there's Xiao Xi.
Right. Go for it!
Go for it!
Shen Wen Yue.
Hmm?
Why do you come?
You're also here?
Hey.
Sit here.
Alas!
You block others' view. Sit down!
Sit down. Sit down.
Hey.
Zhang, Zhang, who's she?
You know her?
Goddess of our university, Shen Wen Yue.
You know what?
She is of Cheng University's computer varsity.
She became the fastest to solve problems
when she was a freshman.
-A geek of technology.
-Hey.
Hi.
No.1: Qin Yue's team
No.2: Jiang Zheng Han's team
No.3: Gao Chen's team
We can use Hash table
to deal with the data structure here.
Try it by yourself.
Ask me if you need my help.
Here is the result of this problem.
Senior.
Well, input the data
according to Qin Yue's answers.
Okay.
Check the data.
All contestants, attention please.
Now we're in the last hour.
We'll stop accumulating points.
No.1: Qin Yue's team
No.2: Jiang Zheng Han's team
No.3: Gao Chen's team
Now the first three teams will
compete for the first two places.
The first place, Qin Yue's team,
their points are very close to
that of the second place,
Jiang Zheng Han's team.
Gao Chen's team is experienced
and performing steadily.
Jiang Zheng Han's team and Gao Chen's
must compete fiercely
with Qin Yue's to rise in rank.
They have to fight for the decisive point
and for the second place.
It's a pity the third place
will be knocked out.
Senior, someone is attacking our program.
Who?
Gao Chen's team that ranks the third.
What should we do?
We must fix the program.
Get ready to defend
the attack from Gao Chen's team.
-Okay.
-Wait.
We should tolerate Gao Chen's attack.
What do you mean?
The score of Jiang Zheng Han's team
is the closest to ours.
If Gao Chen can get one point,
the two teams have to fight.
Then our team can be definitely safe.
Hurry up, Chen Yi Chuan.
Now,
Gao Chen's team has attacked
Qin Yue's using their best strategy.
Can Qin Yue's team
defend the attack successfully?
This becomes a highlight
of the competition.
Now, let's observe
Jiang Zheng Han's team.
What on earth
will they react to the attack?
Will they continue to
compete with Qin Yue's team,
or attack the program of Gao Chen's team,
so as to keep the second place?
Hold on. Don't be disturbed.
Will they get an opportunity
by using tactics?
Brother Zheng, something is wrong.
Here is the situation,
even if we get another point,
as long as Qin Yue's team
makes concessions for them,
we still have to compete for No.2
against Gao Chen's team.
On the contrary, Qin Yue's team...
If we can win now,
why do we choose to wait?
No. You...
Don't you get what I said?
I said maybe Qin Yue's team
is making concessions for them!
Jiang Zheng Han, Duan Ning's right.
We should...
I don't believe he would do so.
Duan Ning, continue to attack the program.
Lin Xi.
Try to solve the last question by yourself.
Let me read the next one, okay?
-Let me have a try.
-This problem...
The time is limited. Hurry up!
Okay.
We're out of time.
How long do you need, Mrs. Jiang?
You must solve it quickly.
Concentrate on it.
Yes.
Go for it.
Look here.
In the problem, the char sequence...
I've finished all.
Good.
Shi Ying, this one.
How is it?
I...
Lin Xi.
It's the answer for linearity.
Check the data.
Give me all the problems about
dynamic programming of the database.
Okay.
Brother Zheng, come and check this for me.
Here.
Hello! Would you come and have a look?
Does it break the rules?
Well, let me see.
Look here.
About the sequence numbers,
just output them.
And...
Chen Yi Chuan.
Fix the program.
Ah?
Qin Yue, you...
We're in a competition.
There aren't any tactics.
We must deal with the bug we've got.
Points calculating:
Jiang Zheng Han's team
Qin Yue's team
Gao Chen's team
Okay.
It's a surprise that
Jiang Zheng Han fought back head-on
No.1: Jiang Zheng Han's team
with toughness by his excellent ability.
He became the champion finally,
while Qin Yue's team got the second place.
Wow.
Yeah.
Jiang Zheng Han. Jiang Zheng Han!
-We won!
Yeah!
We won!
Brother Zheng! Sis Xia!
Jiang Zheng Han! Jiang Zheng Han!
Qin Yue.
Xiao Chuan.
Sis Xia.
Let's go, Xiao Man.
I said you would win.
Thank you for the last point.
It's a competition.
You won. You're welcome.
Me too.
I was too nervous to work properly.
Xiao Xi.
Xiao Man, Qiu Yan.
Professor, are we cool?
Yeah!
Wow, you're awesome.
Hey, you young men
should have a celebration.
-Yes.
-I won't join you. I'm leaving.
It's your treat next time, professor.
-Okay.
-No problem.
-Bye, professor.
-Bye-bye, Professor Shi.
-Jiang Zheng Han, you're great.
-You're awesome.
I know.
Did you see how cool I was just now?
Handsome?
I don't know.
Xiao Xi, I noticed Xiao Chuan
was very disappointed just now.
Is it because
he only got the second place?
Xiao Man, can you not only care about him alone?
I'm still here.
I understand
such a feeling.
Yo, brother Zheng.
Great sweet words.
Well, you did a good job today.
Let's dine out together.
Okay.
Where's Zhang Huai Wu?
He went to the so-called goddess.
Forget him.
I also have something to deal with.
See you.
Beauty, see you.
Alright.
Well...
I'll put something in the dorm first.
Then see you later.
Jiang... Leader Jiang.
Yes.
Member Xia.
See you later.
Leader Jiang, bye-bye.
Wow.
-Member Xia.
-What's going on now?
Let's go.
Hurry up, Xiao Xi.
Talent Jiang, well done in the contest.
Thank you.
Jiang Zheng Han.
Do you miss me?
Shen Wen Yue, why are you here?
Surprise?
I've been looking for you for long.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪In the long corridor of youth♪
♪Stored so many secrets♪
♪The unmodified dreams and thoughts♪
♪Were all on our faces proudly♪
♪The direction that leads to wider sky♪
♪Was the place that
we promised to go together♪
♪Your warmth filled my luggage♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that
you'll always accompany me to look up♪
♪We occasionally got hurt on the way♪
♪Just to spend all my time with you♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that our love never changed♪