Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪From morning to night,
my heart flutters for you♪
♪You are my everyday joy♪
♪Even when you appear in my dream♪
♪When I open my eyes, I still miss you♪
♪You are the blue sky
in the early morning♪
♪I feel shy
as if I'm kissed by the sunset♪
♪I know you will wink at me in my dream♪
♪When I wake up, I still miss you♪
♪You are the sweet glass of water
in the early morning♪
♪I immerse myself in your freshness♪
♪You are in every scene
that I've ever imagined♪
♪I'm waiting for you to
appear at the next moment♪
♪LaLaLa...♪
♪I wake up and fall into
your arm without a care♪
Forever Love
Episode 14
Snoopy Represents My Heart
Isn't it nice here?
There's a lot of space here,
and it's close to our university.
Let's start sorting things out.
Wait a minute.
Come here with me.
What's up?
Listen to me,
this is a French window
with great day-lighting.
I settled on this after a careful study.
What's wrong?
You must make sure
to close this window
every time you go out.
You're on a low floor. It's dangerous.
The bedroom?
-What do you think of the bedroom?
-It's fine.
The closet is quite big, too.
Good.
What's this? The bathroom?
How is it?
Good.
Over there is the kitchen.
Look at this.
This is the gas valve.
Always turn it off before you go out.
Otherwise, it would...
Boom!
Gas valve...
However,
you don't cook,
so you could just leave it closed.
I can learn to cook.
All right.
But you live here alone.
I'm still worried.
I think it's not so good.
What's not so good?
Think about it...
Why this is not so good?
Just think about it.
There might be rats and cockroaches.
When you're alone,
they might swish under your feet,
and climb on you when you're asleep.
Besides, you are a girl, and alone.
What if when you're out there alone,
and you got
stalked by some pervert?
He might just
climb up the pipe
and get in through the window,
and then show up
in front of you all of a sudden.
Stop it, stop it.
Then...
-What should I do?
-It's OK.
I can actually move in with you.
You can't do this. We're just freshmen.
Does that mean
I can when we're sophomores?
No, you can't.
At least...
At least until we're juniors.
You always carry it with you?
How about throwing it away?
Why?
Because I envy him.
For what?
Because he could accompany you every day,
but I can't.
Jiang Zheng Han, you're really
more and more shameless.
From Zhishu Bu Dali:
It's almost the end of the month.
When will our codes be ready?
Or you forget your GitHub password?
If it can't be debugged before the 29th,
we won't pay you the balance.
Can you help write api and texts?
Urgent! We need your help here...
So many people asking for your help?
Do you want to have a break?
I have two more jobs and
an assignment to hand in today.
I might need to do this all night.
Do you want me to help you?
No need.
Don't worry.
I'll go back when you fall asleep.
I... I didn't mean to rush you.
I know.
But it's so late after all.
It's not as safe as
the dorm here by yourself.
Don't worry.
I'll go back to our university
when you're asleep.
Then you can work here first.
I can't help you with programming.
But,
it's amazing to
make money through programming.
Why did I hear a trace of
worship from your words?
Stop it.
All right.
Do you like programming?
Why do you ask this all of a sudden?
I mean,
if you learn something
because you like it, it'll be
a great impetus to support you.
When I was in Grade 12,
my family needed a lot of money.
But at that time,
I didn't even graduate from high school,
so I couldn't find any jobs.
So at that time,
programming was all about
a way to get money.
But that pressure is gone now, and
the technology is changing
with each passing day.
I think I need to explore and learn more.
Anyway, I feel like
it's an interesting process.
Is this PHP language hard to learn?
It's hard for me anyway.
It should be
not that hard for you.
Would you like to teach me?
Well, how are you gonna
pay for the tuition fee?
I can give you money.
Actually, except for money,
it could be something else.
What?
Get back to your work.
I'll go to sleep now.
So early?
Why are you going to bed so early?
Why should you care what time I go to bed?
Well, you go to bed first.
I can't concentrate
if you keep staying here.
Good night.
Don't stay up too late.
OK.
Help me give Professor Shi
the USB drive on the desk.
It's my homework.
I got something else to do first.
Professor,
here's Jiang Zheng Han's homework.
Jiang told me that. Just put it here.
OK.
Professor, then I'll leave now.
Xia.
Come.
Sit down.
Please tell Jiang that
the final of
the ACP Contest is in two days.
He should be well-prepared.
Some well-known companies
of the industry will be there,
with internships to offer.
If he got chosen by any one of them,
his salary would be much more
than his current programming jobs.
And it'll be paid off
by each project done.
Then he wouldn't have to hold onto
his broken computer any longer.
His computer isn't good enough?
It's not "not good enough",
but not good at all!
A work that normally takes two hours
has to cost at least
half a day with his computer.
I suggested to give him a new one.
But that brat refused me, alas...
I see, professor. Then I'll leave now.
Okay, off you go.
Love isn't something
you can buy at your wish.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Here you are.
Thanks.
Huai Wu.
You know, Chuan is already an adult now.
But why is he still so fond of Snoopy?
He's childish.
He's into it since high school.
What about Gu Xiao Man?
Did she know that back in high school?
So,
they started it since high school?
Yeah, they did. Listen to me,
at that time, Chen Yi Chuan
even wrote a love letter to Gu Xiao Man.
That caused a big fuss in our class.
-Chen Yi Chuan?
-Yeah, it's true.
I can't believe he did that.
It's not what you think.
Listen to me,
Chen Yi Chuan actually tried to
apologize to Gu Xiao Man. But...
Just tell me.
But Gu Xiao Man took it as
a confession of his love to her.
So that's the case.
Fortune favors fools,
and he's one of them.
He knows nothing about love.
But he's loved by such a good girl.
And she even loves Snoopy because of him.
What a pure love it must be!
You... You sound like
a little envious.
Of course, listen to me,
I, Prince Duan,
have dated countless girls.
Why didn't anyone of them
treat me like that?
All right.
Don't be envious.
Listen to me,
Chen Yi Chuan has no EQ at all.
It must be hard for him to get married.
I'm sure he'll be single all his life.
He is a typical
love herbicide.
What do you mean by that?
Kills love from the root.
Instant noodles?
You're all here.
Brother Zheng.
WetChat message from Xia Lin Xi
Come to my house in the evening.
-I have something for you.
-Chen Yi Chuan had a fever today.
We carried him to the infirmary,
on our shoulder.
Is he still alive?
Yes.
I'll say it.
Well, brother Zheng.
What did you have
for breakfast this morning?
What did you eat?
Breakfast? Bag and porridges.
Buns and porridge.
You got a new idea for that project?
You got a new idea?
A little bit.
Which stage are you and sis Xia at?
Which stage?
Just... Kiss is done.
Wow!
Take this guy down!
-Take my waving kicks!
-No, no.
Take my one-point finger!
-Tell us about that!
-Why should you hide it from us?!
One-point finger, one-point finger.
Okay, okay, I'll tell you.
Really?
-Yeah, yeah.
-Really?
You sit down first.
-Hurry, hurry.
-Come on.
-Come on!
-Hurry up!
We're in love with each other.
Student Cafeteria Building A
Cross-bridge Rice Noodles
Happiness Bento
Gu Xiao Man, you eat so much?
You are indeed a pig.
No, I bought this for you.
Aren't you just
recovered from a serious illness?
I wanted you to
eat more to get more nutrition.
So I bought so much food.
Please eat more, okay?
What is all this?
I'm almost full. This is too much.
How is it? Tastes good?
Sounds like it's you who cooked all this.
Xiao Chuan. Xiao Chuan.
Do you like that Snoopy doll?
What Snoopy?
Why do you mention that all of a sudden?
I like it as long as it's Snoopy.
Great! I knew you would like it,
Xiao Chuan.
Eat more, eat more.
To replenish all the energy
that you wasted on the illness.
You don't have to remind me of that.
Xiao Chuan,
this chicken fillet looks delicious.
I'd like to try it, too.
Get it by yourself if you wanna eat.
What are you doing?
It's unhygienic.
Chuan.
Xiao Man.
What are you guys eating?
This beef looks good. Is it tasty?
No.
What happened?
No idea. You know,
she always loses her temper for no reason.
Alas, what's wrong?
I think Xiao Man is not bad.
Not bad?
She just follows me around.
Clingy girls are
more suitable for a relationship.
What do you know?
Judging from your reaction,
are you trapped in love?
What are you talking about?
To be honest, Chen Yi Chuan.
Are you a man?
The girl is so initiative.
Visited your ward and gave you a gift.
Why don't you give some reaction?
How did you also know that?
Of course! You know my capacities.
Don Juan at Jing Hua University.
Now beg me,
then I'll perhaps give you some advice.
Beg you?
Just save your bad tricks
to those brainless ones.
-The woman worthy of me...
-Has yet to be born, right?
Listen to me, Chuan.
That's not a good thought.
You'd better quit it.
In my opinion, a man like you
could not get married
even reaches the age of 40.
Yi Chuan.
Are you feeling better?
I'm much better.
I feel completely alive now.
That's good to hear.
Then I'll leave you two talking.
Senior. Senior.
Thank you.
I'll keep fighting with Snoopy's spirit.
Okay... Keep it up then.
Senior is really
a beautiful and talented woman.
Chen Yi Chuan. Chen Yi Chuan.
Come here, come.
You like this type?
Of course.
A smart woman like senior Shi Ying
is worthy of me.
Enough, enough.
Stop watching. She's gone.
Listen, judging from
my years of experience,
this goddess
is not as simple as what we can see.
You gotta be careful.
What do you know?
The little fool adores a senior.
Where did he get the confidence?
Do you have time now?
Let's meet.
Running downstairs.
Running downstairs?
I'll come to you.
Xiao Chuan.
Your leg is still not recovered?
Um.
Hey.
I'll be fine
soon after receiving your concern.
The clothes you're wearing today
is quite complicated.
You look so beautiful today.
I know.
You like my dress today, don't you?
I mean...
You don't have to
dress up so complicated, okay?
You're beautiful
even if you don't dress up.
I know I'm beautiful
no matter I dress up or not.
The moon is so beautiful today.
Isn't your leg still not recovered?
Stop running. Be careful! Hey!
Xiao Xi.
Xiao Man, what's up?
Be ready for this.
I'm going to tell you a big good news!
What's up?
You could never expect this.
My wait pays off.
The sago cycas is blossoming.
Chen Yi Chuan
confessed his love to me.
You'd better tell me all about
how he told you that exactly.
You can never imagine that.
He used a classic allusion
of Natsume Soseki.
"The moon is so beautiful tonight."
He confessed his love to me
in an euphemistic way.
Well...
I don't mean anything else.
But I'm just worried about his low EQ.
And he is not so good at
literature as you think.
With a low EQ and
unable to express himself well,
he could only turn to
"the moon is so beautiful tonight",
instead of "I love you",
to implicitly express his love to me.
Well, why does that mean "I love you"?
When Natsume Soseki
was a teacher of
English translation in Japan,
one of his students translated
"I Love You" directly.
But he felt that love should be implicit.
Doesn't that sound exactly like Chuan?
So he told the student
it's better to express love
by saying
"the moon is so beautiful tonight".
That's what Xiao Chuan did.
Xiao Man, calm down first.
You know, back in high school...
It's just that...
Are you sure he knows the allusion?
Well...
I'll tell you what I'm thinking.
As I know about that blockhead,
it's likely that
he was just talking about the moon.
No way.
Do you remember
I told you I gave him a Snoopy?
I asked him,
and he said he loved it very much.
This time, I won't misunderstand it again.
Really?
Xia Lin Xi.
I think...
We have to end our friendship
and start changing it into kinship.
-Come on, be happy for me.
-I...
Next, I'm going to
study advanced mathematics.
I gotta make myself smarter
to protect Chen Yi Chuan's dignity,
and for the sake of the average IQ
of our children in the future.
Okay?
I have to go.
Yes! Love you.
LIDE TREE PEOPLE
Hello, Chen Yi Chuan. Where are you?
Are you being kidding or serious?
If you're kidding,
you shouldn't accept her gift.
That you told her you liked it
would make her misunderstand you.
It's my own business
to like something or not.
It's not up to you.
You...
Princes Royal
How did you also know that?
If you're serious,
you should treat her well.
I'm serious, of course.
Really?
Yeah.
Then...
Then don't hurt her again.
Be mature.
Hello.
Aunt.
She's still here.
I don't know where she has gone now.
What?
OK, I'll take a look.
How did they all know
about me and senior Shi Ying?
It's time for dinner, Lin Xi.
Lin Xi.
Come here to have dinner.
What's up?
What are you doing?
Looking at me with a weird smile.
What's up?
I'll give you a present.
Whatever it is, you just accept it, OK?
Why do you give me a gift all of a sudden?
What gift? Say it first.
I bought a computer for you.
-This computer...
-I didn't use my parents' money.
I used my scholarship to buy this.
Xiao Xi.
No, this is too expensive.
Go return it for refund.
Hey.
I've torn up the invoice, no refund now.
You can't return it now.
You have to keep it.
What's the smile about?
You know what, even without the invoice,
if I put it on the market,
I can sell it at the original price
within a month.
You just sell my present for you
to some stranger like this?
You can give it back to me in the future.
If... If you insist to give it back to me,
I'll throw it away.
What are you smiling about?
I... I didn't.
Jiang Zheng Han,
you don't believe me, do you?
Watch this.
What are you doing, Xia Lin Xi.
If you don't take it,
I'll throw it out from here.
I'll throw it away now.
Okay, okay, I'll take it. I will.
Who told you I don't want it?
Give it to me.
Then I'll just take it.
Come with me.
What's wrong?
Come here.
Come here first.
What do you want?
Don't look.
IOU: Jiang Zheng Han
temporarily borrows RMB 20,000...
Don't look.
I won't look.
Okay.
Jiang Zheng Han temporarily borrows
RMB 20,000 from Xia Lin Xi.
Promises to pay it off in five years,
with RMB 50,000 of interest,
a wedding ring,
a marriage certificate and
a property ownership certificate.
All to be paid off
at a time with no delay allowed.
Promise maker, Jiang Zheng Han.
Who wants your marriage certificate
and property ownership certificate?
This is my
contract to you.
I'll give you the money and myself.
Then I'll charge more interest.
If it's this kind of interest,
I don't mind paying more.
I'm scared to death.
Xia Lin Xi, why did you lock the door?
Open the door.
It's my cousin.
Hide yourself up.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪In the long corridor of youth♪
♪Stored so many secrets♪
♪The unmodified dreams and thoughts♪
♪Were all on our faces proudly♪
♪The direction that leads to wider sky♪
♪Was the place that
we promised to go together♪
♪Your warmth filled my luggage♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that
you'll always accompany me to look up♪
♪We occasionally got hurt on the way♪
♪Just to spend all my time with you♪
♪Search for
the distant place that we painted♪
♪With each other's simple courage♪
♪Get every answer for life♪
♪Taste bitterness and joy together♪
♪Never learned
the complicated calculations♪
♪I'd rather just believe my heart♪
♪Believe in the way that you called me♪
♪Believe that our love never changed♪