(Mao) ⟨ I was an ordinary office lady →
With my company's elite boss, drunkenly
I got married all of a sudden! ⟩
(Sou) Please marry me.
(Mao) ⟨ But this encounter wasn't a coincidence⟩
I will love only So-san for the rest of my life.
⟨ But...⟩
(Eiji) If you choose you →
So will lose everything.
(Sou) Did you do it? Answer!
(Eiji) She has woken up, and you should become an adult too.
(Mao) Don't come again, goodbye.
[I didn't like you]
(Mao) [with me →
Please divorce me
(cry)
>> Are you okay?
Are you okay? Shall we stand it up? Yeah?
Shall we stand it up?
Wipe it with this.
It's a pain if you catch a cold.
(Mao) Sorry.
(Mao) Thank you very much.
>> Oh? you….
Maybe Koshiba?
(Mao) Why did you say my name?
>> As expected!
I'm Fukuzumi Hanako.
You are my lifesaver.
(Mao) What?
♪～
(Mao) Sorry, thank you for the bath.
>> Are you warmed up? (Mao) Yes.
It smells amazing. >> You're hungry, aren't you?
It's messy, but sit there and wait.
(Mao) Yes.
Can I help you too?
(Mao) Is potatoes OK with 8 equal parts?
>> Yes That's right.
Yes, thank you.
Would you like to taste it? (Mao) Yes.
>> Yes. (Mao) Thank you.
>>What do you think? (Mao) Ah, it's tasty.
>> Ah, huh...
(Mao) Looks tasty. >> Now sit and sit.
(Mao) Yes.
Ah, thank you very much.
(Mao) Thank you so much, I'm really grateful for this.
>> That's fine, that kind of thing to do. (Mao) No.
>> It's me who says thank you.
(Mao) What?
>> Thanks to you for helping me five years ago →
I can stay healthy like this.
[Sound of falling] [Scream]
(Mao) [Are you okay? 〕
[Someone please call an ambulance! 」 (Female) [Yes]
(Mao) [Excuse me]
(Female) [A woman is in the emergency room]
(Mao) [Someone please bring me the AED, I think it's at the station]
>> [Station? 」 (Mao) 〔Please
〔１･２･３･４…〕
(Hanako's voice) I heard it later →
Thanks to your skillful rescue →
I was able to save my life.
At that time →
Thank you so much, really.
(Mao) That's good... I've been interested in it for a long time.
I'm really glad you're doing well.
>> Thank you.
Let's eat while it's warm.
(Mao) Yes.
(Eiji) It's rare, it's not like it's coming from you.
How was your overseas business trip?
(Sou) It was all up by you.
>> What is it?
I just fired an employee who embezzled it.
(Shu) I'm →
I have no intention of marrying anyone other than her.
>> If so →
You don't need this company.
Don't be swayed by temporary emotions.
She woke up.
You too →
Become an adult.
(Mao) Thank you. >> Have you calmed down a bit?
(Mao) Yes.
that….
It's me who has to say thank you.
>>Huh?
(Mao) Thanks to helping Hananoko that day →
It led to many encounters.
(So) [Mao joined the company, Masaya realized it immediately]
(Mao) [Ah! Because I was late for the day of the company's entrance ceremony? 〕
(Shu) [Yes]
(Mao) I was able to meet someone I really love.
>> The tears from earlier →
It has something to do with that person.
(Mao) I said goodbye.
>> Ah, yes...
(Mao) Cook dinner every day →
Eat together →
I wanted that kind of normal happiness.
(Mao) It didn't work.
But →
I was really depressed, but
My stomach is fine →
If you eat something delicious →
You can smile.
>> Food made with the other person in mind →
It's packed with lots of love →
Smiling flowers bloom.
(Sou) [Tasty! 〕
[It's the best dish I've ever had]
[I might not be able to eat anything other than Mao's homemade food]
♪～
(Mao) That's right.
>> I've heard what you've entered, but what are you planning to do now?
(Mao) I'm thinking of going back to the countryside.
>> Yes...
I hope there's something that can be of help.
(Mao) It's enough to meet him like this.
(Mao) Thank you so much.
♪～
(Mao) [Please divorce me]
(Mao) [Goodbye]
♪～
(Tsuruji) I was surprised that my sister was suddenly.
(Mao) Sorry I can take a little break.
(Hinako) Big sister, welcome back!
I'll do it, I'll do it. (Hinako) Already →
You're saying you shouldn't pamper a pregnant woman. Yes.
(Mao) Once again, congratulations on the baby, Ryuji Hinako.
>> Thank you.
But it's just my first time, so I'm excited.
I wish my sister was there. (Hinako) Really.
(Mao) That's good too.
>>Huh? (Mao) Hmm... Hey →
I have a place I want to go a little bit.
♪～
>> Sister, rest.
(Mao) Yes, I understand.
Ah, it's soaking. (Tsuyoshi) Hahaha...
No, I thought my sister would definitely take over as a farmer.
(Mao) Hey! I thought so too. >> Why wasn't it inherited?
(Mao) I want more people to eat our vegetables.
That's why Smile Foods came in.
>> I see.
So you can't join such a big company →
Sister is amazing. (Mao) No, no, Takatsugu is more amazing.
I go to the fields on rainy and windy days and provide for my family.
>> I'm still a lot.
I work hard every day, so I'm doing my best. (Mao) Yes.
>> But it's been so much fun lately.
I'm thinking of increasing the variety of vegetables from next year.
(Mao) Ah, that's fine. >> Right? (Mao) Yes.
>> Who is it? That face you never see.
(Mao) What's wrong?
(Kota) No, I heard that he's gone back to his parents' house.
See, I asked for the address before.
(Mao) Ah... I've made an appointment to meet my parents.
In the end, Kota was forced to take it off.
(Kota) Sorry.
(Mao) I'm sorry to have you come this far, but I don't have the money to lend you.
>> No, it's not that I came to borrow money.
(Mao) So what did you come for?
(A stomach throbbing sound)
Ah...
That's it... (The sound of my stomach pounding)
Sorry I haven't eaten anything since morning.
(Kota) I'll take it.
good….
Yeah….
(Mao) Is something really happening?
>>Huh?
(Mao) No, this is the first time I've been told that it's good.
(Mao) Are you okay?
>> Why didn't you realize it?
I've been spoiled by Mao for a long time.
♪～
(Choosening sound)
(Mao) Just a moment! Because I'm panicking to eat.
Thank you. (Mao) Be sure to be strong.
>> Mao Something has changed.
(Mao) What?
>> I thought I was even more depressed.
When I was dating →
I feel like a different person.
something….
I've become stronger.
(Mao) If so →
Thanks to someone.
>>Are there anyone?
(Mao) Yes.
A important person.
>> I see...
Mao, that's it...
(Eiji) [If you say something unnecessary →
You won't be able to stay at work either.
(Mao) Is there really something wrong with you?
>> No, it's nothing.
(Mao) That's right.
Then, when I eat, I'll go home.
Ah, Kota.
(Mao) Work →
good luck.
♪～
>> What are you doing? Me...
(Yuka) Manager Ando.
(Sho) Something? (Yuka) I have a story.
There's no way someone like Koshiba would steal money!
(Sou) Ah. >> I want to find the real culprit.
Director Ando will also help you, right?
(Shu) But why on me?
>> Because →
The manager is the same as me, right?
(Sou) Are you the same?
>> You like Koshiba-san.
I always looked at Koshiba.
I've not been well since I returned to Japan.
If you ask me, it's a waste.
(Shu) Da... Dada leak?
>> That said, it seems that the club manager will be married to Higashi-san.
I don't really know, but there are a lot of things, I'm sure.
Manager Ando.
Please save Koshiba.
I saw it.
The night before that money was lost →
Takada-san, who was on holiday that day, →
I'll come out of work late at night.
(Sou) What?
(knock)
Excuse me.
(Kota) Manager Ando: What?
(Sou) Did you do it?
>>Huh?
(Sou) What did you do to Mao?
>> Mao? (Sou) Answer!
>> Manager: What is your relationship with Mao?
(Mao) [If that's the case, thanks to someone]
[The important person]
>> Is that what it is?
I met Koshiba today.
(Sou) What?
>> The reason why Koshiba was fired is not just about money.
(Sou) What does it mean?
(Kota's voice) Cutting the contract between my family's farmer and my company →
I was threatened by the president.
(chime)
(Mao) Yes.
(Sou) ＼Mao／
Have you heard it?
Why didn't you say that your dad was threatening you?
＼Because I'll do something／
I will never let Mao's family get in trouble.
(Sou) Mao!
(Mao) Please go home.
It's annoying.
This is not just a problem for us.
(Sou) It's our problem!
Me →
I came to ask Mao what she really felt.
I'm not changing forever.
10 years ago →
Just like when I met Mao.
I've always loved Mao.
＼It doesn't matter about the company! /
As long as Mao is there →
That's fine.
(Sou) I want to be with Mao.
(Masaya) [If you do that, Smile Foods will change]
[To prevent it →
I have to have So be in the office for sure.
(Mao) If you abandon the company for such irresponsible reasons...
(Mao) Really about you →
I'll hate it.
Please protect the company.
(Mao) Don't come again.
\Goodbye/
(Sou) I won't give up.
(Sho) It's sure to...
I'll come to pick up Mao again.
(Sobbing)
(Shop clerk) This will be here.
(Sou) Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Sorry.
(Kosuke) It's all here.
Finally, tomorrow's 50th anniversary party →
We are pleased to announce So and Mika's engagement.
The future of the two →
To celebrate the merger of Smile Foods and EstoCampani.
cheers.
(Everyone) Cheers.
♪～
(Eiji) I'm looking forward to it. (Kosuke) Yes, I'm looking forward to it.
(Tsuruji) Sister!
Sister is tough.
(Mao) What's wrong?
>> This.
♪～
(Secretary) President Notifications to all over the country have been completed.
I understand.
♪～
(Tsuji) Smile Foods →
I'm gonna cancel the contract...
♪～