THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
EPISODE 7
I got a call from Banseok.
Your son's heart condition
has deteriorated.
If he doesn't get a transplant right away,
it might stop working anytime.
It's an obsidian blade.
It's much sharper than it looks.
Some doctors still use it as a scalpel
for surgeries that require precision.
It's not a metal,
so it gets past a metal detector too.
ALWAYS REALIZE THE VALUE OF LIFE
All good. You may go in.
Now, talk.
What do you want to say to me
about the case from six years ago?
Sorry.
I didn't want to do this to you.
What?
Nam Junhwan.
If you stab me now, your son will die too.
How did you…
Nam Hyukchul.
Drop your weapon.
Answer me.
How did you know about my son?
How could I not?
He's the only child
between you and your wife.
Three years.
That's how long it took
for Seokju to find a donor.
Do you think
your son could wait that long?
I can save
Nam Junhwan.
Nam Hyukchul.
Three years?
He doesn't have that much time.
-Nam Hyukchul!
-That's why
I have to kill you!
Nam Hyukchul!
Cho Junghyun is coming here.
I just got a call from the office.
Cho Junghyun
is here to see you.
-Why would she come here?
-Why else?
She is trying to save her son.
Just like you.
She knows that you killed Park Kitae.
-That's why she's coming.
-Don't try to fool me!
She would never come here. Never!
Hyukchul! Don't do it.
Don't do it.
If you kill him now,
Junhwan will be in greater danger.
You choose.
Whether you'll just sit
and watch your son die
or put your last hope in me.
Are you all right?
Get up.
Get up, Hyukchul!
Prosecutor Geum,
could you please give us a minute?
It's bleeding quite a bit.
Shouldn't you go get it treated?
It's okay. I can handle this.
-Can you do this for me?
-Sure.
It was close.
If I had gotten there even a second later…
But you came just in time.
And thanks to you, I'm fine.
Do you think
Nam Hyukchul will do what we want?
We should hope so.
What's going on?
Why… Why would you come here?
I told you,
we should never see each other again.
If people were to find out
about me and Gu Jingi--
So it is true.
Director Gu Jingi
ordered you to kill Dr. Park Kitae.
Dr. Han knows everything.
He knows how I helped Director Gu Jingi
and removed the patient's heart too.
Then you should've just let me.
-You should've just let me kill him.
-Then,
the chance for Junhwan's survival
goes down too.
I came to save our child.
Just like you.
Junhwan won't last much longer like this.
-He could die.
-That's…
That's why we should ask Gu Jingi
to get him one soon by any means.
Yes, of course.
But what if he can't?
We need a backup plan.
If it appears that
we might side with Dr. Han,
Director Gu Jingi would be
pressured to get him a heart soon.
If not,
Junhwan can get the surgery then.
We can choose
whoever offers
a higher chance of saving our child.
RECORDS MANAGEMENT ROOM
INTERROGATION ROOM
He needs some time to think.
Once you get
your medical license restored,
let's talk again.
I'll give it more thought too
on whether we would choose surgery
or a heart transplant.
PRISONER TRANSPORT
Before the upcoming murder trial
for Park Kitae,
we need him to confess that
Gu Jingi ordered him to commit murder.
It's going to be a race against time.
Now tell me.
How do you plan
to restore your medical license?
I made a deal with Jayden.
While he is in Korea,
I'll be his legal advisor.
In return, he'll restore my license.
Isn't it payback
for saving him from drug overdose?
I know you can't answer me.
Attorney-client privilege is a basic ethic
that lawyers must follow.
But I can't
cooperate blindly either.
So let me meet Jayden.
I'll hear from him directly.
Failed?
He failed even though I set up
a perfect opportunity for him?
I'll have to confirm the details,
but Nam Hyukchul returned
to prison for sure.
Contact the medical director
and find out what happened.
Since his only child's life
is on the line,
I doubt he would betray me.
But if he did, by a chance in a million,
I'll need to keep his mouth shut.
Understood, sir.
Please enjoy.
My goodness, Hyunseong. What a surprise.
You said it'll be a casual dinner,
but this place is quite fancy.
I wanted some brownie points
and to apologize for what happened.
You are still worried about that?
I forgot about it already.
Let me go touch up my makeup.
Sure, go ahead.
What a clichéd proposal.
It suits Hyunseong.
Don't be nervous.
Are you ready?
Play music as soon as she enters.
She is coming.
I apologize for surprising you,
but I couldn't wait any longer.
We began to meet because of our fathers,
but I want to choose my future
of my own volition.
Forever,
be my woman.
I will be your man.
I never thought I would receive
such a confession today.
It's very touching,
but I can't accept it yet.
-"Yet"?
-Yet.
You and I
still have a lot to achieve.
The man I want to spend
the rest of my life with
isn't the Director
of Planning and Coordination.
Are you asking me to become
the chairman of the foundation?
No.
I'm asking you to surpass that position.
Surpass even your father.
-It has been a while.
-Director Gu.
Are you studying?
It's an SAT course.
Although my departure has been delayed,
I shouldn't get behind any further.
I am proud of you.
But you shouldn't overexert yourself.
I won't.
Let's take a look.
EF is 70%.
As for IVSD…
Oh, no.
It became thicker.
There is SAM too.
Don't worry.
Let's increase the dose.
I don't see Chief Cho.
She is usually here all day long
outside her working hours.
Is something up?
She said she would come late today.
She has to meet up with a friend.
I see.
A friend.
Director Gu.
How did you…
I realized
that I have been too neglectful.
From now on,
I will oversee Junhwan's treatment
and be more attentive.
I will have to increase the dose.
The heart wall shouldn't thicken
before transplantation.
But if he develops a tolerance…
What is there to worry about?
He will get a transplant before then.
BANSEOK UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
Don't you know that
such a thing as a personal life exists?
I didn't even work overtime
when I was on Wall Street.
I am sorry. It's a pressing matter.
It looks that way.
You are the one who stopped me
from entering the penthouse that day.
Correct. That's my job.
Come to think of it, it's a bit strange.
You stopped me
as if something big was going on.
But once I entered,
you simply stood and watched.
It seemed like
you had stopped me for a show.
I don't know what you mean.
I am not fluent in Korean.
I understand.
It's not something you can answer.
They are here.
Good work.
You can go now.
Okay.
Please sit down.
Prosecutor, you wanted to see me.
Yes. I wanted to put an end
to what happened the last time.
Put an end?
Didn't we do that the last time?
It was your misunderstanding.
Naloxone.
I found it in the bedroom.
It's a medicine
that is used for a drug overdose.
Please don't misunderstand.
I wanted to arrest you with this evidence,
but Mr. Han stopped me.
Are you saying you want to investigate me
at this point?
No. I don't care
whether you did drugs or not.
I want to know
with what purpose
you dragged us into this.
It's a popular phrase in Korea as well.
It's my favorite saying.
The winner takes it all.
I will enter into a new contract
with Chairman Gu Jingi.
Then I will take more shares if the stock
prices fall for Banseok R and D Center.
If you join forces to reveal
the evil deeds of Chairman Gu Jingi
and Banseok University Medical Center,
it will help me greatly.
So using us to make the stock prices drop
is your purpose.
Correct.
I will secure as many shares as possible
by making the stock prices drop
and have Banseok R and D Center
belong to Honours Hand.
Does it make you uncomfortable?
Despite being your enemy,
the medical group represents Korea.
So perhaps you don't want
a foreign company to take over.
Not at all.
Even if that happens,
it will be a price for the sin.
Now,
let's hear what your purpose is.
Is it revenge
on Chairman Gu Jingi
for killing your family?
It's what the great president of the US,
Abraham Lincoln once said.
However, I disagree.
Killing the dog won't cure
the physical wound,
but it will cure the emotional wound.
Revenge is the best way
of proving oneself.
After a successful deal,
Viking warriors clinked the cups.
The moment the cups clinked,
drinks overflew and mixed.
So it was a ritual of trust
to prove it was not poisonous.
From here on out,
you must share all of your plans
about Banseok with me through Mr. Han.
Of course.
There can't be any secrets among us.
Cheers.
Are you expecting someone?
No. I'll go check.
You didn't call. What's up?
I wanted to see you.
And I have to tell you something too.
I can't right now. I'm with some people.
Some people? Who? It's pretty late.
My lawyer, Han Yihan,
and Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong
that Gu Hyunseong brought the other night.
Why are they here together?
I'll explain later. You should go for now.
If they see us out here,
it won't be good for either of us.
No. I must see them too.
Your lawyer already knows about us.
And I'm also curious why that prosecutor
came back again.
-Yuna.
-I'm disappointed.
Don't tell me you didn't think
I would be able to handle this.
Don't worry.
I lived my whole life
as a daughter of a diplomat.
Thanks to that,
I'm good at dealing with people.
And this is important to me too.
I can't let you always be my middle man.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lim Yuna,
the director of Banseok R and D Center.
I'm Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong.
And you…
We've met before, right?
Nice to see you again.
What brings you here?
I needed to discuss the new drug
the center is developing.
It must be important
that you came to his house
at this late hour.
I don't like my work piling up.
I could ask you the same thing.
I would like to know why you're here.
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you
the details of my work.
I'm here on duty.
Then let me ask you a different question.
What's your relationship
with Mr. Han?
Why? Is your relationship
strictly professional as well?
We were once engaged.
But now,
our relationship is purely professional.
All right.
Why don't we end our meeting here?
Now that we've cleared up
our misunderstanding.
-Sure.
-I'll call you.
To thank you for helping me that day.
Let me treat you to a meal
when you're free.
There's something I want to discuss too.
Okay.
What's wrong?
-Did something happen?
-No. Nothing happened.
I'll get going too.
And we should steer clear
of each other for the time being.
Why is that?
I need time to sort out my thoughts.
Time to evaluate…
what I really want.
Sure. You should do that.
What? You openly proposed to Director Lim
at a restaurant on the dock?
Yes.
The jazz quartet and the proposal ring
were perfect.
What was the problem?
Was getting on one knee too much?
Come on. That was so awful.
You're not some knight who lost a war.
You should've proposed, not begged.
Did you do something wrong?
Then what should I have done?
You shouldn't do
what you want for the proposal.
You must do what she wants.
Exactly.
How can I find out what she wants?
Gosh.
I shouldn't know the answer to that.
It's not my proposal.
Besides, if you don't know what she wants,
it's too soon to propose.
Gosh.
If I surpass my father,
will she really say yes then?
-Your father?
-Yes.
That's what she said.
She told me to surpass my father.
Then you must work hard.
Rest up.
Goodness. He's so dense.
If she actually liked him,
the place wouldn't matter.
She would've even said yes here.
Try it in the elevator.
She would've been thrilled.
Thank you.
I'll need to work a lot with Jayden
going forward.
This way, everything will be in the open.
Don't thank me. It's part of my job too.
Earlier,
why did you tell her that?
Because it's true.
There's no reason to hide it.
She needs time to think?
NAM HYUKCHUL
MEDICAL DEVICE ENTREPRENEUR
He needs some time to think.
Once you get
your medical license restored,
let's talk again.
I'll give it more thought too
CHO JUNGHYUN'S EX-HUSBAND,
MURDERED PARK KITAE
on whether we would choose surgery
or a heart transplant.
GU HYUNSEONG, LEE DOHYUNG
PARK KITAE, CHO JUNGHYUN
"You are subpoenaed to appear in court
as a key witness of Gil Soyeon's
malpractice suit against Banseok…"
Ms. Pyo, do I have to appear in court?
No. You don't have to comply.
Right. This is distorting the truth.
He dedicated his entire life
to saving lives.
What is this? Attempted murder?
So ridiculous. Seriously.
-Can't we sue them for slander?
-I'll look into that.
That's that.
What will you do about Choi Yosub?
We will advise him to resign--
Gosh, no.
He caused a lot of damage
to my reputation and the hospital.
He's not getting out of this that easily.
-Don't you agree?
-Totally.
That traitor stabbed
a fellow doctor in the back.
We must make an example out of him
to show the others
that traitors will rot in misery.
I understand.
TRANSFER NOTICE OF PERSONNEL
CHOI YOSUB
-Did something happen?
-No idea.
OPERATING ROOM ANNOUNCEMENT
-What are you doing? What did I do?
-We received a tip
that you violated
the Narcotics Control Act.
Who made that ridiculous report?
-It's a misunderstanding. I didn't do--
-Sure.
I got it.
We'll search your office thoroughly.
And if we don't find anything,
we'll leave.
We need to check the hospital's laptop.
Unlock it, please.
I'm so nervous. I hope it went through.
It couldn't have gotten omitted or…
-Come on. Open it.
-Okay.
-I'll check it now.
Hey, this isn't fake. Right?
This is a real medical license, right?
Do you think
they would send us a fake one?
This is the seal
of the Minister of Health and Welfare.
Jayden kept his promise.
Given what he accomplished,
it won't be a bad thing to join hands.
Hey, that's not important right now.
He's a doctor again!
Yes!
Yihan, we should get a new sign.
The first floor is for Dr. Han.
The second floor, Lawyer Han.
Let's make it super cool!
What?
We haven't even opened the hospital yet.
Is that our first patient?
Congratulations.
Come on in. We've been waiting…
Is this Mr. Han Yihan's law office?
Yes, it is.
What is a beautiful lady like you
doing at a humble place like this?
How can I help you?
-You're here.
-Hey.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Ban Soohee, a reporter for MBS.
Excuse me.
Hey, are you taking a shower?
You used up half of the bottle
for a handshake.
Nice to meet you.
I'm the chief clerk at New-Hope Law Office
and the head nurse
at New-Hope Medicine Clinic.
My name is Kang Daewoong.
Okay. I hope we get along, Daewoong.
Gosh. Yes.
I want nothing more than that.
Soohee, don't smile at him
with that pretty face of yours.
Guys like him
mistake kindness for affection.
-When did I…
-Let's go.
Dry your hands before you come up.
I won't dry them.
This is what you asked for.
Thank you.
You weren't lying, right?
You said you had a huge scoop
about Banseok and Chairman Gu Jingi.
You bet.
News agencies assign reporters
for a promising presidential candidate
like Lim Taemoon.
A reporter with a managerial title
at my agency is following him.
As you can see from the file,
nothing is out of the ordinary.
He's a clean politician
which is hard to see these days.
Clean politicians.
Aren't they some kind of mythical figures?
That's why I looked into him on my own.
And I found something interesting.
It's medication for blood pressure.
And cyclosporine.
They are immunosuppressants.
So you two figured it out right away.
Not a lot of people take
this kind of medication, right?
Right.
Patients who received
transplant surgery have to take it
for the rest of their lives.
Where did you find this?
From the recycling bin
in front of his house.
I didn't expect much.
But I hit the jackpot.
If a promising presidential candidate
secretly received transplant surgery,
that would be enough
to get people talking.
Of course, I won't stop there.
So tell me
about this huge scoop you have for me.
Gu Jingi
ordered Nam Hyukchul to kill Park Kitae.
Chairman Gu got someone to commit murder?
Yes.
He even tried to kill me recently
in the interrogation room
at a prosecutors' office, but he failed.
Gosh.
If this is true,
the whole world will be in a frenzy.
Do you have evidence
to support your claim?
Nam Hyukchul's son, Nam Junhwan,
is in Banseokwon
for hypertrophic cardiomyopathy.
If I perform the surgery and save his son,
he promised
to confess everything in court.
Hypertrophic cardiomyopathy?
That sounds like a difficult surgery.
Not a lot of doctors in Korea
performed this procedure.
And it will be even hard for me to succeed
without help from another surgeon.
Then is there a surgeon who will help?
You don't have to worry about that.
I have a surgeon I can trust.
An emergency patient!
-What's wrong?
-Anaphylaxis.
Give him antihistamine
and prepare to intubate.
Okay.
Doctor, we need to perform CPR.
Dr. Choi, hurry.
Why do I have to wait three hours
just to get my blood drawn?
I'm sorry.
I have a lot of emergency patients.
It will sting a bit.
You're doing that on purpose, right?
Press on it.
I'm going to write a post
about this online.
Sir, stop moving.
-Stay still.
-Where am I?
-Don't move, sir.
-What are you doing?
You're trying to mug me, aren't you?
-We need help over here!
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you doze off in the OR?
Must I wait for you to cut?
You can't even do your job.
How dare you put your nose in my business?
Go face the wall with your arms up.
I don't need an incompetent surgeon
who can't even cut.
Go!
Turn around.
Seriously.
Please.
People often say
evil deeds come at a price.
But you see,
sometimes, good deeds
come at a greater price.
Just like you.
I'll give you a chance
to set your good deed right.
Return to your previous role.
I'll make you an associate professor.
In three years, you'll be a professor.
After that,
you will be the Head
of Cardiothoracic Surgery at Banseok.
Then what about Gil Soyeon?
Don't worry about her.
She'll be compensated like the ruling.
It's a gesture of my generosity
that I respect your good deed
and forgive your mistake.
But I need you
to promise one thing for me.
Promise that
you will never associate with Han Yihan
in whatever circumstances.
Think carefully.
This is your last…
This really is
your last chance.
What? Nam Hyukchul
threatened him with a knife?
Yes.
He hid a knife made of obsidian
under the bandages on his hand.
And he tried to kill Mr. Han with that.
Go on. What happened?
His neck was wounded a bit.
But it's not serious.
I should talk
to the deputy chief prosecutor, right?
We should ask the police
to investigate to find out
how he got his hands on--
No. Don't do it.
Will Mr. Han be pressing charges?
No.
He said he'd let it go if Nam Hyukchul
hires him as his attorney.
That's good.
If he says he's okay,
there's no reason to dig into it.
A suspect tried to kill his attorney
in the interrogation room.
If this gets out,
it won't be just me and you in a difficult
position. The chief prosecutor too.
What's wrong?
You don't seem like the person
I know you to be.
Back in the day,
you would tell me to report it
as it happened.
That's the person I liked and respected.
I'll do what you want me to do this time.
In return,
let me be the prosecutor
for Nam Hyukchul's sentencing.
Okay. Do that.
What's wrong?
You're slower than usual.
I'm considering
taking a different route this time.
If I play with the same opening
and the same defense,
it's boring.
Even if it's fun, if you don't win,
it's meaningless.
I agree.
I'm not interested in lessons
learned from the losses.
When did the queen…
-Was this your plan all along?
-No.
I just moved around freely.
After all, that's the queen's charm.
Upon injecting a group of two-year-old
mice with the new drug, A582,
their exchange with other entities and
activity level increased by 32%.
That's impressive.
A two-year-old mouse
is equivalent to an elderly human.
It's as though they've gotten younger.
The difficulty with finding
a cure for Alzheimer's
is that even if you develop a drug,
the brain can't absorb it.
But A582
penetrates the blood-brain barrier.
What's more surprising is how effective
it is in developing the frontal lobe.
If you look at the MRIs
of the patients in the trial,
all of their frontal lobes
are revitalized.
This one drug can cure Alzheimer's
and frontal lobe dementia.
What's the period of administration?
The center's internal standard is 14 days.
For 14 days?
Let's try it again.
Increase the entities and the time frame.
Pardon?
Fourteen days isn't short
compared to other institutions.
Is that necessary?
That's domestic standard.
It's not long enough
to receive FDA approval.
The same goes for Europe.
Plus, we'll be administering it
to more patients in Phase Three,
so we must be careful.
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry,
but can we speak in private?
We have a deadline.
"A deadline"?
For what?
For Chairman Gu's
Minister of Health and Welfare hearing.
We have to pass the rapid approval review
before then.
So you don't want to do
a thorough clinical trial?
No, it's not that.
-I'm saying we've done enough.
-I'm not satisfied.
Do as I say. I'm in charge of this place.
She wants another clinical trial?
-For double the period?
-Yes.
I tried to explain it to her,
but she says
she'd take responsibility for it.
Do what she wants.
-Would that be okay?
-Yes.
She'll figure out that
she'll have to follow my plan soon enough.
Yes, sir.
The key
to hypertrophic cardiomyopathy surgery
is to cut just enough
of the thickened heart muscles.
If you cut too little,
the surgery is meaningless.
But if you cut too much,
the heart will be ripped.
Right. That's why it's hard.
It's hard enough to get the scalpel
in the aorta,
but you have to cut the muscle
and take it out.
What? You lost the knife,
so you couldn't do anything?
Are you serious?
I had no choice.
It's not like I could kill him
with my bare hands.
How could you lose the knife
I wrapped in your bandages?
Be honest with me.
Do you think Director Gu Jingi
would accept this?
Do you think he'd believe you?
If you're considering changing your mind,
wake up.
Your son…
Director Gu Jingi can kill him
whenever he wants.
The same goes for you.
HOPEFUL CORRECTIONS
That's an additional 0.8g.
It's a total of 6.2g.
-Show me more of the inside.
-Okay.
I think I cut off too much.
I need a first assistant
in order to handle an emergent situation.
Don't worry.
Dr. Choi is going to assist you
with Nam Junhwan's surgery.
CHOI YOSUB
Your call cannot be connected.
Please leave your message…
Seokyeong!
-Daewoong.
-How long has it been?
Have you been well?
I'm tearing up.
Have you been well too?
I'm sorry. I know you took care
of Seokju for a long time,
but I couldn't call you.
What are you saying?
I'm grateful you came.
-You're here.
-Yes.
Were you practicing for the surgery?
Yes. I was practicing with a pig's heart.
I need to do this,
so I don't lose my touch.
Yihan, you should go up with Seokyeong.
I'll clean up.
-Thanks.
-No problem.
Let's go up.
What's wrong? Do you not have an appetite?
You said you wanted to meet in private,
so I asked them to stay open late for us.
I want Dr. Han Yihan
to do Junhwan's surgery.
I'm grateful for your consideration,
but I can't wait any longer.
I'd like you to stop administering
the new drug…
I'll prepare the next course.
We stuffed the heart of a suckling pig
marinated in yogurt
and baked it in the oven
with pancetta and rosemary on it.
It's a stuffed pork heart.
Thank you. We don't need any more food.
You may be excused.
Yes, sir.
When I did my first heart surgery,
you were with me.
Yes. I couldn't believe
it was your first surgery.
It was a perfect success.
In order to succeed,
I practiced with pigs' hearts.
It wasn't once or twice.
I tried it dozens of times.
Do you know what I realized then?
There isn't much difference
between a human heart and a pig's heart.
Once I came to realize it, I was surprised
by how I wasn't nervous anymore.
After that, whenever a critical situation
arose during surgery,
I told myself,
"This isn't a human. This is just a pig.
This is a pig's heart."
What's interesting
is that when I did that, my patient lived.
Because bold decisions
that are hard to make on humans
are possible on pigs.
Sir…
I'll put Junhwan on ECMO
to get him higher on the transplant list.
That way, if a heart comes up
in our hospital, he can get a transplant.
But what if there are no hearts?
We have to make it happen.
There's a suitable candidate too.
A man in his 20s
who came in from a motorcycle accident.
Luckily, he's an organ donor.
There is some possibility
that he'll recover,
but I can take measures
for Junhwan's sake.
What do you mean by taking measures?
I'm sorry.
Think of him as a pig.
Five years ago and even now.
If you want to save Junhwan,
don't have useless ideas.
Otherwise,
someone precious to you…
will end up on the dinner table.
A reporter came to see me.
She said she found this
in the recycling bin
at Lim Taemoon's home.
They're immunosuppressants.
It's medication taken by those
who have had organ transplants.
What?
Lim Taemoon,
former Minister of Foreign Affairs.
Five years ago,
when he was the ambassador to the US,
he helped Banseok Foundation
acquire a general hospital in California.
Then does it mean
this person took Seokju's heart?
Calm down. We can't know for sure yet.
I'll find out more about Lim Taemoon
through the reporter.
Seokyeong,
you should focus on Baek Kangho.
Okay.
I'll look into him.
Is it tomorrow?
The day you're meeting Jayden
and Chairman Gu Jingi.
-Yes.
-Will you be okay?
Honestly, I don't think
I'd be able to hold myself back.
I feel the same way.
I'm not sure…
how I will face him yet.
Return the 300 billion won investment
as shares of the R and D Center…
The period being ten business days
after the hearing
for the Minister of Health and Welfare…
The higher the price of shares,
the fewer shares we must give them.
The higher the stock prices are,
the more advantageous it is for us.
Something's bothering me.
If the new Alzheimer's drug gets approved,
our stocks will skyrocket.
Are you trying to take a gamble?
That bothered me too,
so I had a law firm that specializes
in foreign companies review it.
They said as long as the stocks go up,
it's a non-issue.
Gosh.
INVESTMENT RETURN AGREEMENT
ARTICLE 1: PURPOSE
ARTICLE 2: CONTENT
ARTICLE 3: CHANGES
You and Chairman Gu
will meet again at last.
I'm getting excited for you.
Are you going to punch him
when you see him?
Do whatever you want.
Punch him or curse at him.
I don't care.
Thank you.
I feel better thanks to you.
You know that
even if you used to work here,
in principle, you must file a request
to see the materials that have been
transferred to the storage department.
Of course.
I'm only asking you for this favor
since I was in charge of the case.
If it was any other case,
I wouldn't have come.
I'm sure you have your reasons,
Prosecutor Geum.
But next time,
please file a request first.
I will.
SEOUL SOUTHERN DISTRICT
PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
RECORDINGS AND TRANSCRIPTIONS
Hello.
-Prosecutor Geum?
-Yes.
The Criminal Department One material
from when you worked here is all here.
Thank you.
I'll return it as soon as I'm done.
Okay.
BANSEOK UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER
MALPRACTICE DEATH CASE
GUKKWANG GANG ABDUCTION AND MURDER CASE
They're late.
We've already waited ten minutes.
They're here.
We've been waiting for you.
I'm sorry for being late.
The thought of two people
who have bad blood meeting
made me a bit nervous.
We don't have bad blood.
It was resolved
according to law and reason.
Don't you agree?
I received the gift you sent me.
"Gift"?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I never sent you a gift.
Then I should return it
since I don't think it was meant for me.
I bet there was a lot of blood
when you took out Seokju's heart.
It's your turn to bleed now.
Hey!
This is the gift I received.
What is this?
I knew it. I can never predict his moves.
Hey, you punk.
Move that hand in this instance!
Stay still!
-Cut me.
-Father.
If your revenge was to end like this,
you wouldn't have waited five years.
Do it.
If you can.
You're right.
I waited years for my revenge.
It'd be futile to end it like this.
But the thing with revenge
is that it's futile when it ends.
Father, are you okay?
I'm just returning what I got.
I'll make you
the director of the hospital.
Don't marry Gu Hyunseong.
Why not? Do you love me?
I'll let you drive fast.
More! Step on it!
Empty your head!
We'll trust you with our son's surgery.
Are you planning on
stealing another patient's heart again?
What can I help you with?
Can we trust him with something
as important as this?
Didn't you join forces with Han Yihan?
I don't have any loyalties to Han Yihan.
Translated by Won-hyang Son