THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Please take a look at this.
This is a marriage certificate.
We filled it out
the day before she was admitted.
It was a risky surgery,
so whatever happened, we vowed
to be together for the rest of our lives.
But will that be enough
to prove the relationship between them?
Yes.
If the form was filled out
under each other's consent,
the moment you file it at the borough
office, you'll be legally married.
So if I file this,
Sunae and I will be married?
Yes.
But you must think carefully
before you decide.
If you file it, you can't take it back.
And you must also consider the possibility
of Ms. Yang's condition worsening
and not being able
to carry on a normal life.
I'll file it.
I don't care about her medical condition.
Whatever happens,
I will stay by her side to the end.
Then let's go to the office now.
We still have time to file it.
EPISODE 11
Banseok R and D Center
will be listed on the US stock market.
If everything goes as you said,
we'll make a fortune.
The problem is the board.
There are 16 directors who have the right
to vote for the chairman
and the hospital director.
And there are six directors
who will side with you for sure
including us two.
We need eight votes to win over
at least a majority of the directors
to stand a chance.
There's one more.
Director of Banseok R and D Center.
Are you talking about Director Lim Yuna?
I'm certain she will side
with Chairman Gu.
She's about to marry Hyunseong.
Trust me.
And as for the two more votes we need,
I'll get them at the board meeting myself.
Come on. I was enjoying this fine liquor.
What's wrong?
Banseokwon has a VIP client.
She's an assemblywoman.
She makes a big fuss whenever she comes.
She wants us to turn off
all the security cameras.
And we can't walk around the building,
so no one sees her.
Are you talking
about Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon?
Yes. That's her. How did you know?
We're directors and sons of the founder
of Banseok Foundation.
How is it possible there's a VIP client
we can't even meet in the building?
Gu Jingi.
Gu Jingi and the assemblywoman
must be plotting something, right?
Spouse Yang Sunae.
Then does this give me the right
to bring her out from Banseokwon?
Yes. One's spouse has
the highest level of priority
over parents or children.
This is Han Yihan.
I found out something interesting.
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon will make
a secret visit to Banseokwon soon.
Just like the day we took Nam Junhwan.
Hold on.
Assemblywoman Yoon
is on her way to Banseokwon now.
What?
Can you connect me
to Lim Taemoon right away?
I doubted it,
but you really intended
to have both in your hands.
You must be very concerned
about making your daughter fall
into a critical condition.
I am Doh Jinwoo's attorney, Han Yihan.
We will move Ms. Yang Sunae
to New-Hope Medicine Clinic.
Even if it's a guardian's request,
transferring a critical patient
at such late hours is against our policy.
We must think about the patient's safety.
If you care so much about patients,
why did you move Nam Junhwan here
right after surgery?
You even used violence.
Lead us to Yang Sunae
right now.
Fine. However, only her guardian
and her doctor can see the patient.
No.
I must accompany you and check
if the content of the lawsuit is true.
Isn't that what you want?
Yes.
Despite your issue
with my daughter's job at Banseok,
it seems to me that you have a lot of ties
to Banseok just as much.
I don't see any point in answering that.
Receiving preferential treatment
and receiving medical treatment
are completely different matters.
We'll find out soon enough
if that's all there's to it.
And you and I need to talk in private.
How much longer
will he make me do this kind of job?
He's indeed my knight.
He penetrated into the core.
Everything is going as planned.
Is it going as planned?
Is it okay that we're not going
to see Ms. Yang right away?
We have no choice.
Now that Lim Taemoon is here,
he won't leave
without talking to him first.
I made it clear that
you must have only one diamond.
It seems to me you didn't take my advice.
I'm not sure about that. I think
you're also having second thoughts.
Naturally.
I heard the surgeon who was
supposed to operate on my heart
was a medical criminal who made
a ghost doctor perform his surgeries.
I could put up with you weighing
me and Assemblywoman Yoon.
But you had me fooled about my surgery
when my life was at stake.
And I could not forgive you for that.
About that…
I'm sorry. I would like to apologize.
You think
your mere apology can appease me?
Of course, not.
But even if it doesn't,
what would that change?
-What did you say?
-It's uncomfortable for me to say this.
But you have no choice.
Your political career… No.
The rest of your life
rests in my hands.
You must have been mistaken
about our relationship.
Keep this mind moving forward then.
You had had the upper hand
before you accepted favors from me.
But the moment you accepted them,
I, Gu Jingi, have the upper hand
over you.
You…
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
My gosh. They are the worst.
Why did they come
in the middle of the night?
Only my title is fancy.
I'm always on standby for them.
Exactly.
If she didn't want the treatment,
she should've told me.
Must I be on standby
whenever she comes to see her daughter?
Calm down. Okay?
We have to do whatever they want
just until we buy a building in Gangnam.
Well, thanks to her,
we'll get to spend
some quality time together.
Seriously. Your stamina is so robust.
Well, why don't I reap the benefit
of serving the assemblywoman?
Exactly. Come here.
That startled me. Hold on.
Darn it. Why now?
Who is this? It's Chairman Gu.
Yes, sir. I'm listening.
What? What do you want me to do?
I don't have the time to explain.
Put her under deep sedation
right now.
Sir. Hello? Sir?
What is it?
He just told me
to put more sedatives on Ms. Yang.
What? More on top of everything else? Why?
What is he trying to do?
Whatever. Let's go now.
Yuna.
This way.
What is this about? You said
you had to talk to me in person right now.
Well…
Why don't you sit first?
I have incredible news.
I'm sorry about this. I know it's late.
I wanted you to be the first one to know.
And I wanted to celebrate with you.
Celebrate?
Are you ready?
I'm going to be the hospital director.
The youngest director of Banseok.
I told my father
that I would start leading the hospital.
It's only the beginning.
I'll be the hospital director,
the chairman,
and the man that surpasses my father.
She'll be okay, right?
I already made a call. He will arrange it.
This better goes well.
Sunae. What is this?
Open this door right now! Do it.
Sunae, can you hear me? Yang Sunae!
Open the door now.
Don't make a scene.
Sunae.
What is this? What happened?
Calm down, Jinwoo. I'll take a look.
You two. What were you doing here?
I was doing my rounds.
I personally look after VIP patients
as I'm the assistant director.
Why… Why is she…
We performed a corrective osteotomy
to treat the side effect
of the limb-lengthening surgery.
But there was a bigger problem.
Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.
By the time she was admitted,
she was at the terminal stage.
I heard you stayed with her
for more than two years.
Were you really not aware of that?
I mean, Sunae had a weak constitution
by nature. So I just thought--
What a real piece of trash.
My precious daughter is sick
because of you.
But what? You're her guardian and family?
What do you think
someone like you can do for her?
Had she stayed with me the whole time,
I wouldn't have let her condition
get worse like this.
If you saw what you did to her,
don't make a fuss and leave quietly.
Don't even think about showing your face
around here again.
Anyway, if you try to transfer her now
when she's in critical condition,
the patient's condition could worsen.
And it will be a huge problem for her.
If you truly care for your wife,
you should let her get treated here.
-Sir, we'll get going then.
-Sure.
Wait.
Sunae.
What's going on?
Ms. Yang isn't in a coma.
She's breathing on her own.
Why did you intubate her
when she can breathe on her own?
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
What? What do you mean
you can't do this anymore?
I'll get going now.
Let's talk another time.
Wait. Yuna.
Yuna, hold on.
I'm sorry.
But it's quite rude of you to leave
without explaining why you're leaving.
You will find out why.
I'm sorry that I can't celebrate with you.
Why did you intubate her
when she's conscious?
It was for the worst-case scenario.
She could lose consciousness at any minute
due to difficulty in breathing.
So we were preparing ourselves.
-What are you doing? Darn it.
-What are you doing? They're our supplies.
Midazolam.
Dr. Lee, you administered sedatives
to forcefully put the patient to sleep.
Well…
That's right.
Until there was a donor
for her lung transplant,
we were planning to sedate her
with the right amount of sedatives.
So what? Is something wrong with that?
Administering sedatives…
with muscle relaxants
is a different story.
If you add this high of a dosage,
it could cause the patient to die.
Are you aware of this?
Chairman Gu, what is he talking about?
I can explain this to you in private.
You were going to stop her
from regaining consciousness
and hold her hostage here.
Just in case.
Why would you jeopardize her health?
This is a hospital.
Dr. Han.
As of this moment,
I'm Ms. Yang Sunae's doctor.
Get ready to transfer the patient.
Director Gu Jingi.
The police plan to review
all of her medical records
regarding hospital admission, surgery,
drug injection, and treatments.
Please cooperate.
Mr. Kwon Yoonseok.
Yes?
I have a few questions regarding
Assemblywoman Yoon's political funds.
I really hope we can talk this time.
And please don't try to harm yourself.
You ended things with Gu Hyunseong?
Yes. I just told him.
But…
you were supposed to end it
after the board meeting.
And you wanted that too.
I did.
But…
I couldn't do it anymore.
I couldn't lie about my feelings
and date a man I didn't like.
Are you disappointed?
No. I'm touched.
I wanted you to end things with him
as soon as possible.
But I couldn't force you.
I knew that your father and Gu Jingi
had a complicated relationship.
From now on, I will not hide
our relationship from anyone.
Thank you for coming to me sooner.
I'm sorry. I can't do this anymore.
Yuna, hold on.
She can't do this anymore?
Why all of a sudden?
Darn it.
NEW-HOPE LAW OFFICE
NEW-HOPE MEDICINE CLINIC
-Jinwoo, what…
-Sunae.
Sunae… Sunae woke up.
Ms. Yang Sunae.
Can you hear me?
You seem to be in a good condition.
I will remove the tube first.
Try coughing.
Where am I?
You can relax. You are at a hospital.
Mr. Doh Jinwoo is here as well.
Jinwoo.
-Sunae.
-Jinwoo.
Sunae, do you recognize me?
Of course.
I dreamed about you all along.
We will do more checkups,
but she seems to be fully cognitive.
Dr. Han.
Sunae is okay now, right?
Idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis.
It took over 90% of the right lung
and 50% of the left lung.
Is that bad?
Quite so.
Unlike the case with other organs,
lung damage can't be reversed.
The ECMO machine
will keep the patient alive,
but a lung transplant is
the only way to fix the problem.
A lung transplant?
Here is the problem.
While Sunae is on the waitlist,
she won't be able to receive a transplant
unless the donor has blood type O.
And there are three patients before her,
so she will need to wait
for several months.
Then please give her my lungs.
I have blood type O.
As her husband, I can donate my organ.
It is possible,
but I can't operate
if you are the only donor.
A one-on-one lung transplant
is too taxing for the donor.
We will need to transplant the lungs
from two donors
for a two-on-one lung transplant.
In that case…
We need to find another donor.
The person
who can donate lungs the fastest…
is her family.
Her family.
-A side effect?
-Yes.
As you ordered, the formula
was administered for two more weeks.
Some samples had seizures and convulsions.
-And the clinical patients?
-They haven't shown any anomalies.
Run a thorough checkup
on the clinical patients right now.
-Make sure the words don't get out.
-Yes, ma'am.
How will we report to Chairman Gu?
I will do it myself.
What? Han Yihan, that punk,
came here with Ambassador Lim?
That's right.
They showed up when
Assemblywoman Yoon Miseon was visiting.
Why was Ambassador Lim with him?
I think they knew about the tie between
Chairman Gu and Assemblywoman Yoon.
Gosh. In any case,
I got a scare yesterday.
Assemblywoman Yoon, Ambassador Lim,
Han Yihan, and Prosecutor Geum.
Thinking about what happened yesterday
makes my heart bounce.
I ordered Nam Hyukchul to murder someone?
What nonsense is that?
I don't know.
Perhaps this will make you talk.
What's that?
What do you mean? What does it look like?
What kind of a question is that?
I don't know what it is.
You don't know what it is.
I could tell right away.
It's a knife.
It has a handle and a blade.
How could you not know it's a knife?
What I am saying is…
So you knew it was a knife,
but you didn't know where it came from.
Is that what you wanted to say?
Yes. That's correct.
Your mind works in a complicated way.
That wasn't the question I asked.
Nam Hyukchul said you gave it to him
so that he would kill Han Yihan.
Listen. Do you honestly believe
the words of a schizophrenic patient?
Well,
we requested a mental health assessment,
so we will soon see
if Nam Hyukchul is schizophrenic or not.
There is another thing
that caught my eyes.
REAL ESTATE PURCHASE AGREEMENT
Last week, you made a good faith deposit
for an apartment in Apgujeong, Gangnam-gu.
You must make a lot of money.
With my salary as a prosecutor,
I can't even dream of it.
Did you run a background check?
No.
It comes from the police's investigation.
Banseok must have paid you well.
Last month, your wife and two sons
went to Hawaii for their studies.
Did you plan to take the fall
in repayment for your big break?
I won't say a single word
without a lawyer.
Suit yourself. It's your right.
Who will pay for the lawyer?
Will it be Banseok?
INTERROGATION ROOM
Request an arrest warrant
and send him home today.
Yes, ma'am.
Nam Hyukchul will be safe, right?
Of course. Apparently,
the warden is kicking up a fuss.
If another inmate gets hurt or murdered,
he will be sacked.
I am sure you know this,
but keep your guards up for a while.
They will take any measure
when they are cornered.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay.
They said there wouldn't be a problem.
For goodness' sake.
Did you wait for me?
I thought you would need
a lawyer.
Here you go.
You are Chairman Gu Jingi's enemy.
Why would you defend me?
The fact you are worried about
the relationship between Gu Jingi and me
tells me that there are ties indeed.
Don't worry.
My goal isn't you, but Gu Jingi.
It's the same
for Prosecutor Geum Seokyeong.
Do you know why the same crimes
lead to different sentences?
Mitigating circumstances.
You might be a first-time offender.
You might be reflecting upon yourself.
You might settle with the victim.
Those factors reduce the sentence.
If you hire me as your lawyer,
I will overlook the fact
that you handed Nam Hyukchul a weapon
in order to kill me.
After all, a lawyer can't increase
his client's sentence.
But it only applies
if you tell me the whole truth.
There is one thing
I didn't tell you.
Park Kitae said something before he died.
"Garden, USB."
Mr. Park, can you hear me?
Don't speak. It'll go worse!
Garden.
USB.
His pronunciation wasn't clear,
but he said he put
a USB drive in a garden.
Did you tell Gu Jingi about this?
No, I didn't.
I didn't hear it clearly.
Garden?
Perhaps a recording
of his conversation with Gu Jingi
is buried in his garden.
That's nonsense.
Kitae lived in a studio apartment.
He couldn't have hidden it
in someone else's garden.
He couldn't have said
something meaningless before death.
GARDEN?
-Jinwoo.
-Dr. Han, I have something to say.
I will go to the hospital.
-I will be back.
-Okay.
I won't sue Assemblywoman Yoon.
-Is it because of the surgery?
-Yes.
Sunae matters the most to me.
I know how you feel.
But once you drop the charges,
you won't be able
to sue her again for the same issue.
Then you will inadvertently exonerate
Assemblywoman Yoon.
I don't care
as long as Sunae becomes healthy.
Tomorrow, please meet
Assemblywoman Yoon with me.
Please do that.
Okay.
You will drop the charges against me.
Yes, ma'am.
If you donate your lungs to Sunae,
I won't make an issue about the fact
that you tried to kidnap me
and abused Sunae.
That won't be enough.
If she stays with a low life like you,
I would rather see her bedridden
for the rest of her life.
In that case,
what do you want me to do?
Agree to an annulment.
Since you are a lawyer, you would know.
If there were no agreements
between the spouses,
a marriage can be annulled.
There was an agreement,
but Sunae was unconscious
at the time of marriage registration.
So you could sue for annulment.
If you win,
their marriage will be erased
from the records.
Right after the lung transplant,
disappear without leaving a single trace
in my daughter's life.
If you agree to that,
I will think about it.
I will do that.
I will annul the marriage.
I won't see her or contact her again.
So please…
donate lungs to Sunae with me.
I am begging you.
Fine.
The surgery will take place at Banseokwon.
I will schedule it as soon as possible.
Even if you pick Banseokwon for security,
I will be in charge of the operation.
Suit yourself.
You were a cardiothoracic surgeon
who represented the hospital,
so you are bound to have skills.
Gong Gukkwang, the boss of Gukkwang Gang.
Five years ago, he was under investigation
for kidnapping, confinement, and assault
before he got acquitted.
Check out what he is up to these days.
If it's Gukkwang Gang, it's the Southern
District Prosecutors' Office's division.
Shall I ask a friend who is
in Criminal Division One?
Yes. You should do that.
No. Investigate it yourself
without using any connections.
Don't report to the higher-ups.
Does that include Senior Prosecutor Baek?
Yes. Please do me this favor.
I do whatever you ask me to do.
Same here. Leave it to us.
Gong Gukkwang looks
exactly as his name sounds.
It's hard to pronounce his name.
Gong Gukkwang.
Tomorrow, a special board meeting
for Banseok Foundation will take place.
Then there will be a lung transplant
for Yang Sunae,
an election debate between Ambassador Lim
and Assemblywoman Yoon,
and a Chairman Gu's confirmation hearing
as a minister nominee.
Michael and I will attend
the board meeting as investors.
We must stop Gu Hyunseong
from becoming the director.
I wish Yihan would join us
as a director nominee.
Like I said before, I have no interest
in becoming the director.
Find someone else.
I will assist you properly tomorrow
to pay back for everything
you have given me.
Friendship is a strange thing.
When you first stormed the place,
I never thought we would form
this kind of a connection.
It's so reassuring
to have you on our side.
So don't commit any crimes.
Then you won't be scared again.
Noted.
Are you nervous?
No, I am okay.
Okay. No matter what anyone says,
you are qualified to become the director.
Show everyone that you are capable.
Okay.
Let's go.
BANSEOK FOUNDATION'S
EXTRAORDINARY BOARD MEETING
I, Gu Jingi,
will resign as the chairman
of Banseok Foundation
and the director
of Banseok University Medical Center.
Until the hearing ends, I will keep
the position of the chairman vacant.
But for the smooth management
of Banseok University Medical Center,
I wish to nominate a new director today
and ask for the board members' agreement.
Who do you plan to nominate?
I nominate Gu Hyunseong,
Director of Planning and Coordination.
That's ridiculous.
I hoped you wouldn't be so brazen.
You say that you will resign,
but you are putting your son
in your position!
I could never accept such a thing.
I won't.
Why not?
It's not like there is an age restriction.
Director Gu Hyunseong
has worked at this medical center
for over 15 years.
He is more than qualified.
-What nonsense--
-Stop. Please stop.
This isn't a matter
of an emotional quarrel.
If there are differing opinions,
let's decide by vote.
Before we do that,
I'd like to say a few words
as an investor of Banseok Foundation.
It's a rude request.
Nominating and electing a director is
up to the board members.
Even as an investor,
you would be overstepping
if you try to influence the vote.
Overstepping? As things are now,
that could be the case.
But what if the owner of Banseok
changes in a month?
-What?
-Will the owner of Banseok change?
-What is he talking about?
-For goodness' sake.
What nonsense is that?
So it's a private garden
that isn't open to the public.
I see. Thank you.
Okay.
Is it a Korean restaurant?
It's just called Garden.
I see. I am sorry.
We don't have much time until the hearing.
At this rate, we won't find it in a month.
Why are you so busy?
What are you looking for?
In a garden, Kitae put a USB drive
that has a recording of a conversation
between him and Gu Jingi.
-A garden?
-Yes.
But there are countless gardens in Seoul.
There are real gardens
and hundreds of pubs and restaurants
with that name.
It could be a person's name.
Jungwon as in "Garden."
It's often used as a person's name.
You are right.
Perhaps he gave the USB drive
to a person named Jungwon.
If that's the case, who is this person?
Article two of the contract states,
"B will give A 300 billion won's worth
of the Banseok R and D Center stocks."
BANSEOK FOUNDATION
2022 EXTRAORDINARY BOARD MEETING
"Should B fail to follow the contract
without justifiable reasons,
he will pay A a penal sum
of one billion dollars."
-What?
-One billion dollars?
JANG JUNGTAE
What does that mean?
Did you really sign such a contract?
You didn't discuss the matter
with the board.
Stop keeping silent and say something.
I understand why you are concerned,
but the market capitalization of Banseok
R and D Center is over two trillion won.
Giving 300 billion won's worth of stocks
won't affect the management rights.
That only applies
if the stock price doesn't fall.
The stock return will take place
two weeks after Chairman Gu's hearing.
If he gets rejected
as a nominee after the hearing
or the new cure
for Alzheimer's disease falls through,
the stock price will plummet
and the owner
of Banseok R and D Center will become
Honours Hand.
What nonsense are you spouting?
That won't happen!
I will expand on that matter.
BANSEOK FOUNDATION
2022 EXTRAORDINARY BOARD MEETING
I am Lim Yuna, the director
of Banseok R and D Center.
I have something to share
as the person who is in charge
of the new medicine's clinical trials.
Choi Jungwon.
There were only two nurses named Jungwon
at Banseok University Medical Center.
One of them quit
the week after Kitae died.
The timing tells us it's her.
It's strange that she changed her number
and went AWOL.
Thank you.
Yihan, I found out where Choi Jungwon is.
My friend at Banseok University
Medical Center introduced her
to a nursing center in Gyeonggi Province.
Please make a right turn.
EVERGREEN NURSING CENTER
A thorough examination
after the administration revealed
a 5% increase
in cardiovascular diseases.
Let me put it in simple words.
The longer you use the new medicine,
the more you are at risk
for cardiovascular diseases.
Correct.
Thus, as the person who is in charge,
I believe we should cancel
the conditional permission
from the Ministry of Food and Drug Safety.
JAYDEN LEE
LEE DOHYUNG, GU HYUNSEONG
The number is only five out of 100.
Isn't the number too small
to cancel the conditional permission?
Had the number been higher,
the clinical trials
would have been canceled.
As that thankfully isn't the case,
we can cancel the conditional permission
and put more time
into the clinical trials.
You are using it as an excuse
to sell Banseok R and D Center
to Honours Hand.
Banseok Foundation is a medical company
that represents Korea.
We shouldn't let
a foreign company steal it
no matter the case.
Why do you think of it as stealing?
The board members who are here
will gain more.
Imagine Banseok R and D Center
moving beyond this country
and getting listed on Nasdaq.
Then its worth
will increase by tens of times.
And the profits will be shared
among the board members.
A typical biopharmaceutical company
that is listed on Nasdaq
has the market capitalization
of over 300 trillion won.
Is it true?
-Did she say 300 trillion won?
-Over 300 trillion won?
If we succeed in developing
the first cure for Alzheimer's disease
without any side effects,
it will be
Banseok R and D Center's future.
-If we succeed…
-It's better for us.
If the company gets listed…
If you succeed in developing…
That sounds nice.
Thank you for sharing your opinion
as an investor.
But all of these things will happen
only if I, Gu Jingi, get rejected
as a nominee at the hearing.
Do you honestly believe that will happen?
Perhaps you are hoping for it.
There must have been a misunderstanding.
Regardless of the stock return,
Gu Hyunseong should never be
the director of the medical center.
Since he is facing prosecution
for a violation of the Medical Service Act
and attempted murder,
-such a move would be too risky.
-What is he talking about?
-Attempted murder?
-Then he can't become the director.
BAE SEOKHO
JANG JUNGTAE
What is it?
We are the Medical Crime
Investigation Unit. We are going in.
Search and seize
the medical record department first.
-Okay.
-What is this about?
You should have notified us of your visit.
You prepare too much when we do that.
We prefer to keep things natural.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
We have a search warrant as well.
If you aren't going to show us the way,
we will enter on our own.
Please give us time
to ask for the members' understanding.
Time to fabricate evidence, you mean.
The prosecution
and Medical Crime Investigation Unit
are incredibly busy.
I am afraid that we don't have time
to meet such demands.
So please move out of the way
before the members become
more uncomfortable.
Guys, aren't you going to work? Let's go.
-Yes, ma'am.
Ma'am, isn't it nice to step outside?
It's nice, but I don't want
to burden you, Jungwon.
Shall we make another round?
Ms. Choi Jungwon?
Ms. Choi Jungwon.
I am the late Park Kitae's
friend and lawyer,
Han Yihan.
Dr. Han Yihan?
Yes.
I came here because I want to ask you
something about Kitae.
I will… I will explain.
The attempted murder charge
on Director Gu Hyunseong
is a groundless attack
by a prosecutor
who holds a personal grudge
against Banseok University Medical Center.
I swear on my honor
that he did no such thing.
Shouldn't Director Gu Hyunseong
explain himself?
How could you entrust the future
of Banseok University Medical Center
to someone who hides
behind his father at times like this?
I can't agree with such a decision.
I agree.
Excuse me.
What is it?
We are sorry to interrupt.
We will leave
after we perform our official duty.
Who are you people? How dare you do this?
I told you just now.
We are performing our official duty.
How could you say that
when you appear all the time?
It's an abuse of authority!
Actually, it's a use of authority.
A use of authority.
It aligns with my values as a prosecutor.
I look after the weak
and brandish my authority to the powerful.
It's the only way to keep the balance.
If you disobey a subpoena again,
I will summon you
as a suspect the next time.
If you still fail to show up,
I will request an arrest warrant.
Assistant Director Lee Dohyung.
Me?
Please let go.
Judge wisely.
The Legal Team at Banseok
might no longer be on your side.
Excuse me for the interruption.
Please proceed with the meeting.
-What just happened?
-Seriously.
Goodness.
Now, let's have a vote.
Former Chairman Gu Jingi.
Thank you for making time.
Don't mention it.
I knew I would get a visit someday
from you
or Banseok.
What was your relationship with Kitae?
We kept it a secret at the workplace,
but we dated for a long time.
We even thought of marriage.
We met for the last time
before he got arrested.
Why don't you want me
to visit you or go to the trial?
Do you still want to hide
our relationship?
No. It isn't like that, Jungwon.
I don't want
to put you in danger.
What dangers are there?
Please tell me.
You could get arrested tomorrow!
I wanted to propose to you
in the coolest way,
so I made preparations for months.
Who knew it would be so lame?
I am such a fool, right?
I changed my mind.
You know what?
I will put this on your finger
after this situation gets resolved.
Until then,
please hold on to it. Okay?
Afterward, as you already know,
he got arrested
and was murdered in prison.
For a while, I was beside myself.
Then…
I found this.
It was hidden
at the bottom of the ring case.
Did you check the content?
Yes.
As soon as I did, I left Banseok
and came here.
Chairman Gu Jingi ordered a murder, right?
I will announce the result.
The vote was for the appointment
of Mr. Gu Hyunseong as the director
of Banseok University Medical Center.
Five people voted for it
and 11 people voted against it.
Thus, the issue has been rejected.
-Yes!
-We did it!
We did it!
I am glad it got rejected.
I can't believe what he did.
How did Hyunseong get charged
with attempted murder?
What went behind my back?
Please don't drink so quickly.
You already drank quite a bit.
That female prosecutor is
the sister of the boy
who died at our hospital
due to an accident five years ago, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
-It got concluded as the surgeon's fault!
Why is she seeking revenge
after all these years?
Unbelievable.
For a while, stop attending events
and keep a low profile.
Don't go to work at the hospital.
No.
It will look like
I am admitting to the charges.
The attempted murder charge is an utter--
Just… Just do as I say.
None of your actions brought good results!
How is that my fault?
If you hadn't made Han Yihan do
the ghost surgery,
none of this would have happened.
You punk.
You are ashamed of me, right?
I am sick and tired of Han Yihan!
I got compared to him for 20 years
since university.
I wanted to surpass him one day.
But you killed that dream!
-Hyunseong.
-You made him my ghost doctor!
Do you know who made me feel the smallest?
Han Yihan? Jayden Lee?
No.
It's you, father.
Hyunseong.
Come on in.
Chairman Gu, you called for me.
I want to discuss something with you
for the future
of Banseok University Medical Center's
Cardiothoracic Surgery.
With me? About what?
At the trial for Geum Seokju's death,
there is something I want you to do.
As you know,
the process of a lung transplant
is more complex and difficult
than that of a heart transplant.
So cooperation
between the teams is the key.
For smooth extraction and transplantation,
we will open three operating rooms.
In Room One for lung extraction,
we will cut
Mr. Doh Jinwoo's right lower lobe.
In the room for lung transplantation,
I will open Ms. Yang Sunae's chest,
cut her right lung,
and transplant
Mr. Doh Jinwoo's right lower lobe.
While I perfuse
Ms. Yang Sunae's right lung
and cut her left lower lobe,
you will cut Ms. Yoon Miseon's
left lower lobe in Room Two.
In three operating rooms,
the patient and two donors
will go through anesthesia,
pneumonectomy, and transplantation
in a systematic way.
Set aside hard feelings
and focus on having
a successful operation.
How fascinating.
Although we were
at each other's throats yesterday,
we are hoping for a successful surgery
with one mind today.
It seems like you are entertained.
Of course not.
It's a matter of life and death.
I am simply here
to stop any unpleasant incidents
that might arise,
so don't hate me so much.
Ms. Yang Sunae,
the current time is 11:21 a.m.
We will administer anesthesia.
Okay.
Oxygen.
I will relay the information.
Everything has gone smoothly
with the extraction in Room One.
They are done with Mr. Doh Jinwoo,
so we can begin the operation.
Let's begin.
Contact Room One and ask them
to bring lung from Mr. Doh Jinwoo.
Yes, doctor.
Ms. Yang Sunae's operation has begun.
Please deliver the lung.
It's a bit small.
I will extract a lung.
Mr. Doh Jinwoo's left lower lobe
has arrived.
The condition is good,
but the size is a bit small.
Mr. Doh Jinwoo had tuberculosis.
This isn't unexpected, but…
It can't be helped. Let's begin.
I will attach the bronchial tubes first.
Forceps.
-Put the head down.
-Okay.
The clamps are coming off.
-Prepare for the bleeding.
-Okay.
-Injecting 500mg of steroids.
Use the Ambu bag.
Using the Ambu bag.
-Suction.
-Okay.
Removing air.
Good.
Tell Room Two to begin extraction.
Yes, doctor.
-We will now work on the left lower lobe.
-Okay.
Excuse me? What are you talking about?
Doctor.
What's the matter?
It's…
Ms. Yoon Miseon refused to donate
right before general anesthesia.
Dr. Han. I detect pulmonary edema.
It will be dangerous
if we don't transplant the lungs now.
Know this.
Your stupidity and greed are
the cause of her death.
My father can never betray
Chairman Gu Jingi.
Is there another reason why
he can't let go of Gu Jingi?
The living authority never gets inspected.
So please become the president.
Take it. It's yours.
Why are you giving this to me?
Think of it as a deposit.
I will buy the tip of your tongue.
This is Kwon Yoonseok.
Please come to the address
in the message. You must be alone.
Is this a trap?
Translated by Won-hyang Son