THE NAMES OF PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, AND
BACKGROUNDS OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
EPISODE 9
Hey, I'm ready.
-Yosub.
-Yihan.
Please let me join you too.
Thank you for coming.
It couldn't have been easy.
Let's go and operate.
Go to New-Hope Medicine Clinic.
Go and operate with Han Yihan.
Why do you want me…
Could it be…
that you want me to kill the patient?
Was everything to your satisfaction?
It was nice. Good work.
It was an honor to serve you.
1 HOUR 30 MINUTES BEFORE TRIAL
1 HOUR INTO OPERATION
Inject the cardioplegia solution.
The body temperature is 30°C.
Cardioplegia solution entering.
Cardioplegia solution has been injected.
Let's cut the aorta.
What was that lawyer's name, Han Yihan?
Will you let him be?
The Legal Team is preparing
to press charges.
Things will quiet down,
so please don't be concerned.
Make sure to shake him off.
The last minister had
a dishonorable discharge.
If you fail at the hearing
due to a scandal,
I would lose face as someone
who recommended you.
Don't worry.
Would you like to step inside?
No. I have somewhere to be.
Now that I am old,
it's hard to wait endlessly.
Prosecutor Geum, I don't think we need
photos of her leaving. Shall we go?
You should go.
You're of no help anyway.
Why do you want to stay?
I am not complaining because I am tired.
I don't want her to enter the trial
without a wink of sleep.
Wait. She is coming out.
What? She is coming out.
That took her long enough.
I wonder what kind of treatments
she received,
but her face is glowing.
Seriously.
Who would think
that she is close to hitting 60?
Thank you for today.
I will head straight to the court,
so wrap up and get off work.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay.
30 MINUTES BEFORE TRIAL
2 HOURS INTO OPERATION
We have a visual.
Scalpel number 11.
Yihan, are you okay?
I am okay.
Would it be necessary to go?
There will be reporters.
I agree with him.
I am sure it won't happen,
but if Nam Hyukchul tries something…
"If you seek revenge,
you should dig two graves."
-Pardon?
-He dug his own grave for revenge,
so I should put my heart into this.
It's time.
COUNSEL
PROSECUTION
DEFENDANT
What brings you here?
I am here to see
how my investment comes to fruition.
You have stopped hiding your intention.
Fine. In that case,
I will let go of manners for an investor.
You should, Father.
That brat has neither honor nor class.
We should have never associated with him.
Class?
Someone who hasn't achieved anything
other than being a chairman's son
would say such things.
But once Bankseok falls,
you won't have anything left.
Not wealth and honor.
-Not even Yuna.
-You little…
Nonsense.
Banseok will never fall.
Do you know why?
I won't let that happen.
The weather is nice.
SURGICAL TIMER, CURRENT TIME,
ANESTHESIA TIMER
Are you all right, Yihan?
-Please wrap it up.
-Okay.
Cut.
Taking off ACC.
The vital signs seem to be stable,
so let's reduce the pump.
Please reduce it.
Okay. Reducing the drainage.
Pump flow 70.
Reduce it further.
Pump flow 30.
Clamp.
Stop the pump.
Stopping the pump.
One, two, three.
We stopped the drainage.
-Check the ventricular septum.
-Yes.
The ventricular septum is 160mm.
The pulse pressure is 57mmHg.
The pulse pressure is still…
SURGICAL TIMER, CURRENT TIME,
ANESTHESIA TIMER
Let's stop the heart again.
Start the pump.
Starting the pump.
One, two, three.
The pump has been started.
Aorta clamp.
Inject the cardioplegia solution.
Give me 700ml.
Cardioplegia solution entering.
Yihan, will you stop the heart again?
His problems will return soon.
Another open-heart surgery
will be more dangerous.
Still, the trial…
SURGICAL TIMER, CURRENT TIME,
ANESTHESIA TIMER
Right now, we should focus
on saving the patient.
Cardioplegia solution has been injected.
Removing the suture. Scalpel.
Yihan.
Your hand…
Hurry up and give me a scalpel.
I'll do it.
Your arm isn't in the right state.
Let me operate.
Have you done
hypertrophic cardiomyopathy surgery?
"If you fear the first,
you can't be a good doctor."
You told me those words.
I know it's a difficult surgery, but…
But I will do it.
It's a surgery you must succeed in…
on time.
We'll switch places. Come to my side.
Okay.
Don't be nervous. I will assist you.
Scalpel.
I will begin.
All rise.
Please sit down.
The attorney isn't here. What happened?
The defendant's attorney is absent.
Absent? Without notice?
Yes, your Honor.
He scaled up the situation
and went out of contact.
Defendant, did you hear anything
from your attorney?
PROSECUTION
COUNSEL
It can't be helped.
As the attorney is absent, the trial--
Your Honor.
The defendant's attorney
contacted me before the trial.
Did he contact you? What did he say?
He has to run an operation
on an emergency patient at his hospital,
so he wanted permission
on delaying the trial to the afternoon.
Since he couldn't contact
the justice department,
he had no choice
but to relay the information to me.
An operation?
That doesn't excuse his absence.
He told me that
defending the accused is as important
as operating on the patient.
So if the justice department
doesn't allow the delay,
he will halt the operation and come.
In my 30 years as a judge,
it's my first time
seeing an attorney run an operation.
The current time is 10:15 a.m.
The trial will resume in an hour.
If he can't come until then,
he should choose between the two jobs.
All rise.
You are doing well.
So that it doesn't become thick,
cut the inside.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I think there's a tear in the heart wall.
What happened? Did something go wrong?
-For how long has the pump been going?
-It has been going for 45 minutes.
It's okay. The heart is on arrest,
so there won't be bleeding. We have time.
-But…
-We can suture the damaged area.
So keep going.
Believe in yourself.
Okay.
-Is it done?
-Yes.
Further inside.
SURGICAL TIMER, CURRENT TIME,
ANESTHESIA TIMER
Is the defendant's attorney still absent?
Yes, your Honor.
The trial isn't a joke.
If the attorney doesn't show up right now,
the trial won't take place today.
What is it?
Your Honor, my name is Pyo Eunsil
and I am a lawyer.
If the accused wishes, could I provide
my legal service to the defendant?
No.
Ms. Pyo Eunsil is
the Head of the Legal Team at Banseok,
the hospital
where the murdered doctors worked at.
Their interests overlap.
We also can't rule out the possibility
of her becoming the witness.
Thus, she can't defend him.
Banseok Foundation?
Are her words true?
Yes, your Honor.
However, all Korean citizens
have the right to be assisted
by the attorney of their choice
in order to protect themselves.
Thus, the defendant should have
a chance to choose a new attorney.
Defendant, do you have the intention
to change the attorney?
COUNSEL
I will think about it.
Understood.
It's unprecedented,
but we have no right to disallow
what the defendant wants.
We will adjourn for ten minutes.
Ms. Pyo, talk to the defendant
and get his consent.
Thank you, your Honor.
All rise.
That was unexpected.
The Head of Banseok's Legal Team
stepped forward to defend the accused.
They want to silence him,
but he won't turn that easily
because his son's life is at stake.
Are you telling me
Dr. Han will kill the boy
if Nam Hyukchul
doesn't do what he promised?
No. He would never kill a patient.
A hostage you can never kill.
Such a hostage has no value.
You are right. However,
Nam Hyukchul wouldn't think that.
He is a murderer, so he will think as one.
You are right.
He killed two people for his gain.
In any case, Dr. Han is the only one…
It's him.
Hey. How did it go?
The surgery went well.
I am on my way to the court.
Please buy me some time.
Okay.
But Pyo Eunsil is having a meeting
with Nam Hyukchul.
Pyo Eunsil? Why?
She wants to defend him.
The court will allow it
if Nam Hyukchul agrees.
Okay. I will be there as soon as possible.
How did it go?
The surgery was successful.
He is on his way to the court.
What is this?
Why do you want to represent me?
You don't understand the situation fully
because you are locked up.
You don't want to hurt your son
by making the wrong decision, do you?
After using me as you saw fit,
you threaten me about my son.
If I think about the way
you toyed with me,
I want to reveal everything in court.
Shall I do that?
Get your facts straight.
You toyed with us.
You are the one who betrayed the chairman
and sided with Han Yihan.
You should have saved my son
from the start!
I killed two people.
But you kept pushing things off
and refused to take action!
Calm down. I am not here to fight.
What is it?
Check it yourself. We'll talk then.
Defendant, did you make up your mind?
Yes, your Honor.
I won't change the attorney.
He won't change the attorney?
Understood.
Then we will decide on a new trial date.
Your Honor.
The defendant's attorney is
on his way to the court.
If you give him more time…
No. We have waited for too long.
Besides, in this situation,
he should have sent another attorney.
Why does he keep contacting you?
We are scheduled for other trials
in the afternoon too. We will end…
Your Honor!
I'm the defendant's counsel, Han Yihan.
There was a patient I had to save
with this surgery,
so I couldn't make it on time.
I'm sorry.
So did you save the patient?
Yes, your Honor. I did.
I was able to finish the surgery
thanks to your patience.
Thank you.
Great. Then we will begin
the trial right away.
-You may take your seat, counsel.
-Thank you.
WITNESS WAITING ROOM
Han Yihan is in the courtroom now.
It's not too late to refuse to testify.
No.
We'll stick to our plan.
The prosecution indicted the defendant
for murder. Correct?
Yes.
The defendant pleads guilty to the charge.
But he's arguing that it was
involuntary manslaughter due to insanity.
-Yes.
-Your Honor.
Can I elaborate regarding my investigation
to obtain evidence?
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
I'd like to present evidence number 20,
the victim's visitation log from prison.
During the three months the victim,
Park Kitae, was incarcerated,
the defendant had never contacted
the victim.
But the defendant's counsel
was changed for the trial
regarding Lee Hojun's death.
The night before
the ruling was to be announced,
the defendant attacked the victim
and killed him in the end
as if he was trying to stop the victim
from getting released
after the ruling the next day.
Your Honor, the last claim is
subjective speculation
from the prosecutor.
Sustained.
Do you have evidence
to support your claim?
Yes, I do.
This is the defendant's medical record in
the detention center, evidence number 19.
The defendant visited the infirmary
once a month
ever since he was incarcerated
six years ago.
But at the point
of the victim's incarceration,
the number of visits increased notably.
Ten visits a month.
Is that relevant to your claim
that the defendant was instigated
to commit murder?
Yes, it is.
The person who delivered Chairman Gu's
murder request to the defendant
was the medical director
at the detention center.
Objection.
The prosecutor's claim is not true.
She's making a one-sided claim.
Who was it?
Not everyone can get their hands
on a knife made of obsidian.
Who gave it to you?
Answer it.
We must know so we can trust you
and at least come up with a plan.
The medical director
from the detention center.
I got the order from Gu Jingi
to kill Park Kitae
and heard
that my son's condition got worse
all from him.
I'll have a reporter cover the suspicion
of Chairman Gu's instigation of murder.
And I will defend you for
involuntary manslaughter due to insanity.
Due to insanity?
Why? That won't work. I'm on death row.
Even a death-row inmate deserves counsel.
As your attorney, I'm going to do my best.
Prosecution, will you be able to take
responsibility for what you just said?
Of course.
To prove my claim, I would like to
question Chairman Gu Jingi as my witness.
I'll add that once I finish investigating
the witness for instigation of murder,
and I'll indict him accordingly and alter
the charge on the arraignment as well.
Okay then.
Guard, bring in the witness.
Okay.
CHAIRMAN GU JINGI OF BANSEOK FOUNDATION
HAD A DOCTOR MURDERED
Witness, you are asked to testify.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Witness, proceed with the oath.
I solemnly swear
to tell the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth
under pains and penalties of perjury.
Witness Gu Jingi.
Witness, you may refuse any questions
relevant to your criminal case.
Prosecution, question the witness.
Yes, your Honor.
You are Director
of Banseok University Medical Center and
Chairman of Banseok Foundation. Correct?
Yes, correct.
The defendant used to supply
medical equipment to your hospital.
And he murdered two of your doctors.
What do you think about this?
As the director of the hospital,
I feel ethically responsible.
Ethical responsibility. Is that all?
That's correct.
Let me ask you again. Witness.
Did you order the defendant,
Nam Hyukchul, to commit murder?
Hold on.
Witness, I already informed you
that you can refuse to answer
any questions
relevant to your criminal case.
Think carefully before you answer that.
I did
no such thing.
I'm here today to quash
an absurd suspicion
a certain news agency wrote about.
I did not have any sort of business
with the defendant.
Your Honor,
may I question the defendant to see
if the witness is telling the truth?
-Right now?
-Yes.
I believe this is the surest way
to judge if the suspicion
about the witness is true or not.
Let us discuss that.
We kept our side of the bargain.
It's your turn now.
WITNESS
All right. We'll check now.
Defendant.
Do you agree with the claim
the witness just made?
Let me ask you again.
Is it true that the witness
ordered you to commit murder?
Yes.
I was told to kill him.
DEFENDANT
I…
I said I didn't want to do it.
But he kept whispering to me.
I was told to kill the devil.
Only then I would be saved!
I was told to kill the devil
with my own hands!
Defendant, what is this nonsense?
I saved Hojun's soul!
I will be saved too!
I brought justice to that devil!
Defendant, calm down.
If you disrupt the court again,
you will be escorted out!
He kept mumbling to my ears.
Stop screaming at me!
I'm so sick of it!
It won't be easy, as expected.
What was that?
Guard! Take him out!
I did what I was told!
Get your hands off me, you devils!
Get off me!
I will be saved!
Get off me! I'll be saved!
All right.
We'll end today's trial here.
If you have
any additional evidence to submit,
you can do so in writing.
All rise.
Hey, Daewoong.
Yihan! Mr. Cheon is here
with security guards.
I'm trying to stop them, but I don't think
I can hold out much longer.
Come at me, you punks!
YIHAN
Congratulations.
So you aced your first surgery
after five years.
I knew you could do it.
What's that look?
You should be thanking me.
I sent you Dr. Choi
right when you needed him.
So you saved the patient.
You sent Yosub to me?
Hostages are valuable when they are alive.
So I told him to go and save my hostage.
Could it be
that you want me to kill the patient?
Kill the patient?
What are you talking about?
Go and do your best
to save the patient as a doctor.
Call me once the surgery is over.
Why should I call you?
Yosub. Don't think about anything.
Just focus on your surgery as a doctor.
Okay.
-You punk.
-Stop!
You never said you would hurt him.
Come on.
That's enough. Move the patient now.
Doctor.
Proceed.
PATIENT ROOMS 1-3, OPERATING ROOM
So you kidnapped the patient?
You kidnapped a patient who's recovering
from surgery. And a minor at that.
This is beyond violating
the Medical Service Act.
Kidnap?
I got the parent's consent
and transferred him.
If you don't believe it,
you can check it yourself.
I felt ethically responsible
for your brother's death.
So I've been very lenient with you.
But if you come after my son
and Banseok again,
you must be ready to face the consequence.
Do you see it now?
Even if you dig two graves,
I won't be joining you.
So give up.
Unless you want to end up like your dad.
The plan fell through, right?
What will you do next?
You're on bad terms with Gu Jingi now.
They caught my knight.
So I must move my queen.
Lim Yuna?
In the hypothetical matchup against
Candidate Yoon Miseon of Daehan Party,
the gap was 4%.
But the gap in the ratings went up to 7%
in a four-person matchup
with the ruling party's candidate.
Various media outlets covered Ms. Lim
being the youngest director
of the R and D Center.
But Assemblywoman Yoon
raised suspicions if she had received
preferential treatment.
Due to the series of recent lawsuits
against Banseok Foundation,
its reputation has been damaged.
And it may possibly affect your ratings
to drop again in the future.
Do you think
I made you my campaign adviser,
so you could tell me what I already know?
If there's a problem,
bring me an alternative plan.
To make a crisis into an opportunity.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll come up with a counterplan soon.
What brings you here?
I invited him.
I thought the ratings
might be giving you a headache.
I'm here to offer my help.
You want to help me? How?
Howard L. Junior,
the Republican presidential candidate.
How about a meeting with him?
The US and Korea.
A meeting between two
presidential candidates from two countries
would mean a lot, wouldn't it?
This is offensive.
I'm sure you know
about the bad blood between him and me
since my post as an ambassador in the US.
That's why I would like to help you.
I will set up a meeting so you two
can sort out the misunderstanding.
With the influence of Honours Hand.
I'm curious to know
why you are offering your help.
I would like to show you
that I will be more useful in helping you
become the president
than Chairman Gu Jingi.
He also knows
that Chairman Gu Jingi is weighing you
and Assemblywoman Yoon.
When someone tries
to have diamonds in both hands,
then you can
just break one of the diamonds.
I'm not sure
if this golf club will suit you.
Would you like to take a swing?
There's a similar proverb in Korean too.
An artisan doesn't blame his tools.
DR. HAN YIHAN
Dr. Han.
Was this your plan all along?
No. I…
Come to New-Hope right now.
It's all right. I wasn't wrong.
I got it! Stop talking to me!
Stop whispering to me!
Shut it! Shut your mouth!
Gosh. It only took a couple of days
for him to lose it.
He's a total nutcase now.
No. The gut of an investigator
with 30 years of experience tells me
that he's putting on an act.
If that's an act,
he should win the Grand Award.
He's been at it for 30 minutes.
-I'll be saved.
-Prosecutor Geum, tough case.
Can you give me some privacy?
-What?
I need to find out
why he's screwing us now.
INTERROGATION ROOM
I'll be saved.
Stop it! I did everything you asked me!
Stop whispering to me.
Stop talking to me. Just stop.
Stop it.
What? Keep acting crazy.
Cut your act. We need to talk.
I turned off the cameras.
I told everyone to leave the room.
If you don't trust me,
go and check it yourself.
I don't stab people
in the back unlike you.
I'm sorry…
for not keeping my promise.
You're sorry?
An apology won't cut it!
I had no choice.
That lawyer threatened me with my son.
A transfer request?
Yes. If you sign it,
we'll move your son back to Banseokwon.
You think I'm crazy?
Why would I let you
hold my son hostage again?
That's right.
He's a valuable hostage to us.
That's why when someone else has him,
it's better to get rid of him.
What are you implying?
Come on. Don't glare at me like that.
This is nothing new to you.
You killed Dr. Park too.
Wouldn't it be easier to kill your son
since he's not even conscious now?
If you do that, I will…
What? What are you going to do?
You're on death row.
You'll never get out of prison.
Are you going to stay
by his side or something?
If you still can't make up your mind,
let me tell you one more thing.
Prosecutor Geum's supervisor,
the senior prosecutor of Medical Crime
Department is on our side too.
This was a losing game from the get-go.
What if something were to happen to him?
You don't have to worry about that.
The people from New-Hope Medicine Clinic
aren't the type to harm a patient
in any circumstances.
I wanted to keep my promise. I mean it.
But my son is still unconscious.
If they were to do something to my son…
Right.
Mr. Han Yihan would never hurt a patient.
But I'm different.
I'm sure your wife must have told you.
I may not be able to kill your son,
but I can make him live in hell.
So you will have to do your best
to tell me all the secrets
between you and Gu Jingi.
If I don't get anything useful from you,
I don't know what I will do.
I was in the dark too.
I didn't even think
that he would request a transfer.
I'm sorry.
You saved my son's life.
I need you to testify then.
Not now.
He has my son again.
If I testify…
So…
-will you join hands with him again?
-No.
I have no intention of doing that.
It tormented me too.
If it weren't for my son,
I would've walked away long ago.
As soon as he wakes up,
I'll get him discharged right away.
And I'll testify to everything.
If I testify, my husband will do the same.
I don't want
to be forced to commit crimes
by the chairman any longer.
How can I trust you again?
You already betrayed me once.
Right. It won't be easy to trust me again.
So…
I want to tell you
one more crime I committed.
It's about Dr. Han Jihyuk.
Who?
Dr. Han Jihyuk…
didn't commit suicide.
He was forced to commit suicide.
Dad!
-Honey…
-No! Dad.
What do you mean?
My father
was forced to commit suicide?
I killed him.
What do you mean?
-I heard Yihan's father committed suicide.
-Right.
He hanged himself at his house.
And Director Gu Jingi
and I made him kill himself.
The late doctor and Director Gu Jingi
did compete for the Head
of Cardiothoracic Surgery position.
But they got along
until that incident.
"That incident?"
The former director of Banseok,
Jang Taejun.
You know him, right?
He was the founder of Banseok Foundation.
Your dad performed emergency surgery
on him for the aortic dissection.
But he died in the end.
How can I forget?
That surgery
ruined my family.
I was
on his surgery team.
And so was Assistant Director Lee Dohyung.
I'll stop the heart.
After that, I'll run
the cardiopulmonary bypass machine.
And I'll operate
using the brain perfusion method.
That way, his heart will keep functioning,
and we can avoid brain damage.
No. It's too risky.
There have been only two cases.
I can't perform
an unverified surgery technique.
There were only two cases,
but their post-ops were excellent.
And the recent experimental research paper
had good results as well.
No.
I see him as my father-in-law first
before the chairman.
I can't let my family member
take such a huge risk like that.
Trust me, and let me do this. Okay?
I'll perform the surgery
and take full responsibility.
This technique will give him
a better chance of recovering.
I can't give up without even trying first.
The brain perfusion method
with the cardiopulmonary bypass machine…
is widely practiced now.
But 20 years ago,
no one tried that technique.
Even a major hospital like Banseok
didn't have a proper curriculum
for extracorporeal circulation back then.
But…
-my father…
-Yes.
But there was a problem.
His BP is dropping.
His BP keeps dropping. At this rate…
Pump. Keep his vitals stable.
What about his head? Cerebral oximeter.
It's at 12. It keeps dropping.
-Increase the pump flow.
-I can't. Not enough drainage.
He might have a cardiac arrest.
Raise it!
Oddly, the bleeding was severe.
Back then, I wasn't as experienced.
So I couldn't handle
this type of emergency situation.
To be honest, there was something
I couldn't understand even more.
The late chairman's health condition
couldn't be disclosed to the public,
so I understood the minimum number
of staff was on the surgical team.
And I knew it was an emergency surgery.
But Dr. Lee Dohyung
had just gotten his medical license.
And making him the anesthesiologist…
Who put together the team?
Chairman Gu Jingi.
He was never going
to save the late chairman.
That's why he put Lee Dohyung on the team.
An inexperienced anesthesiologist
who doesn't deserve to be called a doctor.
So they wanted the patient to die
from the beginning?
Why?
Because Jang Taejun
had chosen to appoint Dr. Han Jihyuk
the next director of the hospital.
He thought
if Gu Jingi became the director,
his sons, Jang Jungtae and Jang Yoontae,
wouldn't be able to survive in Banseok.
A father was looking out
for his incompetent sons.
But still.
How could he kill his father-in-law?
He was his wife's father.
Think about everything he did so far.
You know
he's more than capable of doing so.
Look who's talking, right?
I'm the one
who framed Dr. Han Jihyuk for bribery
under Director Gu Jingi's order.
Just like
how Han Yihan was framed five years ago.
INTERROGATION ROOM
You said my father was
forced to commit suicide.
How did Gu Jingi
drive my father to death?
Back then,
it was before the computer system
was implemented.
So we had to write
the surgery records manually.
But…
You want me to change the record
about administering hemostatics?
But why…
He said he would take full responsibility.
So we must give him what he wants.
But that's a crime.
I'm sorry.
I'll pretend I didn't hear…
Then will you take responsibility?
Pardon?
If Han Jihyuk doesn't take responsibility,
you will be next
to blame for operating
the cardiopulmonary bypass machine.
Wouldn't that be unfair?
If he didn't insist
on the brain profusion method,
this wouldn't have happened.
Just this once.
If you turn a blind eye just this once,
I'll promise you
that a lot of things will change.
Just once.
I was only going to do that just once.
Back then, I was young too.
And I was scared.
I regretted what I did
after your father left the hospital.
But not my husband.
It took years for him to invent
a surgical device, Contentor.
And Chairman Gu Jingi
approved the purchase.
So he was barely able
to avoid going bankrupt.
I was against this,
but I couldn't reason with him.
He said it was too late to pull out
and we were on the same boat with him.
So…
after framing my father for everything,
the hospital shamelessly filed a lawsuit,
demanding an astronomical sum of money
for the damage.
That was all
to corner my father to death.
It was Gu Jingi.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect
Dr. Han Jihyuk to die like that.
It didn't even cross my mind.
I continued to regret it.
But then Junhwan was born,
and I found out about his weak heart.
Since then, I had no choice
but to obey him.
I'm sorry.
I'm… I'm so sorry.
You've done well.
You successfully finished
that tough surgery,
so I could end everything smoothly.
Don't mention it.
You won't face any problems
at tomorrow's heart transplant
if you perform like today.
It should even be easier.
It's much less dangerous than
hypertrophic cardiomyopathy surgery.
And you'll be with an experienced senior.
Hyunseong, you should leave
the past behind.
You two should trust each other and
lead the Cardiothoracic Surgery together.
Dr. Choi is a talent
we cannot live without
in this hospital.
I should do that.
Let's have a good run, Dr. Choi.
Yes.
All right. Have a drink.
What a loss.
That was expensive liquor.
I feel bad for Han Yihan.
He keeps getting betrayed
by the ones he trusted.
Anyway, welcome aboard.
Let's make things work together.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me.
Just throw it out after.
And wipe that too.
Father, it has been days.
Enough is enough.
I'm sorry, my son.
I'm…
I'm sorry.
You always say you're sorry,
but it's just words!
Don't you see this?
We're about to lose our home
because of your malpractice.
You aren't the only one who's in distress.
Mom is out preparing for the lawsuit.
You can't sit here and drink.
I'll take responsibility.
I'll take care of everything.
I'll make sure our family doesn't suffer.
I'll take responsibility.
I'll do it.
I'm sorry.
I receive a lot of help from you,
but your plan didn't go through.
It's all right.
Not all investments lead to success.
However, this time,
I need you two to cooperate with my plan.
What's the plan?
There's an extraordinary board meeting
for Banseok Foundation next week.
THE FOUNDER OF BANSEOK FOUNDATION
JANG TAEJUN
Jang Yoontae and Jang Jungtae.
The sons of Jang Taejun,
the founder of Banseok Foundation.
They're both directors of the foundation.
Five years ago, the princes' coup failed,
and they've kept low profiles since then.
But apparently, they've been meeting
other directors in secret
before this extraordinary board meeting.
Our plan is to make the chairman
out of the older son, Jang Yoontae,
to minimize the influence
Chairman Gu Jingi has over the board.
This is our only timing.
Chairman Gu Jingi will put down
every title related to Banseok Foundation
before his hearing for the ministership.
2022 THE 3RD EXTRAORDINARY
BOARD MEETING ITEMS
Directors Jang Yoontae and Jang Jungtae
will take the lead
in suggesting your dismissal
of the titles you hold at the foundation
before your appointment.
It'll be tough to fight.
That's the custom.
But I cannot let those two
have the chairmanship.
Once your wife returns, she can take
the chairmanship of the foundation.
But do leave the hospital director open
until you find an adequate candidate.
I'll do it.
Yuna is much younger than I am,
but she's the director of a center.
I don't see why not.
Please trust me and leave it to me.
I'll prove myself.
And the hospital director?
The director of Banseok University
Medical Center will be left open soon.
Do you have anyone in your mind?
Of course.
I see him right before me.
If Honours Hand takes
Banseok Foundation over as planned,
I'll have Dr. Han appointed
as the director of the hospital.
Thank you for your offer,
but I am not interested.
Are you sure?
If you become
the director of the hospital,
it'll be the best revenge you can have
against Chairman Gu Jingi.
We still have time, so give it a thought.
If you do not take
what your enemy cherishes the most,
no matter what your revenge is,
how can that be any meaningful?
You're getting way ahead of yourself.
It's not like Honours Hand
already has enough shares.
You don't know
if the directors will do as you like.
That's why I prepared
the best card to convince the board.
I heard the story.
That you are
the best cardiac surgeon in Korea
who stood in for Director Gu Hyunseong.
Is this true?
Please give me an answer.
Have you been operating
on the hearts of Banseokwon's VIPs
in Gu Hyunseong's place?
That's correct.
I'm the doctor
who operated in Gu Hyunseong's place.
I'm his ghost doctor, Han Yihan.
WE THANK LEE JUNGYEOL
FOR HIS SPECIAL APPEARANCE
Can you be in charge of my heart?
Have you ever received heart surgery?
Did you put a tail on us?
What do you mean?
Let's talk for a moment.
I'm not with them. I'm an attorney.
Tell me.
What happened between
Assemblywoman Yoon and her daughter?
I'll have your mean heart fixed too.
I call 1.5 billion won.
The gentleman in the back
bid 1.55 billion won.
-I call 1.7 billion won.
-Again, 1.75 billion won.
What about 1.8 billion? Anyone?
It's a present for the new chairman
of Banseok Foundation.
Translated by Dong-joo Park