Oh.
You awake.
Wow.
They look delicious.
Hey!
Be careful!
Whoa!
You should be waiting outside.
You’re blocking my way.
I have to cook.
Go, Wait outside.
Hey bro!
What are you doing?
I'm working.
You dare lie to a satellite operator like me?
Huh?
If you already know, what are you asking for?
Right?
Hm.
So what do you want?
Nothing.
I just wondering
that
What are you doing?
Just hurry up and destroy the world.
Then come back to the space.
Well.
I am.
Um.
I.
How about this?
I will go meet you there.
But
after my work.
Let's meet at our usual coordinates
No!
Hey!
What?
Oh no.
Here is your food.
Wow.
So
Do you really treat me to a meal?
Hm.
Well, when you get a job.
You can treat me back.
Oh and
if you feel sick or unwell
you can tell me.
Oh.
Thank you so much.
Enjoy your food.
Mm.
Huh?
If you already know, what are you asking for?
Right?
Hm.
So what do you want?
Maybe he’s a psychiatric patient?
Strange.
Oh my!
I like it!
Korean style.
Here.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Thank you.
Thank you too.
Please come back again next time.
See you later.
Mimi?
Where are you going?
Did you come alone?
Come here.
Come to me.
I would like to get a haircut.
This way please.
Your coffee is here!
Why don't you wear the head part?
I need a break.
So hot.
Here.
Your coffee.
Gosh!
I’m so tired.
Why are you wearing it then?
You always complain.
Well my Boss told me to wear it.
He said it was for marketing.
Hey. I ordered only one cup
I didn't order this one.
You order this one.
But I think that guy.
That one.
He wants this one.
Hm?
Fine.
Thank you!
Any special price for two?
Oh, come on. They’re for selling not bargaining.
Hm.
Don’t forget my change.
I don't have change. How about this evening?
I will give it to you.
Tan!
Stop there!
Mm! Mm!
Mm!
Wait a second
Wait.
Can you give me more money?
Huh?
Hm.
Well I
want more money.
Could you
find me a job?
Job?
Yes.
Again?
Like.
There is no other job in this world?
Well.
You look cute!
Right?
What are you laughing at?
Cute.
Look at how cute this is.
Fine. Cute then.
Well.
You need money.
You can split the job with me, half a day each.
And I will share the money with you.
Hm.
Here.
Take this.
I will go deliver the coffee first.
Um.
Oof!
And follow me ok?
Don’t slack off.
Hm.
Be careful.
Here.
Coffee.
Mm.
Hm.
Hm!
Ah.
Wow.
So refreshing!
Woo!
This planet is absolutely amazing!
I'm ready!
I’m ready to work!
For this planet!
Yay!
Hey.
That sounds familiar.
For the star~
I long to be~
To be the star, the dream isn't far~
Are you a fan of the show The Star?
Huh?
My favorite is the 6th season.
Gun, Rit, and Tono.
"Especially Gun, he sings so incredibly well!"
How long will it take you to do this~
What?
Why do you seem confused? Never heard of it?
Never watched?
What is that?
About Rit I'm not sure. Maybe he's a doctor now.
He isn't sing anymore.
Just go.
Oh! Wait! Wait!
H-huh?
Wait a second.
Hm.
Take this with you.
Oh.
I made it for you.
For when you feel hungry.
Thank you so much.
Hey!
Yes?
You forgot this.
Oh.
Here.
Very good.
Hey!
Come on!
Ouch!
I’m just kidding.
Wrong side.
I’m sorry. Sorry.
There.
Here.
Put it on.
Ok.
Looking good.
Be careful ok?
Ok.
And keep singing.
For the star~
Huh?
Sing after me.
For the star~
I long to be~
The dream isn't far~
Very good keep singing.
Why don't you sing it yourself?
Hm.
Good luck .
Bye bye.
Oh, you left so much food, Mimiw!
Hello, Uncle.
Oh, hello.
Are you preparing food for Mimiw?
Hm.
Always leaves the leftover.
Oh, I bought this for you.
Thank you.
From which restaurant?
The one um.
Oh, the grandma’s restaurant right?
Ah, yes
The grandma cooked the food well.
But when it comes to her grandson.
I’m not sure if it would be delicious.
Hm.
I think
it's pretty delicious.
Yeah?
Oh and.
Where is Mimiw?
Hm.
I don't know. He must be traveling somewhere.
Hasn’t come back yet.
Hm.
Why don't you cage him?
Oh, no no.
You can not cage them.
Cats are animals that love freedom.
If we cage them
and once they are free
they will never come back.
Hm.
I see.
Let me prepare the food for you.
It's ok just leave it there.
Leave it there.
Well.
I will wait for Mimiw to come back first.
Yes.
Mimiw.
Meow. Meow.
Where are you little one?
Your food is ready.
Come eat them.
Where are you?
Mimiw?
Come here.
Come eat your food.
Where did you go?
Come. Come.
Mimiw.
Where are you?
Uncle.
I’ll take my leave then.
See you later.
Oh, alright.
Goodbye, uncle.
Um.
Meow. Meow.
God!
Gosh!
I can’t do this anymore!
Sigh.
Hi.
Ah!
You low-ranking engineer of space.
What is this?
What are you wearing?
Heh.
I'm just stopping by
Seriously.
When will you
blow up this planet.
I know that.
I’m working on it.
Working?
On what actually?
Each day.
I see you do nothing.
How did you know?
Eh?
Mm!
Ah!
Have you been secretly spying on me?
Not secretly.
I intend to do that.
Hm.
Actually.
I came here to tell you.
That our organization
is keeping an eye on you.
What do you mean?
Well, your duty
is to destroy this planet.
So that we can build a space expressway, right?
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and destroy it.
So you could get a promotion.
Plus, you get a hundred thousand food capsules!
I know that.
You do?
If you do, then hurry up.
I’m tired of answering other people's questions now.
They have been following me around.
Even more than how I follow you.
And why is that?
Don’t forget that
right now, I’m on satellite surveillance duty.
I can track you.
I’m here to warn you.
Come to think of it.
This planet is plain.
And
there’s no point in us staying for a long time.
That isn't true.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever.
Here.
Take it.
I brought it for you.
You may have nothing to eat.
I must go now.
Hurry up and destroy this planet, then come back quickly.
I will go now.
Heh.
Of course, I have.
There are delicious foods here, after all.
Dim!
Tan.
I told you that I don't want the coffee anymore.
Please take it.
If you don't
I’ll lose a whole glass's worth of income.
Please buy it.
Pretty please.
I do this much and you won’t buy my coffee?
What are your looking for?
Mimiw.
Have you seen him?
Oh.
Mimiw
Mimiw?
Mimiw.
Where is he? Maybe I had seen him?
Do you see it?
Do you want to know the answer?
If you want to know then
order my coffee first!
Hey.
I was kidding!
I haven’t seen him.
Just that.
Here.
Take it back.
Huh?
Wait! Dim!
Wrong side!
Come back and help me first!
It's a wrong side!
Dim!!
Come back! I can’t take it off.
Help me!
Sigh
Ah.
Sigh.
Why it's so tiring living on this planet?
Or should I hurry up and blow up this planet?
Then go back to working in the cold comfortable room.
As it was before?
Hm.
Sigh.
Wow.
Why is it looks so delicious?
Oh wow.
Wow!
Look so delicious.
Meow.
Heh-heh.
Hm.
Meow.
Meow. Meow.
Hey!
What are you doing?
Why are you staring at me?
This is my food, Not yours.
Pff.
I won’t eat your food!
Because I'm a cat.
I must eat cat food.
Heh.
But it smells really good.
I agree.
Hey,
by the way.
At your planet
what type of food did you have?
My planet?
Hm.
Capsule.
Huh?
Capsule?
Mm!
Oh!
We are the same.
Huh?
We also eat capsules on my planet.
So that's mean that
in this world
they have different foods from other planets.
Oh.
Hm. Sigh.
By the way.
You’re lucky.
Hm.
I got to eat a lot of different kinds of strange food.
Unlike me.
Eating only cat food.
So boring.
Well.
You are
a cat.
Heh-heh.
Hm.
That smells good.
Why? Are you hungry?
You have a lot more.
I want to try it.
Just small pieces.
Small piece.
But this is human food.
You are hungry, right?
It's made from fish. I can eat it.
Heh-heh.
Hm.
Smells good.
Aha.
Ah, I understand.
I understand now.
Here.
Take this.
Open it.
What is this?
Ah!
Capsule?
Yes, capsule.
You brought it with you?
Yes, I have some left.
Oh well.
You can keep it for yourself.
It's alright. I have my food here.
You can eat the capsule.
Capsule?
So that we can eat together
Mm.
So delicious.
Hm.
Mm!
This thing is really good.
Have a good taste.
I don't know how they cook it.
Oh wow.
Heh-heh
Why don't you eat the capsule?
Come on. Eat it.
Hm.
Come to think of it.
I haven’t eaten it in a long time.
Hm.
I don't even remember the taste of it.
Already forgot.
Hm.
But
it doesn't look delicious
like that you're eating.
Are you full?
Eat it.
Come on.
Hm.
Finally.
Aha.
How is it?
It's stiff.
Stiff?
Yes.
Then try to swallow it.
My throat feels dry.
Swallow it.
I cannot.
Cannot?
Mm.
Then lift your head up.
Aha!
Let me help you.
Not yet?
Help!
It stuck in my throat.
Can’t swallow yet?
It stuck in my throat!
Hm.
Hm!
Swallow it.
Swallow it!
Hey!
Come on! Swallow it.
Hey! Hey!
Swallow it!
Huh?
What are you doing?
You must be so scared.
Huh?
It's ok now.
I just.
I’m trying to help him.
Help?
You're trying to kill him!
What?
Wait.
Kill him?
Me?
I didn't try to kill him.
Well, it’s obvious!
There. There. It's ok now.
Are you scared?
Huh?
Wait. No. No.
I was helping him.
Let's go.
I will take you home.
Wait.
Hey.
Hiss.
Let's go home.
Ahem!
Ah!
Huh?
What?
Oh.
You.
Hey, you.
Why are you dressing up to mock me?
What? No, I’m not mocking you.
This is my working costume.
Oh,
by the way.
Did you came from
the planet Mau like Mimiw?
Sigh.
You can say that.
That's good.
You have a friend.
What do you mean by that?
Well,
you have friends too, coming from the same planet.
Unlike me. I have no friends
that came from the same planet.
Are you sure?
I’m sure.
Is that so?
It is.
That's not true.
I saw you
staying at the human house.
The one that opens a restaurant.
How did you know?
Of course I know!
I’m Ngao!
The genius!
I know everything in this planet.
Oh.
Everything huh?
You can say that.
What?
You mock me twice already.
Oh and
is he kind?
Are you talking about the humans who sell food?
Hm.
Heh.
Sigh.
Huh?
By the way, how long have you been here?
Very long.
But
I have no home to live.
Unlike that round-headed orange cat."
The one with a funny face.
But I think he looks like you.
Thank you.
That's the third time already.
Third times.
Oh.
Whatever.
However, I
don't like having an owner.
An owner?
Yes,
I like being alone.
If you want to live in this planet
you must have an owner.
If not, you will become a stray.
Hm?
Stray?
How stray?
Wandering around.
No home to live.
No bed.
If it rains,
you have to find a pile of garbage
to take shelter from the rain.
When I'm hungry
I have to wait for a kind person to bring me food.
If no one gives me
I have to find it in the trash.
Talking about it makes me feel sad.
Crying.
Hm.
Oh,
fish smell.
Can you smell it?
I start to feel hungry now.
Then I'd better go get something to eat.
A cat like me has dignity.
I don't eat food from human hands.
Must be only trash.
Meow!
Hey!
Oh.
Sigh.
Hm.
We are home.
Just a moment.
Hm.
Uncle.
Oh.
Mimiw?
Come here.
Gently. Gently.
Here. I prepared your food.
Go ahead.
This one is really stubborn.
Why don't you eat?
Look at that. Why so small bite?
Next time, if you don’t eat, I have to punish you
so you’ll learn.
So stubborn.
Look at him.
I think.
Sigh
He is walking away.
Look at him.
I think he isn’t hungry yet.
This cat is bad.
But thank you.
You’re neither my child nor my grandchild.
But you always care for me.
I'm happy to help, Uncle.
Because you’re an elder.
And you live alone.
Oh and
have you eaten the food that I brought you this morning?
Oh,
I will eat together with Mimiw.
You can go do your work.
Don’t worry about me.
Well then,
I’ll take my leave now.
See you later.
Sigh.
So messy.
I should hurry and finish my last meal.
Then
I will blow up this planet.
Hm.
Mm.
So good.
Sigh.
I cannot.
If we blow up this planet
Then I  won’t be able to eat delicious food.
Sigh.
Hey!
Hm.
Mm.
Hey
How did you get here?
I'm afraid someone might get lost.
So I come to check on you.
Hm?
Are you taking a break to eat?
Mm.
Why eat only that one?
Why don't you eat them all?
I went through the effort of cooking them for you.
Here. You have to eat them together.
Together like this.
It will make them more delicious.
Try it.
Hm.
Mm!
It's really delicious!
Hey.
Give me.
Hm!
What?
Hey!
Wait! Wait!
Stop! Stop!
Calm down.
Hey!
Give me some!
It's difficult for you.
I’ll feed you myself.
Stay still.
You might strain Tan’s costume.
Hey.
What?
Can you be my owner?
Be my owner, can you?
What owner?
What do you mean?
I don't want to be a stray.
I want to have a bed.
To have a delicious food to eat.
I’d like you to feed me every day.
Well, if you don’t have anywhere to go
you can stay with me for now.
Really?
Hm.
Yay!
That's good!
Then I’ve already decided!
I’ve decided that I won’t blow up this planet yet.
And you
feed me every day.
Won’t blow up this planet?
Must feed you everyday?
It’s like I’m cooking to save the world, huh?
Please.
Fine.
Yay!
Yeah.
Really?
I finally have an owner!
Hehe.
Do you want to keep eating?
Yes!
Would you like a chicken feet?