(Ji Chang Wook)
(Sung Dong Il)
(Choi Soo Young)
(Won Ji An, Nam Tae Hoon, Yang Hee Kyung)
(Kil Hae Yeon, Yu Soon Woong, Jeon Chae Eun, Shin Ju Hwan)
(If You Wish Upon Me)
(Final Episode)
I mean...
There are many other rooms here. Why of all rooms...
Why does it have to be this room on the fourth floor?
I just don't get it.
In this room,
I was born again.
And there are many memories attached to this room.
Okay, fine. As long as you're comfortable here.
- Gyeo Rye. - Yes.
Sit down.
Why? What now?
Oh, boy. What are you going to nag me about this time?
About your late father...
What? Will you...
tell me to forgive him...
or that I should put everything behind me and move on?
No.
Your father...
must've been very lonely too.
I know.
I know that too. Yes, he must've been.
But what goes around comes around.
You see, I learned something from him.
He taught me not to live like he did.
If I do,
I'll be all alone and lonely...
when I breathe my last.
Yes.
Now,
you learn 10 things on your own when I try to teach you 1 thing.
Oh, stop.
You're right. No matter where you are,
if you are...
with someone you love...
and don't feel lonely,
where you are can become your Hogeweyk Village.
Right?
You don't have to go all the way to the Netherlands.
(If You Wish Upon Me)
Where are we going? Why won't you tell me?
You woke me up so early and made me pack lunch.
Where are we going?
Come on. Do we have to have a destination?
Why can't we just go for a drive?
It's nice to be out on a date. It's been too long.
A date? This is a date?
Are you just calling it a date...
when you're going to make me do some weird training again?
I'm not doing it.
What?
Rock-paper-scissors!
I can't believe you lost.
What is this?
- Let's do it again. - Do you want to?
- Yes. - Sure.
- Rock-paper-scissors! - Rock-paper-scissors!
I guess today is not your day.
Gosh.
Let's go!
Stop swinging your legs back and forth! You're so heavy.
My gosh. Pick up the pace, will you?
Move it. Let's go!
But why do I have to give everyone a piggyback ride?
We played rock-paper-scissors, and you lost.
If I had lost, I would've given you a piggyback right away.
Well, I didn't know it was for this.
Stop wobbling!
The food will get thrown upside down.
(Kim Mi Sun, Rest in Peace)
Hi, Mom. I'm here.
Thanks to my driver here, I had a comfortable ride.
Hello, I'm her driver.
Mom. He looks skinny, but he's quite brave.
What? I'm not skinny.
I've been working out very hard these days.
Look at this, Mom. He made all this food for you.
Ma'am, I am...
Well, how should I put this?
I'm a great cook.
Well...
Your daughter...
chose a good guy.
Had I known we were coming here,
I would've prepared a feast for you...
with many different dishes.
Too bad I didn't know.
Gosh.
Mom.
So many things happened in the past year.
There were times...
when I thought, "My gosh, I really can't handle this."
The only thing I could rely on was knowing that...
everything eventually passes with time.
But...
I now have someone I can rely on, Mom.
When you're carrying...
a bucket of water with one hand, it feels very heavy.
But it feels lighter if you carry it on your back and have...
both shoulders support the weight.
Mom, I...
I mean...
Us.
We'll be fine.
Hey.
- Here. - What's this?
It's you.
- Hey. - Yes?
You're always with old people, so you think I look like a granny too?
And this is me.
Can we grow old together...
until we see this?
Well, I'm not sure.
We'll see.
My gosh, I look so beautiful.
I did a good job, right?
Mom, look. He can even draw well.
Everything that has happened feels like a dream.
I feel like I'm back exactly where I was four years ago.
You've been through a lot.
If you feel pain, just call me.
Don't expect any special treatment from me.
Pay your hospital bills on time and...
Thank you.
- Gyeo Rye. - Yes.
Here.
Give it to the director.
- What is this? - Just give it to the director.
Don't open it and look.
Okay, all right.
Oh, hold on.
Did our hospital have a director?
Every hospital has one, you silly goose.
Oh, that's true.
But I don't think I've seen the director's office.
It's right by the chapel.
Go find it.
Okay, all right. Get some rest.
What's in this? Oh, get some rest.
Don't open it.
Okay, I heard you. My goodness.
Gosh. Hello.
What is this?
Telling me not to open it will only make me want to do it more.
Shall I just open it and see?
Forget it. I won't.
(Director Lee Jong Sook Lucia)
(Assistant Director Lee Jin Young Julia)
Most directors' offices are big...
and fancy. Am I wrong?
This office is...
This is the biggest and nicest office here.
- That's right. - I see.
Oh, right. About that man who hurt Mr. Gu...
and threatened the chief nurse.
The one who was in the room on the fourth floor.
Did everything go well?
Right, I'm sorry about what happened.
I apologize.
What? Why are you apologizing?
That man...
will be judged for what he did now that he's up there.
But you know, Gyeo Rye,
when you're ready to let it all go,
just forgive him...
even if you don't really want to.
Not for him. Do it for your own sake.
Okay. I will try to forgive him.
Oh, here.
Mr. Kang told me to give it to you.
What does it say?
What is it?
Well...
It's Mr. Kang's will.
Well, I wrote one too when I first...
got here.
Anyway, I'm off.
Directors. The titles suit you.
You look...
very cool.
He's so fond of Mr. Kang.
I wish Mr. Kang could stick around for longer.
Yes, I know.
You're invited.
(You're invited.)
(Invitation)
I want to formally ask Team Genie...
to grant my last wish.
Do you want another lettering tattoo?
No. Today...
Here, I brought this photo.
It's my dog. He was like my son. I want to get this tattooed on me.
I have a scar here.
That's where I want the tattoo. Can you do it?
Yes, sure thing.
You can cover the scar, right?
- Yes, I'll cover the scar. - Good.
The other day, I had a customer around your age...
who got a tattoo over a scar on his ankle...
from a burn he got when he was little.
I see. What kind of tattoo?
He got a tattoo of Taekwon V, the robot we used to play with as kids.
I see, Taekwon V.
Taekwon V. That's nuts.
What?
You've gained some weight.
The food must be good.
I eat better here.
Before I came here, I barely ate one proper meal a day.
Me too.
I eat better these days.
I'm doing much better.
It's good to see you.
But...
don't visit me again.
I said we should go to the gopchang place together.
I take it back.
I can do whatever I want.
Besides, since when did I listen to you?
Right, you never did.
But this time, you should listen to me.
I have nowhere else to go.
Do you know how empty you feel when you have nowhere to go?
You think I wouldn't know?
Don't visit me again, Jun Kyung.
Thanks a lot for coming all the way here to see me.
But live your life now.
As if you've been reborn.
You survived the fall from the rooftop,
which means you're destined to live.
The same goes for you.
You survived that accident too.
We're so much alike.
Gosh.
You never listen to me.
Whatever. I'll come back next week.
I'll earn lots of money and bring an expensive lawyer.
I'm off.
Oh, right.
I got you a gift.
But...
I'll tell you about it next time.
Other girls also recorded videos of what Pyo Cheol Woo did.
Did you record something too?
If you do, let's report him together.
I do have a video.
But I didn't record it myself.
It's a video of him stealing drugs.
A friend of mine sent it to me.
(In Mourning)
It's a video of Pyo Cheol Woo stealing morphine from a hospital.
We're planning to go to the police office tomorrow.
I can tell them to contact you for an interview, right?
I'm sure you have a lot to say too.
I want to be there too.
But how did you even think to record a video...
at that moment?
You must've been terrified.
Because I wanted to live.
I wanted to live. That's why.
Hi, guys. It's Anger here.
But from now on,
please call me YouTuber Hazoneburr.
Starting today, I'm going to upload my daily exercise videos.
To tell you the truth,
I've never really exercised in my life.
But I met a cool lady who is like a fitness pro.
I want to be like her, so I'm going to give this a shot.
I still need to discipline myself mentally.
But I want to be healthy and strong physically at least.
(You already look so pretty and healthy.)
(Me too! Let's be healthy!)
(I'm going to work out too, starting today!)
I'll try harder. Bye, guys.
(Like the video and subscribe!)
- You can't go in there. - Step aside.
Hey, Pyo Cheol Woo!
Come out.
- Let go of me. - Stop it.
- Seriously. - We're the police.
- Take him in. - Let go, punk.
Come out at once.
Gosh, how many times must I repeat myself to leave this here?
But somebody keeps...
Please give Mr. Cho in Room 201 a massage.
Okay.
And can I get a foot massage tonight?
You really...
- Hey. Mr. Yoon. - Yes?
I went on a blind date during the weekend.
I see. Congratulations.
She was 100 percent.
No, 1000 percent my ideal type.
I'm going to make it work.
Like that.
Seriously.
A fling.
What a handsome man.
Love is good.
- And you're so pretty. - Gosh, stop it.
Right. But it sure feels weird.
Why are you telling me this?
You can be...
lovey-dovey with Nurse Seo.
Is that so?
Returning to the subject,
Chief Nurse?
Hey, Mr. Yoon.
Sorry.
I got the wrong idea and doubted you.
Oh, come on.
Forget it. It's all in the past.
Well, I forgive you.
What?
It's okay. It happened in the past. There's no need to bring it up now.
You had it rough with Room 403.
In a way, you suffered because of me.
No. Everyone in this hospital knows...
it wasn't because of you.
- So I'm sorry. - Gosh, stop it. Alright?
What is it this time?
You see,
I nagged a lot about what Team Genie did.
So I wasn't sure if I should shamelessly bring this up or not.
But Dr. Yang told me to ask at the least.
What is it?
Does Team Genie only grant...
the wishes of people?
Can you also grant...
the wish of an object in its final moments?
An object?
(A Joyful Day)
There was something my father was doing...
until a week before he died.
He passed away suddenly without finishing it.
He wanted to give a letter and gift of appreciation in person...
to 43 subscribers who read the first issue...
to the last for more than 20 years.
He believed "A Joyful Day" would want to bid farewell...
to the subscribers.
I tried to do it alone...
but found it impossible.
It was too much for one person.
And two more patients suddenly got admitted,
so I couldn't leave the hospital.
Separate from my father's death,
the magazine was going to discontinue.
Nobody was purchasing it anymore...
aside from the 43 subscribers.
(Yours)
Magazines and newspapers in paper form will soon disappear...
from the world, won't they?
Children born later than me...
might not even know these existed.
Well, you can't stop time from passing by.
Do you two know this magazine?
I remember seeing it when I was little.
Often at my grandma's place.
But I rarely saw it these days.
It was really nice. You know, "A Joyful Day."
I especially enjoyed it when I had to travel long by train.
It helped kill the time.
The stories of each person...
were fun, bantering,
and relatable.
I read a few when I was young.
- Really? - Yes. The ones you had.
- I see. - It was fun.
You're still young.
I'm glad there are people who will be with this magazine's...
final moment.
And a total of 43 subscribers, to boot.
Ms. Oh will soon bring more helpers.
- Let's wrap it up before that. - Okay.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
I'm here to deliver the last issue...
of "A Joyful Day."
Before the president passed away, he wanted it...
- to be handed out... - Before the president passed away,
he wanted it to be handed out in person to the dear subscribers.
"For subscribing to the end..."
"even though times have changed..."
- "Thank you very much." - "Thank you very much."
I continued reading...
what my late mom was reading until the end.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Right.
"The journey of A Joyful Day ends here,"
"but I hope you spend a joyful day until your last moment."
That is what...
my father left in his will.
Once again, thank you from the bottom of my heart.
("Yours", "A Joyful Day")
Time really flew by.
It has already been 24 years.
The stories in this magazine were fun to read.
You're right.
Please don't cry.
I had no idea the subscribers would love it that much.
But they really did.
Right.
The fact that people aren't the only ones...
with the last moment got me thinking a lot.
Gyeo Rye.
What is it?
It's about time...
I say it.
Say what? What is it? Spill it.
My...
last wish.
Last wish, my foot.
Team Genie only grants...
real last wishes, for goodness' sake.
Wishes of those who are about to die. You're still fine.
Final wishes shouldn't be said so recklessly.
Gyeo Rye.
Whatever. I'm too busy right now. Let's talk later.
Rest, okay?
He may have made the team, but he can't change the rule.
We only grant last wishes. How annoying.
It's something you like, right?
Oh. My heart skipped a beat.
Gosh. I love how it rests in my hand.
If I had a sense of shame and conscience,
I wouldn't have been able to ask your team to grant the wish.
It's okay.
Nobody can live a perfect life.
Let's loosen up, okay?
Living a perfect life only wears you out.
You can do it.
You forgot your chart.
See? Not being perfect is charming.
Hello.
Hi.
It's been a while since you were outside.
I'm the little captain. Do you remember?
Yes, of course.
You're our hospital's little volunteer captain.
That's right.
How are you today?
How do you feel?
Are you able to clean today?
Of course.
Both my body and mind are going strong today.
You know,
I don't feel that happy today.
Despite the amazing weather.
My close friend keeps trying to give up.
He should think about how many wishes he has granted.
You are invited to Kang Tae Sik's early funeral.
(You are invited to Kang Tae Sik's early funeral. From Kang Tae Sik)
Seriously, he just does as he pleases.
Amor fati
- Amor fati - I need to get going, ma'am.
What are you going to tell him?
Amor fati
Oh.
What does "amor fati" mean?
Come on. Amor fati.
Love...
your fate.
"Love your fate?"
Why don't you let...
Mr. Kang love his fate, Gyeo Rye?
Amor fati.
Love your fate.
What are you doing?
("The End of the World")
Darn it.
Did you get the text message?
Yes, I did.
What do you think?
What do you mean? I think it's a good idea.
How is it a good idea?
I think it's the worst idea ever.
Holding your funeral early makes no sense, does it?
He's been so selfish,
ever since we first met until now.
I seriously don't want to grant his wish.
Hey.
There are no good or bad wishes.
Wishes are just wishes.
And...
he's none other than our captain.
It's his last wish. We should grant it.
You should, Little Captain. What do you say?
No, I don't want to.
Smile.
Stop being ridiculous, will you?
I'd be willing to grant your wish...
if it was a reasonable one.
How can you hold your funeral early...
and even invite people to it?
Do you think it makes sense?
Gyeo Rye.
What is it?
You're even bathing me.
Thanks.
Don't thank me. Forget it.
If I bathe you...
for ten more years...
How annoying.
Room 403.
Thank you for having me until now.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
Here we go.
(Ambulance, Patient Transfer)
Gyeo Rye.
Don't go over the speed limit.
Okay, I won't.
Stop nagging.
I'm closing the door.
Do I have to go too?
Cut that nonsense.
- Of course, you do. Get in. - Right. Yes, I do.
You're my friend.
Okay. See you later.
- Hi. - Oh, my.
- Hi. - Welcome.
Hey.
Drive safely.
Okay, I will. Don't worry.
Are we really going to the sea?
That's right.
Yes, we're going to the sea. Aren't you excited?
I'm psyched!
I'm starting the car.
- Yes. - Let's go.
See you later.
- Bye. - Have a safe trip.
- Bye. - Come back safely.
Here. Pass it to the back.
Thank you.
- Dig in. - Thank you.
- Thank you for the food. - Sure.
It's one per person...
and not two, Mr. Gu.
I know. Why are you saying that to me?
- Who didn't get one? - Me.
- I got two. - Me too.
Okay. I must have missed you.
- Everyone, please enjoy. - Thank you.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
Amor fati.
I love everyone's fate.
I love my wife.
Oh, come on.
You have a wife, Mr. Hwang?
He has a wife.
What is wrong with you? Stop it.
Go do it to your wife.
Gyeo Rye.
- Yes. - Promise me one thing.
Not to cry?
No, that's up to you.
But let's keep a smile on in front of Mr. Kang.
I can't control it.
I'm getting so upset.
Still.
Promise me.
Hurry. Promise me.
Let's smile. Like this.
Good job.
It's the sea.
You're right.
It's been so long. Has it been ten years?
- Twelve. - What?
- It's been 16 years for me. - What?
Now that you have a girlfriend, you shouldn't work so much.
You're not the one to say that.
That's true.
My.
We don't have to go to the sea on our own, right?
I know. It's so nice.
We should go to the mountains together.
I love the mountains.
This country is surrounded by the sea.
But you never had a chance to go?
Everyone. Today, I will...
drive slowly. Enjoy your time.
- Yes. - Thank you.
Sonny. Should we stop now?
Gyeo Rye.
What's this?
Your birthday gift.
My time...
stops here.
From now on,
it's yours.
What stops here?
Besides, you don't know my real birthday.
Gather here please.
- Is everyone here? - Yes.
Now, let's begin Gyeo Rye's first birthday party.
What?
There wasn't much to choose from for five dollars.
We're not here...
for Mr. Kang's last trip,
but for your birthday party.
It's also Team Genie's first trip.
We're all here for you.
For Gyeo Rye who's reborn.
Gyeo Rye.
Spring is perfect for your birthday.
Throwing you a birthday party...
is Mr. Kang's last wish.
(You're invited.)
(Invitation)
You're invited to Yoon Gyeo Rye's first birthday party.
(You're invited to Yoon Gyeo Rye's first birthday party.)
"Invitation."
"You're invited to Yoon Gyeo Rye's first birthday party."
Does that mean he's one year old?
What?
- Happy birthday to you - Happy birthday to you
- Dear Gyeo Rye - Dear Gyeo Rye
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday. - Happy birthday, captain.
- Happy birthday. - He's crying.
- He's crying. - He's getting tearful.
- Don't cry. - Don't cry.
- Don't cry. - Cry.
Cry.
- Don't cry. - We should leave them alone.
Let's go check out the sea.
Let's go.
- Wait. - What are you doing?
Come on.
If there's a deity,
he...
probably led me here.
Though they cannot save everyone,
thanks to Mr. Kang and the hospital family's...
will to save me at least,
I was saved...
just before falling into a swamp.
What is all this?
Happy birthday.
My son.
Hence, Yoon Gyeo Rye's real life...
begins now.
(A year later)
What time is it?
Oh, I've got to go.
Gosh.
It's crazy.
The weather is crazy.
Let's go.
I told you to put it back.
Hello.
- Morning. - Morning.
Hello, ma'am.
No octopus spaghetti today.
- Why not? - Not three times a week.
- But... - No.
- But... - I told you.
Hello.
As Kang Tae Sik Narses wished,
a site was arranged here...
to establish Make a Wish Foundation and the Angel Village.
His entire fortune was also donated.
(Late Kang Tae Sik)
Hi, little captain.
Hello.
You look pretty.
You're done.
You're amazing.
You're very good for your age.
I'm sure you'll own...
many salons in the future.
I hope so.
- How much is it? - It's 15 dollars.
Can you give me a dollar discount?
I can't do that.
One, two, three...
Four. I don't have enough.
Okay.
Thank you.
- Bye. - Bye.
She just left.
(Genie Bank)
My husband must be starving.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
She just headed to the bus stop.
Where are you going, ma'am?
Where else?
I'm going home after work.
I see.
My husband is waiting.
That's nice.
I suppose you're having something delicious at home.
- Yes. I'm hungry. - I see.
The bus is here.
Hi.
(Bus)
Bye.
- Take care. - Bye.
Hello.
Bye.
(Bus)
Have a good day.
Bye.
I will. I always have a good day.
She's going in.
Okay.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Did you have a good day?
Same old.
Give it to me.
Labour for Choi Duk Ja. Choi Duk Ja for labour.
The food looks so good.
It's your favourite beef brisket doenjang jjigae.
I love it.
Come on in. Let's eat.
Come in. Hurry.
- That looks good. - Come in.
That looks good.
What did you do today?
Have a seat.
Enjoy.
- Let's eat. - Yes.
- Thank you. - It looks good.
You're welcome.
Enjoy.
- It's so good. - It's good.
- Here. - Thank you.
Wherever you are, if you're with...
the people you love and are not lonely,
that will be...
Hogeweyk Village.
(Angel Village)
You're always late just like your dad.
Preparing a meal twice is...
I know it's a hassle. It's such a hassle.
What's this?
Brachycarpa?
This is shepherd's purse.
Spring greens are good enough with plain rice.
You changed the topic just like your dad.
Oh, right. We're getting a new volunteer today.
Yes.
Good luck.
He needs to learn from one to ten just like you.
Don't worry. Who am I?
Captain Yoon of Team Genie. Yoon Genie.
Sure. Why not?
Enjoy your meal, Captain Yoon.
Thank you. It's so good.
What's taking her so long?
Look at the time.
Gosh. This place is so lame.
A turtle?
This is crazy.
(Thank you for watching If You Wish Upon Me.)
(Thanks to Lee You Mi and Kim Shin Rock for special appearance.)
(If You Wish Upon Me)