(Ji Chang Wook)
(Sung Dong Il)
(Choi Soo Young)
(Won Ji An, Nam Tae Hoon, Yang Hee Kyung)
(Kil Hae Yeon, Yu Soon Woong, Jeon Chae Eun, Shin Ju Hwan)
(If You Wish Upon Me)
Ma'am. Are you going home?
Yes, I'll come back next week.
Where are you coming from?
I lost a game and had to buy ice cream.
Would you like one?
Thank you.
Watch out.
- Ma'am. Are you okay? - Yes.
That little...
Gosh.
Goodness. It's in the middle of nowhere.
Hey!
You're that jerk from last time.
Are you the volunteer who's supposed to come today?
Yes, so?
Oh, gosh.
- Look, lady. - What...
Have you gone mad? What are you doing?
Look what you did. Are you out of your mind?
If I wasn't, do you think I would've done that?
That looks like a fancy car.
Why did you run so fast and drive me crazy?
Where do you think you are? It's a hospital.
How can a volunteer show up like that?
Do volunteers have to crawl from there?
What have you done?
- She's in a mess. - Let's go back in.
Let's get some coffee. Come on.
If I did that, I'll pay to get it cleaned.
Pay for the repair.
I'll pay you when you get the estimate.
Are you...
a grandson of some wealthy family?
Or are you some rude idol I'm not aware of?
You got all the expensive stuff, but you can't hide how shallow you are.
Mr. Kang. We shouldn't let him drive.
He has no manners.
Still, we can't send him back.
My ice cream.
Aren't you coming in? Do you want to go back to prison?
Come in.
This is crazy.
Darn it.
(If You Wish Upon Me)
(Episode 2)
Most people here have...
last-stage cancer.
You must get a proper volunteer education.
So, don't even think about slacking off.
I haven't made a decision yet.
This volunteer job.
I haven't decided whether to work here yet.
I thought about doing it after taking a look,
but because of that crazy woman,
I don't feel like doing it.
Should I call it a coincidence?
This is totally strange.
Why do you happen to be...
in my volunteer work place?
Because it was me...
who requested a driver.
Besides, who made me unable to work?
To be honest, I never expected you to come.
Stop nagging at me for a tiny accident.
What have I...
Be quiet. Wait here.
Where are you going?
Here. Where else?
Sir.
Please wait here.
Well...
I'll be right back.
Okay.
You see,
this week might be his last week.
Will it be possible?
Sister. Who are we?
We're Team Genie.
The Avengers of Wish-Granting.
See you later.
What?
Are you telling me...
to drive this?
Or? Are you going to push it?
This is...
Your car's side mirror is broken. You can't drive that.
What's this? Antenna?
Put that back in.
Stop messing around.
If you're here to drive, drive.
Oh, geez.
What are you doing? Hurry up and get in.
Oh, dear.
Seriously.
It's darn tight.
You better get a new car.
My goodness.
Hey. Are you...
taking that dog too?
Do we have any other choice? I might not come back here again.
Oh, dear. What a devoted father.
You're the only volunteer...
to bring a dog.
Didn't you have anyone to look after the dog at home?
Don't you have a family?
Do you live alone?
Oh, it actually works.
It won't be easy to start this car.
Sonny. Let's go.
Sonny?
Is his name Sonny?
So you do have a family.
Old man. Be quiet. Where to?
Get out of here first.
It does move.
Where are we going? Are we picking up a patient?
Why didn't you just take the ambulance?
You'll see when you get there.
By the way, this car is perfect for you.
No matter how hard you hit it, it won't speed up.
And if you drive a car that goes as fast as you want,
you'll die early.
I don't plan to live a long life anyway.
My car is perfect.
If this gets into an accident, we'll die on the spot.
Does it even have air bags?
- It came with the car. - My goodness.
(Seok Jun)
Why are you looking at my phone?
(No Trespassing)
I think his house is near here.
Where is it?
Tell me.
It's somewhere around here.
Where is it?
It's right here. The persimmons.
It's right in front of you.
(No Redevelopment in Hyeyoung-dong)
Yes?
Hello.
We're from Woori Hospice Hospital.
Why did you ring the doorbell?
It's upsetting.
What's her problem?
- I... - You cult.
I'm so sick of it.
You're nothing but a pain in the neck.
Why is she turning us into a cult?
Stop bothering me and leave.
(No Redevelopment in Hyeyoung-dong)
Hey.
What are you doing? Hey.
That punk. Hey.
Are you out of your mind?
Get out of there now.
That punk. We're not loan sharks or petty thieves.
Why would you jump over the wall? Get out of there.
I'll handle it. Stay quiet.
Just stay quiet.
Hurry up and get out of there.
Why does it matter? I thought you wanted to go in.
Still, you can't jump over the wall.
Lady.
Lady!
Are you crazy?
Get in the car.
- You're home. - Yes.
Dong Ho. You're home.
(Baekil Express)
Dong Sik.
Wash your hands and join dinner.
You too.
Enjoy.
Are they a silent family?
What's a silent family?
I saw it on TV.
A family lives under the same roof,
but they don't talk to each other at all.
A family...
is the most unreasonable human relationship...
and upsets you the most.
You didn't even get to choose it, but there's so much responsibility.
I don't think the family that upsets you is the dog behind you.
I'm serious. It's true.
I didn't get anything.
So you borrowed money, but you never got it?
I withdrew money from the bank myself...
and sent it in a bag.
Three hundred and twenty thousand dollars.
Are you saying my boys are lying?
No.
I can bet on my family.
I never received...
But that's the truth.
You're obviously a gambler for betting on your family.
I'm sorry.
- Seok Jun. - Yes, boss.
You dropped Yoon Gyeo Rye off in front of his school, right?
No outside cars were allowed.
But I dropped him off and picked him up.
No. That's not true.
He didn't come.
How could you gamble as an economics professor?
I'm sorry.
Have you found Yoon Gyeo Rye yet?
Everyone has to meet...
to see who's lying.
- I'm sorry. - It's not your fault.
Tell him the interest is 1,000 dollars a day.
Yes, boss.
If he still doesn't show up, he wishes to die.
I should grant his wish.
You're always borrowing money, yet you wear expensive underwear.
I can't do that.
Even if he was the former owner, I don't know him at all.
You're asking us to let him die in this house?
Of course I understand.
But the former house owner lived here for decades.
He's very attached to this house.
That's his problem. I have a problem of my own.
The whole neighbourhood is redeveloping.
I have to move out by next month.
It's hectic. I have a lot on my mind.
Do you think you can move a week later?
My family can't wait to move out,
let alone wait for a week.
So it's been over eight months since we moved in,
but we still haven't unpacked yet.
Look, man.
I don't think it's that big of a deal.
Why don't you take this and rent your place?
- Hey. - We're only...
Why are you giving them money?
Stop it.
There's a studio the former house owner used to stay.
You could stay there for a while if you want.
It may be small.
You'll have to tell each other to move,
go, clean up,
eat, sit down, lie down.
But that's life, right?
You interact with each other.
But you get to talk to your family.
If you want a hotel,
we could provide you with one.
I'm sorry.
It's not an easy decision. Goodbye.
Come in.
If you change your mind...
If this isn't enough, I'll give you one more.
Two.
Hey. Stop it.
You see...
Yes.
How much time does he have left?
Well, the doctor said...
before this week.
But then, it's never certain.
- Okay. - Thank you.
But...
I'm sorry.
What stock investment?
You never even read a book about it before.
Are you stupid or brave?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
What do we do now?
- What do you mean we're moving? - Dong Ho.
I'm taking SAT next year!
I'm sorry. Oh, my goodness.
I feel terrible.
My goodness.
Maybe this house...
meant so much...
to someone.
But...
how did we end up hating it so much?
Let's see.
Come here.
Let's go.
Mister, here. The car key.
Take it.
Have dinner.
Dinner? No, I'm good.
Come inside.
Come in and have dinner.
- Here. - Gosh.
- Oh, my goodness. - Amazing.
It doesn't look visually appetizing at all.
- Oh, my. - No, Ms. Yeom.
Don't lose your temper.
You won't be able to say that after a bite.
How about it?
She's right. Ms. Yeom's bibimbap is the bomb.
Totally. You don't even know how skilled she is.
Just have it without me.
It's my taste. Stop nagging about it.
Gosh. This jerk sure is playing hard to get.
- Why don't we enjoy it ourselves? - Okay!
- Let's dig in. - Give me a spoon too.
Oh, my gosh.
- I'm psyched! - It looks good.
How did you make the eggs look so round?
Her over-easy eggs are to die for.
- Have some. - It's so good!
- Why aren't you eating the egg? - Can I have it?
- Seriously. - This is what you call bibimbap.
Gosh, I'm drooling.
It's a masterpiece.
Fried eggs are a must in bibimbap.
Of course!
You feel empty without them.
As expected of you, Ms. Yeom.
- Over-easy eggs aren't easy. - It's really good today.
- I know, right? - Isn't it extra good?
- I made it more special today. - I see.
Love
I wonder if that alone
Can bring a miracle
Can't you make at least one of my wishes
- Come true? - This isn't a single room.
When will she get that this is a shared room?
Can't she sing someplace else?
And how can she feel like singing in this situation?
How dare you talk back to someone older than you?
Being here alone is frustrating...
to the point I want to die.
Die? That's easy for you to say...
since you're not dying.
- They're fighting. - It's your husband and me,
his roommate, who are dying.
All you are feeling is frustration,
but we're on the verge of our death.
- That nasty temper got you sick. - Quiet, my foot.
- I bet all the female patients... - Gosh.
- hate you. - It's freaking noisy.
Isn't that why you got transferred to my husband's room?
What did you say?
I got sick because of my nasty temper?
Excuse me. Quiet down, will you?
- Yes. And that's why... - Stop it.
none of your family members come to visit you.
Ma'am, come on.
- Quiet. - It's either you or me...
that'll leave this room today.
- Stop. Talk it out, okay? - Darn it.
- Let go of me! - You're strong for a patient.
Let go.
- Let go before I head butt you. - Okay.
I'm sick of it all.
My poor life.
How can you say that when your husband is sick?
- You wicked woman! - Enough. Stop it!
- Who are you? - A volunteer worker. Got a problem?
Bollocks. You, a volunteer worker? Seriously?
- I'd rather die. - What did you say just now?
- What did you say? - How miserable.
Get out!
Darn it.
Whatever.
For real?
Who the heck duct taped it?
Seriously.
Who did this?
Who wrapped duct tape on my car?
You little...
Why did you use duct tape on the side...
If you hate bibimbap, try this yakbap.
It's easier to eat and delicious to boot.
A review of it is a must, okay?
- No, I'm good. - Take it.
Forget it. I don't eat things like this.
Gosh, that punk.
For goodness' sake.
Judging by his imported car, he must be really rich.
He's rich but a parvenu.
A spoiled kid raised by parvenu parents.
He's not rich. You can tell at a glance.
No rich person could possibly resist my food.
Am I wrong?
It's perfectly seasoned.
I love your bibimbap.
If you hate bibimbap, try this yakbap.
- No, I'm good. - Take it.
Goodness. Why was she acting all friendly?
Unbelievable.
Hey, what's wrong? Are you in pain, Sonny?
What is it?
Darn it. Is he getting car sick?
Hey, you barely eat.
But you hate the hotel.
Do you hate this car too?
What now?
I don't know.
Everything sucks for me too, Sonny.
This is all I can get?
It's not even half of what I paid.
This, right here.
How can you say that after breaking this side mirror?
- I was being very generous. - Gosh.
Fine. Have a nice life.
Are you leaving already? Okay, alright.
Why don't we go inside and look at other cars over a cup of tea?
What?
Did you call Seok Jun again?
Gosh, you jerk.
Darn it.
What?
Good morning. You're up early.
For goodness' sake.
What are you two doing?
- Oh, my. - No, I'm okay.
- Gosh. - I'm totally fine.
Stop it. You're wearing a cast.
Why are you sweeping the ground?
And stop wiping my car.
It's already clean enough. Seriously!
Goodness.
Please enjoy! From Team Genie.
Oh, man. Really.
I have to do volunteer work solely because of you.
You failed to get any sleep at that fancy hotel.
What? Is it comfier here?
(Ambulance)
Aren't you here to do volunteer work?
So why are you slacking off?
Hey, just keep walking.
And stop picking a fight for nothing.
But if you're still going to,
do it after you pay for the repairs, Lady.
How much did it cost?
Are you going to pay me right away?
I'll get a loan or ask for my room deposit,
so tell me how much it cost.
Goodness. Wouldn't you be wealthier...
if you kept your temper in check?
I'll take care of my own wealth.
Just tell me already.
The repair cost?
Around 18,000 dollars.
A big shocker, right?
What? 18,000 dollars?
Yes, 18,000 dollars. Do you have the money?
Gosh.
Well, 18,000 dollars. That's...
less than 20,000 dollars.
The deposit for my house is 20,000 dollars.
I'll have 2,000 dollars left.
Goodness. So you're going to move out?
And where will you live with that 2,000 dollars?
I'll take care of that myself.
Thanks to you, I'll become the first woman living in nature.
Gosh.
This is fun.
She's out of her mind.
A weirdo.
My house feels more precious today.
The repair cost? Around 18,000 dollars.
Mom.
I met a really weird guy.
Listen. Like...
What a jerk.
He was annoying.
Seriously annoying.
Are you really going to sleep here?
For real?
You're not, right?
Why on earth do you sleep like a baby here?
You've got an unusual taste.
I find it really uncomfortable here.
I can't possibly sleep here.
Sonny.
Fine.
But we're leaving tomorrow...
for the hotel, okay?
This is all because of you.
- Hey, Gyeo Rye. - I'm not sleeping.
- Did I scare you? - No.
We did it.
Did what?
Gosh. Look.
We decided to push back the contract to a week.
See that?
There is nothing Team Genie can't do.
This is why I do my best.
We need to move early tomorrow morning,
so get some sleep.
I won't charge you for the bed or electricity.
You have nowhere to go anyway.
What?
Nowhere to go? Nonsense.
I have a room in that expensive hotel.
And you can't charge me for anything.
What are you? A thug?
- I'm off. - Okay.
I'll be back.
Hi.
Are you going again?
Yes.
I'm allowing you to go today since you're simply taking him...
to his old house.
But there was that car accident last time.
So I want you to be more mindful.
Okay.
He's right.
Don't feel pressured to do something special.
Everyone in this hospital is doing their best.
So there's no need to go all out for those patients.
We all feel the same way.
You're right. I know.
I'll be more careful and mindful.
I'm off.
- I'll be back. - Have a safe trip.
Gosh, you're already ready to go.
- Hey. - I'm sorry for being late.
- Good morning. - Are you feeling okay, sir?
Goodness, my ears hurt.
There he goes again with his awful driving skills.
That's why people need to learn.
(Transporting Patient)
Don't speed like with your car.
Be careful, got it?
Don't speed, okay?
(Pyeon Yong Ho)
Welcome.
- Let's carry it together. - Gosh.
(Ambulance, Transporting Patient)
You're happy to go home, right?
Yes.
Hey.
Sonny? Hey, Sonny. Are you happy too?
What a cutie.
(Ambulance, Transporting Patient)
Hey.
Drive properly, will you?
You nag too much.
I'm driving properly, aren't I?
If you change lanes, you should turn on the blinker.
Gosh, I'm not a driver instructor.
Must I have to teach you?
There are no cars anyway. Just leave it to me.
You're butting in too much. Stop nagging, okay?
This isn't an ordinary car.
You punk. We have a patient at the back.
So be careful when you drive.
Darn it. Does it even matter?
He's about to croak anyway.
What did you just say?
It doesn't matter, does it?
- Stop the car. - What?
Stop the car, you jerk!
(Ambulance, Transporting Patient)
Get out.
Why?
Get out now.
What is it?
Seriously, what?
Why did you have to say it like that?
But I'm right. He's on the verge of passing away.
So what is it?
That's no way of putting it, brat.
"He's on the verge of passing away?"
Is there anyone who will grieve over your death?
So why are you still alive?
Why?
Darn it. Let go.
Who was the one who stopped me from dying?
It was you!
Why did you stop me?
You should have just let me drown. So why?
For goodness' sake.
What right do you have to scold me?
Who the heck are you to meddle in my life?
You.
If you want to complete the rest of your volunteer hours,
think twice before you speak.
And drive safely.
Sorry. Let's go.
It's okay. Hop in.
It's okay.
What are you doing? Aren't you coming?
Hurry up and get in the car, or we'll just leave without you.
(Geum Village)
It's okay. Come on in.
My gosh.
They even decorated this. This is so cute.
(Make happy memories together. From Team Genie)
It's very clean here.
If you don't like it here,
we can go on a trip with the money they gave us.
How about we go to Jeju Island?
We had so much fun the last time we went to Jeju together.
Darn it, my charger.
What's wrong? Did you forget something?
Darn it!
- Sir. - Yes.
Which room would you like?
Over there.
- That bed over there? - Yes.
All right.
- All right. I'll pull this down. - Okay.
Hey, can you come over here and give me a hand?
Come on.
You work out a lot. Can't you do it alone?
Come and help.
There we go.
Sir, if your pain gets worse, you have to tell me right away.
Don't hold it in.
I'm not in pain.
Pardon me?
Now that I'm back at home,
all my pain is gone.
I bet. There's no place like home.
Come back home. Home sweet home.
But...
I heard...
this house would be demolished.
Yes, they're building an apartment complex.
That persimmon tree...
used to bear so many persimmons every year.
- Oh, that's a persimmon tree. - Yes.
(Divine Sauce, made by Yeom Soon Ja)
All right, guys. Let's eat.
Try it.
Dig in.
Is it good?
Dong Ho, come and eat.
You didn't eat all day.
I put in stir-fried bracken, your favourite.
You always do whatever you want.
I didn't even want to come here.
Why? Do you not like bibimbap?
- Should I order you something else? - Gosh, seriously.
Even if you do this, we can't go back to how we used to be.
I can't take this. Kim Dong Ho! Must you be so rude to your mother?
- What? - Honey, it's okay.
Can't you see that we're all trying hard to patch things up?
Can't you at least pretend to play along for once?
Or we'll all just live separately!
If you don't want to cooperate, get out!
Earn money and support yourself if you're that confident!
Let's eat.
May I help you?
Hello, Officer. I was just wondering...
if I could ask you some questions about the hit-and-run...
involving an imported luxury car, which took place on August 19.
A hit-and-run? In August...
- One moment, please. - Sir.
Thanks.
- Oh, right. Hey. - Yes, sir.
The hit-and-run with the imported car last month.
You know, the guy who ran away. Remember?
Well... Yes, I remember. That man who drove the ambulance.
That's right, the ambulance.
Oh, okay. What about it?
Well, my car was damaged in the accident too.
- I see. - But I didn't press charges.
- You should. - Yes.
Do you really not want to eat? There's a lot of food left.
Thanks for the food. I'm going to bed.
Yes, get some sleep. I'll tidy up.
I'm sorry I yelled at you earlier.
It's not like you've never done it before.
When we first met, you dragged me by my collar.
You punk. That was...
You brought it upon yourself.
Anyway, I'm going to bed.
Wait.
Well...
You know, the program that grants patients' wishes.
Aladdin or whatever it's called.
- Genie. Team Genie. - Right, Genie.
Do people...
have to pay for this?
Gosh.
I guess rich people only think about money.
No. It's 100 percent volunteer-run.
Okay.
Hold on. Why do you treat me like a rich man?
Wouldn't it be weird if I thought you were poor?
I mean, from the way you dress to how much you spend.
And your car too.
Most importantly, when I first met you...
Do you know what you were doing?
- When you first met me? - You threw money in the air.
Cash, 50-dollar bills at that.
You were throwing cash around...
as if you were blowing white dandelion floaties.
You must be loaded.
In any case, you need to eat something.
You can have this. It might be too late to get things delivered.
Wake me up before the shift handover.
I told you to eat with us.
Why would she give me this?
These days, you can get anything delivered 24-7.
- Honey. - Yes?
Our Spring and that persimmon tree. Are they friends now?
Yes, they are friends.
When will it start getting tall?
When Spring turns three?
How about we name this tree Summer?
Grow nice and tall, Summer.
You too, Spring.
Be careful.
- You're so adorable, Hee Sook. - Hee Sook.
Look at your earring.
Look, persimmons!
- Hurry and pick more! - You picked so many.
Daughter, look at this persimmon I picked.
It looks like you, Hee Sook.
How many did you pick?
Hee Sook, come here and eat.
Honey! You too.
Come and have some fritters first. Come down.
Sir.
Yes.
Aren't you scared?
What?
Of death.
You know...
To be honest, I was afraid.
But you see,
life scares me even more.
What should I do?
Come here.
What is it?
Thank you so much...
for driving me home.
Sir.
If there is anything you need,
just call me over.
Sir, my name is...
Yoon Gyeo Rye.
But you can just call me "Hey".
Okay.
Sonny seems to be feeling chipper today.
All right.
It's such a gorgeous day, isn't it?
Yes.
- Good morning. - Oh, you woke up.
Did you have a good night's sleep?
(Cancel the redevelopment project!)
What happened? Where did those persimmons come from?
It's Yoon Gyeo Rye.
He was busy all night. The hustle and bustle kept me up.
I barely got any sleep.
Yesterday,
Mr. Pyeon said the tree used to bear many persimmons.
Yoon Gyeo Rye made it after hearing that.
If he felt bad, he could've just said sorry.
I suppose he's not a total jerk after all.
Pick up the rest of his stuff.
Make sure you bring his family photo.
Seriously. Why couldn't we have taken everything at once?
Why make two trips?
What? Where did he go?
Sonny, where...
Hey, how did you even get up here?
Sonny. My goodness.
Hey, come here. You little troublemaker.
What are you doing here?
Don't go in.
- Sorry? - Just listen to me and don't go in.
Why can't I go in?
Hold on. Is this not one of the wards?
Why is this locked?
Listen to me and don't go in. Do not ask questions.
Oh, boy. Something's very fishy here.
- Are you curious? - Yes.
(We thank Kim Shin Rock for her special appearance.)
(If You Wish Upon Me)
Do you know why I entrusted you with that big chunk of money?
What would be your last message?
Be honest. You want to live.
What kind of miracle do you want to see happen?
If you're in pain, scream. Otherwise, no one will know.
Kang Tae Sik gave us the perfect job.
Can I keep wearing the bandages?
It's okay so far.
I want to feel happy, even just once in my life.