=Fortune Writer=
(Based on the original Zhihu novel)
=Episode 20=
I fell from a cliff
and narrowly escaped death.
I've been sitting here all day thinking
about you since I came back.
Su Yunqi, I have always felt
that meeting you is the only
good thing in my life.
Lu Huai.
Your feelings are too heavy for me.
I approached you only to use you,
don't you understand?
I don't care. Just keep lying to me.
Lu Huai, I don't want to be involved
anymore. Let me go.
Just consider it my fault.
Su Yunqi, I am a human.
I can feel pain too.
(Final Chapter)
(Prince Chun marries Su Luoluo.)
(Lu Huai shoots Su Yunqi to death.)
You knew instead of me, Su Luoluo saved
you when you were little.
Our fate began because of it.
If it weren't for
all the misunderstandings,
you'd have fallen for Su Luoluo.
She's the right one for you.
There are no misunderstandings.
This hairpin...
It's the one I made it fall
when I first met you.
From that moment, you...
Right.
So no matter who saved me
when I was little,
it was merely an act of kindness.
I know the difference.
Besides, Lady Luoluo did save me,
but I have already repaid her kindness.
When?
She gave me steamed buns,
and I granted her a favor.
She took my jade pendant.
I see.
Are there any other problems now?
If everyone says
I am unforgivably evil one day,
will you stand by me?
I will.
If one day, I need to kill someone
without reasons, what will you do?
No matter who you want to kill,
just let me know.
You needn't do it yourself. And...
If anyone tries to hurt you,
I'll kill them.
Su Yunqi, I have fallen for you.
I want to be with you.
Let me think about it.
(Can I trust him?)
(What if this is another trap
set by the Fortune Writer?)
(He could make others mock me
with just a few strokes.)
(Can I afford to bet on it?)
Miss, make a wish.
It takes five wen of silver,
and it really works.
Is that so?
All requests will be granted.
(This world is manipulated
by the Fortune Writer.)
(To whom else can I request?)
(Together Forever)
(Is there truly no hope?)
No matter where you go, I'll find you.
If you take a step back,
I'll move forward.
(Lu Huai, I believe in you.)
(We can survive together against fate.)
(Together Forever)
It's late.
Yeah, it's late.
You should go back now.
I'm afraid you'd run.
So you're gonna watch me all night here?
Playboy.
What?
Playboy...
No, try again.
Lu Huai.
No.
I'm really sleepy. I'm going to bed now.
Alright, I'll make a bet then.
What?
I have my bet on you.
Lady Yunqi, I'm betting on your win.
My Lady, it's time to get up.
What are you doing?
Serving you with washing and dressing.
Who asks for your service?
Didn't you feel
that you've always followed me before?
From now on, I'll follow you.
So, you'll give me whatever I want?
Of course.
Then I'll ask for something tricky.
I want to see fireflies.
As you wish.
Didn't you sleep well last night?
Why are you blushing?
The place we're going to see fireflies
is called Ethereal Valley.
Legend has it
that the mountain god of Ethereal Valley
will bless every couple going there
and let them be together forever.
Lu Huai, I am actually a bit afraid.
Don't be afraid.
I will protect you for a lifetime.
(Fortune Writer)
♪Pen in hand,
fog disperses, light dawns♪
♪Soft whispers, gentle moves,
tattered clothes♪
♪Foot prints are marked by the world♪
♪Life is but a fleeting play♪
♪Exposed plot in the tapestry of fate♪
♪A thousand threads
in a gamble of life and death♪
♪Reluctance and hesitation,
as wavering shadows of a lamp♪
♪Breeze brings a whole night of rain♪
♪From afar, I've drawn you on a scroll♪
♪The inkstone,
finely carved with delicacy♪
♪Love ignited, hair parted from comb♪
♪The writer can never escape the pain♪