The Long Ballad
Episode 18
Did you catch up?
I don't think so.
It's a life-saving pill.
Is this what you should do?
I'll let them settle the bill tomorrow.
By tomorrow,
there will be a group of thugs
who won't pay for the food.
They'll eat and drink.
What are you doing, Yan Yuzhi?
Since they are thugs,
I should do something I don't usually think about
and I don't dare to do.
The Long Ballad
It's beautiful.
Do you want to see it more closely?
Come on.
Hurry up.
Look at this.
Qin, I'll go buy some drinks.
Wait for me here.
Don't run away.
The Long Ballad
Deputy Chief.
Qi.
What's wrong?
I thought you were gone.
I couldn't find you.
Didn't I tell you
I'd go buy some drinks?
When did you say that?
I must have seen the fireworks
and saw her naked face.
I didn't hear it.
You're stealing again.
Why are you stealing so fast?
Silly girl.
You really think I'm stupid?
I'm here to date you.
Why should I not bring my wallet?
I was just kidding.
I want to make our date special today.
A little more unforgettable.
Do you mind?
I think you're really
boring sometimes.
Qi.
I discussed with Baishi.
He said it was an emotion.
What emotion?
It's boring.
Fine.
I'm sorry.
Don't be angry.
By the way,
when I went down,
there were a lot of fun things.
Let's go and have a look.
Then you have to promise me
you won't play the long ballad again.
I promise.
And I'll clean up Baishi when I go back.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
So you changed her comment.
I care too much.
I won't have you as a gift.
So you can go now.
Xiao Tao, you don't need to be mean to me.
Actually, the message 탖
has the end of year.
The line was fun
when we last met and forbade you.
I didn't expect Wei Zhanghong
to leave the Imperial College.
He always
treated Song Lotian with respect.
But he ended up
in a bad situation.
Poor him.
Song Lotian didn't even come to see him off.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Deputy Chief Yan, Dr. Feng,
Dr. Guang,
I'm leaving Bianjing in a few days.
I'll say goodbye to the teachers here.
Even if you leave the Imperial College,
don't forget to study.
Don't forget the school.
I'll remember it.
It's getting late.
Stop the nonsense. Take him away.
Yes.
Stop.
They're here.
Hurry up.
I'll let you live.
Song Lotian.
Young Master, you can't.
Master didn't want you to leave the mansion.
If you make trouble again, be careful of getting punished.
Put it down.
Don't worry, Wei Zhanghong.
I'll ask my father to help you.
No need.
I won't
have any more business with your family.
Take him away.
Yes.
Go back to class.
Let's go.
Please.
Mr. Zhuo,
why did you find such a place to meet me?
You can only stay awake
when you're in a state of absence.
You can't be too happy.
Aunt said
the Grand Tutor has lived in the temple for a long time.
It's inevitable that he's lost his mind.
He should come out more often.
You're right.
I should come out more often.
I'm afraid
I can't be with you.
I came here early.
About the tea garden,
you've helped me solve the problem
without any other way.
If you want to be an official,
I'll help you.
Thank you, Grand Tutor.
Although you
have taken the responsibility,
you can't
keep the truth.
If you can't
bear the blame,
I'll be the one to be blamed.
Besides,
Yan Yunzhi is not easy to deal with.
If it wasn't for his nephew,
the tea garden wouldn't have been exposed.
I'm afraid
he won't let go of the matter.
If you can be an official,
you can keep the good news.
Don't worry, Grand Tutor.
I have my own plans.
What's the prize?
What prize?
The Imperial College will hold a lecture tomorrow.
Dr. Song is the main actor.
How capable Dr. Song is!
He's going to give a lecture on behalf of the official.
Besides, the tea garden ceremony
has just passed.
It's too childish.
It shows that
Dr. Song is trusted by the official.
The lecture
is for the benefit of Grand Tutor.
It's to
eliminate the prejudice against him.
I think
it's just a premonition.
He just wants to make it look good.
As for whether he can make it or not,
it's up to us.
Look.
How about this?
Good.
I see.
The lecture tomorrow
will be inappropriate.
Sang Qi.
You're causing trouble again.
This is a serious matter.
Don't get into trouble again.
I'm not.
Let me make it clear.
I'm not causing trouble.
Dr. Song
is unlucky.
Yes.
It's the will of God.
The will of God.
Be careful.
Don't get caught.
That's what friends should say.
I'll say it again.
Look.
You must
hold this rope.
Okay.
Don't let Dr. Song find out.
Don't worry.
I
have been a man of the world.
I've tried my best
and finally succeeded.
I've made great achievements
and made great achievements.
I'm doing this
to live up to
the expectation of the officials.
Hmm.
I know
that some people
have been spreading rumors
to blackmail me.
You
are eunuchs.
You are easily fooled.
You have some misunderstanding about me.
I don't care.
Look.
I guess you all know
that this tree
is the famous
bamboo cane.
Back then,
the boatman was talking about
this tree.
This bamboo cane is very spiritual.
It can be used to make a middleman.
Only loyal officials
can stand under this tree.
Do you know that?
Be careful, Your Highness.
There are assassins.
Be careful.
Catch them.
Hurry.
Sir.
This is...
Great.
You people in the Royalòngs Muhow
Fine.
Then don't blame me for being rude.
Please calm down, Grand Tutor.
Deputy Chief.
Deputy Chief, look at this.
Grand Tutor Song,
I'm willing to take all the responsibility.
You're willing to take all the responsibility?
Please punish me, Grand Tutor.
Don't cover up
these evil swordsmen.
Please punish me, Grand Tutor.
It's inevitable that you'll be punished.
I think
you should be punished.
It's inevitable.
I think the school style of the Imperial College
is the sun and the moon.
The head of the Imperial College
has violated the law
and offended the officials of the court.
It's really
a bad thing.
It's hard to save him with this.
Don't look at Deputy Chief.
Grand Tutor Song was humiliated.
It's reasonable to
vent your anger at this time.
Don't do it.
It's reasonable not to?
Say no more.
Grand Tutor Song,
do your own job.
Let me do it.
Shut up.
Go.
We've made a mistake,
it has nothing to do with the pancakes.
it has nothing to do with pancakes.
We've made a mistake,
How dare you!
Don't you have a sign?
Grand Tutor Song,
I know who is the traitor.
Who?
After all,
it's because of this tree.
Although it's a sacred tree
that the official has certified,
it was also
hit by Grand Tutor Song
when he was unconscious.
Fortunately,
the tree was cut down
and he was able to breathe.
Am I right?
Yes.
Get me out of here.
Go.
This...
Come on, Third Master.
Go.
You...
Grand Tutor Song,
we'll satisfy you
with whatever you like.
If you're cold,
I'll cut it into wood
to keep you warm.
If you're tired,
we'll make you
a long-awaited sweet wooden bed.
You have everything you need.
You can choose.
I can choose?
If you're...
If you're bored...
It's easier to say if you're bored.
I'll make you a wooden stick
and sprinkle some of my
unique secret ingredients.
It's fun to tell stories.
Choose.
You...
Nonsense.
How can you do that?
Grand Tutor Song.
Grand Tutor Song,
or 15 Zemun revvers.
The one cut
is done by Grand Tutor Song himself.
You're not my sunlight underlings.
I'm sorry.
Grandfather.
Please.
You're going against me?
Are you going against me?
Are you trying to rebel?
Are you?
You...
Your father, Wang Zi Cheng,
will give you a good lesson.
Take it.
Song Luo Tian.
You're a traitor.
You...
Listen.
Fine.
I'm going to report this
to the government today.
Wait and see.
Father.
Please calm down.
Grandfather.
Father.
Please calm down.
I...
I'm going to the palace.
Why are you going with me?
You're a unfilial son.
You're embarrassing me.
Get out.
I...
Father.
Please calm down.
Get out of here.
Father.
Please calm down.
Get out.
Mom, thanks.
I asked seeds before I chestnut or earned my pockets.
I never borrowed the money.
I Jewelry Store
Do everything according to plan
선anas watch out for the events
Rbinche
I'm okay
How dare you bore one's part?
Youестil all my troubles.
I
The one who sent the letter threw away the Wei family.
Yan Sanlang made a mistake.
Yan Yunzhi,
I'll take your private position now.
First,
I do want to calm down
the anger of Grand Tutor Song.
Second,
without the private position,
you can help me
investigate the Song family.
You're wise, Your Majesty.
I won't let you down.
Remember,
don't say anything bad.
We're secretly reading Chen Cang's book.
You must be careful.
Don't let Grand Tutor Song
catch you again.
Yes.
Grand Tutor Song
won't give up easily
in the past.
I wonder
what crime
we'll be punished for.
It's okay.
The Song family
is the master of the Zhao family.
We can just do what we want.
Why are you so confident today?
Something bad happened.
What's wrong?
The private position is gone.
What?
It's gone.
The private position is gone again.
Yesterday,
under the strong demands of Grand Tutor Song,
the official family exempted
Yan Yunzhi's private position.
Yes.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Go.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Private position.
What are you doing?
Where is the private position?
There is no rule.
You're so loud.
You made a scene.
Today,
you don't know how much you're being punished.
Yan Yunzhi really doesn't come to the Imperial College?
It's arranged like this for now.
In the future,
I'll be in charge of it.
The official family
still values
Grand Tutor Song's feelings.
Let's go to Grand Tutor Song's mansion
to get justice for Deputy Chief.
I don't believe it.
We have so many people.
He can take us to the river.
Am I right?
Yes.
Get justice.
You...
We'll break through the city
and break the blood stream.
Can you talk?
We'll build a city
and make the world a better place.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Grand Tutor Song.
I'm sorry.
Look at you.
You're so mad at Grand Tutor Song.
You're going to see the saint.
Deputy Chief.
Ren Zhi.
You're finally here.
I can't
control these naughty students.
I just came back to get some books.
Yesterday, you were so disrespectful to Grand Tutor Song.
Didn't you think about the consequences today?
From now on,
listen to the teachings of Grand Tutor Feng
and be patient.
Do you understand?
Yes.
I understand.
Miss.
Get the carriage ready.
Let's go.
You don't feel well?
No.
Father.
I'm hungry.
Let's eat.
Do you want to eat?
Go to the Yan's Mansion.
Okay.
Don't go.
Brother.
Deputy Chief Yan is not in the Imperial College.
I have a lot of questions to answer.
Don't think too much.
It's all for learning.
You're so hardworking.
You want to be a man of honor.
Don't think I don't know
what you did to Grand Tutor Song in the Imperial College.
Now it's a joke
that the court officials are telling.
If I knew you would cause trouble,
I shouldn't have let you go to the Imperial College.
From now on,
you won't go to class.
Don't go out.
Close the door.
Yes.
Yan Ping.
When the lights in Father's room are dimmed,
we'll...
We'll go out from the backyard.
Miss.
Don't talk about me in this trick.
Grand Tutor is also confused.
He almost stepped on his back and left.
Yan Ping.
You're so smart.
You can turn half of your mouth.
How nice.
Why are you here?
Mr. Zhuo.
How did you get in?
No one can catch your future master.
Who's your master?
What are you doing here?
I'm taking you out for a meal.
Let's go.
Miss.
No.
I'm sorry.
What do you think
about Deputy Chief's absence?
I think
he's a little bit dull.
Maybe he's feeling down
and crying at home.
No.
I think
he's doing something bad at home.
Think about it.
How did he deal with us?
How could a thousand-year-old fox
stay at home without any worries?
You said
Deputy Chief
was free and just stroked his feet.
What does that mean?
Is he like this
or like this?
He stroked his feet like this.
Mr. Sang.
You're here at the right time.
Mr. Zhuo.
Let's go to the Yan Mansion
and see Deputy Chief.
Calm down.
You're an old man.
You should calm down.
Although
Deputy Chief's absence
is indeed a big deal.
But is he
really like this?
He's not.
Maybe he's feeling down
and doesn't want us to bother him.
Right?
You're usually
very concerned about Deputy Chief.
Why are you suddenly
not concerned about his actions?
No, I...
Right.
Isn't Sang
the most anxious person?
I...
I'm just like you.
I'm just guessing.
I just think
Deputy Chief is
like this.
If we rush to him,
he'll be upset.
You don't know
that he's always in the rain.
I can't figure it out.
I'm afraid that
we'll do something bad, right?
If you insist on going,
I can go with you.
Then...
Let's go.
Another issue.
It'll be troublesome
if we disturb Deputy Chief.
Let's go.
Do you think
Deputy Chief will go up the mountain
to find Master to solve it?
Let me tell you.
If you dare to go up the mountain to find Master,
he'll definitely punish you
for pretending to be a thief.
That's annoying.
It's enough for today.
We've been working so hard to find Deputy Chief.
Maybe he...
He's...
He's in the bathhouse
right?
Let's go back.
Right.
He's not in the bathhouse yet.
Master Sang.
It's inconvenient for women to go there.
But I, Yan Yan,
can't be easily fooled.
I'll go.
No, Yan Yan.
Yan Yan.
You're...
Trust me.
How could he be in the bathhouse?
I'm so impressed.
You don't know.
How could it be?
Don't...
What do you want me to do?
You're so romantic.
What did you say?
I just left Guo Zi County.
You changed your mind so quickly.
Deputy Chief.
You're here.
Don't call me Deputy Chief.
Just call me by my real name.
You...
Si...
Yan Yan.
The maid has been looking for you for a long time.
It's not her fault.
She pulled me and made trouble everywhere.
I'm just trying to relieve your boredom.
She came to my house
to play the piano and draw.
But she drank all my wine.
I took her to the wine room.
She was so drunk.
She refused to go in with me.
She pulled me.
It's not fair to be rude to a gentleman.
Yan Yan, you know it.
Then drink with me.
I know.
I can drink with you.
I'll drink with you.
Take it.
We'll be good brothers in the future.
We'll go out and have fun together.
We'll drink together.
We won't bring Qing Xuan Jun with us.
To be honest,
I'm tired of it.
I'm your Deputy Chief.
I'm tired of your stupidity.
I finally got out of the bitter sea.
Now I'm no longer your Deputy Chief.
In the future,
we'll have a lot of time to play together
and drink together.
But Sang Qi can't bring you with him.
It's okay.
In the future,
you can drink with me.
What are you waiting for?
Let's drink.
You...
You saw it.
Deputy Chief...
Deputy Chief Qian
is much better than us.
Let's go back to our home.
You...
Brother Yan.
Let's forget about it.
Since we're brothers,
why don't we become sworn brothers
so we can enjoy the beauty together?
Let's go!
I haven't enough homework.
Am I being teased?
Come on.
Bring all the wine out.
What's wrong with you?
You're so drunk.
You're just a private servant of the Imperial College.
You're really going to do nothing
after losing the official position.
Wen Shi.
Bring the wine.
Go get the wine for me.
If you don't bring the wine out,
I'll tell you what you'll do.
Wen Shi.
Bring it out.
Hurry up.
Qi Lang.
You're being polite.
You'll ruin the reputation of our family.
How can you do that?
Stop drinking.
No.
You're so drunk.
Alright.
Go, aunt.
Bring the wine out.
Qi Lang.
Let's drink.
Your Highness.
According to the informant,
the team that's going to arrest Lord Wei
has left Bianjing.
What we can be assured of is
Lord Yan has sent people to protect the Yan family.
Keep an eye on their whereabouts.
Lord Yan asked me to give you the map.
This is the route to be left.
Jingzhou.
An Shi.
Yes.
Bring a message to Lord Qingxuan for me.
Tell him
I asked him to come to the capital.
Yes.
I asked him to go out to have fun.
Tell him to get ready
to pick me up.
Yes, Your Highness.
Miss Su.
Baishi.
What's up?
Is Lord Qingxuan here?
He's awake.
Just tell me if you need anything.
Here's the thing, Miss Su.
My son invited him to go out to have fun.
He asked Lord Qingxuan to come to the mansion
to ask my son to go out.
Okay.
I got it.
Thank you, Miss Su.
Lord Yan is not in the Imperial College.
I don't think you should send a message in person.
Yan Yunzhi left.
And Dr. Feng is still here.
Have you forgotten?
Dr. Feng is taking over the Imperial College.
He's getting more and more strict.
He's reading his grandpa's homework every day.
I'm still studying hard.
Unlike Yan Yan.
He can fall asleep in every class.
I'm really convinced of him.
Yan Yan?
He's a really free person.
He can treat Guo Zijian as his family.
He can sleep wherever he wants.
You're called...
What's that?
A teacher in the Imperial College.
What are you talking about, Miss?
Qian Yan.
Qian...
Sorry.
It's okay.
Miss Sang Qi.
Let's go.
Lan Ji.
Qi.
Long time no see.
You've ordered so many things.
I need to go back to the villa for a while.
Where?
Qi is not pushing me away, right?
What?
I'm just kidding.
Qi is serious.
It's Yun Zhi.
He asked me to go out for a trip tomorrow.
I'm here to do some things he likes.
Go out?
Could it be...
I haven't seen Mr. Yan for a long time.
How is he doing recently?
He's free at home.
But the elders are a little anxious.
But I think
it's good for him to take a break.
He was busy with the Imperial College affairs.
I rarely have time to spend with him alone.
It seems Lan Ji is not angry.
That's great.
He's still thinking about going out for a trip.
He said he was not forced to do so.
That's great.
Lan Ji hasn't finished some things yet.
He'll invite Qi to the mansion some other day.
dickey
Given up
You midway
Father,
don't worry, the
up quick
Let your blessing of..
I can do it!
It's none of your business!
You mean
Who?
Yeah, who?
Do what?
There's nothing like my rope.
A little compounds is said that
the link
Isn't it?
Start
It's all right.
You're getting late.
gave the rings to our concubine.
Come in.
Many people have been watching us.
I'm afraid
Lord Wei can't get to us.
It's okay.
There are many people in Jinzhou.
It's a good job.
I'll teach you to change your shape
and prepare to pick up the people.
Yes.
Love Me if you Are Sharp
If it's love's persistence
that has made us fall in love
I'm the one who has this vision
If it's attachment
that has made me a part of it
My part
I can't
hold it
and ignore this perfect story
It's the way
I feel when I'm crazy
In this small city
I've changed the beginning
and lost the love that I didn't love
I've written the lyrics of the new moon
and I've finished this city
In the future, I'll break through the barrenness
and melt into the deep
and warm room
In the future, I'll break through the barrenness
and melt into the deep
and warm room