The Long Ballad
Episode 16
Baishi,
did you bring the painting to Qingquan Jun?
Why hasn't he come yet?
I did tell Qingquan Jun,
but...
Time is flying
No one is worth anything
His Majesty assessments me
Being a grown man,
is there a tether to my position?
Yes
It has always been the young master
raise the child
If Yuanzhi found out
about this,
your whole family
Are you Trance Oh, Don't, or else?
Sang Qi,
so much is law wound now.
You have no other options.
The investigation is over.
It's obvious that Wei family is a puppet.
But there's no direct evidence
that it's the Song family.
It's obvious that
it's related to Xizhao.
But brother and Song family
have nothing to do with each other.
Brother.
It's like there's a hole here.
The news is scattered.
There's no way to push it.
Or there's a part of the dead leaves
that didn't tell me about brother.
How dare you
call me the Song family?
I don't care about the Song family.
Give me a place to eat and drink.
Yeah.
What's going on?
There's really no place.
Song Ruotian,
why are you so insolent?
What's going on?
I don't know what's going on.
Are you alone?
What?
May I ask for your help?
Song Ruotian,
although we both
are in the same field,
most of the time,
we are not in the same field.
You're willing to drink with me today.
You want to find someone
who's familiar with you, right?
I don't care.
Even if it's you, Sang Qi,
I'm fine with it.
Then you can go out.
I just found out
that Wei Zhanhong's joke
is about to be revealed.
Wei Zhanhong?
How is he doing now?
He's not doing well.
Before he left,
I gave some money to the officials
of the Wei family.
I told them to take care of Wei Zhanhong.
But I just got a message from the station.
They said they would arrive at the capital soon.
Does Grand Tutor know about this?
No.
No?
My father didn't allow me
to mention the Wei family.
His relationship with the Wei family
is very clear.
So I have to come alone
and get rid of it.
Before this, I thought
Song Ruotian,
Wei Zhanhong is just a junior in your class.
But now it seems
you have some feelings for him.
It's a sight to behold.
However...
Just say it.
Wei Zhan Hong is not loyal to you.
But it's true that the Wei family is guilty.
With your trust in Wei Zhan Hong,
you can help Wei family.
I've been trying to break him up.
But we've known each other for years.
My father is strict.
I'm a little stubborn.
So I can only ask Wei Zhan Hong to do some work for me.
Speaking of which,
I'm sorry.
Get up!
Can't you say half of it?
You have to finish it.
What work?
I asked him to do it.
I played tricks on you.
But he messed it up.
You're so annoying.
Let him go.
Please forgive me this time.
I forgive you.
But you have to tell me
which one is it, right?
It's the time when you were poisoned by Guo Zi Jian.
I asked Wei Zhan Hong to put the medicine in the food.
You insisted on cooking for Deputy Chief.
I put the medicine in the bowl.
What did you ask Wei Zhan Hong to do?
I asked him to do something.
The medicine.
Look at this.
No.
I didn't eat the medicine.
It's the poison powder from Xizhao.
It can kill people.
So,
Wei Zhan Hong
must have something to do with Xizhao.
Oh, no.
We're being plotted.
Wait.
We agreed that
we'll be good friends after drinking.
In the future,
I'll drink with you if I have a chance.
No.
Sang Qi.
Come back.
I, Song Luo Tian,
don't have friends after all.
I'm sorry.
My Lady.
My Lady, why are you going to Jinzhou?
Qi.
Mr. Zhuo, you're just in time.
Help me convince my Lady.
Why are you going to Jinzhou?
Deputy Chief is hiding something from me.
I'm going to save him.
He's in trouble.
It's worth your life.
It's worth it.
My Lady.
Wait, I'll go with you.
Childe,
it's been a while since we came out of the camp.
Why haven't they arrived yet?
Did something happen on the way?
The enemy is a tough one.
It won't be that fast.
Hurry up.
Do it.
Help!
Childe,
there's an enemy ahead.
Retreat!
Help!
Your Grace...
Go, quick.
Yu Jerk Kai,
you have tutor's цๆosion now!
For you,
Yanwnan Jue's
little sister has
the same strong medicine ceremony as Yuанные!
Duke Wei,
leave!
Run!
Are you okay?
Why are you here?
I'm fine.
Zeyan.
Step back.
Master Yan,
We're here under Lord Yan's order.
Don't worry about the past. Go after them!
Follow me!
Yes!
Master,
call a young master.
Brother,
go after Master Wei.
I'll go after Master Wei.
Be careful.
Qi.
Qi!
Young Master!
Sang Qi!
Go!
Stop!
I'm late.
Sir,
please go after them.
I have to go back to the canal.
Yes!
Go!
One!
говорю
Young Master, are you feeling better?
Allある
How is it?
I'm late.
Master Fei is dead.
Baishi.
His injury is so serious.
We need to go back to the city to save him.
It's not a good idea to drag him out.
Let's go.
Qi, you go back first.
Don't worry about me.
The people from the medical department are attacking again.
I want you to be safe.
Ning Yunche.
This is not the Imperial College.
I don't want to hear this from you.
Are we still waiting for Mr. Zhuo?
He should be fine.
Those people didn't go there for him.
They won't do it alone.
There are so many people waiting for him.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Come on.
Let's go.
I'll take you.
No.
I don't want to do it with you.
But...
You should have said it earlier.
Be careful with your wound.
I'm afraid we can't bring Wei Zhanhong back.
Don't worry.
The plan has failed.
He has no reason to live.
According to our original plan,
after Yan Sanlang received the news
that the Wei family was arriving in Jingzhou,
Yan Yunzhi would surely follow them secretly.
I just didn't expect
that he would kill a funeral instrument halfway.
So far,
I have no idea
what Yan Yunzhi is up to.
So far,
I think we should forget about it.
I have already figured out
the possibility of the plan's failure.
I have ambushed people on the way back.
I will not let it go.
You can't hurt the funeral instrument.
I know that you have
already told me
that you will never hurt your little funeral instrument.
I won't hurt it again.
Yourmaybe is hurt.
How can you stens the strength as the strength stops?
I said that you should be here.
Why were you running back?
There are ghosts in the Wei family.
You must be in danger with them.
Do you know why they're not here?
You know she's not a ghost.
Su Lotian told me
that she gave me the antidote.
After Wei Zahong's hand,
she changed to the poison powder of Xizhao.
It must be something serious.
%%
Sean.
Yeah.
Come on.
Come here.
Look at me.
It's really Xizhou's men.
They want to kill us.
They really don't know what to do.
He Qi.
Young Master.
How could this happen?
We only have one horse now.
It might be difficult to get back to the city together.
He Qi.
It's dangerous here. You should go back first.
We'll wait for you here after we get the doctor and horse.
I'll stay with you.
Baishi.
Please go to the village.
I...
Okay.
I'll leave it to you.
Be careful.
He Qi.
Don't look at me like that.
I'm fine. I know what I'm doing.
You're badly injured.
Take a good rest. Don't talk.
I want to talk.
If you want to talk,
tell me
what's the connection between you and Xizhou.
Yuxiu.
To make you feel better,
I'll give you a massage.
I stole the best wine of my father.
Yuxiu.
What's wrong?
You look happy in the daytime.
What happened to the competition?
One thought is a mistake.
One thousand miles is a medicine.
One thought is a mistake. One thousand miles is a medicine.
What does it mean?
I've been thinking about it for a while.
Yuxiu died in front of me the next day.
According to what I said,
Yuxiu was ill and had a heart attack.
But Yuxiu told me
that he was getting better.
When I wanted to
find out the truth
and find clues,
I found that all the traces of Yuxiu
were cleared.
Could it be
because Yuxiu knew something
that was important to me?
What are you doing?
Who told you to burn Yuxiu's stuff?
We don't know.
A man who claimed to be a government official
told us to burn it.
He told us to clean up the mess.
Those who burned clothes
can't be investigated, right?
Yuxiu's case was soon over.
From Guo Zijin to Taiwei Prefecture,
I knew that
he died of illness.
I knew it clearly.
But I knew that
someone must have
killed him behind his back.
But he was a secret.
I was a student at that time.
I couldn't pursue him
and I couldn't fight him.
It's because of your persistence
that I didn't get away from death.
But
how did you find the clue
that Xizhao knew?
Since I knew Zijian,
I've been investigating.
I've been secretly noticing
the state of death
between Yan Sanlang and Yuxiu
using the information of the plant.
Just before you entered Zijian's study,
we found
a crime scene that looked very similar.
We found the powder of Xizhao there.
How could it be so coincidental?
Now the clue points to the Song family
and the Wei family.
Although they are in the dark,
I can assure you that
they are very powerful.
When I entered Zijian's study,
you made me suffer a lot.
Later, you arranged me to go to Lingwu Peak to pray.
Actually, it's all for...
Protect you.
It's all for protecting you.
Hmm.
Who on earth are you?
I just hope
you can barrier yourself
after you get experienced.
I'm afraid it'll finally end
as soon as you become like this.
Deputy Commander.
Well,
Deputy Commander, are you alright?
Qi,
I suddenly
I want to...
I want to rest.
No, no.
You can't rest.
Ye Yunchi!
Look at me!
Open your eyes and look at me.
If that's the case,
how can we meet?
Are you really willing to let me live with this feeling?
When can we meet?
You know that.
Yes, sir!
Who says she know you last?
She just came to visit her.
much better than you.
Let her go.
All right.
Is it not you?
She seems like other woman.
Who is she?
Get out!
Come on.
This is my sword.
Okay.
Go.
Sir.
Mr. Yan.
How's the investigation going?
Sir.
Mr. Wei is dead.
The coroner found
a pattern of Xizhao on Mr. Wei's shoulder.
Wei Zhanhong is missing.
His life is still unknown.
The Wei family's charge is settled.
But the scene has been cleared.
I wonder
who the upper family is connected to.
Yan Yunzhi went to investigate the Wei family.
How is he now?
Mr. Yan.
He was seriously injured
to find out the truth.
Yan Yunzhi
Morning, Deputy Chief.
Morning.
Deputy Chief.
Morning, Deputy Chief.
Morning.
Deputy Chief.
Mr. Yan.
Yunzhi.
You're here.
Why are you so serious about studying?
We're just doing our daily tasks.
We don't want to be
in a mess on the exam.
I brought some food for you.
Sir.
After you put it down, I'll get you some water.
Be careful.
Let's wash our hands before eating.
Thank you, Deputy Chief.
You're so popular now.
When you were writing the article,
why did you hang some shoes?
My father has been
missing you all.
Yan Yan.
I was going to ask you to go to Xiaozhuo
for a drink.
But Dr. Feng is so strict with you.
I think we should forget it.
No, no.
Xiaozhuo is a man of his word.
Let's go.
Dr. Feng asked you to study
for your own good.
You must learn to be a man of your word.
Understand?
Yes.
Look.
The words of Mr. Guo Chengjun
are all written on the paper.
I don't need to read the article.
I know you've improved.
Thank you, Deputy Chief.
Water is coming.
Let's take a break.
Let's eat something.
Let's go.
Come on.
Thank you, Deputy Chief.
Come on. Let's wash our hands.
Hurry up.
Let's fly.
What's this?
Let me see.
Hurry up.
So many.
Deputy Chief, this is a secret box.
Where is it?
It's in the hole.
There's a hole in the door.
It's so dark.
What's this?
Don't worry.
We'll play the game.
Look.
Thank you, Deputy Chief.
Come on.
I want this.
Here you are.
Qi.
I want to talk to you later.
There's more.
Here.
I ate one.
This is delicious.
Try it.
Qi.
Master Sang.
Hello, Deputy Chief.
Qi.
Master Sang.
Why are you here alone?
What are you doing here?
What are you looking at?
You're robbing me.
Give it back to me.
Take a look.
What's so good about you that I don't understand?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You're bored by yourself.
Exactly.
I'm not bored.
You can go back.
Deputy Chief Yan.
Zhuo Yunyuan isn't in, is he?
No.
Mr. Zhuo isn't here.
Master, Mr. Yan is here.
Grand Commandant Sang.
I'm sorry for the sudden visit.
What's up?
I'm here to talk about
Sang Qi's study.
But I remember
you're no longer the Deputy Chief of the Imperial College.
You're at home now.
Grand Commandant is right.
I don't have any work to do now.
So I'm doing some private activities
for my uncle's family.
I think
Sang Qi needs support
at school.
Yang Yanzhi.
Just tell me what you want to say.
I'll tell you the truth.
I'm old enough to get married.
I've been in love with Sang Qi for a long time.
I hope Grand Commandant Sang
can consider me as
the future husband-to-be of Sang Qi.
Lin Ping.
What are you eating tonight?
Today, the third young master of the Li family
prepared a big plate.
I've asked the chef to make it.
You always send these to our house.
It seems that Grand Commandant's Mansion
is lacking this dish.
I can only say
that our Qi is very popular.
Now the young girls in Bianjing
don't know what they're thinking.
What four young masters and four beautiful ladies?
In my opinion,
they're far from me
as I was back then.
They all look like
a bad girl.
They even play the role of the peaches and the bees.
Grand Commandant.
Our young master is...
Look at my memory.
I forgot that you're still here.
I'm listening.
Shulan.
The two families of Yan Sang
are the two big families of Bianjing.
They're a family of two.
But everything has its own side.
If they get married,
I'm afraid they'll be in trouble.
I understand Grand Commandant Sang's intention.
But marriage is a big thing for life.
You should consider Sang Qi's feelings.
Yuan Ping.
Young Master Yan has been here for a long time.
Why can't you even bring a cup of tea?
How do I teach you?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
I'm going to get it.
No need.
I'll wait until Sang Qi has made up his mind.
I'll visit him in person at that time.
Thank you, Grand Commandant.
I'll leave now.
Okay.
What did he say?
He's really a man of his word.
I've heard that
he's a bad man.
Now he's put down his armor
and is laughing so hard.
It seems that it's not good.
Qi will be taken away by him sooner or later.
Master.
You just drove him away.
What do you know?
He'll come sooner or later.
Father.
Master.
You're just in time.
Look at this.
I heard that Chen Liu has a position.
He's free and needs someone.
So I recommended your name to the Ministry of Personnel.
Chen Liu?
Although the place is small,
it's close to Bianjing.
It's a job.
Think it over and you'll get the job.
If you keep being so reckless,
you won't even be able to get a wife.
I'll marry a fairy too.
Go get her.
Is life so Graphic porphyr ports?
Steve Ye has really left?
Left?
To where?
N small chat Reports from Ministry of Power
said he's gonna serve their train in Chen Liu.
He'll be leaving for the office in a few days.
Our fate is so close.
I have a good idea.
What idea?
Wait for the test.
Don't be too concerned.
Just deal with it.
You mean
Dr. Feng will feel that Dr. Feng is not here.
We are all out of our mind.
Sang knows me well.
Dr. Feng will be angry
and tell the officials.
The rest
will be settled.
Yes.
Brother Zhuo,
especially you,
don't always be a stubborn person.
We need to
work together to solve this.
Am I right?
Yes. Yes.
I don't know what you are worrying about.
The Imperial College is not as good as
Yan Yun Zhi.
You don't want Yan Si to come back?
I come to study.
I don't come to follow him.
You are still too young.
What's wrong with him?
He is really young.
Yes.
What does he mean?
Stop writing.
Ruo Boyuan.
Ruo Boyuan...
Put these here.
Go to the 不血 regardless.
Go back quickly.
Wait for good news.
Okay.
Let's go.
A'Qian,
do you want to go back so easily?
Not only me,
all the swordsmen want to go back.
In fact, they are
very afraid of Deputy Chief.
But in their heart,
they all agree
with his teaching philosophy.
They think Dr. Feng
is too old-fashioned.
I'm asking you,
not others.
Forget it.
I'm in a bad mood today.
Go to the Qingfang Restaurant with me to have a drink.
But I have something to do today.
You go by yourself.
Now the old man who killed my brother
is in the same place as me.
Now the murderer who killed my brother
is in danger.
The danger is close.
Is Deputy Chief going to Chenliubin?
Someone has come.
It's really a good thing.
We meet again after a long distance.
You are so sneaky.
Aren't you afraid that I'll be shot and fly out?
Don't forget that
I'm your senior in martial arts.
Besides,
you can't win.
You are going to Chenliubin.
Why can't I win?
You already know it?
Of course I know it.
I know it from others' mouth.
I was still against it a few days ago.
Now such an important plan
doesn't know how to tell me.
I'm still a stranger.
Qi,
I only went to Chenliubin
to guard that official post.
I have the courage
to go to your mansion
and propose to your father.
Propose?
Who said I would propose to you?
I held it back.
I held it back
and you are going to be my wife.
I forgot that you are injured.
Are you okay?
Qi,
if you don't let me go,
I won't go.
My brother's will is not completed yet.
Besides,
I didn't find out about the wedding.
You can't avoid it.
I'm asking you.
There are various ways to and from others' mouth.
Qi,
look.
You should do it later.
You are prettyyself
who is willing
to Asheum to hurry to detail with you.
Go.
From the day I die, I will never forget
I will use this cup to exchange for the time we met
To leave my position in the past
If the persistence of love has made us fall in love
I will have this vision
If ten years have become my time
I will never be able to make it
To write a perfect story
To look determined in the wind
The heart is in the city of unknown
Changed the beginning
Lost the vision of love
I wrote the destiny of the stars and the moon
I also finished this life and death
In the future, from the short and short, it will be a deep kiss
I will never forget
I will use this cup to exchange for the time we met
To leave my position in the past
If ten years have become my time
I will never forget
I will use this cup to exchange for the time we met