The sound of the zither is like water, like a shadow, like a wolf
Episode 16
My Lord, the whole Sang Mansion has been searched.
There's nothing unusual.
Are you satisfied now?
Xi.
Stop talking.
Send the guest out.
The sound of the zither is like water, like a wolf
A'Jie.
What's wrong with you?
You're awake.
Weren't you better before?
Why are you like this again?
A'Jie.
I will definitely find the best doctor for you.
Use the best medicine.
Let's find the patient together.
You brat.
A'Jie has three short stories.
I'm not done with you.
A'Jie.
Who wants water?
Go. Go. Go.
Young Master.
Miss Sang's illness...
It's the same as what Qian Jiu described.
It should be the poison in the box.
The poison has been released.
You've thought it through.
It's not long.
I didn't ask Qian Jiu for the antidote.
No one returned to the inn.
Jing Meng.
Spread the news of Sang Qi's illness as much as possible.
Since we can't find the person who caused the cloud,
we should spread the news.
Let him come to us.
Doctor. Please.
I'm sorry. I really can't.
Qingfeng Restaurant
Qingfeng Restaurant is always here.
I remember that
we were celebrating the end of the imperial examination here.
It was a mess back then.
Yes.
Sang Qi also spread the big news about him and Deputy Chief.
Think about it.
When Sang Qi entered school a year ago,
it was so chaotic.
It was so wonderful during the Shangyuan Festival.
It was even more magnificent when the gold medal was announced.
Now, I heard that he was very ill.
He said he was ill and was ill for a long time.
Life is really full of ups and downs.
Who can't be sure?
Sang Qi
Miss Song.
How is he?
Sang Qi's pulse is strange.
I've never seen such a strange symptom.
If it's a poison,
it's never been before.
Father.
Qi.
Why are you out?
Sang Qi came to see me on purpose.
How can I not see him off?
Sang Qi.
I know my health.
You don't have to worry too much.
Just be careful.
When can we meet?
Qi.
Don't say that.
Remember to take the medicine I gave you.
The grass is like gold.
The sky is bright and the earth is clear.
This is a dream.
Take a glance.
The thing that's in the dream.
My mother sent me to a forest
and found me a magic star.
I define the pe해도es
with the same letter than the upper auspices
and can form two
Do you mean that
I'm not going to save you, right?
Don't talk nonsense.
Have a good rest.
I know
my own body.
No matter what,
I won't be like this.
You poisoned me.
Don't think too much.
Now that it has come to this,
I don't know what I can't admit.
I didn't go back to Heaven.
I just want to die.
Chief dishes and drinks,
don't make me pathways muk recovered
and
are my assets completed?
Now that's why.
Zhao Wan Yuan.
About my brother,
I don't think shooting you...
Looking at why you were trying to hurt my dad,
I want to give it all for it.
종聲аз uncomfortable,
right?
Why did you never think of me
as your brother?
Have you forgotten your feelings?
I tried my best to get your attention.
I hoped you could look back at me
even for a moment.
But you didn't.
You didn't.
You forgot our past.
You forced me to go this far.
I know Zheng Weiyuan.
He is a man of the common people.
He is a young man.
He is definitely not a man like this.
He has gone through all the hardships and made mistakes,
but he is a man who is full of people.
You know Zhuowen Yuan.
Do you really know him?
Can you understand him?
You can't.
You are the daughter of the Grand Commandant's Manor.
Your father protected you since you were a child.
Your brother favored you.
You grew up in the country without any worries.
But what about me?
What about you?
My father made a mistake.
Our whole family was expelled from Bianjing.
Fortunately, my aunt was in the back palace.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have the chance to come back to study.
I will always remember
those who were in the situation
and were unable to take advantage of the situation
and looked down on me.
I will follow the existing rules
and take them step by step.
I'm afraid that everyone will look down on me
and respect me.
I'm afraid that I won't be humiliated anymore.
I'm afraid that I can't live a normal life.
For the sake of a day,
when you need me,
I can stand by your side and protect you.
Anxi,
you are my bottom line.
Since you came to Bianjing
and kept messing up my plan,
I never blamed you.
I've been holding the strings between Xizhao and my aunt.
I've been protecting you with all my heart.
I've been thinking about marrying you
more than once.
But you...
You've been betraying me
and lying to me one after another.
Now,
it's all your choice.
Anxi.
It's a pity
that I met you
and made the most wrong thing
in my life.
I'm going to die.
Now, you are...
Losing you
is a regret in my life.
But if I lose you,
I'll do nothing.
I'm going to die.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
I'm going to die.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
I'm going to die.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
in the last moment of your life,
the one who was by your side
was me.
Anxi,
are you and Bianjing
having an ill relationship?
Sang Yu died of illness four years ago.
Now Sang Qi
can't escape from the same fate.
It's just that Sang Tai is crying.
I heard that he was ill
and was ill all the time.
Didn't you see that Sang Qi was ill today?
He didn't come to the host.
He said that after today,
he would report to the government
and leave Bianjing.
Life is so hard.
I'm sorry.
Brother Zhuo.
Zhuo...
Let's go.
Go.
How dare you come here?
I'm a friend.
I can't even pay you a hundred times.
Friend?
I'm afraid that Sang Qi won't recognize you.
Aren't you afraid that he will come back
and settle the score with you?
Grandpa.
Fine.
I won't argue with you
here today.
But in the future,
I will settle the score with you.
Then I will
take Yan Xiaolang in.
Move aside.
I know he will come.
But I will never let him
see you for the last time
and forgive me.
I'm sorry.
He really came.
Send a letter.
Arrest him.
The dead are the greatest.
I don't think he wants to escape.
Why don't we wait until he's defeated
and then arrest him to return to the dark?
What?
You don't want to hide it anymore?
Zhou Wen Yuan
Let me in.
Let me see her for the last time.
After that, I'll naturally go with you.
Lord Yan,
I told you clearly
that I won't let you see Sang Qi for the last time.
I want you to use the power of the card
in this place.
Master four.
I want you to remember forever
that the last person to see A'qi
is me.
Then I won't have to wait for you anymore.
Si Yi!
Father, you...
I lost you because I lost the baby.
I'm going to help Si Yi today.
Chu Wan Yuan.
Don't!
Chu Wan Yuan!
Chu Wan Yuan, what are you doing?
Master.
Master!
Chu Wan Yuan!
A'qi!
San Yue.
Master!
A'qi!
You're sleeping so well.
You're making me feel so quiet.
It's already like this.
You still don't admit your guilt?
Looking back, I've always been a little bit of a coward.
I have no rules.
You're still so virtuous.
That's good.
I'll go to sleep.
I have something to tell you.
That day, you sent someone to send Yan San Lang to the mountain.
It was a good idea.
But he wasn't in good health.
Grand Concubine Sang.
She lost her son and daughter.
She's so fragile that she's in bed now.
She hasn't been in the imperial court for days.
As for your Yan family,
although you've already cut off all ties with them,
but the Prime Minister has been a good man.
You always do things in a bad way.
Now you're thinking about your own family.
Yan family...
I don't even have to say it.
Yan Yan Shu is just a minor official who has nothing to do with it.
It's impossible for him to just return to his family.
The strong grass of the Song family is now very obedient.
It sounds like I'm going to be empty-handed with you.
Now the upper and lower classes and the common people
are all counting on you.
Everything you wanted to do
is not for me.
Even if you, Lord Zhuo,
is just a criminal son,
if it wasn't for the fact that
I opened the gate for you and let you study,
where would you be today?
Don't call me father.
He's incompetent.
He's not me.
I can only depend on myself to get to where I am today.
It has nothing to do with him.
I won.
Do you really think you won?
Zhuo Yan Yuan, let me ask you.
Now Sang Qi is gone.
Is it that important to lose and win?
Even if you and Fu Kui,
Sang Qi is gone,
is it worth it?
I've been thinking about this for a long time.
I want to answer it well.
I want to choose it well.
But Sang Qi has never given me a chance.
It's you
who forced me.
You're so stupid.
What are you laughing at?
What else do you have to laugh at?
I know you won't let me go.
I know I won't live long.
But don't you think you're more miserable?
If you lose,
you lose more than I do.
Do you believe I'll kill you now?
Okay.
If you want to kill,
I'll say it.
There's always a change.
Fercendo,
incident of expression.
So,
if you want to
change your mind.
Your Highness.
Do you want to get changed
before going to see the Noble Consort
to avoid the bad luck?
No need.
I can't stand the bad luck.
Let's go to the palace.
Yes.
Home sweet home area
The optic syncope gigs
spectacular girls
has been found
and is now in the Jinzhao mansion.
The official is ordered to be interrogated by Lord Xiao.
He has evidence, account books,
and witness.
He also has the motive to hide his identity
and suppress him for years.
Even he has confessed.
Aunt,
don't worry.
He is a murderer,
a thug,
and even murdered a court official.
Everything is a big mistake.
It should be solved earlier.
I understand.
It's clean outside.
Everything can be restored.
I have repaired
the waterways and roads.
It will be able to operate normally in a few days.
Now,
without the redness of the west Zhao,
we are
even more rich.
With these savings,
we can plan bigger things
and buy more people.
Have you hidden the money?
Never hide it in Zhuo mansion again.
Aunt, don't worry.
Before the chaos,
I have transferred it slowly.
Now,
it's placed in a place
that is absolutely safe.
If your father
had half of your wisdom,
he wouldn't have been killed
as a scapegoat.
He even got you involved in the war.
I have been in the cold and warm world.
Now, we are working together.
From the decline of Zhuo family
to the new nobility in the court,
it's not a waste of
all these years of experience.
Wen Yuan,
I was worried that you wouldn't be able to do anything
because of the girl from the Sang family.
Now, it seems that
I have been thinking too much.
Zhuo is still far from here.
All the way here,
she will be stubborn.
From now on,
no one will oppose us again.
It depends on the face of Zhuo family.
SUBJECT
Next Fall
Where are you going?
You've already seen me leave
before you finished your dinner.
Do I look like I'm emerge free?
Come and have some dinner.
If you have anything to say, just remain fistful.
You asked me to be frank.
Tell me.
Is Sang Qi's death
related to you?
What did the roomers say?
It has nothing to do with me.
She's in such good health.
How could she be gone in a few days?
I'm not sure.
I don't know much about medicine.
Besides, you're a weird person.
Since you met Sang Qi for the first time,
you two have been acting differently.
You're always waiting for her to show up.
Why are you suddenly concerned about her death?
Indeed.
Sang Qi and I are not good sisters.
We always have a good relationship.
But I heard...
But I heard that she died
because she wanted to see her again.
She dared to do something wrong
in the big Bianjing city.
She doesn't see me as a lady of the Song family.
It's interesting to think about
the days when she was with us.
Although I wish her well,
I don't want her to die.
Don't cry.
The food is getting cold.
Let's eat together.
Okay.
You've been too busy these days.
You haven't had time to go back to your mother's house, right?
I'll go back with you tomorrow.
Really?
Are you willing to go with me?
There are too many things these days.
I'm tired of it.
I want to stay with my family.
After all, we are family now.
You mean we are family?
From now on,
we are family.
I will treat you well
and cherish what's in front of me.
Tie Meng.
Yes.
Prepare some gifts for the date.
You can go there empty-handed tomorrow.
It's not a good idea.
I'll do it right away.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
You don't think I'm a bad person now, do you?
You are not a bad person.
You are a family.
Honey, let's eat.
Let's eat together.
I'll eat.
Dad,
why don't you see your mother?
I have something to talk to Xianxu.
Go to the back room and find your mother.
Dad.
Be good.
Okay.
I won't bother you.
Go. Go.
Xianxu,
I heard that you solved the case of Xi Zhao.
It's a great achievement.
I also heard that Yan Yunzhi also confessed.
I have NO way out of Yan Yunzhi.
Yes.
How about the ledger
Don't think about it.
I'll remember it.
Then, do you think we can...
Xianxu, look.
We're a family now.
Everything I do
is for the good of our family
and for the good of the Noble Consort.
So, Xianxu, I...
Oh.
Three or four batches of goods
haven't come in yet.
The south is in a mess.
The warehouse is in poor condition.
The goods are in great loss.
If it's safe,
we can move.
It's good for everyone.
Look.
I've told Aunt.
She said it's fine.
Now, this matter is over.
Mr. Xiao is writing a security document.
Since it's over,
no one will pay attention to
the rest.
Oh.
Then,
can we move the goods?
Yes.
The world is in a mess.
If we don't move the goods,
will it be
a mess?
Yes.
Xianxu is smart.
Put this over here.
Yang Zhuo.
Sir.
This is the transaction thing.
Please see here.
Let's go.
I have something important to report.
I want to see the officer.
Please pass it on.
Search the place.
Yes.
Sir, we have a clue.
Sir, we have caught the spy in the capital.
How did you catch him?
It's...
Say it clearly.
I think I saw it clearly.
But it's impossible.
I think we should go back to the capital.
Yes.
I have this.
If I think about the past,
it becomes my
sense of direction.
My sense of direction.
I can't
be the one
who forgets the perfect story.
Is it the way I feel?
The city where the heart is in the unknown.
Changed the beginning.
The person who lost the love.
I wrote the words of the new moon.
I also finished the life in this life.
In the future, we will have a deep talk.
We will have a deep talk.
I'm sorry.