Amo
Since when did there begonia
You always have begonia in your yard
It blooms at this time of year
That cyclamen and purple cloud vine over there
And goldfish
Has it always been
Yeah
Always have
Why didn't I find it
All these years, General, you have lived so unpopular
Everyone else enjoys wine, money and beauty
But you are determined to kill the enemy
Nothing is on the eye
Even if it's your own house
Not even looking at it
but
Why did you pay attention tonight
I
stupid
Because there are more people in the family
What do you mean
By the way General
What to do with that woman
disposition
You taught me
Don't have mercy on traitors
We must return the other bodies in the other way
Why don't we take her
I taught you, too
Take care of your knife
Make a decision after figuring everything out
Shen Que
You're awake
You
Take care of me all night
No, I just arrived
Then it's time to settle our accounts
Where to start
Since I killed you
I stabbed you
It's time to pay the debt with blood
I just want an answer
what
You were
Do you really want me dead
When the rebels rebelled
Fall of the capital
Your brother fell to the rebels
Cricket
Where's the cricket
be careful
Run Girl
stop
Shen Que
Jiang Song
Let her go
Little lady
Is this your little beau
Are you trying to make your little beau lose his head
Let's have fun together again
Do you want him to watch us have fun together
Let's send you all on the road again
If you touch her, I'll kill you
Pretty tough
To live
What are you saying
I can't hear you
I said
What kind of beau is he
Just slaves
The little girl has admired heroes since childhood
I hope the general will let me live
If the general doesn't believe
As good as
Let the little girl kill him herself
As a gift of surrender
OK
I'll fulfill you
Someone bring her a knife
Jiang Song
Why
Nothing survives me
More important
When I wake up
Already in my foster father's barracks
I ask you
Did you really want me dead
Otherwise
NO
When the rebels tried to kill me, I would die
But if you move to avoid the vital point
I could still survive, right
You think too much
I just want to live by myself
Once upon a time I was a slave
Long born with no love
But when you said you found me
I admit that your hide-and-seek skills have improved
But
I'll always find you
You pulled me back into the world
Years after parting
I was filled with resentment
Every day is like a walking dead
Until last night
I saw a tree full of crabapple flowers
I was surprised to realize that my world was back
Because
I found you
At that moment I asked myself
The one who pulled me back to the world
Why can't I trust her again
Tell me the answer
Jiang Niangzi
Your grandmother came to take you home
I'll ask you
How did you become like this
Frame the younger brother
Night stay up
Killing by disfigurement
What else are you afraid to do
Where did my good girl go
Your darling girl
Isn't it at your house
And you blame me for keeping her
If I hadn't planned more
How the Jiang family turned over
Seeing Yao Zu understand Yuan
You're going to marry into the prime minister's house
But you ruined it all
You're the one who ruined it all
And you came to contradict me
Mrs Jiang, please respect yourself
Mrs. Jiang, how can you beat your wife
Do you know how badly she was hurt
That's it, that's it
I can't control you anymore
The wedding is in five days
You don't have to show up again
You want her to marry me
You don't know clearly with a man now
Abandoned the Jiang family again
This marriage has nothing to do with you
Day-dream your dreams
The man who married Choi You-an five days later
It can only be me
I am the one with whom I share three books and six rites
Why let others take it away
The more she wants
The less I will let her
I must marry Choi Woo-an
certainly
Where is the imperial grandson
Can you say it now
No need
Choi You-an
This lady
My bride is not you
Father
Even if we can't find our imperial grandson
And I wouldn't sacrifice anyone
Make my marriage a deal
Choi You-an
I'm not marrying
I'll tell you the whereabouts of the imperial grandson now
Think of it as my wedding gift
I figured it out
Twisted melons are not sweet
As long as you're happy
I'll be content
After the emperor's grandson lived among the people
Alias Zhao Si
Opened a sesame cake shop here
Shopkeeper Zhao
There's a visitor
Shopkeeper Zhao is a visitor
Shopkeeper Zhao
And so on
Something's wrong
I'm rude
Lord, I'll go and see
No one's stuff was emptied
Choi Woo-an, you have to believe me
I saw him two days ago
They sell sesame cakes here
I'm not lying to you
You believe me
I'm really not lying to you
Young Master Prime Minister is here
Let me see who of you dares
be careful
Jiang Jiaojiao
Choi You-an
You believe me
I'm really not lying to you
Stop talking, I'll take you to the doctor
You believe me
I believe in you I believe in you
Choi Woo-an, I want to tell you a secret
Okay, you talk, I'll listen
Don't fall asleep
From the first sight I saw you
I fell in love with you
I really like you so much
Can you try to like me
Try to like me, okay
Bachelor Cui has no need to worry
The arrow missed the point
Lang Jun
I think she's just playing with us
She didn't know the whereabouts of her grandson
Why don't you skin her off
Throw it out and feed it to the dog
Lord
I took someone to inquire
What Jiang Jiaojiao said is true
just
It seems that someone took the imperial grandson two days ago
Almost blamed her wrong
actually
Actually, Nineteen wants to say
The lord married Jiang Song for faith
But she plotted against you after all
And Jiang Jiaojiao risked her life to save you
Lord why
Don't pity those around you
hello
May I ask where is the shopkeeper here
He moved away
Moved away
Why did he move away
That's wrong
It says on this
Choi Woo-an is the day after
The imperial grandson found here
This time hasn't come
Why did he move away
Is Jiang Song not dead
Had a butterfly effect on the plot
Now I don't know where the imperial grandson is
How to explain to the Prime Minister
Take a gamble
Wait for the time
I brought Cui You-an into the baked-seed cake shop
Just do it
Then the bitter plan you mentioned
How do we cooperate
You attacked him
I blocked his knife
But watch out
Get gently
Don't be light or heavy
Don't worry, I killed a pig
Have a sense of measure
Knife skills are trivial
You better be
Sure enough, all the male protagonists in novels do this
Idiot
We agreed to use a knife
Who told him to use the arrow
It hurts me so much
Who
What is it
How do you know
You don't know
The man who shoots the arrow
I actually arranged it
You still want to kill me
of course
You forgot
You can't kill me
Yeah
I can't kill you with my own hands
But can I borrow someone else's hand
I want to try
It seems to be ok
It's a pity that it's a little worse
By the way
Do you know why the imperial grandson suddenly moved
It's you
"Pampered"
I always feel that something is wrong with her
It turns out that she has a strange book about predicting the future
Imperial grandson
So what you mean
The Prime Minister will know I'm here at any time
Right
A woman will definitely inform the prime minister
Where are you?
Think about it
Except for the third prince
You're the only one who can be the crown prince
They won't let you go
It turns out that all along
You're fighting me with this book
Predict the Future
Now that you've seen it
You should know
It's all about me
Nothing to do with you
It's useless if you take it
Take away
Why do you think so about me
Jiaojiao
I already told you
I've never been signed in my life
People can rely on
Only here
The book
It should be your sign
don't
Predict the Future
Now
It's fair