Where are they
Are you afraid that the guilty women will live
Cloud surge reappears
Involved in the case of the former prince
Gibberish
Xiangfu
The same queen and the three princes are all glorious
Lose everything
You should be afraid too
don't say
Just waiting for the blood to dry and die drop by drop
His Majesty Shen Que summoned
A great general
For some guilty girls
Is it worth losing your life
Because they're weak
I'm a knife-wielder
Is my life worth more
They have to die
The surge of clouds does not completely disappear
Rivers and mountains are unstable
Sacrifice is inevitable for the overall situation
Your Majesty
Is he afraid that the grievances of the first prince will be washed away
The courtiers will support the imperial grandson
The Third Prince can't successfully inherit the rule
Presumptuous
You're a smart man
But you're too young
I don't understand people's life
Whether it's an ordinary man or a prince
Only two words at the end
however
How are others
Nothing to do with me
All I know is
There are too many ghosts in this world
In a glossy skin
Do dirty things
But you won't
You used to be a magnanimous boy under my bright universe
If even you are beyond recognition
What else can I believe
I don't want to
You can't be that kind of person
I've seen a lot
A man who thinks he can change the world
In the end, it's not a bow
It is a drop of blood that becomes the tip of my knife
In the turbid currents of their abhorrence
What's their name again
I have long forgotten
Your Majesty
Their names
Call your people
Your Majesty, Your
Why can someone drag Shen Que down
Your Majesty
Zimin
Bachelor Cui
My master wants to see you
Who is your master
Princess Changning
Busy business
Have no time to get out
The princess has five fish
Five fish that can eat nightmares
Maybe it's what the bachelor is looking for
Five fish
Where is your princess
Right in your room
My room
The princess is the goddess of fire
I'm interested in your stay here
You should be happy
Your Majesty has approved
Princess Changning
Bachelor Cui please stay
Please hear me tell a story first
All ears
A fish farmer acquired a fish by chance
That fish is ordinary
But because he swallowed a night pearl
It can glow in the night
The man began
Just have the same nightmare every night
That dream was terrible
As time passes
He hated dreams more than fish
And then what
Then he found a way not to have nightmares
Gained relief
What's the way
What is it
Please listen to the next breakdown
Interesting
Is this fish farmer me or His Majesty
Maybe both
It's just Bachelor Cui
How do you know there is a night pearl in this fish's belly
Doesn't matter if you have it or not
What matters is that nightmares start from it
It can only be destroyed, isn't it
Yeah
I was lucky enough to acquire five fish
It is said that there is a fish with a night pearl in its belly
I don't want to repeat the mistakes of fish farmers
I wanted to give it to Bachelor Cui
Princess Wise
Just don't want the fish
I don't want the night pearl either
So what do you want
stop
What do you want
I'll tell you later
Take a look at these five fish
Is there anything you're looking for
Where
Fish in front of you
You open it and see
You dare to play with me
Where is the guilty woman
You're not giving me what I want
Why should I give you what you want
What do you want
Lotus Pond Fish Cake
what
You put these fish in front of you
Make me lotus pond fish cakes
Then please me
Please me and kneel to me
I will tell you the whereabouts of the guilty girl
Who the hell are you
Jiang Jiaojiao is obviously dead
I'm a storyteller
The cold room is simple
If the princess likes it, she will live
It's just that this joke can't be played casually
Even if I can't kill your body
I can destroy your spirit, too
Jiang Song is the best knife
How can I let you find it easily
The Zhenren said to make you the princess
You can bless me Corning
These days
I really calmed my nerves a lot
What I want to tell Your Majesty today is
The story of Mulian saving his mother
The mother of Buddha's disciple Mulian
Fall into the realm of hungry ghosts and suffer
So he was at the obon party
With the strength of monks from ten directions, his mother can have enough food
But not all children
As filial and righteous as Mulian
Help me
What are you trying to say
First Prince Xiaobi Mulian
And the third prince
An unfilial person
How do you govern the world, Your Majesty
cousin
What is it
That Shen did confess the whereabouts of the guilty girl
Father gave him permission to capture them back and perform meritorious deeds
Shen Qe spoke
The blood was released for three days and three nights
I guess I can't stand it
I'm afraid of death
Just wait and see
But now the question is
Father asked him to catch him alive this time
Could it be that
He wants to retrieve the Cloud Chung Order
Help the first prince reverse the case
In this way
Wouldn't that boy Zhao Chengze be the crown prince
Shen did say where the guilty woman was
Lord
Not found
There's movement there. Go over there
Chase quickly
Bachelor Cui
Found your letter
Choi You'an, long time no see
Sure enough it's you Jiang Jiaojiao
The story goes on one day
Fish farmers no longer have nightmares
Gained relief
Because she put the fish
Killed
She
The fish farmer is a woman
The fish farmer is not Your Majesty
It's not me
It's Jiang Jiaojiao
Such a simple story
You just figured it out
By the way, the fish you're looking for is in the room
If you come alone, you may not have time to save her
Jiang Jiaojiao
Cicada Niang
Madam, spare your life
I won't tell you
You-an, he won't know
Madam, please spare your life
Madam Madam
Cicada Niang, you must die
You can't let others know that you'an him
Choi You-an
Jiang Jiaojiao
What you said
Nightmares arise only because of fish
It can only be destroyed by fish
Jiang Niangzi
Only by killing her
So that I can completely get out
The nightmare you brought me
don't
You begged me
I beg you what do you want
I can give it to you
Late
It's your turn to have nightmares
don't
Jiang Niangzi
Cui Yongzi
I would never let anything happen to you
I'll take you to the doctor now
Why don't you just let me go
Because you are the only one who can save me
You are high above you
How can I save you
NO
Not
I'm not on high
I am
You can't let others know about you
You'an is
I'm not
What are you
You'an is a bastard you born
I was born to a cicada mother
I'm a bastard
My foster mother
Killed my real mother
It's not your fault
Really
False
So this is the secret of your heart
You divide people into three, six and nine
Actually, I am the least classy
ridiculous
Choi You-an, listen to me
You wouldn't be the leading man if it weren't for me
Because I chose you
You're the leading man
Actually, you're nothing
Doing this can really force Choi You-an to die
We can only gamble
Even if I don't die this time
I also have a way to make him fall from a high position
How to do it
The Third Prince is as stupid as a pig
He's just a stepping stone
The ending of the story
Cui You'an will become emperor
But
If there is no third prince
What will happen
Can you move the third prince
I have my own way
But why don't even you know
Cicada Niang is Choi You-an's biological mother
I'm really not impressed by this
I didn't care about Cicada Niang at first
But I was in the prime minister's house
See that he has been drawing pictures of Mulian saving his mother
The servant has also been concerned about the cause of Cicada Niang's death
Cover up
I suspect there's something else
So I tied up Sister Kim
He said that Cui You'an was born to the Prime Minister and the cicada mother
But he was adopted by his mistress since childhood
Seeing the feelings between Cui You'an and Chan Niang
Getting better and better
Plus rumors about his life experience
The mistress killed the cicada mother
It happened that this scene was caught by Choi You-an