You dare kidnap me
Your Majesty
There are many people in the uterus with miscellaneous eyes
I can only help you come here
Your Majesty, please make an edict of abdication
Located in the seventh prince of the youngest son of the queen mother
Seventh Prince
But nine years old
It's also an easy puppet to control
Your Majesty, your Majesty, help me
Your Majesty I don't want to die, Your Majesty
Your Majesty
Every stick of incense will kill a civilian
You dare
Hold it fast
Your Majesty
Please, your Majesty
I'm still in the capital
How dare they rebel
Follow me to East Camp
Bring Li Dacheng's soldiers into the palace to escort him
Zhang Chao
Where is he
Zhang Chao, don't let him run
You are going to rebel today
We, our defenceless civilians, also fought with you
Who said I was going to rebel
I saw it with my own eyes
The rebels are flying your Zhang Chao banner
Shen is indeed under your orders
And killed so many people
Isn't it for today
Yes, yes
We all saw it
We saw killings
Still quibbling? It's too much
Fuck off
I don't want to talk crap to you
Dear neighbors, we as
Zhao's descendants
I want to sacrifice my life for righteousness today
Get out of the way
You kill, you kill
So many people have lost their lives
It's not a few of us
Yeah, it is
No, I'll kill us all
They all killed
Kill
You kill
If you kill us all, you do
Come on, come, kill, kill them all
Kill us
Do it right, kill, kill
Get out of the way
This
General
Zhang Chao
What's going on
It seems that it is really not General Zhang who rebelled
But he is tyrannical
Killed so many people
Good and evil are rewarded
He should pay for his life
Just did so many bad things
Can it be offset by doing a good deed
That's right, but you said he
adoptive mother
Unexpectedly
I, Zhang Chao, didn't die on the battlefield
But to die in the land I guard
adoptive mother
Que'er
So many years
If it weren't you
The foster father will kill more people in vain
Father, thank you
I'm wrong
I shouldn't be soft-hearted
Que'er
You remember
Let the world judge right and wrong
Only you stick to your heart
I am not a good person
Deserves to go to hell
But you
You're different
adoptive mother
Zhang Chao
Your Majesty, help us
Your Majesty
Don't kill me
Help the grass people
General can't
roll
General, you never kill civilians
You'll regret it
Shen Que, remember
No matter what happens in the future
Even if everyone
All leave you
They turned their backs on you
Don't forget who you are
Is it okay
Fairy Sister
It's her
And you're free
It turns out that it's Jiang Song from beginning to end
Dr. Li
If you want to serve your country
Go to Dongdaying and find Li Dacheng
Enter the palace to rescue the driver
Good
Your Majesty, save me
Don't kill
I write
What is this
This was when the former prince investigated the night walkers
The Yun Yong Order taken from the Queen Mother
This is the cloud surge order
great
Clouds surge to make a fire
Another midnight traveler will be here soon
You'an, get it here quickly
Jiang Jiaojiao
I'm not Jiang Jiaojiao
I am
Jiang Song
You
Your Majesty
Your Majesty, you must not compromise
Shen will surely come to save us
And so on
Your Majesty
A stick of incense is almost finished
I write
Your Majesty doesn't want it
Finished writing
Leave them alone
Prime Minister
Shen was seriously injured
We can finish
Good
Even if there is no Yunyong Order
The world is still mine
You An
go
Congratulations
The story is finally coming to an end
What do you mean
The world is actually a story
You're the leading man
The favored son of heaven
Male leading actor
right
And Jiang Jiaojiao is the heroine
Your loot
Except yourself
No one can hurt your life
So she tried to kill you repeatedly
You survived
Amazing, isn't it
Shen Que
The edict of abdication has been issued
Why do you have to resist
Everything you need
When you were created by God
Just being favored
Just have everything
What are the shortcomings
To put it so
My life has been a farce from beginning to end
You should understand it as your legend
But why is it me
Does this matter
Why
Actually, there is no reason
I'm empty here
Getting empty
No matter what, it can't be filled
What am I doing wrong
Heaven wants to treat me like this
Lang Jun did nothing wrong
Everything is a trick of nature
NO
There must be a reason
It turns out there's really no reason
What about the cicada girl
Why must she die
Cicada Niang
Which cicada girl
My real mother
The woman
It's nothing
Probably for your childhood memories
Add some color
So she died for me
Do you care
Yeah
I don't care
I have everything I need
amusing
It's interesting
Let me see
What else am I short of
You've got what you want
Leave them alone
If you want to kill me, kill me
Do you hear that
Your masters are bowing their heads
Aren't you throwing up
Lao Tzu is partial
Shen Que
Jiang Song
How can you miss it
What about the wonderful picture of his death
Look how pitiful he is
Why don't you give him a ride
Don't cry
Your butterfly embroidery is crooked
Fairy Sister
Don't look back
Forget me
You An
Don't rush
Sure enough it can't kill me
It's amazing
You
I've given two people my heart
Cicada Mother died for me
And you
But you want me dead
Push me to a desperate situation
This is what you mean
NO
This is my sincerity
You see
I'm not empty
I learned to love people
I'm no longer a monster
I am not a monster
Kill
The final general Li Dacheng was late to rescue him
After I die
Put a river lamp for me
Is it okay
Do not move
Be honest
It's okay
No matter No matter
It can still be repaired, it can be repaired
God
I am your most true disciple
I would sacrifice my life
Punish the untamed for you
Jiang Song
Who are you
I am
Ginger
Jiang Song
I am
Jiang Jiaojiao