Come soon
Eat more
You see, you have lost weight
Is it sad
Look at your virtue now
Having nothing
So what
Can I help you
How can you help me
Jiang Jiaojiao thought
She is the creator of this world
She's wrong
She once made a wish to God
So God according to her novel
Created a perfect life for her
But she doesn't know how to cherish it
So she's trapped in her own nightmare
Fall
Snap
Her internal organs were completely broken
Time after time
That's enough
What are you panicking about
This is a great thing for you
You alone in the novel
Little people who haven't lived a chapter
Now is your chance
What opportunity
Didn't you always want to leave
The heroine is the key to connecting the two worlds
You just have to be Jiang Jiaojiao and become the heroine
End this story
You can open the city gates and be free
From a few lines of text to a real person
What if I don't
NO
Come with me
Is it good-looking
You wear it
Soo Soo
Show up
She escaped too
Resisted
Finally cornered
Be forced home
And then go crazy
It's not just her
Do you think
How did Adie go crazy
In this world
Disobedience
You can only become a crazy woman
Now you have three options
One is to become them
Second, listen to me
Become Jiang Jiaojiao
Third,
To ask Shen Que
just
But seeing newcomers laugh
I don't see the old man crying
Will he still help you
Who am I to make the choice you give me
I don't even choose
You think you can escape
I'm not running away
Thanks for showing me to see them
To make me understand
Escape shouldn't be a woman's destiny
Weakness only transfers power
What I want to do
It should be rooted in this soil
No matter how barren or bad
I
I also want to break out of my own world
What a pity
This world
It's coming to an end
What do you mean
It's a fantasy world
Is a giant ship about to sink
Even if you don't be Jiang Jiaojiao
When it comes to the end, it will end
Why not seize the chance
Win a new ticket
Start a real life
How much longer
Ten days
This young one belongs to me
This older man
Let's go together
Then thank Young Master Qin
Come and have a sip
Fill whatever you want
come
I won't pursue it if I die
Drink, let you drink
I'll do it
I thought you ran away
So I went to buy wine to honor you, Master Qin
Yeah
Let me honor
Your uncle
Are you seeking death
What are you doing
Yeah
Let my friend go
Or I'll burn this place down
Qin Yongzi
Let him go now
Yeah
Let me go
Shut up
I don't believe you dare
I'll count three
three
two
Stop
Release
Go quickly
As soon as you get out
I'll send someone to bring you back right away
Next time you can't run
Someone wants to hear it
Qin Yongzi at the Princess's Birthday Banquet
A handmaid is frivolous
The story of being punished by the princess with fifty staff
Nonsense
False remarks
It seems that
Young Master Qin was ill in bed some time ago
Is it true
Actually, I have heard of it vaguely
Also
Young Master Qin bought a geisha a few days ago
When I wanted to do something rainy, I found
Shut up
Yourself
No way
How the hell do you know
If I and my friends are damaged at all
The whole capital will know
All the scandals of your Young Master Qin's life
Understand
One more thing
I want you to release Dongmei
Your losses will be paid back slowly
I really can't help this
How can there be no way
According to the law, the mountain master can only be released if he doesn't pursue it
I put that mountain yesterday
Gave it to my brother-in-law Shen Que
You have to save her
Gotta go find him
It's okay
It seems that Soo Soo's family
Still no repentance at all
It looks good, Xiu Xiu, don't move
Miscombed
Soo Soo
No matter what
As long as everyone is together
Days will always get better
It's just bitter for Dongmei
I put that mountain yesterday
Gave it to my brother-in-law Shen Que
You have to save her
Gotta go find him
From the Yao Mansion six months ago
There are as many as seven houses that harbor night walkers
It's hard to catch someone alive this time
Give up two little bosses of the Night Walkers
Two brothers Shen Tu Long Shen Tu Hu
Yao Xiaozhi said that night walkers were loyal to the Queen Mother
Does the general think there's something wrong
By the power of the Queen Mother alone
Can cultivate so many night walkers
The general is suspicious of the prime minister
Your Majesty has just ascended the throne and the situation is unstable
There is no ironclad evidence and complete certainty
Do not act rashly
The subordinates understand
General, there's something else
Qin Sizhe gave it to you two days ago
All right
You don't have to tell me about him
Shen
General Shen
What did you call me
What do you want from me
I would like to ask you to release the winter plum
She broke the law
Why should I let her go
I know that by law
I have to pay back the mountain master a thousand taels of silver
But Dongmei is weak
I'm afraid she won't stand it
Can you just let her out first
I'll pay back the money slowly
What do you have to do with me
I hope the general will remember the past affection
What kind of relationship was there between you and me
Then you and Dongmei are old acquaintances
The law does not tolerate mercy
Jiang Song
Don't think you came over to pretend to be pitiful
I'm gonna break the rules for you
But I can only find you
You can ask the government
Find the mountain master
Why did you come to me
But aren't you the mountain
Aren't you
Because I used to like you
You chose to leave
You and I are strangers
You should have heard that too
I'm getting married soon
Or do you want to come and be my concubine
Forget it
I'm not like you
Can't learn to go all day and night
Shen Que
You know this guy
Not important
Is she that Jiang Song
I've seen a lot of women like you
Red eyes with tears
Inspire a man's affection
Talk about yourself
In fact, everything depends on men
Qin Niangzi
Please watch your words
Don't call me lady
I'm a soldier
I'm not like women like you
I immediately cut my knife
Pleasant battlefield
Unlike you guys
I starved myself out of human shape for my small waist
Affectionate
Squirm
Qin Niangzi
Women in this world
Not everyone is as lucky as you
What kind of life do they lead
They didn't choose it
Why be so harsh
Whether it's free and easy
Wen Jing Nei Xiu
Sentimental or even aggressive and jealous
Who rules what a woman should be like
I don't think there's any difference
Say so much
Have you never leaned on a man
I leaned over
Not only did I lean over
If necessary in the future
I will still rely on
Well, that's all right
Haven't you leaned
Don't you rely on the help of your comrades when you kill the enemy on the battlefield
I'm not like you
I don't see any difference
People should help each other
It doesn't matter whether he's a man or a woman
There are not many roads left for us in this world
It's a fool if you don't go there
Tooth sharp mouth
Let's go
Be quick for a moment
Where can I find a thousand taels
Come over
Say things
The end of the world is coming
You're still in the mood to save a little character
So what
As long as life goes on
I wouldn't give up every moment
I have a way to rescue Dongmei effortlessly
Do you want to try
What's the way
Your hands
Isn't there a novel that Jiang Jiaojiao left you
Apply for tomorrow
Qin Sizhe will tie Jiang Jiaojiao at Guanyin Bridge
Shen Tu Long given to the black market
Listen to me
Old rules
Someone who wants to fight me
Lost
Compensate me for such a big piece of gold
Won
The gold is yours
This meat ticket
It's yours too
The Shentu brothers used the tied meat tickets as bait
Let others challenge
Victory in many battles
I don't know how much money I won
Master Chu, are you interested
Chu is not a troubled person
Today's meat ticket is a good treasure
Look at it
Such a pretty little beauty
Why is there no one to save me
I'll do it
OK OK
Who is this Chu Muzhi?
The other suitor of the heroine
Heir to the world's number one money house
look
How nice it is to be Jiang Jiaojiao
How do I do this
Go to Guanyin Bridge and wait
Everything will naturally go as the story is written
Do you have any other options
One thousand taels
You've never seen so much money in your life, have you
Since Shen Que and Cui You'an can't rely on it
It's hard to have a new backer
Don't catch it quickly
Didn't you just say it's not shameful to rely on men
What are you still hesitating
Will that Qin Sizhe really show up
Isn't this the bitch