♪You're my gentle fixation♪
♪Dancing around each other♪
♪To a give-and-take melody♪
♪Can't turn away from all this now♪
♪There is no end to this love♪
♪A test of heart to heart♪
♪Together, we become complete♪
♪You move forward, I look back♪
♪How many times
have I let go in the moment?♪
♪Torn between nostalgia
and knowing you're the one♪
=My Boyfriend=
=Episode 17=
(You're the only family I have)
Dad, are you sure about this?
If we get caught, we'll...
So what if we get caught?
What do you think we still have to lose?
I'm just worried about Yi Ning's temper.
What if she refuses?
I don't believe she'd risk her life.
When the time comes, move quickly.
You hear me?
Got it.
Boss!
When is the person
we're waiting for getting here?
What's the rush? Be patient.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Someone's coming.
Shen Qianze?
Whatever, if we
can't get Yi Ning, he'll do.
Get him!
Move!
That way.
Where'd you find these guys?
Qian Family Village.
Mr. Lei, I think he's waking up.
It's you.
Looks like you weren't beaten senseless.
Shen Qianze.
I'll give you a chance.
Be my man.
You'll cook for me, do my laundry...
- Forget it, keep dreaming.
- That way, I could...
Tie him up!
Stop wasting time talking to him.
Shen Qianze, you'd better behave.
As long as Yi Ning
brings the share transfer agreement,
I'll let you go.
Like Yi Ning would actually come here.
(I'll have to save myself)
Don't be naive.
Yi Ning would trade Yi Yuan to save me?
Would you trade Yi Yuan
for Jiang Xinlian?
I...
Stop trying to drive a wedge between us!
My parents truly love each other!
Tie him up!
But not Yi Ning and me.
I'm just her contract husband.
The only thing
she cares about is Yi Yuan.
There's no way she'd come here!
Then I'll make the whole world see
that the CEO of Yi Yuan
is someone who sees lives as worthless.
You think she hasn't considered that?
Qian Lei, your perfect plan just failed.
If I were you,
I'd think carefully
about working with me.
I might actually help you.
Dad, don't fall for it.
Guys who look good like him
are the best liars.
Still trying to fool me?
Qian Lei, don't forget
where you are right now.
You're nothing but a stray dog.
You've got no other choice
but to trust me.
Shut up!
Qian Lei!
Let him go!
I'm here.
(She actually came.)
(Why?)
Where's the stuff?
- Ning, don't worry about me.
- Don't move!
- Get out of here!
(Share Transfer Agreement)
Go!
You'd better not try anything funny.
Don't worry about me, Ning.
Dad, it's real.
Yi Ning.
Didn't expect you to be different
from that money-hungry woman Yi An.
You're actually someone loyal and kind.
You got what you wanted.
Can I have Shen Qianze back now?
Cancel the lawsuit first.
Release him first!
Tie him up!
No! Don't get worked up.
Stop trying to bargain with me.
Hello, Ms. Yi?
Secretary Liu, we're
dropping the charges. Cancel everything.
That's more like it.
Now can you let him go?
You're seriously letting him go?
Dad, someone's coming.
We've got what we wanted.
Let's just get out of here.
I'll double your pay!
- Hit him!
Boss, what do we do?
Run!
Ze!
Stop! Don't run!
Stop!
Ze!
Are you okay?
Ze...
Don't scare me.
Someone help! Somebody!
Don't move. I don't want to hurt you.
Are you okay?
It's fake.
Ning. There's something
I've been meaning to ask.
Why did you come that day?
You knew it was a trap.
I knew it was a trap.
But you were the bait,
how could I not go?
But now Yi Yuan is in Qian Lei's hands.
Even if I lost Yi Yuan,
I could win it back.
But I can't lose you.
If anything had happened to you,
then I...
I wouldn't have any family left.
♪Love is silence♪
♪Love is helplessness♪
♪Love is a pair of eyes
gazing at the stars♪
(Ning, thank you.)
So, what are you planning
to treat me to today?
That depends on how well he performs.
I'm already full
just watching you two being lovey-dovey.
Ning.
Shen Qianze's got pretty good taste.
Of course he does.
Why else do you think I chose him?
Do you smell something kind of weird?
No, nothing.
Everything about this place is great
except for one thing.
This whole place stinks
of cheesy romance.
Ugh, stop it.
Ning, come on, sit here.
Are you hungry?
Wait, maybe you two
should flirt a bit longer.
I'll see myself out.
Please sit.
You said last time
you wanted scallion oil chicken rice.
I've been practicing it
these past few days.
I'll make it for you later.
Really?
Thank you, Ze.
Can you add two more dishes?
I also invited Mr. Su.
Ze?
You're the man, brother-in-law.
Ning
has never called anyone's name
in such a sweet tone before.
Alright, I'll get back to work.
Wow, I can't believe it.
Back then,
you were like an AI programmed for work.
No emotions at all.
But now, look at you. Crazy in love,
all clingy and affectionate.
What? A strong woman can't fall in love?
I'm happy for you.
You've finally become
a little more human.
Was I really that bad before?
Only I could put up with you, okay?
You used to...
What are you two
chatting about, so happily?
Mr. Su.
Fengyue.
- Hello.
Mr. Su, about what happened earlier,
I haven't had a chance to thank you.
No need.
By the way, everything's okay
with Yi Yuan now, right?
All good.
Thanks for helping me
find someone back then,
and for saving the recording.
I believe
the police are already
following legal procedure.
The agreement
I gave Qian Lei won't be valid.
Weren't you afraid
the plan would backfire,
and Yi Yuan would really
end up in his hands?
Sometimes you have to take a gamble.
Right?
I'll leave you two to talk.
I'm going to check on Ze.
So you planned all of this?
I really thought
you were just crazy in love.
I love him,
but that doesn't mean
I'd do something stupid.
Alright, you're always right.
Uncle...
Mr. Su is here.
You staged that kidnapping stunt
without telling me first?
Even if it worked, it was way too risky.
- It wasn't an act.
- You...
What?
I never imagined
Yi Ning would trade the company for me.
How could I plan for that?
But it does prove you've got her
in the palm of your hand.
Ze.
You could totally
use her love for you to control her
and take Yi Yuan.
Uncle... I don't really
want revenge anymore.
What do you mean?
She said I'm her family.
And because of her, I slowly remembered
what it feels like to be cared for.
Right now, I want to love her
more than I want to hate her.
But have you thought about this?
Your relationship
was built on a lie from the beginning.
If she finds out
you were lying to her from day one,
do you think she'll still love you?
I...
We've come this far, Ze.
Don't do something you'll regret.
Don't worry.
If you can't bring yourself to do it,
I'll do it for you.
What do you mean, you...
Cheers.
Yue, try this.
As a female celebrity,
- I guess I'm only allowed to eat vegetables, right?
- Ms. Yi...
- Do you know...
- Ning.
What's wrong?
My head hurts a little.
Is it bad?
Sorry.
Maybe we should call it a night.
No worries, go ahead.
Health comes first.
Let's go.
Be careful on the way.
Should we keep eating?
Mr. Wen.
Mr. Shen is back.
Did we have a guest today?
Yes.
Chairman Su of Shangsu Group
came to visit Ms. Ning.
So he was like that even as a kid.
Ze, you're here. What's wrong?
Why is Mr. Su here?
(Next Episode)
She's just a woman, that's all.
You've got Yi Yuan in your hands.
What's there to worry about?
Ze.
It's time to reel it in.
Please answer our questions.
Please say something.
Give us a response.
- Ms. Yi.
Give us an explanation.
♪I remember your hands♪
♪They were always so gentle♪
♪I just wanted
to hold your hands in mine♪
♪What we had may be old♪
♪But this longing still feels fresh♪
♪How do I even ask you to stay?♪
♪What about the laughter
we once shared?♪
♪How long has it been
since we first met?♪
♪Somehow, the blue sky
has turned gray again♪
♪This foolish self-deception♪
♪How can excuses ever mend the pain?♪
♪Love is silence♪
♪Love is helplessness♪
♪Love is a pair of eyes
gazing at the stars♪
♪Quietly shining for you♪
♪Love is silence♪
♪Love is holding on♪
♪Even if I still cling
to a senseless hope♪