♪You're my gentle fixation♪
♪Dancing around each other♪
♪To a give-and-take melody♪
♪Can't turn away from all this now♪
♪There is no end to this love♪
♪A test of heart to heart♪
♪Together, we become complete♪
♪You move forward, I look back♪
♪How many times
have I let go in the moment?♪
♪Torn between nostalgia
and knowing you're the one♪
=My Boyfriend=
=Episode 9=
(To Cool Down in Hot Weather)
- Leave the Group, Yi Ning!
- What's happening?
A layoff?
I've never mentioned that.
Leave Yi Yuan Group, Yi Ning!
- It must be Qian Lei again.
- Ning.
You should stay away
from the office today.
No way. Avoiding from the problem
isn't going to solve it.
But this is too dangerous.
I'll come with you.
What's good about Guilinggao?
We're not buying it.
Let's get this instead.
Sure.
This is it.
(Young consumers,
milk, coffee, Guilinggao)
(Milk, coffee, Guilinggao, milk tea)
Come, I'll take you to a place.
Here.
Please have this dessert
before the meal, Ms. Yi.
I've never liked
our Guilinggao.
It's too bitter.
But it cools you down.
Also, it doesn't contain additives.
Yet, people aren't buying it
because it doesn't taste good.
No one cares about how good it is.
It will be taken off the shelf
eventually.
Actually, there are those who need it.
Look.
No one was buying our Guilinggao
at the supermarket.
I never thought
it'd be well received here.
They are different consumer groups.
Customers at the supermarket
not only care
about its cooling function,
but they also want it to have
an innovative flavor and packaging.
So, instead of getting rid of it,
I should market it in two different forms.
That's right. You're smart, Ms. Yi.
If so, I should introduce
an affordable, classic version
and an exclusive one
with an innovative design.
How brilliant of you.
(Guilinggao)
Eat first. You can continue later.
No, I can wait no more.
I need to finalize the new product line
soonest possible.
How about this?
Tell me your ideas. I'll do the typing.
Shall we eat first?
Sure.
Thank you for today.
You showed me what I never came across.
Like I said,
I will be your left-hand man.
But I want you to be my...
Your hubby.
Well, I only shell prawns
for you alone.
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Let's go check it out.
You've approached Li
and the others, haven't you?
Of course.
We must fight Yi Ning until the end
and force her leave Yi Yuan.
I've told Secretary Liu to arrange
the execution of the new product line.
So you may stay.
We're sorry, Ms. Yi.
We were fooled
into believing that you were here
to wreak havoc.
Surprisingly, not only did you
not make us pay for causing a scene,
but you've also considered
our benefits.
You were right.
I shouldn't have focused
on temporarily benefits
by compromising
our camaraderie and goal.
You are certainly a loyal person.
As expected of the successor
chosen by Yi.
- Yes.
- Indeed.
Mr. Li.
Regarding the planning of our product,
let's about it.
Sure.
What is this?
This way, please.
I don't know either.
It was her, Ms. Yi.
She was fanning the flames
in an attempt to drive you out of Yi Yuan.
Stop talking nonsense, I didn't do that!
- It was you!
- You said that!
It was you!
Mr. Qian...
Jiang Wenwen.
Just speak your mind.
You don't have to pull such petty,
dirty tricks behind my back.
It... It's all a misunderstanding.
I thought Mr. Li and the others
would be dismissed.
Did I mention about a layoff?
- No... No.
- Not at all.
You never said so.
I...
Jiang Wenwen, head home for a rest
if you're not feeling well.
You are no longer needed here.
I'm all right.
I just felt dizzy.
I'm going back to work.
Don't just stand there, get to work.
Get back to work.
- Let's go.
- Quick, let's go.
Mr. Li.
I'm counting on you all.
No problem.
Rest assured, Ms. Yi.
Boss.
Why are we using
this ready-made Guilinggao
as dessert now?
I remember you ever said
we only used fresh ingredients,
not these
cultivated raw materials.
This Yi Yuan Guilinggao
doesn't contain additives.
It's good enough.
Are you talking about the Guilinggao
or its owner?
If you're too free,
go clean the cups again.
Look at you.
You are glowing.
Don't tell me you're being serious?
Have you fallen in love
with Yi Ning for real?
Boss, just a heads up.
It's not going to work for you two.
I know.
Ri'an. Try this.
I've got it especially for you.
It's your favorite
Pre-Qingming Longjing tea.
How kind of you.
Just say it. How can I help?
Well,
I'm planning to introduce
a brand new high-end gift box
with our existing Guilinggao model.
I'm talking
about a premium Chinese style branding.
Yet, regarding its design,
I need your help as you're a master
of traditional Chinese painting.
Sure.
But I have a request.
Well,
I can give you whatever you want.
Let me have half of your office.
That way, if we ever run into an issue,
we can communicate with one another directly.
That's it?
Yes.
It's no big deal.
Great!
(Yi Yuan Guilinggao)
Ning.
Check this out.
What do you think?
It's really nice.
Pretty good.
(Next Episode)
If you're not mad, that means
you're jealous.
Now that I own Yi Yuan,
I can give you
whatever you want.
♪I remember your hands♪
♪They were always so gentle♪
♪I just wanted
to hold your hands in mine♪
♪What we had may be old♪
♪But this longing still feels fresh♪
♪How do I even ask you to stay?♪
♪What about the laughter
we once shared?♪
♪How long has it been
since we first met?♪
♪Somehow, the blue sky
has turned gray again♪
♪This foolish self-deception♪
♪How can excuses ever mend the pain?♪
♪Love is silence♪
♪Love is helplessness♪
♪Love is a pair of eyes
gazing at the stars♪
♪Quietly shining for you♪
♪Love is silence♪
♪Love is holding on♪
♪Even if I still cling
to a senseless hope♪