- Kopi.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
It smells great.
Let's go give it a try.
You know we'll be late for class, right?
It'll only take a minute.
Alright?
Okay. Okay.
Two cups of kopi, please.
Coming up.
They have the same type of coffee your dad used to serve.
But this one is weird.
Where are all the customers?
Come on.
I want me some kopi.
We'll be late for class.
It's only a minute or two.
- Doing this is good, right?
- Yes.
Hello.
(Sale for business)
(Sale for business, only some people.)
Phu...
I'm already exhausted from running.
What are we doing here?
I'm supposed to present my project.
Pity my poor body, won't you?
I still need to go home to shower.
Oh?
If you came to me, you would've opened it by now.
Instead you went to Joe and his potty mouth.
Phu!
Come on.
The middle lane is free.
Quickly!
Come on!
Who are you?
Who are these people?
Hi!
Hello!
I must apologize for my friend's behavior the other day.
Yes.
He's off his meds.
We've taken him to many psychiatrists.
Do you remember me?
I used to order a sweet, rich kopi from you.
Daddy, who are these people?
I used to be your father's regular way before you were even born.
Does that make you important somehow?
I'm beginning to understand Joe now.
No, no...
I'm just saying I used to be a regular.
Oh, I remember now...
You were looking to buy the place, right?
Yes, that's right.
You're too late.
What happened?
Someone has already made an offer.
She's even paid the deposit.
What?
It's the mum of Patrick's friend from school.
She is going to make it a nail salon.
Patrick...
Can you tell me who she is?
I've got to go now.
Phu...
If you like it so much, just come here more often.
Are you saying I need my nails done, Nan?
Nan, wait for me please.
Why were you MIA last night?
What about my celeb suggestions?
I need to book them in advance, you know?
Nan...
Does Plan B work?
Nan Fah...
Why haven't you gotten the team to look into the celebs' availability?
We can't present the list to Ken
without knowing their availability and charges.
What the hell are you doing?
You've been working here for years.
Do I have to re-teach you everything?
Everybody, stop!
Listen to me.
Please wait until the meeting.
Nan, wait.
Here we go with the show again.
Who does he think he is?
Why does he have no respect for me?
I don't think it's funny.
Not funny at all.
You won't pass!!
Nah Fah.
Ken will see to that.
Hey!
Nah!
You okay?
I'm okay.
But I'm not.
This is a group chat.
Oops!!!
First of all,
I'd like to inform you
that I have had our Legal team speak to Jackie's management.
I have also spoken to him personally.
Wow! So that ended well?
It did, but what about us?
We've still got to find a presenter fast
to ensure our marketing plan can still go ahead.
The billboard we've rented
must also be ready on time.
What?
In 3 weeks?
Don't worry about that, Ken.
I've tasked Nan Fah to come up with a plan.
Go ahead, Nan Fah.
Have you got any interesting celebs?
I've checked.
All the best ones are fully booked,
and I don't want to use a presenter who has worked with other brands.
I've looked into options that are more suitable than a celebrity presenter.
Unfortunately, I feel that limiting ourselves to
such individuals is holding us back,
though I do have an idea.
Future Biotechnology for Men's Skin
Our mission is to build understanding for our products among our target demographic,
which is men over 30.
We need to communicate to them
that we use highly potent stem cell extracts.
Our biotechnology,
which we've researched for more than 5 years,
maintains the properties of these extracts,
nourishing and repairing skin
at a cellular level.
They can provide solutions for a range of skincare problems.
Our rejuvenating products are easy to use
and suitable for the lifestyle of modern men.
This is why our next presenter
should be...
a regular man.
However, this ordinary man
places great importance on his skincare routine.
He is also interesting.
All of this says choosing Devonte
is choosing the best for yourself.
Fantastic, Nan!
What are you talking about, Nan?
Can't you see that Ken isn't on board.
Our brand represents the highest technological standards
and expensive ingredients that aren't typically available in Thailand.
How can our presenter be a regular man?
It's not suitable.
Right, Ken?
Man...
Look at Nan Fah. He's presenting right now.
Just look.
Keep looking.
It's free.
Okay.
My lips are dry.
Got some lip balm?
I've got some Tiger Balm.
I think his idea is cool.
Our products resonate with people who care about quality
and who select the best products available.
If they like something,
they'll stick with it forever.
I like how you are thinking.
An ordinary man
with extraordinary taste.
But the challenge will be
to find a presenter who fits the bill.
Let me take responsibility for that.
Let me help, too.
We'll get it done.
I'll help as well.
I think I know just where to find him.
Don't forget the deadline.
Let me head this project.
I've got the skills for the job.
- How did you like my presentation?
- Excellent!
You've got game.
Not telling anyone what you were up to.
Presenting by yourself and taking all the glory.
Well, when I was working on it last night,
I didn't see you volunteering to help.
Pathetic.
Forget about him.
You've done well.
I was wondering why you went MIA last night.
Let's celebrate tonight.
I want a cold drink.
Today?
I can't.
I've got something to do.
You've forgotten me now you've got that new friend.
It's not like that...
Then what is it?
Alright... If you're free,
come and help with something.
With what exactly?
What are you doing here?
Picking up your kid?
Trust me.
Ahem!
What's up, old man?
I'm not that old.
I've bought you some snacks.
No, thank you! I'm trying to lose weight.
What game are you playing?
None of yours.
I can help you pay for items in the game.
Special ones.
Deal?
What do you want from me?
Alright. Fine.
I want to know the lady who is buying your father's old café.
Introduce me to her, will you?
A million.
It'll cost you a million.
A million!
That's a bit much, fatty!
Hey! Don't bully a little kid.
I'm sorry.
That's still a bit much.
No money, no talk.
Ooh!
Do you like her?
Quit it.
Fair enough.
Oh!
Look at those boys staring at her.
You can't compete with them, can you?
So...
Do you like her or not?
If you do, you should let her know.
Are you crazy?
I can't.
Do you always chicken out in front of the ladies?
I agree.
If you like her, you should tell her.
I know that from experience.
Hey!
Who have you secretly fancied?
I don't mean it like that.
I mean...
It's important.
If I didn't tell someone that I liked them,
I'd regret it for life.
Who's studying advertising?
Me, me, me!
Hey!
We've gone past your house!
Eat those vegetables.
They're good for you.
Nathi, give me your plate.
How is school these days?
Work hard! You'll graduate soon enough.
And you, Namnuea?
No, thank you.
Huh? Why?
There's no way he'll let me study advertising.
He thinks
if you study medicine, you become a doctor.
So, if he asks me what I'll do with an advertising degree,
what am I going to tell him?
Just talk to him like we practiced.
He won't understand.
My brother and sister are in medical school.
I'm the black sheep of the family.
If I don't get in,
he'll have me take over the family's pharmacy.
This is your last chance.
If you don't tell him, your chances are 0.
If you tell him,
there's at least a chance.
Are you going to give up on your dream
and just take over the pharmacy?
It's up to you.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can!
Hi, Mum! Hi, Dad!
What does your story have to do with this?
It's all the same.
Here!
Take this chocolate over to her.
Everyone likes chocolate.
It makes everyone happy.
Don't you want to see her smile?
Come on. Take all of this.
I can't. Who's going to smile at a fatty like me?
You won't know if you don't try.
If you don't try, your chances are 0.
But if you do, who knows what could happen?
Aah!
Minnie!
Ouch!
You fat little...
Oops!
Hey!
Patrick, are you okay?
You're Patrick, right?
Thank you.
And you?
I think it's broken.
Gie Gie!
What are you up to?
Phupha!
Is Nan Fah home?
He's not answering my calls.
Didn't he go into work?
Yes,
but when he finished the presentation
he left to go somewhere with Party.
Those two are like twins.
They're always together.
Party...
The one who comes here to work with Nan Fah?
Are they very close?
Very close.
I forgot the keycard,
so I can't take all this to Nan's room.
Could you let me in?
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
Does Nan Fah usually give his passcode
to his colleagues?
Just me and Party.
He needs me to pick up things all the time.
Party, he's mostly here to party.
Thank you so much.
Oliang!
Do you mind if I play with Oliang a little?
Oliang.
Ouch!
I had to practically beg Dad
to get her to come see us.
You owe me a pizza for this.
No problem.
Make it count.
Don't waste time.
Jiab?
That's right.
Hello!
Hi!
Say what you've got to say.
I've only got 30 minutes.
I'll get straight to the point.
Ok.
This used to be our regular coffee shop
when we were at university.
Now that it's up for grab,
my friend would very much like to buy it.
Er...
It's an amazing location.
I am planning on opening a nail salon.
Jiab, here's why.
My friend's dad had a coffee shop in Chiang Mai.
When his dad died of heart disease,
they had to close it down.
When we got to university,
we came across this place.
The coffee was just like what we used to drink.
It made my friend happy.
The aroma and taste
made him feel like
he was with his father again.
I sympathize with you,
but I've already paid a deposit
and started planning.
More importantly...
I promised my mum
before she passed away that I'd open
a nail salon of my own to make her proud.
On her death bed she told me
it had to be at a location exactly like this.
Her story is as heartbreaking as yours.
You've got so many fish.
How many?
Oh, you've got coffee, too.
Do you like coffee?
Yes, I do.
And books?
Correct.
Me too.
My favorites are the prayer books.
Look at all these plants.
It feels like a forest!
What's this picture?
Never forget.
What does that mean?
Nothing.
I just wrote it as a joke when we were at uni.
It's lovely.
Put it out here.
Why would you hide it away?
Your room is so vibrant.
It's nothing like Nan's room.
His room is soulless.
What's that?
I'll read your fortune for free.
Pick one.
Really?
Place it here.
Don't look so confused.
Wheel of Fortune.
This could mean an event is about to occur
over which you have no control.
Expect the unexpected.
In a good or bad way?
It could be either.
That's all I know.
Is something bothering you?
It's nothing.
Anyway, do you like coffee?
I'm a bit of a coffee addict, to be honest.
That's why I've got my own cup.
Wow!
I thought it was some other kind of juice.
Oh, no, no, no!
Just kidding.
Let me make you some coffee.
Are you going to roofie me?
I'm not that kind of girl.
In that case, you'd better go.
I'm kidding...
- Is this your coffeemaker?
- Oh, yes!
It's so cool.
I've never seen anything like it.
They call this a syphon.
It's like a cross between a Mokka pot and a drip.
The result is neither too intense, nor too weak.
These beans are from my Granny's farm in Chiang Mai.
You're a coffee expert.
You even have your own farm.
You should open your own coffee shop.
That's the dream,
but I've run into an obstacle.
Expect the unexpected.
That's what the card has foretold.
But will it be good or bad?
It must be something good.
Smell that.
Careful. It's hot.
It smells amazing.
Nah!
Joe!
The table's inside.
I'll be there in a minute.
Ok.
Is that your friend?
He's quite something.
That's Joe, the owner.
If I'd known I'd get hurt helping you,
I'd have stayed home drinking by myself.
That's why I owe you a drink.
Go all out!
It's my way of paying you back.
Here we are, same as before.
Ouch!
Hey!
Sorry!
I didn't see you there.
Are you his new friend?
Enjoy!
He doesn't seem so cool anymore.
Can I punch him?
Calm down.
Here!
Have some more.
Have we come here because of him?
The more, the merrier!
You are doing a whole lot for him.
Does he know what's going on?
Of course not.
There's no need to tell him.
Alright.
Cheers!
He sat on my hand.
That very hurt.
You're such a drama queen. Is that better?
Is that better?
No?
How about now?
Party, you alright?
Okay. Keep drinking.
Pour. To the top!
Phu! Wait!
Come drink with us.
I told you I don't drink.
I'm going home soon.
I'm worried about Oliang.
What are you worried about?
Oliang's probably asleep already.
Stay here with us.
I'll go home with you later.
It's okay. I'll take you.
You?
Taking me?
Look at yourself?
You can't even take yourself home.
Call a cab.
Leave the car here.
I can drive.
I'm not drunk.
Yes, you are.
Okay, I'm off.
Bye.
Alright. Alright. We're all going.
The end.
And who are you going with?
Hold on tight.
Yes.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I said hold on.
You focus on driving!
I'm about to fall off.
I said hold tight.
Ah...
Go, go, go!
You're such a burden.
Turn right.
Right to what? It's a wall.
Turn left.
We are here.
Let me do it.
It's my room.
But that's my cat.
Wait a moment.
Oliang!
Here is your cat.
Oliang,
I've missed you so much.
I haven't seen you in so long.
Oliang, over here!
Oliang!
Hey!
About your coffee shop.
Forget it.
If I can't have that location,
I'll probably just sell my coffee beans instead.
"Moo" (Coffee shop owner)
Nan!
Moo, the coffee shop owner is calling.
Answer him!
Hello?
Hi.
My first buyer has dropped out
and is asking for her deposit back.
Are you still interested?
If you are still interested,
you can come in and sign the contract tomorrow.
Of course!
I'm interested.
I'm very interested.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Thank you!
Nan!
I got the place!
(Previously)
Hey!
I need a piss.
Just go.
I'm scared. It's... it's...
It's what?
There's something there.
Doesn't it seem strange to you
that he's kept the shop shut all this time
despite its excellent location?
Lately things have randomly fallen.
What the hell!
Patrick!
Where did he go?
I don't know.
What the hell!
The back storage room.
What the hell?
Dad told me not to go in there.
I've seen it.
Just a body.
No head.
What is it,
Mum? Okay.
My Mum doesn't want me to have this anymore.
The location and the feng shi are off.
I'm in a hurry.
Would you still like to buy it?
I can speak with the owner.
I'll clear things regarding the deposit.
Good luck.
I've got to go.
Something's come up.
That was great!
Are you ready, Mr. President?
I am.
Okay.
1, 2, 3... Yay!
It's official now.
What's that smile for?
I can't tell if you're happy or drunk?
You'll be seeing this smile every day from now on.
Here's your paperwork, Mr. President (in Korean).
Thank you (in Japanese).
I said that in Korean.
I'm going against the mainstream.
One sec...
Yeah, yeah.
I'm going in.
Alright.
What's up, Gie Gie?
Nan Fah, Man is on my case.
He doesn't think we've found a presenter.
So he wants us to send him photos.
Okay.
I'll be quick.
Please let the presentation go well today.
Nan!
Ken will be here for the meeting in 5 minutes.
Yeah.
Wait!
Where did you put the product samples?
What product samples?
I'm so sorry.
I'd typed the message but never hit send.
Yesterday the factory sent us samples.
I put them in your room.
Ken wants to see them today.
I'm so sorry.
We're so screwed.
I'm sorry.
What are we going to do?
He's not picking up.
Ahem!
Do you need a lozenge?
Yeah, I'll have two pills, please.
Stop messing around.
Where are the samples?
Gie Gie, you said Nan Fah had them, right?
Er...
I... I...
I didn't bring them with me.
What?
It's unprofessional to forget the samples for your presentation.
We are discussing the presenter today,
but the products are also important?
We need to see them with the talent.
You've really messed up this time.
Oh my god!
Hey! Oh why!
What are we going to do?
Come on, tell me!
I first talk about the presenter.
The products will come in good time.
Goodness me, I am beyond tense,
and you are making it worse.
I'll put product images up in the background.
You'll be able to see what we're trying to do.
It doesn't feel the same.
Don't make excuses for each other.
How can you mess this up?
It's so simple.
How many years have you been doing this?
Don't stand to apologize,
I've had enough.
I won't accept any apology.
Good morning, Ken!
Please have a seat.
Okay. I'd like to present our timeline.
Don't bother.
Let's get on with the presenter issue.
Phu, I need your help.
I forgot the product samples in my room.
Can you bring them here?
I'll share the location.
The Gen Y target audience of males over 30
are independent,
knows the value of treating themselves,
and have some worldly experience.
I believe that it's best that we
don't use a known public figure for this campaign.
Nan Fah, are you kidding me right now?
You're wasting Ken's time.
Quiet for a moment, Man.
Please finish what you were saying.
Here are the candidates.
First one: Ohm,
a national team swimmer.
Hello?
Are you at the restaurant already?
Hainanese chicken on rice with no chicken.
Next up is Non,
- a chef specializing in French cuisine.
- A delivery?
Yes, just leave it in front of the house.
Someone will get it later.
- and finally, Kitti, a...
- Omakase, right?
Oh, yes, please,
that'd be lovely.
Ok, bye bye.
Each of these men have an interesting lifestyle,
and a powerful gaze.
They also understand the value of living.
They make good choices.
When they find something they love
they are ready to go all in for it
without changing their mind.
I feel like it's missing a certain x factor.
If that's what you're after, allow me to...
Man, have a seat please.
Nan Fah, continue.
Ken...
Is there someone you feel would be suitable for our brand?
What are your thoughts?
Who do you think is the best?
Excuse me.
I'm here to see Nan Fah.
You're looking for Nan Fah?
He is in the board room.
He's in an actual meeting right now.
This one. Non.
As a chef, he is particular about his ingredients.
He's also got those playful eyes.
I think he is the one.
I think he can represent our brand well.
But not perfect.
To be honest,
I don't like any of them.
But if we delay our choice any longer,
we won't make the presenter reveal date.
I think we need to make a decision.
We can't delay the launch.
Losing the billboard slot would cost us a fortune.
Don't you get it?
I've brought something for Nan Fah.
The board room is downstairs.
Thank you.
He's so handsome!
I understand the difficulties involved,
but we can't just choose anyone.
It has to be someone who aligns with our values.
They have to look youthful
for someone around the age of 30.
Excuse me.
Is this what you wanted?
Him!
It's so late.
Where have you been?
Were you out studying or horsing around?
How was it?
Did you do it?
I didn't.
Nan!
Oh, Phupha!
Are you hungry?
Come join us for dinner.
Let's grab him a bowl.
No, thank you.
I've got to speak to you, Uncle.
If you're here about him studying advertising,
the answer is no.
It's a waste of money.
If he can't get into medical school,
he can work in the pharmacy.
Uncle...
He can't live your dreams for you.
Please don't rob him of his.
It may not be what you want,
but I know it will lead him to success.
I'll study with Nan Fah.
I promise that I'll keep a close eye on him
and keep him on the right track.
Please, I beg you to let Nan Fah make you proud,
just like his siblings have done.
Honey...