Juliet, my darling,
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
Phu... are you in there?
We'll enter the darkness together, just as we promised.
Phu!
In the darkest hours, you kept your promise to stay by my side.
You kept your promise to stay by my side.
Phu!
Thank you.
Hmm, I'm going home now.
Ok.
Hang on a moment.
Um...
Hello.
Are you Nan Fah's friend?
Yes.
Not just any friend.
They're very close.
They're extremely good friends.
They live in the same condo complex, opposite each other.
Um...
This is my boss.
Goodness me, have you any manners at all?
We're in the middle of a meeting
and you just waltz in here like it's nothing.
I'd like to apologize to you all.
I thought Nan Fah needed this urgently,
so I just rushed in.
Ok, I'll go now.
Goodbye.
I'll be off.
Hmm, ok, thanks again.
This is unacceptable, Nan.
We can't just let anyone into the offices.
Right, Ken?
Your friend is very interesting.
I'm better than him.
Right, Gie Gie?
Ken, sir.
I hope I'm not overstepping my boundaries here
but I saw how you were looking at him.
I know you were thinking the same as me
when Phupa walked in just now.
What an aura he had!
He has pet fish,
he's a musician,
he has his own coffee plantation
and, most importantly,
he makes the best drip coffee I've ever tasted!
That's quite enough, Gie Gie.
Deary me,
when did you find out all that about him?
This is what I do!
In fact, I've got something to ask you, Nan,
how the hell did you overlook Phupa?
I thought you were best friends.
He doesn't seem so special to me.
I can't see him making it big.
His face is boring and expressionless.
Is this him?
He's blowing up on social media.
People are sharing his stuff everywhere.
That's him all right!
Look at this, Ken.
This shows that Gie Gie and I aren't making this up.
That's right.
Nan Fah.
Yes?
How would you feel about us
casting your friend for our project?
Um... I...
No problem at all.
If that's what you would like,
we'll make it happen.
Answer him,
otherwise we'll see his angry side.
Not a problem, sir.
I'll have a chat with him.
Hmm.
He looked great.
Ken saw what a great fit he'd be for us.
He has an aura about him.
Let me help.
Hmm.
Where do you want it?
Over there.
Put it down.
I can't believe it. You're famous!
May I ask: Do you have a manager yet?
I could manage you if you like.
A manager?
Yes.
What about your dad doing it?
Very funny, you idiot.
Hmm.
Phu... I want to thank you for today.
You're welcome... my burden.
It's good you said that actually,
I don't need to worry what you'll think anymore.
I'll be your personal burden for ever.
I'm already exhausted.
Oh, Phu.
You know that coffee shop next to my office?
They're looking for a bean supplier.
I took them some of your beans.
They're interested.
You should talk to them.
Really?
Really.
And they trust you of all people?
I work in marketing, you fool.
Don't you think I know how to present products?
What do you think,
that I just bumble through each day not knowing what I'm doing?
Exactly.
Whatever. Thank you for doing that.
Oh, Phu.
What would you have said about the coffee then?
It's like that, is it?
Yeah.
I'd tell them what was so good about the beans.
I'd say they were grown on a bountiful farm
and that every bean was of the utmost quality
because every bean had been allowed to grow
for the perfect amount of time before being harvested,
which is why they're so fragrant and flavorful.
Drinking this coffee makes you feel like you are in an orchard.
Phu...
What are you thinking about?
How did I overlook you for that role?
You know,
ever since we've known each other
and to this day
I've only just understood
that you are the one.
Phu...
Let me cast you as our presenter.
Oh, I get it...
This is why you contacted them about the coffee,
because you wanted me to be your presenter, right?
It's not like that.
They really are interested in your beans
but my boss is interested in you, too.
You know I'm not capable of doing that.
Don't you remember what I did
during that uni contest?
Phupa... are you ready?
I'm ready.
Ok... if everyone's ready,
these are our 5 finalists.
Give them a round of applause.
Next up is the part you've all been waiting for,
the talent showcase for the handsome young gentlemen
of the faculty.
Our first contestant is going to put on a show
known as a tragedy
from one of William Shakespeare's
most famous romantic plays:
Romeo and Juliet.
If you're all ready,
I'd like to welcome onto the stage
Phupa from the Faculty of Communication Arts.
Hang on a minute,
what the hell is he going to do up there?
Well, he's studying communication arts
so of course, he's going to put on a show.
A show?
He hasn't passed a single subject yet.
That's why he's up there now,
his lecturer said that if he can do this show,
he'll give him a pass on this subject.
Oh no.
OMG.
We've got to believe in him.
Phu!
You can do this!
You can do it!
Phupa! Phupa! Phupa! Phupa!
Oh, Juliet, my darling,
the grim reaper has taken your life,
but he couldn't take your beauty.
Love is... Hey!.
Love is... what was it?
Err... what was the line?
Hey!, Phu!
Oh, Juliet, my darling,
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath,
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
Forbidden love...
Phu!
Who is Phu?
Phu, are you in there?
will keep us together for ever.
Phu!
Hay!...
Are you OK?
Nan, I'm sorry...
Don't worry about it. It's a difficult line.
Phu...
Are you ok?
Take a deep breath.
Why do I always mess up when people are watching?
It's always the same.
You did it so well when we rehearsed together.
Hang on. Try this.
Phu... repeat after me
look ahead and say
Oh, Juliet, my darling
Say it! Juliet, my darling.
Oh, Juliet, my darling,
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
hath had no power yet upon my beauty.
Not my, you idiot...
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
Forbidden love... sit down.
Forbidden love
has brought us to the end.
Here I will remain.
Look up to the sky and open the bottle.
Will I set up my everlasting rest,
We shall enter the darkness together
just as we hath promised.
Together
until the bitter end.
Kiss...
Kiss me!
Really?
Yes!
Phu!!
What are you doing?
I meant a fake kiss, you idiot.
Ok, done.
Phu!
Joe
Phu's fainted.
What?
I'm so exhausted.
Phu.
Huh?
Thank you so much for your help up there.
Without you, we'd have gotten a beating from those senior students.
All that practice and you still needed me next to you.
I saw how well you knew those lines.
If it'd been you up there,
you'd have won.
This award
What?
should belong to you.
Put this sash on too
Here.
It's not that simple.
This belongs to both of us,
half each!
Hmm.
But this will be the last time...
The last time I will ask for something from you.
I know. Don't repeat yourself.
Ok? I promise.
You really promise
that you won't do it again?
Yeah.
You know I don't like it when there are crowds of people.
Is that because the only person you want around is me?
Hey! There's something on your crutch?
What?
Hey!
Why?
Yeah.
Hey, what are you doing?
Come on, say it.
If you don't say it, I'm leaving now.
You...
Yeah, yeah.
I give in.
I promise not to do it again.
What was that? I didn't hear you.
Ok?
Excellent. Come on.
Is that all?
Give me my crutch back.
Come and get it.
I'm coming, ok?
Now, give it back.
You idiot
I'm going.
Wait up!
I'll see you back at the room.
Hey!
Hey! Wait up.
Phu!
You Bastard.
You made the promise. Have you forgotten?
I have not.
But it's hardly the same thing.
You should find someone else.
I don't want to make a fool of myself.
And I don't want to mess things up at your job.
Hmm...
But they really are interested in you at the coffee shop.
Don't forget about tomorrow.
Hmm... thank you.
I'll be there tomorrow.
Granny's  calling. Hang on.
Hmm, do what you need to do.
Hi Granny... What are you up to?
Hello, Phupa!
I'm...
with my friends doing teenager stuff.
We're also drinking some of the craft beer you made.
You don't mind, do you?
Not at all, just don't drink too much.
Oh... do you want to keep it all to yourself?
I guess I won't be getting any at my own funeral.
No, no, I'm concerned.
Oh, Granny, how is the farm looking?
Not great, to be honest.
It's nothing like it was 4–5 years ago.
Oh, Granny...
You know that shop I mentioned?
Don't worry.
I've got a coffee shop now.
It'll have a little showroom
where we can display our products for the customers to try.
It'll be great.
My friend already talked to a potential customer earlier today.
I'll meet them tomorrow.
Oh a friend, who's that?
This guy.
Nan, come here.
Wow... Nan Fah!
I haven't seen you in ages!
Hello, Granny!
How are things?
Well... quite lonely.
It's boring without Phu here for company.
Me and the gang just look for stuff to do.
You must have missed  Phu terribly.
Phu's been in Melbourne for a decade, eh?
Hmm... yes... it's been extremely difficult.
Ok, I'll leave you two to chat.
I've got some work to get on with.
Hmm...
I'm going home now.
Hmm.
Hey!
Your secret almost slipped out there.
You still haven't told him about Melbourne, have you?
If he knew I was in Thailand all this time,
he'll be pissed off at me.
He'll want to know... why I did something like that.
Phupa, Nan Fah was looking all over for you.
He even came to the farm a few times.
Secrets are never good, you know.
You either tell him or he'll eventually find out.
Think about it.
I'll leave it with you then.
He's very busy right now,
but I'll find the right time and let him know.
And are you going to tell him everything?
I miss you, Granny! Sweet dreams... bye bye.
Take that! Hmm... ooh.
Ohh...
Yeah!
Take that...
Quickly!
Oh!
Follow him.
How was your chat with Phupa last night, Nan?
Do you need to ask?
His face tells it all.
Oh... I don't think you need to try and convince him.
People would kill for this opportunity.
Hmm... true.
If it were me, I wouldn't bother talking.
Hmm.
Gie Gie, hold this.
Play for me.
Quick! Just for a minute.
How do you play this again?
What about the presenter?
Have you found one yet? It's stressing me out.
I'm serious.
Oh, Ken, hello.
Hello.
Ken, sir.
You know my friend you wanted to cast?
Well, he...
Ah yes, I was just going to say,
there's no need to cast him anymore.
See, Ken has come to his senses.
Casting someone like Phupa would be a waste of time,
right?
Yes, a complete waste of time
because I've already decided on him being our presenter.
Yes.
How did you come to that realization without casting?
I've already casted him earlier today.
Have you?
Indeed.
Ok.
How... How can I help you?
Can... Can I help you with anything?
I'm a friend of Nan Fah.
I've brought some coffee beans.
Oh!
Khun Phupa.
Nan Fah has told me all about your coffee.
I wanted to try it for myself.
Please would you make me a cup to try?
It would be my pleasure.
May I come in?
Of course, the door is just there.
Can I use this?
Go for it.
May I try a cup?
Do you remember me?
We met in a meeting at my offices.
Oh... hmm...
I must apologize,
there were so many people around that day.
No problem at all.
Is this your coffee?
Yes, sir.
In that case, could you tell me what's so special about it?
About my coffee?
Yes...
These beans have undergone a new roasting technique,
giving them an intense aroma.
It has a bitter start but sour finish,
leaving a fruity taste on the tongue.
None of those people you presented during casting
were to my liking,
so I've concluded that Phupa is the one we need.
Your coffee is ready, sir.
It's just like you said about the fruity taste on the end of my tongue.
This is delicious.
It's delicious because you willingly waited for it.
You're so right.
If we place importance on something,
it becomes important by definition.
I've saved you all time, isn't that a good thing?
Yes, it's not that I'm lazy or anything.
Anyway, you're right.
Phupa's the best option for us right now.
It's not important who we select
because if we can overcome this crisis as a team,
there'll be a reward waiting for you.
I'll give you 3 hearts each.
And, whoever gets in touch with Phupa
will get an extra 2 hearts.
Wow!
Oh!
I'll see you soon!
Wow, thank you so much!
Nan, you simply must get this done!
These hearts of our jobs
haven't moved in the right direction for a long time.
If I can get just a few more, I'll be eligible for promotion.
That's applicable for all of us.
Most will get a promotion, and most will get a bonus.
Those hearts are there to encourage us to do our best.
Yes and that is why Phupa must join us!
There's no way Phupa's going to do it
You're breaking my heart.
Can you not destroy my moment of joy?
What's so difficult about it?
Man, I know him very well.
He's an introvert, who hates crowds of people.
Most importantly, he knew he can't do this job.
I won't allow my billboard to remain empty
because we don't have a presenter.
Who are you talking to?
I don't know.
I just know that Phupa has to change his mind.
Gie Gie,
I'll sort this out.
Gie Gie... you just find us an auspicious moment.
An auspicious moment would be...
one where you to mind your own business.
only 2 more stars!
We'll catch up with Man if we can sort this out.
Forget about that, we've got plenty of time.
Nan,
you know in the last 3 years
I haven't moved in that leaderboard like you guys.
You won't be angry at me
if I ask to try sorting it myself, will you?
Please...
Why isn't it going in?
Is it stuck on something?
Are we doing the right thing here?
Hmm...
Don't worry,
today's Wednesday... orange is the color of hope.
Here he comes.
What are you guys doing here so early?
Oh... um...
Hey, come here.
I've never seen him so angry.
I'm busy decorating.
Oh, ok.
Oh.
Gie Gie's brought you something.
I brought you a gift for the new shop.
A special Buddhist figurine for luck and dexterity.
Sorry...
I meant luck and prosperity.
I hope it brings your shop good fortune.
Thank you.
Sathu.
I'll leave it here.
Ok.
Remember when we looked at those fortune cards?
They were accurate in their predictions
when they said there'd be some unexpected changes afoot.
Then you got this shop!
Oh yeah, you're right.
They were spot on.
So, would you mind if we have another go?
Hmm... another go?
Ok, ok.
Let's take a look.
Ok, I suppose we could.
Cut them equal times to your age.
Equal to my age?
Exactly.
Make a wish before you choose.
Go ahead, choose one.
This one.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Sure?
Sure, do it.
I'm sure it will be great.
Death.
Something will come to an end or expire.
Doesn't sound so great.
No problem,
choose again because I...
I'm not going to let anything bad happen to our presenter.
Wait a minute.
Who is your presenter?
You didn't mention this.
Um...
Oh... it's...
She's presenting you with this statue
Um... yes... that's it.
It's nothing to do with anything else.
That's right.
Yes, we're talking about this figurine.
Obstacles are like grains of sand.
Despite their number, they're easily removed.
Are you talking to me?
Pardon me?
Hello? Check, one, two. Ok.
Hmm...
I can hear your heart beating.
Fear can actually be something...
which we create ourselves.
Fear of speaking.
Fear of expressing ourselves.
fear of making mistakes.
Once more please.
Ah ha!
You're scared, aren't you?
Look here please.
Who's scared?
Not me.
What do those without fear end up with?
And what is lost through fear?
Don't... hey, hang on.
We must therefore
try not to keep our fear inside of us
because it will build up
and end up in an explosion.
It could end up holding us back, right?
Something difficult to deal with.
Once it reaches that stage, oh dear...
How much is that, Phupa?
How much?
No! Don't stop!
Exactly, how much longer must we be fearful?
A very long time.
Non-stop.
That's it, pick that fear up
and kick it away into Asgard.
Once it is in the Asgard
we'll see it if it comes back into focus and
push it away again, keeping it there.
We can lock it up in Asgard.
Bang! And then we look
You can do it! You can do it!
Yay!
But I can't do this.
Oh dear... that's a big knife.
Don't worry, that's quite normal.
Fear is entirely normal.
See, I'm stuttering now
because I'm feeling fearful.
Oh... why are you following me?
It's ok, I'll leave.
I've been fearful since I was little.
Since I was still in the womb.
They had a knife and I was just like ‘ahhh'.
So, there I was in the womb
and, hey, I was scared.
I was very fearful. It's normal.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm leaving, sir.
Leaving?
We've hired you for the day!
I'm leaving.
Can't you see that huge freaking knife?
I'm off!
Hey, wait, Coach!
I'm gone!
Coach!
This was your doing, right?
I think you'd all better leave.
Gie Gie, quickly!
Go, get out.
Me too?
Yes... go.
Gie Gie!
Huh?
Get out.
Of course.
Where are you going?
I'm leaving.
Please don't.
Look at the size of that knife!
He's crazy.
Look at his face, he wouldn't dare use that thing.
It's for cutting things.
I want to tell you something,
acting according to our heart's desire
isn't difficult.
It's only weaklings and cowards
who can't do it.
Where are you going?
Prawet, Bang Khen, Sam Sen, Pattaya, Pathum Kongka, Wattana, Bang Bor, Bang Sue,
Bang Son, Bang Krabue, Bang Bon, Khonkhaen, Yasothon, Phra Nakhon, Bang Khae.
He's gone!
Nan Fah!
You traitor!
Look what you've done.
The whole team is here, and that coach cost a fortune!
He wasn't here 10 minutes and he's already left.
But you shouldn't have snuck in like that.
So what?
We've come to make a show with him.
If we'd have made it, we'd all have been happy!
I think it is best if you all leave now.
My friend is extremely angry.
If he calls the police about trespassing, what will you do?
Oh my goodness...
Coach, wait up!
Man doesn't know what he's doing.
I told him this plan wouldn't work.
Right?
You too, please leave.
Me?
Yes.
Ok.
Bye bye, Party!
Me too?
Yeah.
Party, wait for me!
Phu, please may I have a photo with you?
Hmm.
Of course, I'll take it for you.
Strike a pose.
1, 2, 3.
Say cheese.
Outstanding.
It's a lovely photo.
Here, let me take a few more.
Don't forget to use #Joehaseverything
A great place to eat while listening to beautiful music from a handsome singer.
Thank you.
Hello.
Take a seat.
Can't you smile for my customers?
Not really.
Just playing in front of them makes me want to die.
Why?
Are you going to fire me?
Oh, come on...
Who in their right mind would fire you?
Oh, by the way, there's someone over there
who has come to see you.
He looks familiar, like he's been here before.
You haven't come to listen to me play, right?
I was listening actually.
You've got a great voice.
It got me thinking about why you can do this
but refused to be in our advertisement.
I do things I'm good at, not stuff I'm bad at.
I don't drink.
I quit a long time ago.
Is that true?
Nan drinks until he can barely walk.
How can you two be friends?
We've been friends for almost 30 years.
Don't count the 10 years you disappeared for.
I've come to ask you to reconsider.
If you're talking about the presenter job,
I'm not going to do it.
Sorry, I've got to go.
It's ok.
I'll sort it out.
What's going on here?
Phu, don't be afraid.
He's a shaman.
He can help alleviate your woes.
He'll send those evil spirits on their way.
It'll help.
Gie Gie.
What are you doing here?
I've just come to help.
Why are you doing this?
I just wanted to help out.
Go home.
But...
Go home now!
Ok, let's go.
I'm going. I'm going.
Quickly.
Ohm... ohm.
That's enough!
Ok, we're going.
You've got no respect.
Phu, I'm sorry about this.
I'm exhausted.
Not only that, but I'm also angry.
Look at how stubborn your friend's been.
I hired one of the best life coaches around and he didn't cares.
He threw it straight back in my face.
That wasn't clever and another thing is that
I don't really agree with Ken's vision anyway.
Is there something wrong?
Oh.
Ken, sir, hello.
Yeah.
Hello.
What were you doing down there, Ken?
I was fixing a plug socket.
There seems to be a lack of maintenance around here.
All the plugs are broken.
Have a seat.
Ok.
I don't mind if people don't agree with me.
I just see Phupa as having a rare gift.
It's an x-factor in his eyes.
He looks so honest and straightforward,
but that he's also hiding something.
Ken, sir.
I don't think Phupa is going to take this job.
What?
Well...
I hope this doesn't come out like
I'm throwing the blame around but
Nan Fah has been putting obstacles in our way
and now Phupa doesn't seem interested in the job.
Is that right, Nan Fah?
Well... I know that my friend hates this kind of job.
Ken, sir, could we try this?
How about we hire someone well-known instead?
We can't.
It won't align with our concept of an everyman.
This concept is perfect for us.
I promise I'll find the right person for us.
Just like who you are looking for.
And what if you don't?
Are you going to take responsibility and quit?
I will.
Oh my goodness.
Can you please leave us alone.
Sure.
I'd like to speak with Nan Fah.
Of course.
You've made your promise.
Take a seat.
I don't think quitting is an answer to any of this.
Yes, sir.
It's true I've done very little about this,
but I'm not going to force my friend to do something
if he's not willing to do it.
It seems you really care about this friend of yours.
I do.
The reason I made that promise to quit just now
is because I want you to have confidence in my ability.
I promise I'll do everything I can to find a presenter.
Ok.
I accept your promise, too.
Hey! Find someone to sort this plug socket out.
Ohm... maha sane... wait.
What was it again?
Om sane maha sane om na metta mahametta.
Om metta deva cittam
Believe and it will be.
Let's do this.
Which foot did the book say?
The right, no, try again.
Women go left foot first.
What if it isn't the one? Today's an even day.
Phupa.
Phupa, I just wanted to apologize for last night.
I didn't mean to...
Don't worry.
Forget it.
You were doing what you thought was right. I'm not angry.
The balm worked!
Phupa.
Will you do this presenter job for us?
No, thank you.
That hurts worse than being broken up with.
Why?
Why didn't that work?
I must've said the wrong spell.
I'm not giving up.
Let's try again.
Believe and it will be.
Oh dear, it must work this time.
Gie Gie, what are you doing?
What?
It's special balm.
When put on the lips, your words come true.
The shaman said it was completely safe.
It's white magic.
It's made from specially harvested beeswax,
viper bones, and gecko saliva.
Eugh.
What?
Ew!
Wow.
Nan!
Oh.
That's very disrespectful of you.
How can that help us now?
You can't rely on magic to solve your problems.
I just wanted to help us all.
Gie Gie, isn't it our teamwork
that has brought us success in the past?
It had nothing to do with magic.
Oh, I see, you're blocking our team's path to glory again,
just like Man said.
Concentrate.
You seem to have been taken in by all that nonsense.
Look at your lips.
They're all swollen.
It must be the balm punishing me!
For you guys throwing it away.
Ah, come on!
You're allergic to the balm.
Get to the hospital and sort it out!
And promise me you won't do something like this again.
Go!
I'm just not as talented as you are, Nan.
That's why I need all that other stuff.
Charms, auspicious colors,
They give me the confidence I need to work here.
Gie Gie, calm down and just listen for a moment.
You're here because of your talent.
Yes.
You support us all the time.
And you always encourage me when I need it.
Yes.
Believe me, we'll get through this.
I feel bad about what I did
but I feel more itchy than bad right now.
You shouldn't have made that promise to Man.
I don't want to lose you from the team.
Hey... I'm more worried about losing you right now.
Go, get some help.
Oh, Phu, I'll be back, ok?
Uh hmm. Please go.
Oh, Gie Gie.
Nan!
What is it?
Who died?
The little one.
What little one?
Oliang?
Which little one?
This one.
The plant?
The plant's dead?
One of your little ones is still alive.
Hmm... it's ok.
Don't worry.
I can help.
Take it out.
Wash it with water.
This is an anti-fungal solution.
Just a few drops in the water on it, like this.
Only 3-4 drops.
Then leave your little one in there to soak
for about 5-10 minutes
then you replant him in a new pot of soil
That's all.
Ok, I'd better go.
Hey, wait a minute.
You still haven't...
Are you still angry with me
about my colleagues getting involved?
Not at all.
But I do wonder why they're so persistent.
They're just quite odd like that.
Hmm.
Can't you stick around? It hasn't been 5-10 minutes yet.
Take care of my little one while I do some work.
Pretty please.
Ok, ok.
Oh yeah, Nan.
Do you still remember the lines to Romeo and Juliet?
Oh Juliet, my darling,
Death, that hath sucked the honey of thy breath,
hath had no power yet upon thy beauty.
Forbidden love has brought us to the end
but here I will remain.
I can't believe we remember that.
I was so grateful for your help back then.
If I didn't have you, I would've been terrible.
I was happy to help.
I'm going to stay here with you forever.
And you… don't ever leave my side.
I need to carry on with this.
Oh!
This is terrible.
Oh... it's all destroyed.
Phu...
Don't worry about it.
It's ok, we'll print out new ones.
No.
Yes.
You mean you're not happy with Nan Fah's suggestions, right?
I just think Phupa is the best fit for the role.
If we're forced into choosing an unsuitable candidate,
I'm worried we'll end up doing more damage
than we'd lose on the billboard.
True, but if we leave that billboard empty,
we'll be losing the company a lot of money.
Nan Fah, don't forget your promise.
Oh, it's such a terrible position we're in, Ken.
What are we going to do?
I've come to inform you that I'll be your presenter.
If you're here to talk about the presenter job, don't bother.
There's no way I'll do it.
What if it was Nan asking?
What is that supposed to mean?
Sit down and listen for a moment.
Oh, I don't smoke anymore.
I understand you.
You haven't seen him for 10 years,
so you don't feel like you know him as well as before.
Aren't you suspicious about how you secured this place?
It was Nan who came here every day
to convince them to take you on.
He never told me that.
Why would he?
He doesn't want you to feel bad.
If he asked you to be a presenter and used this against you,
you'd rightly see that as being dishonest.
Let me tell you something else.
It's not just about our boss being upset,
Nan has promised to quit if he can't find the right guy.
If it were me, I wouldn't stand by and let that happen.
Nan cares so much about you.
Thank you.