song credit
♫ ♫
[Scarlet Heart 2]
[Episode 1]
Team credit
Your Majesty.
If you can't come to my world to look for me,
then I'll go to yours.
Send this thing to the Northwest.
To Ruoxi's hometown.
Quick.
The sandstorm is coming, let's go quickly.
Quick!
Quick! Keep up.
- Quick.
- Keep up!
Let's go.
Your Majesty.
[In the thirteenth year of his reign, Yongzheng passed away on the 23rd day of the 8th lunar month]
[and was buried in Shizong in Xiling.]
[Yongzheng's tomb was raided 250 years after his death.]
[Life is ever-changing like the wind, and neither love nor matter can withstand it.
[The Early 80s of the Last Century]
[Northwest China]
Water.
- Why aren't you drinking it?
- I'm not thirsty anymore.
Camel, forget it if we can't find it. Let's go back.
No way.
The weather isn't looking too good.
Let's go back to our camp first. We're running out of gas too.
No way, it wasn't easy for us to get here. We can't go back empty-handed.
I'll go back myself if you don't.
Chenggui, we've tried our best.
- Don't be reckless.
- Reckless?
I've put in all the money my family gave me for my studies.
How can I just go back without getting anything?
We've been searching for the past ten days.
- So what?
- What if the box is just a legend?
That's impossible.
Stop fighting. The weather really doesn't look too good right now.
Brother, wake up.
- We found it?
- No, but someone here wants to quit.
I'm here to look for treasure, not to risk my life.
Camel, head back.
Okay.
No way!
- What are you doing?
- Chenggui, let go!
- Leave me alone.
- Chenggui!
- Don't be so stubborn.
- Just leave if you want to!
Keeping us here is like leaving us to die.
If you want to leave, don't blame me for not giving you this opportunity.
- Are you crazy?
- Stop fighting!
Go, leave.
- Just go.
- What are you talking about?
Go.
Stop fighting! The tornado is coming! Get in the car!
- Get into the car, Chenggui.
- Quickly!
Tornado.
Get in the car!
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Okay.
Chenggui.
Brother.
- Don't let go.
- Hold on tight, Chenggui.
- Brother.
- Hold on tight.
- Chenggui. Don't let go.
- Brother, save me.
- Don't let go, Brother.
- Hold on tight.
Brother.
Don't let go.
- Hold on tight.
- Save me.
Chenggui.
Brother.
Brother!
- How are you doing, Chenggui?
- I'm fine.
Me too.
Xiao Hua.
Brother.
Look.
God has blessed us.
He knew we were having a hard time finding it, and it is right in front of us now.
There's more over here.
We're rich.
Come take a look.
What is that?
Let me see.
I guess this is the box of Emperor Yongzheng.
Not necessarily.
Brother, your knife.
Here.
Be careful.
What's written on here?
I recognize two characters.
One of them is "you", and the other is "I".
Everything's fine. We're rich now.
It was a misunderstanding just now. Everything's fine now.
We're fine now, cheer up.
Let's take a picture.
Wait.
Wait for me.
Okay.
Hurry.
[Present Day]
Thinking about the past, I have many regrets.
I hope I can mend all those moments.
For the past three months, I've been spending time in this museum.
Looking at the people in these paintings, I still can feel their presence.
What am I looking for?
Am I looking for those familiar faces and trying to recall what they had said?
Shouldn't I understand the pain of parting by now?
Is the pain of parting with a loved one really more painful than death?
What's going on with me?
Am I so afraid of losing those memories so I'm unable to let it go?
No way.
I can't keep myself here.
I need to move on.
What's he doing here?
Are you looking for me?
I'm right here.
Can you see me?
Do you still remember me?
Do we know each other?
Are you okay?
Fourth Prince.
No, I can't let you go.
I'm sorry.
You can't run in here.
My balloons.
Are you blind? You're paying me back for those balloons.
I'm sorry. How much is it?
There were many balloons. At least 500.
I don't have that much money right now.
Maybe you can give me your address. I'll bring the money to you tomorrow.
I don't trust you. Let me see your purse.
Your phone looks nice.
I'll take this as collateral.
This should be enough.
You know who I am now?
Do you recognize me?
I really don't recognize you.
I'm sorry.
I thought...
You were someone I knew.
Whether it's someone you thought you knew or whatever the reason is,
it's dangerous to follow a man around.
Director Yin, the chairman is here.
How long do you need?
Hi, Director Yin.
Good morning, Director Yin.
Director Yin, the chairman is already in the conference room.
Everyone is waiting for you.
It's such a nice day. Can we talk about something else?
Regarding Aili's incident, I've asked the Internet water army to refute the rumor on Weibo.
I've just called her agent to give her a warning.
Let's go.
- It's Director Yin. He's so handsome.
- Director Yin.
Director Yin.
Are you alright?
He is really handsome.
Director Yin.
Hi, Director Yin.
Hi.
Miss, please show your employee ID.
What?
Do you work here?
- No.
- I'm sorry.
Only staff of Zheng Tian Group can go inside.
I'm here for an interview.
Please proceed to the reception area to check in.
Please.
Don't wait for him, let's start the meeting.
Haven't started yet?
I could've gotten a cup of coffee from downstairs first then.
You're 35 minutes late.
It's 36 minutes now.
With Mr. Chairman here, there's no need for me as the vice president.
If you don't respect yourself and your work,
it's meaningless for you to stay in this conference room.
Mr. Chairman. Don't be angry.
Director Yin went to the Qing Treasures Exhibition to prepare for the winter auction next month.
That's why he's late.
He put a lot of effort into advertising for the auction next month.
Then let's start the meeting.
Mr. Chairman.
First of all, I would like to apologize for being late.
Now please just give me five minutes to explain my proposal.
Look at that. He is well-prepared.
Since you have a plan already, just go straight to the point.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Please take a look.
Survival competition.
Mr. Chairman. And everyone in charge of the winter auction.
I think the best way to advertise is to first make it become a hot topic among the people.
And I think a survival competition is a very good way to do so.
We can offer the title of ambassador of the auction
to organize a big audition.
If we do this, the media will report it.
It's not very realistic.
Mr. Chairman. I'm not even done yet and you already think it's unrealistic?
What we're discussing now is the advertising plan for the winter auction.
Not some entertainment show.
You always teach us to change and improve with the times.
This has nothing to do with that.
Of course it does.
That's actually your biggest flaw.
You refuse to adapt and you're opinionated.
Vice President.
You always say one thing and do another.
How dare you?
You can leave.
Everyone knows about my plan now.
Just let me know if the chairman wants to use it or not.
Mr. Chairman, I'll take my leave now.
Cheater Huang.
How old are you? Still playing this?
How old are you? Can't even play a game with me?
What are you doing here?
I have big news.
What do you want exactly?
Come sit down first.
Xiaoxiao, let's get back together.
Get lost.
I thought you just started a new relationship.
You broke up already?
Don't mention her, she spends a lot.
All my credit cards got maxed out. My debit card too.
Now I have no money left. But it helped me realize something.
You're the one who treats me the best.
Xiaoxiao, forgive me. I won't cheat on you again.
I won't get seduced by other girls anymore.
Stop.
I don't want to hear this anymore. And stop playing the victim.
We're done.
Find a basement room for 40 yuan a day.
This is enough for two weeks of expenses. You're on your own after that.
Xiaoxiao,
since your accident, housing prices have soared.
Where can I find a basement room for 40 yuan a day?
How much do you need then?
I'm not here to ask you for money.
I know I've wronged you in many ways.
I cheated on you and upset you.
I know you don't believe that I still love you.
But...
Taking into consideration that we've been together for three years, can't you allow me to stay?
You should take responsibility for me, Xiaoxiao.
Xiaoxiao,
I'd rather be crying on your bathroom floor
than be smiling on a bed of a basement room.
Xiaoxiao, please let me stay.
I know you'll allow me to stay.
Because you are the kindest, the most gentle, the prettiest...
Enough.
I'll do this for you one last time.
It's the last time.
You can only stay here for a month. After that you need to move out.
Understand?
Yes.
Understood.
Where should I sleep?
The bathroom.
You really want me to sleep in the bathroom?
That was your own choice.
Shit. I was just kidding.
[Qing Treasures Exhibition]
You went to the museum again?
It's been three months since you woke up.
Why you go to the museum everyday?
I know you might think that I'm long-winded, but I ask because I care about you.
In this cold city, I'm the one that cares about you the most.
I don't want to see you playing as the museum curator.
Sooner or later, you'll go crazy.
Although you had a dream
that all the men in the Qing Dynasty fell in love with you, you still need to come back to reality.
In the real world, I, Huang Di, is the one that loves you the most.
Enough.
You can stay here, but food is at your own expense.
And also... don't say the word "love" in front of me.
Xiaoxiao, I'm so hungry.
Make me some food.
Food is at your own expense. Don't make me repeat myself again.
I really don't have any money.
You can search me if you don't believe me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You met someone?
It was just a random guess.
You really did?
Ex-boyfriend? Ex-ex-boyfriend?
- Ex-ex-ex...
- Stop it.
Give it back.
This is our boss' fake son.
What?
This is Zhen Tian Group's Kang Zhentian's adopted son.
I know him.
You know him?
Director Yin, I just met with the chairman.
He seems to be bringing an antique specialist to check out the exhibition antiques in the storeroom.
But I can tell he's still mad at you.
One more thing, I heard that Kang Sihan is back.
- Hello?
- Director Yin, the flowers will be there before 4 o'clock.
Don't worry.
Great job.
I asked you to find out why Kang Sihan is back.
Did you find out?
Yin Zheng's mother is Kang Zhentian's second wife.
And Kang Zhentian is Yin Zheng's mother's second husband too.
And I heard that Kang Zhentian has another son.
That means he has a brother.
Yin Zheng's background is very complicated.
Don't even think about approaching him.
If you like those kind of playboys, you might as well come back to me.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
Come with me.
Take a look.
Look at his scandals.
As I was saying, unfaithfulness is hereditary.
Take my dad for example. He is a playboy.
That's why it's difficult for me to be loyal to women.
It's hard for me too.
Xiaoxiao. Can you sympathize with me now?
Shut up.
Why did you take pictures of him?
You have a crush on him?
Love at first sight?
Or did he take advantage of you?
Are you guys in a relationship already?
He would never be interested in you.
You don't have a sexy figure nor are you pretty enough.
Shut up.
I'll go to buy something to eat then.
Why does he look so much like him?
Very familiar.
Is it just a coincidence?
Give it to me.
This hairpin and I are really meant to be.
When I first saw it 25 years ago, it was buried under the sand.
I never thought it would come back to me again.
What a miracle.
Mr. Chairman, you're blessed. That's why your wishes always come true.
Right, right.
Mr. Chairman,
this hairpin is the only antique from Yongzheng's dynasty that we have for the auction.
It has delicate carving.
It is made of top quality jade and looks smooth.
- Right.
- It's a quality antique.
- Yes.
- It will definitely sell for a lot.
Yes.
It's not for sale.
It'll just be put on display but not for sale.
Xiao Chen.
Take good care of it for me.
This hairpin means a lot to me.
So this is the famous Zhen Tian Building.
How imposing.
I've been here before.
Wait.
I work for the Zheng Tian Group planning department.
What?
An employee.
Enough nonsense.
[Zhen Tian Group]
Wait for me. Let me give you a brief.
The chairman's office is on the 38th floor,
which is also the highest floor in this building.
Yin Zheng's office is on the 37th floor.
To occupy such a lofty position, second only to the chairman.
That feeling is just like being in an imperial palace.
This is my only chance to get in touch with Yin Zheng.
Maybe I will get my answers very soon.
It's all up to you from here on out.
Let's go.
Come on.
Hurry.
Zhang Xiao.
Take a seat.
Where did you work previously?
At an advertisement company. I've also built a webpage for a magazine.
You often change your job. And you didn't last long for any of them.
You just have a bachelor's degree and from a third-rate university.
You don't have much work experience, and the companies you worked for are all pretty unpopular.
You should know that Zhen Tian Group is the leader
in the auction house, jewelry, and Yuesai cosmetics industries.
Our jewelry and cosmetics target the elite group.
Do you think we need someone like you?
You can take a look at my previous designs first.
Insights and anima are the most important things for a designer.
Although I don't have much working experience
I hope that I can have a chance to showcase my talents here.
You're asking for a lot.
Not classy at all.
Fortunately, your look passes the test.
But if you want to stay here for long, good looks won't be enough.
So.
You can go home now.
Good morning, Mr. Chairman.
He's Zhen Tian Group's chairman?
He looks just like Kangxi.
Please take your seats.
What's your name?
Mr. Chairman, these are her personal details.
My name is Zhang Xiao.
I'm here to interview for the graphic designer role.
Why do you want to work here?
Your resume doesn't really fulfill our company's requirements.
I want a fresh start.
You're only 25. And you already want a fresh start?
I didn't know what kind of job I wanted before.
Now I want a new opportunity for growth.
We have a Spring Auction next month.
What do you know about the ancient emperors from the past 5000 years of Chinese civilization?
I think the emperor that I most familiar with is Emperor Kangxi.
Emperor Kangxi?
Tell me you think about Emperor Kangxi.
His merits and demerits will be assessed by history.
What I respect the most about him is that during his 61 years on the throne, he never stopped working for even a day.
He was diligent and loved his people. He was one in a million.
Unfortunately, he was faced with a great dilemma due to disputes of throne succession.
I think that was his biggest pain too.
If you were to describe him with a poem, which poem suits him the most?
It's a pity Emperor Qin and Emperor Wu were lacking in literary grace.
Emperor Taizong and Emperor Taizu lacked poetry in their letters.
Genghis Khan, the proud son of Heaven, knew only of bending his bows to shoot eagles.
They're all people of the past; Brilliant heroes are those whom we will see today!
You are quite interesting.
Your hometown is Ganlin?
Yes.
Ganlin is a good place.
What do your parents do now?
My father was a physical education teacher but he's retired.
My mother passed away when I was young.
Mr. Chairman, have a safe journey.
Come to work tomorrow.
Really?
Of course.
Thank you, Mr. Chairman.
Mr. Chairman, do you like tea?
So you are trying to find out my hobbies before you even start working here?
Are you trying to please me?
No.
It'll take more than some flattery and a pretty face to hold your ground here.
Remember to report to me tomorrow.
I want that girl's family background and detailed information on her parents.
Yes, Mr. Chairman.
Cheater Huang. I have some bad news for you.
I passed the interview.
I will start working tomorrow.
Okay, see you later.
Team credit
Are you okay?
Lan Lan. Are you okay?
- Lan Lan.
- Excuse me.
Lan Lan, are you alright?
Ms. Lan, let's go take a break.
Come, follow me.
Who was that?
Why does she look exactly like me?
She is Ruoxi.
song credit
♫ ♫