=Parallel World=
(Adapted from Wei Yu's novel "Parallel World")
=Episode 16=
(This story is a work of fiction.)
What's going on?
What are you guys talking about?
Liu.
Hurry.
Help her get in the car.
- Don't be afraid.
- Gao Shen, am I going to die?
Get her in.
I'll deal with that Scorpion Eye.
No, you won't.
Liu.
Don't cry.
There are many reports online
of people getting stabbed in fights
without even realizing it.
Some even went to the hospital
by themselves,
and they all turned out fine.
That's different.
Hospitals were accessible to them,
but right now,
we have no idea where we're heading.
There's a hospital here too.
Aren't there Yellow Soil City
and Black Stone City?
- There must be a hospital there.
- He's right, Liu.
We'll likely get well
once we receive treatment at the hospital.
(Yellow Soil City)
Mister.
Where's the hospital?
Up ahead. At that dead-end.
Go.
Doctor.
Where's the doctor?
Inside.
(Huang Ji's Clinic)
The doctor is here.
Hurry.
Calm down.
What's the hurry?
Doctor.
Here.
Take a look at this.
She has a dagger stuck in her head.
Don't move.
I'll go get some helpers.
Hold on a second.
Quick, get a stretcher.
Bring the patient in.
(Huang Ji's Clinic)
Considering her current condition,
she requires surgery.
As you can tell,
the facilities here
are barely sufficient.
I suggest getting her to Black Stone City.
It's a three- to four-day ride
by metallic van.
What do you mean?
Aren't you a doctor?
Why can't you treat her?
Doctor.
I beg you.
Please save her.
I can't wait three or four days.
I can perform the surgery,
and I've seen worse cases than this.
The dagger can be extracted,
but what potential complications
might arise within the skull,
and what could the resulting outcome be?
This is something
I can't promise.
What's the worst that could happen?
I'll state
the worst from mild to severe.
In the short term,
the patient could suffer
impaired consciousness, coma,
hemiplegia, aphasia,
or even death.
Gao Shen.
Liu.
Is your head still hurting?
It's less painful compared to my arm.
I want
to have the dagger extracted.
If things don't go well,
pass my word to my godfather.
Tell him I'll repay his favor
in my next life.
Don't blame yourself.
It's simply fate if I meet my end here.
Don't say that.
If you have to say it,
how...
how will I explain it to Qi?
Go away. I don't want to see you again.
Alright.
Just calm down.
Doctor.
We'll leave her in your hands.
I'll fetch the emergency kit
and check if there's anything
we can use for the surgery.
Let's get prepared.
Let's go.
Does it hurt?
Bear it.
I told you to bear it.
Liuxi.
Is Valley Guardian really dead?
Why isn't it moving at all?
It could be feigning death.
Feigning unconsciousness
whenever danger is near.
Bring it outward.
There we go.
Faking dead whenever danger is close.
No combat ability at all.
It's fine as long as it's alive.
How is it, Doctor?
The surgery went relatively smoothly,
and the dagger was successfully removed.
Now is the critical period.
Don't disturb her,
and let her rest well.
Got it.
Doctor.
Can you please check my friend's eyes?
It's nothing major.
Just get some sunlight,
and you'll be fine.
So, I'm not going blind, right, Doctor?
You're overthinking it.
Just get more sunlight. Got it?
Got it.
What is preoccupying you?
Liu is still young.
The way you say it
makes it sound like she is beyond hope.
You're right
that she's still young,
but her recovery ability
is also at its strongest.
I believe
she'll definitely pull through.
But the conditions here are so poor.
The surgery isn't even aseptic,
and we can't even get a brain scan.
You're right about that.
Think about it, though.
In ancient times, people engaged
in hand-to-hand combat,
hacking away so savagely at each other,
but many people survived,
didn't they?
And besides, at the time,
there was no medical equipment at all.
Do you really want to argue with me?
What would you expect?
Should I agree with whatever you say
and have a good cry with you?
Getting along with people
is really difficult over time.
When I first met Liu,
no matter if she lived or died,
I wouldn't even bat an eye.
This feeling right now is so weird.
To not worry,
you have to act like you don't care,
but usually, the apathy is mutual.
If you never care about others,
it means
you've never been cared about.
But that's not good either.
Chang Dong.
I feel so awful about Liu's situation.
You must've felt even worse
back then, right?
Since the incident,
you're the first one to comfort me.
The first thing my uncle, Ding Zhou,
said to me at the time was,
"You are my nephew, so I won't
just stand by and do nothing for you."
"But really,"
"this is too nasty."
This is the first time
someone ever asked me if I was upset.
Why did you attack us?
Speak!
It was the van.
When I was at Red Flower Tree Inn,
I heard you guys
were driving a metallic van,
so I took an interest in it.
Liuxi.
No, no, no.
Dude.
I'll give you another chance,
so come clean about it.
Was it just for the van?
I had my eye on you guys
when you were drinking at night.
There are two women
and a skinny guy among you.
My scorpion and I
could easily take care of you guys.
But I didn't expect...
Well, it's a shame.
It's a shame? What for?
It's a shame
that we didn't expect you to have guns.
Guns are rare here.
Even Zhan hasn't owned one.
Who is this Zhan you're talking about?
Zhan is
Jiang Zhan,
the leader of Scorpion Eye.
Do you not know about him?
How did you
manage to have a metallic van then?
Where is Jiang Zhan at?
From now on,
I won't say a single word.
Fine.
Fine? What's fine?
Wait a minute.
What should we do with him?
Let's lock him up in here.
Mom.
Please don't kill my mom.
No!
You're awake?
How are you today? Can you see anything?
I think I'm feeling better
than yesterday.
Now I'm 70-percent blind.
Alright, let's go wash up then.
I don't have time
to look after you alone.
Come on.
- Watch out for the threshold.
- Ouch.
Morning.
Good morning, Dong.
The tap is running.
Go ahead and wash up.
Has Liu woken up?
Not yet.
The Scorpion Eye guy, is he dead?
Huh?
The Scorpion Eye guy.
Is he dead?
Nope. We had the doctor set his bones.
He's locked away up there.
Why did you have someone set his bones?
His arm was badly swollen.
It was unbearable to see.
He deserved it, didn't he?
Well, it's okay.
I can break them again, anyway.
- What are you looking at?
- Liuxi.
Are you done washing up?
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh.
- He's asking me.
- Oh, okay.
Sit here.
Aren't you going to put on some oil?
I'm poor. I don't have any.
And I've got good skin.
Dong, can I put on some of your oil?
It's here.
This map is already quite detailed.
It's quite a long way
from one city to another.
The names of each city
are derived
from their building materials.
For instance, the city where we are now
is named Yellow Soil City
since most of the buildings in this city
are made up of yellow soil.
The doctor also mentioned
that the cities aren't large,
about the same size
as that of a town outside the pass.
There are Feather Guards
and sorcerers in every city.
To put it simply, the Feather Guards
for public security,
while the sorcerers
deal with exotic beasts.
The civilians are responsible
for sustaining them.
Look at this.
This place is named Huyang City.
It's located in the northeast
inside the pass.
Here lies Scorpion Eye's stronghold.
Over two years ago,
Scorpion Eye
hanged a lot of Feather Guards here.
Later, in retaliation, Feather Guards
set the place on fire.
Feather Guards?
Right.
What about the south?
Is there something
that marks the location of Yumen Pass
over there?
Heading south,
you'll find the Flowing Sand Yardang.
Further south, there's the Demon Museum.
So, is there no marker
for the entrance of the pass?
What is the Demon Museum?
I'm not quite sure about the rest.
Let's wait until Liu wakes up.
Then, we'll go to Black Stone City
to ask about it.
Alright.
By the way, come with me
to the market later.
We need to buy some gasoline.
I'll join you.
You go there and soak up some sun.
It's good for your eyes.
Just go.
Valley Guardian.
Come on.
Go soak up some sun
with me.
Liu.
Please wake up.
I just want you to be safe and sound,
but I didn't expect...
Liu.
As long as you wake up,
I'll do whatever you ask me to.
Who's got the ace?
You do.
Wait for me for a moment.
Can I know
where I can get gasoline around here?
Gasoline?
Yes.
Is there gasoline available recently?
- You can try checking over there.
- Maybe you can go there.
They have everything down there.
In that place?
Yes.
Thank you.
Come.
Let's continue.
Who got the ace just now?
Why are there so many mirrors here?
Funhouse mirrors.
Let me take a look at you.
We have things to do. Let's go.
Why are you pulling me?
Look in the mirror.
What are you looking at?
That exotic beast
is here to work for the market.
There's no problem.
You two go ahead.
Don't block the way. Hurry up.
Chop chop.
There.
Why aren't they selling under the sun?
It feels so crowded and gloomy.
The doctor said
bandits used to frequently attack.
It's not safe outdoors.
Only Black Stone City is fearless.
Other smaller places operate indoors
for safety's sake.
(Meizi Beauty Salon)
Can you walk faster?
I don't want it anymore.
You can come back if you want it.
Aren't you feeling hot?
This place is quite stuffy.
Have a look.
Our knives are pretty good.
What about that one?
Of course, miss.
You have a good eye.
This knife is my prized possession
for the store.
The top blacksmith in the pass
used obsidian from the gold mines
to forge it.
I'll let you have a good look today.
Watch closely.
This knife is indeed excellent,
but
I'm not selling it.
Why are you showing it
if you're not selling it?
Name your price.
Miss, you can choose
any other knife you like,
but I'm not selling this one.
A metallic van
and a crate of cold medicine. Deal?
Don't joke around.
Let's go.
If it's that wristwatch,
we can negotiate.
Let's go. I am not interested anymore.
We're here for gasoline.
I have my own knife.
(Gasoline)
Boss.
Boss?
Excuse me. May I ask
why is this shop closed?
It's been closed for a while.
We've been short on gasoline
for a long time.
Thank you.
(Black Stone's new tea arrival.
Welcome to try.)
What should we do without gasoline?
We'll figure something out.
You really don't want that knife?
Do you think I'm stupid?
This watch of yours
costs tens of thousands, right?
Why sell it cheap?
Besides, I have a knife.
It's been with me for a long time.
It's handy.
That knife of yours
has had its blade sharpened many times,
hasn't it?
Let it be sharpened then.
It's chopped up plenty of melons
with me.
It's got sentimental value.
Alright then. Keep using it.
I need to use the restroom.
Boss?
Coming.
Exchange this for the knife.
Thanks.
Here you go.
Your knife.
The common currency inside the pass.
Why did he give you change?
My watch is limited edition
even outside the pass.
For real.
There definitely won't be any
inside the pass.
I told the boss
that he can at least double his profit
when he sells it.
I don't want it.
I didn't pay for it.
I didn't say I'd give it to you.
Why did you put it in front of me then?
To let me touch it?
You can touch it.
I'm lending it to you.
Your knife skills are good.
It's best for you to have it
for everyone's safety.
So, it is to get me to work.
You better take good care of it.
I'll check on it regularly.
But remember,
you only have the right to use it.
Its ownership still belongs to me.
Got it.
What about your knife?
Do you guys think
the men from Scorpion Eye
will they lose their heads
when they return
since they suffered a defeat
in Yellow Soil City?
I heard  that Jiang Zhan
has a really bad temper.
How can you call that a defeat?
That's called a diversion.
They sent a small group of people
to create chaos in Yellow Soil City
one moment
and went to Red Brick City the next.
It's all a cover.
They don't want anyone
to know their true intentions.
I've heard differently.
Jiang Zhan has already infiltrated
Black Stone City.
Isn't that just seeking death?
Black Stone City
has many Feather Guards and sorcerers.
Is Jiang Zhan not afraid of them?
You never know. There might be
another Beast Head revolt again.
Cut it out. You're talking nonsense.
Two months ago,
the Qian family had asked Silver Snake
in Black Stone City.
The Sheep's Horn
was nowhere to be found.
Sheep's Horn.
Let me tell you.
After the leader of Beast Head,
Li Wangdong,
was killed
by the sorcerers and Feather Guards,
their treasure, the Sheep's Horn,
had mysteriously disappeared.
I think
it was stolen by some thief.
Silver Snake once predicted
that when the Sheep's Horn reappears,
Beast Head awakens.
The Sheep's Horn reappearance
will cause chaos.
You're just talking nonsense.
If
the Sheep's Horn hasn't appeared yet,
what does Scorpion Eye amount to?
Scorpion Eye is similar
to the Beast Head group.
Even their names are remarkably similar.
I heard that Jiang Zhan
doesn't actually have the Sheep's Horn.
Stop looking.
The sorcerers and Feather Guards
are here.
Go. Move aside.
Don't block the way.
Sit down quickly.
Let me tell you.
There are usually five people on patrol.
Why are there fewer people today?
Yes.
What those people said just now
is for reference only.
The truth has been distorted
as it passed from mouth to mouth.
Where is the Sheep's Horn?
It's still here.
Where?
In the car.
You left such an important thing
in the car?
I know.
Where in the car?
I'll get it myself in a moment.
Are your eyes okay?
I've been basking in the sun
all afternoon, Liuxi. I'm better now.
I can see clearly.
Where did you get this knife, Liuxi?
What dynasty is this from?
Don't touch it.
Dong,
are there many things at the market?
Mostly old stuff.
Go take a look yourself
when your eyes are better.
That's the stuff I want to see.
Liuxi.
What about your knife?
You don't want it anymore?
You want it?
Yes.
Take it.
Give it to me, Dong.
With this,
I'm not afraid of anyone anymore.
You scared me.
I just wanted to take a look.
(Observe desert rules.
No trespassing nature reserves.)
♪Hidden dreams slumber♪
♪Quietly setting the hidden stage♪
♪The twilight of destiny♪
♪Turns into the fortress of truth for love♪
♪When sealed memories♪
♪Slumber with the winds and sands♪
♪When choosing to continue the journey♪
♪With unwavering determination♪
♪When the enigmatic world
and the parallel reality contradict♪
♪Let the other side bring a colorful end♪
♪Ambiguity between truth and falsehood♪
♪Intoxicated between reality and fantasy♪
♪All beings are but for love♪
♪Spin in endless circles♪
♪Swear to enter the dangerous pass♪
♪Even if the future
is filled with swirling snow♪
♪Only to have a clear conscience♪
♪Ambiguity between truth and falsehood♪
♪Intoxicated between reality and fantasy♪
♪All beings are but for love♪
♪Spin in endless circles♪
♪Swear to enter the dangerous pass♪
♪Even if the future
is filled with swirling snow♪
♪Only to have a clear conscience♪