[English subtitles are available]
[Wife Above All]
[Episode 23]
That night,
bandits came to our house.
They killed people and set a fire.
They robbed us.
My mother and I hid in the attic.
That's why we survived.
Where did the bandits come from?
They acted so arrogantly.
Actually, they were not
real bandits.
I heard their conversation
in the attic.
Back then,
it was indeed Mo Xiang, who came to the capital,
who delivered the medicine to the frontline.
But Prince An kept the medicine to himself without permission.
They did a clean job.
They didn't leave any trace behind.
That's why General Yun
thought Mr. Mo was the one
who harmed the Yun family.
I'm sorry. I...
Shut your mouth.
You continue.
Later, I heard them say
they were targeting the two biggest clinics
in the capital.
But Mo Xiang was determined.
He only treated civilians.
And he was deeply trusted by His Majesty.
So it was inconvenient for them
to take action on Mo's Clinic.
That's why they targeted
Qin's Medicine Shop.
My family members were killed.
Although I survived,
Qin's Medicine Shop
doesn't belong to the Qin family.
Prince An kept the medicine to himself
and forced my family members to help him transport the medicine.
After that,
he set a fire and burnt the whole village.
Our family members
are gone.
So,
all these years,
Prince An has gained so many ways
to transport the medicine.
What exactly does he want to do?
What kind of place
needs to use medicine constantly?
It's either a clinic
or a military camp.
A military camp?
Prince An wants to start a...
The Yun family.
The Qin family.
The Mo family.
The Huo family.
Those who have collected military supplies
were either punished
or killed for no reason.
I know you don't want to see me.
But now,
you've offended Liu Zhengming.
Mr. Mo was also killed.
Noble Consort and Prince An
won't let you go easily.
Since we all want
to take revenge on Prince An,
you should stay in the camp for the time being.
If something happens,
I can still take care of you.
Stay.
Prince An has many followers.
And now, he's favored
by His Majesty.
There are only a few of us.
If we fight against Prince An,
isn't that like throwing an egg at a rock?
Count me in.
Sister,
only by working together
can we avenge our father.
We won a great victory at Qulingguan.
Thanks to His Majesty, I, Yun Zilong,
had the chance to lead you to guard Qulingguan.
We won a great victory this time,
but we've suffered great casualties.
I
feel guilty towards you.
General is mighty!
General is mighty! General is mighty!
Qin.
You won a great victory at Qulingguan.
When you return to the capital,
His Majesty will definitely give you
a lot of things as rewards.
Congratulations.
What great victory?
It's just that General Yun
doesn't want to hurt the soldiers' feelings.
In a few days,
I'll ask someone to escort you back.
We can't retreat the troops at Qulingguan
for now.
You are not going to go back?
What happened again?
Have you become a fool
after being poisoned these days?
No.
So there was something wrong with your brain before you were poisoned.
According to what is said in the ledger,
the weapons in the military camp
are
more than enough.
But the weapons we have
are far from enough.
We were lucky to win this time
because General Yun and the soldiers
put up
a desperate fight.
I can't believe he takes wars at the border as a joke
just for money.
Prince An is cunning
and vicious.
I'm afraid this victory
is just a trap set by him.
What do you mean?
You heard this before.
Quelling the unrest at Qulingguan
was under the leadership of the crown prince in the capital.
The victory at Qulingguan
means
the crown prince's position in the court
has been strengthened.
So Prince An
will have less chance, right?
Wait.
You just said
the army is short of weapons.
But the rebels came aggressively.
Even though they were defeated,
how could they
lose so badly?
Prince An and the rebels...
Don't talk nonsense without evidence.
If my guess is right,
the rebels at the border
will definitely come back.
By that time, Prince An
will incite the officials in the court
to say that the crown prince fails his duty in the capital.
Then he'll personally lead an army to conquer the rebels.
In that way,
he can make a great contribution.
If the rebels really come back
like you said,
General Yun will be accused of lying about the war situation.
The charge of failing his duty
will become real.
Why don't
you and General Yun go back to the capital first
and tell His Majesty everything?
Even though His Majesty favors Prince An,
he won't ignore
the national military affairs.
If we go back to the capital and report to His Majesty,
we can surely stay out of it.
But
what about the civilians at the border?
There are so many innocent people.
I still want to stay.
I want to save as many as I can,
even if I'll be cursed.
Fine.
I've made up my mind too.
I won't leave either.
Why?
Didn't you say
you're not afraid of getting me implicated?
By God's will,
His Majesty's edict:
General Yun Zilong
has made a contribution by quelling the unrest at Qulingguan.
You are supposed to return to the capital immediately
to be promoted as the Commander of the Imperial Guards.
However, you said
you want to eliminate the rebels.
Considering your loyalty
to the country,
I allow you to stay at Qulingguan.
You can come back to the capital to receive rewards some other day.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
[Side Story]
The mission I'm about to tell you
is very important.
General
has ordered us
to listen to Mr. Qin.
Good.
Which one of you
knows how to make sugar figures?
Sugar figures?
Can you teach me?
General Yun said
you're best at drawing.
I draw city defense maps.
City defense maps?
What about you?
I draw notices for wanted persons.
I only know how to make mud people.
It's still drawing, right?
How can they be the same?
I don't care.
Go find someone.
I don't believe I can't find a person
who knows how to make sugar figures at Qulingguan.