[English subtitles are available]
[Wife Above All]
[Episode 9]
General Yun!
You can argue with my sister, but you can't...
Get out! Get out!
You're even occupying the room of our Qin Family?
Leave me alone.
I just want to get divorced peacefully,
but she insists on repudiating me.
Divorce?
With my sister's personality,
I think she'll issue a repudiation letter.
It's okay.
Let me try.
Yun,
let me tell you.
You're a matrilocal husband,
and something like arguing
with your wife
often happens.
Right?
As a matrilocal husband,
if you run away from home like this,
it's against the moral code for a husband.
Go away!
General Yun.
You're occupying someone else's room in the middle of the night.
You think that's reasonable, huh?
If you don't come out,
-I'll…
-Get lost!
I'll...
do something else.
I can't afford to offend those who are sad.
Drink it.
What is this?
I was going to give it to you after I came back to my room.
Now I'm worried that
it'll get cold. Drink it while it's still hot.
You just put it...
Don't think that I don't know it.
You didn't even take the medicine previously.
In the early years,
many people already checked
my broken leg.
Drinking herb soup or medicine isn't effective.
I know
my own condition.
Give it to...
Qin Chonglou.
We had a deal.
I'll treat your disease,
and you'll give me dividends.
I once saw that
you tried to stand up behind my back.
It means that this medicine was effective.
I thought that
we had a good time today,
so you wouldn't be so resistant.
I've already said this.
Will you drink it or not?
This medicine is very expensive.
I'll give it a try.
Come on.
All the medicine is...
I've finished drinking it.
Over there.
The warning didn't work.
Our men
were even hurt by Yun Zilong.
Maybe our men
were not able to assassinate him,
but they were very good at escaping.
They didn't leave any clue.
But I think when Yun Zilong
married into his wife's family,
he was quite unwilling to do it.
How come he's so eager
to protect Mo Jingyu now?
Actually,
Mo Xiang has more than one daughter.
I've heard that
he also dotes on
his youngest daughter Mo Banxia.
Why don't we
try to influence
the Qin Family?
The Qin Family?
Right.
Prince An.
His Majesty's second son, Prince An.
I'm going to announce His Majesty's verbal instruction.
This cripple doesn't need to kneel down.
His Majesty said that
Qin's Medicine Shop failed to examine the medicine carefully,
which almost let to a big disaster.
Therefore, from today onwards,
Qin's Medicine Shop
doesn't need to provide medicine to the palace anymore.
General.
Are you really going to give up taking revenge?
How could I forget
the revenge for the Yun Family?
Then where are we going now?
Are you going back to the Mo Family?
Have you really been touched by
Mo Xiang's concern for you?
Last night, I heard the conversation
between you and Mr. Qin
in the bathhouse.
You even dared to peep at me while I was taking a bath?
Do I
look like a coward?
I have my own strategies.
You don't understand.
I'm going back to the Mo Family this time
just in order to find the evidence.
As for her,
I won't
get close to her at all.
Let's go.
Come on, Miss. Look at this.
Just buy one.
Miss.
General.
Are we going back to the Mo Family?
We'll still go back to the Mo Family?
How can I
go back on my word?
Enough!
The imperial edict has been issued.
Stop talking about it.
No.
We've just
burned a batch of herbs.
If you return another batch,
even though our Qin Family
is rich,
we can't withstand such losses.
I actually
want to help you.
Go ahead.
However,
it depends on
whether you can return the favor.
Stop hiding.
Come out.
You...
Don't come over.
Don't come over!
Those are my younger sister's herbs.
Put the herbs down.
I'll explain to the government clearly
and ask them to punish you lightly.
That's her own business.
It has nothing to do with you.
Besides,
you cut off Young Master Chu’s route for gaining money.
Because of that,
I'm also hated by everyone now.
Let me tell you.
At worst,
I'll make you die with me. I...
Let me tell you.
My family's business is my business.
How dare you try to harm them?
Don't think too much.
I just didn't want to see
a commoner being bullied.
If you had not come,
I could've solved the problem myself.
I'll confess it.
I'll tell you everything.
Come on. Hold it for me.
Take him away for me.
Don't move!
We are Prince An's personal guards.
We passed by this place,
and found that Miss Mo had met a problem,
so we specially came to help her.
Since...
Miss Mo is fine,
we'll leave now.
Let's go!
[Side Story]
Such good herbs are all burnt?
That's right.
I've heard that Mr. Qin's
newlywed wife
ordered to do this personally.
I'm afraid
this Mrs. Qin will destroy the Qin Family.
Mr. Qin has married a bad wife.
Everyone,
all those who are present here today
can get a lucky bag.
Each bag contains some nutritious herbs.
Please often come to Qin's Medicine Shop
to buy herbs in the future.
Come on. This way.
Thank you.
What are you looking for?
Where's Lu Rong?
I've arranged a new job for him.
You've arranged a new job for him?
Lu Rong works for me.
But even you're my man now.