We have an important announcement
for all guests of the resort.
We're currently experiencing heavy rain
and high winds on the island today.
Due to the inclement weather,
all outdoor activities have been canceled.
For your safety
and the safety of your Pokémon,
please make your way
to the indoor facilities,
which remain open at this time.
Haru!
Look sharp and be careful!
Right!
The river's so high, it's gonna flood.
That's not good!
I'm gonna head upstream
and check on the Magikarp!
Haru, get these Pokémon
to the lobby as soon as you can!
Yeah! Right!
Be careful, okay?
Yeah, you too!
It's already flooding out of control.
It washed the bridge away!
Eevee!
I'm so sorry!
It's fine! Don't move! Stay there!
I could really use your help, Bulbasaur!
Closer. Just a little closer.
Eevee! Jump into my arms!
C'mon, you can do it!
Steady, Eevee!
Arcanine?
Hey, thank you!
Wait.
Do I know you?
You seem so familiar. Who are you?
Arcanine!
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. Thanks, I'm fine.
Kent?
Haru?
Haru…
Your hair's wet. You want a towel?
Oh, yeah.
Thanks, Kent.
I didn't know you were staying here.
Y'see, I was off when you arrived.
Ah, gotcha.
You know, I haven't seen you in a while.
Sorry about the whole river thing.
Nah.
I'm glad you're doing well.
Mommy! Do you know when
the rain's gonna stop?
Oh yeah. That guy's
totally her ex, no doubt.
For real?
Oh, Haru! She should
just stay away from that guy!
Calm down. It's not like you're her dad.
What's wrong, Psyduck?
I think Psyduck's a little jealous of
the ex getting all the attention.
Ya know…
I was really surprised.
I never thought you'd be
a concierge at a resort.
Who, me?
-But why not?
-C'mon, Haru.
Your life used to revolve
around high heels
and giving higher-pressure presentations.
And now…
I'm covered in mud.
Soaked and wearing sandals and sweatpants.
No, I…
-I'm sorry.
-No worries.
So…
I've been promoted to area manager.
Yeah? Congratulations!
Thanks so much!
I thought that a good way to celebrate
would be to come to this island.
To have a really good time with Arcanine.
That's great.
The weather will
definitely clear up tomorrow,
so I hope you have fun!
Thanks so much.
This is unreal!
I never thought Kent would ever come here!
So many feels!
These are from
our very first vacation together.
Psyduck, look!
What's that face for?
Yes, that's really what I looked like
when I was younger.
Kent seems like he's really grown up.
But also, he seems to look
incredibly tired.
You know what?
Since the rain stopped, let's make sure
Kent and Arcanine have the best day ever.
What's that cool-looking spot there?
That's the athletic ground, you see?
-Good morning everyone!
-Trainers and their Pokémon…
-Are you observing some rare Pokémon?
-Does it get busy?
Gotta go. Lots to do today
and I don't wanna fall behind.
Sealeo!
Hi!
You're too heavy. Please get up!
Look!
Bon appétit!
Thanks a lot.
It's really good!
You chased it away? Good job, Mudkip!
Drenched yet again!
I'm sorry.
It's a lot more hectic today than usual.
Yeah.
Oh, no… What's wrong?
Haru, I…
You must've been really unhappy back home.
So you had to get out.
I'm so sorry I didn't see that.
What?
-I don't--
-Haru!
Can you come help me with these berries?
Uh-huh! Sure thing!
I'll be right over!
Sorry! Duty calls! Be right back!
Okay.
Haru's such a wonderful employee
and has been doing quite well here.
I…
I'm sure she is.
Haru may seem awkward at times,
but she's very well-suited
for her concierge position.
The way she always puts
the needs of others first
is something I've never seen before.
Today she took care of Arcanine.
It's suffering from dry paws.
So she came to me early this morning
and asked for some cream.
Noticing certain things
Trainers might overlook
is one of Haru's most helpful qualities.
-And this one?
-That goes right over there.
-'Kay! Got it!
-Hold onto that.
The view from up here
is absolutely breathtaking!
Whoa!
I know, right? I love this island so much.
I was thinking,
maybe I was trying to get away
from everything when I first came here.
However, now it just feels like home.
Okay.
I understand.
Oh, yeah!
Our whole team put this slide together!
It was a huge job
and took us about two months to build,
but all of our guests love it,
especially the Pokémon!
Follow me, Arcanine!
Yeah! Let's go!
Wow…
Hey, you guys! Come on down!
Don't be scared! It's awesome!
All right, here I go.
Man, Haru sure is young at heart.
She's really acting like a kid.
Kent, you should see yourself right now!
What, I'm a joke to you?
Hey, watch where you're goin', Psyduck.
Finally.
I was hoping that
I could finally get you to laugh.
I'm happy
because you're wonderful.
Psyduck? What's wrong?
Wait! Where's Arcanine?
Dunno. I thought it was
right behind Psyduck.
What happened? Are ya stuck, Arcanine?
Hang tight. I'll pull ya out.
What's wrong?
Kent, no! Arcanine's paws, remember?
Sorry, Arcanine! I know!
I could use its Poké Ball for this!
Poké Ball… Where is it?
I can't find it! Where did I put it?
Could you help me, Psyduck?
I have an idea!
Arcanine!
Hey! It's gonna be okay!
Tickle, tickle…
You're okay!
Haru…
Arcanine!
I'm glad you're all right!
Everything okay? How's Arcanine?
Yeah, it seems just fine.
Haru… How did you do that?
Thought if I could get Arcanine to laugh,
it would just let go.
Just let go?
It's how I used to be.
I thought about how I acted back then.
Every day I just worked harder,
struggling from burnout.
I was desperately trying
to improve myself,
but I managed to somehow
fall behind instead.
It was rough. Who was I going to be
if I kept living like that?
It's like I was resisting something
and it was holding me back.
-Haru…
-I finally realized
that I had to stop fighting with myself.
Once I let go and relaxed,
I actually laughed until I cried.
Suddenly, I was able to
move forward without any effort.
Moving here helped a lot.
Working actually makes me happy.
No more stress.
And I'm able to work harder too.
Ya know what?
-I think that you're really cool, Haru.
-What?
No, no! You're making a joke, right?
I'm not cool!
Haru, look I…
Nothing.
This has been great.
And I feel like I'm recharged for work.
Good!
You got this!
What's up, Arcanine?
Haru…
I want to thank you.
Thank you too.
Psyduck, what was that for?
Love you too, Arcanine.
You're so funny, Psyduck!
Ready?
Onward to a brand-new day!
Sometimes there's a storm in the sky.
And sometimes
there's a storm in your heart.
But no matter what,
your strength will always help to guide
you through whatever life may bring.
Even though there are bound to be
bumps along the road,
as long as you never give up,
you can overcome any obstacle.
And our wonderful friends
that we've made along the way
always remind us that we're never alone.
Good work!
Thanks! Bring 'em over here!
I know, but I hope you had a good time.
-Bye bye!
-Hope to see you folks again soon!
Come back soon, okay?
I've made my decision.
I want to stay here
because this is my home.
I've looked for you for so long
I finally found you on this island
For us to be able to watch
This beautiful sunset together
When I was alone
When I was lonely
I thought of you
Please tell me and only me
The sound of your
Secret onomatopoeia
This is a healing island
A sparkling island
It's overflowing with love
You act shy and timid when
I press my cheek against yours
As we hug
And hold hands
My heart was always looking down
My head hung low
I may not have been unhappy
But I struggled under the weight of living
It's all in the past now
It blew away with the wind
The machinery of smiles
Fills my heart full
Overflowing, unable to contain it
Come to the healing island
An exciting island
Immerse yourself inside this fluffy love
Unravel the puzzle that will solve
This complicated maze
And open the door
With you on this healing island
A smooth island
A complicated love is fine
We don't have to become adults
We can stay forever
In this bright moratorium of youth
Onomatopoeia Island
A sparkling island
A fluffy island
A woolly island
A smooth island
A squishy island
I press my cheek against yours
As we hug
And hold hands
Subtitle translation by: Daisy Savage