Hey there! Everyone good?
Hold on, Sealeo! Wait a minute!
Yo!
Are you okay?
I'm… good… thanks.
What? The ship's not leaving?
No. One of the crew is leaving next week,
unfortunately,
and they can't find a replacement in time.
Maybe they should've made it a priority
to hire some new staff by now.
And we're also short-handed.
True enough.
-Is Sealeo around anywhere?
-Wait, Sealeo!
Come back!
Where're ya goin'?!
Just look at that energy!
Hey, Haru! Alisa!
I'm beggin' you, help!
-Wait!
-All right, all right.
Stop! Come back!
Pansage! Panpour!
Pansear! I'm countin' on you!
Let's go!
Sealeo, stop! Don't move!
Calm down. Good Sealeo.
Sorry, Sealeo is causing you
so much trouble. I know it's a lot.
That's fine. No problem, Uncle Dan!
-Uncle Dan!
Back when I was a tiny little dude,
my uncle here watched over me.
We always loved to ride the gnarly waves
on his sick boat!
You have a boat?
Of course!
I used to be a fisherman a while back.
So cool!
I remember that Uncle Dan was super tough!
A real powerful
and strong-lookin' kinda guy!
And when I was rude,
he would get so mad,
you could hear him
throughout the entire neighborhood!
What?
No way! I can't believe that!
Sure. Go get it!
Nice catch, Sealeo!
All right, all right.
Sealeo, that's enough. Calm down.
Sealeo really loves you, Dan.
Ya know, Sealeo was just a Spheal
when we floated into each other's lives.
I was a young fisherman back then.
I was out at sea, fishing
on my boat as usual, when suddenly,
a Spheal that was swimming by
hopped right onto my boat.
I kept trying to return the Pokémon
to the sea,
but each time I did,
it would leap back onto the boat.
I wondered if this poor Spheal was lonely
and just needed some company.
It was very friendly,
so I quickly grew attached to it.
So I decided,
that maybe I should be Spheal's Trainer.
The two of us have been inseparable ever
since. It eventually evolved into Sealeo.
That's amazing Sealeo! Congrats!
I'm impressed, Uncle Dan!
It's a challenge. You never realize
how huge a Spheal will get.
How's Sealeo at home?
You have an apartment don't you?
-Do you live close to the sea at all?
-No…
Unfortunately, my son and his wife
insisted I live near them.
I said all right, but it's tough to manage
a Sealeo instead of a Spheal.
Pokémon sizes can be different
when they evolve.
So then, is Sealeo
in its Poké Ball all the time?
I can only let Sealeo out
in a nearby park occasionally.
Looks like Sealeo's a little overexcited,
since it never has enough space
for playing or swimming outside.
But now, I'm afraid Sealeo's causing
trouble around here for everyone else.
Don't you worry!
On this island, our goal is to make sure
the Pokémon are having
as much fun as they'd like!
Have a ton of fun today, Dedenne!
Frozen goodies!
Okay, Dan! Ready when you are!
Wow!
Look at that!
Your Sealeo
is having a wonderful time today!
Oh!
I haven't seen Sealeo this happy
in a very long time.
How long have you and Sealeo
known each other, Dan?
For about fifteen years now.
I remember how small it used to be
when it was a wee baby Spheal.
It was so cute waddling around
on its short little legs
and it rolled up happily
whenever I came home.
Back then… I was surprised it gave me
so much happiness.
POKÉMON CONCIERGE
Oh, Tyler. Hi.
Why are you calling me at this hour?
Yeah. Uh-huh. What?
All right.
I see. Yes.
Could you keep a look out
just in case he returns?
I can't find him,
and his room's cleaned out.
I'm afraid he's not in the lobby
or outside on the terrace either.
But why?
I'm stumped.
He just left Sealeo here.
Where in the world could he have gone?
Did we look behind this pool
or this tent though?
No. We can try to look there.
Hey, Tyler. Try along the river.
-Tyler!
-Uh-huh!
Sorry!
I'll uh…
I'll have another look
down by the waterfall.
Hang on! I'll join you!
Sealeo, wait!
Tyler, wait!
I have an idea where Dan is.
Do you think he might be on the ship?
What?
Don't worry, I'll head there now!
The ship's gonna leave soon,
so I gotta hurry!
Look! There he is!
Dan, wait!
Dan, please!
But why?
Hey, Sealeo, wait!
Attention, passengers.
-We've stopped temporarily
-Mommy, Mommy!
-for a safety check.
-Look at that Sealeo,
-what's the matter with it?
-Once we're finished,
we'll resume our course.
In the meantime,
-thank you for your patience.
-Excuse me. Coming through.
Sorry, please excuse me.
Sealeo, no!
Get away from the ship. It's dangerous!
Go back to the harbor!
Attention, passengers.
We must return to the Pokémon Resort.
We apologize
for any inconvenience this may cause.
Sealeo, what's going on?
Sorry.
Forgive me.
Why, Dan? You just…
Please, Uncle.
What was your plan?
Were you trying to abandon Sealeo here?
Ms. Watanabe.
No, I would never dream of such a thing.
Leaving your Pokémon behind
is the very definition of "abandoned."
May I ask
why you felt the need to leave it?
Do you know how difficult it can be
to take care of a Pokémon this big?
I just can't keep up with it anymore.
Believe me, I wish I could.
Pokémon can evolve at any time.
And they usually become a lot bigger.
If you weren't prepared to handle this,
then you never should've had one
in the first place.
Right.
But Uncle…
Tyler, wait!
Haru, don't.
Tyler would always speak highly of you
and say how proud he was
to be your nephew.
So brave, and always helping others.
He looked up to you and admired you.
I'm sorry for causing trouble.
You've always been
a really great role model, Uncle.
I never thought you'd walk away
from something so important.
Now, I'm not so sure.
Yeah, I'm disappointed in myself too.
I wanna do what's right.
It was okay when Sealeo was a Spheal.
But when it evolved, everything changed.
And I became so anxious about the future
and what could possibly happen to us.
Why?
Well it's gonna keep getting bigger
and bigger for sure.
It's still young.
Could even evolve into Walrein one day.
I guess I thought Sealeo
would be much better off living here.
Especially if that happens.
I mean, just look at all the space
and freedom it could have to play.
Enough! That's just a selfish excuse!
Tyler.
You always said when I was a kid
to never make any excuses!
But look who's making one.
Please tell me the truth.
Do you really wanna give up Sealeo?
No, I would never wanna do that.
But how? Even if I find a place
that has more space,
I know Sealeo would be
a lot happier outside.
I truly only have Sealeo's best interests
at heart.
Okay.
I get it now. You're right.
Sorry, Ms. Watanabe! I'm begging you!
Please allow Sealeo to stay here.
Tyler.
I'm sorry. Please, Ms. Watanabe!
You're right! Uncle Dan shouldn't have
left Sealeo here without telling us!
But that's not Sealeo's fault.
Please consider it.
Looking after a Sealeo
is not going to be a piece of cake.
I'll take responsibility for it, ma'am!
You can't handle more.
I don't want you to neglect
your work schedule.
Your responsibilities
are that of a concierge first.
I can help Tyler watch Sealeo.
Give us a chance. It won't be a problem
if we just work together!
Alisa.
Haru, please tell me what you think.
Me? I uh…
I can help too.
However,
I dunno if it's the right thing to do.
I don't…
To be separated from Dan like that…
Haru.
Having Sealeo stay
while Dan has to go back home,
would that be okay?
Is that really the best option
we can come up with?
Would they both be happy?
You're right.
Would Sealeo and Dan
want to live like that?
Very well, then.
Sealeo can stay here
at the Pokémon Resort.
I've seen how well it gets along
with the other Pokémon staying here.
They find it quite entertaining
and friendly.
Really? Thank you very much!
It can stay only on one condition.
Right. Yes, I'll do whatever you want.
Well, Dan…
Would you like to possibly work here?
You can work here and spend
as much time as you want with Sealeo.
But hold on a minute…
How can I work here after all of the
horrible things I put you all through?
Yes, it's true. What you did
was unacceptable.
However,
you did what you thought was right,
because you love your Pokémon
unconditionally.
It seems to me
that your personality is very suitable
for working with all the Pokémon here.
What a neat trick, Sealeo!
Look at you go!
Sorry. Sorry, my friend.
Ms. Watanabe, I can't thank you enough.
-Ms. Watanabe.
-Ms. Watanabe!
You're the best ever!
Everyone!
I'm looking forward to working here!
Yo! Let's go out and play!
For Sealeo!
Show 'em how it's done!
Subtitle translation by: Daisy Savage