Sorry, babe,
it's just not working out. So, bye.
Last week, on Saturday,
my boyfriend of six and a half years
broke up with me in a text message.
The next day, Sunday,
I wore my favorite shoes
and immediately stepped in gum.
On Monday,
I was late for a vital presentation.
On Tuesday, my work bestie quit.
Wednesday,
I trimmed my eyebrows all wrong.
Thursday, I spent three hours
making curry, and it sucked.
Friday, my important presentation failed.
And on Sunday,
I stepped in gum again!
And because of that,
I am now here.
Hey, Daddy, look! It's a bunch of Wingull!
You can see the island!
Come on, let's get going!
The Pokémon Resort…
I can't believe I'm actually here!
A Bulbasaur!
Huh? Is that for me?
Thanks so much!
So you're the new employee?
Thank you for traveling so far
to get here!
Oh, sorry, do you work here?
Excuse me,
I'm going to start working here today.
My name is Haru.
I'm Ms. Watanabe.
Ms. Haru, welcome to the Pokémon Resort.
Thank you so much.
The Pokémon are
really staying here as guests.
See you afterwards, Metagross!
As you can see,
people and Pokémon can enjoy
the resort together or on their own.
We also have Pokémon on staff.
And sometimes…
A Wooper?
There are also wild Pokémon who call
the resort home. This Wooper, for example.
Around here, our motto is "Pokémon First."
And so, our job
is to take care of these Pokémon
and ensure they enjoy the resort.
In other words,
you'll be the Pokémon concierge.
A concierge, huh?
-Wow!
-Wait up!
What is this?!
What's going on?
Rattata?
That's enough.
Furret, no running near the pool.
Shall I take you somewhere
with a bit more room?
It's also a concierge's job
to keep our guests safe.
Now then, I know you've just arrived
but I've got a very important job for you.
Uh, right!
Then today, you'll stay
and enjoy the resort as a guest.
Wait. As a guest?
I'm supposed to work here…
Yes, that's right!
Please make yourself at home.
Right…
Oh no, am I being tested here?
Whoa!
-I think I'll have this!
-Hey, I want to try those lessons!
Hey! Over there!
Why don't you come and give it a try?
Nice to meet you.
It's my first day of work today--
Yeah, you're Haru, right?
My name is Tyler. Sanitation.
And fitness lessons, just for fun.
Nice to meet you!
Yes…
Wh-Who are these Pokémon?
They're on the staff with me.
You could call them my right-hand Pokémon.
They can be real pranksters,
so you'd better watch out.
Yeah?
So, I'll be--
Yeah! You'll be doing it, right?
Excuse me?
Oh no!
Aren't you glad you warmed up first?
Come and see us again!
I also teach swimming,
wakeboarding, and yoga!
Right…
Need a way to get around?
Those orange scooters
are totally free to use.
Hurry up! I'm leaving without you…
Wait for us!
I've never been on one of these before!
That being said,
that guy should look out for newbies
like me, but he was not helpful.
It really is a Pokémon paradise!
All right! Just like that!
Excuse me…
Hello, my name is Haru!
Today is my very first day.
Nice to meet you!
My name is Alisa.
I work here part-time every summer.
Hey there.
Yes, hi, it's so nice to--
Huh? Part time?
Mudkip!
Are you their Trainer?
Yeah.
They just started following me around.
Did you really?
You're so cute!
It only does that when it's really happy.
So… What's up?
Well, today is my first day.
And I have no idea
what I'm supposed to be doing.
Do what you want.
You're supposed to be a guest today, no?
I mean…
That's what I was told to do, but…
I'm feeling a lot of pressure right now.
Am I going to get a lecture?
You come with me.
Is she going to rough me up
behind the gym?
Yeah, I guess that'll do.
In here, Pokémon can get
fancy, too, right?
Basic services start off
with a simple trim.
But our guests also love a new fur-style,
and a cute new outfit
can make them extra happy, too.
Still, this kind of thing
is all part of the job.
Oh…
Hey! Lunch is almost ready!
Huh? We get free meals here?
Tyler's cooking.
It's better than you'd think.
Beautiful blue sky…
Beautiful blue ocean…
And a tasty lunch amid the sea breeze.
I'm in paradise!
That was really great!
The Pokémon Resort is the best!
It's the first time I've felt so relaxed.
Excuse me.
I was told I could get a massage here…?
Yes.
Please come right this way.
Huh? Ms. Watanabe, it's your job?
That's right.
I'm so skilled I can make
any Pokémon fall asleep with a touch.
Yeah, but maybe… I don't know…
Just leave it to me!
You know… I managed to meet
some of the other staff earlier…
They're all pretty interesting, right?
Yeah. They're definitely unique…
And I noticed
they both had
Pokémon of their own with them.
That's right.
You naturally become friends,
and then you're inseparable.
I'm sure there'll be
a Pokémon here for you, too.
That sounds so nice…
Ms. Haru?
Oh, no! This is bad.
I was way too relaxed!
And I fell asleep
in front of my supervisor!
I've got to make up for it.
Did you sleep well last night?
I guess…
So then…
What did you think of it all?
Could you tell me about your day?
Here it is!
What's this?
Right! I built a report
on my activities yesterday
and drafted some
personal work policies for myself.
We know the Pokémon Resort gives
a luxurious experience, so the--
Hold on.
As much as I appreciate
your data compilation,
honestly, I was hoping for
a different kind of answer.
S-So sorry!
My presentation was inadequate.
I'll try again!
Say, Ms. Haru…
How did yesterday go?
When you ask me "how"…
I can't possibly know
the right answer to this!
Ms. Haru? Are you all right?
No… It was just super funny…
What's funny?
The Pokémon here are doing
what they want and having fun,
and when I saw that, I realized
how silly all my problems have been.
Recently, I've had
a series of stressful incidents.
And it made me wonder,
what is the point of my life?
But this place popped those bad feelings
just like a balloon, and it was so fun!
Oh… I'm sorry!
Here I'm a professional,
but I'm talking like a toddler…
No, that is exactly what I wanted.
Huh?
It's about having fun,
and now you understand.
This here is proof
that you are a concierge.
The rule is,
you have to wear it while working.
Aside from that, there are no other rules.
Here.
Thanks…
So then, what are my duties
as a concierge?
Well, I have one request.
Choose a Pokémon, and before the sun sets,
I want you to make the Pokémon feel
the same way that you do.
This job is impossible!
I didn't want to let her see it,
but I have no idea what I'm supposed
to do to complete this task.
What do I do?
A Psyduck?