[Subtitles in the making and will be available soon]
Let's go! Let's go!
#
A new wish challenge begins again.
We need to buy ingredients
in groups.
They bought a lot.
They bought so many things.
We'd better follow our principle
we'll try our best.
Which group do you want to eat?
Pick your own food, please.
OK. Come on.
Our fourth wish challenge
It's a badminton game.
to get the tool to play badminton.
Don't run.
What are you doing?
You are mine.
How can I call this?
Get in.
Let's go.
One.
Yes.
A: &
Ywa7ij
What is this
What is this?
What?
Don't talk.
I'm not filming today. I'm leaving.
Good morning.
Today is the second day of team building.
A new day
A new wish challenge begins again
Before the challenge begins,
let's divide them into three, three, two
into three, three, two.
Three groups.
Same.
It should be the same group.
The tallest person in our team is together.
Today's wish challenge
is still related to your profession.
Yes.
rich life experience
It makes actors
to increase gradually.
He transforms into old men and women
Kind cotton iron
and complete the challenge of the dragon catching.
The Dragon King is here.
Three groups of players draw a word respectively.
as the opening phrase for shopping catching a dragon.
South American white and shrimp.
Pineapple.
Peanuts.
Start counting when you get off.
60 minutes.
Members of each group are shopping in the market.
Ginger.
Ginger sugar.
Lastly, the food bought by the dragon
for other teams.
The longest team
can choose one group
and enjoy the food.
The last one will be punished.
The amount for each group is 200 won.
Sir, may I ask
Can we repeat our words?
We can't buy things that repeat.
No matter what you choose for others,
you have to catch the dragon to the longest.
The longest way to choose. Right.
I'll definitely take care of Jacky.
He lost all day yesterday.
Let's make him work hard today.
What's in your bag?
Take a bottle.
So many Chunzhen yogurt.
Of course.
It's hot.
It's really good for thirst
Try it.
The fruit fragrance is so strong.
And the ingredients are very simple.
It has strong blueberry fragrance.
Do you feel fresh?
Cheers.
Here we go.
Where are you going?
Fishery.
Find a fish.
Let's go to the fruit first.
You three are here, right?
The whole one, right?
What about us?
Seafood.
I saw
I saw it.
Let's go.
Shrimp.
Do you have shrimp?
Is this right?
Look at this.
How much is one?
We'll buy one.
We'll just buy one.
Buy more.
Thank you.
Shrimp.
Let's find a good one.
Shrimp pancake.
Biscuits.
Biscuits
Where do you buy shrimp pancakes?
That restaurant
Shrimp pancakes need to go to the restaurant
Do you have shrimp pancakes?
Yes.
Buy a bag
After buying this
Biscuits
What are you doing?
It's okay to dry chili.
Chili
Beef white.
Biscuits first.
Then dry and spicy.
And white.
Do you have cookies?
Yes, here.
I don't want a box. I only want one, okay?
Sure.
Dried chili.
Give me one.
Geng Bai.
Right?
This one.
One.
Just one.
We're still following our principle.
we should buy as much as we can.
Try the cheapest.
Sure.
Pineapple first.
Hello.
How much is the pineapple?
If you want one,
7 yuan per catty.
I want one for 7 yuan per catty.
OK.
Let's count the money.
18 yuan.
Can you give me a discount?
We're all northerners.
OK.
How about this?
and raise ten yuan.
Is it too much?
Okay.
Let me.
I'll carry it for you.
You'll bargain.
Okay, I'll bargain.
Pineapple, radish.
Then buy the radish first.
It's okay, auntie.
We'll take all three radish.
Nine yuan in total?
9 yuan.
Can you give me a discount?
I'll say a price.
For auspicious six yuan.
Eight yuan.
Eight, okay?
15 yuan for three catties.
Give me another discount.
12 yuan.
You're good at bargaining.
Thank you.
Wish you a good business.
Have a good business.
The tofu is over there.
This tofu
How much is this?
Six yuan a catty.
Let's take a bag first.
Are you from Sichuan?
We're all northerners.
Northerners?
Are you from Sichuan?
Fellow.
I'm from Chongqing.
Right?
I went to a university in Sichuan.
Well...
The next step is to bargain.
How much is this bag?
Two kilos and ten taels?
How much?
Give me 14 yuan.
14 yuan.
It's already cheap.
People from the same hometown are useful.
There are no peanuts.
We're fine. Let's take a look and think.
There must be.
Hello, auntie.
Where are the peanuts?
It's where we sell peanuts.
Do you want peanuts or...
Do you have peanuts?
Yes. Then...
Let me see which one.
Where?
Sure.
I like all of them.
How much is this?
This is 7 yuan per catty.
I can buy more from you.
Can you give me a discount?
This is the lowest price.
I can't buy a cheaper one.
Can it be cheaper?
Are you picking vegetables?
Help us chop it.
How much is this?
His is 26.
26. Make it thirty.
Let's make it thirty.
Liu Liu Da Shun, 16.
Liu Liu Da Shun is 26.
I'm determined not to take advantage of you.
Are you going to whip me?
Let's go.
And I'll buy ginger from you.
Ginger. Ginger.
Wait, think about it.
What's behind the Kang?
Kang
What?
Jiang Xuening.
Ginger tea.
Ginger sugar.
This is good.
Boss, do you have ginger sugar?
I have ginger and sugar.
There's no ginger sugar.
What should we do? Let's go.
Kang
I have a headache now.
We want to win.
Jiang Xuening.
I'm very anxious now.
Ask for help.
I don't know.
Please help me.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Do me a favor.
Just wait to lose.
What is it?
What's your name?
White coconut.
Gimbap
White coconut seaweed
Buy a white coconut.
Purple sugar blue.
Blueberry.
Plum pork.
Meat.
This is squid.
Five minutes left.
Five minutes countdown.
We don't care.
It doesn't matter.
We already won.
Let's see what they're buying.
Let me see.
Wang Xingyue.
Welcome eight guests.
I heard you are very good at the market.
Some people have received a lot.
Who is it?
Our team.
Absolutely our team.
No.
They have a lot.
We have a lot too, right?
We have a lot too.
We have different advantages.
Let's announce
the third place of food relay.
I'm nervous.
The third place of catching the dragon is
Liu Xiening and Jacky Qin.
always lose.
Now I'll announce the first place
The first place is...
Who is it?
Tell me.
White deer, Wang Xingyue, Ye Xiyue.
Congratulations.
Congratulations on getting the right to choose.
Which group
which group will you choose?
We choose our own.
Choose ourselves.
I followed the rules.
No.
No violation.
We can't break the rules.
The ingredients we bought
for the other team members.
You can't choose your own.
No.
Yes.
Fair and just.
Why?
Choose your own.
Please.
Pick your own one.
No.
No, I don't agree.
What is this meat?
Pig skin.
No.
Why did you buy a pot of ginger?
I don't know.
for something.
How about we
ally?
Just connect it.
Buy them
some bad food
so they can't eat.
Yes.
Okay.
Ginger.
And ginger.
This one
This is not good
Then the dishes may taste bad.
Buy more
What is the cheapest pork for pig
Five pieces of pork skin
Buy something bad.
and make them unable to eat.
Unfair.
I don't eat pork skin.
So we choose this.
Bai Lu, stop thinking about it.
Let's choose this one.
We can only choose this one.
We're really wolf whiskers in the market.
To win this game,
to win this game?
The white deer group chose
of Liu Xiening's group.
Because we can't choose our own food.
Liu Xiening's team got
Zhang Linghe's group.
Zhang Linghe's team got the food from White Deer Group.
Yes, we're yours anyway.
They can't choose their own.
I made a mistake.
Seriously.
Come on.
Come on, let's exchange.
I don't want yours.
What is this?
Pig skin.
How to eat this?
Come on.
The collagen.
Thank you, Zhang Linghe.
Zhou Dawei and Cui Shaoyang.
Thank you.
Why are you still holding a grudge against us?
No.
Thank you.
I mean thank you.
I mean
Thank you.
Let's enjoy
The fire is on.
You can eat now.
I don't need to cook.
It's raw.
This will cause diarrhea, right?
You didn't even buy any meat.
I really...
It's not us.
Ask them.
Why don't you buy some meat?
There's no meat.
Isn't it delicious?
You even put ginger in it.
Ginger is for detoxification.
It's okay
The fish is sliced
Good choice
Who bought this squid
Delicious
Squid is really delicious.
They're... They're...
Plum dried vegetables.
Cabbage.
I don't want to eat olive anymore.
I'm really good at making this.
Try it.
Is it okay?
Not bad.
Let's enjoy life.
We can only enjoy delicious food.
You need to apply the side of the noodles like this.
Like this
Then what? Like this.
Right in the middle first
You have to get the stuffing first.
Hold on.
Look.
First school is good. Not bad.
Let me show you.
It's good.
It's so delicious.
Babies.
Welcome to our lunch today.
Have a look.
This is provided by our White Deer Group.
super delicious dumplings.
The dumplings are too thin
I cooked it lightly.
I believe it melts in the mouth.
Have a dumpling.
Let me eat north in Sanya.
Let's go home, guys.
The dumplings are too thin.
Give me a dumpling.
Let me eat north in Sanya.
Let's go home, guys.
Mom, I'm home.
Very good.
I think their food
are better than ours.
Do you want a dumpling?
Do you want a dumpling
I made them.
I made dumplings for her
This is fried egg dumplings.
It's made. Look.
It's delicious.
Heart dumplings.
You two don't have meat.
I'll give you some meat.
We can give you some.
Okay?
We can share some with you.
It's okay.
Sure.
I’m happy.
Wang Xingyue, have some shrimp.
Don’t you like shrimp?
Give me some meat.
I can't take it anymore.
Eat.
I think it's good that we enjoy it.
It's about unity and friendship.
This is delicious.
Take more.
I want one.
Smells good.
I'm full.
You just enjoyed the delicious food.
Now,
we'll announce the punishment of the third place.
I heard you worked very hard
during filming.
With high temperature
wearing thick and thick clothes.
Our punishment is
in the high temperature of Sanya,
in Sanya.
Put on the coat.
Take a photo.
Now Liu Xiening and Jacky
put on your clothes.
Put it on.
Take care.
Remember to team up with me.
We may lose.
I've memorized it.
This is your
in your drama?
This is mine.
It's yours.
Okay.
It's cool.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We just want to show it.
Good.
You should look at the camera.
Y-7
YXATj
YXAZZ.
Please take your seats.
Next is our favorite
our favorite official box.
Please send your representatives
to draw three wishes.
Let them smoke.
They wear leather clothes to smoke.
Okay, I'll draw one first.
Then you do it.
He stabbed Wang Xingyue’s face.
Let me see.
I want to see Wang Xingyue’s abs.
I have a question.
Who was
our main player?
Am I always there
I've been eating.
Hurry up.
Here's your fan's wish.
Dawei, come and be my substitute.
Substitution.
Come, Dawei.
Let's show
of "Peace Like a Dream".
Wow, he's hard when he's not nervous.
Really.
Come on. Come on.
Dawei can do it.
One, two.
Substitution.
What about yours?
Just make Dawei's face into mine.
Dawei's body is really good.
Come on.
Princess.
It's your turn.
You've got the vibe.
Look.
Zhen.
Take a look.
Why are you blushing?
What's this sound?
What is this?
No, read it out.
I can't.
What's wrong?
Let me show you.
I can't read it.
Wow this
I want to see all boys show their abs.
Everyone, show your abs.
The crew has gone too far.
They arranged us to have this meal for lunch.
I want it.
This has to be high and low.
Sorry. Come on.
Come on.
I want to see.
I want to know
is this the only one?
Qing.
Actors' body and physical fitness
needs to match the character.
So let's test
the actors' results.
Open it.
Just try and see what's inside.
Wait.
Let's take a look.
I haven't called yet.
Let me do it.
Let me see.
Let me see this.
Dawei, this one.
This is mine.
This is good.
Right?
What are you doing?
You...
Girls look at you.
Gentlemen.
Hurry up, you five.
Hurry up.
I don't have it.
I don't have any.
Let me see.
You do this first.
Give me a light here.
Can I hit it from top to down?
I need a corridor lamp.
Round lamp.
Let me do it.
Who's the first?
I'll light it up for you.
I'm old.
The first one.
Come on, the first one.
Is low light OK?
Dawei.
Let Dawei show the last one.
Let him show us first.
It's okay.
The sooner you die, the sooner you come back to life.
Let me block it first.
Open it.
Okay, okay.
OK. OK.
I'll do the next one.
Three, two, one. Start.
Wow.
You first.
Cover it.
Me too.
It's okay. Come on.
Twist it.
Fold it.
Two pieces.
I want these two pieces.
Let's support him.
No matter what we do later, we'll be wow.
OK.
One, two, three.
Wow.
Okay, next.
I'm crazy.
Next.
Is it my turn?
Your turn.
Wrap it up.
Make a dent.
Show your clothes.
Lower line.
OK. Come on.
Squeeze like this.
Three, two, one. Come on.
I'm suffocating.
I can't.
Let me see the light first.
Okay. One, two, three.
Just hit it.
Is that your stomach?
It comes out.
Okay, thank you.
It was amazing.
It's amazing.
So
who will draw the third wish?
Didn't I just smoke?
Doesn't that count?
He wants the one in his hand.
Let me see this.
Let me see one.
Dawei, this one.
This is mine.
This is good.
I'll pretend to draw one.
I pretend to draw one.
I want to see Jiang Xuening choose to cover it once.
Please.
Look.
How can I...
What choice?
Let me help you.
Who are you playing?
He has to choose me.
Come on.
It shouldn't be like this.
Go over there.
Stand over there.
Come here.
Me?
This is not a choice yet.
This is abandoned, right?
Yes.
I'm leaving.
Bye.
Let's go.
Let's go. Cover.
I haven't acted yet.
What are you going to do?
I have to stop you.
Okay, come on.
Sorry, sir.
This time I have to choose
Lord Zhang.
Xue Ning.
I can't stop her.
Zhang Bao.
Take care.
What do you mean?
It's handover.
Okay?
Thank you for your wonderful performance.
Next I'll announce
the fourth wish challenge
in the show.
We know that badminton is
your favorite sports when filming.
Without a scene,
we'll play badminton.
What do we usually do tomorrow morning?
Tomorrow morning?
Let's play. Let's play.
Question mark.
Then go.
The point is we were too addicted.
As long as we don't work, we're done.
I have to take off my makeup for two hours.
So?
The sports challenge we're going to complete together
is the badminton game.
The two teams will compete for
the throne of Peace and Feather Ball.
I can finally make a splash.
This time our badminton game
are different props.
I knew it.
You won't refuse to give us the Internet cafe.
Just give us a beat.
It's scarier if he doesn't give us the ball.
How can we get props?
We will take the props
through an exercise.
See you at the beach later.
Let's change the scene.
Chunzhen Zhenzhen yogurt "Ten million Promises"
Shark breath.
What did you see in front?
Shark
I saw what scared us yesterday.
Our shark is very honest.
Next,
I'll announce the rules of Shark Breath.
On the beach, every shark
has badminton props.
The game is divided into four rounds.
Each team sends a member
to grab the props.
Take the chosen shark back to its starting point.
as a tool.
Three minutes per round.
Now we need to discuss
how to arrange the formation.
The first player not only needs to run fast,
He's going there.
I'll tell you after I've seen as much as I can.
Which one are you going next?
Yes.
The best.
Brother.
She has tied her shoelaces.
White Lu is good at running.
Is the first one OK?
Send our white deer first.
Xingyue.
Trust me.
Who is the first?
The two of us.
The first group.
Three minutes.
Start counting.
Come on.
Go!
L.
Go! Hurry!
Start.
Wang Xingyue, what are you doing?
Come on, Wang Xingyue.
You can’t be tempted by beauty.
Run!
Look, they've run away.
So annoying.
You are annoying.
Wang Xingyue is immersed in
being bewitched.
So we chose a good one.
Oh, no. Thank you.
Thank you. Dangerous.
You don't look right.
It's stiff.
This one.
It's not a big deal.
It's nothing.
Why is she still in the water?
The white deer asked her to go to the sea.
That's probably hard.
It's a badminton racket.
Maybe it's a badminton racket.
To the sea.
Wang Xingyue in the sea.
The one in the sea.
Wang Xingyue.
Let me show you this.
No.
Wang Xingyue, can you hear me?
Wait.
Let me see the note.
Do you have a note?
Let go of me!
The one in the sea.
Brother.
Do you have a note?
No.
What's the use of this?
Let's go.
The one in the sea.
In the sea.
Wang Xingyue.
There’s a racket in the sea.
This?
Let it out.
No.
It's okay.
Leave the next one to me.
I have slippers.
Bucket.
Your basket.
Wait.
Don't move.
Don't run!
Thanks for the bucket made by Danger.
Radio.
Xue Dingfei is a fan for heatstroke.
This won't do.
Jiang Xuening's pillow.
Let's go.
What is this?
Wang Xingyue, be a man.
What are you doing?
Wang Xingyue, don’t grab it.
What are we?
Feather racket.
Wow.
Oh my god.
What?
The badminton racket.
Is it a badminton racket?
The crew's old badminton racket.
The crew is old.
The broken badminton racket.
Wang Xingyue is off work.
Go back to the hotel.
I'll just grab one randomly.
What are you?
I caught the most useless one.
I'm a brush.
A brush.
What are you doing?
What did he bring back?
A brush.
And handkerchief.
Clothes.
What are you?
The brush to wipe her throat.
You really can't.
I was the first to take a basket.
What are you holding?
My badminton racket.
There's a badminton racket.
We are the old badminton paddles of the crew.
Okay, ready.
Take it easy.
Why are you still in the water?
The one in the sea.
That's probably hard.
Wang Xing, the one in the sea.
Come on!
Zhang Linghe, come on!
Zhang Linghe.
He's afraid of water.
Don't move.
Let me see.
Hold a fan.
Finished clapper.
It's you. Let's go.
You're awesome.
Come with me.
This way.
Let me have a look.
The ruler. Come on.
The script.
What about that one?
The ruler is not yours.
I just...
What about the one I just saw?
Is it your brother?
A fan.
Where's the wrap board?
The wrap board.
Tell me.
Where's the wrap board?
You guys are so bad.
Why did you run away?
Let's go.
You guys are so bad.
A ruler is fine too.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Don't go.
A basket?
Jiang Xuening's pillow.
What are you?
A ruler.
Ring.
The ruler is good.
It's hard for your team to win.
Your team's brush and ruler.
It doesn't matter. We win by technology.
Look how good I am.
Low.
I was the first to take a basket.
I'll do the next one.
Okay.
Basket.
Let's go.
Come on.
Dawei.
This is the fight between the royal family.
You want your sister to be successful.
He doesn't want to do that.
Brother.
Don't abandon me.
Run!
Are you okay?
Who is it?
He subdued him.
You don't have to.
Just bring it here.
It's a uniform.
Get up.
I'll carry you up.
I'm sorry.
What?
The sunscreen.
Stop!
Dawei.
Zhou Dawei.
It's wrong to call you here.
Wrong.
Basket.
You're smart.
This is...
Xue's comb. No.
Basket.
A fan to relieve heat.
No.
It's a wrap.
Clap.
This is good.
Let's go.
Okay?
Come with me.
Come here.
Let me see what it is.
Let me see.
What is it?
What?
What is a replica?
Which one is bigger?
What?
Go away.
Don't take mine.
What are you looking for?
Dawei can't bully girls.
Dawei.
It's okay.
What is this?
Don't take mine.
Countdown 30 seconds.
The plaque.
A plaque?
Do you still want me?
Let's go.
What are you?
Why did this shark come by itself?
The shark ran away.
Don't run!
What are you doing?
You're mine.
What is this?
The replica of Palace of Peace.
The plaque will kill you.
The cards of my Palace of Peace...
The plaque.
Like this.
Okay, plaque.
There's another planner.
Basket.
A basket full of chicken rice.
Okay.
I'm going to the sea to cool down.
I want to go too.
You have to take off your shoes.
Be careful.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm going crazy.
I'll fan you.
Don't go too deep.
What else?
What's better?
There's a script.
A script?
I'll look for it.
I want that planner.
Okay.
The last group, get ready.
Let's go.
What is this?
Paper.
Good.
Awesome.
You can do it.
We won.
Who is this?
Family bucket. Let's go.
Are you tired?
It's too hot.
I saved you, right?
I'll wait for you.
Just wait for me.
What?
The script?
I'm holding Xie Wei's family bucket.
This is awesome.
I wonder what this family bucket is.
I got a family bucket
Game over.
Gather around.
I don't want to go up.
Soon.
We'll take it off after this part.
Thank Jacky and Xiening.
You can take off your thick costumes.
Thank you.
You can pick up
your own badminton tools.
Your pillow is so small.
I thought it was this big.
This brush
It's strong.
This ball
will never break.
You don't know how heavy the badminton is.
You can't even swing this.
It's fine.
Definitely.
Thank you, my favorite family bucket.
You can hit me like this?
Add a point.
Xingyue, do you want to change this?
Take the corn with a brush.
Our crew's badminton racket
Even if it's shabby,
the thread should be complete.
Just make it up.
How to play this?
How to hit it?
You're not flexible.
What's the use of this?
This brush
I can't hit any of them.
They demolished the Palace of Peace.
Who allowed you
tear down my Palace of Peace?
Stop.
Where did he go?
He dropped his badminton racket.
I'm...
Are you proud?
That's too much.
Touch the net, touch the net.
Does this count?
Why not?
Okay, give them one.
Give them one!
Excuse me.
Don't play like this.
It's no fun.