♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 40=
Boss, the car is fine.
Okay.
Get ready to leave.
Laoliu,
you carry Jun.
Okay.
Peel.
Grab the injured policeman
and make the hostages
walk around us.
You guys get off the bus
back to back.
Then the snipers
won’t dare to shoot.
Grab one hostage,
so they won’t dare to
make a surprise attack.
Boss, what about you?
I’ll guard these two lovebirds.
I’ll get her.
You,
lead the way.
The hostages are too close
to them.
Group One can’t shoot.
Group Two can’t shoot either.
Roger that.
Put your hands behind your head.
Hold on.
Peel.
Come over.
Move on.
Slow down.
Put your hands behind your head!
Hurry up!
Stop!
You!
Get in there!
Big bro!
-Get in there!
-Big bro!
Sir, the kid is young.
Get in there!
Sir!
Go away!
Sir, the kid is young.
Get in there!
Sir!
Sir, please.
Get in!
Sir!
Get in now!
Get in!
Sir, please!
Sir!
Get in!
Get in now!
I...
Withdraw! Hurry up!
Come on!
Xing Kelei.
Doctor!
What’s wrong?
You can’t breathe?
Look at me.
I’m here.
The first aid kit.
He must have been
stabbed in the left lung.
That caused a leak in the alveoli
and a tension pneumothorax.
The saline bottle.
Use a tube to release the air.
The Infusion needle and tube.
Just a second.
Hang in there.
I can do it.
Just a second.
It will be all right.
You can do it.
Xing Kelei.
Doctor!
You are awake.
When did you wake up?
Why didn’t you call me?
Who are you?
Do you really not know who I am
or are you faking it?
Who am I?
Where am I?
Xing Kelei.
I am your mother.
Don’t laugh.
How can you still make a joke
even now?
It hurts. It hurts.
Don’t laugh.
You were stabbed.
What a fool.
How long have I been sleeping?
You were in a coma
for a day and a night.
Haven’t you slept since then?
I dare not sleep
when you were in a coma.
When I close my eyes,
I can’t stop picturing
that bad guy stabbing you.
I’m scared.
What are you doing?
I haven’t seen you for two years.
I want to know
if there is anything missing.
It’s okay.
They are still there.
Are you talking about
the fat on my belly?
-Do you miss me?
I miss you.
I know.
Look.
In this case,
you have saved me twice.
I only saved you once.
A drop of water in need,
shall be returned with a spring in deed.
Now I can only
offer myself to you.
Dr. Mi, just take me in.
I can take you in.
But you got hurt
to save me this time.
We are even.
Why have we
been through
so many trilling things
since we were together?
It’s like a movie.
Perhaps it’s because
you are a doctor
and I’m a policeman.
♪The gray city becomes dimmer♪
♪You look into the night
and get lonelier♪
♪The wings that keep flapping♪
Don’t think about it. Have some sleep.
I’m by your side.
♪The call of the wind
sounds like our bond♪
♪I stand by and watch carefully when you
hold on to it like a vulnerable kid♪
♪Who can make you♪
♪Be frank♪
♪Forgive me for whispering
beside your heart♪
♪How can I warm your wandering dream♪
Xing Kelei.
Why are you always so stupid?
You knew it was a knife
and you still stepped in front of me.
Don’t you know I just came back?
We haven’t met for two years.
How did it become like this
just as we met?
♪Can you not make your back♪
♪Look too sad♪
♪Forgive me for whispering
beside your heart♪
It’s the engagement ring you gave me.
♪I’m not afraid to fight for love♪
♪I don’t want to make it hard for you♪
Just wake up
and get better.
We are going to get married.
You promised to marry me.
♪Can you not make your back♪
♪Look too sad♪
How’s the injury of Kelei?
He is much better now.
He is alive and kicking.
He can do harm to the world again.
But the main victim is Mi Ka.
I heard that Mi Ka
took half a month’s leave
to stay with Kelei.
How do you think if I give Yi Qian
the coffee cup we just saw?
The coffee cup? Forget it.
I gave him one
for his birthday last year.
Who would have thought
the bachelor Yi Qian
chose a flash marriage.
It’s not just a flash marriage.
He’ll be a dad in half a year.
He did a good job in the overtaking.
Quite fast and impressive.
Whom did he overtake?
Don’t you know it?
I don’t know.
Let’s go to
the Civil Affairs Bureau tomorrow.
Why are we going there?
To get
a marriage certificate.
Dr. Shao.
I think you are really insincere
when you talk about
getting a marriage certificate.
And also the wedding ring.
You bought
the wedding ring
while taking a walk in the mall.
Now you are talking about
getting married
like having a meal.
Do you do everything
in a flash of inspiration?
We have known each other well
after all these years.
We don’t need those tricks.
I need them.
Are you serious about it?
You want a sense of ritual, right?
Okay. I can get down on one knee.
No problem.
What? A lot of people here.
It doesn’t matter.
Get up now.
I want you to marry me.
Get up.
Will you marry me or not?
All right, what else do you want?
Yi Qian likes red wine.
Buy him a red wine glass.
No more kneeling?
You...
I’ll be like this if you kneel again.
Pick one. They all seem good.
You choose one.
Is this a champagne glass?
Just this one.
Okay, they are all quite good.
This one suits him well.
Pay for it.
You have such a good taste.
You always choose the perfect one,
just like you chose me.
Yeah. It’s mainly because I chose
Dr. Shao.
We’ll go to
the Civil Affairs Bureau tomorrow.
(Outpatient)
(Jiangning Renxin Hospital)
Haven’t we seen each other
for a long time?
It wasn’t that long.
Just two years,
one month and three days.
When did you come back?
Yesterday.
Why didn’t you tell me?
I could have picked you up.
No need.
It’s not easy to ask for leave in ER.
Aren’t you afraid of Director Wei
eating you alive?
I’m not the person I used to be.
I am her competent assistant now.
She can’t do it without me.
Keep bragging.
How long are you
going to stay this time?
I don’t know.
It depends on whether
Renxin would accept me.
Are you going back to Renxin?
You won’t go back to school?
I’ve submitted the resume.
I’m waiting for the result.
You can make it.
You trust me that much?
I’ve always trusted you.
Good Places for Weekends.
Dear friends.
That’s our show
for today.
Next time Xia will take you
to find the Manchu Han Feast
in the alley.
Okay.
Okay?
We got it.
Xia!
We really like you!
We watch
your show every time.
Thank you.
Can we take a photo together?
Okay.
Thank you!
Where shall we...
How about there?
Right here.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Thank you, Xia!
Thank you. Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Xia.
Your personal driver is here.
Hurry up. Get it done for me.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
My husband!
It’s a public place.
Why are you so dramatic?
Am I dramatic?
I know how to behave
in a public place.
Otherwise...
Stop.
You’ve been talking the whole morning.
Have some water
to moisturize your throat.
Honey, you’re so nice.
Do me a favor
if you have nothing else to do later.
What do you need me to do?
Don’t ask about it.
You’ll know it when you are there.
All right.
I’m so tired.
I’ll give you a massage later.
Really?
Keep your words.
No problem.
What’s wrong?
Are you uncomfortable?
I...
Do you want to throw up?
All right.
I’m getting dizzy.
Put me down.
Put it there.
I’ll tidy it up.
Don’t move.
You just had the operation.
Come on, let me do it.
I’m glad
you can tidy yourself up.
I don’t expect you to do it for me.
I haven’t seen you
open this suitcase
since you came back.
But I still brought it back in one piece
from abroad.
It’s normal.
The suitcase
would also get airsick.
Exactly.
I’ll tidy it up.
How can it be so messy?
Let me do it.
What are you looking at?
What a virtuous man.
How are you going to reward me?
I...
I’ll play with you.
Just play with me?
In order to go abroad this time,
I haven’t taken one day off
in the last 18 months.
You should be my maid.
Be your maid?
Do you bear to let me do it?
Yes.
By the way,
why do you bring the soymilk machine?
Didn’t you say
the food abroad is not tasty?
I packed a lot food,
so I can cook for you over there.
Captain Xing, you are a must-have
for home or travel.
After this project,
I promise
I won’t leave you again.
Stop saying that. I don’t believe it.
You won’t fool me.
By the way,
I might need to
go back to the team later.
Come with me.
Why do you need to go back to the team?
There are a lot of procedures
to go through to go abroad.
Go by yourself.
Are you going or not?
No.
Going or not?
Why are you threatening me?
Change your clothes. Hurry up.
-Come on.
-No.
Why do you need me to go with you?
Hurry up.
Let’s go.
Where’s my ring?
Your ring...
-Where did you put it?
-I just...
I put it on the table
before I went to the bathroom.
The bathroom?
Could you drop it in the toilet?
I’ll go to check it.
Don’t.
We have no time for that. Let’s go.
It won’t be lost anyway.
It’s somewhere at home.
It’s really expensive.
Let’s go.
♪Spring brings warm sunshine♪
♪Cicadas sing on summer trees♪
♪A sea of flowers dance in the wind♪
♪Until the autumn rain pours down♪
♪And everything falls silent in winter♪
♪What a beautiful world♪
♪Every moment♪
♪I whisper it to you♪
♪That I’m still here♪
♪The secret of my happiness♪
♪Is to think of you♪
♪Even if I’m not by your side♪
♪I’ve never forgotten you♪
♪I whisper in your ear♪
♪That I’m still here♪
♪The sound of longing♪
♪Is the promise
That travels through time♪
♪With my deep love for you♪
♪I wait for you for eternity♪
♪I whisper it to you♪
♪That I’m still here♪
♪The secret of my happiness♪
♪Is to think of you♪
♪Even if I’m not by your side♪
♪I’ve never forgotten you♪
♪I whisper in your ear♪
♪That I’m still here♪
♪The sound of longing♪
♪Is the promise
That travels through time♪
♪With my deep love for you♪
♪I wait for you for eternity♪
Don’t you need to get something?
I didn’t bring the key.
I’ve asked someone to send it here.
Do you still remember this building?
(Climbing Building)
I would never forget it.
I think I’m the only trainee
who failed it.
You are.
Are you going to
laugh at me for the rest of my life?
No.
Stop laughing.
Didn’t you
overcome it later?
Look.
You even climbed on
such a dangerous truck.
That’s why I decided to
give you the certificate.
Thank you.
(Certificate of Completion Mi Ka)
I was thinking
why this girl is so stubborn?
How would she live a life in the future?
What do you mean?
I’m a doctor.
It’s my responsibility.
What’s more,
I got you by my side.
Did you fall in love with me
at that time?
What?
You heard me.
I really didn’t.
Do you dare to
go up again?
Are you asking me
to rappel down?
I’m wearing high heels.
I’m going to get you up there.
Let’s go.
Isn’t that the place
where Instructor Li taught me
how to rappel down?
Listen,
I saw everything
you two did here.
What did we
do here?
He taught you about the rope.
Look how
petty you are.
I wanted to
teach you by myself.
I was going to see you.
I didn’t expect
that brat to take a step ahead of me.
Have more.
The lamb chop is very nutritious.
Come on.
Thank you. Thank you.
Here.
Mr. Luo, have some too.
Dr. Mi.
You are really considerate.
The person who can be your boyfriend
must be really lucky.
That’s true.
Really. Really.
Then you used your power
for your private revenge.
You had a free combat with him
and kicked him down,
didn’t you?
He deserved it.
Besides,
you were not nice to me
at that time.
You didn’t treat me well either.
You were really strict with me.
You even made me cry.
You asked me to clean the toilet
and the bathroom.
I asked you to clean the bathroom
because I wanted to give you a reason
to take a shower.
Okay?
(Bathroom)
You don’t how nice I was to you.
What a fool.
So,
you kind of had a crush on me
at that time, right?
I guess.
What do you mean?
Take it as a yes.
Look there.
What?
The gate.
Do you remember
the time you ran to me
and hugged me?
You cried all night
without saying anything.
I didn’t cry all night.
Sometimes I feel helpless
and aggrieved
when it’s too stressful at work
or something goes wrong with the patient
but I can’t solve it.
I didn’t know what to do,
then I think
it would be nice
just to hug you
without saying anything.
You always
feel sad because of
other people’s illness.
But I like
the way you smile.
Every time when I go on a mission,
no matter how dangerous it is,
I can handle it calmly
when I think about your smile.
Therefore,
try to smile often.
Do you dare
to take a look over there?
Right now?
Right now,
I’m Captain Xing’s girlfriend.
I do.
(Dr. Mi Marry me)
You told me
that nothing good ever happened
since we’ve been together.
It turns out
you are right about it.
But for me,
it’s the happiest thing
in this world
to meet you.
I want to make
this happiness last.
I wonder
if this ring
and a handsome me
are enough to ask Dr. Mi
to let me be your husband.
Let me spend the rest
of your life with you.
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
Will you marry me?
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
I do.
♪Love by accident♪
♪Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me♪
♪That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪
I wonder,
what Captain Xing and Dr. Mi
are doing up there.
It has been a long time.
It’s cold in the heights.
I think the wind is quite strong.
It’s a good move.
I’ll use this move
when I marry
my husband.
What’s wrong?
No. No.
This way.
That one.
Put it over there.
Yeah.
Move this one.
Okay.
Look at this.
Do it as that one.
Yeah.
Great.
Move it back a little bit.
Move it back.
Put it here.
Is it all right?
Here.
Come on.
Is this okay?
Okay.
Make it face the front.
No, that won’t work.
Take a look.
Look.
It’s too romantic.
(Dr. Mi Marry me)
Withdraw.
Wenjing, we are almost finished.
Roger that.
They must be
really sweet now.
Well, aren’t we sweet?
Just so so.
What are you looking at?
Captain Xing.
This is a happy event.
Shouldn’t you
treat us to dinner?
Yeah, treat us to dinner.
What does it have anything
to do with you?
We’re leaving.
So stingy.
Look at him.
Captain Shu.
Didn’t he promise to
treat us to a meal?
He forgets loyalty when in love.
Honey.
You are off today.
Shouldn’t we go back
to my parents’ house for dinner?
Did you forget it?
I didn’t.
You must have forgotten it.
Let’s go to
have a meal together.
We... we are
going to play game
this afternoon, right?
-Let’s go.
-Yeah.
Let’s go. Let’s go.
Wait for me.
Zhuo Wenjing, let’s...
I also have an appointment.
Very good.
Let’s go to have something delicious.
Who do you have an appointment with?
I have an appointment!
I’ve always wanted to
take you here.
My parents weren’t around me
when I was young.
So, I don’t have
a deep understanding of family.
But every time I come here,
seeing all these lights
and the busy people
inside this city,
I’ll have
a special sense of belonging.
It turns out that there are
so many people
who are guarding us silently
in places we can’t see.
There are doctors like you.
Also firefighters.
Teachers.
Delivery guys.
And I
chose to be
a policeman.
But also because of my identity,
I feel
guilty in some ways.
Because I can’t
always put you first.
Are you willing to accept me
who is not entirely yours?
What else can I do
if I don’t want to accept it?
I can’t stop
liking you.
worrying about you.
We have no control over birth and death.
It’s like sometimes a doctor
can’t control
the result of an operation.
There are too many things
we can’t control.
Let’s just do our best.
I understand you.
I’m not the only one
you are to protect.
You are also to protect the whole city.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪