♪In such an unexpected way♪
♪I came across you♪
♪It was a romantic opportunity♪
♪When we exchanged faith♪
♪In the name of you and me♪
♪Youth starts quietly♪
♪Then you and I are together♪
♪Tired but excited we run along♪
♪Destiny is a mystery But I’m fearless♪
♪Because of you I never shrink back♪
♪In my hands hides my life♪
♪Keep it for me forever♪
♪Let’s be gentle to each other♪
♪My love Everything is precious♪
♪The world is noisy
But the future is promising♪
♪Because of you I expect more♪
♪Of a far-away world♪
=You Are My Hero=
=Episode 28=
What’s so shiny?
Sorry for drooling.
What’s wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Why am I so uncomfortable?
What’s wrong?
You are good at acting.
Considering
that you are my boyfriend,
even if you fake it,
I’ll still give you a massage.
-Okay, nice.
-Are you comfortable now?
Comfortable.
Looks like we’ve
come at a bad time.
That’s right.
Then we’re leaving.
Leave the soup.
You cooked the soup long enough.
Did you have a heart-to-heart talk?
Good friends never do that.
We only talked about cooking, all right?
What?
Don’t you have hands?
I have a girlfriend.
Why should I drink it by myself?
You are really like a baby now.
It’s sweet.
Have you felt
your brother’s love?
Are you jealous?
Just kidding.
Sit up straight. I’ll feed you.
I can’t do this.
I can’t stand it anymore.
I’ll become green-eyed with you.
Yeah, I got to go.
I’ll come to see you another day.
I am leaving.
Go ahead and leave.
I have no time for you.
Oh no.
I promised my friend
that I’ll track the entertainment news.
I’m going to be late.
Why there’s no taxi?
It’s not easy to get a taxi right now.
I shouldn’t have
sent the car for maintenance.
If you are in a hurry,
I can give you a ride.
Okay, thank you.
Let’s go.
What’s wrong? Are you okay?
Ba! Ba! Ba!
Sorry.
Sorry, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Ba!
I want to interview you!
Thank you.
It’s okay.
Stay! Don’t go!
Don’t go!
I’m done.
All right.
How is it? Did you get it?
Yeah, the angle is really good.
Thank you.
No problem. I only lifted a finger.
You did
lift a finger.
I got to go.
I have something to do tonight.
Me too.
I’ll treat you to dinner another day
to thank you.
It’s okay. No thanks necessary.
You are right.
No thanks necessary between us.
Bye.
♪The gray city becomes dimmer♪
♪You look into the night
and get lonelier♪
♪The wings that keep flapping♪
♪You sighed with your back to me♪
♪The call of the wind
sounds like our bond♪
♪I stand by and watch carefully when you
hold on to it like a vulnerable kid♪
♪Who can make you♪
♪Be frank♪
♪Forgive me for whispering
beside your heart♪
♪How can I warm your wandering dream♪
♪I’m not afraid to fight for love♪
♪I don’t want to make it hard for you♪
♪Forgive me for whispering
beside your heart♪
♪My hands are not brave enough♪
♪Even I♪
(Sender: Li Aixia)
♪Can you not make your back♪
♪Look too sad♪
♪The gray city becomes dimmer♪
♪You look into the night
and get lonelier♪
♪The wings that keep flapping♪
♪You sighed with your back to me♪
♪The call of the wind
sounds like our bond♪
♪I stand by and watch carefully when you
hold on to it like a vulnerable kid♪
(Besheen Liqueur)
♪Who can make you♪
♪Be frank♪
♪Forgive me for whispering
beside your heart♪
Come on.
This wine is really good.
Thank you, Auntie.
Come on.
I’m good.
Go ahead and drink.
Besheen mean your hearts.
Drink it
and you can understand
each other’s hearts.
How is it?
It’s good.
Drink it and you will have a soul bond
and be together forever.
♪Can you not make your back♪
♪Look too sad♪
Remember to eat.
Let me take it.
-It’s okay, Mom.
-Hello, Aunt.
Hello.
Don’t worry about me.
Don’t stay up late.
Don’t starve yourself.
-Have meals on time.
-I will.
Don’t forget it when you are busy.
I know.
Have you got everything packed?
Yeah.
Mi Ka is busy today.
She asked me to
wish you a safe journey.
Okay.
Well,
when you arrive at school,
you must take good care of yourself,
and have meals on time.
Don’t try too hard
and tire yourself out.
Don’t do that.
I’m leaving to study,
not to go to jail.
I didn’t have a chance
to choose my favorite subject.
Now I have a chance to study pathology.
It’s good.
Will Aunt be with you?
She just finished the operation.
I don’t want her to be too tired.
I just don’t want you to leave.
After you get there,
can I make a video call
or something else
when I want to talk to you?
As long as it doesn’t bother you.
I’ll be busy with my schoolwork.
But if you want to talk to me,
I can still
save some time for you.
It’s just that our time
is different and you might
need to stay up late.
It’s okay.
I can move my schedule to fit yours.
Well, I’ll get in the car.
Remember to contact me on WeChat.
Okay. Okay.
Mr. Shao.
Did you get Xing Kelei’s
test results?
Yes.
How is it?
I got good news
and bad news.
Which one do you want to hear first?
Are there any other problems?
The bad news is
Xing Kelei’s good days of
getting waited on hand and foot
are going to end.
You mean
he can be discharged?
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Your sense of humor is too scary.
I just want to make a joke
and see your reaction.
Listen,
although Xing Kelei
is ready to be discharged,
he can’t return to the team right away.
Considering
his job,
I suggest he rest at home
at least for one month.
Okay.
During this time,
he can do some
restorative exercise.
But don’t do it excessively.
Come back for examination
half a month later.
If there are symptoms of
nausea, dizziness or tinnitus,
come to the hospital right away.
Okay.
You are a doctor.
You need to keep an eye on him.
I will. Thank you, Mr. Shao.
But
I’m afraid he will act to be brave
and insist on going back to the team.
Can you talk to him for me?
Me?
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Shao.
Doctor.
I came from the county nearby.
My wife just gave birth
to our second child.
She had a headache
a few days after giving birth.
The left part of her body
can’t move these days.
And she can’t think clearly today.
Which department should we see?
The neurosurgery.
Where’s your wife?
Over there.
Dear!
Move!
Move! Move!
Be careful.
Turn.
-The family member should wait outside.
-Leave.
The family member can’t go in.
Wait outside.
Dear...
Is it ready?
Yes.
200 joules, get ready. Move.
Again.
Come on.
How is it?
Again.
The sinus rhythm is restored.
What’s the situation?
She is twenty-nine years old
and just gave birth to a second child.
There is weakness of the left limb
38 days later after the delivery.
She suffered from
unawareness for one day.
She came from a county nearby
and took a car to our hospital
which spent four hours.
Ventricular fibrillation
occurred ten minutes ago.
We just rescued her.
Do a CT
and an MRI.
Are you suspicious of
a cerebrovascular disease?
The possibility of
a cerebral hemorrhage is high.
Her symptoms are not mild.
Notify Mr. Shao to come down
for consultation.
Okay.
Did you see it?
She just nodded at you.
Are you sure it’s me?
Well done.
Excellent job.
Cavernous hemangioma
with bleeding on the right Pontine.
The bleeding is pressing against
the brain stem.
If it doesn’t stop,
it will lead to death.
Do you see it?
This tumor is on the surface
of the brachium pontis.
There is a chance for surgery, but...
It can be risky.
Is there any operating room available
this afternoon?
No.
We can only do the operation at night.
Then let’s do it tonight.
We can work overtime.
Okay, I will prepare it.
Go to thank the staff
of the operating room
and the anesthesiologist.
Okay, got it.
Thank you.
They have two children.
One is two-year-old.
The other is just one month old.
What?
Give it to me. Put it down.
Sit over there.
Sit down.
Let me pack it.
I hope you can
keep treating me in this way.
Then I can
sit all the time at home
like a lord.
No problem.
I can break your legs
and then you can sit forever.
Why are you talking
like my sister?
Isn’t this
your family culture?
Are you saying
you are more like my family member?
I’m willing to become one.
Oh my goodness.
Keyao.
The door is open. Behave yourselves.
Didn’t I tell you
not to pick me up?
Of course you don’t
want me to pick you up.
What a third wheel I am.
You are really not here to pick me up.
Well,
the operation was successful.
We should thank
the chief of surgery.
Yes.
We should thank him.
Mr. Shao just finished the consultation.
He should be in the office now.
Yeah?
Well,
I’ll go to say hello to him
and thank him.
Yeah. That’s right.
-Yes.
-Okay.
Well...
Go ahead,
I’ll leaving.
Take your time.
Okay.
Did I wake you up?
It’s okay.
I’m a little tired.
I just took a nap.
Do you have a troublesome case?
Kind of.
Brain stem hemorrhage.
The position of
the Cavernous hemangioma is not bad.
There is a chance for surgery.
But the postoperative symptoms
will be severe.
It’s rare for you to be nervous
before surgery.
I’m not nervous.
I’m just a little anxious.
Perhaps it’s because
she is a mother of two children.
One of her children
is only one month old.
When we were in college,
I remember you told me
that doctors can’t control
the life and death of patients.
You can only try your best.
I believe you.
Thank you.
What time is the operation?
Eight o’clock.
If you have time,
can you stay with me for a while?
Do you want a cup of coffee?
Unfortunately,
the ground coffee just ran out.
I brought some.
The peripheral brain tissue is icteric.
We are near the bleeding position.
I will start to
separate the tumor from the brain.
What’s the situation?
The heartbeat is only 30.
It gets normal. It’s 60 now.
It’s the brain stem reflex.
I’ll try to separate it
from another place.
The brain stem is a place
where transmitters
are most concentrated.
It’s like the bus of
the telecom bureau.
If you damage a little bit of it,
it will affect a large area.
Mr. Shao, let me wipe your sweat.
Do you see the tumor?
It’s like a mulberry.
A part of it protrudes
into the brain stem.
Change to the fine stripper.
Cotton.
Dr. Shao.
You are amazing.
Did you sleep well?
I...
I wasn’t sleeping.
You weren’t sleeping?
How many times I’ve told you
to not sleep in the car
with the engine on?
It’s dangerous.
I have a cold.
I got a little sleepy
after taking cold medicine.
You can sleep in the dorm.
But I’m waiting for you.
Don’t do this next time.
I’m worried about you.
Okay?
How many times I’ve told you
to not sleep in the car
with the engine on?
It’s dangerous.
I kept the sunroof open.
Why do you stay in the car?
I have a cold
and I was having a rest.
How is the operation?
Very successful.
Well,
I’m hungry.
Hungry?
The restaurants nearby
are all closed
right now.
How about going to my office
and I’ll make noodles for you?
Okay.
Let’s go.
Let it boil for a while.
Any drinks?
Black coffee.
It’s too late for black coffee.
I have a
conference call from Germany later.
Wait for me.
It’s a little hot, be careful.
Why does it smell like this?
Didn’t you say that you have a cold?
Don’t drink black coffee. Have this.
I’m fine.
Follow the doctor’s advice.
The Vienna Symphony Orchestra
will come here to perform next week.
I can get some tickets.
Do you want to go together?
If I’m not too busy
next week,
we can go together.
Okay.
It should be done.
Isn’t the heat too high?
The...
The stuffing is coming out.
Can you not meddle?
Go to sit over there.
Is this still glutinous rice ball?
It’s obviously soup now.
Did you put the fermented
glutinous rice in it?
Stop telling me what to do.
Just wait for it.
Here you are.
Sesame glutinous rice balls
in rice wine.
I saw the sesame.
Where are the glutinous rice balls?
Here.
Isn’t this just a bowl of sesame paste?
-Very good.
-You don’t like it?
It’s good. It’s good.
It’s not bad to have some watery food.
You just had surgery.
It’s good for your stomach.
It’s difficult for you
to digest
too much solid food.
Can you get one more bowl?
Doesn’t it mean
that I need to wash one more bowl?
That makes sense.
Right?
Yes.
Give it to me.
All right.
You have this.
I won’t.
Do you think I’m fat?
No. When did I ever say that?
Just now.
No. Not at all.
Hurry up and eat.
Let me feed you.
No.
You just got discharged,
I should help you eat
-and take care of you.
-This is too sweet.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Eat it.
Then you will also have a fat belly.
Are you feeding a pig?
And we will be a better match.
All right.
Are you finished?
Let me do it.
It has been many days
after the surgery.
I should use my hands now. Come on.
Don’t.
You will have a lot of chances
to express yourself in the future.
Let me do it.
In the future?
When? How long?
Well,
a long time later.
Go to watch TV.
All right.
Nice shot!
Stop watching it.
You just had the operation.
You can’t get too excited.
I’ll get more excited
if you don’t let me see it.
Oh my god.
They won!
Excellent!
Nice shot!
Look! Look!
Look.
They won! They won!
They won!
Can you stop shaking me?
Sorry.
How do you get more excited than I do?
I’m sorry. You are not dizzy, right?
I am not dizzy.
Are you dizzy?
Watch the game.
I am fine.
You are not uncomfortable, right?
I’m not uncomfortable.
I’m so happy.
Nice shot!
Come on.
I mean,
can you be more reliable?
You promised her.
Why should I do it for you?
No.
It’s really not my fault.
I thought I would have time today
when I promised her.
Who knows Luo Ting
would change shift with me?
I need to be on duty today.
Where’s Luo Ting?
Luo Ting has guests today.
He can’t leave.
Just go there for me.
My cousin is still waiting.
She said
she will pay
two hundred yuan for an hour.
Just teach her something about
self-defense,
taekwondo,
and Sanda.
That’s all you need to teach her.
You...
She was followed by a pervert recently.
Do you bear to see
an innocent young girl
be persecuted?
I mean, which cousin is she?
Why haven’t I heard of her before?
I have a lot of cousins.
Which one do you want to know?
All right, I’ve arrived.
I mean,
when did Xia
become your cousin?
Why are you here?
Where’s Li Nian?
He has something else to do.
He asked me to come.
Do you want to learn taekwondo?
Someone is stalking you?
I’m not sure.
There is a pervert
who called himself my fan.
He sends me a lot of disgusting messages
on Weibo every day.
The important thing is
he even knows my home address.
It’s too scary.
Just call the police.
I don’t think they will make it a case.
He hasn’t made any move.
I don’t know who he is.
Can the police
protect me 24 hours a day?
I guess he is just
a perverted internet troll.
I told Li Nian
that I will pay him 200 yuan
for an hour.
No need.
Of course I won’t pay you.
We are good friends.
For a beginner like you,
I will teach you about
free sparring first.
Draw your right leg back.
Shift all the weight backwards.
Protect your cheeks with your hands.
The cheek is
the most vulnerable part of the face.
Your opponent can easily
knockout you through it.
Use your waist to drive your thighs.
I’ll show it again.
I’ll do it slowly this time.
Use your waist.
Kick.
Withdraw.
One, two, three.
Try again.
Next we will practice front kick.
Still the same way to do it.
But the direction is different.
Look how I do it.
Try to do it. Come on.
One, two, three, kick.
Take it back.
One two three, kick.
One of the most vulnerable parts
of the human body is the throat.
Another place is...
Well...
Well,
let’s have a practice.
Come on. Try it.
Won’t I kick you?
It’s okay. Empty your mind.
Kick here.
Okay?
One, two, three.
Nice.
Harder!
Kick here.
Sorry.
I’m fine.
Let’s do it again.
Come on.
Harder.
One, two, three. Go.
Nice.
Great.
Your tendons are not relaxed enough.
So you can’t use your strength well
and kick the target accurately.
Let me stretch your tendons.
It hurts.
Don’t you often do yoga?
I never stretched here.
Come on, relax.
Hang on.
Your knees.
Well...
Sorry.
I didn’t do it on purpose.
You need to stretch your legs...
Come on, get up first.
I think
we’ve practiced enough today.
Okay.
I’ll leave.
Well...
Just take it as a goodbye kiss
between good friends.
Don’t worry about it.
♪Give you my missing♪
♪It’s easy to bear♪
♪I recall your words in my mind♪
♪It’s difficult to understand♪
♪The sky is bluer♪
♪The moon is more beautiful♪
♪I’m so insensible to feel it♪
♪I don’t understand your love♪
♪I will persist with smile♪
♪Change the result♪
♪Exchange our minds♪
♪Love can be ignited♪
♪Like messy palette♪
♪Various colors♪
♪Describes the appearance of♪
♪Happiness♪
Good night.
♪Suddenly clear persist♪
♪Change the result♪
♪Exchange our minds♪
♪Love can be ignited♪
♪Like messy palette♪
♪Various colors♪
♪Describes the appearance of♪
♪Happiness♪
I’m leaving.
Bye.
She is lucky indeed.
She can be saved from
such a severe cerebral hemorrhage.
It’s just that her right hand
will have functional impairment.
The people from the Orthopedics said
that it’s hard for her to fully recover.
I heard that she is
a piano player.
Isn’t there such a saying
that you never know
whether tomorrow
or accident will come first?
How is Xing Kelei doing?
I think he is recovering well.
Good.
Remember you still have some days off.
You can take a rest.
Thank you, Mr. Shao.
I will handle it.
Wenbo.
Well, I’ll go back tomorrow
and get trained with you.
So soon?
Don’t you need to rest
for a few more days?
I’ve rested for a long time.
Training
is the best rest for me.
That’s the deal.
I’m back!
I’ll hang up.
It’s late.
I have a patient
with serious brain trauma.
I just finished the operation.
I heard you say on the phone
that you are going back to the team?
Well,
the combat is about to start.
I’ve rested for a long time.
It’s time to go back.
Why don’t you
discuss with me first?
Well,
I’m discussing with you now.
You’ve called the team
and packed your stuff.
Is that discussing with me?
You’re notifying me.
Are you angry?
No.
You are angry.
It’s all on your face.
Mr. Shao said
you’d better rest for
more than one month.
Why don’t you listen to him?
I think I’m good now.
Look at my body.
Look,
I can even lift you up.
Look.
Here we go.
Put me down.
I’m serious now.
I will take care of
my own body.
I’m worried.
Once you start training,
you won’t remember what Mr. Shao said
and you won’t remember me.
It’s for sure that I won’t remember him.
But I will remember you.
You are not serious at all.
I will always remember
that you worry about me.
Let me go.
All right?
If anything goes wrong,
you must let me know
in the first time.
Don’t make me worry.
I’m really concerned.
Captain Hao.
You’re back.
Next training program
is ten-meter shooting!
March forward!
Captain Shu.
Captain Hao, please check the target!
Return of the king.
It’s impressive.
Salute!
Welcome Captain Xing back!
This shooting practice is creative.
It can be kept.
Down!
How are you?
You have rested for three weeks.
Your hands must be itchy now.
You know me the best.
I haven’t used it for a long time.
I guess it’s mad at me.
Don’t worry, take your time.
You still got time.
You will get the feeling back
a few days later.
We will eat out tonight.
My treat!
Yes!
Dismiss!
If anything goes wrong,
you must let me know in the first time.
Don’t make me worry.
Come in.
Captain Xing.
You are here.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I haven’t seen you since the meal.
Well, Captain Xing,
why don’t we
play a game together
tonight?
I’m not playing.
I need to make a call.
All right.
Do what you got to do.
(Xing Kelei)
Hello.
Are you busy?
I’m watching the surgery video.
How are you feeling now?
I want to ask you something.
Go ahead.
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
When I shot today,
somehow my hands
started to shake.
Could it be
the aftereffect of the surgery?
Pituitary adenoma won’t
cause hands shaking generally.
Do you have
any other discomforts?
What about your eyes?
My eyes are fine.
Only my hands are shaking.
The operation was definitely successful.
Well,
come to the hospital tomorrow.
I’ll take you
to see Mr. Shao.
All right.
I’ll hang up.
Hold on.
I’m happy that you tell me directly
about your problem
and you didn’t carry it on your own.
I promised you.
Of course I will keep my words.
Promise me, relax, okay?
Okay, don’t worry.
Good night.
(Outpatient)
The MRI shows no problem.
Which means your pituitary tumor...
Mi Ka knows it,
it’s a technical term,
you don’t know it.
To put it in a simple way,
the bad thing
in your head
has been removed.
But my hands
are still shaking when I hold a gun.
The brain is very complicated.
It controls a lot of nerves.
Although it’s very unlikely,
I still can’t give you
a 100% guarantee
that this operation
hasn’t affected
your upper limbs nerves at all.
Is there any way
to improve it?
Relax and have more rest.
Let’s observe it for a while.
Is there any rehabilitation training
or something like that?
You can do finger push-up
or lift dumbbells.
It will help your recover
the strength of your upper limbs,
especially your hands.
But I suggest you do it moderately.
After all,
you haven’t fully recovered yet.
Can he go back to the team
for training?
He can.
But make sure to do it
gradually without rushing.
Give your body
some time to adapt to it.
I know
you are in a hurry.
But there is a saying
that two steps forward, one step back.
Sometimes your mental
anxiety or tensions
can also make your hands shake.
Don’t pay too much attention
to your hands.
They will be fine in a while.
Got it.
Thank you, Mr. Shao.
♪My future is a fantasy♪
♪Where there is a sea of stars♪
♪And I will see you
Walking towards me♪
♪I feel lonely in the crowd♪
♪Watching the stories of others♪
♪And wondering
Who will conquer my heart♪
♪Because of an incident♪
♪My life has changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I won’t harm anyone♪
♪I won’t have any regrets♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I am the one
You can count on♪
♪I didn’t expect I would
Come across you♪
♪And thus my life changed♪
♪It’s true that from now on♪
♪I know what is hope♪
♪I’m afraid that I may hurt you♪
♪Yet by the casual twist of fate♪
♪All beautiful imaginations♪
♪Have become real in a sudden♪
♪It seems I do have
Something to look forward to♪
♪Love comes too soon♪
♪To let me realize♪
♪How should I make you
Feel safe with it♪
♪I hope I’m the one you can count on
Do you think the same as me♪
♪Love by accident
Yet it’s more than an accident♪
♪Love indeed exists♪
♪I think you’re free to love♪
♪Until I know it’s me
That can’t be separated from you♪
♪I rely on you too much♪
♪You’re bound to be my dearest♪