(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
I found out which school
Baek Jin Ju went to...
and looked through
all their yearbooks.
I even found a picture of her.
Nicely done.
Right,
- but something here is weird.
- How so?
Check out her photo.
Her photo?
(Personal Profile)
(Hanbit High School
62nd Graduation Ceremony)
See? It's weird, right?
It's not just me.
Hey, go on ahead. I've got to run.
Is this what you found
on Dr. Baek's daughter?
Yes,
but here's the thing.
Just brace yourself.
Dr. Baek's daughter and Min Jun
were dating.
What could be more shocking
than that?
Tell me about it.
But believe me, there's something
even more unbelievable.
- An official statement...
- That's absolutely...
- will be released shortly.
- not true.
We're still looking into it.
- About the design being stolen?
- What?
- Absolutely not.
- The accusation...
is completely false.
At BIT Life,
we prioritize design ethics
above all else.
Please avoid
any speculative reporting.
This is the new symbol for BIT Life.
And this is the design I created.
Now, take a look.
This is plagiarism.
They stole it from me,
just an unknown designer.
My design book...
is gone.
(BIT Life, President Kim Myung Hui)
The legal team came up with
the quickest way to handle this.
Instead of a false accusation,
they're suggesting
we turn it into a real one.
A real one?
Chloe stole that design,
which made Adele Group
an innocent victim.
We pin all the blame...
on Chloe.
Sir, with all due respect...
Besides,
she was disposable from the start.
She got cocky and started
ignoring me, the chairman.
Such an insolent little thing.
This is a chance to show everyone
how ruthless Adele Group can be.
We'll make a scapegoat out of Chloe,
and then just start over.
Why the hesitation?
Will you let this project die...
and get yourself
kicked out of the company?
Don't overthink it.
Make a decision right now.
Please just give me one day.
If I can't find another solution
within 24 hours,
I'll do as you wish, sir.
Why should we waste
even a single day?
I'm the one who recruited Chloe.
If she's forced out
because of a scandal,
I'll be the one held responsible
in the end.
Right now, protecting Chloe
is how I protect myself.
You have until tomorrow morning.
If you don't have
another solution by then,
Chloe's design will be declared
plagiarized. That's that.
Why is there a photo of Chloe?
(Personal Profile: Baek Jin Ju)
(Hanbit High School
62nd graduation ceremony)
Why does Dr. Baek's daughter...
look like Chloe?
(Security Office)
Once we prove
your design book was stolen,
you'll be able to clear your name.
But what if...
I actually plagiarized it?
You never once suspected
I was lying?
Never.
From the moment I met you,
I knew you were an honest person.
You're open and direct
in everything you do.
That's what makes you so confident.
That's who Chloe is, isn't it?
You're right.
That's the kind of person Chloe is.
It's ready.
I reviewed the footage...
from when you left
through this morning.
Right here.
I noticed something suspicious.
No way.
Their face is perfectly hidden.
They clearly came in here
planning to steal something.
They knew exactly where
the CCTV cameras were,
and they came in right before
security locked the main entrance.
I think it's someone
on the task force.
I was thinking the same thing.
Then it could be Manager So,
Assistant Manager Heo,
- or...
- Choi Yu Na.
(Head of Division 1, Park Min Jun)
(Personal Profile: Baek Jin Ju)
They don't just look alike.
Their faces are identical.
That's why when Chloe first came
to Adele, everyone...
And that's why Min Jun...
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Chloe.
(Brand Consultant Chloe Lee,
Let Chloe Lee shape Adele's future.)
Just this once,
may I hold you?
Why is Min Jun...
How...
can they look so identical?
I delivered the baby myself,
so I know she doesn't have a twin.
You haven't shown your face
this whole time,
and I'm sure other companies
have made you better offers.
So why are you
showing yourself now...
and partnering with Adele Group?
Because of Temi Bio.
No way.
What if...
she survived?
You called me in
because of that accusation, didn't you?
If by some miracle she survived...
and came back for revenge...
If she returned
with a different identity,
just like I did 30 years ago...
Why are you looking at me like that?
Don't tell me...
you actually believe those lies
and suspect me.
Suspect you?
Given the circumstances,
I have every reason
to be suspicious.
Please don't jump to conclusions.
We confirmed...
that her design book was taken
from the task force office.
Once we identify the thief
from the CCTV footage,
the truth will come out.
Let's ask the police to investigate
and release the CCTV footage.
Whatever it takes,
I want to clear my name.
If it was stolen
from the task force office,
it was probably an inside job.
Yes, that's what
the evidence suggests.
If an employee is involved,
we have to handle this carefully.
If we bring in the police...
without a clear suspect
or any evidence,
it will throw the company
into chaos.
I see.
So the Adele Group comes before
clearing my name.
I've sent Secretary Jung...
to track down
the person accusing you.
Once we find him and get the facts,
we'll contact the police
and the press.
I just want to be certain
before we act.
If you're innocent,
you can wait one day.
You don't seriously suspect Chloe,
do you?
Do you trust Chloe completely?
Is it because...
she looks exactly like Baek Jin Ju?
I wonder if we're thinking...
the same thing.
What if we're both suspecting
the same person?
Then how about...
we cause a little trouble?
I'm more interested in the truth
than playing games.
Will you help me?
That "definitive answer"
you wanted from Chloe...
was really about figuring out
if she's Baek Jin Ju, wasn't it?
Yes. But...
As you might have guessed,
Chloe isn't Jin Ju.
Choi Yu Na even had Chloe
and James' DNA tested.
Ms. Choi had their DNA tested?
She was probably afraid
I'd think Chloe was Jin Ju,
so she made sure I knew for certain.
Are you sure about the test results?
I checked them myself.
The whole Jin Ju thing aside,
Chloe would never plagiarize.
She really wants
to find the real culprit...
and prove her innocence,
so please help her.
You've already concluded
that she's just Chloe.
But is she really?
Could she be Baek Jin Ju,
back for revenge...
under a different identity?
(Team Leader, Choi Yu Na)
Have you checked the CCTV footage?
Yes. We have footage of someone
stealing the design book.
Does that mean
you identified the thief?
Their face was covered
by a hoodie and a mask,
so you can't really make it out.
Does that mean
they'll get away with this?
The video won't help much,
but we have another angle.
My dad is going to catch the person
who made that broadcast.
He said he's already...
identified the man.
Goodness.
Your dad's very resourceful.
We'll catch him and ask
where he got the design book.
Then it's game over.
President Kim also...
sent Secretary Jung to track him,
so he'll be caught soon.
Choi Yu Na. I knew it was you.
I thought you'd stand up
to Park Tae Ho...
after your wedding was canceled.
But was petty revenge
really your first move?
Or are you just too scared
to stand up to Chairman Park?
Why isn't he answering his phone?
The person you have called...
What do you think you're doing?
Give it back.
Your call history
could be useful evidence.
You can hide your face,
but you can't hide your guilt.
Once they catch your accomplice,
everything you've done
will come to light.
What nonsense is this?
What does this have to do with me?
Where's your proof?
Fine. Go ahead and try to hide
your guilt and the evidence.
If the chairman finds out
you've damaged Adele's reputation,
he might just kick you out.
If you don't have the guts
to stand up to Chairman Park,
I'll force you into a corner
where you have no other choice.
If you don't want to be thrown away
by Park Tae Ho,
you'd better fight back
with everything you've got.
Hey!
Hey, get back here!
You punk!
- Hey!
- Stop right there!
Get back here. Hey, you punk!
Hey!
You're dead if I catch you.
I'm going to tear you
limb from limb, you punk!
I told you to stop!
What...
Darn it.
Gosh, that hurts.
My gosh.
What were you thinking,
falling over like that?
I'm sorry about that.
That little punk.
We almost had him.
I'm sorry.
Did you hurt yourself when you fell?
I'm fine.
Your arm seems okay.
Let me check your leg.
Stop it.
Seriously.
Stop groping him.
I was just checking to see
if he hurt his leg.
That doesn't mean
you can just feel up a guy's leg.
Hold on a second.
Are you two close enough
to be this touchy-feely?
Of course we are.
What?
We're comrades
who just fought side by side.
He's hurt,
so it's my duty to look after him.
Right, sure.
Your duty.
I'm against all of it.
This duty, the touching, and him.
Get up already.
- What?
- I said get up.
- Come on.
- But...
- Not with my sister.
- It's not like that.
- Get going.
- But....
You're here.
I heard you got hurt,
so I stopped by.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
But I'm the reason he got away.
I feel terrible for Chloe,
and I sincerely apologize, ma'am.
Not at all.
I'm just glad
you weren't seriously hurt.
Your daughter and your family
would've been worried sick.
Wait a second.
A daughter? So you're married?
Seriously? You were feeling up
a married man's leg?
No. Gosh, no.
I'm not. I'm as single as it gets.
Chloe's mother and I...
split up...
a very long time ago,
and I've been raising Chloe
all on my own...
ever since.
I see.
It must've been tough.
You have no idea.
Running a business in the US
and raising a kid.
Just thinking back on it...
I'm laughing,
but I feel like I'm crying.
Thinking back...
Unbelievable.
To learn more about Chloe,
I'll need information
about her life in the US.
Looks like our dear chairman
has lost his appetite.
I'm not surprised.
That witch Kim Myung Hui
brought in some delinquent...
and dragged the Adele Group's reputation
through the mud.
What? Did all that talk
make you lose your appetite?
That's disgusting.
How can I eat when you're talking
nonsense at the dinner table?
- Darn it.
- My, was I doing that?
I was just trying
to lighten your mood.
If you're going to lie,
at least make it believable.
You don't know your head
from your feet.
All you care about is the thrill
of talking trash about others.
It was just a joke.
Nothing to bite my head off over.
Besides, you let that Kim Myung Hui
get away with causing a huge mess.
See?
Because you just let her do
whatever she wants,
she's practically beaming
despite all the trouble she's caused.
It's so irritating.
If you're that jealous,
then go live in the annex.
I'll be sure to leave you alone
for the rest of your life.
Hold on a second.
You think I'm jealous?
I've never been jealous of her.
I'm not bad-looking myself.
Unbelievable.
Darn it.
There's something...
I'd like to say.
Let me get this straight.
You haven't caught the thief
who stole the design book...
or the person
who's falsely accusing Chloe,
but I'm supposed to let her be?
Chloe saw the CCTV footage herself,
and she has a copy.
If she's treated unfairly,
she'll release the footage...
and even go after Adele.
So what's your solution?
We'll request a police investigation
and disclose the facts to the media.
So you're going to advertise
that there's a thief inside Adele?
This will show that Adele
handles wrongdoing decisively,
even when it's an insider,
and that we're a fair
and honest company.
It'll also help restore our image,
which was damaged
by the false accusation.
Manager Kang.
Use our police contacts
to request an investigation.
The thief inside Adele...
and the scumbag
who made false accusations.
Round them all up.
My gosh!
Keep it down.
Seriously.
Ms. Oh, why are you
always up to no good?
Does everything your mother does
look bad to you?
I was keeping an eye on things,
worried that the witch
would win his favor...
and get off scotch-free.
It's "scot-free," not "scotch-free."
Scot, scotch, whatever.
I don't see the difference.
Ms. Oh, wait.
Come on, you need to learn
to read the room.
Right. Read the room.
Know when to get involved
and when not to.
Now is the time to get involved.
Absolutely not.
You should stay out of it.
It's not your fight,
even if President Kim
is getting her way.
Because this wasn't...
President Kim's fault
in the first place.
What do you mean by that?
The person
who stole the design book...
and orchestrated
the false accusation?
It was Choi Yu Na.
I'm absolutely certain.
Ms. Choi?
What does she have to do with this?
It seems
her engagement's been called off,
so she's lashing out.
Once
the police investigation begins,
she'll totally lose it out of fear.
So, Ms. Oh,
how about you sit this one out?
Don't jump in
and cause trouble again. Got it?
So, this is all Ms. Choi's doing?
Then this is a game
I can't possibly sit out.
Hey, bring the car around.
What?
Where could we be going
at this hour?
I've reported it to the chairman.
The police are going
to start an investigation.
Okay. I'll pass that along to Chloe.
Thank you...
for your help.
I was wondering...
about Baek Jin Ju.
Is there anything
unique about her...
that sets her apart from Chloe?
I've already given up on the idea...
that Chloe could be Jin Ju.
There's no need
to concern yourself with it.
(Personal Profile: Baek Jin Ju)
Hello, ma'am.
I know it's been a while.
I was hoping
to meet briefly tomorrow.
Would that be possible?
Secretary Jung, wait.
What happened to the person
who made the false accusation?
Well, the thing is,
we almost had him, but he got away.
If James hadn't fallen over,
we would've caught him for sure.
So you went with Chloe's father?
We just happened to meet
in front of the suspect's house.
I'm impressed with his intel.
I wish I could say the same
about his stamina.
Could you give me
the suspect's address?
Hey. What are you doing here?
I heard the false accuser got away,
so I stopped by.
Looks like you beat me to it.
Aren't you scared
being here all by yourself?
No.
I'm not the least bit scared
of some liar.
If I really get caught...
You can't just show up like this!
You!
This is all your fault.
You said no one would find out.
You said everything would be fine.
I got doxxed, and now people
are showing up at my house.
How are you going to fix this?
Fix what?
Why should I fix anything?
You were more than happy
to do it for money.
So you're just going to bail on me?
If I get caught
by the police or Adele,
do you think
you'll get away scot-free?
So just...
lay low.
Then pay up.
Everything costs money
when you're in hiding.
A hundred grand should do it.
What, 100,000 dollars?
Move fast,
or become a jobless criminal.
You don't want me
to say "screw this," get caught,
and spill everything.
Well, now.
Looks like I stumbled upon
something interesting.
(Pearl in Red)
I'm hoping to get information
about these two people.
If Baek Jin Ju has returned
as Chloe,
- is that something to celebrate...
- Dad!
or fear?
You shouldn't be so cocky
when I'm the one holding your leash.
Are you threatening me?
Do you still not get it?
You have to pay
for stepping so far out of line.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)