(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 77)
Here...
This pearl...
will prove
that Oh Jung Ran committed murder.
The blood on this...
most likely belongs
to the killer too.
So that's why...
That's why...
Myung Hui was holding onto this
until the very end.
Myung Hui,
I'm sorry...
it took me so long.
Dad, are you watching?
The pearl in red that you protected
is finally where it belongs.
How will you use this evidence?
I'm going to hold a press conference
and reveal Oh Jung Ran's murder.
The case involving
her boss at Munhwadang...
was dropped
due to a lack of evidence.
But I'm a witness in this case
and the evidence is solid,
so she won't be able to bury it.
A legal conviction
might be difficult,
but she'll be branded a murderer.
Park Tae Ho and Park Hyun Jun...
will abandon Oh Jung Ran.
I'll make sure she's shut out
of the Adele Group she coveted so much.
She's the kind of person
who'd kill to have it all.
If she loses everything
because of her greed,
her life will become a nightmare.
If you hold a press conference,
you'll have to reveal
that Kim Myung Hui is dead...
and that you're
actually Kim Dan Hui.
That's been my plan for seven years.
It'll be a difficult conversation
with Min Jun,
but it's time I dealt
with my own unfinished business.
Then we need to do a DNA test first.
We need to prove the blood
on the pearl is Oh Jung Ran's.
For the test,
we'll need a strand of her hair.
Right. I'll go get it right now.
If it were up to me,
I wouldn't let you go.
Park Tae Ho will be
on your case again.
She's right.
Chairman Park will continue
to be suspicious.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
I have no reason to be afraid
of his suspicions anymore.
In fact, I'm going to make him
even more suspicious.
Hyun Jun's working late.
He must be busy preparing
for the vice president position.
Just tell him to end things
with Chloe already.
- Where's Kim Myung Hui?
- I'll check the annex.
Leave her.
She's a criminal
who was banished to the annex.
Who cares if she eats or not?
Mrs. Ok,
from now on,
I won't be dining with the chairman.
- What?
- What do you think you're doing?
You banished me to the annex
because you don't trust me.
How do you know
I won't poison you during dinner?
Exactly. Her eyes are full of venom.
She should be kicked...
out of the house,
not just sent to the annex.
- Sit down now!
- No.
Have your meal with Jung Ran,
the one you trust and cherish.
Wait. Did you
just speak casually to me?
Oh Jung Ran. Your days sitting
in that chair are numbered.
Kim Myung Hui!
You say
I'm unfairly suspicious of you,
but the evidence is this clear.
- Evidence?
- That's right.
Evidence that you went
to Eunhwa Trading.
Evidence that you conspired
with Chloe to report me.
You knew about Park Cheol Su,
Eunhwa Trading, and...
You mean evidence
that I know about your wrongdoings.
Seven years ago,
the CEO of Temi Bio,
Baek Jun Gi,
was murdered
in a staged car accident.
Yes, I know about that.
Oh Jung Ran told me about it
when she ordered me to leave you.
But instead,
I chose to stand by your side.
Exactly.
- Because you had to use me.
- No.
Because you...
are Min Jun's father.
It wasn't easy to turn a blind eye
to your crime.
Still, I saved you from Oh Jung Ran,
and for Min Jun's sake,
I wanted to be your perfect wife.
Then...
Then what about Chloe?
Oh Jung Ran was the one
who told Chloe about Park Cheol Su.
She must've told Chloe
to dig up dirt on you.
Chloe found Eunhwa Trading...
without knowing what happened
seven years ago,
so I stopped her
before she could find out.
No.
I won't fall for your lies anymore.
I've explained everything.
Whether I'm lying
or telling the truth...
is for you to judge.
Park Tae Ho.
You'll be tormented,
torn between lies and the truth.
You won't know who to trust
and will be suspicious of everyone.
That endless suspicion
will be another prison for you.
What did you two talk about?
What's wrong?
Afraid I might've told him
your son's secret?
Didn't I tell you I'd ruin
your son's life if you talked?
You don't have to be so scared.
I have plenty of ways
to deal with you...
without using your son's secret.
Stubbornly proud until the end.
Now that Park Tae Ho is
suspicious of Kim Myung Hui,
this is my chance to strike.
This is my opportunity...
to prove myself
as president of the bio division.
Gosh, that's good.
So refreshing.
Don't tell me
you're feeling so good...
because you kicked Chloe out,
are you?
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm working this hard
for Hyun Jun's sake.
What does washing your hair
have to do with Hyun Jun?
I tested the product myself
so I can be...
a better president
of the bio division.
So, do you like it?
I washed my hair
with the ionized water,
and this thing is a miracle.
You just switch from alkaline mode
to this one to finish up.
All the stress from Kim Myung Hui
and Butler Ok...
left my scalp irritated,
but now it feels refreshed
and clean.
Your hair does look better.
If it's that good,
our Hyun Jun should try it.
I told you not to say
"our Hyun Jun."
Darn it, watch your mouth.
Our Hyun Jun must be under
a lot of stress too.
(Bion Tech)
There's already some in the jug.
Why did you come in person?
I said I'd send it with Yoon Jung.
I was worried about you.
Didn't Chairman Park
give you a hard time?
I'm sure he's having
just as hard a time.
I fanned his suspicions...
so he won't be able to trust
Oh Jung Ran either.
I told him you have nothing
to do with this,
so you should react the same way.
Yes, for now I've told him...
that Oh Jung Ran sent me
to Eunhwa Trading.
Good. And this.
I've gathered everything needed
for the DNA test.
Okay, I'll request it right away.
You should get back inside
before anyone gets suspicious.
Okay. Be careful.
Those two...
But why?
Yu Na.
Can I ask you something?
Honey, please.
Can't you ask her after we eat?
You're dying to know too.
I'm not the only one wondering
how she got the lawsuit dropped...
and got her job back.
I got Chairman Park released
from police custody.
- What?
- How did you manage that?
Your daughter is more capable
than you think.
I'm in the same boat
as Chairman Park now,
and things are only going
to get better for me.
Goodness.
Do you really have to be
in the same boat as him?
Tell me about it.
How can you trust a man
who even made a bomb?
Didn't you hear me?
I got him out of police custody.
The bomb allegation...
- isn't true.
- But still...
You should cut ties
with that family.
What are you talking about?
That's a family we need to stay
on good terms with.
You're not still trying...
to marry Park Min Jun, are you?
Honey, come on.
She'd have to be out of her mind
to still think that.
Just you wait. I have a plan.
- Oh dear.
- What?
I mean, that girl.
Honestly, I can't...
Can you believe this
from our one and only daughter?
How can she be such a headache?
She's a real handful.
You're telling me.
Some "precious child"
she turned out to be.
No kidding.
Honestly.
So, did you send it for analysis?
Yes, we should have...
- the results tomorrow.
- Right.
For President Kim Myung Hui,
this will be a perfect opportunity
to get rid of Oh Jung Ran.
Kim Dan Hui can finally live
as her true self.
You also need to go back
to being Jin Ju soon.
I really am...
a troublesome daughter, aren't I?
You are.
I finally understand why people say
children make you age.
It was the same
when our Chloe went missing.
The truth is,
I'm afraid I might fail
to protect you too.
Even at my age,
it scares me sometimes.
From seven years ago until now,
you've always protected me.
James, you've been both my rock...
and a father to me.
That's right.
And you're my daughter.
Yes, Dad.
So please cheer up.
Got it.
It seems President Kim...
is putting pressure on Park Tae Ho
in her own way.
Now it's our turn.
I've already got something prepared.
(Adele)
What, a formal notice?
Yes. JKL Partners sent
a formal notice stating...
that they're filing a lawsuit
to recover the penalty fee.
They're claiming a penalty
of 100 million dollars.
Who do they think they're suing?
- Get the legal team in here now.
- Yes, sir.
(Chairman Park Tae Ho)
Father, you must have been
quite surprised.
My father said he was going to sue,
so I rushed him over.
We should settle this
before it gets to court.
Chairman Park.
We at JKL Partners consider
our children's marriage...
to be part
of our joint venture agreement.
And yet,
you threw my daughter out
in a most unjust way.
If you want to dissolve
this marriage,
then cancel the joint venture
and pay the penalty fee.
After everything
you've put me through,
framing me and turning me in,
now you're demanding a penalty fee?
You're the one
who should be paying it!
Don't just stand there.
Call the legal team!
Yes, sir.
Fine.
Let's get our lawyers involved.
We'll settle this in court.
Then I'll have...
to testify about Park Cheol Su
and Eunhwa Trading, won't I?
What?
What are you going
to tell the court?
And if we end up in court,
I'll have to explain that so-called
memory loss of mine too.
I should probably try to remember
what happened at the warehouse.
I knew it.
You never lost your memory.
I really wish
I hadn't lost my memory.
Well, we'll be on our way.
We'll be busy preparing
for the lawsuit.
- Let's go, Dad.
- Sure.
Wait.
Let me ask you one last thing.
Who told you to find Park Cheol Su
and turn him in?
Was it Kim Myung Hui...
or Oh Jung Ran?
I believe I already told you.
You just didn't believe me.
Then...
(Chairman Park Tae Ho)
She already told me?
Oh Jung Ran was behind this
after all?
What the... Darn it!
Who the heck am I supposed to trust?
If Park Cheol Su and Eunhwa Trading
are brought up in court,
things will get complicated.
Plus, if her memory is fine...
and she brings up the warehouse incident,
I'm in big trouble.
How do I clean this up?
Darn it.
- She completely copied it.
- It's identical.
Choi Yu Na...
Isn't she the team leader?
She did this seven years ago?
- Isn't that stealing?
- And she's a team leader now.
What's that?
- Seven years ago?
- She won the grand prize with that.
How shameless can she be?
Just look at her.
(Choi Yu Na, the Design Thief!)
It's all lies. I'm being framed.
Everyone's talking about it...
on the company message board
and anonymous forums.
Ms. Choi, did you really
win the competition...
with someone else's design?
I told you I didn't.
Right, of course not.
How could you study abroad
and earn a special position...
off someone else's design?
No decent person's conscience
would allow that.
Maybe she has no conscience
or she just isn't decent.
Park Min Jun.
You really want to take this
all the way?
She threatened my Hyun Jun...
and tormented him.
Talk about a scandalous past.
Go ahead and tear them down all day.
I'll keep putting them back up
until you give up.
You see,
I still have 100 posters left.
(Choi Yu Na, the Design Thief!)
(Head of Division 1, Park Min Jun)
The chairman ordered you
to back down.
Why are you still making an issue
out of my design?
The posters in the company lobby,
the posts you spread online...
Get rid of all of it.
If it bothers you so much,
go ask my father for help.
If this keeps happening
over and over,
public opinion will turn
against you, and my father...
will get tired of you.
Then,
he'll abandon you in the end.
What?
I told you...
I'd make my father abandon you.
From now on,
wherever there's a crowd,
your crimes will be put on display.
Once you're branded
the nation's plagiarist,
do you think my father
will still stand by you?
Let's see how well you hold up.
What? The nation's plagiarist?
Give me a break.
I have Park Hyun Jun and Oh Jung Ran
in the palm of my hand.
You think I'll go down that easily?
Before you ruin everything,
I'll do whatever it takes
to save myself,
even if it means marrying
into the Adele family.
Women are a dime a dozen,
but there's only one Adele Group.
You said you didn't want to live
as a chauffeur's son.
You want to live
as Park Tae Ho's son.
Then you have to take this chance.
For Chloe's sake,
I wanted to keep living
as Park Tae Ho's son.
- It means nothing without her.
- Fine.
If love were all that mattered
to Chloe too,
then I'd approve.
But she's driven by greed, not love.
Thinking you couldn't help her,
she plotted
with Kim Myung Hui instead.
That got her kicked out.
There was no plotting!
Don't make this any harder for me.
Please just leave me alone.
Think again.
Betting your whole life on Chloe?
That's a stupid thing to do.
Depending on other people
is dangerous and pointless.
Hyun Jun, wait!
Thinking you couldn't help her,
she plotted
with Kim Myung Hui instead.
Are you really...
plotting something with her
behind my back?
What exactly are you trying to do?
Don't tell me...
you want to go back to Min Jun?
Let's talk for a second.
The vice president position.
What are you going to do about it?
Are you asking if I'm going
to break up with Jin Ju...
like our father said?
How about you listen
to our father this time?
What?
To help Jin Ju get her revenge,
becoming the heir has to come first.
You've been given that chance.
Shouldn't you take control
of Adele first,
then find a way
to hand it over to Jin Ju?
To help Jin Ju get her revenge?
It's probably for your sake.
You're just hoping Jin Ju and I
will break up over this,
aren't you?
I love Jin Ju,
but I've let go of my desire
to have her for myself.
All I want is to help her
get her revenge, no matter what.
If you truly love her,
put aside what you want...
and think about
what's truly best for her.
(Bionecos DNA Analysis Center)
You got the test results, right?
It's Oh Jung Ran's blood, isn't it?
I haven't opened it yet.
I thought you should be
the first one to see it.
Take a look.
(DNA Analysis Report)
(The DNA from the bloodstain...)
(does not match either
Oh Jung Ran or Song Geun Tae.)
This can't be right.
What is it?
There's a problem with the results.
What?
Dan Hui...
What's wrong? Is there a problem?
How could this be?
Does this mean Oh Jung Ran
didn't kill my sister?
What are you saying?
No, this is impossible.
Dan Hui!
Why is Hyun Jun so obsessed
with Chloe?
(Bit Life President, Oh Jung Ran)
To become the heir,
he needs to leave Chloe.
Oh Jung Ran.
What is this?
That day, 30 years ago.
What? 30 years ago?
The day you tried to kill me!
Why did you barge in here...
and suddenly start talking
about that day?
Because I remember now.
I remember that day
from 30 years ago.
What?
Are you...
Mr. Park Tae Ho,
the president of Adele?
Please, help me.
I don't remember anything.
That's right.
You said you'd lost your memory.
And now you're saying your memory
came back after 30 years?
That's right, Oh Jung Ran. You...
You tried to strangle me to death.
What are you talking about?
Admit it! You strangled me.
So what if I strangled you?
You survived just fine, didn't you?
So because I didn't die, it's fine?
You're a murderer.
That's right,
I should have killed you.
I should've made sure
to finish the job that day.
If I'd known
I'd be tormented for 30 years,
I would've killed you
100 times over.
For 30 years,
you haven't felt
a single bit of remorse or regret.
You even tried to kill Min Jun.
You, Oh Jung Ran, ruined my life!
So just admit it was you. Admit it!
Admit that you're the one
who strangled me.
Have you completely lost your mind?
Should I finish you off right now?
- Oh Jung Ran!
- Ms. Kim, please.
Oh Jung Ran, tell me the truth.
- Ms. Kim, please don't do this.
- Let me go!
Oh Jung Ran!
She barges in here bringing up
something from 30 years ago?
That I tried to strangle her?
Did getting kicked out
finally drive her crazy?
Darn.
It has to be Oh Jung Ran.
Yoon Jung, you saw it too.
I'm certain it was
Oh Jung Ran that day.
Amnesia, my foot.
See?
This wretch remembers everything!
How are you still alive?
What are you trying to pull,
crawling back here?
She even admitted to trying
to kill me. We weren't wrong.
I know. It was her for sure.
But there could be something
we're missing.
Maybe someone else put her up to it,
or maybe someone we don't know
was involved.
Someone we don't know?
Yes, so just calm down,
and let's figure out
what's going on.
Okay?
But what if...
What if it wasn't Oh Jung Ran?
What did Dan Hui
sacrifice her life for?
You scared me.
Why are you in my room,
sitting there like a ghost?
Seriously,
what's been up with you all day?
It was definitely you.
That day, 30 years ago.
Oh Jung Ran, you strangled me.
You even confessed to Chairman Park
that you tried to kill me.
You took that poison
and came out just fine.
Poison?
So you had someone else do it?
You drugged me until I passed out...
and then you strangled me?
Why are you so fixated
on being strangled?
If I'd known,
I would've used a stronger,
more effective drug back then.
So you didn't actually strangle me?
You just drugged me?
Stop bothering me
and go see a doctor.
It sounds like
your memory hasn't come back.
You're just mixing things up.
If Oh Jung Ran drugged you,
what does that mean?
Myung Hui definitely had...
strangulation marks on her neck.
How can Oh Jung Ran
not be the killer?
Yoon Jung.
What do I do now?
For the last 30 years,
I've been holding on
just to get revenge on Oh Jung Ran.
I gave up my identity
and lived as my sister,
enduring every kind of humiliation.
But...
if she isn't the one
who killed my sister...
What are you talking about?
Who killed whom?
And what do you mean
you lived as your sister?
What's all of this about?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)