(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Kim Myung Hui.
You... Where have you been?
What?
This is for Dr. Baek,
whom you brutally murdered.
Wait, what?
And this?
This is for my sister,
who died unjustly at your hands.
Kim Myung Hui, you!
Shut your mouth!
Don't you dare say my sister's name.
Keep my sister's name...
out of your filthy mouth.
Your sister's name?
So it's true. Kim Myung Hui
and Kim Dan Hui really are twins.
That's right.
I'm Kim Dan Hui.
How dare you try
to poison my sister?
My sister's only crime was
letting Park Tae Ho deceive her.
You're no different from him.
Park Tae Ho, Oh Jung Ran,
you're the ones
who killed my sister.
You little...
You, that's enough!
How dare you make a scene here?
How dare I?
Who do you think you are?
The chairman of Adele Group?
Fine. I'll be the one
to drag you down from there.
You!
Where do you think you're going?
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
The key.
I'm going to find the key you hid,
and I'm going to find
the slush fund ledger.
With that,
I'll strip you of your title...
as chairman of Adele Group.
Get a grip!
What do you
possibly think you can do?
How dare you lay a hand on me?
How can you touch me
with the same hands...
that strangled my sister?
You. I ought to...
My sister was carrying your child.
She was carrying Min Jun.
And yet, you strangled her.
Both my sister and Min Jun.
You tried to kill them
with your own hands.
How could a person do such a thing?
Even a heartless monster
wouldn't go that far.
How could you do that to my sister?
How could you do that
to the woman carrying your child?
Because she had the nerve
to try and leave me!
If she had just lived obediently
as she was told,
there would've been no problem.
She was needlessly stubborn,
so she had to die.
What?
Kim Dan Hui, you're just the same.
If you were going to live
as Kim Myung Hui,
you should've seen it through
to the end.
Why did you have to dig up
what happened 30 years ago...
and cause all this trouble?
Because your crimes must be exposed!
Because I had to bring
my sister's killer to justice.
The statute of limitations
has already passed,
so I can't be punished.
With Adele Group's power,
I can easily bury it as well.
So if you want to live,
keep your mouth shut.
If I want to live?
You'd kill me too?
That's right!
If you keep making a scene...
trying to expose
what happened 30 years ago,
I'll have no other choice.
If you keep making a scene...
trying to expose
what happened 30 years ago,
I'll have no other choice.
To think that a man like that...
is my father.
I think we've heard enough.
Right. Since Ms. Kim got Park Tae Ho
to confess as planned,
let's move on with our plan.
Sure. Dan Hui went into
the lion's den alone to get us this,
so let's get to work right away.
(Audio File Transfer Complete)
I've sent the audio file.
You two, take Park Tae Ho's
confession... No.
Let the whole world know...
about Park Tae Ho's crimes.
Of course.
The intel team is standing by.
- Yes, I'll help too.
- Great.
I thank you in advance.
Jin Ju and I will prepare
for an emergency board meeting.
We'll make sure Chairman Park...
is dismissed.
Right. Let's get to work.
Min Jun, be careful.
Sure.
Secretary Jung, let's go.
Let's do this, team.
Kim Dan Hui.
There's nothing you can do.
You're nothing but a woman
who belonged to me.
You're just an empty shell
of Kim Myung Hui,
nothing but a substitute.
You killed my sister,
and then you shamelessly acted like
you didn't know who I was.
You can bet I'll make you pay
for toying with my life.
And you'll pay
for murdering my sister.
If the law won't do it, I will.
The people will.
The whole world...
will crush you and bring you down.
Talk is cheap.
You need to realize that without me,
you're nothing.
Sir!
Sir, we have a huge problem.
What is it?
Both my sister and Min Jun.
You tried to kill them
with your own hands.
- What's this?
- How could a person...
- do such a thing?
- Isn't that President Kim's voice?
- I think so.
- Even a heartless monster...
- wouldn't go that far.
- It is.
How could you do that to my sister?
- Isn't that President Kim's voice?
- What are we hearing?
Doesn't that sound like
President Kim's voice?
Because she had the nerve
to try and leave me!
- Is that for real?
- It's real.
This gives me the creeps.
If she had just lived obediently
as she was told,
- there would've been no problem.
- Isn't that the chairman?
- I think so.
- Why is this being broadcast?
She was needlessly stubborn,
- so she had to die.
- My goodness.
- He said he killed her.
- What?
Kim Dan Hui, you're just the same.
If you were going to live
as Kim Myung Hui,
you should've seen it through
to the end.
Why did you have to dig up
what happened 30 years ago...
and cause all this trouble?
Because your crimes must be exposed!
Because I had to bring
my sister's killer to justice.
Wait, does that mean
Chairman Park...
killed President Kim's sister?
I mean, how could he do that
to twin sisters?
Oh my goodness. That animal.
The worst kind of scum.
Unbelievable.
Boss. You have to see this.
The statute of limitations
has already passed,
so I can't be punished.
With Adele Group's power,
I can easily bury it as well.
So if you want to live,
keep your mouth shut.
You don't seem surprised.
I'm in complete shock.
Well, I had a front-row seat
to the whole thing.
Park Tae Ho... That animal.
Now,
the truth is finally out.
The truth about Park Tae Ho
and Kim Dan Hui.
I think it's time for us
to make our move.
Both my sister and Min Jun.
- You tried to kill them...
- This.
It's blowing up everywhere.
Park Tae Ho.
Looks like Kim Dan Hui has him
right where she wants him.
So what are we supposed to do now?
Because she had the nerve
to try and leave me!
If she had just lived obediently
as she was told,
there would've been no problem.
She was needlessly stubborn,
so she had to die.
What the heck?
How did what I just said in here
get out?
Kim Dan Hui, don't tell me you...
Darn it.
Darn.
Kim Dan Hui, you.
How dare you play games with me?
You played games with my life
for 30 years.
This is nothing compared to that.
Everyone must know
what kind of person you are by now.
Do you really think
Adele Group's power...
can cover this up, too?
Go on.
Try to fix this.
Kim Dan Hui. I'll kill you.
Go ahead.
Try to kill me.
Kill me!
If I die,
you'll be the prime suspect.
The entire nation heard you
threaten my life.
The statute of limitations
might be up for my sister's murder,
but you won't escape the charge
of murdering me.
You'll go down as a murderer.
So go on. Kill me too.
Kill me right now!
You...
Lock her up!
Drag this thing out of here
right now...
and lock her in the basement.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself
for standing by Park Tae Ho?
Take a good look
at the kind of man he really is.
From this point on,
I have to rely
on Jin Ju and Min Jun.
- My name is Chloe.
- She's helping my mother and me.
I'm aware. Ms. Kim gave me...
a heads-up yesterday.
So what about the matter
she asked you to handle?
Then, you're not Kim Myung Hui.
You're Kim Dan Hui.
And the one who killed your sister
wasn't Oh Jung Ran,
but Chairman Park Tae Ho.
Yes, Mrs. Han.
The incident from 30 years ago...
and the truth that's been revealed
after 30 years.
None of this is a simple matter.
So, how can I help you?
Tomorrow, the whole world...
will know
about Park Tae Ho's evil deeds.
My son, Min Jun,
is going to call
for an emergency board meeting.
At that meeting,
I want Park Tae Ho...
removed from his position
as chairman.
The board of directors...
will have to vote in favor
of his dismissal.
As the majority shareholder,
Moon Tae Jin...
should be able to pressure
the board members.
And the only one who
can get Moon Tae Jin to do that...
is you, Mrs. Han.
The majority shareholder
made his case,
but the vote is split
right down the middle.
Are you still...
going to call for an emergency
board meeting knowing that?
Yes. I'll call the meeting...
and try to persuade them
until the very end.
In that case, you'll need
more definitive evidence.
You need to bring evidence
that can prove...
Park Tae Ho committed murder,
and create a situation...
where they have no choice
but to remove him.
Evidence that proves
he committed the murder?
The bloodstain.
The lab tech working for Park Tae Ho
has the actual test results.
Then you should hurry.
Of course. Thank you.
Thank you.
(Park Min Jun)
Park Min Jun.
He must be in shock.
He's probably not in the right mind
to take my call.
(Head of Division 2, Park Hyun Jun)
Baek Jin Ju.
Why can't I reach you
when a total bombshell just dropped?
Take down that recording now.
Announce that it's fake!
Yes, sir. We'll claim it was
an AI-generated fake.
Who'd believe that?
You killed Kim Myung Hui
and kept Kim Dan Hui by your side.
The details are just too shocking.
This isn't going to be an easy fix.
Stay out of it and leave.
Actually, I have every right
to be involved.
I'm also a victim whom you deceived
and made a fool of for 30 years.
What? A victim?
That's right.
You killed Kim Myung Hui
and framed me for it.
You made me spend 30 years
fighting with Kim Dan Hui.
So what?
Should I lock you in the basement
like I did with Kim Dan Hui?
Do you still not understand
the situation?
What if I side with Kim Dan Hui
and testify that you're a murderer,
and that I saw everything go down
30 years ago?
- What?
- On the other hand,
if I testify that
Kim Dan Hui is lying,
what's in it for me?
Which side I take and what I say...
is entirely up to you.
So you'd better get on my good side.
Over my dead body.
Sir.
Now what?
An emergency board meeting
was called...
- regarding your removal.
- His removal?
Who would dare to do that?
Director Park Min Jun called for it.
Min Jun?
Cancel the board meeting right now.
Well, according to the bylaws,
an emergency meeting...
can only be canceled
by the person who called it,
unless the issue is resolved.
Park Min Jun.
Find him and bring him to me now.
I have to cancel
the emergency board meeting!
And what if you can't?
You need to think very carefully.
If it looks like you're going
to lose your chairmanship...
to Kim Dan Hui and Park Min Jun,
give it to Hyun Jun.
Who'd take it from me?
- Go to the office now.
- Yes, sir.
Man, this is a real rollercoaster.
First Chairman Park's recording,
now an emergency board meeting.
It's making my head spin.
Of course Kim Dan Hui
wouldn't come back without a plan.
She planned all of this
from the start.
So what should we do?
Ms. Oh.
- The chairman's recording...
- I know.
It's true, so drop it.
What about
the emergency board meeting?
Shouldn't we stop his removal?
This is a no-brainer.
If the chairman is removed,
the other side will take over
the entire company.
It's to our advantage
to stop the removal first,
and then demand compensation.
Right.
I may hate Park Tae Ho,
but I can't let them
take the company.
Just like you said,
we'll block the dismissal...
and demand compensation.
I need to get Director Seo
and our directors in line first.
You go to the company
and see what's going on.
Got it.
The chairman is here.
Is the recording true?
Is it true that you murdered
the woman carrying your son?
Where is Kim Dan Hui now?
Everyone,
it's all lies. Lies!
- Let's get you to your office.
- Chairman,
is it true you murdered her?
Hey, Manager Kang.
Park Min Jun is on the second floor.
Go get him.
Excuse me, sir.
Is the recording true? Sir!
The recording was released,
and he's still calling it a lie.
He'll use the power of Adele Group
to try and cover it up.
We have to get him dismissed
at the board meeting today.
I also got the test results back.
If we can prove Chairman Park
committed murder, we can win.
After my father is dismissed,
what's the plan?
Like last time,
do you still think my mother
should become the chairwoman?
To make sure Park Tae Ho
and Oh Jung Ran are punished,
it's probably best for your mother
to have the power.
(Park Hyun Jun)
We should tell Hyun Jun now, too.
Things are moving
too fast right now.
It's better to explain everything
after this is all over.
Are we going to keep hiding the fact
that we know his secret?
Yes.
I'm going to let his secret rest
for now.
Let's prepare
for the board meeting first.
(Head of Division 2, Park Hyun Jun)
They knew my secret all along.
Park Min Jun and Baek Jin Ju.
They know I'm not Park Tae Ho's son.
That's why...
That's why she chose them over me.
She abandoned me...
for Park Min Jun,
the son of Park Tae Ho.
Darn it!
The chairman is looking for you.
- Please come with me.
- No, I'm going to the boardroom.
Jin Ju, you go on ahead.
Park Hyun Jun.
How long have you known?
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
How and when did you find out
who my father is?
I knew it.
So that's why you lied to me,
kept secrets,
and sided with President Kim
and Park Min Jun.
Because I'm not Park Tae Ho's son.
Because I'm useless to you now!
That's not it.
This has nothing to do with you.
Exactly!
I'm just some guy
you couldn't care less about, right?
The son of a chauffeur.
Someone you can just throw away
when he's no longer useful.
Park Hyun Jun.
I...
What are you doing?
I can't just be a fool
who gets thrown away by you.
The son of Chairman Park Tae Ho.
I have to at least hold on
to that position.
Park Hyun Jun.
Without proof, it'll be hard
to persuade the directors.
Before the board meeting starts,
I have to get the test results back.
But what if
I can't get there in time?
It's me, Secretary Jung.
There's a problem.
You need to rescue
Ms. Kim right now...
and bring her to the boardroom.
She needs to be the one
to personally expose Park Tae Ho...
as a murderer.
Cancel the emergency board meeting
right now.
No. You're...
a murderer.
You shouldn't be
in the chairman's seat.
Me? A murderer?
I'm your father.
You're Park Tae Ho's son.
Your mother...
Well, actually,
she isn't even your mother.
So just betray her.
Stop being so emotional
and think rationally.
Think about which side is going
to benefit you more,
and open your eyes.
I get it. Was murder
one of your rational calculations?
Did you decide
it was more beneficial...
to just kill the woman
carrying your unborn child?
Was that actually rational
on your part?
- You brat.
- Park Tae Ho, you...
killed my birth mother
and ruined both of our lives.
You killed the innocent CEO Baek,
and you took Jin Ju away from me.
Now it's your turn to be ruined,
and to know the pain of having
everything taken from you.
You little punk.
How dare you speak to me like that?
Both your mother and Baek Jun Gi...
died because they dared to defy me.
You and Kim Dan Hui lived in luxury
under my protection.
And now this?
Do you really think
you can take me down?
I am the Adele Group,
and the Adele Group is me.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Hyun Jun.
The board is deadlocked
regarding your removal.
If concrete evidence
of the murder is revealed,
you'll be ousted.
Concrete evidence?
The evidence that Park Min Jun
and Chloe prepared together.
It's in my hands now.
Chloe too?
I knew it.
Kim Dan Hui and Chloe.
They plotted this together?
Park Hyun Jun,
what do you think you're doing?
I helped you, Father.
More than Min Jun,
I'm the one who deserves...
to be your son.
Park Hyun Jun.
I have to rescue Dan Hui
and get her to the board meeting.
Yes. This should do the trick.
Nothing beats this
for breaking down a door.
Wait, how would you know that?
When you work a lot
of part-time jobs,
you see things you wouldn't believe.
Nice.
I'll get going.
Be careful.
Dan Hui.
- Dan Hui!
- Hold it.
I knew it.
Kim Dan Hui isn't going
to the board meeting.
I'm telling you,
the recording was fabricated.
Don't you know how sophisticated
AI technology is these days?
We can ask the police
to investigate...
and find the person
who spread this fake recording.
So is the recording
really a fabrication?
That's what I said!
Don't we need to hear from Ms. Kim,
instead of only hearing from you?
Well, that's...
The recording wasn't fabricated.
It's completely real.
Park Tae Ho...
is the man who murdered my sister.
(Pearl in Red)
What is this nonsense?
Who dares to try and take me down?
I am the Adele Group,
and the Adele Group is me.
Things are about to get
a lot harder for you.
You'll regret the day
you betrayed me,
and all the wrong you've done
will come back to destroy you.
I can't go down like this.
I have to survive somehow,
even if it means clinging
to the chairman or Hyun Jun.
- A solution?
- Back me to take your place.
I'll step up as the next chairman.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)