(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
Why are you calling again?
The stock deal is dead,
so why pay hush money?
That's enough.
Stop bothering me with these calls.
- What the...
- My gosh.
I'm so sorry.
Seriously.
Ms. Oh?
We briefly met when you came
to see Ms. Choi.
I'm Chloe,
a consultant in the bio division.
Right. The one Kim Myung Hui hired.
Yes.
Oh no, I've stained your clothes.
I'm so sorry.
Let me get that for you.
Wait, what are you doing?
I said it's fine.
I'm so sorry. How clumsy of me.
You should wash your hands.
Unbelievable.
I guess I was just really nervous
being around you.
I'm not usually this nervous,
even around President Kim.
You just have
such a strong presence.
A strong presence?
You mean something like charisma?
Exactly. You seemed extraordinary
from the moment I saw you.
Of course.
I hear you're good at what you do.
You've got a good eye.
Hold on.
Funny...
You still haven't said
how you'll make it up to me.
You don't think flattery gets you
off the hook, do you?
Of course not.
You can bill me
for the dry cleaning or...
Dry cleaning?
Do I look like I can't pay
for my own dry cleaning?
I heard you were a hotshot overseas.
Get me a designer piece
that's not available in Korea yet.
That shouldn't be so hard.
Yes, of course.
I'll have it ready for you.
What?
What's going on?
I think it's a blackout.
We should leave since it's not safe.
I'll be on my way then.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
Wait, my phone.
What's this?
(Out of service,
Please check back shortly.)
Is anyone there?
Open this door right now!
Over here!
Didn't the lights go out
at the perfect time?
Yes. Thanks to you,
I got out of a tight spot.
I locked the door,
so it'll take her a while.
If she kidnapped someone
and held him captive,
she must've had help.
Let's track her communications
and see who contacts her.
We'll figure this out.
The false accusation,
this forced marriage,
and any hardships we face
in this family.
Thank you, my son.
They say even the toughest hikes
give you a chance to rest.
Though this case is a headache,
you managed to talk to Min Jun...
and clear the air.
I hope you two can be as close
as you used to be.
When I first held Min Jun
as a newborn...
and became part of the Adele family,
he held on to me
with his tiny little hand.
It was as though
he were telling me...
we'd be okay,
as long as we had each other.
I felt the same way yesterday.
Just incredibly grateful and sorry.
Now I need to act,
for Min Jun's sake.
But you still haven't found
the person they're holding.
Don't you need him to testify?
I'll make Yu Na and Oh Jung Ran
confess to their own crimes...
right in front of Chairman Park.
(Driver Song)
Jung Ran, this is just wrong.
You made me a promise.
You promised to hold him
for a few days,
keep him quiet, and let him go.
And now you're going
to sell him off overseas...
to avoid paying him?
Chairman Park didn't order this.
Why do you have to go this far?
Let's just pay him,
make sure he keeps his mouth shut,
and let him go. Okay?
Say something, Jung Ran!
Oh Jung Ran.
She's a truly terrifying woman.
If we don't hurry,
she'll really send him overseas.
Don't tell me...
she came because she knows
what Yu Na did.
Goodness, the tension is killing me.
Why is she just sipping her tea
and not saying a word?
Thank you for your help
the other day.
We kept the shares,
and we have you to thank for it.
Anyway, did you expect us
to get on our knees and thank you?
We're grateful,
but it's rude
to just show up unannounced.
Isn't this Yu Na's...
This was worn by the person
who stole the design book.
I got this from an anonymous source,
and it looks just like
the jacket Ms. Choi has.
Weren't you making a big deal
about a jacket a few days ago?
Are you trying to make our Yu Na out
to be a thief?
For goodness' sake.
Our Yu Na...
As thoughtless as she can be,
she did try to hand over our shares,
but she's just not capable
of stealing.
I see.
If Ms. Choi still has the jacket,
then she's not a suspect.
That's why I'm here to confirm it.
I want to be sure
before I report to the chairman.
You're reporting this
to the chairman?
I'm going to report to the chairman
and give the evidence to the police.
The detectives already said
they would come to the house.
Goodness.
Now,
will you please check
if Ms. Choi has her jacket?
What?
Well, that's...
I took it to the dry cleaner's.
- The dry cleaner's?
- Yes.
Yes, of course.
I'm sure that's the case.
So you're saying
Ms. Choi wasn't involved?
- What?
- Of course she wasn't!
I see.
Very well.
I'll take your word for it...
and report to the chairman.
You'll be the ones...
who make Choi Yu Na walk
right into a trap.
Goodness.
(Team Leader, Choi Yu Na)
Why haven't I heard
from Oh Jung Ran?
Why is she so quiet about...
the stock deal I messed up?
It's unnerving.
I can't even call her first
because she might demand the shares.
This is driving me crazy.
(Mom)
What is it?
We're in huge trouble!
What?
Have you reviewed the videos?
Yes, we compared
the initial accusation video,
the CCTV footage,
and the confession video.
Their dominant hands are different,
and their builds don't match either.
We also think
the confession video is fake.
It's suspicious
that he's off the grid too.
We'll look into it, keeping
kidnapping and confinement in mind.
Right. Please be discreet and quick.
Of course.
Please update the victim, Chloe,
on the new direction of the case.
- Understood.
- We'll be leaving now.
Chloe.
You are a precious...
and perfect person.
I'll remind you
how precious and perfect you are.
What's up?
Got somewhere urgent to be?
I'm on my way to see Chloe.
She wasn't in her office.
- Why are you looking for her?
- It's nothing.
You say that,
but your face says something else.
Isn't this about
that false accusation?
Can't you fill me in
on what's been happening...
since the confession video came out?
You're going to keep
dodging the question?
Do you think I'd mess things up
if I knew?
Or do you just not want me involved?
Tell me what's going on.
Don't make me get serious.
What's the issue
with the false accusation case?
He's being held captive.
Chloe.
If we don't find him soon,
he'll be sent overseas somewhere...
that he can never come back from.
Who's holding him captive,
and who's sending him away?
Don't tell me Choi Yu Na
would go that far.
- It's not her, but...
- Chloe, hold on.
Why did you stop her?
Don't leave me
in the dark like this.
This is urgent,
and we need your help.
You need my help?
Yes.
The one who locked him up is...
It's your mother.
I thought you might need this.
To be honest,
I always suspected she was capable
of doing terrible things.
If our "great" chairman...
had given the job to my mother
instead of yours,
it was never going
to be anything good, right?
I gave her a hard time
and told her to be nice,
but most of the time,
I wanted to take her side.
Because the bad guy...
is our father,
the one calling the shots.
So I figured I should cut her some slack,
since she has no choice.
That's what I thought.
But this?
This?
She chose to do this herself.
It shows
the kind of person my mother is.
You can back out if it's too much.
I kept saying...
that Ms. Oh and I
aren't a package deal.
I guess we were one after all.
She's your mother. Your family.
If I back out of this,
how could I ever look you
in the eye again?
I couldn't be cool around Chloe.
I'd have to avoid her all the time.
That's a pathetic way to live.
Not my style either.
If there's anything I can do,
I have to at least try.
Are you sure about this?
It'll be tough, sure.
It'll be hard, but...
But if you look at it another way,
there's still a chance, right?
I have to stop Ms. Oh...
before things get worse.
Once again,
I used you.
I'm so sorry.
Don't waste your energy.
There's no use
trying to stop Jung Ran.
She's already completely lost it,
and you're as good as sold...
to some foreign country.
You'll meet crueler people than you
and finally get what you deserve.
You should've lived a better life.
You reap what you sow.
There's no escaping karma.
You’ll pay for every sin you commit.
If not you, then your kids...
Right.
Let's be decent
and not drag our kids into this.
Hey, Hyun Jun. What's...
What? You're hurt?
Don't tell me this is instant karma.
Where are you?
However I look at it,
it was that witch.
That brat Chloe,
or whatever her name is,
distracted me and snatched my phone.
She teamed up with Kim Myung Hui
and pulled one over on me.
I won't let them get away with this.
What are you doing here?
What is it? Hey!
Stop right there.
Stop. Do you have a death wish?
Why...
Why are you here?
What about that guy?
Who cares about him right now?
Hyun Jun is hurt!
Hyun Jun's hurt?
How bad is it?
I don't know.
This is why
you should always be good.
I guess karma really does have
same-day delivery.
If anything happens to Hyun Jun,
this is on you!
Where is he?
- Hyun Jun.
- Goodness.
Looks like you two came together.
We just met outside.
I heard you were hurt.
Where? How? How bad is it?
Shouldn't you see a doctor
right away?
I don't need a doctor.
Physically, I'm fine,
but emotionally, I'm not.
- Emotionally?
How should I put this?
Who am I?
Whose son am I?
I felt sorry for some,
ashamed of myself
in front of others,
and disappointed in someone else.
All in one exhausting day.
What are you talking about?
In other words, I'm upset.
What? What do you mean?
I'm screaming on the inside.
Why?
What's worrying you?
That's the question, isn't it?
What do you suppose
I'm so worried about?
I wonder if Ms. Oh...
could solve it for me.
Hold on. Hyun Jun?
What's gotten into him?
What could be bothering him so much?
Poor Hyun Jun...
Where are you going?
He said I can help, not you.
I'll protect my own son.
You go and keep an eye on that guy.
Oh, no.
Hyun Jun, wait!
What is it?
What's been troubling you?
That is the question.
I'm upset and troubled.
I get that. What's going on?
You said I'd be able to solve it.
Ms. Oh.
When a child does something wrong,
parents should guide them, right?
Of course.
But what about
when a parent does something wrong?
What?
Can children...
guide their parents too?
I guess.
Did I do something to upset you?
That can't be it.
I haven't even
been nagging you much lately.
Ms. Oh.
I...
I just wish
you'd understand me, Mom.
Seriously, what's gotten into you?
Did you get into
some kind of trouble?
What did you do...
to be talking like this all of a sudden?
That depends on how you look at it.
Just remember one thing.
I...
worry about you a lot.
You worry about me?
Why have you been
so worried about me lately?
Have you finally grown up?
Are you ill?
I should've followed
Hyun Jun out too.
Darn.
But now I have to go back
to that dump.
The only way to lure Mr. Song out...
is through me.
He goes a little overboard
whenever he thinks I'm in trouble.
He'll definitely
come looking for me.
If you tail him,
you should be able to figure out
where they're keeping the accuser.
That's what...
Chloe wants, right?
What are you doing here?
I'm coming with you.
It's dangerous. Wait here.
Stop being stubborn.
Come on, before we lose him.
President Kim Myung Hui
has my jacket?
How? I'm sure I threw it away.
What's this about an informant?
Wait.
Was it Chloe?
I don't know about that.
It seems a bit too soon
for an apology.
There may still be more
to the story.
Don't tell me she tailed me
to find the evidence.
That means President Kim
has my jacket.
If the police get
their hands on that...
Ms. Choi,
what brings you here at this hour?
I'm here to see the chairman.
I see.
I'll let the chairman know.
Please wait here for a moment.
What are you mumbling about?
Hurry. I have to go!
To the bathroom?
Right.
You've been tied up for hours.
Here.
Good.
Who are you?
We're not here to make friends,
but if you want to get out of here,
follow us.
Why should I trust you?
At least we're not trying
to smuggle you out of the country.
- Really?
- If you want to doubt us,
do it once we're out of here.
What?
Hold on.
Who are you, people?
Darn it.
You punk!
You!
Min Jun!
See?
Like I told you,
the one who stole the design book...
is here to destroy the evidence.
Ms. Choi.
Goodness.
You've arrived just in time, Ms. Oh.
What are you talking about?
We've just exposed Ms. Choi's crime.
Don't you have something to say?
What?
That's not true.
I didn't steal the design book.
Quiet!
Is it true...
you helped Ms. Choi...
in exchange for company shares?
And you went as far as to kidnap
and imprison someone for it?
What? No.
It's true.
Son.
Ms. Oh.
Mom,
I need you to stop right here.
Just come clean...
and ask for forgiveness.
Why are you turning on me too?
This is all your fault, witch.
How dare you frame me?
She's right. This is all a setup.
Fine. If you have proof,
then show it to us.
Here's your proof!
Are things finally about
to go up in flames?
Park Tae Ho, Choi Yu Na,
and everyone at the Adele Group.
I hope they all push each other...
into a fiery pit of despair.
It looks like our key witness
has arrived.
(Pearl in Red)
Choi Yu Na, how dare you lie to me
and tarnish Adele Group's name?
The Adele Group chairman's wife...
resorting to kidnapping
and imprisonment?
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you, I've been framed.
In my own home?
Right in front of me? The nerve!
Are you really going
to leave it at that?
You're not fixing anything.
You're just covering it up.
They will be punished,
but on my terms.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)