(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Episode 53)
Who are you?
Anyway, what am I doing here?
Today's my college orientation.
Did I get into an accident
on my way there?
What? College orientation day?
Park Min Jun.
Min Jun.
Who are you?
What?
What are you trying to pull?
Chloe! Chloe, are you okay?
I hope you're all right.
What on earth happened?
How did you end up
in an accident there?
Wait. Is my name Chloe?
What?
Who am I?
I can't remember anything.
What?
Chloe.
Hello.
What?
Min Jun lost his memory?
You want updates
on Min Jun and Chloe...
at the same time?
Well, they were
in the same accident,
and I'm told they both have amnesia.
I need to know
what's going on immediately.
Yes, I agree.
They both lost their memories.
What on earth is going on?
Please explain.
Is it true?
Did Min Jun really lose his memory?
First, Mr. Park is exhibiting signs
of traumatic brain injury...
and memory loss
following the hit-and-run.
He has retrograde amnesia,
meaning he lost his past memories.
To put it simply,
his mind has reverted to
when he was around 20 years old.
Does that mean he can't remember
anything from after he turned 20?
Yes, that's correct.
How could this happen to my Min Jun?
Oh, no.
Then, what about Chloe's condition?
Right, how's Chloe?
Chloe's condition is more
psychological than neurological.
Psychological?
She has dissociative amnesia
caused by extreme stress and shock.
Simply put,
she doesn't even know who she is.
She doesn't even know who she is?
So, what happens now?
Please give both patients time
and monitor them closely.
Forcing them to remember
or giving them too much info...
could backfire.
What do we do?
Oh, no.
My son is alive,
but I can't even see him...
or hold him.
I should've made Kim Myung Hui
suffer this exact same pain.
For my Hyun Jun's sake,
I should've gotten rid of
that punk Park Min Jun for good.
There you go again.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You had that look when you told us
Park Min Jun was in the hospital.
It's been strange.
I'm not acting any different.
You're the one
who seems different, ma'am.
You're tense, like you feel guilty
about something.
See? Your words have a bite to them.
You're trying to blame me,
aren't you?
Just like Myung Hui,
do you think I'm responsible
for Min Jun's accident?
Who's to say?
Maybe you are, maybe you aren't.
Jung Ran!
Jung Ran, it's about Park Min Jun.
Shut it. I already know.
Oh, you do?
But I thought amnesia was
just something you see in TV shows.
I guess it's a real thing.
And Chloe has it, too.
Double amnesia?
Even TV shows don't go that far.
Wait a minute.
Amnesia?
They both have amnesia?
It must be confusing
to have your memory erased.
Yes.
Honestly, I'm a bit...
overwhelmed.
Mom's here for you, so don't worry.
I'll help you remember
everything you've forgotten.
Okay. I feel like I can believe
whatever you tell me.
That's right.
Don't try to figure this out alone.
Just ask me anything.
Sure. From now on,
I'll only trust what you say.
Well, even though
things turned out this way,
it's not all bad.
I see things between us
haven't changed at all, Father.
By the way,
who are we to each other?
What?
Us?
Are you...
my girlfriend?
I don't really remember,
but when I think about
my time on campus,
it feels like there was always
someone with long hair with me.
Min Jun, are you okay?
What is it?
I'm okay. It's just...
I just have a bit of a headache.
The doctor said forcing memories
will just make things worse.
Take it slow.
Take your time
and let them return naturally, okay?
Okay.
Min Jun is awake and recovering,
and losing his memory
might actually be for the best.
The problem is...
Let's have a word.
At the warehouse, Chloe and I...
met for business.
And you, Ms. Choi,
came there to get your job back.
That's why you made the trip.
What?
When the police ask about
what happened,
don't say anything more
than necessary.
You stick to this story.
Even if they investigate
Min Jun's accident,
what happened at the warehouse...
can never come to light.
All right.
I'll do as you say.
So you have no memory
of the accident whatsoever?
Excuse me, but is there anyone
who might have a grudge against her?
Well...
I can't think of anyone
who'd want to hurt her.
Since both victims have amnesia...
Let's step outside to discuss this
in more detail.
Chloe is still recovering.
- Sure.
- Right, let's step outside.
Where are you going?
Outside.
I just wanted to go
for a walk alone.
You were the one
in my room earlier, right?
I'm sorry,
but I've lost my memories.
Did we know each other?
Yes, we knew each other very well.
If this is just an act
to try and fool me,
you're going to regret it.
Why would you say that?
Why would I pretend to have amnesia?
Was I a bad person?
Chloe!
What are you doing to Chloe?
What do you think you're doing here?
Chloe is my fiancee.
Of course I have to protect her.
Your fiancee?
We'll have to talk about that later.
That must've startled you.
We just met,
and yet I'm saying I'm your fiance.
Strange, right?
Don't worry.
From now on,
I'll protect you.
Chloe!
I'll be the one to protect Chloe.
You can go now, Mr. Park.
Are you okay?
Right. Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
How's the director doing?
He doesn't remember anything
after age 20,
and it doesn't look like
he'll recover anytime soon.
Try not to worry too much.
His memory might come back
if you help fill in the gaps.
Why don't you step outside
for some fresh air?
Don't tell him.
Please don't tell Min Jun
about the things he's forgotten.
This is none of your business,
Ms. Choi.
Min Jun has been through so much.
He was tormented
by Baek Jin Ju's death,
and his relationship
with the chairman...
soured because of Temi Bio.
There's no need to tell him
all of that.
Maybe he'd be happier
starting over from age 20.
Why this sudden concern
for the director's happiness?
I'll start over too,
by Min Jun's side.
What did you just say?
I knew it.
In the end, you were only thinking
about yourself.
I know I've done
a lot of things wrong.
Because you hated me,
I acted arrogantly out of spite.
I was cocky, thinking I only needed
the chairman's approval.
But my feelings for Min Jun
are sincere.
So that Min Jun and I
can start over,
please give us your blessing.
Min Jun truly despised you.
Maybe he doesn't remember anymore,
but I do.
I will never give you my blessing,
so you can leave.
And don't bother coming
to the hospital again.
Who are we to each other?
Are you...
my girlfriend?
I don't really remember,
but when I think about
my time on campus,
it feels like there was always
someone with long hair with me.
His girlfriend?
Someone with long hair?
He must mean Baek Jin Ju.
Should I try to be more like her?
No.
That could trigger
his memories of her.
But if I do nothing...
This might be my last chance.
One, two...
I don't care if I'm just
a replacement for Baek Jin Ju.
Before Min Jun gets his memory back,
I have to do whatever it takes.
Amnesia.
What am I supposed to do about that?
What do you mean,
what should you do?
You should thank Park Min Jun
for surviving.
If he hadn't, you'd be a murderer.
Be grateful and repent.
Kim Myung Hui should be repenting
for taking Hyun Jun from me.
So, is Hyun Jun
still at the hospital?
I want to know how Min Jun
and Hyun Jun are doing,
so go over there right now.
No. I'm not going.
Now he's against me too.
Why is everyone in this family
so cold to me?
Fine. I'll just go and see
for myself.
Darn.
Look at you, alive and well.
So, how does it feel to come back
from the dead?
Get away from my son!
What do you think you're doing?
Is this how you treat someone
who came all this way to visit?
A visit?
I doubt that. You came here
because you thought...
you could hurt my Min Jun again.
I can't even stand the sight of you,
so get out.
You think I enjoy looking
at either of your faces?
You and that brat disgust me.
Watch what you're saying.
Please watch what you're saying.
Whatever.
She's finished now.
Tell me right now! Where is she?
Min Jun!
Over here. Look at me.
- Min Jun!
- Min Jun, are you okay?
I'm here for you.
It's okay. Just breathe.
So, about Chloe...
Is the amnesia for real or not?
I've confirmed it again
with her doctor.
It seems to be the real deal.
The police also questioned her
about the accident,
but she couldn't say anything,
claiming she has no memory.
Really?
I suppose if she remembered,
she would've already told the police
I tried to kill her.
Still, we can't let our guard down.
Use her amnesia as grounds...
to end her contract
and get rid of her.
Before she talks to the police,
we need to send her back to the US.
Understood, sir.
By the way,
what's going on with Min Jun's case?
Still no updates
on the hit-and-run driver?
With no evidence or leads,
and both victims suffering
from amnesia,
the investigation has hit a wall.
Enough with the excuses.
Tell them to find him at all costs!
The punk who hurt my son...
will get no mercy from me.
Min Jun,
are you okay?
Yes.
I'm feeling better now.
Thanks to you,
my headache is starting to go away.
Thank you.
I'm just glad I could help.
Ma'am, I found someone
to guard the director's room.
I'll be his caregiver and bodyguard.
You don't have to worry.
It must've been hard
staying strong in front of Min Jun.
It was.
He's lost his memory...
and must be so confused.
I was afraid that if I cried,
it would make things harder for him.
You can let it all out here.
I honestly thought...
I was going to lose Min Jun.
Thinking I was responsible...
How is this your fault?
Oh Jung Ran's to blame.
Look at her showing up
at the hospital...
after what she did to him.
That woman is a monster.
I mean, even after Myung Hui died,
she came to Dr. Baek's clinic
looking for Min Jun.
I think...
my digging into
Oh Jung Ran's past...
is what caused her
to go after Min Jun.
Because of my revenge,
Min Jun almost died,
and now he's lost his memory.
Don't beat yourself up over it.
Min Jun is awake now,
and he'll get his memories back.
Do you think
he'll ever get them back?
He's in so much pain
whenever he tries to remember.
Part of me...
almost wishes
he'd never remember anything.
Min Jun...
was smiling at Ms. Choi,
and I couldn't tell him the truth...
about their relationship.
It's been so long
since I'd seen him smile...
so peacefully.
I just wanted him to be happy,
even if it meant
forgetting everything.
But is that the right thing to do?
I just don't know...
what to do anymore.
What do I do? My poor Min Jun.
What do I do?
Park Min Jun has amnesia
from the hit-and-run.
He's gone back to being
a clueless 20-year-old kid.
How can we let someone like that
run the company?
The board, executives,
and shareholders must all...
pressure the chairman.
Tell him to remove Park Min Jun
as director. Got it?
Min Jun,
let's go have some fun with this
once you're discharged.
Sure.
Really?
Yes, that sounds good.
Here, have a nice cold drink.
Right, thank you.
It's getting late,
you should probably head out.
It's not that late.
Min Jun, can I stay a little longer?
Sure.
I told you,
you don't have to be so formal.
Sorry. With my amnesia,
it feels like we just met today.
Really? Then maybe we should
start over from the beginning...
Hold on. What are you doing here?
Wait. Do you two know each other?
Well, I'm working a second job
as a caregiver.
My shift's almost over,
so I should get going.
What's with you?
Choi Yu Na, what are you doing here?
And on top of that,
what's with this get-up?
It's obviously because...
Well, Min Jun needs me.
Min Jun got a headache
trying to remember something,
and I was the one who comforted him.
I'm staying by his side
in case it happens again.
You? Taking care of him?
- Is that true?
- Yes.
I had a bad headache earlier.
So, you'd better be careful.
Watch what you say.
You might give him a headache.
Why don't you leave now?
If you stay here any longer,
I might have a lot more to say.
You two don't get along, do you?
- We don't.
- We do.
I mean, probably.
Right.
Thanks for everything.
It was nothing.
But are you really okay?
Between the hospital and work...
There's no telling
what Oh Jung Ran will do next.
Until Min Jun is out
of the hospital,
I should keep a close eye on him.
I'll take it from here,
so head home.
- All right. I'm heading out then.
- Okay.
What?
Is Chloe doing any better?
She can't remember a thing.
"Your name is Chloe."
"I'm your dad."
I even had to tell her that.
For such a brilliant child
to end up like this overnight...
Hello?
What? What do you mean
Chloe isn't in her room?
Yes, okay.
I'll look for her right away.
- I'll help him look for her.
- Oh, sure.
Go.
Park Hyun Jun, that jerk.
Whatever. At least I stopped him
from saying anything weird.
Park Min Jun held my hand,
smiled, and relied on me.
Dressing up like Baek Jin Ju
actually worked.
I have to take full advantage
of this opportunity.
There's no need to be nervous.
They said Chloe lost her memory too.
Seriously.
Why is she staring at me like that?
Could she be faking her amnesia?
Is it a lie?
Excuse me,
why are you staring at me like that?
I've lost my memory.
So?
Do you happen to know me?
No, not at all.
What is this?
What do you think you're doing?
But I feel like...
I recognize you.
Something...
is coming back to me.
What?
We know each other, don't we?
I...
I told you, I don't.
Yes, we do.
I'm so close to remembering.
I remember...
Chloe!
Chloe.
Chloe?
(Pearl in Red)
Ms. Kim, there's a huge problem.
Ms. Choi, this is the police.
What the heck did you do?
Announce
Park Min Jun's amnesia publicly.
Use a provocative headline
and plaster it on the front page.
The succession war at Adele
has begun.
Oh Jung Ran and I will have
to face each other head-on.
I have to take what she has.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)