(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Humangen Diagnostic Center)
(The results are indicative
of a paternal relationship.)
What the...
Park Hyun Jun is Song Geun Tae's...
He's Driver Song's son?
(Bit Life President, Kim Myung Hui)
(Episode 70)
(Humangen Diagnostic Center)
Choi Yu Na.
(Suspicions Grow Over
CEO Baek Jun Gi's Death)
No!
Files on CEO Baek's accident
from seven years ago.
You were trying to hide this
in my mother's desk?
To frame my mother for investigating
CEO Baek Jun Gi's car accident?
You thought
if my father pressured my mother,
I would back off.
Yes, I did.
Even when I begged you,
when I said I'd rather die,
you said you wouldn't stop.
You were determined to dig up
what happened seven years ago.
- I had to stop you.
- It's already too late.
I'm aware...
of everything you did
seven years ago.
What?
You used Jin Ju
to lure out CEO Baek Jun Gi,
and when Jin Ju begged you for help,
you threw a rock at her.
You...
How did you know about that?
You hurt Jin Ju, then went on
to win an award with her design?
You stole Jin Ju's life.
Don't you feel any shame or guilt?
I told you...
I'd make you pay
for what you did to her.
Just you wait.
I'm going to expose every
single evil thing you've done...
and make sure you suffer for it.
What do I do?
How did Park Min Jun find out
about what happened back then?
What am I going to do?
What do I do now?
Please accept me as
the Adele family's daughter-in-law.
Let's be a family
and try to get along.
Father.
And...
Lady Kim.
Lady Kim?
You think you can force your way
into this family?
That's enough.
You two, go upstairs for now.
Sir!
You said
you'd let me handle their matter.
Myung Hui,
I may have left it to you,
but there can't be any issues
with the exclusive development rights.
They said there's a penalty fee,
so let's just think it over
for a few days.
- Thank you, Father.
- What...
We had to move in
to save our marriage,
but suddenly
sharing a room like this...
is a little awkward.
I'll be careful not to make
you uncomfortable.
No, that's not what I meant.
I don't mind
being uncomfortable at all.
I'll sleep on the floor here,
so don't worry.
I'll never do anything
you don't want me to.
I know.
(24H Movers)
What is all this?
Well...
It's Chloe's things.
What?
Since they're married,
she said she's moving in.
Min Jun.
We decided to start
living together today.
There were articles saying...
our marriage was fake
or that we'd broken up,
so we had to rush things.
If you want to blame someone,
blame your mother.
Min Jun.
Did we do something wrong?
We're married
and want to live together.
Why is everyone making
such a big deal out of it?
Sure.
Since you're married,
I guess you can live in the same house.
But if you think this marriage...
will help you take over Adele,
you're fooling yourself,
and you've made a huge mistake.
Because Park Hyun Jun can never
be Adele Group's successor.
President Kim,
even at a time like this,
you only care about Adele Group.
Aren't you being a little
too obvious about your greed?
That's rich,
coming from the person...
pretending to have amnesia
and putting on an act.
I mean, that's outright shameless.
I guess...
I can't stop you
or hold on to you anymore, can I?
Is this the only way I can love you,
by quietly enduring it?
How did we end up like this?
Why? Darn it!
Right.
That's where it all went wrong.
That day, seven years ago.
It all started with that accident.
You used Jin Ju
to lure out CEO Baek Jun Gi,
and when Jin Ju begged you for help,
you threw a rock at her.
Just you wait.
I'm going to expose every
single evil thing you've done...
and make sure you suffer for it.
The rock.
Only Baek Jin Ju and I
knew about that.
How could he have found out?
Don't tell me there was a witness.
I have to stop Park Min Jun.
(DNA Parentage Test Report)
(Subject 1: Park Hyun Jun,
Subject 2: Song Geun Tae)
Maybe I can use this.
I have to find a way somehow.
Why did your father...
try to kill my dad and me?
Did stealing Temi Bio
to satisfy his greed...
make him happy?
There's no way he was happy.
My family...
We all suspect one another,
hate one another,
and try to kill one another.
It's not just my father.
No one will ever be happy.
Why are you asking that
all of a sudden?
I was just curious.
I'm hurting Min Jun...
and using you, Hyun Jun,
to take over Adele.
Will I be happy
once I've gotten my revenge?
I wonder.
I probably won't be happy either,
just like Chairman Park.
Still, I want to watch
Park Tae Ho crumble.
I'm going to see this through
to the end.
What the...
What?
You startled me!
What was that for? Unbelievable.
Why am I here?
What did you do to me?
What did you do?
You're the one
who caused a scene, you know.
You kept saying you couldn't leave
and that you had more questions.
You insisted on coming to our place.
Seriously, you were such a pain.
And that's how you ended up
following us home and passing out...
in that state.
No, I wouldn't have...
Whatever.
Eat before you leave
and sober up a bit.
This is the right way to eat it.
Go on, dig in.
Stop it right there.
What did you just do?
Putting kimchi on his rice
is crossing the line.
Crossing the line?
You're the one
who's crossing the line.
"Even if you hate someone,
you still feed them well."
That's our family motto.
I had to let him know
the kimchi is the main event.
Just shut it and sober up too.
Dig in already.
Hurry up and eat.
Right, sure.
That I should.
This turned out great.
- Hits the spot, right?
- Yes.
Is there anything you need?
No.
I'd like to prepare
my mother-in-law's meals myself.
Here. I'll take that.
I appreciate the thought,
but this is my job.
Then at least let me help.
Oh my.
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
See? I told you I should handle it.
I'll clean it up, so don't
touch anything. Just stay put.
- Good grief.
- Oh no.
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Ok.
Then...
Just unbelievable.
You call these side dishes?
There's no meat.
If you don't want it,
then don't eat it.
I have to go check
on the chairman's meal.
You...
- How can you even eat right now?
- Come on.
You're not even supposed
to bother a dog when it's eating.
Wait, what's this?
Jung Ran!
What is it?
I want to meet with you in person
to talk about Kim Dan Hui.
I'll be waiting outside
the main gate tomorrow at 9 a.m.
Outside the main gate?
She wants you to sneak out of here?
Apparently, Chloe's testing me.
She's practically challenging me
to escape.
What?
I know you're clever,
but how are you going
to get out of here?
Having breakfast together like this
really feels like we're a family.
It's finally sinking in...
that I'm part of the Adele family
and your daughter-in-law.
Since you've already accepted her,
please try to be more welcoming.
Be nice?
To the people
who followed Oh Jung Ran's orders...
and tried to kill me?
I want to kill Oh Jung Ran
this very minute,
but I'm holding back
because she begged me.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
As for you, the only reason
I'm seeing you again is because...
of the exclusive development rights.
Father.
If you can't see me as family,
you can see me
as a business partner.
As JKL Partners launches
this joint development project,
we'd like Hyun Jun to head
the project for Adele.
The chairman is still recovering,
and he promised to make me
the acting chairman.
I plan to appoint someone
with expertise to lead the project.
But you don't hold
that position yet, do you?
The chairman's decision
at this point...
can override
whatever you're planning.
Sir, please make your decision
right here and now.
That's right.
Please firmly reject their proposal
right here and now.
Appoint Hyun Jun
to lead the project,
just as JKL Partners wants.
Sir!
But in return,
promote Min Jun to vice president...
and put him on the successor track.
I'll secure
the exclusive development rights...
while also looking out for my son.
Min Jun is now the vice president,
and he's on the successor track.
Don't even think about
getting in his way.
What do you think I can do?
Or maybe you're that insecure.
This is a warning.
Anyone who gets in Min Jun's way,
including Oh Jung Ran
and Park Hyun Jun,
will be forced out of Adele.
You could be the one
who gets swept out.
After all, you're nobody
without the chairman.
Fine. Go on and be
as arrogant as you want.
The greedier you become,
the more painful it'll be
when Hyun Jun's secret...
comes out.
Here's a change of clothes.
Where did you sleep?
Did you eat breakfast?
I took care of it.
You're coming home today, right?
Chloe and Hyun Jun
are already married,
and Chloe has made up her mind.
I know it's hard, Min Jun,
but you need to move on.
I'd like to say I'll try.
But honestly, I don't think I can.
Then at least throw yourself
into your work.
You saw that you were appointed
vice president, right?
Yes.
Chairman Park is leaning more
toward our side than theirs.
Take this chance...
and focus only on your goal
of taking over Adele Group.
And for now,
leave the Temi Bio issue alone.
It's just Temi Bio, right?
There's another issue
I need to deal with anyway.
What other issue?
Director Park.
I mean, Vice President Park.
Will you be
at the company dinner today?
Thank you all for being here.
I'm happy to have married Chloe...
and to be starting
this joint venture.
It's my treat,
so please enjoy yourselves.
Congratulations.
You two look great together.
Your marriage was the talk
of the office.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
It looks like everyone's here
for a company dinner.
Wait, aren't you the part-timer
from the cafe near our office?
Yes. I work part-time here too.
I see the handsome director is here.
Oh, right.
It's been a while.
In that case,
I'll make yours extra delicious.
When it comes to dakgalbi,
it's all about the hot plate.
At our restaurant,
you get several different items
on one plate,
so it's fun to pick and choose.
No way, look at this.
The cheese is the real deal.
Eating some makguksu in between
refreshes your palate,
so you can keep eating.
Chloe, try it like this.
I've never had
this combination before.
It's unique and delicious.
Here, try some.
The flying fish roe
gives it a real kick.
- It has a unique taste.
- Please enjoy.
Yes, Manager Kang.
Has it been confirmed?
Okay, then please take care of it
right away. I'm on my way now.
Everyone, enjoy your meal.
Something's come up,
so I have to leave first.
Sure thing.
Where's Director Park Min Jun?
He's Vice President Park now.
By order of the vice president,
Ms. Choi Yu Na,
your employment
is hereby terminated.
Terminated?
What are you talking about?
Seven years ago,
you submitted a design
to the New Design Competition.
But it wasn't your work.
I submitted the evidence...
and had your award revoked.
What?
Park Min Jun, you...
Your study-abroad scholarship
and job offer tied to your award...
have also been revoked.
You'll have to return
the study-abroad funds,
and I'm also filing a lawsuit
against you...
for business interference,
- so prepare yourself.
- Is this really necessary?
I'm just getting started.
I'll recover everything you stole
from Jin Ju,
down to the very last thing.
Manager Kang,
- drag her out of here.
- Yes, sir.
Don't be ridiculous.
Everything I have,
I earned through my own hard work.
I'll be back.
I'll find a way to come back!
Let me go.
What's going on here?
It was discovered...
that Choi Yu Na stole
someone else's design...
seven years ago.
Her award has been revoked,
and she's currently
being terminated.
Her award was revoked?
I'm telling you, this is unfair.
Was this ordered by Park Min Jun?
Yes. It was
the first official order he gave...
after becoming vice president.
So that's why he left in a hurry.
In any case,
I'm glad this wrong
has finally been righted.
If you'll excuse me...
Seven years ago,
you stole Baek Jin Ju's design.
I reported it, too.
What?
You reported it seven years ago?
Well,
I reported it
on Baek Jin Ju's behalf.
The judging committee was supposed
to meet again for a review.
I guess we're finally seeing
the outcome now.
You're the one who reported it,
not Baek Jin Ju?
Yu Na!
Anyway, take care.
Let's try not to see
each other again. Okay?
Let's go.
So it wasn't Baek Jin Ju.
It was you, Park Hyun Jun?
My stomach!
Jung Ran, are you okay?
- Jung Ran, come on.
- What's wrong?
Mrs. Ok,
what did you put in our food?
What the heck did you put in it
to make my stomach churn like this?
- My stomach!
- Hold on.
I didn't put anything in it.
Let me see. Where does it hurt?
How bad is it?
- Where?
- My stomach!
No!
Let go of me.
- My stomach!
- Let go of me. Stop.
James asked about my past?
Exactly.
I was trying to see
if Chloe really lost her memory,
but he started asking
about your past, Dan Hui.
Why my past?
Yes, Mrs. Ok.
What? Driver Song got out?
Yes, I hear you.
I'll report this to Ms. Kim.
Driver Song isn't the type
to plan his own escape.
Either Oh Jung Ran helped him,
or Park Hyun Jun and Chloe
broke him out.
We need to quickly find out
what Chloe is up to.
Wait.
What's that?
Did James drop this?
Perfect.
I could barely get a read on him,
so let's go
through his wallet instead.
She told me to get out, so I did,
but she's in there alone.
Will she be okay?
We're doing this to save my mom,
so please cooperate for now.
All right.
What do you need me to tell you?
When President Kim Myung Hui
first came to the Adele family,
please tell us
what it was like back then.
I'm looking into Kim Dan Hui,
and I need to know
what happened at the time.
Are you talking...
about the day
she showed up holding Park Min Jun?
Gosh, just thinking about that day
makes my legs tremble.
A dead person...
showed up holding a baby.
I'm telling you,
I thought she was a ghost.
Wait, a dead person?
That's right.
She was definitely dead.
But she went to an OB-GYN clinic,
had a baby,
disappeared without a trace,
and then suddenly reappeared.
She said she lost her memory
during childbirth,
which is why she came back so late.
I guess...
only she and that obstetrician...
know the truth about what happened.
That obstetrician.
Could we try contacting the doctor?
Gosh, no.
He shut down his clinic
and left for the US.
He'll be hard to find.
Still,
maybe you could give us the name
of the clinic or the doctor.
It was Baek OB-GYN.
The doctor's name was Baek Jun Gi.
Baek Jun Gi?
The name sounds familiar,
doesn't it?
He has the same name
as Temi Bio's CEO.
That's how I remember it.
I see.
I think that covers everything.
Go ahead and help Mr. Song
find a place to stay.
It's all right. I can cover it.
I'm offering, so just take it.
You should head out now.
Once you've helped Mr. Song,
head home.
You should check on your mother.
You're right.
Good.
- Well, I'll be on my way then.
- Yes, of course.
Thank you.
Doctor Baek Jun Gi from Baek OB-GYN.
That's my dad.
Could President Kim...
have some connection to my dad?
(Hanbit High School
62nd Graduation Ceremony)
Why are they in the photo
with Dr. Baek?
Don't tell me Chloe is...
She's Baek Jin Ju.
She was alive?
(Hanbit High School
62nd Graduation Ceremony)
My father told me I was born
at his OB-GYN clinic.
Then does that mean Min Jun and I
were born on the same day...
and at the same place?
Come to think of it,
after Dr. Baek came back to the US,
he looked for someone.
He said it was the person
who delivered you...
and that he wanted to help them.
Don't tell me that person was...
(President Kim Myung Hui)
So Chloe was
Dr. Baek's daughter after all.
Baek Jin Ju was alive.
Kim Dan Hui.
She's the one who delivered me
at my dad's clinic?
What exactly was her connection
to my dad?
(Pearl in Red)
How did Kim Dan Hui manage
to endure all those years?
She had someone to protect.
Why does she care
so much about Min Jun,
yet she's determined
to remain married to Hyun Jun?
What's this?
"Claim for Damages."
One million dollars?
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)