(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
(Marriage Registration:
Park Tae Ho, Kim Myung Hui)
(Episode 75)
So in the end,
you're no different...
from Oh Jung Ran.
Kim Myung Hui,
why were you at Eunhwa Trading?
I promised you marriage...
and access to my slush fund ledger.
Yet, you betrayed me
and conspired with Chloe.
For what, exactly?
This is the money
Park Cheol Su demanded.
Give him this money and tell him
to stay overseas for a while.
If I so much as see his shadow,
tell him he'll never see
the light of day again.
Yes, I understand.
Darn.
Also, effective immediately,
I need to resume
my position as chairman.
Yes, I'll make the arrangements.
Park Cheol Su.
- What do you want?
- Park Cheol Su,
you killed someone with a bomb,
didn't you?
That money in the trunk is
from Chairman Park Tae Ho of Adele.
- Hey, hold still.
- Let me go.
We'll make sure you get
to the police station safely.
Darn, let go of me.
Darn you.
We turned Park Cheol Su over
to the police.
Right. The intel team and I...
found his residence
and tipped off the police,
so they'll definitely find evidence
that he was making explosives.
Then let's request to have
Dr. Baek's accident reinvestigated.
Okay.
This is all thanks
to your help, Ms. Kim.
- Thank you.
- Not yet. It's too soon for that.
We have to prove
Park Tae Ho was involved.
Park Tae Ho is suspicious of me,
and he said
he's returning as chairman.
If Chairman Park returns,
won't he derail the investigation?
It'd be great to get him
under investigation right away.
That way, we could stop him
from returning as chairman.
Is there any way to get him
investigated right now?
We can't get him investigated
for what happened seven years ago,
but it might be possible on charges
related to illegal explosives.
That's a good idea.
I'll have the intel team report it,
and I'll lead the police to him.
James and I will move quickly
to get him arrested.
We'll prepare
for an emergency board meeting.
Once Chairman Park is arrested,
I'm going to take the position
of acting chairman.
We have to stop him from returning.
The police arrested Park Cheol Su?
How did that happen?
He said he'd lay low overseas
once he got the money!
It seems he was caught
while collecting the money.
Whatever!
Get our people
in the police moving...
before Park Cheol Su spills
what happened seven years ago.
Right now!
That's the thing.
I can't get in touch
with our contacts on the force.
After you collapsed,
the payments to them stopped, and...
What?
The problem wasn't
who to entrust with the slush fund.
I should've taken care of those
who were protecting me first.
- Take the money and see them now!
- Yes, sir.
You had me thrown out like you
never wanted to see me again.
What do you want?
The Temi Bio incident
from seven years ago.
Does Kim Myung Hui
really know everything?
I told you she does.
You finally believe me?
How did Kim Myung Hui find out?
Well...
I told her.
What?
You were so infatuated with her
that I had no choice.
Oh Jung Ran!
Anyway, what matters is
that she knows everything.
She won't let you
get away with murder.
She'll turn on you...
and make you pay for what you did.
But me?
As long as you don't abandon me...
and make Hyun Jun your successor,
I don't care about anything else.
I'll even deal with Kim Myung Hui.
Can't you just give me
one more chance?
(Adele)
(Chairman Park Tae Ho)
She thinks she can just
get rid of me,
Park Tae Ho of the Adele Group?
Kim Myung Hui.
You're going to pay
for betraying me.
Sir.
Right. Any update on Park Cheol Su?
What about our police contacts?
Well, we've got a problem.
You have to leave immediately.
- What?
- Hurry.
What's all this?
- You punks.
- Park Tae Ho.
You know Park Cheol Su, correct?
You're under emergency arrest
for ordering...
the manufacture
and use of explosives.
What?
An emergency arrest?
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
Shut it!
Do you even know
who you're talking to?
Which precinct are you from?
What division? You punks.
Let go of me!
- Take him away.
- Manager Kang.
Find out
which precinct they're from.
I'll make sure
they never wear a badge again.
The police or assemblymen.
Get someone on the line!
Let go of me.
Let go.
- Let go of me, you punks.
- Legal Team, get on this now.
Move it.
How dare you arrest me
in my own company?
I'm Park Tae Ho of Adele!
You punks.
You punks. Let me go.
Sir!
Kim Myung Hui.
Sir.
You actually dared to...
What are you talking about?
There's no point
in pretending you don't know.
I already know everything.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
For now, please stay put.
I'll look into this
and handle it immediately.
Kim Myung Hui, you...
Father!
- What is all this?
- What's happening?
He's being arrested on suspicion
of ordering the manufacture...
and use of explosives.
Explosives?
You two. Mobilize the legal team!
- Now.
- Take him.
Let go of me. Let go!
- Let go, you punks.
- Sir!
- Let go!
Let go. Don't you know who I am?
Sir.
Illegal explosives? That's absurd.
Just hang in there.
The truth...
will come out.
You just wait.
I'll expose you
for faking your amnesia...
to fool me.
Let go, you punks. Let go of me!
As the special July session of the
National Assembly gets underway,
the ruling and opposition parties...
remain deadlocked over a budget
and public livelihood bills.
The local elections...
Yu Na says her case won't go
as far as a lawsuit,
but knowing Park Min Jun,
don't you think he'll sue?
Definitely.
Yu Na is kidding herself
if she thinks it won't end in a lawsuit.
Didn't she say
she'd hold her ground if he sues?
That means she's ready for a fight,
one way or another.
Right. Then we need...
- to be prepared.
- Of course.
Of all the lawyers we consulted,
who should we hire?
What about him?
Kim Genius.
- Let's go with Genius.
- Next, news on the Adele Group.
Adele Group Chairman Park Tae Ho
was arrested...
on suspicion of orchestrating
the manufacture...
- of illegal explosives.
- Chairman Park was arrested?
We have the story.
- You've got to be kidding me.
- Adele's chairman Park Tae Ho...
was taken into custody
for commissioning the manufacture...
- of illegal explosives.
- Wait. Chairman Park...
He did what with a bomb?
Oh my goodness.
I thought wrecking our house
was bad enough.
But bombs?
What did I tell you?
Chairman Park is a dangerous man.
Oh my. What do you suppose
he used that bomb for?
Honey, could he have...
killed someone with it?
It's only an allegation.
- What?
- Nothing's been confirmed yet,
so watch what you say.
- What was that?
- Are you taking his side?
I don't know.
Just don't say anything.
Park Tae Ho.
You suspect Kim Myung Hui,
so why aren't you doing anything?
I thought you'd have me
take her on again.
Because I got the best
of you last time,
you won't give me another chance?
What am I supposed to do?
What do you mean?
You have to keep at it.
The plum extract has
to be made today, so hurry up.
I don't have time to be sitting here
plucking plum stems.
Oh Jung Ran.
From now on, your job is to sit here
plucking plum stems.
Face reality.
What is it?
Who's calling?
Why are you being so secretive?
I'm not being secretive.
I'll take this call,
so keep plucking those stems.
If you cause trouble,
I'll report you to Ms. Kim.
And if you even think
about running away,
remember that you'll never
be allowed back in.
Are you my creditor now?
Why are you here again?
Haven't you heard?
The chairman was arrested
for something involving explosives.
What?
Park Tae Ho was arrested
by the police?
(Adele Chairman Park Arrested
on Explosives Scandal)
At this rate,
the Temi Bio incident from
seven years ago could be exposed.
You must've done something...
under the chairman's orders
back then, too.
I knew it.
You were involved somehow,
weren't you?
Right. Ever since you started
blackmailing me about Temi Bio,
I had my suspicions.
That's why we have to get
the chairman out.
Not through his connections,
but through yours.
If we pull this off,
it's a huge opportunity for us.
We cover up the incident
from seven years ago...
and earn Park Tae Ho's trust.
Exactly.
I'll take down Park Min Jun,
and you can...
reclaim your place as his wife...
and go after President Kim.
Then we need connections powerful enough
to get Park Tae Ho released.
Maybe that guy...
Who?
Do you know someone in the police?
I know a guy with power
who loves money.
Then call him. No, go meet him.
Right now.
Wait.
But there's one big problem.
What's that?
Well...
I'm broke.
What?
Park Tae Ho cleared me out
when he locked me in the basement.
That guy will want
at least 100,000 dollars.
What about you?
You must have some money, right?
Were you behind my father's arrest?
Yes, that was me.
I caught the person...
who planted the bomb
in my dad's car seven years ago.
- How?
- James helped me.
Then you should've told me.
You have enough
to deal with already.
I didn't want to burden you
with my problems.
And I can't talk about...
my relationship
with President Kim yet either.
I'm sorry.
Come on.
I'm not asking for an apology.
I just want to help you, that's all.
I know.
The case from seven years ago
can't be reopened just yet,
so for now,
Chairman Park has been charged
in connection...
with illegal explosives.
Where do you go from here?
I'm not sure.
I'll talk to James about it first.
Why do I feel so useless now?
Have you changed,
or am I the one who's changed...
now that I'm not...
Park Tae Ho's son anymore?
What's the deal with my father?
Did you have something
to do with this?
Yes, this was my doing.
With your mother's help.
What?
Your mother found out
that I'm Baek Jin Ju.
I wasn't going to tell you,
but I'm telling you now
because Chairman Park has been arrested.
When and how did she find out?
Does this mean you and my mother...
have worked out your differences enough
to work together?
Just because I worked
with your mother...
doesn't mean anything's changed.
Things are still over between us.
I should still stay out of it,
is that it?
I get what you mean.
If that's what you want,
I'll stay out of it.
Just...
don't do anything too dangerous.
You must be here about your father.
I heard you found out
that Chloe is Jin Ju.
How...
I heard it from Jin Ju directly.
Right.
I found out a little while ago.
I'm sorry
I couldn't tell you sooner.
It's all right.
Jin Ju probably told you not to.
She doesn't like me getting involved
in her business.
But you want to help her, don't you?
Yes.
Then quietly monitor
the legal team's response.
All right.
I'll see to it
that Father is fully investigated.
You haven't told Min Jun
about your sister, have you?
No.
I want to tell him in my own time.
By the way, it seems
Min Jun still has feelings...
for Jin Ju.
It's such a shame that
their shared fate has gone so awry.
Jin Ju's feelings are
just as important too.
If they're not meant to be,
then that must be fate as well.
Mr. Park.
Why did you hand
this bag of cash to Park Cheol Su?
Come on.
I don't know anything about that.
Mr. Park Cheol Su.
You made a deal with Park Tae Ho
regarding explosives, didn't you?
I'm exercising my right
to remain silent.
Look here.
I'm Park Tae Ho of Adele Group.
When the company's lawyers get here,
you can talk to them.
Right, Chloe. I should call her.
She's the fastest way to get money.
Not Chloe.
If we save the chairman
with her money,
she'll get all the credit.
If she wins him over
and gains power,
do you think she'll look out for us?
The two of us have to handle this.
So what are you suggesting?
You really don't have
any money tucked away?
Besides Chloe, is there anyone else
you can borrow money from?
Park Tae Ho cleaned me out
when all this happened.
Besides, who would lend me money
in my situation?
Jung Ran.
What on earth?
Wait, how did you even get in?
You wouldn't leave,
so I had to sneak in
through the crawl space.
I thought I told you to leave
Hyun Jun and Jung Ran alone.
Hold on.
Were you spying on me?
You're harassing both Hyun Jun
and Jung Ran, so of course...
That's it. You.
Mr. Song?
What are the three of you doing?
First...
Run!
- What?
- Goodness. Oh Jung Ran, no.
Let go of me. Oh Jung Ran!
What took you so long?
I've been waiting forever.
So, what's the total?
This is my entire life savings.
You said Hyun Jun needed it,
so I scraped together
everything I have.
What are you going to use
this money for?
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm a cop sent by Mr. Park,
so you'd better start talking.
Wait. Detective Yun? From back then?
Detective Yun?
That's ancient history.
I'm a high-ranking officer now.
The commissioner's right-hand man,
the second-in-command.
Jung Ran,
you said this was for Hyun Jun,
so why is he...
Let's have a seat first.
Then we'll talk.
To what do I owe a visit from Adele?
You must've heard the news
about the chairman.
I need you to get him out.
What? Why are you using my money
to get Chairman Park out?
This is an emergency.
What do you take me for?
I'm not the same person
I used to be.
If you don't cooperate,
we'll report you for taking bribes.
What do you all think you're doing?
Isn't it obvious?
Since money didn't work,
we're blackmailing you.
Take our money,
and get the chairman out.
Or get in trouble
for taking money from us.
For a high-ranking police officer,
isn't just the allegation enough
to cause a problem?
Someone at my level...
can have you...
all thrown in jail
for blackmailing me.
Who do you think you are, trying to
blackmail me with this chump change?
So how about it?
Do you want to see the inside
of a holding cell?
Is this the best Adele can do?
Wait.
What if we up the scale?
Think of this
as just a down payment.
If you get the chairman out,
he'll make sure...
you're compensated properly.
That's right.
Do you think that's all he'll do?
The Adele Group could
have your back, you know.
Second-in-command, are you?
Becoming number one would be
a piece of cake.
Deal?
You told Min Jun
we worked together, right?
Yes. Since Chairman Park
was arrested,
I felt it was time to tell him.
But that doesn't mean Min Jun
is going to work with us.
I already told him
to stay out of my business.
Right, that's what he told me.
I just heard from Butler Ok.
Oh Jung Ran escaped.
She did what?
- How?
- I don't know the details,
but she left with Choi Yu Na
and Driver Song.
After hearing about
Chairman Park's arrest,
don't you think
they're up to something?
I'll look into it.
I planted a bug in the annex
to keep an eye on Oh Jung Ran.
A listening device?
Then we might be able to find out
what Oh Jung Ran...
and Choi Yu Na are plotting.
Yes, I'll go in and see
if anything was recorded.
Okay.
How's the police investigation
going?
Park Cheol Su and Chairman Park
aren't saying anything.
And since
there's no other solid evidence,
they could be released
within 48 hours.
The emergency board meeting is
still on for tomorrow, right?
Yes. I'm going to be appointed
as acting chairman.
I'll try to convince the board
and the shareholders...
to keep Chairman Park
from coming back.
What?
Moon Tae Jin,
the largest shareholder,
is recommending me for that?
That's right.
He...
must've seen the news
about Chairman Park's arrest.
Chairman Park is involved
in a crime,
and on top of that,
he and Oh Jung Ran...
have filed for divorce.
Given the circumstances,
he suggested that instead...
of serving as acting chairman,
you take the chairman's seat.
Me, as chairman?
If you're going to fight
Park Tae Ho and Oh Jung Ran...
and you're determined
to take over the Adele Group,
isn't this a great opportunity?
If you're determined to do this,
Moon Tae Jin will throw
his full support behind you.
Please don't take
too long to decide.
Not Chloe.
If we save the chairman
with her money,
she'll get all the credit.
If she wins him over
and gains power,
do you think she'll look out for us?
The two of us have to handle this.
Oh Jung Ran and Choi Yu Na plan
to buy Chairman Park's freedom.
If he gets out scot-free
and comes back...
I was going to ask you
before I hung it up.
I didn't want to get ahead
of myself again,
like I did when I proposed.
You know there's
an emergency board meeting...
tomorrow morning, right?
Yes. I heard President Kim is
going to be the acting chairman.
What's your plan?
What do you need me to do?
Skip the board meeting tomorrow...
and talk to me instead.
About what?
Can't we talk about it now?
No. We'll talk tomorrow morning.
I still have a few things
to take care of.
Once I'm done,
we'll hang this photo together.
You want me to become the chairman,
not just the acting chairman?
Jin Ju is saying the same thing
Mrs. Han said.
I found out about Oh Jung Ran
and Choi Yu Na's plan...
from the bug I planted in the annex.
They're using police connections
and even money...
to get Chairman Park out.
If Chairman Park gets out scot-free,
it'll be hard to stop him
from returning as chairman.
It'd be better for you to take
the chairman's seat yourself.
Then even if Chairman Park returns,
it'll be difficult for him
to retake the position.
But isn't that different
from your plan?
For now, we have to stop
Chairman Park from coming back.
As things stand,
neither you, Hyun Jun,
nor I are qualified to be chairman.
If we don't want Chairman Park
back in that seat,
you're our best option, Ms. Kim.
I agree with Jin Ju.
Mother, are you good with this?
All right, let's do it.
(Emergency Board Meeting,
Chairman Appointment)
The Adele Group...
emergency board meeting
will now begin.
Today's agenda concerns
the appointment...
of President Kim Myung Hui
as chairman.
First, we'll hear
from President Kim Myung Hui.
How dare you...
try to replace me as chairman?
(Pearl in Red)
Now I finally see what you're
really after, Kim Myung Hui.
How dare you try to push me out
and take my seat as chairman?
You're making a mistake.
You're putting Oh Jung Ran
in my place?
You'll regret it.
If I use Hyun Jun's weakness
to marry into the Adele family,
both he and Adele will be mine.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)