(All people, incidents,
and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious
and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children were filmed
under production guidelines.)
What kind of paintings
did Oh Jung Ran make off with?
Chairman Park said they're paintings
that can't be reported stolen.
They must be pieces that were traded
under the table to avoid taxes.
Since Oh Jung Ran was
in charge of them,
she'd know them better than anyone.
But...
If Oh Jung Ran disappears,
what happens with the divorce?
Filing the divorce papers is useless
if she's not there in person.
Somehow, we have to get her
to come back.
What on earth? Who drives like that?
Hey. Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm fine. And you?
- I'm fine too.
I thought it was Oh Jung Ran.
Oh Jung Ran?
Oh Jung Ran's cornered.
Who knows what she'll do?
It's unnerving that she stole
the paintings and then vanished.
I'm worried about what she might do
to you to protect her secrets.
(Locked)
(Unlocked)
I'm glad it was you who came.
At least you didn't trust that witch
Kim Myung Hui with everything.
The passcode to this storage vault.
You couldn't bring yourself
to give her that, right?
What is this?
You stole the paintings
and were just waiting for me?
Why?
To tell me you're sorry...
and beg me to let it slide
this once?
If I begged you for forgiveness,
would you even spare me?
Good grief.
How could I spare the person
who tried to kill my son?
Not after you took advantage...
of the precautions I put in place
at the warehouse.
Then tell me.
Were you really going to kill me?
I see.
You figured it out,
which is why you pulled this stunt?
It's been 40 years
since we met at Munhwadang.
We've been married
for over 30 years.
But how could you...
even think of killing me?
If our Hyun Jun finds out the truth,
what are you going to do?
Your past as a murderer
has come to light,
along with your crime
of trying to harm my son!
Instead of prison,
you've chosen to go to your grave.
I'll take care of everything...
so Hyun Jun won't get hurt.
You don't have to worry
about a thing.
All right? Don't worry.
Don't you worry.
Don't worry.
(Adele)
Oh Jung Ran...
I at least...
gave you a chance, you know.
If you had said you'd spare me
for Hyun Jun's sake,
I wouldn't have betrayed you
like this.
The drug's hitting you hard,
isn't it?
I never thought I'd end up...
using what I learned from you
against you.
You... How dare you...
You're the one
who made me like this!
Jung Ran?
I've taken care of Director Kang.
From now on,
I'll be the one
painting the picture.
A new one, in a world
without Park Tae Ho.
But don't you worry.
For now,
you're more useful to me alive
than dead.
Ms. Kim.
Is something wrong?
The chairman hasn't come home yet.
He said he had work at the gallery.
I guess he's just running late.
It's just that
I can't reach Director Kang either.
He always calls ahead whenever
the chairman is running late.
With the house in an uproar
over Ms. Oh, I'm very worried.
I know what Ms. Oh is capable of,
so I'm worried something
might have happened to him.
Wait.
I'll try calling the gallery again.
No. Check on Min Jun first.
Right, I'll do that.
Ta-da.
Remember when you got rid
of our burned watches?
I promised I'd make you a new set.
What do you think?
What is it? Don't you like it?
No, it's not that.
Then what is it?
You've been quiet all evening.
- Hyun Jun said...
- Park Hyun Jun?
What did he say?
Forget that. You were out of line
at the cafe earlier.
With what?
You can't be serious.
With that waitress?
You expected me to just stand there
while she was making eyes at you?
All right, I get it.
I'll say I was in the wrong.
Just don't be mad.
When you look at me
with those cold eyes,
it honestly scares me.
It scares you?
As much as I love you,
I'm just as afraid.
It scares me when you're cold to me.
I'm always worried...
that you'll grow to hate me.
From the moment we met until now,
I've always been more in love
than you.
I rushed to come back to work
just so I could be with you,
and I get jealous
of some random server.
That's how much I need you.
Before you get so angry,
can't you try to see
where I'm coming from?
Whatever else I may have forgotten,
I should've remembered
your feelings.
I feel like I've really forgotten
what's most important.
I'm sorry.
Give me your hand.
Let me put yours on first.
I wish you would never
get your memory back.
I wish you'd forget Jin Ju and Chloe
and just smile at me,
and only me.
You finally see me.
Don't go by yourself.
Like this. Let me join you.
- I get it, so please let go.
- Just for today.
Let me have this.
What's going on with my father
is crushing me,
and my mom, who's always hitting
rock bottom, is too much to handle.
Holding on to you like this
is the only way...
I think I can survive.
The person
who's hurting you the most...
might...
be me.
If this is about Min Jun,
don't.
Even though I know...
how much you're struggling,
I still...
I need you
to help me convince Chairman Park.
I also want to meet board members
who were close to your mother.
If President Kim Myung Hui...
takes your mother's place
as the chairman's wife,
it could get in the way
of our plans.
That's...
the kind of thing
I want to talk about.
It'll be hard to talk to my father
because of what's going on with Mom,
but I'll arrange a meeting
with the board.
And as for President Kim,
Min Jun's mother...
She'll take Min Jun's side.
Is that...
the answer you wanted?
I'm sorry.
But at least...
you get how I feel.
Meanwhile, my parents...
don't even care how I feel.
But you hold my hand like this,
and you even tell me you're sorry.
So...
don't be the person
who's hurting me the most.
Be the one who comforts me.
Be that person for me.
Min Jun, are you okay?
Nothing happened, right?
I'm fine.
I just didn't see the text asking me
to come home early until later.
Did something happen
at the house again?
It's about the chairman.
Well,
it looks like there's a problem
at the gallery.
I tried to check
the chairman's access logs,
but the CCTV and security system
were off.
You're saying you don't know
the chairman's whereabouts?
Currently, Manager Kang
and the chairman are missing.
No one's been able to reach him...
ever since he went to the gallery
because of Ms. Oh.
Do you think
she could be behind this?
Oh Jung Ran...
Oh Jung Ran, untie me right now!
You still don't get it, do you?
Did you expect me
to tremble in fear and untie you...
just because you yelled?
Oh Jung Ran!
Then again,
I guess that's how I lived
beside you.
Terrified of you, always walking
on eggshells, trembling,
desperately trying to get
on your good side,
only to be hurt and disappointed
every single time.
That's how it's been
for over 30 years.
I don't know
why I put up with it for so long.
If you stop this right now,
I'll forgive you.
Just untie me already.
You'll forgive me?
I'm the one who should be
doing the forgiving, not you.
You tried to choke me to death.
Fine.
Fine, I get it.
I was wrong, so just untie me.
Let's go back together, make up,
and put this all behind us.
Go back?
To a life spent competing over
who's better?
I'm sick of walking on eggshells
around you,
and now I have to do it
around Kim Myung Hui too?
I...
refuse to live like that anymore.
I told you, didn't I?
I'm painting a new picture.
You just lie there
with your eyes closed...
and watch the show.
No!
Oh Jung Ran!
There's been no word all night.
Something must have happened.
We need to call the police
right now.
No, not the police.
It would cause a panic
at Adele Group.
For starters,
the stock price would nosedive.
Mother.
Now that my father isn't here,
you're starting to sound
just like him.
It's what's best
for your mother, too.
If the police investigate,
everyone will know she was disowned,
making her the prime suspect
in the chairman's kidnapping.
Oh Jung Ran kidnapped Chairman Park?
That's what Hyun Jun said.
Apparently, that's what
President Kim suspects.
Why would Oh Jung Ran do that?
Because she got kicked out
of the family?
But would she really go that far?
There must be more to it, right?
So, what are you going to do?
- Secretary Jung.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hire some people you can trust
to be discreet,
and have them look
for Manager Kang, the chairman,
as well as Oh Jung Ran.
Understood.
What should I tell the company?
Tell them he's recovering
for health reasons.
It's nothing serious,
but he'll be stepping back
from management.
Stepping away from management?
He's only been gone for one night.
You're jumping the gun.
Let's just say he's on vacation
or a business trip.
I'd hate to think
you're making a power grab...
while my father's away.
I know this is a new situation,
and it's unsettling for all of us.
Myself included.
I hope the chairman returns soon,
but we have to be prepared
for the worst.
Things are going to get busy
for you two,
so for the time being,
I need you to do exactly as I say.
Sure.
But please, find our father quickly.
Of course. Absolutely.
Do you really think
Oh Jung Ran is behind this?
If she didn't want the divorce,
she could've just disappeared.
If her secret was the problem,
why target the chairman and not you?
What if...
Chairman Park targeted Oh Jung Ran
because of what she did to Min Jun,
and Oh Jung Ran just struck first?
What?
You think this is the result of them
trying to kill each other?
For now, I'm just considering
the worst-case scenario.
It's hard to imagine Oh Jung Ran
getting the better of Chairman Park.
But even if that were the case,
why should we be worried about him?
After everything he did to Dr. Baek,
who cares what happens to him?
This isn't for Chairman Park's sake.
I'm trying to find him
because I can't trust Oh Jung Ran.
If Oh Jung Ran
is really behind this,
then there's no telling
what she'll do next.
In any case,
Oh Jung Ran is the problem.
So while we're looking
for Oh Jung Ran,
we're going to make the most
of Chairman Park's absence.
Make the most of it?
While the chairman is gone,
we need to build our power base.
I'll consolidate
the Executive Office,
Finance, and Legal divisions...
and bring
all of the company's information,
assets, and legal affairs
under my control.
Can you really pull all that off
at once?
I have a plan.
Call a meeting
with the executives immediately.
Sure.
(Adele)
I assume you've all heard
about the Chairman.
Yes.
Is he going to be all right?
Do we have any idea
how long he'll be gone?
It's hard to say at this point.
What about his wife, then?
We haven't been able
to reach her either.
Is something wrong?
She'll also be away for a while.
Actually, she's gone for good.
For good?
Secretary Jung.
Yes, ma'am.
(Application for Divorce
by Mutual Consent)
The chairman is in the process
of divorcing his wife.
What? Is this true?
Wait a minute.
Couldn't these papers be forged?
If this turns out
to be untrue later on,
you can hold me accountable.
So, you're saying
the divorce is real?
But why?
The reason for their divorce
is a private matter,
so I will not comment further.
Until the chairman returns,
we must focus on
keeping the company stable.
For that reason,
I am forming
an Emergency Management Team.
- An Emergency Management Team?
- What?
What's an Emergency Management Team?
What the...
Wait, but...
Adele Group...
is now under emergency management?
Why would Oh Jung Ran
kidnap Park Tae Ho?
The question is,
what is she planning to do next?
President Kim Myung Hui seems
to be overlooking that.
We need to move quickly...
and track down
Oh Jung Ran ourselves.
Okay, got it.
They still haven't found...
Chairman Park and Oh Jung Ran,
have they?
They're the best,
so let's give them some more time.
Okay.
So, what's your plan now?
You were trying to strip
Chairman Park of his power,
but it looks like Kim Myung Hui...
and Park Min Jun
will end up with it instead.
Regardless, I'll still make my move
to take over Adele.
I can't let someone else be the one
to punish Chairman Park.
James, have the team keep looking
for Chairman Park and Oh Jung Ran.
I'm going to Adele
to see what's going on.
All right, let's get moving.
- What is this?
- What's going on?
What happened?
Where on earth did he go?
What the...
What's going on?
Why is everyone in a panic?
- Did you hear?
- I did.
Don't you think you're coming here
a little too often?
You're not even married
to Park Hyun Jun yet.
Know your place.
The same goes for you, doesn't it?
I heard you got kicked out
of the company.
I'm helping Director Park Min Jun
with company business.
I'm here on my father's behalf
to assess the situation at Adele.
With our exclusive development
rights project coming up,
it's only right to check on things
now that the chairman is away.
Exclusive development rights?
Wait, forget that.
The chairman is away?
- Why?
- For someone helping Mr. Park,
you're a little behind on the news.
Park Min Jun!
Min Jun, I heard the chairman
has gone missing. What's going on?
I don't really know myself.
They're saying Hyun Jun's mother
kidnapped my father.
What? Ms. Oh kidnapped the chairman?
You've always been by my side,
so you know about my family, right?
- What?
- I've been confused...
ever since my accident.
Why would Hyun Jun's mother
try to kill me?
Just start by telling me that.
That's not
what's important right now.
Your mother's forming an Emergency
Management Team. You must help her.
With the chairman and Ms. Oh
both out of the picture,
your mother
will take over management,
and you'll become the successor
instead of Park Hyun Jun.
Did you talk to your mom
about getting me reinstated?
I think I could be a valuable asset
to the Emergency Management Team.
I'll go see if there's
anything I can do to help.
Is she still avoiding
talking about my accident?
My mother and Choi Yu Na.
Why are they hiding this from me?
What exactly happened...
during the time I can't remember?
Kim Myung Hui and Park Min Jun.
Look at them,
living as if nothing's changed.
Even after
I was thrown out like this,
they act like nothing's happened.
Those two must be relieved
that you're gone.
Why did you have someone follow them
and take pictures?
I was hoping
they'd look out for Hyun Jun.
I checked the photos myself.
It seems that Chloe
is taking care of Hyun Jun.
Am I supposed to be relieved?
So what are you going to do now?
Manager Kang.
Are you still thinking about it?
I know you're Park Tae Ho's man,
but he's just going
to keep lying there in that bed.
Are you okay with your mother's
medical support being cut off?
Ms. Oh!
You have no other choice,
so why pretend you're deciding?
Don't you know
the sooner you decide, the better?
I'll do it. I'll do as you say.
Are you trying to interfere
with emergency management?
As I see it, Chloe is an outsider
with no authority here.
Being my fiancee...
gives her every right.
Did the chairman approve
of your marriage?
Does it matter?
Now that my father is gone,
I don't think his approval matters.
I'll be moving forward
with the marriage...
and the exclusive
development rights.
You can do as you please
with the marriage,
but the exclusive development rights
require the CEO's approval.
Now that you've seized
emergency control of the company,
are you saying you won't approve it?
Does that mean you're opposed
to the exclusive development rights?
That goes without saying,
doesn't it?
During a crisis,
we can't approve a deal
that's this one-sided.
Hey.
This has nothing to do with you.
I'm here on Min Jun's behalf.
You're trying to take
Min Jun's place as the successor,
and I'm here to stop you.
Everyone has said their piece.
You may leave now.
Congratulations, Mother.
Congratulations?
For seizing control of Adele.
Even so, now isn't exactly
the right time for congratulations.
Anyway, you're going to make Min Jun
the successor now, aren't you?
But Min Jun still hasn't
recovered his memory,
so if you reinstate me,
I'll stay by his side and help him.
I'll think about it. You may go now.
I have a lot to do.
Sure.
Park Hyun Jun...
He's more aggressive about
the succession than I expected.
Is he getting ambitious
because of Chloe?
Or is Chloe the one pushing him?
(Mrs. Han)
(Adele Group)
(Power of Delegation
for Acting Duties)
We have to stop Oh Jung Ran...
before she returns
with the power of attorney.
(Pearl in Red)
If Oh Jung Ran can't be stopped,
the company
and Min Jun's place as successor...
will both go down the drain.
An emergency board meeting?
President Kim is trying...
- Min Jun!
- to take control of the company.
We must find your mother and prepare
before the board meeting.
It's about time
we made our move, honey.
Want to know why I spared your life?
You're about to find out.
(Subtitles are provided by KOCOWA.)