Let's do this.
What's left?
Seon Ho seems to have pork.
I have my spicy pork.
- To be honest...
- Yes?
I lost my spicy pork.
But I can put my rice in my soup...
and eat it with the kimchi...
- and shredded radish kimchi.
- Okay.
I have the rolled omelet.
- Sae Ho?
- Number seven is seaweed soup.
- DinDin, your number seven is?
- Seaweed soup.
This is about Seon Ho's pork.
- Let's do this. You can manage it.
- Win for me.
Seon Ho will start.
- I go 1st?
- Seon Ho's 1st?
One, two, three, go!
- "Bohemian Rhapsody."
- Correct.
- That's it.
- I'm too scared to play now.
Go!
- Three!
- Sphinx.
- Yes.
- Correct.
One, two, three,
- go!
- "Immortal Songs."
Correct.
One, two, three, go!
- Three!
- "Teach Me."
- Correct.
- Gosh.
- That was a confusing one.
- Okay.
Go!
- Three, two...
- Power bank.
- Yes.
- Correct.
- Here we go.
- It's me again.
I'll give you some pork.
Go! Three, two...
- Toe socks!
- Correct!
- What?
- That was a hard one.
- Toe socks?
- Toe socks.
I thought it was
Pippi Longstocking or something.
Okay, go!
Three, two...
- Vacuum cleaner.
- one!
- Correct.
- Okay, let's go!
I thought it was "air purifier."
That's what I thought it was.
Well done.
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two...
- Oh, okay.
- Everest.
- Yes.
- Correct.
- Okay.
Okay, let's go!
(The fate of Seon Ho's pork...)
(and the guys' seaweed soup
depends on the last quiz.)
Go!
- Three!
- Okay.
- Two!
- Speed bump.
- Okay.
- Okay!
Correct.
You win the seventh round.
(Round 7 is a success!)
- Number 8...
- Number 8!
If we defend number eight,
- it's not too bad.
- We can still eat.
- If we share...
- My number eight...
We can still eat.
I got lots of crunchy fried chicken.
My number eight is rice.
My eight is rice too.
- Mine is rice too.
- We did well.
- You end with pork?
- Spicy pork.
- Please.
- Today...
This is madness.
Let's play.
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two...
- Mona Lisa.
- Correct.
- The first try is hard.
- Go! Three!
- Okay.
- Two...
- "The Wizard of Oz."
- Correct.
- Well done.
- I didn't know that.
- That was tough.
- Go! Three, two...
- Canned...
(Pike mackerel canned)
- One!
- mackerel pike.
- Correct.
- Good.
You eat that a lot at home.
Go!
- Three, two...
- Korea Tourism Organization.
- That's it.
- Correct.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Go! Three!
- Two...
- Orchestra!
- Correct.
- Let's go!
(Orchestra)
One, two, three,
- Go!
- Leaning Tower of Pisa!
- Yes.
- That's it.
- Correct.
- Okay.
- My gosh.
- Let's eat.
- I know every one but mine.
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two...
- "Square's Dream."
- Correct.
- I didn't know that.
IU's song.
Square
Well done, Joon.
Go, Se Yoon!
Give him a second.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
- Let's go. Good luck!
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
Come at me!
- Give it to him!
- Come at me!
One, two, three, go!
- Three, two...
- Oh, it's...
- Beach volleyball.
- Okay.
- Correct!
- Let's go!
You didn't know it, did you?
- Do it.
- Okay, we're on.
The last one. One, two, three,
go! Three!
- Oath of the Peach Garden.
- Two...
Yes!
- Correct.
- Okay!
Round Eight is a success.
Gosh.
Well done.
Good job!
Beach volleyball
was a dangerous one.
That's it, everyone.
- Are we done?
- You kept quite a lot.
We defended a lot.
- We lost just 3 out of 8.
- That's not bad.
I don't have rice. But still.
If we share our food,
it might be a decent meal.
(They obtained 5 out of 8 dishes.)
- Go ahead.
- We can share our food, right?
- We can share it, right?
- Yes.
- Thank you for the food.
- Sure.
- Gosh, thank you.
- Seriously.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Let me give you some.
- Can I get rice from anyone?
- Yes.
- I'll use the lid. Here's the rice.
- I'll give you some of my rice.
I have everything but the rice.
- Yes.
- Do you have any spicy pork?
- Im Cheol, do you have spicy pork?
- No.
- I have some. Let's share it.
- Hey, take mine.
Hey.
- Take the rice.
- Take mine.
- Okay.
- Take some of my spicy pork.
- Sae Ho, how much do you want?
- I'm good. Give it to Joon.
- Take it.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Thank you for the food.
(Se Yoon's first bite
is the seaweed soup.)
Gosh, this is good.
The seaweed soup is tasty.
(Every single staff member loves
the food truck's seaweed soup.)
(Joon has a bite of the spicy pork
and a bite of the rice.)
(Then he takes another bite
of the rice.)
Have some of this.
Gosh, that wasn't easy.
It feels like I'm having a meal
on a picnic.
(It feels like they're on a picnic
as they're eating outdoors.)
This is supposed to be
spicy pork ssambap.
Let me make a wrap.
(Se Yoon starts making a wrap,)
(which is the main dish
of the meal.)
- Thank you, Seon Ho.
- Don't mention it.
- Have more if you need more.
- You gave me meat.
- Can I have one more of this?
- Of course.
Hey, this kimchi is so good.
(He finishes the wrap with kimchi.)
- Gosh, the kimchi is amazing.
- Yes.
(He finishes the wrap with kimchi.)
This is so good.
(The spicy pork wrap
brings a smile.)
(There's a ssam fever
thanks to Se Yoon.)
Gosh, this is so good.
I'm serious. This is so good.
It's the best spicy pork
I had recently.
Even this ssamjang is good.
I think the food truck chef...
- Really?
- made this ssamjang too.
- There's a special ratio.
- Yes.
Really?
I got a lot of spicy pork,
but I lost that plate.
I have a lot of it here.
(I must have one more bite
since I'm disappointed by that.)
Hey, did anyone get this dish?
The more I eat, the more I want
to take back the dishes we lost.
- That's how tasty this is.
- Totally.
But we did pretty well.
- We did pretty well.
- Yes.
- Se Yoon.
- Gosh, this is tasty.
- Can I have a bite of the dessert?
- Gosh.
- Sure.
- Se Yoon, we have a lot here too.
- Thank you.
- We're a family.
Why don't you have one first?
It's yours.
- I'm still chewing. Come on.
- It's still yours. My gosh.
We're a family.
(He smells it first.)
- It smells...
- It smelled so good earlier.
(As if he's under a spell,)
(he puts it in his mouth.)
Is it good?
Gosh, you're savoring it.
(The crunchy fried chicken's flavor
mesmerizes him.)
I just had
the crunchy fried chicken.
Other crunchy fried chickens
are quite sweet.
This one isn't that sweet,
but it's so good.
The food truck chef used to run
a fried chicken restaurant.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The food truck chef used to run
a fried chicken restaurant.)
Then we won't have to play games
for the sleeping arrangements.
I guess we won't have to play
games for that...
because we'll be sleeping outdoors.
You know what? Director Joo might
be touched by our performance...
and give us a chance.
So let's wait and see.
Gosh, I had such a nice meal.
- The kimchi is so good.
- Yes.
I ate my food like a madman.
This is tasty.
Can we go to sleep now?
We...
Can't we just put our heads down
and go to sleep here?
Sleeping under the tables
might be good.
The wind won't bother us that way.
- Right?
- Yes.
We can put the tables side by side.
It's like creating a dark room.
We can put the air mattresses
under the table and go to sleep.
- It'd be perfect then.
- It'd be so perfect.
Totally. Gosh.
- This will be our blackout curtain.
- That'd be amazing.
- This is the best.
- They're like blackout curtains.
What are we going to do?
Let's clean up
and get ourselves organized.
- Okay.
- We'll be back then.
- Okay. Thank you for the food.
- Yes.
(What awaits the members?)
My gosh, it's getting chilly.
(It's quite chilly
now that the sun has gone down.)
- All five of you are here, right?
- Okay.
Are we doing something here?
- Are we doing something?
- That's the plan.
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- The night is long.
I'm feeling energetic after dinner.
How about doing a team cheer?
- One, two, three.
- Let's go!
Thank you for the rescue.
- All right.
- He'll rescue some of us.
- You'll go to sleep soon.
- I bet.
I know that
you guys acquired some supplies.
But they might not be enough
for you to spend the night here.
- You bet.
- I knew it.
- It's so cold.
- It's cold.
I hope the viewers
don't get the wrong idea.
He's the weird one.
It's really cold here.
- All of you...
- It's cold.
will be sleeping outdoors.
That won't change.
- Gosh.
- But only...
- one of you will get a benefit.
- What?
It's the biggest downside
of sleeping outdoors.
This item will protect you
from bugs and mosquitoes.
- It's the mosquito net.
- Gosh, the mosquito net.
- The mosquito net.
- And...
he will get a blanket,
pillow, sleeping bag,
camping mat, and tarpaulin.
- Only one of you...
- He'll get all of them?
will have a chance
to take all of these supplies.
- But are we allowed to share them?
- No.
- Well, based on our rules,
- That's not allowed.
- they are exclusive to one person.
- My gosh.
- One person should enjoy them all.
- Yes, let's do that.
But what if someone kneels down
and bows?
- No. I'll step on their knees.
- No.
(His knees will be crushed.)
- Let me show them first.
- Let's do that.
- Bring them in.
- Gosh.
- That's a premium bunch of items.
- My gosh.
That's everything we need.
You can set up a hotel here.
(Amazed)
If you have them, it might be better
to sleep here than in a room.
(Having these supplies can put
sleeping indoors to shame.)
(Coveted additional
bivouac supplies)
This will be an individual match
with three rounds.
People will be eliminated
after each round.
- Just like "Squid Game."
- Yes.
So the last one standing...
can have this decked-out
sleeping arrangement.
It's better to get eliminated
in Round One if I can't make it.
- I want the supplies. Right?
- Yes.
- That's better.
- All right.
- Here's Round 1.
- Round 1.
It's called Fly, Plastic Bag.
- Fly, Plastic Bag?
- Yes.
- Please set it up.
- Just that.
- How much is this?
This looks nice.
- Gosh, this...
- This is great.
- Hold on.
- That's the best supply.
- Are we going to put that there?
- Don't take it with you.
- Hurry.
- This mat...
Gosh, this mat is amazing.
- It's better than an air mattress.
- Hey, this is...
Guys, you can sort of guess
how to play this game, right?
- Oh, this?
- Grab the jacket with both hands.
And then run toward the mat.
Fall on your belly...
and fly the plastic bag
as far as possible to win.
We'll measure the distance
from the tip of the plastic bag.
If you touch the bag,
you're disqualified.
The one with the lowest record
will be eliminated right away.
Will your lymph nodes be okay?
- I'll do my best...
- Why don't you...
without injuring myself.
Okay.
(Let's play fair.)
Here I go.
(DinDin will give it a try.)
(What will the first record be?)
(He runs toward the mat
with an innocent smile...)
(and then falls flat on his face.)
- Gosh.
- Three,
- Two.
- two, one.
- Let's measure the distance.
- Okay. I'm good.
- Are you okay?
- I'm good!
- Gosh.
- Your face...
- This will hurt a lot.
- Okay.
- And...
- Watch.
- Wait. Is this your nose?
- Yes. That's my nose.
Watch. When you fall down...
If I had gotten a nose job,
it would've ruined my nose.
It survived because I hadn't.
See? I didn't get a nose job.
(He proves that
his nose is all natural.)
- All right.
- Come on. You can't do that.
- Why did you do that on your turn?
- Come on.
I must set it up.
You can't do that!
How come our setup is different?
Well, that's how it is here.
Let's do it.
(He puffs up the plastic bag
with delicate touches.)
My gosh.
What? Gosh.
(But his hat flattens the bag.)
- I...
- It's okay.
- I'm anemic. I'm sorry.
- Really?
- Could you move back a bit?
- Okay.
- If you faint here, it'll hurt.
- Please move back a bit.
- I felt so dizzy.
(It seems they can never play fair.)
I'm sorry.
This looks a bit dangerous.
You'll put your hands
in the sleeves?
He's showing us
all kinds of things today.
(He gets ready to win the game.)
I think that's a good idea.
That's good.
- That's nice.
- Gosh.
First of all, his jacket is
three times larger than ours.
That's like a blanket.
I don't need to jump.
- Go ahead.
- Here I go.
(Se Yoon gives it a try.)
- Gosh, I'm a bit scared.
- My goodness.
This is reminding me
of the paper plane from earlier.
Let's go!
(He suddenly remembers
the nightmare of the paper plane.)
(He develops a trauma
of flying objects.)
Okay. Overcome the trauma!
(I can do this.)
Get that!
Okay. Let's go.
(I'll fly the plastic bag
with my power.)
(With Se Yoon's power...)
Three, two, one.
- Right here.
- Measure it.
- My gosh.
- What?
- Okay. I beat his record.
- That was so close.
I survived!
- Gosh, that was so close.
- I survived.
(He beats DinDin in last place
by a close call.)
- Who's going third?
- Me.
(There are all kinds of ruining
each other's chances.)
Hey, now that I've done it,
this might be better.
- I doubt it will make a difference.
- It won't.
(DinDin is doing everything
in his power to win.)
Hold on. That's way too flat.
Go ahead.
(Fluttering)
Here I go.
- Good luck.
- You can surely beat DinDin.
- I think you'll do well.
- Really?
(He believes in Joon's gut feeling.)
Three, two, one.
Measure the distance.
- All right. Seon Ho is leading.
- Next.
Who's next? Is it me?
- It's me. Lymph Nodes.
- Lymph Nodes.
- Mr. Lymph Nodes.
- Watch out for your lymph nodes.
- I watched you go.
And I don't think
it will damage my lymph nodes.
- I'll go with...
- Let's watch.
with the slapstick comedy style
instead of running.
I'll trip. So I won't have a choice
but to fall.
Then I'll swing my jacket,
and the bag will happen to fly away.
- Lymphadenitis is nothing.
- Okay. It's nothing.
- Mission Lymph Nodes.
- Okay. Here I go.
Mission Lymph Nodes.
Gosh, the bug is getting in my way.
(My lymph nodes may be injured,
but nothing is impossible.)
Here I go.
(I'll just run.)
(Slapstick comedy is possible.)
(What's the result?)
Three, two, one.
- Measure it.
- My gosh.
- Okay.
- It's Mission Lymph Nodes.
- Gosh, that's...
- I did pretty well. Right?
I bet he lied
about his medical condition.
Come here.
Why...
(Sae Ho is in 1st place
with a huge gap.)
I will...
- take it easy.
- Okay.
- I don't even need to run.
- Please.
- Okay. What about your glasses?
- Here I go.
Are you okay? What's this?
Traditional Korean dance?
Or contemporary dance?
What's this?
(I don't need to run
for this mission.)
He'll come in last.
(He gently steps on the mat.)
- What? Is this allowed?
- No.
- You have to jump here.
- You can't do that.
- You must jump here.
- You can't do that. Jump first.
- Then I would've done this too.
- Joon.
- I would've done that too.
- What is this?
- He's being ridiculous.
- Do it here.
- Okay. You must jump here.
- This is your warning.
- It's a warning.
- Or trip there.
- I'm sorry.
- Look at DinDin's nose.
- Let me try again.
- Okay.
- Here I go.
- Go ahead.
What is it this time?
He looks like a nutcracker.
He's showing off his talent
in spades.
(Did he set a new record?)
(He flies up gently...)
(and lightly creates a breeze.)
(His bag stops somewhere
around DinDin's record.)
I beat him!
I'm not sure about this.
Let's turn this.
- They might have to do a rematch.
- What's the record?
No, I beat him.
Hey, this is a close call.
- DinDin won.
- I won.
- My gosh. It was so close!
- Gosh.
(DinDin wins by a close call.)
- You never disappoint me.
- He was being too cheeky.
I'm so grateful to you. Seriously.
(Joon is my lifesaver.)
- Joon. You should've run.
- Round One,
Fly, Plastic Bag.
(Not moving)
- What's this?
- Joon is eliminated.
I've never seen
such a meaningless defeat.
He pretended to be so cool
before the game.
Joon, you'll get a trash bag.
You can use it to throw out trash
anywhere in Seoul.
All right. That's a 20L trash bag.
The trash bags are expensive.
Joon is eliminated.
- Let me tell you about Round Two.
- Okay.
All right.
The game for Round Two is called...
Fly, Upper Body.
- What?
- "Upper body."
We'll fly our upper bodies?
I'm good at that. What a pity.
(I'm good at games
that involve my body.)
Two of you will lie on your belly
and face each other first.
Whoever lifts his upper body
and gets their mark higher...
on the board
within 30 seconds will win.
(But they must grab the pen
with both of their hands.)
The highest mark within 30 seconds
will be your record.
- We get 30 seconds?
- Yes.
(List of Matches for Round 2:
Fly, Upper Body)
- You and I should compete.
- Sure.
Okay. The shorties will go first.
(DinDin versus Sae Ho)
(A big match of two shorties)
- Get ready.
- Hold on.
- Okay.
- Don't draw on my face.
- Of course not.
- All right.
- Gosh, this...
- Get ready.
(Fascinated)
Set...
(DinDin is off to a great start.)
Oh, my back!
(Here's my counterattack!)
(He manages to play defense.)
What?
- Why are they so good?
- Bounce back.
(DinDin)
(Sae Ho)
- What?
- Your records are close.
- Hold it with both hands.
- You guys are close!
(They bounce up at the same time.)
(Sae Ho draws over the 1m line.)
(DinDin's line
goes over the 1m line.)
(DinDin, Sae Ho)
- Gosh, DinDin.
- Oh, my.
You have ten seconds left.
- Sae Ho, you must keep trying.
- A little higher.
(You can do this!)
- Sae Ho, you must keep trying.
- A little higher.
(Did Sae Ho set a new record?)
(He lets go of his pen,
so it won't count.)
A little higher.
(He's pretty good.)
What's going on, Lymph Nodes?
(They give every ounce of energy
they have left.)
One last time.
- DinDin won.
- Gosh, this is a close one.
- We need to check, though.
- No, DinDin won.
He might've done it with one hand.
(DinDin, Sae Ho)
(They set their best record
toward the end of the game.)
Hold on. This is really iffy.
My gosh.
How will we determine the winner?
Sae Ho made it pretty high up
toward the end.
- Gosh.
- Wait.
Hey, can you tell from this?
We might have to use a tape line.
- It's 2.3cm.
- It's 2.3cm?
I think DinDin won.
- Yes, DinDin won.
- It's 2.3cm.
(Anticipating)
It's at 3cm already.
(He's certain that he's won.)
It's 3cm. So it's 3cm versus 2.3cm.
Swear on your conscience.
Did you use two hands?
- Yes, I did.
- You did?
I used both of my hands.
- All right.
- DinDin won.
DinDin won.
- Next pair, get ready.
- That wasn't easy.
He's pretty flexible.
(Severely Obese Se Yoon
versus Paper Doll Seon Ho)
How did you lift your upper body?
- How did you do this?
- How did they do this?
- You used both of your hands?
- How did you do it?
You can do this.
- How...
- Guys.
Don't be weak.
How am I supposed to do this?
- You have to use...
- What?
(But the Paper Doll
isn't flexible at all.)
What? How did you do this?
Is this how they did it?
- You can do this.
- Se Yoon...
- Hey, bounce up.
- has good core muscles.
You must do it in a split second.
- Bring it here. This is...
- Get ready,
set...
Go.
One, two, three.
- Great.
- That's how you do it.
Okay.
(I'm going to beat Se Yoon.)
No.
Se Yoon, you're in trouble.
Oh, my back.
- You must try it at least once.
- What's Se Yoon doing?
You must try it again.
Oh, my back.
- You must try it at least once.
- What's Se Yoon doing?
(Se Yoon continues to play offense.)
- Great.
- That's how you do it.
(Seon Ho has
a good chance of winning.)
(He senses that he's in trouble.)
(He fights back
with every ounce of his power.)
You got it.
(What just happened?)
(He sets the highest record.)
He's in first place.
His mark is higher than DinDin's.
(Then he heroically passes out.)
- You must do it again.
- Five, four,
- Hey, do it again.
- three,
- Oh, my back.
- two, one.
Gosh, I won!
- This is amazing.
- Se Yoon's record...
- Oh, my back.
- It's close to 1.1m.
- I won?
- Yes.
- How did I win?
- Your upper body came up.
But Se Yoon's upper body was
already 30cm higher...
because of his belly.
(Here comes Playful Yoo.)
- He's mocking you.
- My gosh. You...
He's mocking you because he lost.
That's it with you too.
You're Mocker Three.
- Okay. Watch out for the next one.
- Look. He's got a big body.
So he was already 30cm higher.
(Mockers of Se Yoon:
Numbers 1, 2, and 3)
Great.
DinDin and Se Yoon.
You'll advance to Round Three.
We'll play a round
to determine the loser.
Seriously. This is...
This will decide the loser.
Sae Ho, do you have a strategy?
I'll try to bounce up
as high as I can.
I'll bounce up higher than before.
- What about you, Seon Ho?
- My strategy is to win.
- Okay.
(His strategy is to win.)
Get ready!
(It's the last match of Round Two.)
Set...
I'll go up in one go.
In one go.
Great. Nice, Seon Ho.
Hey.
What are you doing, Sae Ho?
(Let's go, Sae Ho!)
(Sae Ho uses his legs
to bounce his upper body up.)
Sae Ho is winning.
- No. Seon Ho is winning.
- He's winning.
No. Seon Ho is winning.
- Seon Ho, you got this.
- My gosh.
(Did he injure his lymph nodes?)
Oh, no. It's your lymph nodes.
- Is it for real?
- Yes, it's for real. Hold on.
(Are you all right?)
- No.
- Wait. Don't move.
Are you okay?
- I'm not lying. Let's go.
- Are you okay?
- Stay there for a moment.
- He desperately wants to beat me.
(His strong will is impressive.)
Hurry up.
- Gosh. I feel bad for him.
- Darn it.
- It's making me tear up.
- Three!
(Trying to reach a higher spot)
(One of his hands
lets go of the pen.)
(Sensing trouble)
- Hey.
- What?
Hey. Seon Ho.
- Two, one.
- Hey, you lost.
- Wait. I...
- Sae Ho...
- What? When did you do that?
- My gosh.
Sae Ho, that's a foul.
You only used one hand.
- Really?
- You let go of the pen afterward.
- Yes.
Are you okay?
I can't describe this
because there are ladies here.
Wait.
Your lymph nodes aren't in pain?
- It wasn't my lymph nodes.
- I see. Okay.
- I see.
- I thought my eggs would break.
- It wasn't about his lymph nodes.
- Seriously.
Seriously. I'm not joking.
When I lowered my upper body,
it felt like
someone punched me there.
(It hurt a lot.)
This is such a tough game to play!
(Laughing)
I was the best.
The final result of Round Two,
Fly, Upper Body.
Sae Ho is eliminated.
All right.
Se Yoon, DinDin,
and Seon Ho have survived for now.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- I can't believe...
- To win the full sleeping gear set,
the last mission is called...
Random Straw Game.
- What?
- Random Straw Game.
- The last round is about luck.
- It depends on luck.
What is this about?
- Is this the final game?
- Yes.
- There's only one winner?
- It's the last round.
- Okay.
- Goodness.
- What?
Two straws are connected
to sweet and sour red vinegar.
One straw is connected
to mineral water.
Choose one straw that's connected
to each plastic bottle...
and drink it up.
The one who drinks mineral water
will be the final winner.
It will be hit or miss.
Can't we tell by looking
at the straws?
- It's hard to tell.
- It's impossible.
- It's impossible to know.
- Right.
Let's just do it.
- Let's start.
- Which number will you pick?
- Tell us before you start.
- You can if there's no overlap.
- Tell us.
- Which number?
- What about you?
You tell me first.
Me?
- Number 3.
- I pick number 2.
- I pick number one. Okay.
- Let's go.
You won't change your mind,
will you?
- No.
- No, we won't.
I'm number one.
- I'm number 3.
- Seon Ho is number 2.
I'm number two.
This is hit or miss.
- We have to leave it to chance.
- Please.
- They can't tell.
- Please start.
- It's making me nervous.
- It's nerve-racking.
Please let me sleep alone tonight.
- Please.
- Start.
(Who will get to obtain
the full package?)
- Drink it up in one go.
- Go.
(The one who picks mineral water
wins the full package.)
One of them is drinking water.
(They've been working hard today
to win the bivouac gear.)
(They overcame their fear of heights
and flew in the sky.)
(Screaming)
(They overcame their fear of heights
and flew in the sky.)
(As expected on a hardcore show,)
(they plunged into the sea
without hesitation.)
(To top it all off,)
(they ended up rowing
against professional rowers today.)
(Exclaiming in pain)
(Bivouac gear
that they carefully collected...)
(by exchanging their underwear)
(And the last highlight)
(Who will be the final winner
to win the full package?)
(At that moment)
(You can hear the sound
of coughing everywhere.)
Everyone is acting.
I don't think Se Yoon
is drinking red vinegar.
(Will Sae Ho's guess be correct?)
All right.
Spit it out
if you can't take it anymore.
(Spitting)
Is yours red vinegar?
(DinDin is eliminated.)
(Seon Ho is eliminated.)
Moon Se Yoon wins.
(Moon Se Yoon is the final winner.)
He got very lucky at the end today.
Moon Se Yoon won...
- the full sleeping gear set.
- He won.
(Se Yoon gets to sleep
with the full package.)
I love you, Ha Na.
I've been picking number one
throughout the day.
Number one.
You may not realize this,
but I've only picked number one today.
(Se Yoon's wife's name
means "number one.")
Ha Na.
(Number 1)
(He also picked
Swim Ring Number One.)
(I pick number 1.)
(He also picked Straw Number One.)
(Even his microphone
was number one.)
I love you, Ha Na.
Ha Na.
- I've been picking only number one.
- Really?
(The losers are still shocked
by the red vinegar.)
- Really?
- It's stronger than normal vinegar.
- Sae Ho.
- My goodness.
Don't try it.
I love things like this.
But...
I like it very much.
- Really?
- Yes.
(It turns out that
Sae Ho loves the sour flavor.)
It's delicious.
(What's wrong with him?)
It tastes good
when mixed with water.
- That's true.
- How good is it?
- Try it, Joon.
- No thanks.
- Goodness!
- I don't want to try it.
(We added a bit of vinegar to it.)
You added vinegar to it?
- You added vinegar, didn't you?
- You added vinegar to it?
- That's why it stung my throat.
- I knew it.
Add more to it.
- You added vinegar to red vinegar?
- Add more.
I can't believe it.
I've never won a survival game.
(I can't believe that I won.)
(The unofficial winner, Joon,
who got eliminated in Round 1)
Can you believe this?
- All right.
- Let's go.
- Congratulations, Se Yoon.
- Thank you.
You may get ready to sleep.
- Can we do this...
- before we end the shoot?
- What?
- The pool bed and air mattress.
- Yes.
- It will be a fight.
- We'll decide who gets what.
- Can you give us the die?
- The die, please.
- I'll give you the die.
- The one with the highest number?
- Yes, the highest number.
- Okay.
First place gets a pool bed...
- and a sleeping bag.
- Okay.
Second place gets an air mattress...
- and a sleeping bag.
- Okay.
Third place gets
the wooden bench and newspaper.
- Okay, that's it.
- Make it nice and neat.
(One man is free
from throwing the die.)
This is for me. Okay.
(It's fine as long as it's not me.)
- Who wants to go first?
- Let's play rock-paper-scissors.
- Rock-paper-scissors.
- Hurry up.
- Anyone can go.
- I'll go first.
(The order of throwing the die)
- Rock-paper-scissors.
Go.
I must pray.
- I'm number 4.
- I'm number 2.
Wait a minute. I'm number four.
(While deciding the order)
- If you pick me as the winner...
- What's the order?
- Numbers 1, 2.
- Numbers 1, 2...
- I'll work hard.
- Numbers 3, 4.
I'll push myself harder...
- But you're not religious.
- Right, I have no religion.
I just have to wish
for it earnestly.
Hurry up, you celebrities.
(Pressured by the audience,
he throws the die.)
(Will Joon's prayer method work?)
What is it?
- Look at that.
- Hey, you.
Number one.
(Confirmed as the likely loser)
- That doesn't work.
- Joon.
You should believe in yourself.
Okay.
Did Joon get one?
It's the worst.
- He's the worst player today.
- Joon placed last.
I bet Sae Ho will throw two.
(I can't get 2.)
(He bows deeply at the die.)
Isn't there vinegar on the ground?
(The vinegar smell
hasn't faded yet.)
The vinegar smell came up
when I lowered myself.
I'll do it solemnly. Be quiet.
- Are you going to bow again?
- You bowed twice.
(Absolutely devastated)
- Are you going to bow again?
- You bowed twice.
(I won't bow twice.)
Okay.
(I pray.)
Even the sky will be touched.
The deity of red vinegar.
(The deity of red vinegar,
I pray for the pool bed.)
Let's go.
The pool bed.
He bowed twice.
(What will the deity
of red vinegar choose?)
What is it?
(The deity of red vinegar chose 2.)
My prediction was accurate,
my friend.
Cho Sae Ho, number two.
Okay, I still have a chance.
(My goodness)
You need to perform a ritual.
Okay.
(Die, I beg you.)
- Gosh.
- A bed!
(What will DinDin's number be?)
Number one.
It's one.
(Will it be 1 as Se Yoon predicted?)
(Please!)
(One More Time)
(DinDin got the highest number
so far.)
(Thank you, die.)
I won the pool bed.
(Joon will definitely sleep
on the wooden bench.)
- Seon Ho hasn't gone yet.
- Seon Ho.
If Seon Ho throws a one,
I'll get the air mattress.
No way.
I pave my own way.
(Performing a ritual once more
for the last time)
I won't perform any ritual.
I pave my own way.
No one can stop me.
Throw a one.
(Please let it be 1.)
(Desperate)
(What will be the number
for Seon Ho?)
He caught up.
(Seon Ho also throws 5.)
Okay, that's good.
(The two younger members
win high-quality items.)
Sae Ho is eliminated.
(Sae Ho will definitely sleep
on the wooden bench.)
Darn it.
(A spinning back kick with rage)
(Laughing)
What are you doing, Sae Ho?
That was your dressing room.
- What are you doing still up?
- Mister.
Mister, how could you...
What are you doing?
Stop shooting.
What are you shooting all day long?
The deity of red vinegar is furious.
You should've bowed more.
Why are you still up?
You know what time it is?
Wilderness, my foot.
Let's go, Joon.
(Joon can't go
because he's busy laughing.)
You don't want to go?
You want to stay a little longer?
Okay.
It's my first time seeing
his spinning back kick.
- I apologize sincerely.
- Okay.
- I lost my temper.
- It happens.
Viewers, I apologize.
- I can understand.
- I'm sorry.
Okay.
Everyone,
please take your sleeping gear...
We'll take care of it ourselves.
It's not necessary to tell us that.
Wait, so who got what?
Did DinDin win the pool bed?
- I got the pool bed.
- What about Seon Ho?
- I got the air mattress.
- He got the air mattress.
Both of you got the wooden bench?
The wooden bench with newspaper.
Why are you asking when you know?
(The wooden bench and newspaper)
Who wants to set up my bed?
Me!
- Would you like...
- Yes, sir.
- It looks like I have a lot.
- I'll do it.
For my bed...
Wait, which area is even?
- An even area.
- An even area?
What do you think
of the red vinegar area?
- Red vinegar? No way.
- Okay.
Not where the red vinegar is.
Can you set it up over there
beautifully with the mosquito net?
- Where?
- What?
In my opinion, this area is good.
It seems to have a nice view too.
We need to spread this out first.
- Spread that out.
- And the cushions.
You have to spread everything out.
You don't need to do all that.
(The building owner,
Mr. Moon, has a lot.)
Gosh, this is difficult.
Don't crumple it.
It should be flat for my back.
Joon, pull it all the way...
- so that he can sleep well.
- Yes.
(Trying to sort things out quickly
for Landlord Moon's comfort)
- You have to set everything up.
- That's good.
- Have you never done it?
- Make it flat.
Spread it out. What are you doing?
Set up the blanket and everything.
Set up two layers.
Spread out the blanket.
What are you doing?
This is what happens when someone
who was penniless gets something.
This is all
for the purpose of sharing.
- Really?
- Of course.
Spread it out nicely.
How is this done?
This is...
You might have to sleep without it.
- There's no other solution.
- You lie down here.
There's no other solution.
Get up. What are you doing?
- What's wrong with you?
- There's really no other solution.
Try it until you make it.
You should give us
a proper mosquito net!
- I apologize.
- It's okay.
That's good. Spread it out.
I can't stand any wrinkles.
That looks great.
Come here, Sae Ho.
Let me pay your daily wage.
(Extremely polite)
- Is this for me?
- You should share it with him.
Hold it up together.
Let's take a commemorative photo.
(A photo commemorating
their daily wage)
(Daily wage)
- All right.
- Thank you.
Sleep well.
- Sleep well.
Please remove your bags.
Why don't I try the bed
and see how it feels?
That's Seon Ho's bag.
- This is just...
- It feels wonderful.
- Wait.
- This is insane.
Wait.
(Landlord Moon locks the door.)
It does look nice.
(I'm jealous.)
Okay.
(The luxurious suite
with a mosquito net)
Gosh, it's hot.
Can we use the cardboard?
(The gap between
the rich and the poor)
- The cardboard.
- Go ahead and use it.
The cardboard...
(The cardboard is precious
to Team Wooden Bench.)
Let's surround the bench
with the cardboard.
- On top of this...
- This?
Spread that out.
Can we get some extra towels
so we can wash up?
Sure.
(Is he giving them for free?)
Can we get some sleeping bags
so we can wash up?
(That's not allowed.)
- No?
- No.
(As it's the Bivouac Special,
they wash up at the faucet.)
(He washes himself alone
with the long hose.)
(It's uncomfortable.)
Could you film
while holding this up?
Sure.
(He's happy to help.)
(Thanks to the director,
he can wash his face with two hands.)
I can only wash my face.
(Se Yoon and Seon Ho
hold the hose for each other.)
Water.
(Hold the hose properly.)
I need water.
(I don't want to.)
Water!
(Giggling)
Pour the water into my hands.
I did. Is it not reaching?
Pour it well.
- One, two, three.
(The revolutionary,
wiping with half the towel)
You seem very close to each other.
I'm done.
- We're each other's other half.
- We are.
- Are you done?
- You're my other half
I'll use the remaining water...
on my feet
that were wet with red vinegar.
(Washing red vinegar off his feet)
That's done.
- The end.
- We're done. I feel refreshed.
(Applying lotion meticulously)
Sae Ho. He's 44.
And he asked me to cover him
with the newspaper.
Yes, thank you.
- Will you take a photo of me?
- I will.
- With your phone?
- Yes, I'll send it to you.
(Somewhere between bivouacking
and sleeping on the street)
Sleep well.
- Good night, Sae Ho.
- Good night.
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay.
(They lie down in the most
comfortable position at their spot.)
(They fall asleep with the vast sky
as their blanket.)
(Soon, the morning arrives.)
(The sun is already high in the sky,
but the members are still asleep.)
(They're sleeping well
even though it's outdoors.)
(Sae Ho gets up at 7:50 a.m.)
(He's the only one who woke up
before the wake-up song.)
(They're both still sleeping.)
(What are those?)
(He spots something
and goes up to it.)
(Microphones and cameras
on the grass)
(And a letter?)
Guys.
You'd better get up.
- They left these here.
- What?
(Half-asleep)
They left everything,
including the microphones.
What's written on it?
(What's written in the letter?)
"Hello members,
did you sleep well last night?"
"I'm sure
everyone wants to go home."
"You must catch me
in order to get off work."
I'm over here. Please hurry.
All members must come together.
(They must catch Director Joo
to get off work?)
There's no one here. Everyone left.
Gosh.
(No one is here
other than the members?)
(1 hour ago)
(Shadows move busily with the
sleeping members behind them.)
(The staff members
are leaving with their things.)
(On top of that)
(Bowing)
(Director Joo cajoled the sleeping members
before leaving.)
(And he checked out.)
(Soon, the base camp became empty.)
(They must find Director Joo
who disappeared.)
(What?)
- If everyone left,
- Yes?
should we leave too?
(Thinking outside the box)
Shall we? That's an idea.
That's a great idea.
(Why didn't we think
of that before?)
That sounds good.
(How will they catch Director Joo?)
What? How do we know?
The sea.
Look carefully. Isn't this the sea?
It could be.
(Another trace left by Director Joo)
I'm over here. Please hurry.
(Director Joo has a big smile on
with a victory sign.)
(Where could he be?)
(It looks like he's by the sea.)
- We received a hint.
- What?
- As a text message?
- From whom?
What is it?
- Listen to it.
- Okay.
(Playing the audio hint)
(What is this sound?)
That's right.
(Replay)
(Do you recognize this sound?)
Isn't he running?
It's the zipline.
- You're right.
- I see.
Can you play it again?
(The sound of zipline)
(It sounds similar.)
- You're right.
- Right?
- That's right.
- Right.
- Your intuition is sharp.
- Nice.
- Right?
- That's good.
There's something called
Daecheon Ziptrek.
- It must be right.
- This is it.
You probably see it
when you glide from the top.
(A photo that Sae Ho found
on someone's blog)
They look similar.
- They took the photo from the top.
- It must be the zipline.
- Don't you think this is it?
- Yes.
That's good.
You're smart.
- Shall we put on the microphone?
- Microphone?
(Experienced)
This can't be helped.
(Professional TV personalities know
how to put on their microphones.)
Is this done like this?
(He doesn't forget
to take the camera.)
So far, we've figured out
that he's by the zipline.
We have been abandoned.
(Joon's Camera)
(Moving to the van
while filming themselves)
Let's get going.
(Will they catch Director Joo
and get off work?)
The address is...
This has to be the place, right?
I think so.
It will take 37 minutes.
Then let's go to Daecheon Ziptrek.
Okay.
If he isn't there...
- After 40 minutes...
- It'd be a disaster.
- Or...
- If not, let's just drive home.
(Reckless)
(Just in case,
he listens to it again.)
It has to be the zipline.
- It must be the zipline.
- Yes.
(Feeling certain)
(Will their guess be correct?)
The weather is beautiful today.
Did you all sleep well?
It wasn't bad,
but it wasn't comfortable either.
It could have been worse.
How was the wooden bench?
I think Joon slept soundly.
I passed out.
- It wasn't the perfect bed, but...
- It was okay.
- Joon said the right thing.
- What?
"If they left, should we leave too?"
We can leave with this van.
He said, "If there's no one here,
let's just leave."
I'll drop off each of you.
Send him a message.
"Come and catch us instead."
(Come and catch us instead.)
- We can send him photos.
- That's right.
Or how about this?
We all have mobile phones.
We could go to a gukbap restaurant.
We can pay with a money transfer.
I can pay with Apple Pay.
I have one too.
We can go to a delicious
gukbap restaurant in Daecheon.
No one is following us, right?
- No, there's no one.
- You're right.
(No one is following them.)
(That means...)
- No one is following us.
- No one is behind us.
No one is in the trunk, right?
- There's no car behind us.
- No car is following us.
(Is that so?)
Shall we show them?
No one is behind us.
- I'm ready.
- What?
Joon is capable of it.
Joon is a man of his word.
The staff made a mistake.
We're like unleashed dogs.
(Glaring)
Im afraid that it would lead
to consequences later.
For doing something on our own
on a real wild road variety show.
- "As you made a mistake..."
- Sae Ho.
It's the real wild
because they unleashed us.
They don't know
when we would find him.
Isn't it awkward to go there
after eating?
We might make the staff wait
for too long.
Sae Ho.
Did Joo Jong Hyun give you
a mission?
Are you in secret communication
with Director Joo?
- No way.
- He's acting strange.
Sae Ho is acting suspicious.
- Cho Sae Ho.
- Yes?
You got up suddenly in the morning.
You were the first person
to find the message.
(Sae Ho was the first one
to find the mission.)
I'm serious. Watch this on TV
when it gets aired.
As soon as I opened my eyes...
I was on the wooden bench.
When I opened my eyes,
I saw the letter,
so I told you guys. That's all.
But you keep talking
like you're worried...
- No.
- about the staff.
- If we're going to do something...
- Yes?
I mean, we're doing it
to show them what we can do.
Then shouldn't we just go home?
Having breakfast doesn't sound
so rebellious, don't you think?
(That's extreme.)
- You think we should go home?
- But going home...
This is how it feels, Sae Ho.
- Eating on our way can be cute.
- Right.
- They could just laugh it away.
- Yes.
But if we go home...
Based on what I've seen
in the past six years,
- I don't think it will end well.
- Right.
(Even the sly DinDin seems
afraid of the consequences.)
- Hey, there's McDonald's.
- What?
They have a drive-thru there.
- Where is it?
- On the left.
It's on me.
Let's eat some food in the car.
Shall we eat in the car?
- Shall we eat on our way there?
- Let's do that.
- Okay. Let's do that.
- I don't think they'll find out.
(Chuckling)
- You have to make a turn here.
- Oh, I should make a left turn.
(They head
straight to the burger place.)
- This is nice.
- The morning menu... Hold on.
- All right. Tell me what you want.
- What can I get you?
Hello.
Can we get one chicken snack wrap...
and four hash browns?
I'll have a sausage and egg McGriddle
with iced coffee.
Can we also get
a chicken cheese muffin...
One cup of iced drip coffee,
one cup of Diet Coke,
and one cup of chocolate milkshake,
please.
And one cup of orange juice too,
(The members order a lot of food,
being unstrained.)
- The payment went through.
- Thank you.
(It's Sae Ho's treat.)
(Cheering)
- He's so nice, as always.
- Thank you.
What are you guys cheering for?
A drive-thru is so nice.
- The world got so much better.
- This is what I'm talking about.
All right. We're going to eat.
- Goodbye.
- I'll distribute the food now.
Please do.
(He has a sip
of his chocolate milkshake.)
- My, this is so good.
- That's mine.
The staff made a huge mistake...
by leaving us unattended like this.
(Eating)
(They're enjoying breakfast
without playing a game after a long time.)
I'm happy.
- I feel like we're on a trip.
- Exactly.
We're all on the same boat now.
- Of course.
- Absolutely.
- Of course, we are one.
- If they ask us if we ate food,
we just have to be shameless...
and deny their accusation
all together.
If Jong Min were here,
he would've admitted it.
- Without him, we can fool them.
- Right.
We'll just say we feel wronged.
I'll get angry and act resentful.
- Good.
- I'll say it in an annoyed tone.
- I can do that.
- Okay. Good.
Let's hurry up and catch him
so we can go home.
(Let's hurry up and catch Jong Hyun
so we can go home.)
(Only 2 minutes before arrival)
We should start
getting rid of the evidence.
We don't have to do that.
We can just say we didn't eat it.
We can say it was in the car
when we got in.
(They're becoming
more and more brazen.)
"Oh, wait.
What are those in the car?"
(Dreaming of a perfect crime,
they arrive at the destination.)
- We're almost there now.
- What's that?
By the way, Joon is good at driving.
That's because Joon had to give
paparazzi the slip many times.
(Laughing)
Such experience helped him
improve his driving skills.
- That's not true.
- No one can chase him.
I see the zipline over there.
- Look up there. It's very high.
- Oh, I see that too.
- All right. Everyone...
- That's such a high zipline.
Joon, I'll catch him,
and you fly kick him.
- Got it.
- He might try to run away.
- All right. I'll do that.
- There's a parking lot here.
Well, this will be...
- Isn't that Director Joo?
- Hold on.
He's at the parking lot?
I should park the car here.
(They get out of the car
to go and catch Director Joo.)
(We left everything to them.
They have such poor filming skills.)
I don't think I'm supposed to
film myself with this camera.
- We should film one another.
- Should we film one another?
- All right.
- What are you doing?
All right.
What are you doing?
Are you sure you're filming me?
- Hello. Have a nice day.
- Hello.
Thank you.
Are we going the right way?
Oh, this is it.
- I think... Wait.
- Are we at the right place?
- Is that man Jong Hyun?
- You're moving too fast.
- No, that's not Jong Hyun.
- Of course not.
- Where should we go to catch him?
- I think he's on the other side.
- I think we should go up there.
- We should go up there.
Are we going up there?
Let's go and find out.
- That's right.
- Hey, look here.
Guys, look. There's a camera here.
- Oh, okay.
- There's a camera here.
- Right. That's the beach we saw.
- That's right.
- Wait. Where does this lead to?
- I see the camera.
Do we have to go all the way down
over there?
But it's quite steep.
- It's almost like a free fall.
- But where is Jong Hyun?
Let's go up and find him.
I think he's up there.
(Will Director Joo be on top
of the tower?)
- Hello.
- By any chance, do you know...
- where our cameramen are?
- I think that's Jong Hyun.
They took the elevator earlier.
- Really? Did they go up?
- I see. Did they go up?
- Thank you.
- So they went up. Thank you.
So you jump off a 52m tower?
There's a weight limit
for the zipline, right?
- This may be the tallest one.
- We don't get to come here often.
- There's no weight limit.
- Really?
I think this is the highest zipline
in the country.
Is there really no weight limit?
Please tell us the truth.
No, you can ride it
as long as the safety gear fits you.
(Will I have
to ride something again?)
- Thank you.
I don't want to
ride anything anymore.
(Tearing up)
(Technology is advancing
so quickly.)
We've been doing a lot of activities
since yesterday.
- Yes. One after another.
- We did a lot of activities.
I've never ridden a zipline
at 9 a.m. before.
We've been experiencing
real outdoor activities.
It's the 19th floor.
Seon Ho contributed a lot.
He guessed the zipline sound
once he heard it.
- He was so smart.
- Right?
- You see...
- Yes. He used to be an idol singer.
- You're now officially one of us.
- Hello.
(If Director Joo is here,
everything will be successful.)
- Okay.
- We're here.
- You're now officially one of us.
- Hello.
- Okay.
- We're here.
- Oh, what...
- Oh, gosh.
- What's going on?
- But Jong Hyun can't ride it.
- You must catch me to end it.
- I know you can't ride it.
- Get him. What are you waiting for?
Goodness, Jong Hyun.
How long have you been
hanging there?
(The safety door opens.)
(Is he going to ride it
to run away?)
(You must catch me to end it.)
(Catch him.
What are you waiting for?)
- What? Hey, wait.
- You must catch me to end it.
- What? Hey!
- Oh, gosh.
(Screaming)
(They lost their target
right in front of their eyes.)
(Laughing)
What's that?
For how many hours
was he hanging here?
(Around the time the members
picked up their food...)
One for me.
(Even though he gets scared easily,)
(Director Joo was hanging here
for nearly 30 minutes...)
(because he didn't know
when the members would come.)
I'm surprised. I thought
he couldn't ride a zipline.
(Director Joo escapes
while screaming resentfully.)
(The scaredy-cat main director
sacrifices himself for the show.)
Is this really necessary?
He can't ride things like this.
(We should go too.
We must ride it to catch him.)
Let's stop
doing activities like this.
(I might just go home now!)
This is driving me nuts.
(All members have put on
the safety gear.)
What? Oh, gosh.
It's open only in front of me.
- That scared me.
- We'll double-check the gear.
(I'm ready to catch Director Joo.)
(Sae Ho and Seon Ho
will ride it together.)
How many activities must we do?
(Director Joo,
just wait until I catch you.)
When I count to three,
just lift up your feet.
- One, two, three. Go!
- All right.
- I'm scared.
- So this is how it moves.
(Exclaiming)
(I'm scared.)
(I'm doing another activity
for the fourth time.)
(Smiling)
(Let's go.)
So this is how it moves.
(They fly like an arrow
with the wind blowing on their backs.)
- So this is how the beach looks.
- Right.
- It's pretty.
- Nice.
- We're moving really fast.
- Yes, we are.
(I'm on cloud nine.)
(The members are flying fast
up above the blue sea.)
I can smell the sea.
(A morning zipline at 9 a.m.
is also amazing.)
(It's really amazing!)
(The Bivouac Race took place
in Boryeong and Buyeo.)
(During the dazzling trip,
they fully enjoyed the summer days.)
(19 seconds later, we'll see
the hidden nature on Jeju Island...)
(with Jong Min who came back
from his honeymoon!)
(All members have landed.)
- Catch him.
- I caught him.
(They also succeeded
in catching Director Joo.)
(2 Days and 1 Night)
(The tall Mount Halla)
(The blue sea)
(And beautiful stone walls
welcome you.)
(We're here on Jeju Island.)
(The first destination of the trip
to the beautiful Jeju Island)
- My, the sand is so soft.
- How beautiful.
Is this Gimnyeong Beach?
- Gimnyeong Beach.
- The color of the water is amazing.
Gimnyeong Beach.
Oh, my. Look at the sea.
- It's magnificent.
- It's so beautiful.
(Sae Ho is in front of Se Yoon.)
Here comes 1 of the top 5 men
Jong Min picked. Go behind me.
- That's annoying.
- All right.
That hurt my feelings last night.
Nice to meet you all.
This is Jeju Island.
Hello. Are you here for your work?
(It looks like Se Yoon's
in a good mood.)
- Hello.
- Why are you so late?
I'm the only one here who was voted
as Jong Min's top five members...
of the show.
- Right, I saw that.
- You didn't get his credit.
- You should work harder.
- I mean...
The four of us last night...
We turned on the TV at the lodging
after having dinner.
- "Problem Child in House" was on.
- Right.
Jong Min was on the show.
We were having fun watching it.
Then they showed
the top five members...
of 2 Days and 1 Night
picked by Jong Min.
We were all nervous.
- It was like an awards ceremony.
- Right.
- "The first winner is..."
- Eun Ji Won.
- Of course.
- He deserves it.
- The second winner is Lee Seung Gi.
- Of course.
- He surely is the winner.
- The third winner is Cha Tae Hyun.
- Sure, he has to be the winner.
I thought it was time for him
to mention one of us.
- "The 4th one should be us."
- The 4th one was...
(It was a nervous moment announcing
the 4th top member of the show.)
(Please call my name.)
(The 4th member picked by Jong Min
was Kim Joon Ho.)
- "It's Kim Joon Ho."
- Right.
That's when Se Yoon
started to make a face.
He said, "I'm not the fourth one?"
- We all made a face. Come on.
- That's when I realized,
- "Only one slot is vacant."
- Right.
Just one more person.
(Will he say 1 of the members
from Season 4?)
This is getting interesting.
(Jong Min picked Se Yoon as
1 of the top 5 members.)
They announced Se Yoon's name.
We all frowned as if they announced
the winner of the Grand Prize.
(The rest of them got all angry.)
The three of them were frowning
so much.
They said, "I'm going to confront
Jong Min when he comes back."
That really put me down a bit.
- Then Sae Ho went to his room.
- Right away.
- Really? I watched it too.
- I went to my room right away.
I cried while taking a shower.
- How did you cry?
- I cried like this.
(Crying)
I didn't want them
to hear me crying.
You should ask him
when he comes back.
- Ask the worst five members.
- Let's do that.
- Worst five members.
- Here he comes.
I smell Europe on Jeju Island.
(Jeering)
Hey, Jong Min.
My best friend, Jong Min.
- I'm 1 of the best 5.
- What do you mean?
You picked me in fifth place.
I did?
- "I did?"
- Did he say, "I did?"
- You don't remember that?
- Boo.
- Stand in the center.
- I mean this is...
This is much better
than Switzerland.
- You can stand here.
- The weather is amazing.
- Goodness.
- Hello.
Jong Min is back.
Jong Min is back in Korea.
(Jong Min is back.)
- Hey, did you...
- We aren't so happy.
- Why not?
- Last night, we watched...
- Don't ask him.
- Do you even remember?
- Remember what?
- You on "Problem Child in House."
- I was on the show.
- Right.
You picked the top five members
of the show.
Right.
Unfortunately,
we watched that episode...
all together last night.
So we are very angry right now.
(You didn't pick us?)
What's the point of shooting
the show together?
Wasn't it fun, though?
It just ruined my mood instantly.
- I'm fine, Jong Min.
- Wasn't it fun?
Let me explain.
You didn't get the whole context.
- Really?
- Let me explain.
It was all edited.
A soccer match is weird
if all of them are Messi.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- Not everyone can be a striker?
- That's right.
We need a defender and a goalkeeper.
We need people of a variety.
This season's team is the best.
You can't jump like that.
(That is so random.)
- What kind of excuse is that?
- What are you talking about?
This is what we want to know.
You can pick the worst five members
of the show then.
Who are the worst five members?
- I can't wait to hear it.
- It would be fun.
- This sounds fun.
- I'm sure this will attract...
more attention than the best five.
I can already picture
about two people in my head.
- You know who?
- Of course.
Of course, I do.
You're one of them. Did you know?
(You're one of them.)
- We should end it here.
- That's too sudden for him.
- We shouldn't pick the worst ones.
- Right.
- Just pick one more member.
- Top six members.
- Top six.
- Sixth place.
- Pick sixth place and move on.
- Sixth place?
- Sixth place.
- Personally?
- Of all the members combined.
- Right.
- Just until 6th place.
- Just 1 more person.
Se Yoon is in fifth place.
- That's right.
- Let's wrap it up there.
Sixth place.
- Members from all seasons combined.
- Be honest.
- Sae Ho's also very good...
(Will he pick
1 of the 4 people here?)
- I know you all are good.
- All seasons combined.
- It hasn't been long...
- Right.
So I'll pick DinDin.
- I mean it.
- I could tell.
How about seventh place?
Seventh place?
(Being clingy)
Okay, then it's Sae Ho.
(Sae Ho is 1 of the top 7.)
Okay, it's Sae Ho.
It hasn't even been a year.
(I shouldn't have asked.)
It surely feels more stable...
- when we have Jong Min with us.
- That's right.
It's nice to have all of us here.
Was your trip fun?
- Was it fun?
- Let me be honest.
I was so happy.
The trip was so nice.
It's your first proper vacation.
- That's right.
- You knew we were filming...
the show while you were
on your honeymoon.
- I knew.
- How did you feel?
For me, I was more like...
I felt anxious.
"Will the show be okay without me?"
I was more worried.
Honestly, I wasn't worried at all.
We also made a video call.
How did you feel?
I trusted that you guys
were doing your best.
So I was not worried at all.
I feel like he's changed.
- He's more relaxed now.
- Right, I'm more relaxed.
Now that Jong Min is back with us,
let's go on a special trip today.
- Okay.
- Jeju Island.
We are dressed up...
- like some expeditionists.
- I know.
They told me to dress up like this.
I could tell right away.
We're going to some jungle, right?
- He's at it again.
- Like Indiana Jones.
We're paddling
next to some crocodiles.
Crocodiles?
- Crocodiles on Jeju Island?
- I just have one question.
Do we have to get ready?
You should always get ready
before filming the show.
- In fact, yesterday...
- Is it like a travel show?
Seon Ho and I arrived yesterday.
It's nice to run around
the coastal area on Jeju.
- Did you run yesterday?
- We ran about 15km.
(DinDin and Seon Ho ran
on the coastal road.)
That's the farthest I ran.
Then we made a video call
to Jong Hyun...
while we were running.
Then he said, "Hey!
Go back to your hotel and rest."
"Go back to your hotel right now."
"Save your energy."
- "What are you doing?"
- "What do you think you're doing?"
"I told you to get some rest."
He said, "What are you doing?"
- I mean...
- So I'm a bit anxious.
Are we going on a tough trip
or something?
- What is it? Tell us right now.
- Not many places are bad here.
You see how you're dressed up.
- You're ready to explore now.
- He's saying...
Today, you are...
designated as
Tamra Treasure Expeditioners.
- I love it.
- Tamra?
- Tamra is Jeju Island.
- That's right.
We're going to explore this place.
Embracing the blue sea
and natural beauty,
Jeju Island.
- I love it.
- It's amazing.
This year marks
the Visit Jeju Heritage Year.
The government designated it.
(To us,)
(it's a familiar and friendly spot.)
(Jeju Island)
(Only it's not familiar and friendly
this time.)
- The road is...
- Hey, this is...
Is this even a road?
(Something we haven't seen before.)
We're going to see
a new side of Jeju Island...
by visiting places
that haven't been known.
(On their way
to this new Jeju Island)
So the concept of today's trip is...
to find hidden treasures
of Jeju Island.
(Finding hidden treasures
of Jeju Island)
Adventure trip special.
(Novice explorers'...)
(adventure trip special)
Tamra Treasure Island.
(Tamra Treasure Island:
Adventure Trip Special)
It sounds very interesting.
It's like we are
at an amusement park.
It sounds very interesting.
It's fun to look for treasures.
It's a group mission.
You're going to explore
all over Jeju Island today.
- When you complete your mission...
- Yes?
- Treasures?
- If you find your treasures...
- For real...
- We'll give you gold.
Real gold?
Isn't that chocolate?
- It's chocolate.
- Come on.
Give me one more of that.
If you can collect
60 pieces of gold,
you all can sleep indoors.
It's a group thing.
Every time you lack
ten pieces of gold,
one of you has to sleep outdoors.
So 1 of you has to sleep outdoors
even if you collect 59 pieces.
- Okay.
- That's the rule.
That doesn't sound easy.
You'll be on your first expedition.
You're visiting different places
in two groups.
You mean, groups of three?
Se Yoon, Joon, and DinDin
are in one team.
Jong Min, Sae Ho, and Seon Ho
You will now go...
- and find treasures of Jeju.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Let's go.
See you later.
- See you.
- Let's go.
Jong Min,
give me back the gold pieces.
Three pieces. Who is it?
Is it chocolate?
Yes, it is.
(They're off to find treasure
after returning the gold pieces.)
What? Are we getting
on an off-road vehicle?
(For 2 Days and 1 Night explorers)
(A special gift from the staff)
I want to drive this car.
I know. I didn't know
they would get us this car.
I want to drive this.
I'm sure we'll get to drive.
(The off-road vehicles make them
want to explore right away.)
Gosh, it's so high.
- Great.
- Nice.
(The car is so nice.)
Nice.
Does this mean we're going off-road
with this vehicle?
I guess.
- I'm sure it's fun to drive this.
- I know.
All right, let's get going.
- Okay, let's go.
- Off we go to find treasures...
(Team Se Yoon is off
to find treasures.)
(Team Se Yoon is determined
Tell them that we'll be back
after finding treasures.
- Thank you.
- We'll be back with treasures!
(Please find a lot of treasures.)
(Off to find treasures
with the crowd's cheer)
Let's go.
When was the last time
I visited Jeju Island?
I was here the year before last
to film a drama series.
I was here for 1.5 months.
- Really? Which one?
- Here?
I filmed "The Escape of the Seven."
We were filming
at these incredible sites.
A bat actually slapped me.
- A bat?
- Yes, a bat.
We were filming the series in a cave
for 12 hours.
Something flew at me. It was a bat.
I was flustered.
It was flying right next to me
as it slapped my face.
It slapped me with its wing.
I saw many weird creatures
here on Jeju Island.
(How can a bat slap you?)
(Soon)
(That story just happened
to be real.)
(They're in panic.)
(They really slap you.)
(What will happen to them?)
I came here for a shoot,
and I came here
with my wife and children.
- On a trip?
- Yes. I like the Jeju vibe.
I really like it too.
It feels really great.
(The city that feels nice, Jeju)
I really like
the unstable weather of Jeju.
- The island weather.
- The weather is unpredictable.
In summer.
- That's right.
- I love it.
It's therapeutic
even if you stay still.
Right.
(It's nice when it's cloudy,)
(and it's nice when it's clear.)
You feel at ease here.
That's right.
There are no tall buildings as well.
(Jeju presents a peaceful heart
to everyone through each charm.)
It's so beautiful. Look to the left.
- It's beautiful.
- The stone walls...
- When I come to Jeju,
I don't really like driving,
but when I come here,
I feel like driving.
- That's right.
- You rent a car.
- The view here is great too.
- It is.
Personally,
I came here when I was 19 or 20.
- I think I was 20.
- That's a bit late.
I came late.
I came here to film...
the music video for Uhm Jung Hwa.
I see.
It was called "Festival."
She filmed the music video here.
There was a song called "Emergency"
in KOYOTE's sixth album.
- "Emergency."
- We filmed...
the music video of that song
here in Jeju.
I see.
Many music videos were filmed here.
- It's pretty.
- It is.
But where are we going?
I'm just following the GPS system.
(No one knows.)
I don't know where we are going.
- A treasure island?
- Wouldn't it be somewhere...
with treasure?
What's your...
number one treasure?
(Number 1 treasure...)
- Sae Ho can say it first.
- I think mine is my family.
- Family.
Exclude family. What about objects?
- Objects?
- What do I have?
- Yes.
It's just an object.
I won't add any meaning to it.
My bag.
- What bag?
- My bag.
- That's nice.
- I'm serious.
- That's possible.
- Yes.
Is there a particular reason?
Not really.
I just worked so hard for it.
I saved up little by little
to buy that bag.
- What about you?
- Treasure?
These days, it's my ring.
- Ring? Come on.
- Really? Your wedding ring?
I should have said that.
- You said it was your bag.
- It's my ring.
The hard-earned bag.
What are Jeju's treasures?
It's very windy because it's Jeju...
and the sky isn't that clear.
Since we are a team,
let's check our fortune.
I'll check our fortune for today.
I'll go first.
"Someone you havent contacted
in a while..."
"or someone you met
during your travels will become..."
"a reliable companion
on your path ahead."
You came to travel today.
This is nice.
(Joon's fortune
is compatible with today's trip.)
- What Chinese zodiac sign are you?
- The fat sign.
- I was born in the year of the dog.
- Dog?
Dog of 1982.
- Dog of 1982.
- Yes.
Hold on.
- Dog of 1982?
- Yes.
- What is it?
- "You must be extra cautious..."
"not to get into traffic accidents."
- What?
- Really?
(Se Yoon, today's driver,
gets such a fortune.)
Hold on. I must be cautious
to avoid traffic accidents?
"Make sure you keep
a safe following distance..."
- Really?
- No way.
"and carefully observe
the road conditions."
Stop lying. Is that true?
- I'm serious.
- Really?
This is an off-road trail.
- We're entering a jungle now.
- Can the car go through this?
- Good. This is fun.
- You really have to be careful.
(An off-road trail appears
all of a sudden.)
- This is fun.
- Really?
- You really have to be careful.
- Okay.
The car is also an off-road car.
Right.
- We really should be careful.
- I've never caused any accidents.
Don't worry about that.
Where are we going
that we're going in like this?
- This is fun.
- Where is this?
This is like "Indiana Jones."
It's like "Indiana Jones."
Nice. "Adventures of Sinbad."
(2 Days and 1 Night Jones:
In Search of Jeju's Treasures)
Nice!
Nice. Let's go find the treasure.
I will turn my life around.
- But the road...
- This...
This location is like
the hidden treasure of Jeju.
- What is this? I'm excited.
- I'm so excited about this.
- This is so fun.
- How could there be such a road?
Is this the place? We're here.
(They finally reached
the unknown place.)
(What adventure awaits the members?)
(The 3 of them reach the destination
after passing the off-road trail)
(The thick oreum of Jeju)
Let's go find the treasure.
What?
It's nearby. Nice.
(They find
the production crew nearby.)
- Amazing.
- I thought we had to keep climbing.
I was worried.
They're nearby, but their clothes...
I guess the treasure is here.
Why are the cameramen dressed...
Why are you dressed like that?
- Is this a game?
- Are we going to "Squid Game?"
You are now...
about to head toward
the path of fire...
where lava once flowed
10,000 years ago.
It's hot.
This place where you are about
to go on a special expedition...
(The special expedition site is
hidden in the magnificent forest.)
- is the Bengdui Cave.
- A cave?
- There is a cave here?
Right.
There are bats inside.
It is one
of the lava caves listed...
as a UNESCO
World Natural Heritage site.
(The Bengdui Cave is one of them.)
This cave is normally
not open to the public...
so that it remains preserved.
Every year, it is opened
only during special periods.
Today, as a special occasion
for viewers of 2 Days and 1 Night,
the Cultural Heritage Service...
and Jeju Island have granted us
permission to enter the cave.
Awesome. Just us?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
So please introduce it well
to the viewers.
We will now get changed
and enter the cave.
- For safety?
- Get changed?
- Let's get changed.
- I'll do that. Here.
(They get changed.)
Let's go, comrades.
Let's go find the treasure.
(They get fully prepared
and head out.)
Bengdui Cave.
- It's a great honor.
- Right.
We wouldn't have been able
to go if we had competed for it.
We'll get going...
since we have to introduce it
to you.
(They nervously enter
the unknown area.)
This place is awesome.
- Amazing.
- What is this?
- It's amazing.
- Look at the colors of the trees.
What is this?
This is amazing.
Look at this.
The trees are really tall.
This is Mother Nature.
- The trees...
- It's really...
(It's full of Japanese cedar trees
that grow up to 40m.)
What is this green color?
Goodness. What is this?
Look at the ground.
If Jong Min saw this,
he would have said,
"They're brackens!"
(Beech fern)
(There are various wetland plants.)
(Longleaf falsenettle)
It really is like "Squid Game"
since we are dressed like this.
You will now enter Bengdui Cave.
We're really going to a cave.
(But they can't find Bengdui Cave
where the treasure is.)
Will we find a cave...
at the end of this path?
- Let's go.
- How is there a cave here?
It's an unlikely place
to find a cave.
It looks like
there won't be any cave around.
My shoes are sinking deep
into the ground.
Wait. This...
What is this? Is this mud?
- Right. It's weird.
- My feet keep sinking.
What is this?
It feels weird.
Did they deceive us?
Hold on.
(His shoe came off.)
My shoe almost came off.
They deceived us.
What do you call that place
where you sink?
- The mudflat.
This is the curse
of the black mudflat.
(He just says
whatever comes to his mind.)
(They keep walking.)
I think something might appear.
- It looks like it will be open.
- It might be open.
It's time something appears.
There is light.
This place. What?
- What is this?
- Why is there a container?
Welcome.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
This is Expedition Curator
Kim Sang Su...
who will help us
on the special expedition.
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Yes.
- You're holding a whip.
- That is right.
- Why?
Like this.
(He's startled.)
The sound isn't coming out properly.
- This...
- Why...
- Right.
- Why do you have this?
Didn't you watch the movie?
"Indiana Sang Su" is the parody...
of "Indiana Jones."
("Indiana Sang Su")
- Jones and Sang Su.
- Yes.
Could you give us
a brief explanation of Bengdui Cave?
Yes. "Bengdui" means
a wide, open field.
- Bengdui.
- It's "bengdui" in Jeju dialect.
That means lava flowed
onto flat land.
(Bengdui Cave was formed
by lava flowing beneath it.)
The length of this cave is 4.5km.
- It's 4.5km.
- Will we be okay?
(They're slightly worried.)
I think it's going to be so scary.
(They will explore
the highlight part.)
We will begin...
- Let's start.
- the exploration.
- Let's go with Indiana Sang Su.
- Yes.
Let's go.
(They head inside Bengdui Cave
with Indiana Sang Su.)
Why does it look like that?
(The security is tight
in front of the cave.)
We're going through this gate.
(He's overly immersed.)
This is a very special place.
Only a few people
from the production crew...
- can go in.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So I'll be at the exit.
- See you.
- Come in.
- Prepare your lanterns.
- I'll turn this on.
(They all turn on their lanterns.)
We'll go in.
I wouldn't get stuck, right?
If I get stuck,
leave everything and save me first.
Just throw away the cameras. Okay?
That's why you're coming.
It's so refreshing.
Come slowly.
- Slowly.
- It's slippery here. Be careful.
- Be careful.
- Be careful of the moss.
(They enter the cave
that's like an underground bunker.)
It's like there will be ghosts.
(It's an amazing space.)
- It's refreshing.
- It's sharp.
As you can see,
the cave connects this way as well.
That's right.
Since Bengdui Cave...
stretches along a flat land,
even when small obstacles were met,
the lava split them up.
- Right.
- The lava...
- moved in and returned.
- I see.
That is how it became
a great maze of a cave.
- This was all created by the lava?
- Gosh.
It must be really scary
to come here alone.
This is amazing.
In case a bad situation occurs,
this line was installed
for safety measures.
- You see this, right?
- The blue line. Right.
We'll move in this way.
I've never been inside a real cave.
- It's really fascinating.
- Right.
- Gosh, it goes in that way too.
- Gosh.
(Different paths can be seen.)
This is crazy.
- All right. Look carefully here.
- Right.
- Gosh, what is this?
- What is this?
This is a cave coral.
When met with air,
these things are formed.
- I see.
- How old is this?
It takes around 100 years
for it to grow around 1cm.
- Around 100 years?
- That's around how long it takes.
Then how old is this?
Right. It is expected...
to have gone through
a long period of time.
It looks so fascinating.
(This was filmed
with an expert's permission.)
I want to take this home.
I can't do that, can I?
He will go to prison if he does,
right?
That can never happen.
This looks fascinating.
(A strange product formed by nature)
- Gosh, the path is narrow.
- Come in this way.
Gosh, it's so low.
Gosh! What is this?
Take a look.
This is a cave and so is this.
This one is a cave too.
This is one path,
and this is another.
- These are all paths.
- Right.
There are three paths.
This is the Nostril Rock.
(It's known as the Nostril Rock
as there are two holes together.)
This part was formed
because of the lava.
It looks just like a tongue.
You will be able to see it
from up here.
(A geological structure formed
like a tongue due to the lava)
We will go in this way...
and come out the other way.
- Really?
- Gosh.
Go in yourselves.
Sorry? Just us?
This one will feel a bit scary.
Gosh, nothing can be seen
without the lights.
This will feel really scary.
Here I go.
- Be careful.
- Gosh.
(Dark)
- Gosh, this is a bit scary.
(Flustered by the darkness)
(DinDin and Se Yoon
enter behind him.)
Gosh!
(He lets out a shout out of fear.)
- What is this?
- It's getting narrower.
It's so narrow.
What did he tell us to do
to come out?
Hey, it's too narrow!
Should we turn back?
We can't turn back.
- Should we move in farther?
- Move in farther.
- Move in farther?
- Yes.
- Gosh!
- This is amazing.
Be careful.
(Panting)
Hold on. It's blocked here.
Gosh.
Gosh, hold on.
It's completely blocked.
(Dead end)
It's there a path here?
- Gosh.
- Gosh, it's a maze.
We can't get out.
(Will they be trapped
in the Bengdui Cave like this?)
- Jong Min.
- I'm excited to see what's there.
We're the first ones...
to go in as ordinary people
in our country.
Was this place never opened?
No one must have witnessed
this place.
- It's called Gimnyeong Cave.
- Gimnyeong Cave?
We must be going inside a cave.
This is awesome.
Are you serious?
This place was designated as...
a UNESCO World Natural Heritage
in 2007.
It's Gimnyeong Cave.
- Gimnyeong Cave.
For the preservation of the cave,
this place was kept hidden.
But the Korea Heritage Service
and Jeju Island...
revealed this area
just for 2 Days and 1 Night viewers.
Gosh, thank you.
- Gosh.
- That decision...
- As the one who will lead us,
we will welcome
Researcher Ki Jin Seok.
- It's great to meet you.
- Hello.
- He's dressed a bit like us.
- Gosh.
I'm the curator who will lead you
through the cave expedition.
- You're a curator?
- Right.
Please open the gate.
It feels cool already.
(They head inside
with excited hearts.)
It feels quite chilly.
I'm serious.
(The cave wind can be felt
from the entrance.)
- It's a jungle here.
- This is amazing.
- Gosh!
(Surprised)
As I heard you were coming,
I turned on the air conditioner.
This is a natural wind.
(It's the grand entrance.)
What is going on?
It's this cool here?
- Gosh.
- This place feels like a movie set.
Gosh!
Gosh! What is this place?
- Gosh, look at these steps.
- Right.
You can feel that this place is old.
- There's water dripping, sir.
- Right.
How long is this place, sir?
It's around 700m in total.
- Around 700m?
- It isn't that long.
It isn't that long.
There's a legend that
a large snake lived here.
That was why it was also called
the Snake Cave.
- The Snake Cave?
- Right.
- I have a question.
- Okay.
Was this really formed
just by the lava? Or...
There was no interference by man.
It was naturally formed.
- It was naturally formed?
- Yes.
The lava was around 800 to 1,200C.
It kept melting the ground
as it was hot.
The cave wasn't formed this deep
right away.
- It happened over time.
- The ground kept melting,
and the ceiling was formed
as the top part hardened first.
A path was formed...
and the lava kept flowing.
From the oreum in Deokcheon-ri,
the lava gushed out.
It flowed out for around 14km
to Woljeong-ri while forming caves.
Isn't this a lava rock?
- Basalt.
- This is basalt.
- It's basalt.
- Basalt.
It's my first time
seeing sand in a cave like this,
- Right.
- and I've seen many other caves.
- I mentioned limestone earlier.
- Right.
This is lime.
- I see.
This is a lava tube,
but this cave also has...
the characteristics
of a limestone cave.
It was designated as
a UNESCO World Natural Heritage...
after its worth was acknowledged.
I see.
The wonders of nature are just...
When else will we get a chance
to visit a place like this?
If you look here,
you will spot bat stools.
- What?
- I see.
- There are bats here?
- Yes. There are bats here.
- There's a lot more than expected.
- These are their stools.
- There's a lot.
- This must be their restroom.
If we turn off our lights
all at once,
it will be intense.
Should we try turning them off?
I'm curious.
- Let's give it a try.
- Let's give it a try. I'm curious.
- We'll turn off our headlamps.
- Where is it?
One, two, three.
(Pitch black)
Check this out.
- Nothing can be seen.
- Right.
My gosh!
(Turning the lights back on
out of fear)
The path is winding like a snake.
Right. This is why it got that name.
It feels nice as it's so cool here.
It's grand.
It feels like entering a coal mine.
The sand...
- is disappearing.
- It's disappearing, isn't it?
It will slowly disappear.
- As we're deep inside.
- Right.
This is amazing.
- Gosh.
- I've never been...
in a cave like this.
Right.
You can see that it's blocked there,
- right?
- Yes.
That is a lava waterfall.
- It isn't that big, though.
- A lava waterfall?
The lava that flowed from the top...
flowed downward,
and it hardened just like that.
- Can we go up that way?
- We can.
Let's go up.
Be careful.
The other team
went to a different cave, right?
- Yes.
- That place is full of slopes.
- Is it narrow there?
- The paths are narrow.
What a relief.
They have to crawl up?
This place is a suite room
compared to that place.
- What a relief.
They must feel really scared.
The path is narrowing.
I'm fine.
- Gosh, what are these?
- What are these?
These are called lava stalactites.
- What are they?
- Stalactites?
The lava dripped down
due to gravity...
- It hardened just like that.
- and hardened just like that.
- Right. I read about this.
- Right.
It feels like we're inside
the belly of a whale.
- Right.
- This is the end.
- We've reached the end.
We've managed to reach
the end of Gimnyeong Cave.
- It's fascinating how it's blocked.
- Right.
(A precious experience
that cannot be bought with money)
Are you done looking around?
- Yes.
- Let's head back.
I'm just left in awe.
(They head back with light steps.)
It's a World Natural Heritage.
- Please stand in a line here.
- We must be doing something now.
It must be our mission.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
- We had a great time, sir.
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
- Won't it be around 10m?
- Right.
(What awaits them?)
Did you enjoy your time here?
- It was amazing.
- I had a great time.
It felt even more exciting as it was
something that was never seen.
Then right here,
- What?
the first mission for the gold coins
will begin.
What is it?
The mission in Gimnyeong Cave...
is called Blackout Motion Capture.
Just like how we turned off
our lights earlier?
- You turned off your lights, right?
- Yes.
- Keep your eyes closed.
- Nothing could be seen.
We have to get used to the darkness.
Really?
What do we have to do?
While the lights are out, you must touch
the person in front of you...
to figure out their pose...
and strike the same pose.
(We have to touch each other?)
You have a time limit of 30 seconds.
You all will succeed
when the three of you...
are striking the same pose
when the lights are turned on.
There are a total of ten attempts.
You will get two gold coins
every time you succeed.
That's a total of 20 gold coins.
- Right.
- That's a total of 20 gold coins.
- That's amazing.
- I think we can do this.
Do you want to go last, Seon Ho?
- I'll make sure to touch well.
- Are you confident?
Can you touch us and get it right?
- Let's begin.
- Let me straighten my clothes.
Can I touch you boldly?
You shouldn't be slow.
Touch my whole body right away.
- If I touch the wrong part...
- Okay.
- You two should turn around.
- Don't think.
- Just touch me and copy my pose.
- Okay.
It's easy.
Let's begin.
Show him the pose.
Ten, nine, eight, seven...
(A somewhat provocative pose)
(Right before the blackout)
- We shouldn't talk?
- Two.
- Earlier.
- One. Blackout.
Jong Min, touch me.
Where are you? Okay.
- Okay. I got it.
- The lower body too.
- Okay.
Let's go. Seon Ho.
- Where are you?
- I'm here. Okay.
- It's easy, right?
- I'll look straight ahead.
- Is your hand here? Okay.
- Yes. In the back.
- All right.
- Five, four,
three, two, one.
Lights on.
- Okay.
(Perfect)
- Correct.
- Okay. Well done.
- It was...
- Jong Min is really fast.
- Really?
- Of course.
(He goes straight to Sae Ho
as soon as the light is turned off.)
(Touching)
Okay. I got it.
Okay.
(Jong Min didn't see the pose
but copied it successfully.)
(Seon Ho also touched Jong Min.)
(They easily earned 2 gold coins.)
- Here's the second question.
- I know the pose.
We should do well.
- Nine, eight...
- You did well, Seon Ho.
Okay. Thank you, Jong Min.
(He strikes the pose
with difficulty.)
(Blackout)
- This is hard.
- Is it hard?
I see.
Three, two, one.
- Turn the light on.
- My gosh.
- This is it.
- No.
Hey, what are you doing, Seon Ho?
(Jong Min was touching well.)
- Come, Seon Ho.
- Where are you?
- I'm here.
- What?
- You should face me.
- Shall I?
What is this?
(Unlike Sae Ho,
Jong Min stretches his arms.)
Go ahead and touch it.
I did this.
- What?
- I did this.
- You did?
- Yes.
- I did this.
- Oh, no.
So I did the same thing.
Really?
Let's continue.
Show him the pose.
Five, four...
(Shocked)
(What is the pose for Round 3?)
- Here.
- What's this?
(Laughing)
- Is it at the bottom?
I can't see.
- Here.
- What's this?
- Is it at the bottom?
- Is it at the bottom? What?
- Okay? Okay.
Is it up or down?
- Is it up or down?
- I can't see.
Of course, you can't.
- Okay.
- What's with your fingers?
What are you doing
with your fingers?
You have ten seconds left.
- You're doing it again.
- Okay.
What should I do?
It's done.
- Five, four...
- Done? You came too late.
- What? What's this?
- Touch my hand.
(Will Seon Ho be able to copy it
within 3 seconds?)
- Okay.
- One. Turn the light on.
(Surprising)
- What did you do?
- We did it.
- I think we got it right.
- It's done.
(Seon Ho copied it perfectly
only in 3 seconds.)
Success!
Seon Ho. You did it in five seconds.
Hey, he did it only in five seconds.
I just imagined it.
- My gosh.
- I touched his bottom,
- so I was like, "Bottom?"
- With only five seconds left.
(Even after that...)
(They succeeded in Round 4.)
(They succeeded in Round 5.)
(They even succeeded in Round 6.)
- Success!
- Yes!
(They earned 10 gold coins
in an instant.)
- My goodness.
- Seon Ho is good at this.
- We're doing well.
- Okay.
We missed only one question.
- Let's go.
- All right. Turn around.
We will change the order.
- Come on.
- Why?
- Why would you do that?
- We planned it in the first place.
- Really?
- Gosh.
It's because we're doing so well.
- Jong Min.
- Okay.
We're too good.
- Let's change the order for them.
- How?
Seon Ho, do you want to go first?
- You go 1st.
- Should I go 1st?
Yes. I'll go second,
and Jong Min will go last.
Okay.
Let's continue.
I bet it will take 0.3...
Show him the pose.
- What is this?
- Nine, eight, seven...
Four, three, two, one.
- You should touch my fingers well.
- Blackout.
Where are you?
What is this?
(Searching without hesitation)
Okay?
- Yes.
- You should hurry.
I should do it too.
- Okay.
- You have ten seconds left.
What?
Okay.
(It turned into a circle
over his head.)
- Okay.
- Five, four,
- Will they get it right?
- three,
two, one.
Turn the light on.
This is it. Isn't this it?
- Wrong.
- Isn't this it?
- Why?
- I was doing this.
You should've done it like this.
Why...
- Why did you do that?
- You told me not to do it.
- The hands should be like that.
- Stay in the back.
What are you doing?
(Laughing)
Seon Ho will sleep outdoors.
No.
Here's the eighth question.
- The eighth?
- Yes.
We've done a good job.
Show him the pose.
- I see. Hang on.
- Seven, six...
(The point is to hold the ankle
with one hand.)
(Confused)
Blackout.
- I'm here.
- Where?
- Are you down there?
- Watch my left and right hands.
- Are you at the bottom?
- My left and right hands.
(Did Jong Min
strike the pose properly?)
- Can you feel it? Okay.
- Yes.
- Three, two, one.
- The hand...
- Just the leg... Done.
- Turn the light on.
What are you doing?
Why are you...
(Jong Min struck the pose properly.)
Seon Ho is good.
- We have five seconds left.
- Four,
- three,
- The position of your palm.
- two...
- Your hand.
Why are you...
(They failed because of Sae Ho.)
(Embarrassed)
- You weren't like this earlier.
- I don't understand.
You were like this.
Should we go with the order
we tried first?
- Let's do that.
- Okay.
(They lost confidence
after failing consecutively.)
Here's the ninth question.
- Turn around.
- Then...
Be careful with your hand.
Show him the pose.
You should copy
the facial expression too.
How would we copy
the facial expression?
How would we know?
(The point is the fatal wink.)
Five, four,
- three,
- Jong Min.
- two, one.
- Yes.
- Blackout.
- Touch my whole face.
- Okay.
- Really?
- Touch my whole face.
- Hang on.
Didn't you say it'd be easy?
Eyes?
How can I know they're your eyes?
- Lips.
- Lips? What?
Why lips?
- Are these your lips?
- Ten seconds left.
Jong Min, you should hurry.
- I'm here.
- You should come.
(Hurriedly approaching Seon Ho)
(Super focused)
(A dramatic success
or 3 consecutive failures?)
Turn the light on.
(Closing both eyes,
Opening both eyes)
You failed.
What? Which part is wrong?
- Which part?
- This is wrong.
You can't come to me
with only three seconds left.
- This is the last question.
- Okay.
Turn around.
(The last round)
(The last chance in Gimnyeong Cave)
I can't see when it's dark.
Right.
All right. Let's continue.
Show him the pose.
What is this?
- Seven, six,
- My gosh, this is crazy.
- five, four...
- This is...
- One. Blackout.
- Wait. I couldn't see it.
- I couldn't see it. Hey.
- Where are you?
- Hey.
- I'm down here.
- Where?
- Are you down?
- Touch me carefully.
Touch both my hands carefully.
- The right and left hands.
- Okay.
And the legs.
What are you doing?
- You should come now.
- Okay.
- Okay. Go ahead.
(Sae Ho succeeded.)
- Where are you?
- Ten seconds left.
Down here.
- What is this?
- Touch both hands carefully.
- And the legs.
- Five, four,
- three,
- Just do it.
- two, one.
- Don't joke around. Just do it.
- Turn the light on.
- All right.
- Two, one.
- Don't joke around. Just do it.
- Turn the light on.
- All right.
- Okay.
- Is that it?
- Did we succeed?
Is this right?
- Success.
- Seon Ho is good.
(They got their pride back
in the last round.)
- Jong Min was missing at first.
- Right.
- My gosh.
- I know.
You did well.
Nice.
You succeeded in six rounds.
- So you got 12 gold coins.
- All right.
You can take these.
(Time to receive the prize)
- Ta-da.
- Okay.
Can we eat this?
If you eat it,
the gold coin is gone.
We should never
give these to Jong Min.
- We never know what he'll do.
- You should keep them.
I don't like chocolate.
Now, let's go meet the other team.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
It's not so hot today.
That's because we just got out.
Is that it?
(Meanwhile, in Bengdui Cave)
Hang on. This is blocked.
(Dead end)
Is there a way?
Yes.
This is a maze. We can't get out.
(Where's the way out?)
- Gosh, what is this?
- Mind the ground.
I bet it collapsed.
(It is a total mess
with the maze and rocks.)
Hey, this is the way out.
(DinDin's camera)
Gosh, this is amazing.
(They see a light in the distance.)
We could sleep in a tent here.
Can we sleep here?
This is a real cave.
Gosh, look at that. How is it...
Can you come down?
(It's quite high.)
(It's not easy to get out.)
I think I can.
(DinDin and Lee Joon
come down carefully.)
I shouldn't step on this?
- Where?
- Like this?
Turn around. Yes.
(Lastly, it's Se Yoon's turn.)
- Here?
- Yes.
Put your left foot here.
Don't my bottoms look too big?
- The right foot here.
- Here?
Further down.
They are huge.
- Can I spank you?
- They're as big as the rock.
- They're really big.
- As big as the rock here.
- Your right foot. Like this.
- My goodness.
I want to spank you.
I'm so humiliated. I'll teach you
a lesson once I get there.
Then you should go back up.
- Go back up.
- I'll go down.
- No, go up.
- Why?
- Hurry and go back up.
- My gosh.
- Take a photo first.
DinDin, you should be here.
- Here?
- Yes.
- Let's take a photo.
- My goodness.
My gosh. This will be
my family treasure.
Seriously.
(The Bengdui Cave photo zone)
(In front of the Nostril Rock)
Let's go this way.
This is a dead cave.
In a dead cave,
you can see cracks like this.
And water seeps in like this.
(He looks up
at the roof of the cave.)
- There are bats.
- Oh, no.
(Flapping)
They're so scary.
(Scared)
(Even DinDin's cameraman jumps.)
What did I tell you? They slap you.
They're so scary.
- Hey.
- That was a huge surprise.
What did I say? I wasn't lying.
- They can hit you.
- What...
We scared the bats.
They don't scare us.
Yes. Sorry.
Come this way.
Are those bats old too?
We'll keep going this way.
- Is there more?
- Yes.
(Next episode)
(It's time for
a special Jeju experience.)
(If you want to live,)
(run.)
(Powerful and thrilling...)
(are Jeju's mountains...)
(and sea)
(Hurry, Se Yoon!)
(Gosh, it's cold.)
(The rough excursion...)
(and the mysteries at the end.)
(And then...)
Gosh, this is...
It's scary.
Where are we...
- What's this?
Why aren't you getting out?
(The members are in
pitch-black darkness.)
Hello?
(A maze in which
they can't see an inch ahead.)
(Will they manage to get back?)
I'll take it off.