(It feels like today will be filled with luck.)
- Gosh, it's beautiful.
- It's beautiful.
This is...
- Gangwon Province.
- What is this place?
- It's no joke.
(Amazed)
This place is beautiful.
- It's like a work of art.
- It really is.
- What's this?
- It's so pretty.
- Hello.
(What awaits the members here?)
- How beautiful.
Have you been well?
- Yes.
We've been doing well, but Jong Min is a bit...
- He bled a little.
- He had a problem.
You can tell from the area under his nose.
- While shaving...
- While shaving, he...
- It's a lot more than...
- Aren't you past the age...
to cut yourself while shaving?
It's nice. He's like Charlie Chaplin.
That's not what's important.
- Then what's important?
- Everyone.
I got a text from Bo Gum...
- exactly two minutes ago.
- Really?
- He gets up early.
- I didn't contact him separately.
"Good morning."
"Good luck with the 2 Days 1 Night shoot today."
"Have a great first day of August."
- What is this?
- Why did he...
suddenly send a text to you like that?
I didn't send one first.
He sent me one, knowing we have a shoot today.
He sent one to you quite late.
He sent me a text at 6:30am.
- Bo Gum did?
- Yes. I was surprised in the car.
- Really?
- I thought it was a spam text.
"What is this?" I checked it like that.
- You got one too?
- He sent me one!
- He really got a text.
- He sent me one at 8:15am.
- Yes! This is how Bo Gum is.
That's Bo Gum.
- Bo Gum!
- Hi, Bo Gum.
- Hello.
- Hey, Bo Gum.
- Today...
- We, who got a text from you,
- are doing our best with the shoot.
- Thanks to you,
we could start the opening with excitement.
- Bo Gum, thank you.
- Bo Gum!
- Thank you.
- Stay healthy!
When will you be back?
- I love you!
- Be on our show again.
- It's really fascinating.
- Of course, I'm grateful.
- How did he text us first?
- Seriously.
He must've texted us...
- because he liked us.
- That's right.
- Of course.
- Seriously, this year...
Jong Min has special news.
- What is it?
- I read an article about you.
There was an article about him?
Apparently, it said KOYOTE was having a concert...
- in Australia on Sunday.
- Right.
So I thought Jong Min wouldn't be here for the shoot.
- How will he perform on Sunday?
- But he was here, bleeding.
Seriously, what...
- You'll go to Australia tomorrow?
- Yes.
As soon as I land there,
- I have to perform right away.
- But...
- That's crazy.
We're okay, so you can leave today.
(Flustered)
We're okay. I feel like Bo Gum will come if we ask him.
- Bo Gum?
- Yes, Bo Gum.
I should finish the shoot, then.
(A survival instinct)
You're going to Australia...
like you're going to a different city in Korea.
There are so many people who want them.
And their new song is doing so well.
"Call me, call me." It goes like this.
- What's that?
- Are you dancing?
(Flustered by his sudden dance)
(And he's quite good!)
- He's good.
- You're good.
- Oh, it's you on the phone?
- Yes. "Call me."
(Working hard so he won't lose his spot to Bo Gum)
Anyway, where are we?
Today's destination is Korea's popular summer vacation spot.
It's Donghae and Samcheok of Gangwon Province.
- That's great.
- Samcheok.
This is a tourist site developed from a former limestone mine.
(Mureung Byeolyucheonji)
(A tourist site recreated from a former limestone mine)
(It's famous for its lavender festival held every June.)
Before we begin our trip, let me tell you this.
- Before?
- Today, it's really important...
to meet a good team.
Let's divide you into teams first.
- Through a simple mission.
- Yes.
- Sounds good.
- A mission to decide your team...
is Youth Song Quiz, which suits the verdant summer.
- Youth Song?
- I love youth songs.
The one who answers...
the singer and the title the most after listening to a song...
will get to decide his team however he wants.
- All right.
- So he'll be a team leader.
The one who gets the most answers.
- Are you ready? The first question.
- Yes.
Play the song.
Wait. What?
- I got it.
- What? I couldn't hear it.
- What is it?
- Did you play something?
"Barefooted Youth."
("Barefooted Youth")
Bucks.
- I got it! What?
- I got it.
- What is it?
- Se Yoon.
"Barefooted Youth" by Buck.
Buck?
Se Yoon, correct.
- Isn't it Bucks?
- Bucks is...
(Let's just dance.)
(Barefooted youth)
(Vocalizing)
- This is a youth song?
- Yes.
(In a trance)
(Here we go!)
(Zoom)
(The youth song from the old days gets you excited right away.)
- In a club...
- This is fun.
It's a club song.
It's not Bucks?
- Wait, who?
- This time,
we'll play a song for the youngsters since we have Seon Ho.
- Okay.
- Let's play for the youngsters.
Play the song.
- DinDin!
- Seon Ho!
(- DinDin!
- Seon Ho!)
- Who said it first?
- DinDin.
DinDin.
- DAY6.
- That's right.
- "Time of Our Life."
- He's right.
- He got it.
- I knew it too.
(A beautiful page of youth)
(They suddenly sing together without any accompaniment)
(Bass, keyboard, guitar)
(Immersed)
- This song is famous.
- Come on!
(The song is played for them.)
(Beautiful)
(A beautiful page of youth)
What?
What is this?
- What is this?
(Introducing today's surprise guests)
(A beautiful page of youth)
(The singer of this song)
(All the members of DAY6 are here.)
(They haven't grasped the situation.)
- What?
- What are they doing?
What? Is it DAY6?
- What?
- Let's party for now. Come on!
(Let's just jump.)
What?
(DAY6 sings "Time of Our Life" live.)
- What?
- Gosh, it's DAY6.
- Gosh.
- What?
(Fascinated)
(DAY6 gets closer to them.)
Sing together!
(Time of our life)
(Singing along)
(Singing along automatically)
(A masterpiece you must sing along to)
(DAY6 has come to 2 Days 1 Night.)
- Is it DAY6?
- What is this?
- Thank you.
- It's DAY6. What is this?
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Have you been well?
- What's going on?
- I'm a huge fan.
- Hello.
- What is this?
- Good to see you.
Hello.
(DAY6, a band that's guaranteed to deliver)
(They honed their skills through busking and live performances.)
(They grew into an all-round band that can write their own songs.)
("Time of Our Life," "You Were Beautiful")
(The band that created a reverse-chart success story)
(1st place on a public TV music show 9 years after their debut)
(Whenever they hold a concert, )
(they sell out.)
(They had a solo concert at Gocheok Sky Dome...)
(for the first time for a band.)
(They captured both popularity and artistry.)
("DAY6 and aespa, the Best Singers of 2024")
(They placed number 1 as the standout singer of the year.)
(Now, the band dashes toward the top.)
(Guitarist and vocalist, SungJin)
(Bassist and vocalist, Young K)
(Keyboardist and vocalist, Wonpil)
(Drummer, Dowoon)
In 1, 2, 3.
- Hello, we're DAY6.
Welcome!
- Yes.
- It's youth today.
- I was really surprised.
- I know.
DAY6 is the busiest these days.
- That's right. They go abroad too.
- We had a hard time inviting them.
- I know.
- Really?
You were on the bus too?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Ta-da.
- They were on the bus with us?
What? Were you on the upper deck?
No, we came just now.
- Oh, after they dropped us off?
- Yes.
Oh, because it's a shuttle bus...
Let's get off now.
Let's start the shoot.
We need to get off quickly.
(The members who were on standby got off the bus.)
(DAY6 got on the bus.)
- Are the cameras rolling?
- Yes.
Hi.
DAY6 is here.
The members have no idea.
(Peeking)
(What are they talking about?)
Passion!
- I'll do my very best.
- Okay.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's... No.
- DAY6.
(DAY6 waited after shouting their team cheer.)
I see. That's why the writers kept on kicking us.
- To get us to leave.
- They rushed us.
- "Go already."
- "Go."
- "Get off the bus."
- "Hurry."
They'll join us...
- for the entire trip.
- They'll stay with us?
- Really?
- Is that true?
(They will stay with the members until tomorrow.)
- They'll even stay for the night?
- It's an honor.
- They'll stay for the night?
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- Why?
- Are you serious?
Well,
- September 7...
- Is there an event to promote?
- will be our tenth anniversary.
- Right!
- Right.
- Already?
After performing for ten years,
we'd like to show other sides of ourselves to the viewers.
The staff invited us to join your show for this episode.
- Our show has a long history too.
- So we decided...
- Right.
- to join you.
- It's a prestigious show too.
- This is great for us.
- What a sweet thing to say.
- They have a similar vibe to ours.
Have you watched our show before?
- We love it.
- Of course.
- I noticed this about Joon.
- Yes?
- He was...
- What about him?
- Have you crossed paths with him?
- Have you?
He was really bad at games.
- So you watched our show.
- You watched our show.
That left a strong impression on me.
Really? Well, it's also part of my character on this show.
- It is, isn't it?
- It's a TV show, after all.
Actually, I'm pretty... I mean, yes.
He can't even speak well.
He's bad at everything, including speaking.
It was entertaining to watch.
SungJin. You know what?
- The eojuk place from Hapjeong...
- Yes.
- You know the eojuk restaurant?
- Eojuk?
- Yes. The fish noodle soup?
- The fish noodle soup.
- Jirisan Fish Noodle Soup.
- I went there to film a TV show.
When I was filming the show, I looked over and saw him there.
He told me it was his regular spot.
- Their food is really good.
- I see.
I really enjoyed the food.
- You have different connections.
- Of course.
- The eojuk connection.
- We both love fish noodle soup.
- Of course, we love it.
It's hard to find that dish in Seoul.
- We crossed paths with them.
- Yes.
But Seon Ho seems a bit shy to meet them.
- You punk.
- Why don't you say hello?
I'm a huge fan. I'm serious.
- Thank you.
I listen to all the songs listed in your album.
- Really?
- Name one.
Like what? Name one song in their album.
- I like "I Loved You."
- Gosh.
- That's a popular title.
- "Love Me or Leave Me." "Upgrade."
I like all of your songs.
- He's a real fan.
- Thank you.
- Seon Ho is a true fan.
- Let's switch spots.
- Come here.
- Let him stand next to them.
- Seeing how much he loves them...
- Seriously. Seon Ho...
- often said he was your fan.
- I mentioned it often.
- Thank you.
- I'm a huge fan.
- He's so shy.
- All right.
We'll have to start our trip now.
The theme of our trip, with DAY6 joining us...
is Welcome to the Real Variety Show.
Great!
(That's a great title.)
(They start singing in sync again.)
(At this point, they're addicted to sing-alongs.)
(Hopping)
It looks like a spirit possessed you.
(Laughing)
Yes!
As it's DAY6's 1st time starring in a real wild variety show,
we prepared a trip with various and fun activities.
Today, you will divide into 2 teams of 5.
- Great.
- Each time you win a mission...
until lunchtime,
you will receive a meal ticket that will allow you to eat...
at a local restaurant in Samcheok.
- That's great.
- Nice.
What happens if we don't win any meal tickets?
- We can't eat at all?
- Really?
You might regret joining our show. I'm serious.
(Gasping)
- You'll be really hungry.
- I think...
You might think, "Must I do this just for some food?"
- I hear Young K is a big eater.
- Right. You eat a lot.
- Right.
- He's a big eater.
That's why I had breakfast.
- Just in case.
- That was good thinking.
- You have the right attitude.
- Just in case?
Is Young K the only big eater?
- What about you?
- I also eat a lot.
- Right.
- Yes.
- He and I are the eating buddies.
- Right.
(They'll show us a proper eating show.)
- Do you eat less in comparison?
- Yes. Dowoon and I don't eat a lot.
- The two of them...
- You don't eat a lot.
- We don't.
Eating with company is more fun. But the two of you don't eat much.
- We're grateful to them.
- Yes.
- They're great at get-togethers.
- They leave some food for you.
- We split the tab.
- Right.
Since your meal is at stake,
your choice of teammate will matter a lot.
- Yes.
- Right.
To balance out the portions among the members of DAY6,
we've paired up a big eater and a light eater together.
Young K and Wonpil will be a pair.
- Okay.
- Really?
SungJin and Dowoon will be a pair.
- Okay.
- Big and light eaters.
- You guys can play...
rock-paper-scissors or another game...
to pick a member of our show.
- Gosh, this is too much.
- My goodness.
- This is too hard for me.
- Gosh, this will be tough.
Being chosen last will hurt my pride.
So it's okay as long as I avoid that.
I think I know who will be chosen last.
(He knows a lot about the show.)
- We probably know who it is too.
- Right.
Does his name have two syllables?
- That's a possibility.
- Is it?
Young K. To be honest,
I was trying to be funny. It's a TV show, after all.
- I'll play for real this time.
- Okay.
I never said it would be you.
- I know.
- It's just an example.
- I'm saying this just in case.
- Okay.
- So you won't be entertaining?
- I won't be funny at all.
- Okay.
SungJin, Young K. Why don't you play first?
- Sure.
- Okay.
(Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors)
What was that? The rhythm was nice.
- He sang it like a song.
- Rock-paper-scissors
- Rock-paper-scissors.
(SungJin wins, and Young K loses.)
- Ready or not - Let's see.
- Rock-paper-scissors - I will choose...
- Okay.
- I'm getting a feeling.
Se Yoon.
Gosh, when it comes to food...
- Of course, it's him.
- Why Se Yoon?
I'm pretty sure he's going to give it his all...
- to win the meal.
- That's right.
- Let's do this.
- You're a good judge of character.
- That's the feeling.
- He just eats a lot.
- He's not good at anything.
- Listen.
- Let me give you an analogy.
- Seriously.
- Of course.
- This is great.
- Great, Dowoon.
- Great.
Thank you for having a small portion.
- I will choose...
- Gosh, they chose me.
- DinDin.
- Nice.
- Gosh. Now...
- Why him?
- Can you tell us why you chose him?
- Why?
Let's hear your reason.
- He's very knowledgeable.
- Right.
- He's good with strategies.
- Yes.
- He did study abroad.
- I chose him solely to win.
- This is the Canadian connection.
- Right.
- You've both lived in Canada?
- Really?
- Canada.
- He's from Toronto,
- Toronto.
- I'm from Vancouver.
- You're from Vancouver.
- Vancouver.
Rock-paper-scissors.
- Gosh.
- His low voice is awesome.
- "Rock-paper-scissors."
- You seem way too excited.
I'll pick my role model, Jong Min.
- Okay.
- Really?
- He's your role model?
- Yes!
- You said it.
- Should he talk about it now?
I've actually been keeping quiet.
- What?
- He...
- Why is he your role model?
- Tell us.
What are you talking about, Jong Min?
He's been saying that ever since he made his debut.
- It started a long time ago.
- Why?
(He's been Jong Min's fan for 10 years since his debut.)
(I just want to have a meal with Jong Min.)
(I don't need anything else. I want to get to know him.)
- It started a long time ago.
- Why?
You knew you were his role model, but didn't say anything?
- Yes.
- When...
- I should've mentioned that first.
- But...
- I missed my window.
- Right.
What? You sound just like him when you talk.
I didn't know because he's been quiet.
- When you started to talk, - Don't they have a similar smile?
- you sounded just like him.
- Right.
He looks like Jong Min when he smiles.
- Yes.
(His silly smile resembles Jong Min's silly smile.)
Can you guys stand next to each other?
What's going on?
(They're more curious to see the two together.)
He said I was his role model.
- Let's hear why.
- I mean,
he looks like Jong Min's cousin.
Why is he your role model?
Oh, right. A long time ago,
my mom told me to pick a role model.
- When I was young, - His mother?
I guess I seemed hopeless to her.
She told me to pick a role model.
That's when I saw Jong Min on 2 Days 1 Night.
He had such an innocent smile.
- I wanted to be like him.
- Really?
- Seriously.
- How old were you then?
- That was a long time ago.
I was in elementary or middle school.
- You're meeting Jong Min...
- Yes.
- as a celebrity now.
- Right.
- How do you feel?
- I realized that...
his smile wasn't all sunshine and rainbows.
You saw the reality behind it.
You thought I was so happy...
- when you were a kid.
- Right.
It must be fun...
- to be with your group.
- Right.
I dig your personality.
He looks like a regular member of our show.
- He keeps smiling innocently.
- He's a good fit here.
I've been waiting for this moment for ten years.
He's so funny.
- I wanted to see them together.
- He's perfect for our show.
(A real fan whose dream came true)
- All right. We should pick too.
- Then...
- Wonpil, let's go.
- Who...
- Wonpil, pick any member you want.
- Right.
- Really?
- No pressure.
- Well, the rest of them...
Are about the same.
(They're about the same.)
- So you can pick anyone.
- I see.
- His gaze...
- I...
- No.
(Sae Ho silently pressures him with his gaze.)
- His gaze...
- No.
- You don't have to pick me.
- He's...
- This is really hard for me.
- Okay.
- It's hard, but go on.
- Tell me who you want to pick.
You're so kind.
- He'll pick Sae Ho.
- Really?
(He chooses Sae Ho.)
- Gosh.
Is it okay to give them a pitiful look?
- This is what he told me.
- Okay.
"How can I not pick him when he's looking at me like that?"
(The victim of exaggeration)
- "I'll pick Sae Ho."
- I am Wonpil's pick.
- Yes.
- Right.
- Okay.
- They must've prepared that.
- This will determine the outcome.
- It's the last round.
- Right. It's the worst now.
- Yes.
Rock-paper-scissors..
- Yes, Wonpil!
- Okay.
- Really?
- I don't want to be the last one.
(Desperate)
- I'll do it.
- Hold on.
- I'm sorry.
- Just don't be the last one.
I'm sorry.
- Please join us.
- Okay.
(He picks Seon Ho.)
- We're going to win.
- What? What's going on?
- What do you think?
- We got the call.
- What's going on?
- You'll go over there.
What?
- I wanted to pick you.
- You wanted Joon?
- Really?
- Of course.
- We have the perfect team.
- Great.
(SungJin wanted Joon all along.)
- By the way...
- You'll regret this.
- Our team is super strong.
- Of course.
- It's crazy.
- Seriously.
Our team looks pretty powerful.
- We look like a powerful bunch.
- Seriously.
Right.
- They're strong, indeed.
- That's all they are.
- You know, we're strong and all.
- They're powerful.
But none of us is smart.
- It's okay. Let's do our best.
- I'll try to take that role.
- Okay. You're on your own.
- I'll try.
The rest of us only have power.
(Power, Power, Power, Power, Brain)
- I'm sorry.
- The rest of us only have power?
- We're teamed up.
- Okay.
So you've divided into two teams.
Let's get going.
- Great.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- I love doing missions.
- Welcome.
- It's fun.
- I like games.
Great.
(2 Days 1 Night with DAY6 begins now.)
- It's hot.
- Gosh, you're here on a hot day.
- Right.
- Thanks for coming.
- He's sweating a lot.
- Do you film this early every time?
- Wipe off your sweat.
- Yes, we do.
- Okay.
- Young K, wipe off your sweat.
- It's okay.
You're sweating so much.
- You're not sweating.
- No.
- I don't sweat much either.
- Me neither.
- You're not sweating. I envy you.
- I don't sweat much either.
- You guys are similar, indeed.
- Young K...
- Yes.
- You don't sweat like Jong Min.
(Even their sweat glands function in a similar way.)
You seemed super charismatic when you played the drums.
But you sound like one of us when you speak.
- Yes.
- I love that.
- Your fans must love that twist.
- It's great.
Dowoon is the best.
(Preview clips of DAY6)
(They will laugh...)
(and have a blast.)
(Our youngest is carrying our team.)
(They will dance...)
(and sing.)
(He'll play air drums too.)
(Is it okay for me to be this happy here?)
My gosh.
(Cool sides of them)
(Unexpected sides of them)
(We'll show you every side of them.)
(This is going to be a fun ride.)
(So please...)
We're joined by DAY6.
This is Korea's best...
Real wild road variety show.
Who are we?
2 Days...
- 1 Night!
(2 Days 1 Night)
(Stay tuned!)
(Welcome to the Real Variety Show with DAY6)
(A double-decker bus awaits the members.)
Gosh, the second floor was spacious.
(They get on the double-decker bus, one at a time.)
The second floor was spacious.
Where should we sit?
- We can sit with our team.
- With our team?
We can sit together.
- I hope we can get along.
- Sure.
- You're younger than him, right?
- Yes.
- You were born in 2002.
- Right.
I was born in 1994.
Can we sit together? We're on different teams.
- Can I call you by your name?
- Sure.
- You can speak casually to me.
- Okay.
- Today,
we have a large workforce.
Right.
- So many people are working today.
- You know?
We've got important workers today.
We've got important workers, indeed.
(Important guests are joining the workforce.)
What's this? Isn't this a lake?
- I'm seeing life jackets.
- What? Why are we going in there?
What? Why are we going in there?
- Life jackets?
- I don't see anything here.
We'll already go into the water?
Why are there life jackets?
- What?
- Everyone.
We've arrived?
- Se Yoon.
- What?
- You'll get off the bus here.
(Only Se Yoon is going to get off?)
He'll be dropping out of the show?
Why are you forcing me out?
Why?
- Se Yoon, it's been fun. Thanks.
- Good work.
And someone...
from the opposing team must get off too.
- From our team?
- Pick someone who will get off.
How come they get to choose when you picked for our team?
- Why? We should get to choose too.
- Listen.
I took a look at it. If you weigh over 100kg,
you can't be on many of the rides.
Be quiet.
Se Yoon is getting off here.
To balance out the looks, we'll pick Sae Ho.
(Sae Ho will get off the bus.)
(Why is it Sae Ho again?)
I don't know what this is, but good luck.
- Here we go.
- Good luck.
I don't know what this is, but here I go.
- We got this.
- Good luck.
- Let's go.
You should stick with your peer.
(The guys born in 1982 get off the bus together.)
(Glancing over)
I think they'll get on a duck boat.
I see cameras installed on the duck boats.
Yes, there are cameras.
But they're making Se Yoon ride the duck boat?
They wouldn't make him play a game that requires speed.
But he can't do a lot of the activities here.
- What?
- He's right.
But he can't do a lot of the activities here.
- I took a look earlier.
- I see.
You couldn't do a lot of them if you weighed over 100kg.
- Other people...
- Yes?
Will ride a luge.
Due to the weight limit, Se Yoon can't ride...
the luge.
I can't ride the luge?
- I want to ride the luge.
- I'm sorry.
Through this mission, you can earn an allowance...
to buy cool refreshments and snacks...
to share with your team.
Why don't you take a look at the lake?
Look at the lake?
Do you see them way off in the distance?
- What are we supposed to look at?
- Some things are floating there.
- The yellow things? Okay.
- Yes.
They are rubber ducks.
We'll give you the amount of money written on the bottom...
of the rubber duck for your snack allowance.
We get along very well. Our friendship is strong.
So let's not fight over them.
- Let's go half and half.
- We can split them in half.
- Who will drive then?
- I'll drive.
I'll do it.
- I like driving.
- Listen.
I'm a safe driver.
What kind of driver's license do you have?
- Why are you asking me that?
- Tell me which one you have.
I have a regular license. Class Two.
- Come on.
- What about you?
I have the Heavy Vehicle Driver's License, Class One.
I'm better-suited for this.
How about rock-paper-scissors? It's fair that way.
Let's do rock-paper-scissors, minus one. What do you say?
Okay. Let's play that game to keep it fair.
- Yes, let's do that.
- Go.
- Rock-paper-scissors, minus 1.
Okay!
(Se Yoon wins!)
- Se Yoon will drive the boat.
- My gosh.
- That was a good game.
- Great.
Okay. I'll drive.
Hey, you. You know, don't you?
Only 1 or 2 rubber ducks will have numbers written on them.
There's no point in taking a lot of them.
- Why wouldn't I know?
- Right.
Let's just take it easy...
- and enjoy ourselves.
- Let's enjoy it.
Let's have fun...
- until they tell us to come back.
- Right.
When will we have this chance?
We're going to abandon our teammate here...
after we personally handpicked them?
Of course.
- Is this normal on this show?
- Yes.
And you don't want to feel a lot of pressure when playing.
So picture yourself losing.
When you picture that, it gets easier.
- This is a travel show, so...
- But when he does that,
- he ends up losing.
- Didn't I tell you?
Getting ten questions wrong consecutively was legendary.
- Getting ten questions wrong?
- Yes.
(It's the Zero Point Man Incident.)
Did you try to answer them as you watched the show?
I got eight questions wrong.
(Young K gives off a similar vibe to Joon's.)
See? There's not a huge difference.
- They were difficult questions.
- Right.
- The quizzes were quite hard.
I'd like to go up against Young K later.
- Let's do a 1-on-1 match.
- Of course.
Nice.
Great.
Where are we going this time?
(The bus continues on the road.)
- Oh, this?
- We're getting on a luge.
(They arrive at the top that overlooks a beautiful view.)
- This is fun.
- All of us will get off here.
- I see.
- Okay.
This is so fun. Everything is a surprise for us.
- They don't tell us anything.
- I see.
Let's go, everyone!
I love the song, "Like a Flowing Wind."
- Really?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Come on out.
- Right.
Let's go.
- Jong Min.
- Let's go.
(He sweetly checks on Jong Min too.)
(Everyone gets off the bus together.)
(They arrive at the luge station.)
- Let's go and win some money.
- Let's go, my friend.
My goodness.
(Se Yoon takes the inner seat.)
Are you all right?
(Sae Ho is the only one looking out for Se Yoon.)
It might tilt to one side, though.
- All right.
- Okay.
(They safely get on the boat.)
This is nice.
(They're off to earn the snack allowance.)
I see. Like this. Hey, it's breezy.
- The riverside breeze is cool.
- Right. Usually, by the river...
Gosh, the water is great.
It's so clean.
- The water is emerald.
- Yes, it's clean.
- It's clean.
- It's so cold and refreshing.
(The emerald water is refreshing.)
Can you see the rubber ducks?
Yes.
All right.
We're going to start now.
Ready,
set, go!
(Se Yoon turns the boat toward the ducks as soon as they begin.)
Okay.
(Se Yoon is off to a smooth start.)
(Se Yoon steers the boat more to his side.)
(There aren't any rubber ducks on Sae Ho's side.)
Come on. What are you doing?
(Empty)
Okay.
- Okay. That's mine.
- Gosh, come on.
(Filming was done safely with the site manager's cooperation.)
(Tilting)
- The boat is tilting.
- Hey.
- Let me pick some up too.
You punk. There aren't any rubber ducks left.
Come on. Turn it that way.
- Why won't you do it?
- Wait. Don't do anything.
- I'm supposed to steer the boat.
- Let's go that way.
- I won the game.
Come on. You're being selfish.
We must steer the boat to that side and do this together.
Okay. Fine. I'll steer the boat.
(But the boat turns toward Se Yoon's side again.)
I'll do it.
(I can't put up with this anymore.)
Hey, what are you doing? This is bad.
- You can't do that.
- You...
- What are you doing?
- No, it's dangerous.
- Let me pick up some ducks too.
- It's dangerous.
(The cameraman stops Sae Ho.)
(I can't put up with this anymore.)
Hey, what are you doing? This is bad.
- You can't do that.
- You...
- What are you doing?
- No, it's dangerous.
- Let me pick up some ducks too.
- It's dangerous.
- It's dangerous, you punk.
- Steer the boat to my side too!
- It's dangerous.
- He must be out of his mind.
- Just steer it to his side.
- What do you mean?
Why would I do that?
What's wrong with you?
- Let's go that way!
- Okay, we will. I got it.
- All right. Look.
- You're steering it...
only to your side.
Gosh, no. What are you talking about?
Even if I did that, you still got more rubber ducks.
- What are you, a thug?
- What do you mean?
Don't get me worked up now!
- Let go of that.
- We played a game to pick seats.
- You would've done the same.
- Come on.
- Why are you steering the boat?
- You're being unreasonable!
- Seriously.
- You're being absurd.
Look. Let me loosen it.
Hold on. We're in the middle. Happy now?
Let's try to pick up the ducks together.
Let's go and get a big one.
Let me pick up a big one. I'm just curious.
The amounts aren't that big.
(Meanwhile, Se Yoon checks the amounts on his ducks.)
I'm just curious. Okay?
Let me just pick up a big one. I'm curious.
- Okay. Get a big one.
- Let me just get this one.
(He generously lets Sae Ho pick up the big duck.)
- My gosh. Over there. Hold on.
- Where?
- You do it. What is it?
- Wait.
(While Sae Ho is distracted by the big rubber duck, )
(he tosses his rubber duck.)
(What's the secret behind the duck Se Yoon tossed?)
- You got it, right?
- Gosh.
- You got your wish.
- Gosh, this is big.
You know what? That's enough. That one is mine.
- This is crazy.
- That one is mine.
That was only five cents.
- I'll take that one.
- That was only five cents.
- I'll take one too.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Go where?
- We'll put on protective gear.
(They arrive at the spot for their first mission.)
Gosh, it's hot. It's cool inside.
Hey, it's so hot today.
Don't you think today is the hottest day of the year?
- Out of all the days we filmed?
- Yes.
It will be really hot if we have to sleep outdoors today.
How do you deal with that in summer?
- Sleeping outdoors...
- You sweat like crazy.
If you lose the game,
- you really have to sleep outdoors?
- Yes.
They don't just film a short clip of you sleeping outdoors?
- No.
- You sleep outdoors for real?
We really have to sleep outdoors. And it's so hot.
You'll be dead in the morning.
Right. Once the sun comes up,
- Right.
- you're bound to wake up.
You just have to get up.
- Everyone, are you ready?
- Yes.
- Let's get going.
- Vroom, vroom.
(Let's go for the refreshing luge ride.)
It's hot!
But it's still beautiful.
This is where you will play the first game.
- Okay.
- This time,
two meal tickets are at stake.
This mission is called O-X Quiz Race.
- What? Really?
- "O-X?"
- This place is...
- We won't just be sledding down.
You will see questions while you descend on the luge.
Read the question.
(It's possible to take out and eat a flea's liver.)
Pick either O or X and continue your route.
Will there be a crossroads?
There will be a crossroads.
You may go either left or right.
- Depending on your answer.
- I see.
That sounds fun.
(Exclaiming)
- You have to answer well.
- There's a total of five questions.
If you fail the O-X quiz,
ten seconds per question will be added to your record.
- It must be an individual game.
- The team...
with the fastest total time wins.
- Okay.
- Yes.
In my opinion, it's better to be fast.
Right.
If you think, you'll take too long.
- That's worse.
- Exactly.
- Just keep moving.
- Of course.
- Just get it wrong?
- Don't try to understand.
Don't try to understand. Keep moving.
Group One, please start.
(Group 1 Match)
(Team A: Joon, SungJin versus Team B: DinDin, Wonpil)
Be careful. Don't get injured.
- Right, don't get injured.
- Of course.
Wonpil.
DAY6 members, whatever you do, don't hurt your throat.
Why?
- They have to sing.
- Because we have to sing.
Dowoon says that all the time.
Because we have to sing.
(We have to sing, so don't hurt your throat.)
That's very cruel.
(DAY6's guardian of vocal cords)
Here we go.
Get ready,
set...
(Joon and SungJin versus DinDin and Wonpil)
Okay.
Let's go!
Hey, that's dangerous. Are you insane?
Let me go.
Wonpil, what are you doing?
Why is it so slow?
Wonpil, why aren't you moving?
What is Wonpil doing?
Wonpil gets scared easily.
(Wonpil, the slow starter, is currently in last place.)
(SungJin, DinDin, Joon, Wonpil)
Let's go.
(On the other hand, SungJin is in the lead.)
It feels refreshing.
(Thumbs-up)
Go!
(This is fun.)
It's fast.
(Speed Racer SungJin is coming out strong from the start.)
(1st, SungJin, 2nd, Joon, 3rd, DinDin, 4th, Wonpil)
(The freshness makes them forget the heat.)
Hey, Wonpil.
(Wonpil, hurry up.)
(The 1st 3 players)
- I'm going to block you.
- That's dangerous.
(They pass through the initial straight section.)
My goodness.
(Shaking)
(Wonpil is the only one who's laid-back.)
(They approach the first sharp turn.)
(Drifting right behind Joon)
(SungJin notices the first question.)
(It's possible to take out and eat a flea's liver.)
"It's possible to take out and eat a flea's liver."
What does that mean?
What does it mean? I'll just pick O.
(It's possible to take out and eat a flea's liver.)
(Joon picks O for no reason.)
(Joon)
I don't know.
(SungJin and DinDin pick X.)
(Joon is the only one who picked O. He's currently in the lead.)
(SungJin is chasing right behind.)
(Even though we're on the same team, I won't lose.)
(Approaching the second turn)
(SungJin takes a drift on the inner line.)
(SungJin overtakes Joon and takes the lead.)
(The second question appears.)
(The inventor of the air conditioner was called Carrier.)
(SungJin picks O immediately.)
"Carrier?"
Isn't a carrier something you use for traveling?
(Joon's Camera)
(Despite SungJin's beckoning, )
(Joon picks X.)
(1st, SungJin, 2nd, Joon, 3rd, DinDin, 4th, Wonpil)
(Chasing right behind SungJin)
(Currently in 2nd and 3rd places)
(The third question also appears.)
(This is Wonpil.)
(SungJin, the leader of DAY6, picks O right away.)
What was the question? I couldn't see it.
I don't know. What was the question?
Whatever. I'll pick X.
(He's funny.)
(By the way, where is Wonpil?)
What's that?
"The inventor of the air conditioner was called Carrier."
This is correct.
(Soon, he faces the third question.)
What is it?
What?
(This is Wonpil.)
Yes, that's me.
(The answer is Dowoon.)
(We expect a lot of endearing goofiness.)
(We expect a 3-way battle in Group 1's match.)
(SungJin, DinDin, Joon)
(The fourth question appears.)
(A snake appears when you whistle at night.)
This sounds like nonsense.
Okay.
Why did you pick O?
Are they stupid? The answer is definitely X.
Why did they pick O?
(Will he be Zero Point Man again?)
(A small octopus has 3 hearts.)
"A small octopus has three hearts?"
(Indecisive)
I don't know.
(He picks O.)
It's definitely X.
There's always one heart.
(Only Joon picks X again.)
(DinDin)
(Joon gets ahead of DinDin in the acceleration zone.)
(1st, SungJin, 2nd, Joon, 3rd, DinDin, 4th, Wonpil)
Okay.
(Joon and SungJin are in 1st and 2nd places.)
Our team is doing well.
(A storming race toward the finishing line)
This is good!
(Very excited)
(The speed is so fast that the camera drops.)
(The finish line is right in front of them.)
Nice.
(1st, SungJin, 3 minutes 48 seconds)
(2nd, Joon, 3 minutes 49 seconds)
We won.
(Did Team A dominate Group 1's match?)
By the way, most of our answers were different.
What's more important is that Wonpil isn't coming.
Wonpil is usually slow.
- Really?
- He tends to be a bit slow.
He's very slow.
- He's probably pondering.
- Really?
He's wondering if a small octopus has three hearts.
But he's very late.
"A small octopus has three hearts?"
(As SungJin said, Wonpil tends to be slow.)
No.
There can't be three hearts.
(Wonpil is fighting alone.)
Why isn't anyone in front of me?
I'm the only one here.
I'm too slow.
(The lonely racer in the area)
(Even if he's in last place, he's still happy.)
I don't think Wonpil understood the game.
I don't think so either.
I mean...
(Without knowing how DinDin feels, he appears looking carefree.)
This isn't how you play it.
(3rd, DinDin, 3 minutes 54 seconds)
(He arrives 1 minute later.)
Wonpil, this isn't how you play this game.
- Right?
- Everyone else was so fast.
How did you go so fast? It was scary for me.
It's supposed to be scary.
What were you doing?
- You have to take the risk.
- Right.
Even if you got all the questions correct,
- It wouldn't work?
- it wouldn't work.
- He was being very careful.
- Right?
While we're racing,
what are Se Yoon and Sae Ho up to?
(They get curious about the other two.)
You're a jerk. You turned the wheel toward yourself at the last moment.
Of course. I did it instinctively.
He's a piece of trash.
Moon Se Yoon is horrible.
You got more rubber ducks than me.
That's not true. Look.
What's wrong with you? Do you owe something to DAY6?
We have to eat, at least.
And I don't?
- Goodness.
- Ten, nine,
eight, seven,
- Hey, I couldn't reach it.
- six, five,
- Darn it!
- four,
- three, - I got it.
- This is my last chance.
- two, one.
- It's my last chance.
- Time is up.
We'll calculate when you get off the boat.
There are negative amounts, and you can't take them out.
- Of course not.
- Okay.
(Sae Ho checks inside his basket.)
Let's go back.
(He takes out a rubber duck secretly.)
No.
This is worth a dollar.
What's wrong? Does the amount bother you?
(He fails to dump the negative amount.)
That's life.
We made it through, my friend.
(They return on good terms.)
(Who earned more money to buy snacks?)
- Se Yoon has no manners.
- Gosh.
I haven't seen such a jerk...
- in a long time.
- He turned the wheel...
for his own good.
You had no right to turn the wheel.
- We could've done it together.
- But we played a game!
After the game, you said that I could also control the wheel!
- You can't behave like this.
- You said I could, didn't you?
Let's go and calculate the total.
Could each of you count the total?
- Okay.
- Let's count individually.
- Fifty cents.
- You go first.
Another 50 cents, so it's a dollar.
It's 1.5 dollars.
Two dollars.
Three dollars.
Negative one dollar.
So it's two dollars.
(Total: 2 dollars)
- It's 2.5 dollars.
You got a lot.
One more dollar.
(Total: 3.5 dollars)
- It's 50 cents.
- You have 4 dollars.
- It's 5 dollars.
- You have 9 dollars.
Negative five dollars.
- You have four dollars.
- Gosh.
Sae Ho has...
a total of four dollars.
Don't take it off.
You aren't allowed to do that.
- When did I take it off?
- You were trying to take it off.
- Is it off or on?
- Look at this.
- Stop it. I'll count.
- Let me go.
- Go.
- I will.
Negative five dollars.
- It's 50 cents.
- You have negative 5 dollars.
Negative five dollars.
- Negative 4.5 dollars.
- Four dollars.
- Give it to me.
It's 3.5 dollars.
- Negative...
- Three dollars.
Two dollars. Two dollars.
(Total: Negative 2 dollars)
- A dollar.
- Negative one dollar.
Negative one dollar.
- Now it's zero.
- Zero.
It's starting now.
- It's 50 cents.
(Total: 50 cents)
- You have a dollar.
(Total: 1 dollar)
- It's 50 cents.
- It's 1.5 dollars.
(Total: 1.5 dollars)
Five dollars.
- You have 6.5 dollars.
It's 6.5 dollars.
(Did Se Yoon earn 6.5 dollars?)
Stay still.
We have to make sure. Stay still.
- Stop it. Don't play dirty.
- Look at this.
- Don't touch me.
- I've been suspicious...
of your right hand for a while.
(Squeaking)
What's this sound?
Hold on. He earned 6.5 dollars?
Yes, 6.5 dollars.
(You're killing the duck.)
It's negative ten dollars.
(Destroying evidence)
(Negative 10 dollars)
- It's negative 10 dollars.
- The total is negative 3.5 dollars.
(Se Yoon's total: Negative 3.5 dollars)
We put out 100 rubber ducks.
There was only 1 negative 10 dollars.
(Se Yoon pulled off the 1 percent chance.)
Now, let's go to the cafe.
- Let's go.
(Hoya is excited after earning money for snacks.)
You punk.
We should get snacks together.
Why are you being so selfish today?
(Se Yoon also gets it.)
(Let's go and get snacks.)
(After you, my friend.)
(Let's go and have some snacks.)
(Glancing)
I put negative one dollar in his basket.
(Actually, Sae Ho earned 5 dollars for snacks.)
What did you say?
I'd like to feel some breeze now.
I'm starting to sweat.
- Are you?
- Yes.
Is it possible to know the current ranking?
- Are you anxious?
- The current ranking?
- Yes.
- He won't tell us.
You'd better hear it from them.
It means that our team...
(He's reminded of his younger member.)
- No.
- DinDin is sly, so he's good.
- He's sly?
- What I mean is...
that he's clever.
(My role model talks about someone behind his back.)
As soon as DinDin set out,
he got grabbed.
- Right.
- Joon pulled him back immediately.
(He's always sly and clever when playing games.)
Wonpil was away in the back.
- That's true.
- Wonpil is sweet.
When I met DinDin...
(Will Seon Ho and Young K overcome Wonpil's record?)
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
(Team A: Jong Min, Dowoon versus Team B: Seon Ho, Young K)
Here we go. Get ready...
Go slowly. Don't get injured.
- Let's not get injured.
- Set...
- Don't cheat or get injured.
- Go.
- Let's go.
- Take your time.
(Group 2's match starts.)
Okay, don't get hurt.
Everyone, stay out of the inner lane.
(Charging through the inside lane from the start)
It feels cool.
- It feels really refreshing.
- It's refreshing.
It feels cool.
(Young K takes the lead on the straight road.)
This is fun.
(So far, there's no huge gap among the four.)
This feels cool.
Wait for me.
(My goodness)
(1st, Young K, 2nd, Seon Ho, 3rd, Dowoon, 4th, Jong Min)
(Suddenly, Jong Min stops.)
You dropped something.
Why isn't it moving?
(There's Wonpil in Group 1, and there's Jong Min in Group 2.)
(Will he be in last place from the start?)
(The gap in the distance is significant already.)
(Young K is the 1st to arrive at the 1st question.)
(It's possible to take out and eat a flea's liver.)
"A flea's liver?"
Is it possible or not?
I have no idea.
(He guesses and picks O.)
(Dowoon, who's chasing after him, picks X.)
It's moving so fast.
(Little Jong Min is struggling on his own.)
(Shaking)
(Turtle Racer Jong Min is as slow as Wonpil.)
(Young K, Seon Ho)
(On the other hand, Young K and Seon Ho are cruising.)
(Young K)
(At this rate, they could make up for Wonpil's record.)
(Dowoon is right behind them.)
(1st, Young K, 2nd, Seon Ho, 3rd, Dowoon, 4th, Jong Min)
(Seon Ho is right in front of him.)
(This team's only hope is Dowoon.)
Why isn't it moving?
(Dowoon's luge suddenly stopped.)
(Dowoon)
(He's getting farther away.)
(He tries everything.)
Goodness.
(His luge doesn't budge at all.)
(Dowoon's role model appears.)
(Checking the third question)
"This is Wonpil?"
Wonpil...
What does "This is Wonpil" mean?
My team is doomed.
(Jong Min also stops.)
Why isn't it moving? How did they advance?
Is it Wonpil?
- What?
- Is it the back of Wonpil?
I don't know.
- Is it Wonpil from the back?
- Is it...
"Wonpil from the back?"
- You didn't see it?
- I didn't read the question.
Is it a photo of Wonpil from the back?
- I didn't get to see it.
- I don't think so.
(This is Wonpil.)
It looks like you.
(He's got a good eye.)
(Is Jong Min picking O while thinking that it's Dowoon?)
Goodness.
(Dumb and Dumber, Jong Min and Dowoon)
(In the end, both of them are wrong.)
When you lean forward,
it descends.
Lean forward?
(Okay, Jong Min.)
(Exclaiming)
(1st, Young K, 2nd, Seon Ho, 3rd, Jong Min, 4th, Dowoon)
(This is definitely a race.)
My gosh.
It's finally moving.
(This team seems doomed.)
(Young K is racing forward.)
(Turning)
Everyone is slow.
The color of the water is beautiful.
(Seon Ho is relaxed enough to enjoy the view.)
(Team Young K widened the gap completely.)
Nice.
(1st, Young K, 4 minutes 2 seconds)
It's Seon Ho.
Nice.
Okay.
(DinDin and Wonpil welcome them enthusiastically.)
Where are the others?
They're very late.
Why is the gap so big?
(1st, Young K, 2nd, Seon Ho, 3rd, Jong Min, 4th, Dowoon)
Jong Min, lean forward.
(He's doing his best to lean forward.)
- It's Dowoon.
- Did they stop in the middle?
Okay.
- What are you doing?
- Okay.
Were you on a date with Jong Min?
Jong Min, this isn't the time to celebrate.
I'm sorry,
but are you on a family trip together?
- Right.
- You could be Dowoon's dad.
Look at them.
I did my best. This is good.
(The remaining factor is the number of correct answers.)
Please get up.
- Everyone.
- Is the difference big?
- I need my answers to be correct.
- The difference is reasonable.
- Is it reasonable?
- There must be a difference.
- I'll announce the answers.
- Okay.
- What about the small octopus?
- It's possible to take out...
and eat a flea's liver.
- Of course, it's possible.
- No, it's not.
- It's not edible, is it?
- But it's the liver.
- The answer is X.
- It's X.
- Right.
- It's impossible.
- Why?
- It has no liver.
A flea doesn't have a liver.
Because a flea doesn't have a liver.
I thought the liver would be tiny.
- Next is...
- A flea can't detoxicate itself?
- Who invented the air conditioner?
- It's Carrier.
- It's correct.
- Right.
- Carrier is correct.
Carrier air conditioner.
How would I know who Carrier is?
(Everyone got it right except Seon Ho and Joon.)
Who was that from behind?
- From the back.
- Was it Wonpil?
Wasn't it me?
- Did you pick O?
- I picked O.
- This person from the back.
- It's Dowoon.
- Exactly.
- Really?
- I said that it's Dowoon.
- You're right.
- I thought that it was me.
- But it's Dowoon.
- It's Dowoon.
- Exactly.
Seriously?
(Jong Min, you got it wrong.)
(Dowoon also got it wrong.)
A snake appears when you whistle at night.
- Of course.
- It's X.
When you whistle in an apartment, it doesn't come out.
That's because there's no snake. If there is, it will come out.
It's asking whether snakes respond to whistling.
Right. The answer is O.
The answer is X.
- Snakes detect sound...
- The sound of a flute.
By sensing vibrations in the ground.
The answer is X.
They're bad at hearing actual sounds.
(Snakes cannot hear sounds.)
Here's the last one. A small octopus has three hearts.
- It's X.
- It has three hearts.
This question was the hardest.
- Does it have three?
- It's correct.
(The answer is O.)
A small octopus?
- A small octopus has...
- Really?
One systematic heart.
And it has two branchial hearts.
- It has a total of three hearts.
- Of course.
It's needless to say.
The person in 1st place among the 8 of you is...
(As a result, the 1st place among the 8 of them is...)
- The person in first place?
- It must be SungJin.
- SungJin?
- I think it's SungJin.
The first place among all of you is...
The person in 1st place among the 8 of you is...
(As a result, the 1st place among the 8 of them is...)
- The person in first place?
- It must be SungJin.
- SungJin?
- I think it's SungJin.
The first place among all of you is...
SungJin.
- Nice!
- I knew it.
That's our team leader!
- I didn't know you were smart.
- I knew it.
- You're smart.
- Oh, yes! We'll win.
- I knew he would place first.
- You did a good job.
SungJin's record is 3 minutes 48.05 seconds.
And he got two questions wrong.
His final record is 4 minutes 8 seconds.
- Who placed last?
- Yes?
- The last place of all is...
- Could it be me?
I think it's Jong Min.
- The person in last place is...
- Who is it?
- Wonpil?
- No way.
- It's Jong Min.
- See?
(Jong Min placed last.)
- I'm relieved.
- That's good. We can relax now.
- That means our team won.
- It's not me.
- The second to last place is...
- I think we'll win.
Dowoon.
- That's great. What a relief.
- Both are on the other team.
- You're better than me.
- Six minutes twenty seconds.
- I think we won.
- So...
- Gosh.
- We'll enjoy the food.
- This is driving me nuts.
- As for this team...
- I feel no suspense.
- We won.
- I think we won.
- Although SungJin placed first...
- "Although."
- Nice!
Shall we call this team Team Young K?
- Team Youngpil.
- Name your team too, please.
- Team Youngpil?
- Team Dojin.
- Team Dojin, it is.
- Team Dojin?
As a result of the O-X Quiz Race,
- Team Youngpil won.
- Oh, yes!
(Team Youngpil wins the O-X Quiz Race.)
- Do we have a big gap?
- Nice!
- We'll enjoy the food.
- The gap is...
Team Youngpil's record is 19 minutes 9 seconds.
- That's quite short.
- It's 19 minutes 9 seconds.
- Yes. And...
- That's a good record.
Team Dojin's record is 22 minutes 6 seconds.
- There's a big record gap.
- Wonpil was like this.
That's a big gap.
(These two widened the gap.)
We'll go and meet the two members who left the group earlier.
- We won!
- We did a great job.
- We gained 2 portions of food.
- We got 2 meal tickets.
- We got two meal tickets.
- The food will be delicious.
- Gosh, it's hot.
- Goodness, it's really hot.
- It's so hot.
- You should drink a lot of water.
Right. You should drink water on a hot day like this.
Or else, you might get dehydrated.
I think this patch works.
Yes, I think...
- it cools the skin.
- Right.
This is fun.
- Are you having fun?
- Yes.
- Watching it is fun too.
- Really?
(Young Hyun finds 2 Days 1 Night fun.)
This will be a good memory.
- Being on this show?
- Yes, I'm sure it'll be.
This is our first time being on a variety show like this.
When things are hard, they become more memorable.
(The optimistic Wonpil)
How many missions do you usually do on a day?
We keep playing games until we go to bed.
- As many games as time allows?
- Correct.
That sounds nice.
- It's not over yet.
- I think we're back where we were.
I think you're right.
I want to have a cup of iced Americano.
(They'll let us have something when we go to the cafe, right?)
Young K said he wanted a cup of coffee.
- He wants something to drink.
- Young K said that.
(He confesses his honest feelings.)
I sure am hungry.
Oh, I want some ice cream.
That looks delicious.
- Cement ice cream? It looks good.
- Cement ice cream.
I want to try cement ice cream.
Bye.
(Can they have dessert as they wish?)
- You're here.
- We're back.
- It's so cool in here.
- What?
- Hello.
- We won.
- You're here.
- Did our team win?
- Yes, we won.
- We won? Oh, yes! Great job!
- We got two meal tickets.
- We won.
- Okay!
(You guys lost too.)
- Really?
- We have nothing to say.
(Feeling bitter)
Those who went for the luge ride wondered...
- what the two were doing.
- That's right.
To have some snacks with you,
they played a game on a duck boat to earn an allowance.
That's great!
(You earned a lot, right?)
- Sae Ho earned 4 dollars.
- I earned 4 dollars.
- If we have four dollars...
- Listen to Se Yoon's record.
- I earned four dollars.
- Then we can have...
As for Se Yoon,
he gained minus 3.5 dollars.
- We'll enjoy the snack.
- All right!
- Pardon?
- Thank you!
We rode a duck boat.
And there were rubber ducks floating on the water.
- We had to use a net...
- We scooped up the rubber ducks.
To scoop up the rubber ducks.
Se Yoon showed such bad manners.
- You're in no position to say that.
- You showed such bad manners.
- You sabotaged me...
- Don't be ridiculous.
- when I tried to scoop up...
- Stop putting on a show.
I'm not lying. You slapped me like this earlier.
(That sounds so satisfying.)
(Did you just hit me?)
- What's wrong with you?
- Ouch!
Se Yoon, stop! No!
- What's wrong with you?
- Ouch!
(Screaming)
(A beautiful page of youth)
(That was funny.)
We were planning this.
- You guys planned it?
- After shouting in turns...
- Hit me.
- Ouch!
(The professional entertainers came up with the skit while waiting.)
- Like this? Okay.
- Yes.
Young K said he'd do his best if he got something cool to drink.
One cup of iced Americano would be really nice.
Give me some ice cream, please.
Right. He'll have ice cream.
- We'll have cement ice cream.
- Cement ice cream, please.
Their signature ice cream is 6.5 dollars.
(Sad news)
We should try cement ice cream since we're here.
Then let's play a random game.
Give us nine cups of cement ice cream...
- and one cup of real cement.
- Real cement?
(Do we have to go that far?)
- Yes, real cement. Let's do it.
- Real cement?
Seriously, I mean, DAY6 is here.
Right. They're doing their best to make our show fun.
- Come on. DAY6 is here.
- Then...
(You will give us ice cream, right?)
Then we'll... We're not supposed to give you this,
but we'll give each team a cup of ice cream and iced Americano...
so you can share them with your team members.
- That sounds good.
- Thank you.
Thank you!
We'll have to play rock-paper-scissors...
to decide who eats first. You know that, right?
(We'll have to compete again?)
Is he still your role model after seeing him like this?
I've never seen him like this before.
(He's learning about variety shows at every moment.)
It looks good.
There's a piece of marshmallow too.
It'll be a little hard to share the marshmallow.
I want to eat one.
(Nutty black sesame ice cream with toasted marshmallow)
- Look at the marshmallow.
- Oh, my.
I thought it was cuttlefish.
- Impressive.
- Hand it over here.
It's so realistic. Look at the details.
- The spoons look like shovels.
- Shovels.
Oh, they look like shovels.
- It's black sesame.
- Oh, my.
(Sweet scent)
(He has a bite of marshmallow.)
(And then he has a bite of ice cream.)
- It's good.
- Indeed.
- It's good just as it is.
- It's good.
- It's so good.
- It tastes so good.
It's very soft.
- It's very soft.
- It's really good.
It tastes like black sesame.
It's black sesame ice cream.
(That's natural as it's black sesame ice cream.)
No wonder.
Eat it all.
(Eating)
(Meanwhile, Young K, the iced Americano lover...)
More ice cream will come.
Here's your coffee.
(He finally has a sip of coffee.)
It's good.
(He even licks the skewer.)
- It's really good.
- It's good.
It's so good.
(Where is their next destination?)
Oh, my.
Counting 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9.
Why is this seat empty? Will no one sit here?
- Can we sit in the front seat?
- Will no one sit here?
Then I'll sit there.
This will be fun. Awesome.
(He hits his head.)
My gosh.
He's unique.
(Dowoon can't stop showing his charming sloppiness.)
Are we good to go?
Shall we leave now? Shall we? Okay.
(Chuckling)
- I really like Se Yoon.
- We don't know where we're going.
You all put on your seat belts, right?
- Yes, we did.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Hold on tight
(Setting off excitedly)
Are you happy with your team members so far?
- Yes, I'm really happy!
- Of course, we are!
(The three members answered right away...)
(while the luge champion stayed quiet.)
- SungJin, are you happy too?
- He...
Yes.
Are you happy with your team members?
Would you like a chance to change team members?
Yes... What?
(Tempted)
(Laughing)
It's so nice to have more people in the group like this.
- It feels like a picnic.
- Right.
- Is this automatic?
- Sorry?
- Yes.
How are you feeling now?
- I like hanging out with people.
- Where did you go?
You're a good fit for 2 Days 1 Night.
I actively go on trips too.
- Oh, my. Really?
- Yes.
Do you guys go on an outing together or something like that?
- We go on trips together often.
- Really?
- We go on trips often.
- The four of you?
- Yes.
Just the four of you? Without anyone else?
- That's right. Just the four of us.
- Nice.
- That's not easy.
- Right.
(They have a strong bond.)
It's been 20 years since KOYOTE debuted.
Have you ever gone on a trip with your group members?
- Just the three of us?
- Yes.
- "Just the 3 of us?"
He gave you his answer. "Just the three of us?"
How about just the two of you?
Just the two of us?
(He hates the idea.)
- Alone?
Yes, alone.
- Just KOYOTE.
- He goes on trips alone.
How many years ago did you guys meet for the first time?
The members...
- The 3 of us...
- It's been about 15 years.
- It's been 15 or 16 years.
- It's been over 15 years?
How long did you train for at the agency?
- For 5 years.
- For about 6 years.
- That's a long time.
- Really?
SungJin set up the band.
Oh, you set up the band?
(Did SungJin set up DAY6?)
- It's because I can't dance.
- I see.
So you picked the ones who couldn't dance?
- No, it wasn't like that...
- SungJin was such a great vocalist,
- so it would be a waste of talent.
- I see.
So the agency decided...
- to set up a new band.
- "Let's give it a try."
(That's how the first boy band from JYP Entertainment was created.)
SungJin, did you know...
that Young K and Wonpil would join your band?
Well... At one point,
it did cross my mind that it would happen that way.
- Really?
- Yes.
When I was practicing dancing so hard?
He and I were going to debut in a dance group.
(Young K and Wonpil were trainees for an idol group.)
Dowoon also learned the basic dance moves.
Really?
It sounds like we could have a dance battle against you guys.
- We're all very confident.
- Yes, that's possible...
I mean, I'm pretty sure you guys are better than us.
(They have no intention to win at all.)
We have Jong Min, so we can win a dance battle.
Jong Min, you can still do a windmill.
- Really?
- He can still do a windmill.
- Is that true?
- Of course.
(I can still do a windmill.)
Dowoon wants to learn how to do a windmill.
- Really?
- Oh, that's right.
He wants to learn breakdancing.
(The youngest member and drummer wants to learn to dance.)
Jong Min, can you...
- I'll show you.
- Okay.
Really?
(Next week, Kim Jong Min's windmill class will open.)
How about we listen to songs by DAY6?
- Sounds great.
- Yes!
I'm not lying. My favorite song by DAY6 is...
"I Like You." When the song was released...
When I met my wife, I just couldn't get myself...
to tell her how I felt about her.
Sae Ho, sing a little bit of the song.
(Sing the song with the emotion you had then!)
(He seems sentimental already.)
The lyrics still make me feel emotional.
- Sae Ho, here we go.
- Here we go.
(The chorus will begin.)
(I like)
(You)
(Vocalizing)
(I tried to hold it back)
(Singing at the top of his lungs.)
(Surprised)
(Disgusted)
- I can't stand it.
- I hate hearing him sing.
(His face is so red.)
This is so nice.
(Young K purifies their ears with his voice.)
(He's run out of energy.)
You must love her sincerely.
- You must love her so much.
- You could feel his sincerity.
- Young K, can you please sing...
- With the original singer's voice.
A little bit of the chorus of "I Like You?"
- Shall I sing the song?
- Yes, please.
We need to hear the original singer sing the song.
(I like you)
(The heart-wrenching voice with a rock spirit)
Is this the same song that Sae Ho sang?
(Sae Ho suddenly starts singing.)
(Imitating Sae Ho)
(You should refrain yourself a little.)
- There are a few songs I like.
- Okay.
One is included in Wonpil's solo album.
The one with the beautiful lyrics you told me about?
- "A Journey."
- Right, "A Journey."
- Was it played on our show before?
- That song is so beautiful.
All right.
This is such a good song.
- Wonpil released this song...
- Yes.
Before he enlisted in the military.
Oh, really?
At the end of the song, it goes, "I'll be back soon."
The lyrics are about how he felt before enlisting in the military.
"It's time to carry the bag I packed and open the door."
And it's also for those who are about to have a fresh start in life.
The song's release overlapped...
- with the Summer Games.
- They overlapped.
It was a good cheer song as well.
The chorus part is really good.
(If you please)
(Wish me luck)
(For my future)
It's the perfect song to hear...
- during the Summer Games.
- It's so great.
(When I come back after seasons change)
It's so good.
(I will have become a better self)
(Look forward to it)
It's such a great song.
Your pitch is perfect.
(Laughing)
That's a relief.
(The medley of great songs by DAY6 continued after that.)
It sounds even better when they sing live.
The solo part!
That was so great.
- That was fun.
- It's a great song.
(It's fun to sing in the car.)
SungJin, can we hear you sing this time?
I want to hear you sing too.
I wonder if we can hear him sing.
I'm not sure.
I wanted to hear him sing.
(The unedited live performance in the moving car)
(Right now!)
(Mellow)
(Impressed)
(It's Wonpil's turn.)
(Getting goosebumps)
My hand!
His voice is powerful.
If so!
Let's go!
- One, two, three, go!
- Welcome to the show
(The part that everyone sings together)
(Covering his mouth in amazement)
(Seon Ho's camera)
(I can't believe DAY6 is singing in front of me.)
(I promise this one thing)
(I will give you my everything)
(I will make sure your eyes are set on me)
(I will stand here looking at you)
- Everyone, I can see the ocean.
- Look at the ocean.
(Oh, my. Look at the ocean.)
Look at that. Gosh.
That's refreshing.
(The vast ocean unfolds before their eyes.)
(The next page of DAY6 to be opened on the refreshing beach)
(What will happen here?)
We should go over there.
We're going to the beach.
(They arrived at the romantic blue ocean.)
The ocean looks so picturesque.
Chuam Beach?
It's beautiful.
I see some things floating in the water. Are they for us?
I'm sure we'll play a game here.
I see a buoy. We'll definitely play a game here.
I'm sure DAY6 will do well.
- They're great at everything.
- We won't do well.
Show your passion. Dive into the water.
I almost forgot. That's right.
- Show your passion.
- I'm an energetic person.
Let's go!
Let's do this!
- This doesn't feel real.
- Hey.
We drive somewhere, and there's a different background.
And then we move again, and arrive at a beach.
Don't worry. We've only recorded 15 percent.
- We have a long way to go.
- Exactly.
(Cheerful)
You just have to play 17 more games before you go home.
- Seventeen games?
- Cheer up.
You only played the luge game. That's all.
This place is called Chuam Beach.
- Chuam Beach?
- Chuam Beach is nice.
(It's beautiful.)
(The combination of the white sand and the blue ocean)
(Chuam Beach is loved by tourists every year.)
- Do you see the rock behind you?
- What's it called?
- That rock is...
- Chuam Rock?
What Chuam Beach is famous for...
and one of the best sunrise watching spots in Korea.
It's called Candlestick Rock.
- Oh, Candlestick Rock?
- Candlestick Rock?
- It's magnificent.
- That's Candlestick Rock?
It's amazing.
Through this game, you can gain two meal tickets.
- Okay.
- Oh, my.
- We'll be okay if we have four.
- That'd be great.
- Six would be even better.
- Right.
The game you'll play this time is The Duck Squad.
- The Duck Squad?
- Yes.
- It's a 5-on-5 team match.
- You already decided the teams.
- Yes.
You'll have 3 rounds. The 1st team to win 2 rounds wins.
- Okay.
- Got it.
You'll play all rounds of the game in swim fins.
There are so many games.
There are so many games in the world.
There's another thing we have to use.
- We'll sleep soundly tonight.
- I...
The first round is The Swim Fins Ocean Operation.
We have to go to the buoy wearing swim fins, right?
Each team will run on the sand...
while carrying an inflatable boat.
- A boat?
- Yes.
You have to carry your boat...
and take the flag floating in the water.
The first team to come back wins.
- That sounds exhausting.
- So we all will go into the water.
But once you go into the water,
one of the five team members should get on the boat.
- Just one member?
- Only the member on the boat...
can take the flag.
(Only the member on the boat can obtain the flag.)
How about we recommend the member to be on the boat...
for the other team?
- You served in the Navy.
- I served in the Navy.
He served in the Navy. He's the man of the ocean.
- The Navy!
- Weren't you a boatswain's mate?
- Yes, I was a boatswain's mate.
- Right.
- Then you should be on the boat.
- A boatswain's mate.
I have my own strategy too.
- All right.
- You have a plan?
I freedive, you know.
(The man who freedives)
- Right. You freedive.
- I scuba dive too.
He freedives. He dives in the water freely.
It's shallow enough for a little kid to stand.
And you'll freedive there?
(You can walk in the water here.)
That kid is standing there.
I'm sure that the kid is taller than you.
(Embarrassed)
You have to put on a different type of mic.
- Oh, dear.
- We won't change our clothes?
We should take off our clothes.
Take off your clothes, everyone.
Or else, we can't do this.
- This is our team's boat.
- SungJin.
(Distributing the swim fins)
Joon.
(Taking off his socks)
It's better without socks.
Seon Ho.
You keep helping me find items for me.
- DinDin must be lighter.
- Shall I get on the boat?
Right. You can get on the boat.
You were trained in the Navy,
- so go into the water.
- Here.
I think we can hold the rope to lift the boat up.
- We just go to the flag...
- But we'll be wearing swim fins.
Right. We can walk backward.
- On the sand?
- No, we'll walk forward.
- We'll run forward on the sand.
- Okay. Got it.
We'll walk backward in the water.
I don't think we should walk backward. It's very short.
But it'll still be hard to walk forward in them.
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, gosh. My feet are hot.
Which one of us will get on the boat?
I might be slower than you. So how about I get on the boat?
How much do you weigh?
I weigh 85kg.
Actually, 48kg.
(Total disaster)
Each of my thighs weighs that much.
Shall we play rock-paper-scissors?
No, Dowoon should get on the boat.
It's only right for Dowoon to get on the boat.
I'll do my best to get the flag.
- Let's go, Dowoon.
- Sure.
But where are we going?
- I mean, get on the boat.
- Right.
(I don't feel good about this.)
Are you all ready?
(DinDin and Dowoon will get on the boats.)
Dowoon, get on the boat as soon as we get in the water.
- What about me?
- The 2 of us will run at 1st.
- Okay.
- I'll run with him first.
- You mean at first?
- Yes.
- Seon Ho...
- But this is...
You should step back a little.
- Okay.
- What's going on?
- What's with you?
- Go back to your team.
It's no joke. He tries to keep us in check.
- Let's go!
- We can do this!
Let's get going.
- Bring it forward.
- No, grab the rope there.
- No, this is right.
- You all stay calm.
Stay calm?
Let's get this started. Ready?
Start.
You know what? Let's just run.
You're doing great!
- Bring it forward.
- No, grab the rope there.
- No, this is right.
- You all stay calm.
Stay calm?
Let's get this started. Ready?
Start.
You know what? Let's just run.
You're doing great!
(Running as fast as they can)
(As discussed, the two of them are running while carrying the boat)
(Only Joon and SungJin are carrying the boat.)
You're doing great!
- Let's go!
Keep going!
(Dowoon goes in the water first.)
(Dowoon's camera)
(On the other hand, DinDin is one step behind them.)
Put the boat down.
(The boat even got flipped.)
We have to flip the boat.
(Team Dojin's boat got flipped as well.)
(Chaos)
(Dowoon's camera)
(There's a hindrance.)
We got this.
(Team Dojin flipped the boat.)
- Okay.
- We got this.
- Let's go!
- Let's go now.
(Dowoon got on the boat.)
(Team Dojin is going first toward the flag.)
Just go!
Let's go.
(Trying their best)
- What?
- The boat shouldn't be flipped.
- Get on the boat.
(DinDin got on the boat.)
It's better to go backwards.
- Backwards.
- We can just go.
- We can just go!
Backwards.
- Let's go.
- It's better to go this way.
It doesn't matter. Let's just go this way.
- Just keep going.
- Keep going as is.
- Backward...
- Let's go.
(Only those who are on the boat can grab the flag.)
(Neck-and-neck)
(We can't tell which team is going to win.)
- Keep going in this direction.
- Hey, let's go.
Something got stuck...
(However, the two old men are falling behind.)
Just keep going.
Let's go.
(Going slowly)
Keep going!
(Joon and SungJin are the only ones who are pushing the boat.)
Having many people on a team isn't a plus.
(Everyone on Team Youngpil is taking part.)
(With all his strength)
(Team Youngpil is speeding up.)
Push the boat a little more.
I got it! Let's go back!
Let's go back!
- Nice.
- Well done.
- Let's go back now.
- Backwards.
- We're very fast.
- Push.
(Team Dojin reached the flag right after the other team did.)
Push.
- Let's go!
- Now, we go back.
(Team Dojin also got the flag.)
(The team that returns first wins.)
- We're very fast.
- Push.
They're coming to block us.
Backwards.
(Trying to get in the way)
(Splash attack)
(It's a very close game.)
Yes!
- We're here.
- We're almost there.
Keep pushing!
(Which team will be the winner?)
Lift the boat now.
- Lift it.
- Now, run!
- Keep going.
- Let's go! We're winning.
(It's Team Youngpil.)
Let's go.
(Trying their best to run back)
(Getting exhausted from splashing water)
(Team Youngpil arrived first.)
We won!
Okay!
We won.
(A daring race of the youth)
You have to come in.
We can chill for a second.
(We lost again.)
(Dowoon drags the boat by himself.)
(Game over)
That was a great game.
I swallowed a lot of water.
(Out of breath)
This is exhausting.
- I know.
- Goodness.
We can't beat them.
(Staggering)
I think I'm too old now.
My legs are sore.
(Mine too.)
The result of the game.
- Who won?
- Team Youngpil won.
- Okay!
- Let's go.
- We won every game.
- We never lose.
- I know.
We won again.
What's the reason behind our defeat?
I think you're shameless.
(You really are asking this because you don't know why?)
See? He's an old man who can't even stand right now.
Let's be honest. You're an old man.
(My body is aching.)
Do we have any other games where we can throw each other?
- Any physical games?
- Let's play physical games.
You see? We are all strong men, including SungJin.
Let's play physical games.
- Sure, let's play.
- Sure.
I'm on a diet these days,
- so I don't really feel strong...
- Right.
- What is this?
- What?
(Entering)
Hey, I see ducks.
(Laughing)
(Real ducks are here.)
This is fun.
Did you prepare the real ducks too?
Are we supposed to...
Cheer up, Wonpil.
You know...
This gently reminds me of the time at the Navy boot camp.
- Really?
- Yes, I'm serious.
Well, everyone. Team Youngpil won.
- Yes.
- Nice.
- Great.
- We can't keep winning like this.
You should go easy on us, at least once.
This is the mission for the second round.
- What is it?
- It's Swim Fins Fight.
- Okay.
- It's a fight.
- Great.
- I won't lose this time.
- Let's beat them all.
You know how to chicken fight, right?
- Yes.
- Oh, chicken fight.
Oh, chicken fight.
You can do a chicken fight while wearing swim fins.
This will be tough.
You have to win 2 out of 3 rounds.
(2 wins out of 3 rounds)
We will have 2-on-2 games for the 1st 2 games.
It will be a 1-on-1 game for the last match.
- Okay.
- Goodness.
We have to come up with the players who can win first.
- Right.
- It's important to win first.
- It means nothing if we lose.
- Okay.
- If we can...
- Let him play first.
- Okay.
Who plays this game better between the two of you?
Wonpil plays it better than me.
- He's a better player.
- Really? How come?
- Because you're tired?
- I think I just...
DinDin and Young K should play first.
- You start the game.
- Okay.
- Sure.
- Then it's you two.
I'll take a rest.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Who is playing this match?
- You share your players first.
- No, you share.
The players should step forward on the count of three.
One, two, three.
- Goodness.
- They're strong players.
- They're strong.
- We're in trouble.
- We got this.
- Yes, we got it.
We'll beat you.
I can feel that they are strong.
It's about time we go easy on them.
(DinDin is trying hard to look cool.)
When they try to attack us,
it's better to help each other.
You know when they attack...
DinDin will play it like...
I will just go outside.
SungJin, all they can do is run away.
Right, they will run away for sure.
They won't do anything. They'll run away for sure.
So you have to find the right time.
Ready?
(It's a chance to turn the tables.)
DinDin will run for sure.
Attack his front teeth.
Okay, you ready?
That's a foul.
Let's go!
Okay.
(Let me show you what a winning duo looks like.)
Start.
(The first match begins.)
(Hesitating)
- He's got it.
- Look.
They are intimidating.
Joon, that's right. Go next to him...
(Provoking)
(Getting closer)
What? Come.
What's with Young K? You should attack 1 person 1st.
(DinDin, Young K, Joon, SungJin)
(Surrounding)
SungJin, come and attack me. Come on, boy.
(Is SungJin turning toward DinDin?)
Don't attack DinDin first. It's a trap.
Go 1-on-1.
Isn't it hard? Come on.
It will be over if you go outside the box.
Just attack his back from the back.
- From the back.
- Push him out.
There you go. You got them cornered.
- You got them.
- It's over.
(Young K's camera)
(Young K at risk)
(Colliding)
Oh, no!
What? Why is he at the back?
(What on earth is going on?)
(Joon is cornering Young K.)
Goodness!
Look at DinDin!
- DinDin!
- No, this can't be happening.
(DinDin)
(Joon is eliminated as he's pushed by DinDin.)
(Young K was helping right next to him.)
(He also gets eliminated.)
- Reset.
- Are you out too?
Hold on. Be careful.
- Gosh.
- You're doing well.
What's going on? It's over if you fall out?
(DinDin versus SungJin)
End it against him. It's just him that's left.
- You can win.
- End it against him.
It's just him that's left. You got this.
- What?
- Gosh!
- What was that?
- Hey!
- That looked pathetic.
(DinDin hit him slightly...)
(and was handed over the win.)
(Flustered)
(Cheering)
(Team Youngpil wins the first battle.)
Nice!
(Here's a reminder that they were the best team.)
We'll start right away.
(Team Youngpil 1, Team Dojin 0)
- Our plan went wrong as they lost.
- All of our plans went wrong.
Who knew that they would lose to DinDin?
We lost against their worst group.
- The next groups should enter now.
- Let's go.
I'll just end things before Sae Ho.
They were pathetic.
- Those two look weak too.
- You can win this, right?
- Right.
- No.
They don't expect much from them.
They're starting with all of the weak ones.
What will happen if we win again?
Our plan totally went sideways.
Let's do this.
Dowoon and I will go out next.
I won't be of much help.
I will corner them, so you should take care of both of them.
Become a hero for us.
After trying it, it seems like going to them first isn't good.
It isn't good to go to them first.
It's definitely advantageous to stay still.
But he falls while staying still.
Right.
(He always fell on his own while staying still.)
(Stuck)
Then rush at them from the start. That's the right thing to do.
Let's hurry up and start!
- Okay.
- Please be understanding.
We will win no matter what.
We haven't won yet.
- Let's go!
It's Se Yoon?
Look at Se Yoon's legs!
Those are all muscles. They're not fat.
We'll begin! Get ready!
(Round 2 might become the decider.)
- Let's go, Dowoon!
- Let's go!
- Hang in there, Se Yoon!
Look at his legs.
(Determined)
(Team Youngpil will take the win if they win this round.)
Do it comfortably.
Set.
(Round 2 begins.)
What? What's wrong with you?
(Wonpil charges at Se Yoon right at the start.)
- What's wrong with you?
- Let's go!
(Flustered by the reckless attack)
(Charging at him again)
- Nice!
- Gosh!
(Wonpil and Se Yoon get eliminated together.)
Nice one.
Nice!
(He gets eliminated without being able to utilize his thick legs.)
No!
Don't feel pressured.
Let's go.
The way he's holding his leg looks off.
- Why is he holding it like that?
- Hurry up, Seon Ho.
That looks off.
- He's looking shaky.
- Don't go, Seon Ho.
- Just do what you want.
- Don't go, Dowoon.
(Making a dive at him)
Go for it.
(Crashing down)
- What was that?
- His legs came down!
- His foot hit the ground first!
- Hold on.
- His foot hit the ground first.
- I'm serious.
- We need a VAR review.
His foot hit the ground first.
(Seon Ho's foot hit the ground first.)
Seon Ho's foot hit the ground first.
- Right.
- Okay!
- Nice one!
- Yes!
(Team Dojin wins Round 2 thanks to Dowoon.)
Nice one!
Nice!
Thank you so much. That was our first win.
You were the first person to charge at me.
Everyone else ran away from me.
- I'll give you that, Wonpil.
- Right.
We'll go with Round Three now.
Sae Ho, make Jong Min's face dirty.
Okay.
- We can do this.
- Think about the 90s.
He was really good at this.
This is the final round!
- Okay.
- We played paper against rock.
Let's go!
(The battle that decides the winner)
Gosh, I feel nervous!
This is the decider.
- This is for my younger brothers.
- Let's go!
For my younger brothers who are all looking up to me.
- Jong Min!
- This is for them.
(Just trust me, my brothers.)
Jong Min has never done anything...
for someone else in his whole life.
We'll begin.
They don't know that.
Please show us this time.
Get ready.
- My brother!
- Set.
Will it be okay?
- Come on!
- Just be comfortable.
- Let's go! Fight like a man.
- Come on!
- Let's go.
- The newlywed groom!
- Don't come near me!
- It's downhill.
Go back up.
- Gosh!
- Attack him.
- You can do it!
- Okay.
- Hold on.
- We won.
- You have to endure it.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Where are you going?
(Sae Ho attacks again.)
He's coming.
- Let's go!
- Don't get pushed out!
Nice!
(Jong Min is in danger.)
Don't get pushed out!
(Dodging)
(Jong Min dodges the attack by turning his body.)
(Sae Ho loses.)
(We won!)
(Our older brother is the best.)
Why did you charge at him?
- Why did you charge at him?
- Yes!
(Team Dojin becomes the final winner.)
What was that?
- What happened to your face?
- Sae Ho!
- Jong Min!
- You did your best, Sae Ho.
- Jong Min...
- Gosh, that's impressive.
Won for the 1st time in 18 years...
for his younger brothers.
- That's my role model.
- Why did I miss him?
Round Three is very simple.
We'll just switch the cameras quickly.
All right.
- All right, everyone!
- Let's get ready!
Stand right there while facing this way.
- Okay.
- I'm hungry.
- I'm going to collapse today.
- Your faces have tanned.
The score is tied right now.
Round Three is Capture the Beachball.
- What is that?
- Capture the Beachball?
All right.
The team that gets the beachball back there...
past the finish line first will be the winner.
- Let's go!
- Where is it?
(Capture the Beachball starts.)
Let's go!
(Sprinting to the max)
No!
(They dive into the sea to secure the beachball.)
(Diving in)
Get ready for it.
- Gosh.
- Get ready.
(I will secure the beachball.)
Nice!
Throw it, Joon!
Joon!
Throw it.
Here.
- Throw it.
- Here.
- Over here.
- Here!
Give it to Se Yoon!
No. Keep it with you.
Keep it with you for a while.
- Gosh!
- Keep it with you!
(Closing him down, Keeping it secure)
(An intense face-off)
- Here!
- Go, Joon!
- Get him!
- What?
- Go!
- Get him!
(Young K is waiting for him outside the water.)
- Young K!
- What?
Go!
(Did he get caught?)
(Slipping)
Go!
What?
(He runs as fast as he can after losing him.)
Gosh.
Yes!
He did it.
My gosh.
Please! I really wanted to win.
I thought you would pass it at least once,
but you kept it to yourself until the end.
- I thought they would lose it.
- You didn't trust anyone.
(His teammates whom he can't trust at all)
You didn't trust anyone.
He took off his swim fins!
- That's cheating!
- You can't take them off!
They came off.
Where are your swim fins?
(What? Where are my swim fins?)
He took off his swim fins!
- That's cheating!
- We should play again!
It's against the rules to take off the swim fins.
That can't happen.
Why didn't you take them off too?
(His swim fins came off while running like crazy.)
- Let's restart the match.
- Okay.
Joon used all of his strength...
that he had saved up for the rest of the day.
We should take the swim fins off then.
- Without the swim fins?
- Let's take them off.
- Okay.
- They come off in the water.
- We'll go without them then.
- Okay.
- Let's go without them.
- Right.
I got a good result after a while.
- Stay in position right here.
- I'm fine.
Catch the person coming.
As we're all running, I'll step on their feet.
- Great.
- What is our plan?
If we get the ball, we have to pass the ball around.
- Should I try to secure the ball?
- Sure.
We will start with all of you facing me.
We'll start right away, everyone.
The team that gets the beachball back there...
past the finish line first will be the winner.
Get ready...
(A refreshing sprint to the sea)
- Oh, right.
- Gosh, it's hot!
(Joon sprints once again with his great stamina.)
(Power dive)
Just let us have it.
- Get closer.
- You'll run out of breath.
Don't go for it.
Leave it. Block the way!
Block the way!
(Seon Ho manages to get the ball.)
Come this way!
(Give me back my ball.)
Find Sae Ho.
Okay. Get ready to receive it.
Come here, Seon Ho.
(Team Dojin closes down on them.)
- What is wrong with him?
- Come closer.
Give it to Wonpil!
(Passing to Wonpil according to DinDin's orders)
(Pass it here, Wonpil!)
(They are close to taking the win if the pass goes through to DinDin.)
- What?
- Dowoon!
- Run!
(The ball falls to Dowoon with a misplaced pass.)
(Kicking hard)
Run, Dowoon!
(Chasing after him quickly)
(However, he already got away by quite a distance.)
Dowoon!
(Team Dojin wins.)
Yes, Dowoon!
(We did it!)
That was so dramatic!
(Nice one, Dowoon!)
Dowoon!
(Hugging)
Go to Se Yoon.
(Team Youngpil was very close.)
Dowoon did well.
The score is 2 to 1.
Team Dojin takes the win.
- Yes!
- You will get two meal tickets.
Great work, everyone. We will head over to eat now.
We will eat right away?
Let's go.
Nice one, Dowoon.
(Feeling proud)
That was quite a scene.
- I'm your successor.
- You kicked the ball.
You kicked the ball and ran after, catching it.
(They head to the next spot after making a passionate memory.)
That was today's moment.
(The intense Duck Squad mission comes to an end.)
Gosh, I'm hungry now.
Your face looks a bit tanned.
- Me?
- Right.
We all got a tan.
All our faces are tanned.
We really are tan.
(Yawning)
Dowoon, you were so cool earlier.
During the Duck Squad mission,
- You're right.
- he was amazing.
To be honest, his team won all the games thanks to Dowoon.
(A victory led by Dowoon after a close match)
- You're right.
- The chicken fight too.
- That's true.
- What did you guys do?
- My gosh.
- You won because of him.
Thank you.
Joon, if it weren't for you...
Are you all right? How much energy do you have left?
- One percent.
- Only one percent left?
(Laughing)
- Who has one percent left?
- SungJin.
- SungJin has one percent left?
- That's bad.
Did you not sleep?
Young K, are you feeling recharged?
Yes. I got about ten percent.
You got ten percent? So how much is it in total?
- Ten percent.
- Ten percent?
What about you, Wonpil?
I'm at about 70 percent.
At about 70 percent?
(A whopping 70 percent)
- He's young.
- Wonpil, you should do everything.
- Gangneung...
- Are we going to a restaurant?
Where are we now?
- We should go to Samcheok.
- Samcheok?
I'm hungry.
(They start to feel hungry.)
So, do we have two meal tickets each now?
- Yes.
- Yes. It's the same.
That's not enough, but it's 2:30pm already.
We should eat now.
We get to eat lunch early today.
- It's almost 3pm.
- It's earlier than I thought.
- Is this early?
- Yes.
We get to eat on time.
We will have dinner at around 11pm.
What kind of show is this?
We will have dinner at 11pm.
We haven't eaten a single meal today.
Right. My gosh.
This is embarrassing. When we have guests,
we should let them eat on time.
I know. This isn't about us. It's for the guests.
Of course. We eat all the time.
We don't have to eat.
Really?
We're serious.
How much do you eat?
These two eat pretty well.
- Young K and SungJin?
- Yes.
- Wonpil and Dowoon...
- Dowoon and I don't.
- have a small appetite?
- Yes.
They both like to eat rice, though.
They eat rice well?
- Just white rice.
- Just rice?
- Wonpil really likes rice.
- Just white rice?
- When you eat rice...
- Two bowls.
- When you eat gukbap?
- All the time?
- More than two bowls.
- Yes, when I'm hungry.
Two bowls of rice are perfect for me.
When you're young, you have to eat two bowls.
- Is this the restaurant?
- A restaurant?
It's a restaurant.
Everyone, you must be hungry.
- Are you hungry?
- SungJin says...
- his battery is at one percent now.
- One percent?
- I'm hungry.
- That's not true.
- I'm starving.
- Wonpil has 70 percent left.
Really?
- Young K is at ten percent.
- Yes.
- I'm hungry.
- I've got ten percent.
They literally cried in the car. Just a little.
(Please give us food.)
Don't embarrass us. We have guests, Director Joo.
- I'll try.
- We should feed the guests.
- We should treat the guests well.
- Right.
We should maintain a good relationship with JYP.
(Thankful and embarrassed)
You sweated a lot today.
- So we have small octopus bossam, - Okay.
Which is good for revitalizing your energy.
- That's great.
- That must be delicious.
(The nutritious small octopus grilled directly over flames...)
(and tender boiled pork are nicely matched.)
(Today is the small octopus bossam day.)
We can't miss out on small octopus bossam.
- All right, everyone.
- I'm so hungry.
Here's the result of the mission.
Team Youngpil has two meal tickets,
and Team Dojin has two meal tickets.
- We're on good terms.
- Nice.
This is...
the last mission for lunch.
So the winning team will get two meal tickets and mung bean jeon.
- Great.
- And two meal tickets?
That's good. If we win, we'll have four tickets.
With two extra meal tickets and mung bean jeon,
- we will have enough food.
- Right.
Even if we win, one of us won't get to eat.
You're right. The tickets...
This is disappointing, Director Joo.
- We should treat them well.
- We have guests here,
- but some of them won't get to eat.
- Three meal tickets.
SungJin asks for three meal tickets.
- Are you giving only two?
- So all of you can eat?
Yes. Make it 3 so all the members of 1 team can eat.
- SungJin, three meal tickets?
- Three.
- Right.
- Can you do that?
- Please.
The losing team will have...
- only two members eat anyway.
- Sand is coming out of my ears.
It will come out even tomorrow.
- Please do us a favor.
- One of the two teams...
- should eat.
- Okay.
- Wonpil, go and lie down there.
- Then,
we will give you three meal tickets and mung bean jeon.
- Nice.
- Let's do that.
He is tender-hearted.
He is.
- You should ask for more.
- Okay.
Should we ask for four tickets?
(Laughing)
I didn't know negotiation could be this easy.
This mission is...
the Count-up Naming Game.
- Count?
- I should use my head. It's bad.
You must name one word that matches the keyword at a time.
From 1 syllable to 5 syllables,
you must name words with one syllable added every time.
- I see.
- Se Yoon is really bad at this.
And Jong Min is a little worse than him.
- Se Yoon is terrible at this.
- Don't look down on our team!
(He's so tough.)
Darn it!
There will be unexpected difficulties.
- Don't let it get to you.
- Right.
- Sure.
- Don't mind them.
Let's just do this.
It goes, 1, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
Dowoon, you should try to steal their answers later.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
- I will...
- Focus.
- This is so much fun.
- While you play the game,
they will start cooking.
You have three options. Less spicy, spicy, and extra spicy.
- Spicy?
- Let's make it spicy.
We will make it spicy and have Cheongyang chili pepper on the side.
Between less spicy and spicy.
- That sounds nice.
- Yes.
- No.
- Come on.
- Hey!
- What's that?
- Spicy?
- Let's make it spicy.
- Spicy works for them.
- We will make it spicy.
- Spicy? Okay.
- Sure.
I want to eat it even more now.
- I don't want to lose it.
- I bet it's delicious.
If we make it less spicy, it won't be enough.
- So... It's small octopus.
- Right. Let's do that.
This is fun. I love playing games like this.
So you want it to be spicy.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Something like male idols.
- By the way,
will you play fair and square or commit fouls?
When did we not play fair and square?
- We always play fair.
- We should.
- Please make sure, audio director.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Let's do this!
- We can do it.
- Go, Team Youngpil.
- One, two, three.
- Team Youngpil!
- All right. The first question.
- Think of your answer in advance.
(Which team will be enjoying a hearty lunch?)
All right.
Korean male singers, including bands that broke up.
- Dojin.
- Youngpil
- Youngpil.
- Dojin.
- Dojin was faster.
- He said Jong Min.
- Se Yoon said Dojin.
- Okay.
- Hurry.
- Three.
- Gal.
- Two.
- What?
- Girl.
- Incorrect.
- Rain.
- What is Gal?
- You said Girl.
- Band...
- Okay. It's our turn.
- Youngpil.
Rain.
- You said Girl.
- VIXX.
- Three.
- aespa.
- Male singers.
- I got it.
Incorrect.
Why?
You should name male singers.
- What did he say?
- aespa?
Dojin!
- Name male singers.
- Male singers.
- Can.
- Three, two...
- Bucks.
(Committing fouls, hiding behind Se Yoon's back)
- Incorrect.
- Youngpil.
(Is it incorrect?)
(Making a fuss)
(This is exciting! It's our turn!)
(Sae Ho is going to win.)
- Hurry.
- Three, two...
Rain.
- Three...
- VIXX.
- Three, two...
- It's over.
- Taesaja.
- That's it.
- Three...
- DAY6.
- Three.
- NCT DREAM.
- Okay!
- Yes!
Correct.
(Team Youngpil gets 1 point.)
- Yes!
- Let's eat!
(Welcome to lunch.)
(Shouting)
- They said aespa.
- I didn't know this one.
I mean, next time...
By the way, what did you say earlier?
- Bucks.
- What is Bucks?
- It's Buck.
- What?
He said Bucks?
- He got it wrong.
- I know.
This is so much fun. Really.
Gosh, our team... Good.
- It's okay.
- Let's move on.
- All right.
- Relax.
(The second question)
- Korean song titles.
- Dojin.
Three, two, one.
- "Only."
- Yes.
- Three, two...
- "Love."
- Three.
- "I Love You."
- Incorrect.
- You can't say that.
Why?
- "Come."
- Correct.
- "Proposal."
Okay. Three, two, one.
- Time's up.
- Three.
- "Bruise."
- Three, two...
- "Love."
- Three...
- "I Love You."
- "I Miss You."
- Three, two...
- "Come Back to Me."
- Okay.
- Correct.
- Success.
- Yes!
(Laughing)
Well done. Our youngest is so good.
Dowoon, you're good.
(Disappointed)
I was waiting to say my answer.
- Wonpil is...
- What was your answer?
(I like you)
I was going to say this.
- By the way...
- Jong Min, what is "I Love You?"
- It's a song.
- By SWEET SORROW.
- I love you - SWEET SORROW.
("I Love You" by SWEET SORROW)
It's SWEET SORROW!
Oh, right.
All right.
- The score is 1 to 1.
- This is nerve-racking.
- Hang on.
- My gosh.
The team that names 5 words 1st wins, right?
Right. It's 1 to 1.
My heart is pounding.
This is really fun.
- My heart is pounding too.
- This is crazy.
All right.
(A heart-pounding game. Who will win the meal tickets?)
(Next episode)
(Things are as heated as the weather.)
Drumsticks aren't a musical instrument.
(Drumsticks)
(Feeling dizzy)
- Why?
- Male singers!
(DAY6 has fully adapted to 2 Days 1 Night.)
(The war of nerves is getting more intense.)
(Exhausted)
(Someone, please stop the members.)
(Shall we change the mood?)
(A midsummer night's party that they enjoy together)
(You thought it was a party, right?)
(It's heating up again.)
(We will win no matter what.)
(It won't be easy.)
(They are totally excited.)
(A showdown under the moonlight)
(The 2nd story with DAY6)
(See you on Sunday night at 6:10pm.)